<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Bloomberg-Green]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Bloomberg-Greennews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/green</link><atom:link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/green" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 02:27:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/v80tmGRj/bbggreen.jpg</url><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/green</link><title><![CDATA[Bloomberg-Green]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 02:27:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[台风 "克利斯朵夫 "逼近台湾 市场连续第二天关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[台风克拉森向台湾西海岸移动，预计将于当地时间中午前后登陆，证券交易所第二天关闭，数千人停电。【原文：Typhoon Krathon moved toward Taiwan’s west coast and is expected to make landfall around noon local time, with the stock exchange shutting a second day and thousands of people without power.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-03/typhoon-krathon-nears-taiwan-after-shutting-markets-a-second-day</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-03/typhoon-krathon-nears-taiwan-after-shutting-markets-a-second-day</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 01:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国可再生能源蓬勃发展，宏伟气候目标指日可待：中国可再生能源学会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据能源与清洁空气研究中心（Centre for Research on Energy and Clean Air）称，中国在清洁能源方面的快速发展使其有可能实现更宏伟的目标，以避免气候变化带来的最坏影响。【原文：China’s rapid deployment of clean energy has made it possible for the nation to achieve more ambitious goals to avoid the worst impacts of climate change, according to the Centre for Research on Energy and Clean Air.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-03/china-renewable-boom-puts-ambitious-climate-goals-in-reach-crea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-03/china-renewable-boom-puts-ambitious-climate-goals-in-reach-crea</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[碳抵消先驱被控诈骗 1 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位开发碳抵消的先驱者被联邦检察官指控伪造减排数据，作为获取数百万碳信用额度和超过 1 亿美元投资计划的一部分。【原文：A pioneer in developing carbon offsets was accused by federal prosecutors of faking emissions-reduction data as part of a scheme to obtain millions of carbon credits and secure more than $100 million in investment.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/former-c-quest-ceo-newcombe-charged-with-carbon-credit-fraud</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/former-c-quest-ceo-newcombe-charged-with-carbon-credit-fraud</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:51:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海伦飓风保险损失预计达 64 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据灾难建模公司 Karen Clark &amp; Company 的早期估计，飓风海伦造成的破坏预计将使保险公司损失约 64 亿美元。【原文：The destruction from Hurricane Helene is expected to cost insurers roughly $6.4 billion, according to an early estimate from catastrophe modeling firm Karen Clark &amp; Company.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/hurricane-helene-insurance-losses-expected-to-reach-6-4-billion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/hurricane-helene-insurance-losses-expected-to-reach-6-4-billion</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国水坝并非为应对当今气候剧烈变化的雨水和洪水而建]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>飓风海伦使北卡罗来纳州和田纳西州的水坝濒临崩溃边缘。美国的许多水坝已经有几十年的历史，在设计时并没有考虑到气候变化的影响。【原文：<p>Hurricane Helene brought dams in North Carolina and Tennessee close to their breaking point. Many US dams are decades old and weren’t designed for the impacts of climate change.&nbsp;</p>】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/us-dams-weren-t-built-for-today-s-climate-charged-rain-and-floods</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/us-dams-weren-t-built-for-today-s-climate-charged-rain-and-floods</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国天合光能称新关税凸显美国扩张计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一直与生产太阳能电池板零部件的中国公司打得不可开交。这一事件凸显了中国的天合光能公司（Trina Solar Co.【原文：The US has been locked in a battle with Chinese companies that produce parts for solar panels. That saga only underscores why China’s Trina Solar Co. wants to expand its presence in the US market.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/china-s-trina-solar-says-new-duties-underscore-us-expansion-plan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/china-s-trina-solar-says-new-duties-underscore-us-expansion-plan</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[议长约翰逊表示海伦之后需要更多救灾援助]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党众议院议长迈克-约翰逊（Mike Johnson）表示，现有的救灾资金不足以满足海伦飓风灾民的需求，并预测国会将需要通过额外的援助。【原文：Republican House Speaker Mike Johnson said existing disaster funds won’t be enough to cover the needs of victims of Hurricane Helene and predicted Congress will need to pass additional aid.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/speaker-johnson-says-more-disaster-aid-necessary-after-helene</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/speaker-johnson-says-more-disaster-aid-necessary-after-helene</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:47:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前高盛银行家海曼被任命为 Desmarais's Power Sustainable 公司首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大亿万富翁德斯马莱斯家族控制的投资公司 Power Sustainable 任命布鲁斯-海曼（Bruce Heyman）为首席执行官，负责从全球机构投资者那里吸引更多资金。【原文：Power Sustainable, an investment firm controlled by Canada’s billionaire Desmarais family, tapped Bruce Heyman as its chief executive officer with a mandate to attract more capital from global institutional investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/ex-goldman-banker-heyman-becomes-ceo-of-desmarais-firm-power-sustainable</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/ex-goldman-banker-heyman-becomes-ceo-of-desmarais-firm-power-sustainable</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:37:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南非需要更多输电线来支持绿色能源计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[竞标办公室负责人表示，南非用于传输新项目电力的输电线即将耗尽，同时还需要一个更新的计划，以继续进行拍卖，从而从新的大型清洁能源设施中获得更多电力供应。【原文：South Africa is running out of power lines to transmit electricity from new projects and also needs an updated plan to keep running the auctions that are responsible for getting more supply from new large-scale clean-energy facilities, the head of the bid office said.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/south-africa-needs-more-power-lines-to-support-green-energy-plan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/south-africa-needs-more-power-lines-to-support-green-energy-plan</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:39:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将提供高达 1 亿美元的资金，促进人工智能在半导体材料中的应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周三表示，计划拨款 1 亿美元用于促进人工智能在新型可持续半导体材料开发中的应用。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Wednesday it plans to award $100 million to boost the use of artificial intelligence in developing new sustainable semiconductor materials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/us-award-up-100-million-boost-use-ai-semiconductor-materials-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4WDBVUTDNOKFCO4IHSUERORGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球保险公司就在俄罗斯 "丢失 "的喷气机展开伦敦法庭之战]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空租赁商的律师周三在伦敦的一次庭审上表示，自两年前乌克兰入侵以来，保险公司正在玩 "传递责任包裹 "的游戏，拼命应对因飞机滞留俄罗斯而产生的数十亿美元索赔。【原文：Insurers are playing "pass the liability parcel" in a desperate fight against multi-billion dollar claims over aircraft stranded in Russia since the invasion of Ukraine two years ago, lawyers for aviation lessors told a London trial on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/global-insurers-fight-london-court-battle-over-jets-lost-russia-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JX4XF67RBVIDRDWEFIY6PCQVMI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车寻求在投资者日缓解股东的紧张情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉该计划的人士透露，通用汽车公司将于下周二向投资者保证，不必对电动汽车需求减速感到恐慌，这家美国汽车制造商甚至有可能在2025年提高利润。【原文：General Motors will assure investors next Tuesday that there is no need to panic about decelerating demand for electric vehicles and the U.S. automaker could even improve its profits in 2025, according to two people familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-seeks-ease-shareholders-nerves-investor-day-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3DGSDXBQNMVNLKARG323C7WFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:47:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管不确定性增加，美元仍将保持坚挺：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查的外汇策略师的预测中值显示，尽管美联储预计将进行一系列降息，但美元在未来几个月将保持稳定。【原文：The U.S. dollar will hold steady in coming months despite an expected series of Federal Reserve interest rate cuts, according to median forecasts from FX strategists polled by Reuters who were, however, largely split on the currency's broad direction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-stay-unfazed-despite-growing-uncertainties-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJDMXHFTWFKKLER24OAGTICOLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼古拉向经销商交付的氢动力卡车第三季度增长 22]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼古拉公司周三表示，该公司在第三季度向经销商交付了 88 辆氢燃料电池电动卡车，高于前三个月的 72 辆，这表明市场对该公司大型钻机的需求稳定。【原文：Nikola said on Wednesday it delivered 88 hydrogen fuel cell electric trucks to its dealers in the third quarter, up from 72 trucks in the previous three-month period, signaling steady demand for the company's big rigs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nikolas-hydrogen-powered-truck-deliveries-dealers-rise-22-q3-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7C77FCSM7FKDHCY73LW6KLJ4MM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:40:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿尼尔-安巴尼的信实集团投资不丹绿色项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿尼尔-安巴尼（Anil Ambani）的信实集团表示，它已与不丹的德鲁克控股与投资有限公司（Druk Holding and Investments Ltd. ）合作，在这个南亚国家开发太阳能和水力发电厂。【原文：Anil Ambani’s Reliance Group said it’s partnered with Bhutan’s Druk Holding and Investments Ltd. to develop solar and hydro energy plants in the South Asian nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/anil-ambani-s-reliance-group-invests-in-green-projects-in-bhutan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/anil-ambani-s-reliance-group-invests-in-green-projects-in-bhutan</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:29:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月私营部门就业人数好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[9 月份美国私营企业薪资增幅超过预期，进一步证明劳动力市场状况并未恶化。【原文：U.S. private payrolls increased more than expected in September, further evidence that labor market conditions were not deteriorating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-private-payrolls-beat-expectations-september-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKSWNTDJZBKD5BLWFHW2OANZ2M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，欧盟的支持足以对中国电动汽车征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[官员和消息人士称，法国、希腊、意大利和波兰将于周五投票赞成对进口中国制造的电动汽车（EV）征收高达 45% 的关税，这足以使欧盟的提案获得通过，此举可能会加剧与中国政府的贸易紧张关系。【原文：France, Greece, Italy and Poland will vote on Friday for tariffs of up to 45% on imports of electric vehicles (EVs) made in China, officials and sources said, enough to get the European Union proposal passed in a move likely to increase trade tensions with Beijing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/france-greece-italy-poland-set-back-chinese-ev-tariffs-sources-say-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2QMEZPDJFLQNIWDB4RDH6JOCY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:18:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海伦把阿什维尔从气候科学中心变成灾难案例研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>这座城市拥有世界上最大的气象数据收集中心。但由于存放这些数据的联邦数据中心仍然停电，因此无法访问这些数据。【原文：<p>The city is home to the world’s largest collection of weather data. But it’s inaccessible as the federal data center that houses it remains without power.</p>】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/helene-turned-asheville-from-climate-science-hub-into-disaster-case-study</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-02/helene-turned-asheville-from-climate-science-hub-into-disaster-case-study</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 与意大利国家贷款机构 CDP 合作，促进人工智能在初创企业中的应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 与意大利国家贷款机构 CDP 签署了一份谅解备忘录，以支持意大利初创企业和创新公司采用人工智能（AI）。【原文：OpenAI and Italy's state lender CDP have signed a memorandum of understanding to support the take up of artificial intelligence (AI) by Italian startups and innovative firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-italian-state-lender-cdp-team-up-ai-use-startups-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYOVRR5SERIFFIT6WWV6MODW3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:59:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东危机引发供应担忧，美国能源公司股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心中东紧张局势升级可能威胁供应，油价上涨推动美国能源公司股价周三盘前攀升。【原文：U.S. energy companies' shares climbed premarket on Wednesday, propelled by gains in oil prices on concerns that an escalation of tensions in the Middle East could threaten supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-energy-companies-shares-gain-middle-east-crisis-sparks-supply-fears-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEL4O3ZWFVOANHWXXDG3OHNQ4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:48:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行调查发现，金融企业对全球经济更加担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行（BOE）周三的一项调查显示，对全球经济衰退给英国金融体系带来风险的担忧急剧上升至2019年下半年以来的最高水平。【原文：Worries about risks to the UK financial system posed by a global economic downturn have risen sharply to their highest level since the second half of 2019, a Bank of England (BOE) survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/finance-firms-more-worried-about-global-economy-boe-survey-finds-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDNOVP4BGZMALAF4IRRJOQ6VSU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:46:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司将投资 45 亿美元在印第安纳州新建工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国制药商礼来公司（Eli Lilly）周三表示，将投资 45 亿美元在印第安纳州新建一个先进制造和药物研发中心。【原文：U.S. drugmaker Eli Lilly said on Wednesday it will invest $4.5 billion to create a new center for advanced manufacturing and drug development in Indiana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-announces-new-45-bln-manufacturing-site-indiana-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5V5IF3HF5JPREHSOKH3ITBMDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:39:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求疲软导致康奈格拉品牌公司第一季度销售额不佳]]></title><description><![CDATA[康奈格拉品牌公司（Conagra Brands）周三公布的第一季度销售额不及分析师预期，原因是预算意识较强的消费者在购物时优先考虑价格较低的替代品，而不是该公司价格较高的主食。【原文：Conagra Brands reported first-quarter sales on Wednesday that missed analysts' estimates as budget-conscious consumers prioritized shopping for lower-priced alternatives over the company's higher-priced pantry staples.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/conagra-brands-posts-bigger-than-expected-drop-quarterly-sales-weak-demand-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJ3HMELPVJLETLUVWLMFWBUWWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Humana 称其评价较高的医疗保险优势计划的会员人数在 2025 年有所下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[Humana公司称，2025年该公司为65岁及以上老年人提供的、评价很高的医疗保险优势计划（Medicare Advantage）的注册会员总数有所减少，这使得该保险公司的股价在盘前交易中下跌了约12%。【原文：Humana said the total members enrolled in its highly rated Medicare Advantage plans for people aged 65 years and above have reduced for 2025, sending the insurer's shares down about 12% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/humana-says-members-its-highly-rated-medicare-advantage-plans-fell-2025-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UULVLIQD7NNDDOWRJ34PFZTPBI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国基金协会选出新一届董事会，高税收和新法规风险迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[另类资产管理行业组织 "管理基金协会"（Managed Funds Association）周三宣布了新一届董事会成员名单，以及该协会主席、市值 160 亿美元的信贷投资公司 AB CarVal 的执行总裁乔迪-冈德森（Jody Gunderson），该行业正准备应对高税收和新监管的威胁。【原文：The Managed Funds Association, an alternative asset management trade group, announced on Wednesday its new board of directors, as well as its chair Jody Gunderson, managing principal at $16 billion credit investment firm AB CarVal, as the industry prepares for the threat of higher taxes and new regulation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-fund-association-picks-new-board-risks-loom-higher-tax-new-regulations-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSFOS4WJ3NJ2FPT5MBFFD5JVCY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会委员称，美国海鲜餐馆因谎称本地捕捞的食品而受到警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会的一位官员周三表示，美国主要的海鲜餐饮连锁店已受到警告，该机构将严厉打击谎称本地捕捞的行为，此前国内渔业曾投诉菜单和广告存在误导。【原文：A U.S. Federal Trade Commission official said on Wednesday that the country's leading seafood restaurant chains have been warned that the agency will crack down on false claims of locally caught fare, following complaints from the domestic fishing industry of misleading menus and advertising.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-seafood-restaurants-warned-over-false-claims-locally-caught-fare-ftc-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDQQWNUY2VL73CAW3VK4OSKP4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克股价下跌，原因是预测撤销令投资者担心扭亏为盈的时间表]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克股价在周三的盘前交易中下跌了约 6%，此前该公司撤回了年度营收目标，这让投资者对这家运动服装巨头在新任首席执行官埃利奥特-希尔（Elliott Hill）领导下实现扭亏为盈的时间表充满了猜测。【原文：Nike shares dropped about 6% in premarket trading on Wednesday after the company withdrew its annual revenue target, keeping investors guessing on the timeline for a turnaround at the sportswear giant under incoming CEO Elliott Hill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-shares-dip-forecast-withdrawal-worries-investors-about-turnaround-timeline-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNBUMJ2W4ZJQFMIWQSYORNHZHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:34:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海伦颠覆投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着飓风海伦引发的历史性洪水在美国东南部地区消退，该地区面临着一场规模惊人的人道主义、经济和生态危机，其影响可能会持续数年。【原文：As historic floodwaters unleashed by Hurricane Helene recede across the US Southeast, the region faces a humanitarian, economic and ecological crisis of staggering scope, with effects likely to last years.】]]></description><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-10-02/helene-upends-voting</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-10-02/helene-upends-voting</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:34:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+将在小组会议上维持产量政策不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士告诉路透社，定于周三召开的欧佩克+部长级小组会议不太可能建议对政策进行任何修改，从而允许该集团从12月开始逐步增产。【原文：An OPEC+ ministerial panel scheduled to meet on Wednesday is unlikely to recommend any changes to policy, allowing the group to start gradually increasing production from December, two sources from told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-set-keep-output-policy-unchanged-panel-meeting-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRF62IGLFNJ7DMQN4CN6OGK534</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:32:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美联储降息和人工智能乐观情绪影响，9 月科技市场价值飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储降息通常会提高高增长公司的未来利润和现金流，受此提振，许多科技公司的市值在 9 月份飙升，对人工智能的持续热情也进一步推动了市值的增长。【原文：The market capitalization of many tech firms surged in September, buoyed by a Federal Reserve rate cut that typically enhances future profits and cash flows for high-growth companies, and further fuelled by continued enthusiasm for artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-marketcap-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHW2I56RIVK7TMBDHMBLH4PSHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>