<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 02:47:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 02:47:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[日本喜剧演员变身投资家，与前高盛 "股票怪才 "共同发起基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[从表面上看，作为日本最新股票基金的幕后主脑，这两人似乎很难让人产生信心：一个曾是喜剧演员，另一个则是千篇一律的 "宅男 "怪才。【原文：On the face of it, the duo hardly seem fit to inspire confidence as the brains behind Japan's newest stock fund: one, a former comedian and the other, every bit the stereotypical "otaku" geek.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-comedian-turned-investor-launches-fund-with-ex-goldman-stock-geek-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMJZYJH4WVNYBGH6VFYEOYVR7U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 01:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚最低工资将增长 9.54%，2025 年达到每月 323 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚总统古斯塔沃-佩特罗（Gustavo Petro）周二表示，哥伦比亚的最低工资将在 2025 年提高 9.54%，在政府、商业协会和工会之间未能达成协议后，他通过法令宣布了这一涨幅。【原文：Colombia's minimum wage will increase by 9.54% in 2025, Colombia's President Gustavo Petro said on Tuesday, announcing the hike by decree after a deal was not reached between the government, business associations and workers unions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-minimum-wage-increase-954-323-per-month-2025-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NW5KNPYPMFLKTCNC4ARRCBSLQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 21:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道墨西哥央行副行长称 2 月可能考虑降息 25 或 50 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥央行副行长乔纳森-希思（Jonathan Heath）告诉路透社记者，墨西哥央行董事会可能会在 2 月份的下一次决策中讨论降息 25 个基点或 50 个基点的问题，尽管他警告说美国贸易的不确定性正在增加。【原文：Mexico's central bank board could discuss a rate cut of either 25 basis points or 50 basis points in its next decision in February, Deputy Governor Jonathan Heath told Reuters, even as he warned of growing uncertainty regarding U.S. trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/mexico-central-bank-could-weigh-rate-cut-25-or-50-bps-february-deputy-governor-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XP7BYDCC7ZKATJMTCH43646ZBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 17:35:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田将为特朗普就职典礼捐款 100 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在底特律的福特汽车公司和通用汽车公司表示将提供相同数额的捐款后一天，丰田汽车公司发言人周二表示，北美丰田汽车公司将为当选总统唐纳德-特朗普 1 月 20 日的就职典礼捐款 100 万美元。【原文：Toyota Motor of North America is donating $1 million to President-elect Donald Trump's Jan. 20 inauguration, a company spokesman said on Tuesday, a day after Detroit's Ford Motor and General Motors , said they would give the same amount.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/toyota-is-donating-1-million-trumps-inauguration-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33NR7EFHD5P2DHMQSNH7V5MHXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 15:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者称，塔吉特的假日广告推广只能到此为止]]></title><description><![CDATA[在多年来竞争最激烈的假日季，美国主要零售商塔吉特（Target）和沃尔玛（Walmart）正在加大广告投入，以便通过短视频应用 TikTok 和流媒体平台接触购物者。【原文：In the most competitive holiday season in years, major U.S. retailers Target and Walmart are spending more on ads to reach shoppers on short-video app TikTok and streaming platforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/targets-holiday-advertising-push-will-only-take-it-so-far-investors-say-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAVX5QMRVRMR5IBCOFWMYQOSLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 15:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果寻求为谷歌在搜索案中支付的十亿美元辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司已要求参加谷歌即将在美国举行的在线搜索反垄断审判，并表示不能依靠谷歌来维护收入分成协议，因为谷歌将其 Safari 浏览器作为默认搜索引擎，每年会给这家 iPhone 制造商带来数十亿美元的收入。【原文：Apple has asked to participate in Google's upcoming U.S. antitrust trial over online search, saying it cannot rely on Google to defend revenue-sharing agreements that send the iPhone maker billions of dollars each year for making Google the default search engine on its Safari browser.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-seeks-defend-googles-billion-dollar-payments-search-case-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5HJNP7Y6RLQTMNFLOARUBYZNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 15:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国营媒体称伊朗解除对 WhatsApp 和 Google Play 的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据伊朗国家媒体周二报道，伊朗当局已经解除了对 Meta 即时通讯平台 WhatsApp 和 Google Play 的禁令，作为减少互联网限制的第一步。【原文：Iranian authorities have lifted a ban on Meta's instant messaging platform WhatsApp and Google Play as a first step to scale back internet restrictions, Iranian state media reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/iran-lifts-ban-whatsapp-google-play-state-media-says-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3AQZBPQ4ZICZCOPPMLLZCYFAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:43:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[减肥药数据令人失望，散户投资者买入诺和（Novo）跌停股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Vanda Research 公司称，美国散户投资者流入诺和诺德公司的资金周五激增了 32 倍，原因是这家丹麦制药商的肥胖症药物数据弱于预期，提供了一个难得的逢低买入机会。【原文：U.S. retail investor fund flows into Novo Nordisk surged 32-fold on Friday, as the Danish drugmaker's weaker-than-expected obesity drug data offered a rare dip-buying opportunity, according to Vanda Research.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/retail-investors-buy-novo-dip-after-disappointing-weight-loss-drug-data-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHWUZMABJZPTHHWKCKUQ2MLZ4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:38:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国药明康德将在美国限制措施下出售先进疗法部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国药明康德（WuXi AppTec）周二表示，其子公司已与美国私募股权公司 Altaris LLC 签订协议，出售其细胞和基因治疗生产部门药明康德先进疗法公司（WuXi Advanced Therapies），出售金额未披露。【原文：China's WuXi AppTec said on Tuesday its subsidiaries have signed a deal with U.S.-based private equity firm Altaris LLC for the sale of its cell and gene therapy manufacturing unit, WuXi Advanced Therapies, for an undisclosed sum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-wuxi-sell-advanced-therapies-unit-us-private-equity-firm-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SVRQLNXK5P3NKY4GBBDN742XY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行和商业团体就压力测试框架起诉美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国银行和企业的团体周二表示，他们将起诉美联储，挑战他们所称的 "压力测试框架的不透明之处"。【原文：Groups representing U.S. banks and businesses said on Tuesday they were suing the Federal Reserve to challenge what they described as the "opaque aspects of the stress testing framework."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-bank-business-groups-sue-fed-over-stress-test-framework-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFA5UY4UVVJFNC66LRGKYW7QJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本田和日产的合作需要双方都腾不出的时间：时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[本田和日产希望从潜在的合并中获得巨大利益，以创建世界第三大汽车集团，但来自中国的激烈竞争让人怀疑它们能否及时实现合并。【原文：Honda and Nissan expect big benefits from their potential merger to create the world's third-largest auto group but intense competition from China raises questions about whether they can make it work in time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-nissan-tie-up-requires-something-neither-can-spare-time-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRV3SPR4ZNKIDBSOLGKIGCNY4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 13:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据CNBC报道，大型银行计划就年度压力测试起诉美国联邦储备委员会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周二援引一位熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道，各大银行正计划就美联储进行的年度压力测试起诉该监管机构。【原文：Major banks are planning to sue the U.S. Federal Reserve over the annual stress tests conducted by the regulator, CNBC reported on Tuesday, citing a source familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/big-banks-planning-sue-us-fed-over-annual-stress-tests-cnbc-reports-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRF4KJVYZBMLBDXGHJETXCNAVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 13:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在繁忙的平安夜停飞所有美国航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司（American Airlines）周二称，由于一个不明的技术问题，该公司停飞了其在美国的所有航班。【原文：American Airlines on Tuesday grounded all its flights in the U.S. due to an unspecified technical issue, according to the company and a regulatory notice, disrupting the travel plans of thousands of passengers set to fly out for Christmas Eve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-says-experiencing-technical-issue-with-its-flights-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBOTKDA4KBPB3PMMPXYB3QQRYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 12:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圣诞节前夕交易缩短，期货价格低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周二缩短的交易时段之前，美国股指期货依然低迷，华尔街在结束连续第二年上涨之前进入了一个历史上强劲的时期。【原文：U.S. stock index futures remained subdued ahead of Tuesday's shortened trading session, with Wall Street entering a historically strong period before rounding off its second consecutive year of gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-muted-before-shortened-christmas-eve-trading-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVLSOJ5VORPLHGQ7LIMWAPFO6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 10:56:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称星巴克罢工将在平安夜扩大到 300 多家美国门店]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克工会表示，星巴克美国门店的罢工将于周二扩大到 300 多家门店，预计将有 5000 多名工人离职，为期五天的停工将于平安夜晚些时候结束。【原文：A strike at Starbucks' U.S. stores will expand to over 300 stores on Tuesday, with more than 5,000 workers expected to walk off the job, before the five-day work stoppage ends later on Christmas Eve, the workers' union said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-strike-expand-over-300-us-stores-christmas-eve-union-says-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6EJGCNHDZMHJHQVHB2PIAQ4YA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 06:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国计划明年发行 4110 亿美元特别国债]]></title><description><![CDATA[此举正值北京准备减轻唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）1 月份重返白宫时美国对中国进口商品加征关税的预期带来的打击之际。【原文：The move comes as Beijing prepares to soften the blow from an expected increase in US tariffs on Chinese imports when Donald Trump returns to the White House in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-plans-411-bln-special-treasury-bond-issuance-next-year-sources-say-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVAYMC4KPRIKLEWJZUUV22VTAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将增加预算赤字，加大国债发行以支持经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国财政部周二表示，2025 年中国将提高预算赤字率，加大财政支出力度，加快支出进度。【原文：China will raise its budget deficit ratio, intensify fiscal spending and accelerate expenditure in 2025, the finance ministry said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-increase-budget-deficit-ramp-up-govt-bond-issuance-support-growth-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQCFFMXBZJI3PMWWYRDEIVHQAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 04:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 单位支付 420 万美元解决加州排放调查问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 旗下的 FCA 美国公司周一表示，同意支付 420 万美元，以解决加州对超标排放的调查。【原文：Stellantis unit FCA US agreed to pay $4.2 million to resolve a California investigation into excess emissions, the state said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-unit-pay-42-million-resolve-california-emissions-probe-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRMRKB2U35OKNDZQPCOE4IAUAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 02:47:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市上涨，美元受债券收益率上升支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者对美联储 2025 年降息次数减少有所准备，美国国债收益率走高，帮助美元保持在两年高位附近。【原文：Asian stocks edged up on Tuesday, though moves were subdued in a holiday-curtailed week, while the greenback held near a two-year high helped by elevated U.S. Treasury yields as investors prepared for fewer Federal Reserve rate cuts in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJJYTY5GYFOHLO4GPCTKAYDDYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 02:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圣诞节前交易清淡，油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，油价在圣诞节假期前的清淡交易中上涨，美国经济数据和世界第三大石油进口国印度不断增长的石油需求为油价提供了支撑。【原文：Oil prices were up on Tuesday in thin trade ahead of the Christmas Day holiday, with prices supported by U.S. economic data and rising oil demand in India, the world's third-largest oil importer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-up-thin-pre-christmas-trade-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPCLMVPNXBMW5BQHFUABJ7VEYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 01:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[10 月会议纪要显示，日本央行讨论加息需谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的会议纪要显示，日本央行决策者在10月份同意，如果经济走势符合他们的预测，将继续提高利率，但一些决策者强调需要谨慎对待美国经济政策的不确定性。【原文：Bank of Japan policymakers agreed in October to keep raising interest rates if the economy moves in line with their forecast, but some stressed the need for caution on uncertainty over U.S. economic policy, minutes of the meeting showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/some-boj-called-caution-raising-rates-oct-minutes-show-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLKUKTD3R5MAZEIPFOSY4JNQRA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 01:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amicorp 集团否认在马来西亚 1MDB 丑闻中涉嫌诈骗 70 多亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业服务供应商 Amicorp 集团否认了其在知情的情况下促成 70 多亿美元欺诈交易的指控，这些交易与挪用丑闻缠身的马来西亚国家基金 1Malaysia Development Berhad 的资金有关。【原文：Corporate services provider Amicorp Group has denied allegations it knowingly facilitated more than $7 billion in fraudulent transactions related to the misappropriation of funds from scandal-hit Malaysian state fund 1Malaysia Development Berhad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/amicorp-group-denies-alleged-fraud-over-7-billion-malaysias-1mdb-scandal-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P26FIDX2GJOFVO47G3DIOWFTUQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:53:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元坚挺，美国利率前景占主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，由于美国利率长期走高的前景仍是投资者的首要考虑因素，美元走强，导致其他货币在里程碑低点附近挣扎。【原文：The dollar was on the front foot on Tuesday as the prospect of higher-for-longer U.S. interest rates remained top of investors' minds, leaving other currencies struggling near milestone lows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-firms-us-rates-outlook-dominates-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FN6PNLGLCRJEVA6RVCBLGOPXIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华邮》报道：美国外国投资委员会无法就新日铁竞购美国钢铁达成共识]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周一报道，美国外国投资委员会（CFIUS）已告知白宫，它无法就新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司所涉及的国家安全风险达成共识。【原文：The Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States (CFIUS) has told the White House it is unable to reach a consensus on national security risks involved in Nippon Steel's bid for U.S. Steel , the Washington Post reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/cfius-unable-reach-consensus-nippon-steels-us-steel-bid-wapo-reports-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORVMSCZKEBMZBFBHG7UUIJHLFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼加拉瓜考虑由国家控制私营银行的领导权]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼加拉瓜立法机构将就一项全面改革中美洲国家银行系统的法案进行表决，该法案将赋予国家任命该国私营金融机构领导层的控制权。【原文：Nicaragua's legislature is set to vote on a bill overhauling the Central American nation's banking system, which would give the state control over appointing the leadership at private financial institutions in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/nicaragua-mulls-state-control-over-leadership-private-banks-2024-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQOWMESZZZPERBKEGKMLSXAJQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 21:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[钒锂公司股东批准 67 亿美元力拓交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arcadium Lithium 周一表示，其股东已投票赞成以 67 亿美元的价格出售给澳大利亚矿业巨头力拓。【原文：Arcadium Lithium said on Monday its shareholders have voted in favor of a $6.7 billion sale to Australian mining giant Rio Tinto .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/arcadium-lithium-shareholders-approve-67-bln-rio-tinto-deal-2024-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SN3LPTGPJZP6PAYTAP6NALNTLI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 21:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储宣布根据法律裁决对银行压力测试进行重大调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会周一表示，鉴于最近的法律进展，它正在考虑对其年度银行 "压力测试 "进行重大修改，包括允许贷款人就其使用的模型发表意见，这是华尔街银行的一次重大胜利。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve said on Monday it was considering major changes to its annual bank "stress tests" in light of recent legal developments, including allowing lenders to provide comment on the models it uses, in a major victory for Wall Street banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-announces-changes-bank-stress-tests-boost-transparency-trim-volatility-2024-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2QITBK5RQZKCRLYTYRRYPCLTTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 21:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利对英美资源集团矿山提出四项环境指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利环境监管机构周一表示，已对英美资源集团（Anglo American）控制的大型铜矿洛斯布朗塞斯（Los Bronces）提出四项指控，称其违反了环境许可规定。【原文：Chile's environmental regulator has filed four charges against the major Los Bronces copper mine, controlled by Anglo American , for non-compliance with environmental permits, the agency said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chile-files-four-environmental-charges-against-anglo-american-mine-2024-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQIAOXWTHVLX5FZPMIHUQELXYU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 21:03:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计 2025 年美国企业债券利差将一路颠簸]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025 年，美国企业债券利差可能会一路颠簸，投资者和策略师预计市场波动会更大，因为特朗普新政府实施的改革议程可能会引发通胀，并减缓美国降息的步伐。【原文：It could be a bumpy ride for U.S. corporate bond spreads in 2025, with investors and strategists expecting more market volatility, as the new Trump administration implements a reform agenda that could be inflationary and slow the pace of U.S. interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bumpy-ride-us-corporate-bond-spreads-expected-2025-2024-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WACARHRG6JOQJLOQCH7BWZZRSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 19:35:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称 TPG 正在洽谈收购太阳能公司 Altus Power]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周一告诉路透社，收购公司TPG的气候投资部门正在洽谈收购Altus Power公司，该公司是一家为商业地产业主和住宅提供太阳能的供应商。【原文：Buyout firm TPG's climate investment arm is in talks to acquire Altus Power , a provider of solar power to commercial property owners and residential homes, people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/tpg-talks-acquire-solar-firm-altus-power-sources-say-2024-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BCGCQMBUJVNQXADJQ6CBTVURKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 19:32:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>