<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:35:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:35:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司将扩大在圭亚那的石油和天然气产量，为长尾项目申请许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油巨头埃克森美孚在圭亚那的负责人周三表示，埃克森美孚牵头的一个财团正在为圭亚那非常活跃的一年勘探和生产做好准备，因为该财团对一些浮动设施进行了升级，扩大了其产能，而且预计第四艘船将抵达圭亚那。【原文：A consortium led by Exxon Mobil is getting ready for a very active year for exploration and production in Guyana amid upgrades that expanded the capacity of some of its floating facilities and the expected arrival of a fourth vessel, the head of the U.S. oil major in Guyana said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-expand-oil-gas-output-guyana-seeks-permit-longtail-project-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSFXVDJFKBP7RIKBZAORT5NR5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰有哪些重要矿产，特朗普为何想要它们？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三抵达基辅，讨论一项重要的矿产交易，乌克兰正在与俄罗斯交战的危险外交关头争取美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的支持。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent arrived in Kyiv on Wednesday to discuss a critical minerals deal as Ukraine vies to win the backing of U.S. President Donald Trump at a perilous diplomatic juncture in the war with Russia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/what-are-ukraines-critical-minerals-why-does-trump-want-them-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F62OI35VMJJT3DEZXKYOCAIAB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多米尼克能源公司提高五年资本支出计划，以满足数据中心的电力需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[多米尼恩能源公司（Dominion Energy）周三上调了其五年资本支出计划，这家公用事业公司试图抓住全美数据中心增加带来的电力需求增长潜力。【原文：Dominion Energy raised its five-year capital expenditure plan on Wednesday as the utility firm sought to cash in on the potential growth in power demand from a rise in data centers across the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/dominion-energy-raises-five-year-capex-plan-meet-data-centers-power-demand-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAHN5DK6GFIZBD22CJZOSC3I4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔重返国会，数据显示 1 月通胀率跳升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）前往美国国会发表第二天证词之际，周三的数据显示，1月份美国消费者物价涨幅超过预期，这表明通胀方面的进展可能仍然停滞不前。【原文：U.S. consumer prices rose faster than expected in January in a sign progress on inflation may remain stalled, data showed on Wednesday, as Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell heads to the U.S. Congress for a second day of testimony.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-heads-back-congress-data-shows-inflation-jump-january-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJD2SLZB3ZNPRPJYUIUEQRYTSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:18:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金瞩目闪耀的里程碑，熊市也随之升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着多头抓住美国进口关税计划带来的经济不确定性，金价已进入未知领域，但在冲击每盎司 3,000 美元纪录的背后，一些熊市的旗帜也已插上。【原文：Gold prices have marched into uncharted territory as bulls latch on to economic uncertainty created by U.S. import tariff plans, but behind the prize of hitting a record $3,000 per ounce, some flags of a bear case are also being planted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-eyes-glittering-milestone-bear-case-also-rises-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DS5HYYRDU5MDVD7N3J2GIATOJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe 推出人工智能视频工具，与 OpenAI 竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[Adobe 周三发布了可生成视频片段的人工智能工具的首个公开版本，并透露了它的收费标准，但表示要到今年晚些时候才会为电影公司等主要用户定价。【原文：Adobe on Wednesday released the first public version of an artificial intelligence tool that can generate video clips and revealed how much it will charge, but said it will not set pricing for major users such as studios until later this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/adobe-launches-ai-video-tool-compete-with-openai-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D477RSKO6RM2ZFST7FKYJNZHGA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴里克公司首席执行官表示，一旦能够运送黄金，巴里克公司将恢复在马里的运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴里克黄金公司（Barrick Gold）首席执行官马克-布里斯托（Mark Bristow）表示，一旦马里当局允许恢复黄金运输，该公司将恢复已关闭的马里卢洛-古恩科托（Loulo-Gounkoto）矿场的运营。【原文：Barrick Gold CEO Mark Bristow said the miner will resume operations at its shuttered Loulo-Gounkoto mine in Mali once authorities in the country allow it to resume gold shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/barrick-will-resume-operations-mali-once-it-can-ship-gold-ceo-says-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GG662XNMR5JLTMKGP4DCL6LRHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国1月CPI意外升温有损美联储即将放宽政策的理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 1 月份消费者物价指数的增幅超过预期，强化了美联储的信息，即在经济不确定性日益增加的情况下，美联储并不急于恢复降息。【原文：The U.S. consumer price index increased more than expected in January, reinforcing the Federal Reserve's message that it was in no rush to resume cutting interest rates amid growing uncertainty over the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-hot-jan-us-cpi-surprise-hurts-case-fed-ease-soon-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQHE6KA2I5OUJKYFAXD6VDM5WY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:57:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克坚持 2025 年和 2026 年全球石油需求增长预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克周三坚持其对2025年全球石油需求相对强劲增长的预测，称航空和公路旅行将支持消费，潜在的贸易关税预计不会影响经济增长。【原文：OPEC on Wednesday stuck to its forecast for relatively strong growth in global oil demand in 2025, saying air and road travel would support consumption and potential trade tariffs were not expected to impact economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/opec-sticks-2025-2026-global-oil-demand-growth-forecasts-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VPVJSOAWZJF7B373VNQDL7RNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称降低利率将与关税齐头并进]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三表示，应降低利率，这将与他即将实施的关税政策 "齐头并进"，尽管经济学家们预计关税将加剧通胀并推迟降息。【原文：President Donald Trump on Wednesday said that interest rates should be lowered and that would go "hand in hand" with his upcoming tariffs, despite economists' expectations that tariffs would fuel inflation and postpone rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-says-lower-interest-rates-would-go-hand-in-hand-with-tariffs-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5GAH5LJAVKCBO6RRU6QXUOXNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:52:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥纽约证券交易所将在得克萨斯州重新注册成立]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约证券交易所周三表示，该公司在芝加哥的分部将在得克萨斯州重新注册成立，此举可能会加剧该州上市场所的竞争。【原文：The New York Stock Exchange's division in Chicago will be reincorporated in Texas, the company said on Wednesday, in a move that could intensify competition for listing venues in the state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nyse-chicago-reincorporate-texas-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UOJPXZOIQRMELE435QJLM2Q2HA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:46:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月份消费者价格增幅高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 1 月份消费者物价涨幅超过预期，强化了美联储的信息，即在经济不确定性日益增加的情况下，美联储并不急于恢复降息。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased more than expected in January, reinforcing the Federal Reserve's message that it was in no rush to resume cutting interest rates amid growing uncertainty over the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-prices-increase-more-than-expected-january-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYJQANIE3VN35JY6X3HG74BWEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普高官在基辅讨论矿产和能源协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三访问了基辅，讨论一项重要的矿产交易，乌克兰正在与俄罗斯交战的危险外交关头争取美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的支持。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent visited Kyiv on Wednesday to discuss a critical minerals deal as Ukraine vies to win the backing of U.S. President Donald Trump at a perilous diplomatic juncture in the war with Russia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/top-trump-official-kyiv-discuss-deal-minerals-energy-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52KTZKRNRZJVZA7SY5N7Q54YK4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国在集团部长会议上表示，欧盟应通过谈判避免贸易战]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国经济部周三在欧盟部长视频会议前表示，欧盟应集中精力与华盛顿谈判，避免跨大西洋贸易战，同时做好反制措施的准备。【原文：The European Union should focus on negotiating with Washington to avert a transatlantic trade war while being ready with countermeasures, Germany's economy ministry said on Wednesday, ahead of a video conference of EU ministers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/eu-should-negotiate-avert-trade-war-germany-says-bloc-ministers-meet-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDVCOV25T5JFJPPWDLHZRMCR7A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广告支出疲软，Interpublic 季度业绩不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国等主要市场的客户削减了广告支出，Interpublic 集团周三公布的第四季度业绩不及预期。【原文：Interpublic Group missed estimates for fourth-quarter results on Wednesday, as clients in major markets like the U.S. cut back on ad spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/interpublic-misses-estimates-quarterly-results-weak-ad-spending-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPQVX2O54FLBJPCL3CH6H2JH3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公用事业公司 Exelon 预测 2025 年利润高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Exelon 公司周三预测年度利润将高于华尔街预期，因为这家美国公用事业公司预计将受益于电力和天然气费率的上涨。【原文：Exelon forecast annual profit above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, as the U.S. utility expects to benefit from higher rates for electricity and natural gas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/utility-exelon-forecasts-2025-profit-above-estimates-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIZHJWIQUBMINIRAUGR76LXWUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰石墨矿希望与特朗普达成协议，但表示回报不会立竿见影]]></title><description><![CDATA[在乌克兰中部拥有 90 年历史的 Zavallivsky 石墨矿，首席执行官 Ostap Kostyuk 梦想着将纯度足够高的石墨用于锂电池，但由于缺乏投资，他将此比作 "在车库里制造劳斯莱斯"。【原文：At the 90-year-old Zavallivsky Graphite Mine in central Ukraine, CEO Ostap Kostyuk dreams of making graphite pure enough to use for lithium batteries, something he compares to trying to "make a Rolls-Royce inside a garage", given the lack of investment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ukrainian-graphite-mine-hopes-trump-deal-say-returns-wont-be-instant-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYBW3VGIXZMQNI5XFW3BBWTWRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲活动强劲，CME 集团第四季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易所运营商芝加哥商品交易所集团（CME Group）周三公布第四季度利润增长，原因是投资者希望降低地缘政治和经济不确定性带来的风险，从而增加了对冲活动。【原文：Exchange operator CME Group reported a higher fourth-quarter profit on Wednesday, helped by increased hedging activity by investors looking to mitigate risks from geopolitical and economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cme-groups-fourth-quarter-profit-rises-strong-hedging-activity-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CN4MXGHRONKC5K57BWXITLUCUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格任命百事公司高管大卫-肯纳利为下一任首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[克罗格公司周三表示，百事公司高管大卫-肯纳利（David Kennerley）将接替托德-福里（Todd Foley）担任公司首席财务官，4 月 3 日起生效。【原文：Kroger said on Wednesday PepsiCo executive David Kennerley would succeed Todd Foley as the company's chief financial officer, effective April 3.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kroger-names-pepsico-executive-david-kennerley-its-next-cfo-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMJAHV4DJBOZ3DTBQMX67UDSVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:13:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机票价格上涨提振航空公司利润前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[有限的运力和强劲的消费需求缓解了航空公司为填满飞机而打折的压力，航空公司正在灵活运用定价权。【原文：Airlines are flexing their pricing power as limited capacity and strong consumer demand have eased pressure to discount fares to fill their planes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rising-airfares-boost-profit-outlook-airlines-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BR7E63APPBLH7E5CMGS46LE3YI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡夫亨氏预测年度利润低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡夫亨氏（Kraft Heinz）周三预计全年利润低于预期，季度销售额也不及预期，因为这家包装食品生产商在涨价后面临着午餐肉和包装肉等产品需求低迷的问题。【原文：Kraft Heinz forecast annual profit below estimates and missed quarterly sales estimates on Wednesday, as the packaged food maker faces sluggish demand for its products such as Lunchables and packaged meat following price hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kraft-heinz-forecasts-annual-profit-below-estimates-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WO3PKYWFJNETNUWQ3TKD6TP24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:08:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，吉利与雷诺正在就巴西的销售和生产交易进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士称，法国汽车制造商雷诺及其中国合作伙伴吉利汽车（GEELY.UL）计划在本月晚些时候宣布一项协议，将双方的合作扩展到巴西。【原文：French automaker Renault and its Chinese partner Geely (GEELY.UL) plan to announce a deal later this month on expanding their cooperation to Brazil, three sources said, as they seek new growth markets amid broadening global trade wars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/geely-renault-talks-over-sales-manufacturing-deals-brazil-sources-say-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4NKTU6KPJNLFKGWQWTY2MP2SU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 将以约 23 亿美元收购 Richards Manufacturing]]></title><description><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 公司周三表示，将以约 23 亿美元现金从橡树资本管理公司（Oaktree Capital Management）管理的基金和比尔家族成员手中收购理查兹制造公司（Richards Manufacturing Co），旨在拓展能源市场。【原文：TE Connectivity said on Wednesday it would buy Richards Manufacturing Co from funds managed by Oaktree Capital Management and members of the Bier family for about $2.3 billion in cash, aiming to expand in the energy market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/te-connectivity-acquire-richards-manufacturing-about-23-billion-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJTLTPOTNROI7NGQ4CMV3J576Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁使伊朗和俄罗斯的石油滞留在油轮上，导致原油成本上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易消息人士和分析师称，由于美国更严厉的制裁措施减少了买家数量，导致可用来运送货物的油轮数量减少，并推高了原油成本，俄罗斯和伊朗的石油装船量创下了多个月来的新高。【原文：The amount of Russian and Iranian oil held on ships has hit multi-month highs as harsher U.S. sanctions reduced the number of buyers, leaving fewer tankers available to deliver cargoes and driving up crude costs, trade sources and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-sanctions-strand-iran-russia-oil-tankers-driving-up-crude-costs-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAWWQTBC3VKCFCYQMPMBBNWIPY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:58:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌首席执行官皮查伊称中国的 DeepSeek 做得非常好]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 首席执行官桑达尔-皮查伊（Sundar Pichai）说，中国初创公司 DeepSeek 做了非常出色的工作，展示了人工智能的全球化程度。【原文：Alphabet CEO Sundar Pichai said Chinese startup DeepSeek has done very good work that showed how global artificial intelligence is.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/googles-ceo-pichai-says-chinas-deepseek-has-done-very-good-work-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54WTHZWOGFN2LCTTXZF6CWPZUI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制药商百健公司预测 2025 年利润低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美元走强和治疗多发性硬化症药物竞争激烈的影响，百健公司周三预测 2025 年利润低于华尔街预期。【原文：Biogen forecast 2025 profit below Wall Street expectations on Wednesday, hurt by a strong dollar and fierce competition for its drugs to treat multiple sclerosis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drugmaker-biogen-forecasts-2025-profit-below-expectations-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AI4F6CU3FFMITEQXZLMA7EKPOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:47:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰首相承诺采取行动帮助科技初创企业蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰首相迪克-肖夫（Dick Schoof）表示，荷兰政府正在努力促进该国技术初创企业的发展并吸引风险投资，因为周三的行业研究显示该行业正在衰退。【原文：Dutch Prime Minister Dick Schoof said his government was seeking to boost the country's technical startups and lure venture capital, after industry research on Wednesday showed the sector was flagging.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/dutch-prime-minister-promises-action-help-tech-startups-thrive-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4B6JXNNIY5JYJEXJTXJH7JT7KY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:44:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉堡王母公司 Restaurant Brands 因需求强劲，收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[餐厅品牌公司（Restaurant Brands）周三公布的季度收入超出了市场预期，这主要得益于汉堡王连锁店对超值餐饮的强劲需求，以及蒂姆-霍顿斯咖啡店的强劲表现。【原文：Restaurant Brands on Wednesday topped market expectations for quarterly revenue, helped by strong demand for value meals at its Burger King chain and strength in its Tim Hortons coffee outlets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/burger-king-parent-restaurant-brands-beats-revenue-estimates-strong-demand-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXXEXHUGQZIP5PLSCVQXQUD7UU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗成本降低，CVS Health 季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 周三公布的第四季度利润降幅小于预期，原因是这家医疗保健企业集团的医疗费用增长速度放缓，而药房业务的收入则大幅增长，这使其股价在盘前交易中上涨了 9% 以上。【原文：CVS Health reported a smaller-than-expected drop in fourth-quarter profit on Wednesday as the pace of medical cost increases slowed at the healthcare conglomerate and revenues jumped in its pharmacy business, sending its shares up more than 9% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-health-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-lower-medical-costs-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDKUAX4QRNKINITS4JJCVHE6UY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Randstad 首席执行官表示，尽管德国工业发展指数发生变化，美国公司仍将致力于营造包容性环境]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰人才派遣巨头兰斯塔德公司（Randstad）首席执行官周三表示，"头条新闻比现实更暗淡"，因为一些美国公司正在改变其多样性、公平性和包容性（DEI）政策，而这些政策正是唐纳德-特朗普总统所针对的。【原文：The CEO of Dutch staffing giant Randstad said on Wednesday "the headlines are bleaker than the reality" as some U.S. companies change their diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) policies targeted by President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-firms-will-aim-have-inclusive-environment-despite-dei-changes-randstad-ceo-2025-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NWCYAU4ZFKOFKV42JWLSWAUOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>