<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:08:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:08:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月工厂活动放缓，需求疲软导致库存堆积]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于进口关税导致价格上涨，抑制了需求，导致未售出商品堆积，可能阻碍整体经济的增长，11 月份美国工厂活动放缓至四个月以来的最低点。【原文：U.S. factory activity slowed to a four-month low in November as higher prices because of tariffs on imports restrained demand, leading to a piling up of unsold goods that could hinder growth in the overall economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-factory-activity-slows-november-inventory-piling-up-amid-softening-demand-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXKZUEYDSFIJNCEMKG3ZERF44Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:59:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来成为首家因减肥需求激增而加入万亿美元俱乐部的制药商]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司（Eli Lilly）周五市值达到 1 万亿美元，成为首家进入由科技巨头主导的独家俱乐部的制药商，并彰显了其作为减肥巨头的崛起。【原文：Eli Lilly hit $1 trillion in market value on Friday, making it the first drugmaker to enter the exclusive club dominated by tech giants and underscoring its rise as a weight-loss powerhouse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-becomes-first-drugmaker-join-trillion-dollar-club-weight-loss-demand-boom-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U2XTO6PW5MQJEOS44W27R3HN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根呼吁 "在一段时间内 "保持利率稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周五呼吁，在央行评估当前的借贷成本水平对经济的抑制作用有多大的同时，"暂时 "按兵不动政策利率。【原文：Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan on Friday called for leaving the policy rate on hold "for a time" while the central bank assesses how much of a brake the current level of borrowing costs is putting on the economy, with soaring stock prices one reason to think it may not be much.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-calls-holding-rates-steady-for-time-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EL4ED2D5NNNWLDN4BBU22VOI4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯在接受 CNBC 采访时反对 12 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周五表示，在经济充满活力的背景下，货币政策正处于正确的位置。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said on Friday that monetary policy is in the right place amid a resilient economy, in comments that suggest she remains skeptical of the need to cut interest rates again at next month’s monetary policy meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-collins-leans-against-december-rate-cut-cnbc-interview-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RJ2WMZWXBNZPK3V57GZRHFWCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RTX 合资公司与以色列签订了价值 12.5 亿美元的 "铁穹 "导弹合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[国防承包商 RTX 公司周五表示，其合资企业雷神-拉斐尔防护系统公司已获得一份价值 12.5 亿美元的合同，将为以色列提供地对空导弹。【原文：Defense contractor RTX said on Friday its joint venture Raytheon-Rafael Protection Systems has secured a $1.25 billion contract to supply Israel with surface-to-air missiles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtx-jv-secures-125-billion-iron-dome-missile-deal-with-israel-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KT72SW6PGRI6NA4LTP4G6QNEDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道Kering 首席执行官计划成立 "梦想之家 "投资部门，帮助减少对 Gucci 的依赖]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的文件显示，Kering 新任首席执行官 Luca De Meo 计划成立一个新部门，负责寻找新晋品牌进行投资，因为他希望开发新的收入来源，减少集团对陷入困境的 Gucci 的依赖。【原文：Kering's new CEO Luca De Meo plans to set up a new unit to scout for up-and-coming brands to invest in, documents seen by Reuters show, as he seeks to tap new revenue streams and trim the group's reliance on struggling Gucci.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kering-ceo-plans-house-dreams-investment-arm-help-trim-reliance-gucci-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3NW6STVJVJINGLEPJQI4P3UAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:14:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰斐逊人工智能相关股票的上涨不太可能是网络股繁荣的重演]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储副主席菲利普-杰斐逊（Philip Jefferson）周五表示，他认为目前人工智能相关股票的飙升不太可能重演上世纪 90 年代末网络公司股票暴涨以爆跌告终的情形，这在很大程度上是因为人工智能相关公司已经发展成熟，并有实际盈利。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson on Friday said he feels the current surge in stocks related to artificial intelligence is unlikely to be a replay of the late 1990s dot-com stock boom that ended in a bust, in large part because AI-related firms are well established and have actual earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-jefferson-ai-related-stock-gains-unlikely-be-dot-com-boom-replay-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C32Y6FQT7BLKPJNTTG2QKB2FGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:48:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金连续第五周吸引资金流入，财报表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股票基金连续第五周吸引投资流入，原因是投资者关注第三季度强劲的盈利增长，并消除了对科技行业估值过高的担忧。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted investment inflows for a fifth week in a row as investors focused on robust third-quarter earnings growth and brushed off concerns of lofty tech sector valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-attract-fifth-straight-weekly-inflow-amid-robust-earnings-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGXF52DXEBIY7HK5SMXEQPFXYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国皮具制造商探讨以高达 12 亿美元的价格收购半导体公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[皮具制造商中国国际发展集团周五表示，该公司正在探讨以高达 90 亿港元（11.6 亿美元）的价格收购龙腾半导体有限公司（Lonten Semiconductor Co Ltd）。【原文：Leather goods maker China International Development Corp said on Friday it is exploring the acquisition of Lonten Semiconductor Co Ltd for up to HK$9 billion ($1.16 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinese-leather-goods-maker-explores-semiconductor-firm-buyout-up-12-billion-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7HIVQTYDJPTBCY4RP2A7Q4HXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:13:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对市场大跌的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者继续抛售高估值的科技股，周五亚洲和欧洲股市延续了全球股市的颓势，美国股票期货也显示华尔街开盘疲软。【原文：Asian and European shares extended a global rout on Friday and U.S. stock futures also pointed to a weak opening on Wall Street as investors continued to offload richly valued technology stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-selloff-quotes-instant-view-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WOYEHDO5VOVHGKCZOE7C4AD5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:54:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称 AIP 计划出售或上市法国铝厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位工会官员周五表示，美国投资公司 American Industrial Partners 计划出售法国最大的铝厂 Aluminium Dunkerque 或将其在股票市场上市。【原文：U.S. investment firm American Industrial Partners plans to sell or list on the stock market Aluminium Dunkerque, France's largest aluminium plant, a union official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/aip-plans-sale-or-listing-french-aluminium-plant-union-says-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46GM5WJGOZOHTDYFRAFFYH3WNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:49:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯称美联储仍可在 "近期 "降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，美国联邦储备委员会仍可在 "近期内 "降息，而不会使其通胀目标面临风险。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve can still cut interest rates "in the near term" without putting its inflation goal at risk, New York Fed president John Williams said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-williams-says-fed-can-still-cut-rates-near-term-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2E5N6OM2BK25FRF7MTT4ACHZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度和欧洲央行同意启动连接国内支付系统的初始阶段]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度储备银行（Reserve Bank of India）周五表示，印度和欧盟央行已同意启动国内支付系统联网的初始阶段。【原文：The central banks of India and the European Union have agreed to start the initial phase of linking domestic payments systems, the Reserve Bank of India said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-europe-central-banks-agree-start-initial-phase-linking-domestic-payment-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2KODRZJBFNZZICG5PM4SPXTOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业盈利乐观，全球股票基金连续第九周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球股票基金连续第九周吸引资金流入，原因是基金投资者受到第三季度整体强劲财报的鼓舞，消除了对科技股估值过高的担忧。【原文：Global equity funds attracted inflows for a ninth straight week as fund investors, encouraged by an overall strong third-quarter earnings season, brushed off concerns about lofty tech valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6ME45HSRJOT5LQUXHFSJ34EFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:09:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标信息交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克-多兰（Mike Dolan）和投资回报率团队周末兴奋阅读、观看和收听的一切。
编辑的话【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.
From the Editor】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENQBAZ3A3BODNITIVPHTRMBLRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普取消对巴西的关税后全球咖啡价格暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[面对美国消费者对食品成本高企日益增长的忧虑，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普取消了对包括咖啡和可可在内的巴西农产品征收 40% 的进口关税，导致周五全球咖啡价格暴跌。【原文：Global coffee prices plunged on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump removed 40% tariffs on imports of Brazilian agricultural products including coffee and cocoa in the face of growing angst from American consumers about high food costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-coffee-prices-plunge-after-trump-removes-tariffs-brazil-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYUZXY3BONNAXLULPTO4CASLII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[红十字会将裁员近 3000 人，缩减预算以应对捐赠疲劳症]]></title><description><![CDATA[红十字国际委员会周五在一份声明中说，它将把 2026 年的预算减少 17%，减至 18 亿瑞士法郎（约合 22.3 亿美元），并裁员 2900 人。【原文：The International Committee of the Red Cross will reduce its 2026 budget by 17% to 1.8 billion Swiss francs ($2.23 billion)and cut 2,900 jobs, it said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/red-cross-shed-nearly-3000-jobs-scale-back-budget-amid-donor-fatigue-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42HJ74GH2ZOIDMKXZ6WXU5BYFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VinFast 季度亏损因巨额支出而扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南 VinFast 公司周五公布的第三季度净亏损增加，原因是这家电动汽车制造商斥巨资扩大业务范围，并在激烈的竞争中提高销售额。【原文：Vietnam's VinFast reported a bigger third-quarter net loss on Friday as the electric vehicle maker spent heavily to expand its footprint and boost sales amid stiff competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vinfasts-quarterly-revenue-jumps-strong-deliveries-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBFD3BRI5FKCJD6UISFLWV75RE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[页岩钻机闲置，裁员人数增加，60 美元的油价考验二叠纪的抗压能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国得克萨斯州的页岩产业中心，石油产量正在不断攀升。但如果你和马克-沃特斯（Mark Waters）交谈，你就不会知道这一点，他拥有一家向石油公司销售工具和安全设备的商店。【原文：At the heart of the U.S. shale industry in Texas, oil production is climbing. But you wouldn't know that if you talked to Mark Waters, who owns a store that sells tools and safety equipment to oil firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shale-rigs-idle-layoffs-rise-60-oil-tests-resilience-permian-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O43FN2AJKRLTDEDCWVBEGZTLJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:10:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国各州瞄准数据驱动定价，以减轻消费者的痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在白宫试图推翻各州关于人工智能的法律之际，各州也在推行越来越多的法案，禁止技术驱动的定价行为，以减轻消费者的高成本负担。【原文：Even as the White House seeks to roll back state laws on artificial intelligence, states are pursuing an increasing number of bills to ban tech-driven pricing practices in an effort to bring consumers relief from high costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-states-take-aim-data-driven-pricing-ease-consumer-pain-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKV7LAMZ55JEFCBZ2FIUWBBDGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国两年来最大规模购买美国大豆提振价格，引发陷入困境的农民出售大豆]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周美国向中国出售了两年多来最大的大豆，这可能只是中国政府加速购买计划的开始，在此之前，由于与华盛顿的贸易战，这个世界第一大进口国已连续数月避开美国的供应。【原文：The largest U.S. soybean sales to China in more than two years this week could be just the beginning of an accelerated buying program by Beijing after the world's top importer shunned U.S. supplies for months due to a trade war with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-largest-us-soybean-buy-2-years-buoys-prices-triggers-sales-by-struggling-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGKAKNM2DBKM7EUVDXZKI7VMO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻：黑色星期五让坎坷市场聚焦消费支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国股市在本月陷入低迷，投资者将在未来一周寻找美国消费者走强的迹象，黑色星期五将成为假日购物季的焦点。【原文：With U.S. stocks in the midst of a grim month, investors will look in the coming week for signs of strength in the U.S. consumer with Black Friday putting the spotlight on the holiday shopping season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-black-friday-puts-focus-consumer-spending-rocky-markets-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHSQITHZYJIJPNFQKBAFMQSQT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普的 "金顶 "导弹防御系统面临延误和挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[八位熟悉情况的消息人士告诉路透社，唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "金色圆顶 "导弹防御计划正面临重大延误，原因是政府停摆43天，以及缺乏明确计划来使用今年夏天为该计划拨付的首批250亿美元资金。【原文：President Donald Trump's Golden Dome missile defense initiative is facing significant delays, hampered by the 43-day government shutdown and lack of a clear plan to spend the first $25 billion appropriated for the program this summer, eight sources familiar with the situation told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delays-setbacks-loom-over-trumps-golden-dome-missile-shield-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UO4RSZMIJNL5RBFZQ3XIFWHTDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[反垄断审判即将结束，谷歌希望避免广告业务被分拆]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国司法部的反垄断案接近尾声，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司将于周五在美国法院为避免其广告技术业务被分拆而提出最后的请求。【原文：Alphabet's Google will make its final plea to avoid a breakup of its advertising technology business in a U.S. court on Friday, as the Department of Justice's antitrust case draws to a close.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/google-aims-dodge-breakup-ad-business-antitrust-trial-wraps-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAGAMHAQ3FOX3ECFETDDCYQCWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国科技巨头纷纷涌入债券市场，人工智能支出引发的恐慌情绪将加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者越来越担心，用于为人工智能投资提供资金的公共债务迅速增加，可能会给美国企业债券市场带来压力，并最终削弱科技股的吸引力，尽管目前大多数大公司的杠杆率仍然很低。【原文：Investors are growing uneasy that the rapid rise in public debt used to bankroll AI investments could strain the U.S. corporate bond market and eventually dampen the appeal of tech stocks, despite leverage across most major companies remaining low for now.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/jitters-over-ai-spending-set-grow-us-tech-giants-flood-bond-market-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2LJ5UR6EZOJTAUCCCH5E7UM6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技股继续下挫，标普 500 指数和纳斯达克指数期货承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，纳斯达克和 S&amp;P 500 指数期货下跌，包括英伟达（Nvidia）在内的大多数科技股在前一交易日下挫后继续承压，原因是市场对该行业估值过高的担忧持续存在。【原文：Futures tied to the Nasdaq and the S&amp;P 500 fell on Friday, with most technology stocks, including Nvidia, remaining under pressure following a selloff in the previous session, as concerns over stretched valuations in the sector persisted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sp-500-nasdaq-futures-under-pressure-tech-selloff-continues-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MEW62RIJRIERLALIRHA2OQSH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国对俄罗斯石油巨头的制裁将如何影响卢布和经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对俄罗斯石油公司（Rosneft）和卢克石油公司（Lukoil）的制裁将于格林尼治标准时间周五17:01生效，以下是制裁可能对俄罗斯外汇市场产生的影响。【原文：Here is a look at how U.S. sanctions on Russian oil firms Rosneft and Lukoil, which take effect at 1701 GMT on Friday, may affect the Russian foreign currency market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-us-sanctions-russian-oil-majors-will-impact-rouble-economy-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APBWT3WA7JLW5F46QFYZXX55QA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:51:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行称，2025 年科技股仍将创下 750 亿美元的流入纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（BofA）周五发布的每周资金流向显示报告称，今年科技股仍有望实现创纪录的 750 亿美元资金流入，这凸显了市场对该行业的需求，即使该行业因估值过高而面临压力。【原文：Tech stocks remain on track for a record $75 billion inflow this year, BofA's weekly flow show note said on Friday, highlighting demand for the sector even as it comes under pressure from concerns about lofty valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-flows-bofa-urgent-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZLAOJXKUVM5LDMRC4D5EFXRJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:01:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长拉加德：欧盟可通过国内贸易打败特朗普的关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）周五表示，如果欧盟降低一些内部壁垒，就可以抵消美国贸易关税的影响。【原文：The European Union can offset the impact of U.S. trade tariffs if it knocks down some of its internal barriers, European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eu-can-beat-trumps-tariffs-with-domestic-trade-ecbs-lagarde-says-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHJSB7CQLNN3FMARJJRVAGY6O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元干预迫在眉睫，但未必奏效]]></title><description><![CDATA[日元的顽固疲软使日本濒临多年来第三次干预货币市场的边缘，但分析人士称，这很可能是无效的，当局必须谨慎行事，以避免引发新一轮抛售。【原文：A stubbornly weak yen has Japan on the cusp of intervening in the currency market for the third time in roughly as many years, but analysts say it's likely to be ineffective and authorities must tread carefully to avoid triggering a fresh selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-intervention-looms-large-it-may-not-work-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4XBCFFIONILNIA5HYBIRGBUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:24:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>