<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:34:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:34:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[杰克逊广场航空公司订购 50 架 A320neo 系列飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国飞机租赁公司杰克逊广场航空（Jackson Square Aviation）周三发表声明称，该公司已向空中客车公司直接订购了50架A320neo系列飞机。【原文：U.S. aircraft leasing firm Jackson Square Aviation has placed its first direct order with Airbus for 50 A320neo Family aircraft, it said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/jackson-square-aviation-orders-50-a320neo-family-aircraft-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYGJDLYJINJE7GAZ6ALQVBBDJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:29:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国出版商和作家就人工智能案对 Meta 提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国主要出版和作家协会对美国科技巨头 Meta 提起诉讼，指控其未经授权大规模使用受版权保护的内容来训练人工智能（AI）系统。【原文：France's leading publishing and authors' associations have filed a lawsuit against U.S. tech giant Meta for allegedly using copyright-protected content on a massive scale without authorisation to train its artificial intelligence (AI) systems.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/french-publishers-authors-file-lawsuit-against-meta-ai-case-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HU4QZPJLH5KK7CLP7R5FMVU5AA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:27:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官表示，Inditex 已做好充分准备应对关税不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的上市时装零售商 Inditex 首席执行官奥斯卡-加西亚-马塞拉斯（Oscar Garcia Maceiras）周三表示，Inditex 在多个国家采购产品，因此有能力应对全球关税带来的不确定性。【原文：The world's largest listed fashion retailer Inditex is well positioned to face the uncertainty about tariffs around the world as it sources its products in a wide range of different countries, Chief Executive Oscar Garcia Maceiras said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/inditex-is-well-positioned-face-tariff-uncertainty-ceo-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHCQKEM6OFKH7D2FODDEDHK7JE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:26:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[忘掉威胁，关税战已经打响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国早报【原文：Morning Bid U.S.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPFYS3TPNZIBPPGIBUHFZNBVUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊和谷歌签署承诺书，支持到 2050 年将核能发电能力提高两倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊和谷歌等大公司周三在休斯敦举行的 CERAWeek 会议间隙签署了一份承诺书，支持到 2050 年将全球核能产能至少增加两倍的目标。【原文：Major companies such as Amazon and Google on Wednesday signed a pledge to support the goal of at least tripling the world's nuclear energy capacity by 2050, on the sidelines of the CERAWeek conference in Houston.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/amazon-google-sign-pledge-support-tripling-nuclear-energy-capacity-by-2050-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITINKNEFYBNWHEGGDBWDVUW7SI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:58:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司在印度反垄断案中阻止 Tinder 所有者和初创公司获取商业机密]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份机密命令显示，苹果公司已成功阻止其在印度的对手 Tinder 所有者 Match 和一群初创公司访问其商业敏感信息，这些信息是针对美国公司的反垄断调查结果的一部分。【原文：Apple has successfully blocked its opponents in India, Tinder-owner Match and a group of startups, from accessing its commercially sensitive information which was part of antitrust findings against the U.S. firm, a confidential order shows.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/apple-blocks-tinder-owner-startups-commercial-secrets-india-antitrust-case-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WT2GF5C7QBJX3N4JUG74IDSXIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:57:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街大跌后期货上涨；关税、通胀数据受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者评估了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对基本金属进口征收保护主义关税的影响，并展望了一份关键的通胀报告，美国股指期货周三上涨，在前一交易日的波动之后企稳。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Wednesday, steadying after the previous session's volatility as investors assessed the impact of President Donald Trump's protectionist tariffs on base metal imports and looked ahead to a key inflation report.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-rise-after-wall-st-selloff-tariffs-inflation-data-focus-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETECLNRMSZLHRCEAFVJSVEMHBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:21:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼 GoTo 公司首次实现全年基本利润，预计 2025 年实现强劲增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼最大的科技公司PT GoTo Gojek Tokopedia周三预测2025年的基本盈利将大幅增长，同时还首次公布了去年全年的基本盈利。【原文：Indonesia's biggest tech firm PT GoTo Gojek Tokopedia on Wednesday forecast a sharp increase in its underlying earnings for 2025, while also reporting its first full-year underlying profit for last year.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/indonesias-goto-posts-first-full-year-underlying-profit-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFONHX366RO7TC4DT32SUDI7QA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:19:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔日本公司就原材料进口问题起诉印度，双方争斗升级]]></title><description><![CDATA[文件显示，安赛乐米塔尔的印度合资企业起诉新德里拒绝进口一种炼钢原材料，称新德里追溯性地实施进口限制是不正确的，这使其与正在损害其业务的政策变化的斗争升级。【原文：ArcelorMittal's India joint venture has sued New Delhi for rejecting imports of a steelmaking raw material, saying it was incorrectly imposing import curbs retroactively, escalating its fight over a policy change that is hurting its business, documents show.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/arcelormittal-nippon-sues-india-over-raw-material-imports-fight-escalates-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AH5ADTAIFZI3DI3SY6C2JWOD4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[不祥的市场信号显示美股可能面临更多麻烦]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者对令人担忧的市场迹象保持警惕，此前美国股市大幅下挫，导致超过 4 万亿美元的价值和唐纳德-特朗普当选总统后的所有涨幅化为乌有。【原文：Investors are wary about worrisome market signs, after a steep U.S. stocks selloff that has wiped out more than $4 trillion in value and all of the gains notched following President Donald Trump's election.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/ominous-market-signals-show-more-trouble-could-await-us-stocks-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJUAZ4ZXYRN6HFFKGHEHITRTOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行可能降息 25 个基点，以缓冲关税对经济的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[多位经济学家表示，加拿大央行可能会在周三将基准利率下调四分之一个百分点，以缓冲美国关税对经济的影响。【原文：The Bank of Canada will likely cut its benchmark rate by a quarter point on Wednesday to cushion the economy against U.S. tariffs, several economists said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/bank-canada-likely-cut-rates-25-bps-cushion-economy-tariffs-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZFEZMILORMJFMK7GZEVICDY7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行可能降息 25 个基点，以缓冲关税对经济的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[多位经济学家表示，加拿大央行可能会在周三将基准利率下调四分之一个百分点，以缓冲美国关税对经济的影响。【原文：The Bank of Canada will likely cut its benchmark rate by a quarter point on Wednesday to cushion the economy against U.S. tariffs, several economists said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/bank-canada-likely-cut-rates-25-bps-cushion-economy-tariffs-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZFEZMILORMJFMK7GZEVICDY7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彪马将在全球裁员 500 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[彪马首席财务官在记者招待会上表示，作为成本削减计划的一部分，彪马将在全球范围内裁员 500 人。此前，由于美国和中国市场表现疲软，这家德国运动服装集团周二晚些时候给出了令人失望的 2025 年和第一季度业绩预期。【原文：Puma will cut 500 jobs worldwide as part of its cost-reduction programme, its CFO said in a conference with journalists after the German sportswear group late on Tuesday gave disappointing forecasts for 2025 and the first quarter due to weak performances in the U.S. and China.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/puma-cut-500-jobs-worldwide-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3QZGE6AUZMR7JSOCPJER7ASSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道吉利支持的 Ecarx 正与大众谈判，首席执行官称将为欧洲和美国开发智能汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ecarx公司首席执行官周三表示，大众汽车正在与数字驾驶舱系统开发商Ecarx公司洽谈，希望将这家中国公司的技术应用到大众汽车在欧洲和美国等发达市场销售的汽车上。【原文：Volkswagen is in talks with digital cockpit system developer Ecarx to put the Chinese company's technologies in cars it sells in developed markets, such as Europe and United States, Ecarx's CEO said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/geely-backed-ecarx-talks-with-vw-develop-smart-cars-europe-us-ceo-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITGSS6B47ZN2BOPEWFM4VTFJXA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，捷豹路虎搁置在塔塔印度工厂生产电动汽车的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位知情人士透露，捷豹路虎已经搁置了在母公司塔塔汽车（Tata Motor）即将斥资 10 亿美元在印度南部建厂生产电动汽车的计划。【原文：Jaguar Land Rover has shelved plans to build electric vehicles at parent company Tata Motor's upcoming $1 billion factory in southern India, four people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jaguar-land-rover-shelves-plan-build-evs-tatas-india-plant-sources-say-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2VI2ZX4NZI5XLFBQ5HQOW24BM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:40:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国泰航空在激烈的地区竞争中利润略有增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[国泰航空公司（Cathay Pacific Airways）周三公布的全年利润略有增长，但由于亚洲航空公司在大流行病后继续恢复运力，竞争激烈导致机票价格下跌。【原文：Cathay Pacific Airways reported marginal full-year profit growth on Wednesday, but airfares fell because of intense competition as Asia's airlines continue to restore seat capacity after the pandemic.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/cathay-pacific-reports-slight-profit-growth-amid-strong-regional-competition-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OORNPMG5FM2NFU2LJMSFTJOJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 08:52:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉加德警告：贸易和国防冲击有可能放大欧元区通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）周三表示，欧元区经济正面临着来自贸易、国防和气候问题的特殊冲击，这可能会扩大通胀波动，并提高物价增长变得更加持久的风险。【原文：The euro zone economy is facing exceptional shocks from trade, defence and climate issues, possibly amplifying inflation volatility and raising the risk that price growth becomes more persistent, ECB President Christine Lagarde said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/europe/trade-defence-shocks-risk-amplifying-euro-zone-inflation-lagarde-warns-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4E3RXGRZRJTZGUO6TDDLWSFMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 08:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国营媒体称中国商务部与沃尔玛就供应商定价问题举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据央视下属社交媒体的帖子称，中国官员本周与沃尔玛会面，讨论媒体报道的美国零售商要求中国供应商降价以抵消美国对来自中国的商品加征关税一事。【原文：Chinese officials met with Walmart this week to discuss media reports that the U.S. retailer has asked Chinese suppliers to slash prices to offset U.S. tariffs on goods from China, according to CCTV-affiliated social media posts.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinas-commerce-ministry-met-with-walmart-supplier-pricing-state-media-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2DYYNAB6FKMFFFQ6UYLLFRSUI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 08:20:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国钢铁减产谈判重启，铁矿石受到惊吓]]></title><description><![CDATA[铁矿石期货放弃了早盘的涨幅，周三走低，原因是市场重新开始讨论中国削减粗钢产量以控制困扰该行业的供应过剩的计划，从而扰乱了市场情绪。【原文：Iron ore futures surrendered early gains to trade lower on Wednesday, as sentiment was spooked by resumed market talks of China's plan of trimming crude steel output to rein in oversupply plaguing the industry.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/iron-ore-spooked-by-resumed-talks-chinas-steel-output-cut-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAQXE2YSNVISTLFOZW74JFRMHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 08:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国工商银行发起 110 亿美元科技创新基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球资产规模最大的商业银行--中国工商银行周三宣布推出 800 亿元人民币（110.4 亿美元）的科技创新基金，以支持民营经济。【原文：Industrial and Commercial Bank of China , the world's biggest commercial lender by assets, announced on Wednesday the launch of an 80 billion yuan ($11.04 billion) technology and innovation fund to support the private economy.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/chinas-icbc-launches-11-billion-technology-innovation-fund-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7OBFMQRR5K7VATI4UOLBB3PKA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 08:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通经济学家认为美国经济衰退的可能性为 40%，存在 "过高特权 "的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席经济学家表示，今年美国经济衰退的可能性约为40%，如果政府破坏了人们对美国治理的信任，那么美国作为投资目的地的地位就有可能受到持久损害。【原文：There is about a 40% chance of a U.S. recession this year and a risk of lasting damage to the country's standing as an investment destination if the administration undermines trust in U.S. governance, according to J.P. Morgan's chief economist.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/jp-morgan-economist-sees-40-us-recession-chance-risks-exorbitant-privilege-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO6UUZQTHRKT7CADLXIZXNFGSQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:22:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱茵金属预计 2025 年销售额将因乌克兰战争和美国脱钩而大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国莱茵金属公司（Rheinmetall）是欧洲重新推动国防投资的主要受益者，该公司周三表示，预计 2025 年的销售额将大幅增长，并承诺在考虑到近期地缘政治的发展后更新指导意见。【原文：Rheinmetall , a major beneficiary of Europe's renewed push to invest in defence, said on Wednesday it expects significant sales growth in 2025 and promised to update guidance after recent geopolitical developments are taken into account.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rheinmetall-forecasts-2025-sales-jump-ukraine-war-us-decoupling-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYJALR2FQJIJLFFKQLOCV5YHTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彪马股价因前景黯淡而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[彪马股价在周三的盘前指标中下跌了 8%，因为这家德国运动服装集团在前一天晚上对第一季度的销售前景作出了令人失望的预测，原因是在美国和中国市场表现疲软。【原文：Puma's shares were seen falling 8% in Wednesday's premarket indications, after the German sportswear group gave a disappointing outlook for first-quarter sales due to a weak performance in the U.S. and China the night before.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/puma-shares-seen-falling-downbeat-outlook-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGPGYYZHPNIOXD3JVIB762DCHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:07:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在澳大利亚和新西兰遭遇破坏和销售疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[2015 年，澳大利亚人迪克-弗兰德（Dick Friend）购买了一辆特斯拉汽车，他对特斯拉的环保理念和性能赞不绝口，于是他和妻子又购买了两辆特斯拉电动汽车，还持有埃隆-马斯克领导的公司的股票。【原文：When Australian Dick Friend bought a Tesla in 2015, he was so impressed with its environmental credentials and performance that he and his wife bought two more of the electric vehicles, plus shares in the Elon Musk-led company.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vandalism-weak-sales-hit-tesla-australia-new-zealand-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XR2NLSPXONJTPDVDHTW736NJVY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zara 所有者 Inditex 符合第四季度销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zara 所有者 Inditex 周三公布了截至 1 月 31 日的第四季度销售报告，符合分析师的预期，标志着这家全球最大的上市快速时尚零售商又实现了一年的强劲增长。【原文：Zara owner Inditex on Wednesday reported sales for its fourth quarter ending January 31 in line with analysts' expectations, sealing another year of strong growth for the world's biggest listed fast-fashion retailer.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/zara-owner-inditex-meets-fourth-quarter-sales-forecast-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKAXRHGTI5KPZAJBIJKU34G674</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷 2024 年净利润减少三分之一，股息保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[保时捷周三表示，尽管根据路透社的计算，保时捷 2024 年的净利润下降了 30.4%，但该公司仍将把 2024 年的股息维持在上一年的水平。【原文：Porsche said on Wednesday it will keep its dividend for 2024 at the previous year's level despite a 30.4% drop in net profit, according to Reuters calculations, as the luxury carmaker battles high costs and weak demand in China.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsches-net-profit-slashed-by-third-2024-keeps-dividend-stable-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XJ3MNMSVJOA7BBYI4VNH4MTZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗氏与新西兰制药公司合作开发肥胖症候选药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士罗氏公司周三表示，该公司已与丹麦肥胖症药物生产商西兰制药公司（Zealand Pharma）达成一项独家合作和许可协议，共同开发肥胖症治疗药物佩特林肽（petrelintide）。【原文：Roche has entered an exclusive collaboration and licensing agreement with Danish obesity drug maker Zealand Pharma to co-develop petrelintide as an obesity therapy drug, the Swiss company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/roche-develop-commercialize-obesity-drug-with-zealand-pharma-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSPWMNU3S5N4HD37ZWXG2ZG6JE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[两名独立董事辞职，Seven & I 公司管理层继续调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本便利店运营商 Seven & i Holdings 周三表示，该公司两名独立董事已经辞职，因为面对加拿大 Alimentation Couche-Tard 公司价值 470 亿美元的收购要约，该公司正在调整管理层。【原文：Two independent directors of Japan's Seven & i Holdings have resigned, the convenience store operator said on Wednesday, as it rejigs its management in the face of a $47 billion takeover bid from Canada's Alimentation Couche-Tard .】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/two-seven-i-outside-directors-resign-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHCSL7OT4JLZ5CDXDMIJ4INNZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：欧洲央行解决战略评估中的基本问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）正在推出一份新的战略评估报告，该报告涵盖了有关其工作方式的一些重大问题--从大规模购买债券是否仍是一种好的政策工具，到它在应对气候变化的斗争中应发挥什么作用。【原文：The European Central Bank is launching a fresh strategy assessment seen covering some big questions on the way it works - from whether massive bond buys remain a good policy tool, to what role it should play in the fight against climate change.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecb-tackle-fundamental-questions-strategy-assessment-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2STOQQS7ZPQTIF7CWO6GI65OY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税，韩国钢铁制造商关注美国生产和高附加值产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[在全球主要生产商为周三生效的美国钢铁和铝进口增收关税做准备之际，韩国两大钢铁制造商正在考虑投资新设施的方案。【原文：Two major South Korean steelmakers are considering their investment options in new facilities as major producers worldwide brace for increased tariffs on U.S. steel and aluminium imports that came into force on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/south-korean-steelmakers-eye-us-production-higher-value-products-trump-tariffs-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNY6CY2Z3FMWTFBIDFFARYAASY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>