<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 08:42:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 08:42:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[经济不景气，中国省政府允许官员兼职]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国经济低迷迫使地方政府削减工资和奖金之际，南方某省告诉官员们可以从事副业，称兼职司机、小说家或健身教练都没有问题。【原文：As China's sluggish economy pushes local authorities to cut salaries and bonuses, one southern province has told officials they can pursue side jobs, saying it is OK to be a part-time driver, novelist or fitness coach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-province-says-ok-officials-hustle-side-tepid-economy-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNCE5VHBF5KSVAQ3DZJ6NGRVCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 08:13:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源署（IEA）在 "欧佩克+"（OPEC+）最新上调石油供应量后上调 2025 年石油供应量预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在欧佩克+组织（OPEC+）最新决定增加石油产量后，国际能源机构周五上调了今年的供应增长预测，同时下调了需求前景，称最近几个月石油使用量大幅放缓。【原文：The International Energy Agency on Friday raised its forecast for supply growth this year after OPEC+'s latest decision to pump more oil, while it trimmed its outlook for demand, saying that in recent months oil use has slowed down significantly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/iea-boosts-2025-oil-supply-forecast-after-latest-opec-hike-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMHPOP2NOZIKTNCG6LGRQ5JBFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 08:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税波动，大韩航空季度货运收入下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[大韩航空周五报告称，本财年第二季度货运收入下降了4%，原因是美国关税政策导致市场波动。【原文：Korean Air reported on Friday a fall of 4% in cargo revenue for the second quarter of its financial year, pointing to market volatility stemming from U.S. tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/korean-air-quarterly-cargo-revenue-falls-amid-volatile-us-tariffs-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z27B6H355JJSNPHJXDFADEK7GM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 08:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 GDP 增速将放缓，政策制定者压力增大：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于与美国的贸易紧张局势加剧了通货紧缩的压力，预计中国经济在第二季度将从年初的稳健增长中放缓，从而加强了中国政府可能需要推出更多刺激措施的预期。【原文：China's economy is expected to have slowed down in the second quarter from a solid start to the year as trade tensions with the United States added to deflationary pressures, reinforcing expectations that Beijing may need to roll out more stimulus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-gdp-growth-set-slow-raising-pressure-policymakers-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKJSNJCQ2VNHZEXXEFSF2BABPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴里克首席执行官称，尽管美国征收关税，但铜的长期积极走势不会改变]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴里克矿业公司（Barrick Mining Corp）首席执行官马克-布里斯托（Mark Bristow）在赞比亚表示，即使美国即将对铜矿征收 50%的关税造成短期价格波动，铜矿商仍然看好铜矿的未来前景。【原文：Copper miners remain bullish on the metal's future prospects even as a looming 50% U.S. tariff creates short-term price volatility, Barrick Mining Corp CEO Mark Bristow said in Zambia, where the company is expanding its operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/coppers-positive-long-term-trajectory-unchanged-despite-us-tariff-barrick-ceo-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HI6KTM4OU5ILNC4FPPQRVEALNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息知情人士称潘多拉正在探索重组陷入困境的中国业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦珠宝制造商潘多拉（Pandora）的线上和线下销售连年下滑，两位熟悉内情的人士透露，潘多拉正在探索重组其中国业务的方法。【原文：Danish jewellery maker Pandora is exploring ways to restructure its business in China, said two people familiar with the matter, after years of plunging sales both online and off.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/pandora-exploring-ways-restructure-struggling-china-business-sources-say-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7OTVU3GJVM6ZBQ5VTKG24SJMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合信贷银行首席执行官称不打算放弃德国商业银行的投资，报纸报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五援引意大利联合信贷银行首席执行官的话说，该银行不打算听从德国政府的建议，放弃收购德国商业银行的野心。【原文：UniCredit has no plans to heed the advice of the German government to drop its ambitions to take over Commerzbank , the Italian bank's CEO was quoted as saying on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-ceo-says-no-plans-abandon-commerzbank-investment-newspaper-reports-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JREDBC64A5IMPPSNRNVWXVPEP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:26:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市连续第二个月吸引外资流入，但关税前景阴云密布]]></title><description><![CDATA[受投资者对美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）降息和美元走软的预期提振，6月份亚洲股市连续第二个月吸引外资流入，但涨幅因美国即将加征关税而受限。【原文：Asian stocks drew foreign inflows for a second straight month in June, buoyed by investors wagering on U.S. Federal Reserve interest rate cuts and a softer U.S. dollar, though gains were capped by jitters over looming U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/asian-stocks-attract-foreign-inflows-second-month-tariff-outlook-clouds-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRWWUORA5FJZVP6VT6UBE4KMY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Warehouse 房地产投资信托基金转而效忠 Blackstone 的甜蜜出价]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国的 Warehouse REIT 周五向其股东推荐了 Blackstone 的甜蜜出价，撤回了对业内同行 Tritax Big Box REIT 对这家物流专业公司出价的支持。【原文：Britain's Warehouse REIT recommended Blackstone's sweetened bid to its shareholders on Friday, withdrawing support for industry peer Tritax Big Box REIT's offer for the logistics specialist.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uks-warehouse-reit-shifts-allegiance-blackstones-sweetened-bid-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCW6DED6XRLETCYL4L5VMRGGWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚稀土类股因 MP 材料公司在美国的数十亿美元交易而飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在总部位于美国的 MP Materials 公司与美国政府达成数十亿美元的协议以提高稀土磁铁的产量之后，包括 Lynas 和 Iluka Resources 公司在内的澳大利亚稀土矿商的股价周五飙升。【原文：Shares of Australian rare earths miners, including Lynas and Iluka Resources , soared on Friday after U.S.-based MP Materials' a multibillion-dollar deal with the U.S. government to boost production of rare earth magnets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/australian-rare-earth-stocks-soar-mp-materials-multi-billion-us-deal-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFHZD2OXIZNO7E22GKJASMFIWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团将 2026 年中期 MSCI 全球股票指数目标定为 1150 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周五提出了 2026 年中期 MSCI 所有国家全球指数（ACWI）的本地目标，因为他们预计全球股市在年底前将处于区间震荡，"有意义的 "涨幅将出现在明年上半年。【原文：Citigroup on Friday introduced its mid-2026 target for the MSCI All Country World Index (ACWI) Local as they expect global equity markets to be rangebound until year-end, with "meaningful' gains coming in the first half of next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/citigroup-sets-mid-2026-target-1150-mscis-global-equity-index-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UIJFKVPHRJT7B2JRC2EXPIAXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 05:52:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价新关税剧震撼自满的市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5RSHT4P2AVLOLIIJ4AQFUUKREY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:45:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在与美国的微妙休战中，中国 6 月出口增长有望回升：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心与美国达成的脆弱贸易休战协议可能破裂，唐纳德-特朗普总统可能会恢复对中国商品征收额外关税，出口商急于提前装运货物，受此提振，中国 6 月份的出口增长可能走高。【原文：China's export growth likely edged higher in June, buoyed by exporters rushing to front-load shipments on fears that a fragile trade truce with the United States could unravel and see President Donald Trump reinstate extra tariffs on Chinese goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-export-growth-expected-edge-up-june-amid-delicate-truce-with-us-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Q2CLPRUCRIVVATN6BHNN4IPQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:42:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 MUFG 瞄准美国证券化业务，计划增加员工人数]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大银行集团三菱日联金融集团（Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group）的一位高管在接受采访时表示，该集团计划在全球范围内拓展证券化业务，重点是北美地区，并将把这一领域的员工人数增加约 25%。【原文：Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group plans to expand its securitisation business globally, with a focus on North America, and will increase headcount in this area by around 25%, a senior executive at Japan's largest banking group said in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japans-mufg-targets-us-securitisation-business-plans-boost-headcount-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EE2M6MM6LBNHFOYQMY4HFXHKX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国政府推动消费贷款，中资银行步履维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的银行正在努力遵守中国政府新出台的促进消费信贷的指导原则，因为它们受到了个人贷款违约激增的影响，而且很难找到经济状况良好、愿意贷款的家庭。【原文：Chinese banks are struggling to comply with new Beijing guidelines to boost consumer credit as they reel from a surge of defaults on personal loans and have a hard time finding households in good financial shape that want to borrow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/chinese-banks-stumble-beijings-consumer-lending-push-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLLNBNDB2VMS7C63R3CEC6L7WA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:33:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上海监管机构考虑对稳定币和加密货币采取政策应对措施，这是一个重大转变]]></title><description><![CDATA[上海一家监管机构表示，它本周为当地政府官员召开了一次会议，以考虑稳定币和数字货币的战略应对措施--这对于禁止加密货币交易的中国来说是一个明显的基调转变。【原文：A Shanghai regulator said it held a meeting this week for local government officials to consider strategic responses to stablecoins and digital currencies - a marked shift in tone for China where crypto trading is banned.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/major-shift-shanghai-regulator-mulls-policy-responses-stablecoins-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QIHZMKAHBIGNFNCU4Y4X2GJ4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:22:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，谷歌将为美国政府提供折扣云计算服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引美国总务管理局（GSA）一位高级官员的话报道称，谷歌将为美国政府提供的云计算服务大幅打折，交易可能在几周内敲定。【原文：Google will heavily discount cloud computing services for the U.S. government in a deal that could be finalised within weeks, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing a senior official at the General Services Administration (GSA).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/google-discount-cloud-computing-services-us-government-ft-reports-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72G5QKLZRVJIXEBKZHP7T66JIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期限表显示，日产汽车出售债券融资 45 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五查阅的一份条款书显示，日本日产汽车公司已发行 45.2 亿美元的美元和欧元高级无担保债券，募集资金将用于为现有债务再融资。【原文：Japan's Nissan Motor has raised $4.52 billion in U.S. dollar- and euro-denominated senior unsecured bonds, according to a term sheet reviewed by Reuters on Friday, with the proceeds intended to refinance existing debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-motor-raises-45-billion-bond-sales-term-sheet-shows-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUTT4ZDDO5JFJENLJEFJ3MEP4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:06:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将于 7 月 15 日在孟买开设印度首家专卖店]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商特斯拉（Tesla）周五表示，将于7月15日在印度金融中心孟买开设首家展厅，并将其称为 "体验中心"，从而进一步拉近了在印度的销售距离。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Tesla inched closer to start its sales in India, as it said on Friday it would be opening its first showroom at the financial hub of Mumbai on July 15, dubbed as an "experience center".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/tesla-launch-first-india-store-mid-july-mumbai-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBDQFSQ2RNIIVJBTPE2WTYT4TY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 03:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称，松下将推迟美国电动汽车电池计划，原因是特斯拉销售缓慢]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周五报道，松下控股公司计划推迟其在美国堪萨斯州新建的电动汽车电池厂在2027年3月前实现满负荷生产的计划，因为其主要客户特斯拉公司（Tesla）销售低迷。【原文：Panasonic Holdings plans to postpone its plan to bring its new electric vehicle battery plant in the U.S. state of Kansas to full capacity by March 2027 as Tesla , its main customer, is experiencing sluggish sales, the Nikkei business daily said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/panasonic-postpone-us-ev-battery-plan-slow-tesla-sales-nikkei-says-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHQ46PVVDFLOLDPMPBVARINCDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:49:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[审计发现违规行为后，中国奇瑞、比亚迪或需偿还补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国工业部的一项审计发现，奇瑞（CHERY.UL）和比亚迪在截至 2020 年的五年内销售的环保汽车共不当申请了 5300 万美元的政府补贴，占不当申请的近 60%。【原文：China's Chery (CHERY.UL) and BYD improperly claimed a combined $53 million in government subsidies for eco-friendly vehicles sold in the five years to 2020, accounting for nearly 60% of improper claims, an industry ministry audit found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-chery-byd-may-have-repay-subsidies-after-audit-finds-irregularities-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGDMGUEDSRL3TCKQZJVVMSIQX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:33:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动卡车销量飙升对中国柴油车使用造成新的打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[在补贴和充电桩快速推广的推动下，电动重型卡车在中国的市场份额迅速扩大，进一步抑制了柴油的使用，并削弱了全球最大原油进口国对石油的需求。【原文：Electric-powered heavy trucks are rapidly gaining market share in China, driven by subsidies and the quick rollout of chargers, further curbing diesel usage and denting oil demand from the world's biggest crude importer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/soaring-electric-truck-sales-deal-new-blow-diesel-use-china-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKKCLJUTONOZTBOQIUPWDHRJLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:19:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：特朗普的铜关税计划将包括半成品]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对铜征收50%关税的计划将包括半成品，如用于电网、军事和数据中心的半成品。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's plans to impose 50% tariffs on copper would include semi-finished products such as those used for power grids, the military and data centers, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trumps-copper-tariffs-plan-include-semi-finished-products-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3F3MU7RXRM2TNKKM7QC3PHY5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 01:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布征收新关税，美元上涨，卢比下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布征收更多关税，并表示计划对大多数贸易伙伴一律征收 15%或 20%的关税，全球贸易格局出现更多动荡迹象，美元周五上涨。【原文：The U.S. dollar rose on Friday on more signs of upheaval in the global trade landscape, as U.S. President Donald Trump announced more tariffs and said he planned to impose blanket levies of 15% or 20% on most trade partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-rises-loonie-falls-trump-announces-new-tariffs-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2FCAKZU47ZIIZMD2NQT7BPMCRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 01:32:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布对加拿大和欧盟征收关税后，华尔街和欧洲期货下滑；美元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普加强对欧洲和加拿大的关税威胁之后，周五亚洲的美国和欧洲股票期货下滑，扼杀了该地区股市早盘的反弹。【原文：U.S. and European stock futures slid in Asia on Friday after President Donald Trump stepped up tariff threats against Europe and Canada, snuffing out an early rally in regional share markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARUOAINPCFKU5LQWZOTNUL7VSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价小幅回升，但受美国关税和欧佩克降级影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）新关税（预计将损害经济增长）和欧佩克（OPEC）需求预测下调的影响，油价在上一交易日下跌2%后，周五早盘企稳。【原文：Oil prices steadied in early trading on Friday following a 2% drop in the previous session that was driven by U.S. President Donald Trump's new tariffs, expected to hurt economic growth, and a cut to OPEC demand forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-recover-slightly-us-tariffs-opec-downgrade-weigh-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPCPOWTMDRKN7HCEPRXYBJ2NOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 01:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对加拿大征收 35% 的关税，对其他国家征收 15%-20% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美国将于下月对从加拿大进口的商品征收35%的关税，并计划对其他大多数贸易伙伴一律征收15%或20%的关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday the United States would impose a 35% tariff on imports from Canada next month and planned to impose blanket tariffs of 15% or 20% on most other trade partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-puts-35-tariff-canada-eyes-15-20-tariffs-others-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GE3XH2FPLVM37NQYTLNUU3SNGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布对加拿大征收 35% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四宣布，从8月1日起对从加拿大进口的商品征收35%的关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday announced a 35% tariff rate for goods imported from Canada, starting August 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-announces-35-tariffs-canada-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBJCV2HCFBMJFGYWOUXFOBY7K4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:23:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛任命本-华莱士为美洲地区并购联席主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部备忘录，高盛集团周四任命本-华莱士（Ben Wallace）为美洲并购部门联席主管。【原文：Goldman Sachs appointed Ben Wallace as co-head of Mergers and Acquisitions division in the Americas on Thursday, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-appoints-ben-wallace-ma-co-head-americas-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LUTC4ZP3VPFNO3ZEEHP5POYP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达州总检察长调查 Robinhood Crypto 声称的低成本交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[佛罗里达州总检察长詹姆斯-乌斯迈尔（James Uthmeier）周四对 Robinhood Crypto 发起调查，称该平台可能误导了客户，宣传自己是购买加密货币的最便宜方式。【原文：Florida Attorney General James Uthmeier on Thursday launched an investigation into Robinhood Crypto, alleging that the platform may have misled customers by promoting itself as the least expensive way to buy cryptocurrencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/florida-ag-probes-robinhood-crypto-over-claims-low-cost-trading-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4OQOD3MDONN7ZKHC35SAQNTMFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 22:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>