<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:34:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:34:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中美 RedNote 用户找到难得的坦诚交流空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[从经济悲观主义到对马克思主义的愤世嫉俗，再到对潜在战争的恐惧，红笔记的中美用户本周进行了罕见的坦诚交流，测试了中国社交媒体平台审查制度的极限。【原文：From economic pessimism to cynicism about Marxism and fears over the potential for war, Chinese and American users of RedNote took part this week in rare candid exchanges that tested the limits of censorship on the Chinese social media platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-us-users-rednote-find-rare-space-candid-exchanges-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIT7MTIBCNIM7JJG7SC5S6OPCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈里王子将与默多克报社对簿公堂]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈里王子对鲁珀特-默多克（Rupert Murdoch）的英国报业集团提起的诉讼于本周二在伦敦高等法院正式开庭，查尔斯国王的小儿子将在下个月的庭审中亲自出庭作证。【原文：Prince Harry's lawsuit against Rupert Murdoch's British newspaper group officially begins at the High Court in London on Tuesday, with King Charles' younger son set to appear as a witness himself at the trial next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/prince-harry-set-court-battle-with-murdoch-papers-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQON62FJ7RNGTMKXDBPGFCRWXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工业安全产品需求低迷，Fastenal业绩未达预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Fastenal 公布的第四季度利润低于分析师预期，原因是建筑行业的持续放缓抑制了对其紧固件和其他安全产品的需求。【原文：Fastenal posted fourth-quarter profit below analysts' estimates on Friday, as a sustained slowdown in construction sector dented demand for its fasteners and other safety products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fastenal-misses-estimates-amid-sluggish-demand-industrial-safety-products-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFGUJ5E3T5IIZF7TUPL3VLSKRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场押注特朗普上台后中国会让人民币贬值，但幅度不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融市场押注，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）第二任总统任期内，中国将不会把人民币作为抵消美国关税预期的政策工具，因为有人认为，像第一任总统任期内那样的大幅贬值对陷入困境的经济弊大于利。【原文：Financial markets are betting China will not use the yuan as a policy tool to offset expected U.S. tariffs in a second Donald Trump presidency, based on a view that sharp depreciation like that seen in his first term will be more harmful than helpful to the struggling economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/markets-are-betting-china-will-let-yuan-fall-trump-takes-power-not-much-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLBUKQSIQRKBXOTGI72YO3B5TQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Truist 因投资银行业务收益而实现超预期的季度利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于资本市场走强，投资银行和交易活动更加活跃，特里斯特金融公司周五公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Truist Financial on Friday exceeded Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit, helped by stronger investment banking and trading activity as capital markets strengthened.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/truist-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-investment-banking-gains-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APKSSZ4YSRJRJONSDMANHGJ4IA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:32:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗证券申请中国证券牌照]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citadel Securities 是全球最大的做市商之一，在其全球首席执行官表示有意进入中国市场约一年后，该公司于周五提交了在中国的证券牌照申请。【原文：Citadel Securities, one of the world's largest market makers, on Friday filed an application for a securities licence in China, about a year after its global CEO expressed interest in entering the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citadel-securities-applies-securities-licence-china-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLN2XXA6YZJJTFENCLF2AC2JMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政策引发通胀忧虑，美联储 1 月将维持利率不变：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社调查，绝大多数经济学家认为，美国联邦储备委员会将在1月29日维持利率稳定，并在3月恢复降息，因为决策者们正在消化华盛顿方面预计将出台的一系列新经济政策。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve will hold interest rates steady on Jan. 29 and resume cutting in March, according to a slim majority of economists polled by Reuters, as policymakers digest an expected barrage of new economic policies from Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-hold-rates-jan-trumps-policies-stir-inflation-worries-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7LBSUIF3ZLYNBHC24RMXCTABY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:16:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟加强对马斯克 X 的调查，提出新要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五表示，正在加紧调查埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体网络 X 是否违反了欧盟关于内容节制的规定，要求该公司提供信息，并命令其保留相关文件。【原文：The European Commission said on Friday it was stepping up its investigation into whether Elon Musk's social media network X breached EU rules on content moderation with requests for information and an order for it to retain relevant documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-steps-up-probe-into-musks-x-with-new-demands-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJ5ICYKQKFPYZMKFCOKWDAH33E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际业务强劲，SLB 季度利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于北美和国际市场对钻井设备和技术的需求增加，这家油田服务供应商的第四季度利润超过了分析师的预期。【原文：SLB beat analysts' estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Friday as the oilfield services provider benefited from higher demand for its drilling equipment and technology in North America and international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/slbs-quarterly-profit-beats-international-business-strength-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOYAOBONBZNXDE42S6SAU6TMOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:57:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典萨博 2024 年有机销售增长高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典防务设备制造商萨博公司周五表示，预计2024年全年的有机销售额将增长23.4%，高于此前预期的15%至20%之间的上限。【原文：Swedish defence equipment maker Saab said on Friday it expected an organic sales growth of 23.4% for the full year of 2024, above its previously expected outlook at the upper end of the range between 15% and 20%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/swedens-saab-posts-higher-than-expected-organic-sales-growth-2024-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4PCRDQ74FL7PPM2TLTS2COTKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:44:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构结束对近 7000 辆菲斯科电动 SUV 的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构周五结束了对 6971 辆菲斯科 Ocean SUV 因不慎启动自动紧急制动系统的调查，因为它预计不会从这家破产的电动汽车制造商那里获得更多信息。【原文：The U.S. auto safety regulator closed its probe into 6,971 Fisker Ocean SUVs on Friday over inadvertent activation of the automatic emergency braking system, as it does not expect to get further information from the bankrupt EV maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-auto-safety-regulator-closes-probe-into-nearly-7000-fisker-electric-suvs-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BM62Y6B52BPT3AQ5LYKXPIA3E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达首席执行官表示不会出席特朗普就职典礼]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋周五表示，他不会出席美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的就职典礼，而是将 "在路上 "与员工及其家人一起庆祝农历新年。【原文：Nvidia's chief executive Jensen Huang said on Friday he will not be attending U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's inauguration, but will instead be "on the road" celebrating the Lunar New Year with employees and their families.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/nvidia-ceo-says-not-attending-trumps-inauguration-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEOR4VHYSVMKDJSEYKDC32BNEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息疑虑重重，美国股票基金资金外流激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月15日的一周内，美国股票基金的资金流出量激增，原因是美联储今年降息的前景黯淡，而投资者对正在进行的季度财报季持谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw a spike in outflows for the week ending Jan. 15, as the outlook for Federal Reserve rate cuts this year had dimmed while investors were cautious about the ongoing quarterly earnings season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-fund-outflows-surged-doubts-over-fed-rate-cuts-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5CVW3I5TRIKNG6FS2KSWC2RIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:35:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局对超过 87 万辆通用汽车展开初步调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，在收到有关通用汽车公司生产的877,710辆汽车发动机故障的报告后，正在对这些汽车展开初步调查。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday it was opening a preliminary probe into 877,710 vehicles manufactured by General Motors , after receiving reports alleging engine failure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-opens-preliminary-probe-into-more-than-870000-gm-vehicles-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QXIZ6BN5JJBPNRWNS7RM6QVLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:25:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 利率上行削弱小盘股力量，小盘股失去特朗普的支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在投资者寻找能在唐纳德-特朗普担任总统期间大放异彩的资产之际，美国股市有望从共和党政策中受益的一个角落却步履蹒跚。【原文：As investors seek assets that will shine under a Donald Trump presidency, one corner of the U.S. stock market expected to benefit from the Republican's policies has been stumbling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-small-caps-lose-trump-bump-rising-rates-sap-strength-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYLDWBOKBRJ6BJR3IAXZJTJZ74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标沃勒和贝森特帮助国债收益率回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7KZW72TOZIRNL2WTYVTEGALWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:16:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关注特朗普就职典礼，期货走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货上扬，S&amp;P 500指数和道指有望创下11月以来的最大单周涨幅，而投资者则在等待即将上任的特朗普政府的一系列政策变化。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged up on Friday, with the S&amp;P 500 and the Dow looking set to log their biggest weekly advances since November, while investors awaited a wave of policy changes under the incoming Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-higher-with-all-eyes-trump-inauguration-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDOSYHZR4ZJSVAQOCKKCT2I7H4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业为节省债务成本而进行的对冲可能加剧了 10 年期债券的抛售]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家和分析师们说，最近几周美国国债市场的抛售很可能因企业计划本月在债券市场上借入近1900亿美元而变得更加严重，这凸显了今年可能持续存在的市场风险。【原文：A sell-off in U.S. Treasury markets in recent weeks was likely made worse by corporate plans to borrow nearly $190 billion in the bond market this month, bankers and analysts said, highlighting a risk for markets that is likely to persist this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/corporate-hedging-save-debt-costs-may-have-worsened-10yr-sell-off-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3C7ZP7GZD5NGVJHB5THELD5UCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，再保险公司放弃了对中东地区的一些限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士告诉路透社，包括瑞士再保险公司在内的再保险公司在 1 月份的保单续保季中更愿意为中东地区提供保险，并取消了一项条款，即如果加沙冲突升级，再保险公司可以退出。【原文：Reinsurers, including Swiss Re , have become more willing to provide cover for the Middle East in the industry's January policy renewal season, removing a clause which allowed them to pull out if the Gaza conflict escalated, industry sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/reinsurers-drop-some-middle-east-restrictions-sources-say-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAIGKBUO5NO47AR3GV5B47MV5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:12:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普开创新纪元，华尔街银行感受到放松资本规则的机遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[据业内高管透露，由于即将上任的特朗普政府更加友好，而且他们去年成功削弱了提高资本金的草案，美国大型银行计划推动对美国其他资本金规则进行彻底改革。【原文：Emboldened by a friendlier incoming Trump administration and their success last year in weakening draft capital hikes, big U.S. banks plan to push to overhaul other U.S. capital rules, according to industry executives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-banks-sense-opportunity-looser-capital-rules-trump-ushers-new-era-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYFKZNLJUJPRVFIUVQCA6NCLVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 大力推广体育可能推动了假期季度用户增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于 "杰克-保罗对迈克-泰森 "拳击赛的成功和美国国家橄榄球联盟（National Football League）热门比赛的首次亮相，Netflix 在体育赛事上的巨大赌注预计将推动假日季度新增 900 多万订户。【原文：Netflix's big bet on sports events is expected to have driven more than 9 million subscriber additions in the holiday quarter, lifted by the success of the "Jake Paul vs. Mike Tyson" boxing match and the debut of popular National Football League games.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflixs-sports-push-likely-fueled-subscriber-growth-holiday-quarter-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MI65W3GITVO5PALI3NOHX7ATO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:06:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员拜登或特朗普仍能拯救 TikTok；方法如下]]></title><description><![CDATA[当唐纳德-特朗普下令美国政府在 2020 年禁止流行的中国社交媒体应用 TikTok 时，他说这一 "积极行动 "是 "保护我们的国家安全 "所必需的。【原文：When Donald Trump ordered the U.S. government to ban popular Chinese social media app TikTok in 2020, he said the "aggressive action" was necessary "to protect our national security."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/biden-or-trump-can-still-rescue-tiktok-heres-how-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFBYDHGE3BIR5LWW5G4ACWZGTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总统就职日的美股表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二是唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）就任白宫第二任总统的第二天，投资者将密切关注股市的走势，以观察美国股市能否延续近期在总统宣誓就职后的上涨趋势。【原文：Investors will closely monitor stock markets on Tuesday, the day after Donald Trump is inaugurated for his second term in the White House, to see if U.S. equities can continue their recent trend of posting gains after a president is sworn in.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-stock-performance-dates-presidential-inaugurations-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CH7VHRUO6JIJRG4CPHYQA2BGCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Codelco 与沙特就铜矿投资进行谈判，2025 年产量有望增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利的 Codelco 公司是世界上最大的铜生产商，该公司董事长周五在接受路透社采访时表示，该公司正在与沙特阿拉伯就潜在的金属联合投资进行谈判。【原文：Chile's Codelco, the world's largest copper producer, is in talks with Saudi Arabia over potential joint investments in the metal, the company's chairman told Reuters in an interview on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/codelco-saudi-talks-copper-investment-2025-output-seen-up-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSQTKONSDZIUPO3B5JBFBVQTVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TPG 和 Transneft 撤销了俄罗斯大亨在英国的 140 亿美元诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权公司 TPG 和俄罗斯国有企业俄罗斯原子能公司（Rosatom）和俄罗斯石油公司（Transneft）周五胜诉，阻止了狱中大亨齐亚武丁-马戈梅多夫（Ziyavudin Magomedov）在伦敦提起的价值 140 亿美元的诉讼，该诉讼涉嫌阴谋剥夺其资产。【原文：U.S. private equity firm TPG and Russian state-owned firms Rosatom and Transneft on Friday won their bid to block jailed tycoon Ziyavudin Magomedov's $14 billion London lawsuit over an alleged conspiracy to strip his assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/tpg-transneft-throw-out-jailed-russian-moguls-14-bln-uk-lawsuit-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7WOQ6GSWZOBBINPGBKNNLIHXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国启动补贴汽车以旧换新]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周五启动了汽车以旧换新补贴项目，该项目类似于美国的 "旧车换现金 "刺激计划，去年该计划促进了中国的汽车销售。【原文：China's commerce ministry kicked off subsidised auto trade-ins on Friday, extending a program likened to the U.S. "cash-for-clunkers" stimulus that had bolstered China's car sales last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-kicks-off-subsidised-auto-trade-ins-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIVQZYEQERNL5MQH6BYL3LYEZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，美联储哈马克称通胀仍是个问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周五在接受《华尔街日报》采访时表示，通货膨胀仍然是一个问题。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack said in an interview published in the Wall Street Journal on Friday that inflation remained a problem.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-hammack-says-inflation-remains-problem-wsj-reports-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RFC4YTC7EZLZNGCPD4IWZG3R4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《明镜》报道，大众汽车希望深化与美国电动汽车制造商 Rivian 的合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国大众汽车公司首席执行官在周五发表的评论中告诉《明镜》杂志，该公司正在考虑如何深化与美国电动汽车制造商 Rivian 的合作关系。【原文：Volkswagen is considering ways to deepen its partnership with U.S. electric car maker Rivian, the German company's CEO told Spiegel magazine in comments published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-looking-deepen-partnership-with-us-ev-maker-rivian-spiegel-reports-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YY46UZRFXBL33F75ZVN7Z2QZTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:27:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在航空会议上，ESG 因飞机短缺而退居其次]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，一年一度的大型航空金融会议在很大程度上绕开了可持续发展的话题--这与该行业通常在遏制排放方面的严密信息传递大相径庭，让一些代表对 "环境、社会和治理疲劳症 "的影响感到担忧。【原文：A major annual air finance gathering largely skirted round the topic of sustainability this week - a rare departure from the industry's usual tight messaging on curbing emissions that left some delegates concerned about the impact of "ESG fatigue".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aviation-meeting-esg-takes-backseat-jet-shortages-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2OWY24G2BMQXG3C5UYJIMRMII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:21:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国债收益率上升导致全球股票基金需求下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 1 月 15 日的一周内，全球股票基金的需求急剧下降，原因是美国国债收益率上升，而且在强劲的就业报告公布后，市场对美联储降息的预期下降。【原文：Demand for global equity funds declined sharply in the week through Jan. 15, as U.S. Treasury yields rose and expectations for the Federal Reserve's interest rate cuts fell following a robust jobs report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQB5NJL5YVPCPDZNDQQ63VC4QI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 09:43:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>