<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 23:35:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 23:35:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[北卡罗来纳州州长表示花旗集团将在夏洛特增加 500 多个工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[北卡罗来纳州州长乔希-斯坦恩（Josh Stein）周二表示，花旗集团计划在夏洛特新增 510 个工作岗位。【原文：Citigroup plans to create 510 new jobs in Charlotte, Josh Stein, governor of North Carolina said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-add-over-500-jobs-charlotte-north-carolina-governor-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62CFCASZBNJAVM7FCFZSB3OG3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 22:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：关税不明朗，市场无波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KCTGAESO5I4FPGYRY6HPOTMVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:41:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国议员再次关注 GenScript 与中国的关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院中国问题委员会周二致函联邦调查局局长和国家情报局局长，鉴于 GenScript 生物技术公司与中国的关系，再次对该公司与美国公司的合作表示担忧。【原文：The U.S. House of Representatives committee on China on Tuesday sent a letter to the directors of the FBI and national intelligence, renewing its concerns about GenScript Biotechnology's work with U.S. companies, given its ties to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-lawmakers-renew-concerns-about-genscripts-ties-china-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4FXQBJ5EBJH3CR5MWHPG2SBPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商受亚洲国家关税影响的程度]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示将对十多个向美国公司供应大量纺织品的国家征收关税，其中包括越南和印度尼西亚等几个亚洲国家，美国服装零售商和鞋类公司正面临着更高的关税风险。这些征税大致从 25% 到 40% 不等。【原文：U.S. clothing retailers and footwear companies are facing heightened tariff exposure after the White House said it would put levies on more than a dozen nations, including several Asian countries like Vietnam and Indonesia, that supply large volumes of textiles to U.S. companies. Those levies range roughly from 25% to 40%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retailers-exposure-tariffs-asian-countries-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSZVL6BXUJML7IFIF4RIUOC5RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 "点击取消 "规则被上诉法院驳回]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国上诉法院阻止了一项要求企业像注册一样方便取消订阅和会员资格的规定，称制定该规定的机构没有遵守协议。【原文：A U.S. appeals court blocked a rule that would have required businesses to make it as easy to cancel subscriptions and memberships as it is to sign up, saying the agency that created it did not follow protocol.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/us-click-cancel-rule-blocked-by-appeals-court-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BH3VCN66URIZNDCUIYUPQLCTQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:19:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称金砖国家 "很快 "将被征收 10%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，美国将 "很快 "对从金砖国家进口的商品征收10%的关税，这引起了刚刚主办了金砖国家年度峰会的巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）的不满。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday the U.S. would "pretty soon" charge a 10% tariff on imports from BRICS countries, drawing another complaint from Brazil President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, who just hosted the bloc's annual summit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-brics-nations-get-10-tariff-pretty-soon-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMMFUC3CHBOV5NH3J5Q7SQKJYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球最大铜生产国智利在特朗普关税重磅炸弹之后陷入观望状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）出人意料地宣布对进口的红色金属征收 50%的关税后，世界第一大铜生产国智利正处于观望状态。【原文：Chile, the world's No. 1 copper producer, is in wait-and-see mode after U.S. President Donald Trump announced a surprise 50% tariff on imports of the red metal, with the Andean nation blindsided while its top miner held out hope of exemptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/worlds-top-copper-producer-chile-wait-and-see-mode-after-trump-tariff-bombshell-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJCPLDHC4FO5FEQ3B7G36URTVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果任命内部人士萨比汗为首席运营官]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周二任命内部人士萨比-汗（Sabih Khan）接替杰夫-威廉姆斯（Jeff Williams）担任首席运营官。【原文：Apple on Tuesday named insider Sabih Khan as its chief operating officer, succeeding Jeff Williams.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-names-insider-sabih-khan-coo-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDL5JZDRMZMXLHXZE5Z2CSMLTQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:42:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Meta 持有雷朋母公司 EssilorLuxottica 约 3% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周二告诉路透社，Meta Platforms 收购了眼镜制造商 EssilorLuxottica 近 3% 的股份。【原文：Meta Platforms has acquired a nearly 3% stake in eyewear maker EssilorLuxottica , a source told Reuters on Tuesday, amid growing consumer interest in AI-powered wearable devices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/meta-takes-around-3-stake-ray-ban-parent-essilorluxottica-source-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSSUCQ6DJJPEJO46LSNJR4B7QA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:20:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会要求加强对 "美国制造 "在线销售声明的监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周二呼吁亚马逊公司和沃尔玛公司打击在这两家零售巨头的在线市场上宣称 "美国制造 "的第三方卖家。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday called on Amazon.com and Walmart to crack down on third-party sellers that make deceptive "Made in USA" claims on the retailing giants' online marketplaces.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-ftc-demands-better-policing-made-usa-online-sales-claims-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GVXFWC4HJIJRCXULZTLBVR724</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院解除阻止特朗普大规模裁员的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周二为唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府恢复大规模裁员和机构重组扫清了道路，这是他缩减和重塑联邦政府的运动的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court cleared the way on Tuesday for President Donald Trump's administration to resume carrying out mass job cuts and the restructuring of agencies, elements of his campaign to downsize and reshape the federal government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-supreme-court-lifts-order-that-blocked-trumps-mass-federal-layoffs-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZNN4WDDNBLDFOGFSHBLKMRHP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国的铜从哪里来？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，他计划在当天晚些时候宣布对进口铜征收 50%的关税，这让全球铜产业大吃一惊，因为铜的产量对电动汽车、军事硬件、半导体和各种消费品至关重要。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday said he planned to announce a 50% tariff on copper imports later in the day, surprising a global industry whose output is critical to electric vehicles, military hardware, semiconductors and a wide range of consumer goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/where-does-us-get-its-copper-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6L6VMABLZNN5MWT6HK7W77K2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:40:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥 6 月总体通胀有所缓解，核心通胀率攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二的一项民意调查显示，墨西哥6月份的总体通胀率在连续四个月上升后可能有所回落，但核心通胀率预计仍将继续攀升，这加剧了市场对墨西哥央行将放缓降息步伐的押注。【原文：Mexican headline inflation likely eased in June after rising for four straight months, though core inflation is expected to have kept climbing, fueling bets the central bank will slow the pace of interest rate cuts, a Reuters poll showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-headline-inflation-seen-easing-june-with-core-rate-climbing-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5JBXLODKVNC7HTSYGAUTVVYI4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[衍生品转换后，联合信贷银行获得德国商业银行 20% 的股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利第二大银行意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）持有德国商业银行约 20% 的股份，并拥有相应的投票权。【原文：Italy's second biggest bank UniCredit owns an equity stake of around 20%, with corresponding voting rights, in Commerzbank after converting into shares derivatives which gives it an overall 29% holding in its German rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-gets-20-equity-stake-commerzbank-after-derivatives-conversion-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTT3WKTDUBPUXKIOPGQOBALHAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普推迟关税期限给贸易伙伴和企业带来希望和困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最近推迟关税的做法给主要贸易伙伴日本、韩国和欧盟带来了一些希望，即仍有可能达成放宽关税的协议，但同时也让南非等一些较小的出口国感到困惑，并让企业对未来的道路感到迷茫。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's latest tariff delay provided some hope to major trade partners Japan, South Korea and the European Union that deals to ease duties could still be reached, while bewildering some smaller exporters such as South Africa and leaving companies with no clarity on the path forward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trumps-tariff-deadline-delay-brings-hope-confusion-trade-partners-businesses-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YUQ6QQFW5MGJDTKEG2GQMYEQQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 18:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将对铜进口征收 50%关税后，COMEX 铜价创下历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示将宣布对进口金属征收 50%的关税后，美国铜价跳涨逾 12%，创下每吨 12,330 美元以上的历史新高。【原文：Copper prices in the United States jumped more than 12% to a record high above $12,330 per metric ton after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would announce a 50% tariff on imports of the metal on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/comex-copper-hits-record-after-trump-says-he-will-impose-50-tariff-copper-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DR77EYO5WJJRPMHAOZNRMW2KUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 18:21:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者在关税动荡中汲取 "解放日 "教训]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收全球关税导致市场暴跌后又猛烈反弹三个月后，投资者正在努力应对仍在变化的贸易背景带来的影响，并调整策略以抵御突如其来的政策变化。【原文：Three months after President Donald Trump's sweeping global tariffs led markets to plunge and then rebound ferociously, investors are grappling with the fallout from the still-shifting trade backdrop and adjusting strategies to withstand sudden policy shifts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-put-liberation-day-lessons-work-scarred-by-tariff-tumult-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GW344KSUCNJMRCTV7I7WBPR5WA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:54:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将于周二对进口铜征收 50%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他将于周二宣布对进口铜征收 50%的关税，以促进美国生产对电动汽车、军事硬件、电网和许多消费品至关重要的金属。【原文：President Donald Trump said he will announce a 50% tariff on imported copper on Tuesday, an effort to boost U.S. production of a metal critical to electric vehicles, military hardware, the power grid and many consumer goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-says-he-will-impose-50-tariff-copper-imports-tuesday-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWIVXGKBJFKLDJQ6HC6URNWISM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称摩根大通与古根海姆资深人士合作扩充技术团队]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份员工备忘录，摩根大通正在聘用古根海姆证券公司（Guggenheim Securities）高管迈克-阿梅兹（Mike Amez），因为这家美国最大的银行将继续扩大其技术投资银行团队，并为中型企业提供特定的专业知识。【原文：JPMorgan Chase is hiring Guggenheim Securities executive Mike Amez, as the country's biggest bank continues to expand its technology investment banking team and to provide specific expertise to medium-sized companies, according to a staff memo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jpmorgan-expands-tech-team-with-guggenheim-veteran-memo-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQ5NLIXJJVMTVLIM5O7UQF2I4E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:16:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国财政部部长贝森特将缺席下周举行的南非 G20 财金会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特计划的消息人士告诉路透社，他将缺席下周在南非举行的二十国集团财长和央行行长会议，这是他今年第二次选择不出席在东道国举行的二十国集团会议。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent will skip a Group of 20 finance ministers and central bank governors meeting in South Africa next week, sources familiar with his plans told Reuters, marking the second time this year he has opted against attending a G20 meeting in the host country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-treasurys-bessent-skip-south-africa-g20-finance-meeting-next-week-sources-say-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVPTUBIZBFLXJILEXDV45KA524</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，消费者机构将公平借贷最高官员排除在外]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟知内情的人士透露，美国消费者金融保护局负责监督公平借贷的最高官员已被安排休行政假，唐纳德-特朗普总统正试图最大限度地减少（如果不是彻底消除的话）这一监督机构的另一位高级官员也被排挤出局。【原文：The top official overseeing fair lending at the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau was placed on administrative leave, according to two people familiar with the matter, sidelining another senior figure at a watchdog agency President Donald Trump is seeking to minimize if not eliminate outright.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/consumer-agency-sidelines-top-fair-lending-official-sources-say-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36EFG7ZXUZMQ3J3NI2ZEII36ZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:56:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界黄金协会称，2025 年上半年黄金 ETF 吸引了五年来最大规模的资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界黄金协会（World Gold Council）周二公布的数据显示，1月至6月，实物支持的黄金交易所交易基金创下了自2020年上半年以来最大的半年度资金流入量。【原文：Physically backed gold exchange-traded funds recorded their largest semi-annual inflow since the first half of 2020 from January to June, data from the World Gold Council showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gold-etfs-drew-largest-inflow-five-years-during-first-half-2025-wgc-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISJLOQS4WFJ2VOWUL2MZRFX3HQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储鲍威尔应立即辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔应立即辞职。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell should resign immediately.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-feds-powell-should-resign-immediately-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YW5SGFOJIJJ37A2LOKDNL3URLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司称上半年交付 306 架飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司周二表示，今年上半年交付了 306 架飞机，比 2024 年同期的 323 架下降了 5.56%。【原文：Airbus said on Tuesday it delivered 306 airplanes in the first half of the year, down 5.56% from 323 in the same period of 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-says-it-delivered-306-airplanes-first-half-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6NVCJBZUVM3RIRZLHPI5VJEMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:57:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[X 称印度政府命令其封锁路透社在印度的新闻账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府上周直接命令 X 屏蔽 2000 多个账户，其中包括路透社新闻的两个账户，该社交媒体平台周二表示，这是对印度 "正在进行的新闻审查 "的一次尖锐的公开抨击。【原文：India's government last week directly ordered X to block more than 2,000 accounts, including two belonging to Reuters News, the social media platform said on Tuesday in a sharp public attack on "ongoing press censorship" in India.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/x-says-indian-government-ordered-it-block-reuters-news-accounts-india-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMBUL3RDIBM43OCG3SNCIVRTR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:37:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监督机构负责人告诉普京，俄罗斯企业在跨境支付中使用净额结算、黄金和加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯金融监管机构负责人周二告诉弗拉基米尔-普京总统，俄罗斯公司正在成功使用净额结算、黄金和加密货币来促进国际支付。【原文：Russian companies are successfully using netting, gold, and cryptocurrency to facilitate international payments, the head of Russia's financial watchdog told President Vladimir Putin on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/russian-firms-use-netting-gold-crypto-transborder-payments-watchdog-chief-tells-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPAVPZKMC5KL5LFCJR56XMHB7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司 6 月交付 60 架喷气式飞机，其中 8 架交付中国，恢复交付]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二表示，该公司 6 月份交付了 60 架飞机，与去年同期相比增长了 27%，其中 8 架飞机是在两国贸易争端结束后首次交付给中国客户。【原文：Boeing said Tuesday that it delivered 60 airplanes in June, a 27% increase compared to a year earlier, including eight to Chinese customers for the first time since a trade spat between the countries ended.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-delivers-60-jets-june-including-8-china-it-resumes-deliveries-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPGLSG6V3RIHJB2PELPLH2XRTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[扎克伯格的 Meta 超级智能实验室在硅谷挖走顶尖人工智能人才]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 正在为其新成立的超级智能实验室（Superintelligence Labs）争夺顶级人工智能人才，以便更好地与包括 OpenAI、谷歌和 Anthropic 在内的竞争对手竞争。【原文：Meta Platforms is racing to secure top artificial intelligence talent for its newly created Superintelligence Labs to better compete with rivals including OpenAI, Google and Anthropic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/zuckerbergs-meta-superintelligence-labs-poaches-top-ai-talent-silicon-valley-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDLCWHAEGVJOLPGCU2HWPBUA3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储：美国消费者对财务状况更满意，预期通胀稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储周二发布的一份报告显示，上个月美国人对通胀的展望变化不大，因为家庭对自己的财务状况和获得信贷的能力的看法有所提高。【原文：Americans' outlook on inflation was little changed last month as households upgraded their views on the state of their finances and ability to get credit, according to a report released on Tuesday by the New York Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumers-happier-about-finances-expect-stable-inflation-new-york-fed-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGR5SV3VTJKV5LUA53SUFX6EOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部长表示 "不会特赦 "被驱逐出境的农场工人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部长布鲁克-罗林斯（Brooke Rollins）周二表示，农业工人不会因特朗普政府驱逐所有非法入境移民的努力而获得 "大赦"。【原文：U.S. Agriculture Secretary Brooke Rollins said on Tuesday that there will be "no amnesty" for agricultural workers from the Trump administration's efforts to deport all immigrants in the country illegally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-farm-secretary-says-no-amnesty-farmworkers-deportation-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3MSKO3VWNMGHJTWB7UDYVX6YM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>