<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:34:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:34:55 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称福特因照明故障召回逾 10.5 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，福特汽车公司将在美国召回10.5万多辆野马汽车，原因是密封不严的面板可能会渗水，导致外部照明灯失灵。【原文：Ford Motor Company is recalling more than 105,000 Mustang cars in the U.S., citing improperly sealed panels that may let water seep in and cause external lights to fail, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recalls-over-105000-us-vehicles-due-lighting-failure-nhtsa-says-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTYONI22JBINZHTJMPP6XR3HY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:27:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[枪支制造商柯尔特将以 10 亿美元收购捷克硝化纤维公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于捷克的枪械制造商 Colt CZ Group SE 已同意分两个阶段收购捷克硝化纤维素制造商 Synthesia Nitrocellulose，交易估值为 220 亿克朗（10.5 亿美元）。【原文：Czech-based firearms maker Colt CZ Group SE has agreed to buy Czech nitrocellulose maker Synthesia Nitrocellulose in two stages in a transaction valuing the target at 22 billion crowns ($1.05 billion), Colt said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/gunmaker-colt-buy-1-billion-czech-nitrocellulose-company-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTME7QATS5M5TGJNHCANATBLGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:13:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，在美国发动贸易战之际，中国加大了从阿根廷和乌拉圭购买大豆的力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位贸易消息人士称，由于华盛顿和中国政府之间的贸易战久拖不决，中国的大豆进口商明年将增加从阿根廷和乌拉圭的采购量，以填补因美国不发货而留下的供应缺口。【原文：China's soybean importers are boosting purchases from Argentina and Uruguay over the next year to fill the supply gap left by the absence of U.S. shipments as the trade war drags on between Washington and Beijing, according to two trade sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-boosts-soybean-buys-argentina-uruguay-amid-us-trade-war-sources-say-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TYRM4U7FJL4BJBKKQWQ4A5YSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国汽车游说团体：欧盟铺平道路后，华盛顿必须迅速削减汽车关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车工业协会（VDA）表示，在欧盟启动取消美国商品关税的立法程序后，华盛顿必须迅速履行与布鲁塞尔达成的协议，从8月1日起将欧盟汽车进口关税从27.5%降至15%。【原文：Washington must swiftly honour an agreement with Brussels and cut tariffs on EU auto imports to 15% from 27.5% as of August 1 after the EU started the legislative process to remove duties on U.S. goods, Germany's auto industry association VDA said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/washington-must-swiftly-cut-auto-tariffs-after-eu-paves-way-german-car-lobby-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QR47TMVN5RNYVG5K2MSWUFXVCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳新银行首席执行官称自动邮件解雇员工 "站不住脚]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳新银行集团首席执行官努诺-马托斯（Nuno Matos）周五表示，银行职员被自动邮件告知被裁员是 "不可辩解的，令人深感失望"。【原文：ANZ Group's Chief Executive Nuno Matos said on Friday it was 'indefensible and deeply disappointing' for bankers to have been told they were being made redundant by automated emails, adding that the bank was taking steps to ensure no repetitions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/anz-ceo-says-firing-staff-by-automated-email-was-indefensible-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OT4BIPMHROF3F7LYHRVRHCVUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:47:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Binance 称所有期货交易暂时不可用]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Binance 周五表示，其平台上的期货交易暂时不可用，并补充说正在努力解决问题。【原文：Crypto exchange Binance said on Friday that futures trading is temporarily unavailable on its platform, adding that it is working to resolve the issue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/binance-says-all-futures-trading-is-temporarily-unavailable-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAOXUZKEF5OITIKTFMYPEXO75U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:47:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门批准日产中国与东风公司成立新合资公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周五发表声明称，已无条件批准日产（中国）投资有限公司与东风汽车公司组建新的合资企业。【原文：China's market regulator has unconditionally approved Nissan (China) Investment Co's new joint venture with Dongfeng Motor , according to a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/chinas-market-regulator-approves-nissan-chinas-new-jv-with-dongfeng-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVRVILTOBJJPZD2UBO5IUBL5LM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Forever 21 希望与新合作伙伴一起复活中国和北美业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[快时尚品牌 Forever 21 正在第四次进军中国市场，自 2008 年以来，它已三次进入和退出这个世界第二大经济体。【原文：Fast fashion brand Forever 21 is making its fourth run at the Chinese market, having previously entered and exited the world's second-largest economy three times since 2008.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/forever-21-looks-resurrect-china-north-america-business-with-new-partners-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVU4HWUKVJOQVOFCK4KUQ2C4JE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行主席奎格利辞去董事会职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰财政部长尼古拉-威利斯（Nicola Willis）周五表示，新西兰储备银行行长尼尔-奎格利（Neil Quigley）已提出辞去董事会主席一职，并立即生效。【原文：Reserve Bank of New Zealand Chair Neil Quigley has tendered his resignation from the board and as chair with immediate effect, Finance Minister Nicola Willis said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rbnz-chair-quigley-resigns-board-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSKFLRVZHFKODIUE7ZG2GBZPYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:59:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求疲软，就业困难，中国工厂活动再次萎缩 - 路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，8月份中国的工厂活动可能连续第五个月萎缩，制造商们正在等待与美国达成贸易协议的更多澄清，而就业市场的摇摆不定和房地产危机抑制了国内需求。【原文：China's factory activity likely contracted for a fifth straight month in August, with manufacturers awaiting more clarity on a trade deal with the U.S. while a wobbly job market and a property crisis curb domestic demand, a Reuters poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-factory-activity-seen-shrinking-again-soft-demand-job-woes-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKGQVQNX25OV3HMRDVHBJ72IFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人头马君度酒在美欧达成协议后下调关税影响预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国和欧盟达成贸易协议后，人头马君度酒公司周五下调了美国对欧洲进口商品征收关税的影响预测。【原文：Remy Cointreau cut on Friday its forecast impact of U.S. tariffs on European imports after the U.S. and the EU reached a trade agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/remy-cointreau-lowers-tariff-impact-estimates-after-us-eu-deal-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PESMQMYEKVN7JIJBDI4AFUS7WE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度以具有竞争力的价格增购美国石油，缩小贸易逆差]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易消息人士称，受具有竞争力的价格吸引，印度炼油商本月加大了对美国原油的采购力度，此举可能有助于在两国关系紧张的情况下缩小印度对美国的贸易逆差。【原文：Indian refiners boosted U.S. crude oil purchases this month, drawn by competitive prices, trade sources said, a move that could help narrow the country's trade deficit with the United States amid tensions between the two nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/india-boosts-us-oil-purchases-competitive-prices-narrows-trade-deficit-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HID6YZRKTRPPDPLHT225NDESUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:30:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲银行的辉煌业绩内幕：迈向还是超越甜蜜点？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年以来涨幅超过 40% 的欧洲银行股面临考验，法国再次出现的不确定性已经对市场情绪构成挑战。【原文：Resurgent European bank shares, up over 40% this year, face testing times with sentiment already being challenged by renewed French uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/inside-european-banks-stellar-run-towards-or-beyond-sweet-spot-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4EB5SPYEZMGXNE7MEBZQMLYAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价等待 PCE 为利率提供线索]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJ23SH4HRBMGVL4X5AYI4LTMMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:33:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[说明：微量豁免的终止将如何影响美国消费者和企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周五终止了美国对价值低于800美元的包裹的免税进口，这种所谓的 "微量 "豁免推动了全球卖家向美国消费者发货量的激增，而美国消费者现在可能将面临更高的价格。【原文：The Trump administration on Friday ended U.S. duty-free imports of packages worth less than $800, the so-called "de minimis" exemption that has fueled a surge in shipments from global sellers to U.S. consumers who will now likely face higher prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/how-end-de-minimis-exemption-will-impact-us-shoppers-businesses-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUYDTWVL7JL27MH46OIFNKPDUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:06:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国低价值包裹关税豁免结束，托运人和消费者成本增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对价值 800 美元以下的包裹运输的关税豁免于周五结束，这提高了电子商务公司、使用在线市场的小企业和消费者的成本，并扰乱了他们的供应链模式。【原文：The U.S. tariff exemption for package shipments valued under $800 ended on Friday, raising costs and disrupting supply chain models for e-commerce companies, small businesses using online marketplaces and consumers alike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-low-value-package-tariff-exemption-ends-raising-costs-shippers-consumers-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H74JCL7KCBMJXEZAW264QXOGQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前印度央行行长乌尔吉特-帕特尔被任命为国际货币基金组织（IMF）执行董事]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府周五发表声明称，前印度储备银行行长乌尔吉特-帕特尔（Urjit Patel）已被任命为国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）执行董事。【原文：Former Reserve Bank of India Governor Urjit Patel has been appointed as executive director at the International Monetary Fund, a government statement showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/former-indian-central-bank-governor-urjit-patel-appointed-imf-executive-director-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAK7KODRTBIUJF73XGYNSJNQQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克要求驳回美国证券交易委员会关于其持有 2022 股 Twitter 股份的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周四提出动议，要求驳回美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）的民事诉讼，该委员会指控马斯克在2022年披露其在推特（Twitter）所持巨额股份的时间过长。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk on Thursday filed a motion to dismiss the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's civil lawsuit that accused him of waiting too long in 2022 to reveal his large stake in Twitter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musk-seeks-dismissal-secs-lawsuit-regarding-his-2022-twitter-stake-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5HVMSW57RNVFNHPPF42LLK67U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:31:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场等待美国通胀数据，华尔街提振亚洲市场情绪高涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲股市走高，搭上了华尔街科技股反弹的顺风车，投资者目前的焦点转向当天晚些时候将公布的美国关键通胀数据，以寻找有关美联储利率前景的进一步线索。【原文：Asian stocks edged higher on Friday, riding a tech-driven rally on Wall Street, with investor focus now turning to a key U.S. inflation reading due later in the day for further clues on the Federal Reserve's rate outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGOO5WZDMZI7RELP3QMO5YFFHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国将增加预算支出，以促进人工智能引领的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国新任总统试图通过促进人工智能投资的政策来刺激经济增长，因此韩国政府计划以四年来最大幅度提高明年的预算支出。【原文：South Korea's government plans to raise budget spending for next year by the steepest pace in four years as the country's new president seeks to spur economic growth through a policy of boosting investment in artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-boost-budget-spending-bid-spur-ai-led-growth-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FX3TBOVENNMRPJ5RZADLGZ7LP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡淡马锡过去二十年的主要变化]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡国家投资公司淡马锡（TEM.UL）周四宣布对其业务进行重大重组，这标志着该公司 51 年历史上最重大的结构性转变之一。【原文：Singapore's state investment company Temasek (TEM.UL) announced on Thursday a major reorganisation of its operations, marking one of the most significant structural shifts in its 51-year history.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/key-changes-singapores-temasek-over-past-two-decades-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOIXFEMRRNLSDE5QSEBRST3GUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因需求担忧而下跌，但本周有望上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周五下跌，但本周仍将上涨，原因是随着夏季需求期的结束，全球最大的石油用户美国的需求预期将下降，而俄罗斯的供应又存在不确定性。【原文：Oil prices fell on Friday but are set for a weekly gain, caught between expectations of lower demand in the U.S., the world's biggest oil user, as the summer demand period is ending and uncertainty around the availability of Russian supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-fall-demand-concerns-headed-weekly-gain-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QY3GKD3MRZMU3A2PUQX5PPSCBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[YouTube与福克斯达成协议以防止中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的 YouTube 和福克斯公司周四表示，双方已达成协议，将继续向 YouTube TV 用户提供福克斯新闻、福克斯体育和其他福克斯频道。【原文：Alphabet-owned YouTube and Fox said on Thursday they have reached an agreement that will keep Fox News, Fox Sports and other Fox channels available to YouTube TV subscribers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/youtube-reaches-agreement-with-fox-prevent-disruption-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6C6MJ2N36ZJMVPJ7ISMJWUTFIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元将因降息赌注而出现月度下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美联储下月降息的可能性上升，同时对美国中央银行独立性受到威胁的担忧挥之不去，美元汇率周五出现波动，8月份兑主要货币有望下跌2%。【原文：The dollar wobbled on Friday, poised for a 2% drop in August against major currencies on rising odds of the Federal Reserve cutting interest rates next month while worries about the threats to the U.S. central bank's independence linger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-headed-monthly-drop-rate-cut-wagers-2025-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5XGNKG2YUZJVDAM7SAK7O6JYY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称巴西启动评估美国关税报复的正式程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，巴西外交部周四晚间下令政府贸易机构 Camex 开始分析是否可以利用当地的互惠法来对付美国。【原文：Brazil's Foreign Ministry ordered government trade body Camex on Thursday evening to start analyzing whether a local reciprocity law could be used against the United States, two sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-starts-formal-process-assess-us-tariff-retaliation-say-sources-2025-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAMYQQLTQ5PIFL2F7ZMUKHDZJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，据说边疆航空公司董事长将与精神航空公司高管会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，美国精神航空公司（Spirit Aviation）已与竞争对手边疆集团（Frontier Group）进行了高层会谈，商讨该航空公司在破产不到六个月后，如何继续努力开辟前进的道路。【原文：Spirit Aviation has engaged rival Frontier Group in high-level talks about the carrier's ongoing efforts to chart a path forward less than six months after emerging from bankruptcy, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frontier-air-chairman-said-meet-with-spirit-air-executives-bloomberg-news-2025-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI5XL5L3HNJYZDHFHVYLDYN5VE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:51:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚明星娱乐公司报告年度亏损收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚星空娱乐公司周五公布的年度亏损额有所收窄，这得益于未计提拖累去年盈利的巨额减值费用，尽管补救成本和顾客消费低迷继续对公司的盈利底线造成压力。【原文：Australia's Star Entertainment reported a narrower annual loss on Friday, helped by the absence of a massive impairment charge that weighed on last year's earnings, though remediation costs and subdued patron spending continued to pressure the bottom line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-star-entertainment-reports-narrower-annual-loss-2025-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LSB6JMQUNLK7MYPXAN2J7FNOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[维珍澳大利亚公司报告年度利润增长 28]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，维珍澳大利亚公司公布了其全年基本利润增长近 28%，这是自上市以来的首次业绩增长，主要得益于其航空公司和忠诚度计划部门的强劲表现。【原文：Virgin Australia reported a near 28% rise in its full-year underlying profit on Friday, in its first result since listing back, driven by strong performance in its airline and loyalty program segments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/virgin-australia-reports-28-rise-annual-profit-2025-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIMOW4BTW5LO7MP3ZHFZ2EWUA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美联储人选米兰将于 9 月 4 日接受参议院听证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院银行委员会将于 9 月 4 日举行听证会，审议唐纳德-特朗普总统提名的联邦储备委员会成员斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）。【原文：The U.S. Senate Banking Committee will hold a hearing September 4 to consider President Donald Trump's nominee to the Federal Reserve Board, Stephen Miran, it said in a notice issued Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-fed-pick-miran-get-senate-hearing-sept-4-2025-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2CXK2DAJ5IB7HDVQL5TXN2N5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员怀登和沃伦就网络攻击后的贷款偿还问题向 UnitedHealth 施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员罗恩-怀登（Ron Wyden）和伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）致信 UnitedHealth 高管，要求他们提供有关该医疗集团在其技术部门去年遭受网络攻击后提供贷款的信息。【原文：U.S. Senators Ron Wyden and Elizabeth Warren wrote a letter to UnitedHealth executives asking for information about the loans the healthcare conglomerate provided after the cyberattack at its tech unit last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/us-senators-wyden-warren-press-unitedhealth-loan-repayments-after-cyberattack-2025-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBLEBUZAMFI7BLUKE5PKAE4ELQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:33:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>