<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 22:04:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 22:04:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特斯拉将推迟在美国推出经济型电动汽车--成本更低的 Model Y]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士告诉路透社记者，特斯拉备受期待的平价汽车计划包括其最畅销的电动 SUV Model Y 的精简版，该车将在美国生产，但投产时间已被推迟。【原文：Tesla's much-awaited plans for an affordable car include a stripped-down version of its best-selling electric SUV, the Model Y, that will be made in the United States, but the production launch has been delayed, three sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-delay-us-launch-affordable-ev-lower-cost-model-y-sources-say-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BMP2EOXW5PA7CNQW7P3UJNN4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 20:34:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：在特朗普的贸易战中，银行家们发挥创意签署并购交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策导致全球市场横盘之后，硅谷私募股权公司银湖合伙公司（Silver Lake Partners）在其与芯片制造商英特尔（Intel）历时数月谈判达成的交易中增加了一些新条款。【原文：After U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs sent global markets sideways, Silicon Valley private equity firm Silver Lake Partners added some new terms to a deal it had spent months negotiating with chipmaker Intel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bankers-get-creative-sign-ma-deals-trumps-trade-war-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PL352ZBRKZOMLA7MDG2RBXVCYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 18:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：因关税问题，福特停止向中国出口汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税后，福特汽车公司已停止向中国运输其 SUV、皮卡和跑车。【原文：Ford Motor has halted shipments of its SUVs, pick-up trucks and sport cars to China in the wake of President Donald Trump's tariffs, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-halts-shipments-vehicles-china-amid-tariffs-wsj-reports-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LINYCZDH2NOW7BUKT5T63FVRB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 18:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，KKR 是争夺阿布扎比地区制冷业务的资产管理公司之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士称，KKR 和 I Squared Capital 是竞购阿布扎比倍增集团（Multiply Group）所拥有的区域冷却业务的全球资产管理公司之一，倍增集团是阿联酋最有权势的酋长之一所监管的 1.5 万亿美元帝国的一部分。【原文：KKR and I Squared Capital are among global asset managers bidding for a district cooling business owned by Abu Dhabi's Multiply Group, part of a $1.5 trillion empire overseen by one of the UAE's most powerful Sheikhs, three sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kkr-among-asset-managers-vying-abu-dhabis-district-cooling-business-sources-say-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKASPPMSMZOCTANAKTIIKM6H54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 17:36:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普关税影响，沃尔沃将在美国裁员多达 800 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔沃集团（Volvo Group）发言人周五表示，面对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策，由于市场不确定性和需求担忧，沃尔沃集团计划在未来三个月内在美国三家工厂裁员多达 800 人。【原文：Volvo Group plans to lay off as many as 800 workers at three U.S. facilities over the next three months due to market uncertainty and demand concerns in the face of President Donald Trump's tariffs, a spokesperson said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cut-up-800-us-jobs-trumps-tariffs-bite-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7V5S6GY665JGDJMRNODOKFFGYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 17:33:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[唐宁街：英国首相斯塔默与特朗普讨论贸易问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐宁街发言人周五表示，英国首相基尔-斯塔默（Keir Starmer）与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）进行了会谈，讨论了两国之间的贸易问题以及乌克兰和伊朗局势等其他议题。【原文：British Prime Minister Keir Starmer spoke with U.S. President Donald Trump, discussing trade between the two nations among other subjects including the situation in Ukraine and Iran, a Downing Street spokesperson said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk-pm-starmer-discussed-trade-with-trump-downing-street-says-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DT4CHFGKJBJ63P66OOBUXXXBI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 17:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀进展缓慢，美联储戴利称可能需要等待降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联储主席玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周五表示，虽然她对今年的几次降息仍然感到满意，但通胀风险的上升意味着央行可能需要做得更少，尤其是考虑到唐纳德-特朗普总统贸易政策的不确定性迄今为止几乎没有对仍然稳固的美国经济增长造成破坏。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve President Mary Daly said on Friday that while she is still comfortable with a couple of interest rate cuts this year, rising risks of inflation mean the central bank may need to do less, especially given that uncertainty over President Donald Trump's trade policy has so far done little to disrupt still-solid U.S. economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/with-inflation-progress-slow-feds-daly-says-rate-cuts-may-need-wait-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3O53HVZBZNI5MRYHJ5K7SNAL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 17:18:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行业监管机构批准 Capital One 与 Discover 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储和货币监理署周五表示，已批准 Capital One 和 Discover 合并，为两家公司成为美国第八大银行铺平了道路。【原文：The Federal Reserve and Office of the Comptroller of the Currency said on Friday they have approved the merger of Capital One and Discover, paving the way for the two firms to become the eighth-largest bank in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-banking-regulators-ok-capital-one-discover-deal-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKKXP64X7ZIWHG5HB5GZBXRPG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称巴西国家石油公司批准重启巴西东北部化肥厂招标]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，巴西国营石油公司（Petrobras）董事会周四批准了选择合作伙伴重启其位于巴西东北部化肥厂运营的计划。【原文：The board of Brazilian state-run oil company Petrobras on Thursday approved plans to select a partner to restart operations at its fertilizer plants in northeastern Brazil, according to four sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/petrobras-approves-tender-restart-fertilizer-plants-brazils-northeast-say-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6PCCTJQHNMWFGBT73TP752EWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府启动扩大海上钻井计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国内政部周五表示，将开始就新的五年期海上石油和天然气租赁计划征求公众意见，该计划可能包括在北极和其他地区设立新的区域，以最大限度地开发能源。【原文：The U.S. Interior Department on Friday said it would begin taking public input for a new five-year offshore oil and gas leasing program that could include new zones in the Arctic and elsewhere to maximize energy development.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-kicks-off-plan-expanded-offshore-drilling-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NE6NXQYGWZPUDFI6AZHJ73NYNQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利同意美国反对 "歧视性 "科技税]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利和美国周五发表了一份联合声明，反对对数字服务征收 "歧视性 "税收，这可能是罗马放弃征收令华盛顿恼火的税收的一个信号。【原文：Italy and the United States issued a joint statement against "discriminatory" taxes on digital services on Friday, in a possible signal Rome is moving away from a levy that has irked Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italy-agrees-with-us-oppose-discriminatory-tech-taxes-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTV2PLRZJNLNTMZYIXXHDIUZQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:12:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顾问称特朗普将研究是否解雇美联储主席鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周五在被问及解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔是否是一个选项时表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统及其团队将研究此事。【原文：White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said on Friday that President Donald Trump and his team would study the matter when asked if firing Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell was an option.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-will-study-whether-fire-fed-chair-powell-adviser-says-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIP7V4VSSFOZ5GF7OZCIQEYXOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 14:56:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1-3月中国财政收入同比下降1.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年前三个月，中国的财政收入降幅有所放缓，因为中国政府在努力支撑经济的同时，也在抵御美国不断加征关税的风暴。【原文：China's fiscal revenue decline slowed in the first three months this year as Beijing works to shore up its economy while weathering the storm from mounting U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-fiscal-revenue-falls-11-january-march-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TALQVZAL2NOW7PIWDARNUOGADE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:57:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌将就美国法院在垄断案中的部分判决提起上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司计划就美国司法部针对该科技巨头垄断案的法院判决中的 "不利 "部分提出上诉。【原文：Alphabet's Google plans to appeal against the "adverse" portion of the court decision in the U.S. Department of Justice’s monopoly case against the technology giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-appeal-against-part-us-courts-decision-monopoly-case-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJZ7AF4HDFII3LKTEQYJSY4Q7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:57:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利报纸对人工智能大加赞赏，称其具有讽刺意味]]></title><description><![CDATA[处于人工智能实验前沿的一家意大利报纸的编辑说，人工智能可以写出精彩的书评，也擅长讽刺，但它不会取代高质量的新闻报道。【原文：Artificial intelligence can write a great book review and is good at irony, but it won't replace quality journalism, said the editor of an Italian newspaper at the forefront of AI experimentation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/italian-newspaper-gives-free-rein-ai-admires-its-irony-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYD3RWSXBRMUDO22WAODIYPYQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:42:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发布服务业扩大开放规划]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五发布了进一步开放中国服务业的计划，建议取消对应用程序商店服务的外资股比限制。【原文：China on Friday issued a plan to further open the country's service sector, proposing to lift foreign equity ratio restrictions for app store services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-issues-plan-expanding-service-sector-opening-up-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Q7PLX66YNPAHDSJOMRYM5JQ2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:28:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利时尚品牌华伦天奴 2024 年利润下降 22]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利时尚品牌华伦天奴（Valentino）上周五表示，由于奢侈品行业面临全球高端商品需求放缓的问题，尤其是在亚洲，该公司去年的营业利润下降了 22%。【原文：Italian fashion house Valentino's operating profit dropped 22% last year, the company said on Friday, as the luxury sector faced a slowdown in global demand for high-end goods, particularly in Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/italian-fashion-house-valentino-suffers-22-profit-drop-2024-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDXN7FYLGRKERM2DZ452OEIGSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美国财报周市场忙于应对关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周美国公司的一系列重大业绩将考验因美国贸易政策改革而受到冲击的股市，该政策颠覆了全球经济和美国企业的前景。【原文：A heavy slate of U.S. company results in the coming week will test a stock market shaken by a U.S. trade policy overhaul that upended the outlook for the global economy and corporate America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-busy-us-earnings-week-confronts-market-grappling-with-tariff-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YFF7HVBYZKR3OVXQV2N4AIBLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察：在美国唐人街，商人们 "不希望贸易战成为战争]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，在纽约唐人街桑树街的 Sun Vin Grocery 商店，一包米饼的价格是 4.99 美元。【原文：Last week, a pack of rice crackers at Sun Vin Grocery store on Mulberry Street in New York City’s Chinatown cost $4.99.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-chinatowns-merchants-dont-want-trade-war-be-war-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I34V4XEVXZNLJJMMZJVIQT23M4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本警惕特朗普贸易政策带来的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府警告说，美国贸易政策的影响具有不确定性，因为关税可能会损害全球经济，但日本政府在周五的月度报告中也表示，由于企业部门的稳健发展，日本国内经济正在温和复苏。【原文：Japan's government warned of uncertainty over the impact of U.S. trade policies as tariffs could hurt the global economy but it also said in a monthly report on Friday that the domestic economy was recovering moderately thanks to a solid corporate sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-cautions-about-uncertainty-trump-trade-policies-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYTV4WZGBFMGRNLIZIWPBDUTUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 09:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯卢布对美元汇率突破 81，自 2025 年初以来上涨 40]]></title><description><![CDATA[在油价上涨的支撑下，俄罗斯卢布兑美元汇率突破 81，达到 2024 年 6 月 28 日以来的最高水平。【原文：The Russian rouble strengthened past 81 to the U.S. dollar, supported by rising oil prices, reaching its highest level since June 28, 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/russian-rouble-strengthens-past-81-vs-us-dollar-up-40-since-start-2025-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBMZ7CUBZNJ6VIHUIWBZZ2KQKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 09:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长维勒鲁瓦称美联储鲍威尔是央行行长典范]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（ECB）决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周五表示，美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔是一位堪称典范的央行行长，他对美国经济说出了不光彩的事实，而且没有向政治压力低头。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell is an exemplary central banker, telling the unflattering truth about the U.S. economy and not bowing to political pressure, European Central Bank (ECB) policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-powell-is-an-exemplary-central-banker-ecbs-villeroy-says-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQPX2JSTERJBPPSHJ6F25XCWY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 08:26:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰表示将在一周内完成矿产交易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[双方的目标是在 4 月 26 日之前完成最终协议的讨论。【原文：The aim of both sides is to complete discussions on the final deal by April 26.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/ukraine-says-aiming-wrap-up-mineral-deal-talks-within-week-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYUFDUVRCBLY3EFAKUM2S6W3QE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 08:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在与美国的紧张关系中推进反 "霸凌 "议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国外交部长王毅警告全球南方国家说，"单边霸凌 "正在伤害一个以规则为基础的世界，同时中国政府继续对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普施加外交压力，要求他收回其惩罚性贸易关税。【原文：China's Foreign Minister Wang Yi warned Global South nations that "unilateral bullying" was hurting a rules-based world, as Beijing kept up the diplomatic pressure on U.S. President Donald Trump to roll back his punitive trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-pushes-anti-bullying-agenda-amid-tensions-with-us-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQEOCB257RKRPNQEPVCL7AMVUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度莫迪与马斯克讨论技术合作潜力]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪（Narendra Modi）周五在 X 上发帖称，他与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）进行了交谈，并谈到了 "各种问题，包括我们今年早些时候在华盛顿特区会晤时涉及的话题"，但没有说明谈话是何时进行的。【原文：Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi spoke to Elon Musk and talked about "various issues, including the topics we covered during our meeting in Washington DC earlier this year," he said in a post on X on Friday, without saying when the conversation took place.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indias-modi-musk-discussed-potential-collaboration-technology-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXPJ2AVNLJOXPDO2ZTLVA3AXC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:36:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，越南公安部旨在获得互联网公司的多数股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一份文件显示，越南公安部计划收购该国最大的互联网服务提供商之一 FPT Telecom 的多数股权，作为其加强国家网络安全努力的一部分。【原文：Vietnam's Ministry of Public Security plans to take a majority stake in FPT Telecom, one of the country's largest internet providers, as part of its efforts to boost national cybersecurity, according to a document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/vietnams-public-security-ministry-aims-take-majority-stake-internet-firm-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54QV4OIZWRPQFNH5IRBO4FAFT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易协议有望达成，日本日经指数创 3 个月来最佳一周表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普能够促成与包括日本在内的一些主要贸易伙伴的贸易协议抱有更大的希望，日本日经平均股价周五上涨了1%，创下三个月来最好的一周。【原文：Japan's Nikkei share average rose 1% on Friday to clock its best week in three months, as investors turned more hopeful that U.S. President Donald Trump would be able to broker trade deals with some of its top trading partners, including Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-nikkei-notches-best-week-3-months-trade-deal-hopes-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QL75D4XI6RJALCSTJ5QCNNZXIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称丰田考虑在美国增产新款RAV4以应对关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士称，丰田公司正在考虑在美国生产其最畅销的 RAV4 SUV 的下一代车型，成为最新一家重新考虑供应链以减轻美国对进口汽车征收关税的冲击的汽车制造商。【原文：Toyota is considering producing the next version of its top-selling RAV4 SUV in the United States, three people familiar with the matter said, becoming the latest automaker to rethink supply chains to lessen the hit from U.S. tariffs on imported vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-weighs-adding-us-production-new-rav4-response-tariffs-sources-say-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QD7JKTSQLFIIZPMUKKGKSNIYFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着日本电产收购战的白热化，凯雷正在与牧野进行白武士谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位知情人士透露，私募股权巨头凯雷正在与日本牧野铣床公司谈判，希望将其作为潜在的白武士买家，以应对日本电产 18.1 亿美元的恶意收购。【原文：Private equity giant Carlyle is in talks with Japan's Makino Milling Machine as a potential white knight buyer to counter a $1.81 billion hostile takeover bid from Nidec , four people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/carlyle-white-knight-talks-with-makino-say-sources-nidec-takeover-battle-heats-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TITPHDYFX5NXJPL42OO43JT5AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将保持贷款利率稳定，但关税引发宽松押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项调查显示，市场普遍预计中国将在周一的月度定盘会上维持基准贷款利率不变，但面对不断升级的中美贸易战，市场正在赌中国会很快推出更多的刺激措施。【原文：China is widely expected to leave its benchmark lending rates unchanged at the monthly fixing on Monday, a Reuters survey showed, but markets are wagering on more stimulus being rolled out soon in the face of an escalating Sino-U.S. trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/china-set-leave-lending-rates-steady-tariffs-raise-easing-bets-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z52TACX6AZOSPMKXQFQJ4MGFV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 05:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>