<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:06:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:06:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 首席执行官必须面对 Bed Bath & Beyond 的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 的亿万富翁首席执行官 Ryan Cohen 必须面对曾被称为 Bed Bath & Beyond 的公司提起的诉讼，以收回在这家家居用品零售商破产前交易其股票所获得的 4720 万美元利润。【原文：Ryan Cohen, the billionaire chief executive of GameStop , must face a lawsuit by the company once known as Bed Bath & Beyond to recoup $47.2 million of profit from trading its stock before the home goods retailer went bankrupt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/gamestop-ceo-must-face-bed-bath-beyond-lawsuit-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EVVTPFRARIF5HQAYCUVM6O25Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:49:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月领先指标在关税影响下大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[衡量美国未来经济活动的一项指标在 3 月份大幅下降，可能预示着今年的经济增长将在关税影响下变得乏力。【原文：A gauge of future U.S. economic activity fell sharply in March, potentially flagging tepid growth this year amid tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-leading-indicator-declines-sharply-march-amid-tariffs-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEQTOFIVIZNNTEQVNZPN2Z44PQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:26:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普警告称，除非美联储降息，否则经济将放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，除非立即降息，否则美国经济可能会放缓，并再次批评美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔行动迟缓。【原文：The U.S. economy can slow down unless interest rates are lowered immediately, President Donald Trump said on Monday, repeating his criticism of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell as being slow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-warns-economic-slowdown-unless-fed-cuts-rates-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGVQFUBBCZKVJGN4LCRY5UBRO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回 CSX 恢复对诺福克南方公司反垄断诉讼的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一拒绝审理货运铁路巨头 CSX 提起的反垄断诉讼，该诉讼指控竞争对手诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern）非法限制其进入弗吉尼亚州东海岸的一个重要码头，导致 CSX 损失了数亿美元的利润。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Monday to hear freight rail giant CSX's bid to revive its antitrust lawsuit accusing rival Norfolk Southern of illegally restricting access to a key East Coast terminal in Virginia, costing CSX hundreds of millions of dollars in lost profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-rebuffs-csx-bid-revive-antitrust-suit-against-norfolk-southern-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKUMTIOTX5LEDOMJFSRV7A6VDI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chipotle 计划进军墨西哥市场，首家分店将于 2026 年开业]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chipotle Mexican Grill 公司周一表示，它将在墨西哥开设一家分店，并将于明年初开业，从而向国际市场扩张，首次为该地区的人们带来墨西哥卷饼和卷饼。【原文：Chipotle Mexican Grill is expanding internationally with a location in Mexico that is set to open early next year, it said on Monday, bringing its tacos and burritos to the people in the region for the first time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chipotle-plans-mexican-foray-with-first-outlet-2026-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYCN33IVFZI7BDMTH2LWL34HMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:38:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙宣布美国海湾巴利莫尔项目首次出油]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙（Chevron）石油公司周一表示，该公司在美国墨西哥湾的一个项目已开始生产石油和天然气，这使该公司向今年将该海盆的产量提高 50%的目标又迈进了一步。【原文：Chevron has started oil and gas production from a project in the U.S. Gulf of Mexico, the oil major said on Monday, bringing the company a step closer toward its goal of growing production from the ocean basin by 50% this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-announces-first-oil-ballymore-project-us-gulf-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLHY4QS5JVLEZGTW6XZM4BONQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计俄罗斯央行将把关键利率维持在 21%：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[参与路透社民意调查的 25 位分析师周一均预测，俄罗斯央行将在 4 月 25 日的董事会上将基准利率维持在 21% 不变，因为全球经济动荡加剧了人们对俄罗斯经济状况的担忧。【原文：The Russian central bank will keep its benchmark rate on hold at 21% at a board meeting on April 25, all 25 analysts who took part in a Reuters poll predicted on Monday, as global economic turbulence adds to concerns about the state of the Russian economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russian-central-bank-expected-keep-key-rate-hold-21-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEXLZ3HRWFNUNE4EB2OPFIISUE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:06:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因关税引发的通胀担忧，美国债券基金遭遇第五周资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至4月16日的一周里，美国债券基金面临着沉重的抛售压力，这凸显了人们对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税措施可能会加剧通胀并使经济陷入衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. bond funds came under heavy selling pressure in the week to April 16, highlighting concerns that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff measures could fuel inflation and push the economy into a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bond-funds-suffer-fifth-weekly-outflow-tariff-driven-inflation-fears-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWBZPITG2VMZ3OG56XUF4KFJPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国从美国私募股权投资中撤退]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周一报道，在全球最大的两个经济体之间贸易战不断升级的背景下，中国的国家支持基金正在撤出对总部设在美国的私人资本公司旗下基金的投资。【原文：China's state-backed funds are pulling back from investing in the funds of U.S.-headquartered private capital firms amid an escalating trade war between the world's two biggest economies, the Financial Times reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-retreats-us-private-equity-investments-ft-reports-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXZB2OR23NMXZK3MNWZATXI7DY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者涌入欧洲股票基金，因关税问题逃离美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月16日的一周里，欧洲股票基金吸引了大量资金流入，而美国基金则面临大量资金流出，原因是投资者对美国贸易关税的担忧以及对美国经济实力的担忧不断加剧，从而继续转移资金。【原文：European equity funds drew massive inflows in the week ended April 16, while U.S. funds faced hefty outflows, as investors continued to shift capital on concerns over U.S. trade tariffs and mounting worries over the strength of the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2XJQ6UH6NKOPOHEWIKWLWKKVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:49:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示将不分首席执行官和所在地执行数字规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）告诉 Politico，无论 X、Meta、苹果和 Tiktok 等公司的负责人是谁，也无论这些公司的总部设在哪里，欧盟都决心执行其完整的数字规则。【原文：The European Union is determined to enforce its full digital rule book no matter who is in charge of companies such as X, Meta, Apple and Tiktok or where they are based, Commission President Ursula von der Leyen told Politico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/eu-says-it-will-enforce-digital-rules-irrespective-ceo-location-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Q6YLCVVXVJPFKO5NJ4JTJ5ZHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度竞争监管机构批准谷歌在安卓电视案中的和解计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度竞争监管机构周一表示，已批准谷歌就安卓电视案提出的和解方案。【原文：India's competition regulator said on Monday that it had approved Google's settlement proposal in Android TV case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/indias-competition-regulator-clears-googles-settlement-plan-android-tv-case-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6WAT23AQBPHNOHXPR32GJH6YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易战升温，多伦多证券交易所期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大主要股指期货周一下滑，原因是中国警告说，将对以牺牲美国利益为代价与美国达成交易的国家采取 "反制措施"，这加剧了投资者对贸易战经济影响的担忧。【原文：Futures for Canada's main stock index slipped on Monday as China's warning of "countermeasures" against countries striking deals with the U.S. at its expense increased investor worries about the economic fallout from the trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsx-futures-fall-us-china-trade-war-heats-up-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLBDYDK4I5II3GOK6L5BEJXVMU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:24:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道LG、三星就电子垃圾定价政策起诉印度政府]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，韩国的 LG 和三星公司已经起诉印度政府，要求撤销一项增加对电子垃圾回收商赔偿的政策，并加入其他大公司的行列，以商业影响为由对印度的环境规则提出质疑。【原文：South Korea's LG and Samsung have sued India's government to quash a policy which increases payouts to electronic-waste recyclers, court filings show, joining other major companies in contesting the country's environmental rules citing business impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/lg-samsung-sue-indian-government-over-electronic-waste-pricing-policy-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CODBEBWE5PQ5FVYRDKDAWDGTI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩托罗拉解决方案公司推出人工智能工具和新设备，以缩短应急响应时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩托罗拉解决方案公司周一推出了一款名为 SVX 的设备，它集远程扬声器麦克风、车载摄像头和名为 Assist 的人工智能助手于一身，可帮助急救人员寻求节省时间和应对紧急情况的方法。【原文：Motorola Solutions on Monday launched the SVX, a device that combines a remote speaker microphone, body camera and AI assistant named Assist, to help first responders seeking ways to save time and react to emergencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/motorola-solutions-launches-ai-tool-new-device-cut-emergency-response-time-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZA6J4XUREFKBZDPNJFHSBNP43A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:06:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者涌向安全的美国短期政府债券基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国短期政府债券基金本月获得了大量资金流入，尽管其他大多数资产类别的基金在市场受到美国关税和经济衰退风险担忧打击时遭遇了大量抛售。【原文：U.S. short-term government bond funds have received large inflows this month even as most other funds across asset classes suffered heavy selling in markets hit by worries over U.S. tariffs and recession risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-flock-safety-us-short-term-government-bond-funds-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHTSHTKAOJOQXPW4BXN3MJBMV4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达沃斯会议创始人克劳斯-施瓦布卸任世界经济论坛主席一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[克劳斯-施瓦布（Klaus Schwab）已辞去世界经济论坛董事会主席一职。【原文：Klaus Schwab, founder of the World Economic Forum which gathers the world's business and political elite in the Swiss mountain village of Davos every year, has resigned as chair of its board of trustees, the WEF said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos-meeting-founder-klaus-schwab-steps-down-world-economic-forum-chair-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DBR6ASJYJKG5LSVUFZMO262KU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道信件显示，美国投资者卡梅伦出价 50 亿美元收购哈萨克矿业巨头 ERG]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商人詹姆斯-卡梅隆（James Cameron）在给欧亚资源集团董事会的一封信中表示，他愿意以 50 亿美元的价格收购该公司，因为该公司准备参与哈萨克斯坦稀土产量的大规模扩张。【原文：U.S. businessman James Cameron has offered to buy mining giant Eurasian Resources Group for $5 billion, a letter he sent to its board showed, as the company prepares to participate in a major expansion of Kazakhstan's rare earths output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-investor-cameron-offers-5-billion-kazakh-mining-giant-erg-letter-shows-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMC32BJHP5KQVHDT5GOMCWSQHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，尽管存在特朗普关税风险，日本央行仍可能保持加息信号不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉日本央行想法的四位消息人士称，日本央行预计将在下周发出信号，表示美国提高关税的风险不会破坏工资和通胀上升的周期，而工资和通胀上升被视为继续加息的关键。【原文：The Bank of Japan is expected to signal next week that risks from higher U.S. tariffs won't derail a cycle of rising wages and inflation seen as crucial to keep raising interest rates, said four sources familiar with its thinking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-likely-keep-rate-hike-signal-intact-despite-trump-tariff-risks-sources-say-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YYEIS56MZK5LCFI3V4JFI7OTQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称华为准备大规模出货新型人工智能芯片，中国正寻求英伟达的替代方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，华为技术公司（HWT.UL）计划最早于下月开始向中国客户批量发货其先进的 910C 人工智能芯片。【原文：Huawei Technologies (HWT.UL) plans to begin mass shipments of its advanced 910C artificial intelligence chip to Chinese customers as early as next month, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/huawei-readies-new-ai-chip-mass-shipment-china-seeks-nvidia-alternatives-sources-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K73PCU76PJKFRAKKB3NCX3OST4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:16:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌在美国结束搜索垄断面临审判]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周一将面临一场历史性的审判，美国华盛顿的反垄断执法人员将寻求迫使这家科技巨头出售其 Chrome 浏览器，作为恢复在线搜索引擎市场竞争的努力的一部分。【原文：Alphabet's Google faces a historic trial on Monday as U.S. antitrust enforcers in Washington seek to force the tech giant to sell off its Chrome browser as part of a bid to restore competition to the market for online search engines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-faces-trial-us-bid-end-search-monopoly-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJ2VMZW7IJIX3O73R2MNQO6V3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:14:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共和党议员在制定税收法案时面临清洁能源难题]]></title><description><![CDATA[致力于延长美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的减税法案的共和党议员们在国内正面临着清洁能源的难题，因为他们选区内的主要清洁能源投资与特朗普对该行业的怀疑态度相悖。【原文：Republican lawmakers working to extend U.S. President Donald Trump's tax cuts legislation are facing a clean-energy conundrum back home, as major clean energy investments in their districts are at odds with Trump's skepticism of the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/republican-lawmakers-face-clean-energy-conundrum-they-work-tax-bill-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXTP22ZBA5PURE7VLYBEUB7QWQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 在董事会争斗中就 Citgo 公司利益冲突问题回击 Elliott]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封信称，菲利普斯 66 公司认为埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）应该放弃拆分这家能源公司的努力，因为这位激进投资者与收购菲利普斯 66 公司竞争对手的另一项努力存在冲突。【原文：Phillips 66 is arguing that Elliott Investment Management should back down from its push to break up the energy company because the activist investor is conflicted from a separate effort to acquire one of Phillips 66's rivals, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/phillips-66-fires-back-elliott-over-citgo-conflict-interest-amid-board-fight-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I67H4X5Q5FN6DKJ65WBGEUJANE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:09:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：特朗普着眼于煤炭复兴，他的裁员措施却削弱了对矿工的黑肺保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[乔希-科克伦自 22 岁起就在西弗吉尼亚州的煤矿深处工作，拿着六位数的薪水，得以与妻子斯蒂芬妮一起买房，业余时间打猎和钓鱼。【原文：Josh Cochran worked deep in the coal mines of West Virginia since he was 22 years old, pulling a six-figure salary that allowed him to buy a home with his wife Stephanie and hunt and fish in his spare time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/trump-eyes-coal-revival-his-job-cuts-hobble-black-lung-protections-miners-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCEAEQVSENL2FKCZT53CR4XK7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:08:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司缓解了最新的 737 MAX 头疼问题--螺母和螺栓短缺]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位业内消息人士告诉路透社记者，波音公司已经获得了新的专用螺母和螺栓库存，这些螺母和螺栓用于组装其最畅销的商用喷气机，从而暂时避免了美国飞机生产因一家主要供应商的工厂发生火灾而放缓。【原文：Boeing has secured new stocks of specialized nuts and bolts that hold together its top-selling commercial jet, two industry sources told Reuters, avoiding for now any slowdown in U.S. plane production due to a fire at a key supplier's factory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-eases-latest-737-max-headache-shortage-nuts-bolts-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSR5G7NG2NJF3LG4ZPI22Y7PQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:05:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在马斯克的反击和竞争损害需求之后，特斯拉的经济型电动车和机器人轴成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉的投资者将迫不及待地向首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）询问两个迫切的问题：平价汽车何时推出，机器人出租车计划是否如期进行？【原文：Tesla investors will be eager to ask CEO Elon Musk two pressing questions when the electric vehicle maker reports results on Tuesday: when will the affordable vehicle launch, and is the robotaxi plan on schedule?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-affordable-ev-robotaxis-focus-after-musk-backlash-competition-hurt-demand-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTQP3MTEIRPWTCK2APRZVKPHHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特阿美石油公司与中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪签署开发协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特石油巨头阿美石油公司（Aramco）周一表示，该公司与中国电动汽车（EV）制造商比亚迪签署了一项联合开发协议，探讨在新能源汽车技术开发方面的合作。【原文：Saudi oil giant Aramco signed a joint development agreement with Chinese electric vehicle (EV) manufacturer BYD to explore collaboration in the development of new energy vehicle technologies, Aramco said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/saudi-aramco-signs-development-deal-with-chinas-ev-giant-byd-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZOR34CY7RIEXOT5N73AKGJ6C4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国央行敦促国有企业在海外扩张中优先使用人民币]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行周一表示，鼓励国有企业在海外扩张中优先使用人民币支付和结算，这被视为在全球贸易紧张局势加剧的背景下加快人民币国际化的官方尝试。【原文：China's central bank said on Monday it was encouraging state-owned enterprises to prioritise yuan usage in payment and settlement in their overseas expansion, in what is seen as an official attempt to accelerate yuan internationalisation amid intensifying global trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-central-bank-urges-state-owned-businesses-prioritise-yuan-overseas-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6TGMNGRLZM3XM4G4IUV5BFKVE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 09:56:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普抨击鲍威尔，美股期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周一下跌，原因是唐纳德-特朗普总统对美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的抨击引发了对央行独立性的担忧，令已经在努力应对不断升级的贸易战的投资者感到不安。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Monday, as President Donald Trump's attacks on Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell sparked worries about the central bank's independence, rattling investors already grappling with an escalating trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-drop-trump-takes-aim-powell-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X24NCQ7RU5OAJMDRQWNF3MZHSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 09:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix股价上涨，美好前景平息投资者对关税的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 的股价在周一盘前交易中上涨了约 3%，原因是这家流媒体巨头乐观的年度营收展望让投资者放心，在充满关税的经济环境下，它可以抵御任何经济衰退。【原文：Netflix shares rose about 3% in premarket trading on Monday as the streaming giant's upbeat annual revenue outlook reassured investors that it could withstand any economic downturn amid a tariff laden economic climate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-shares-rise-rosy-outlook-calms-investors-nerves-amid-tariff-fears-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHQDXQGH5BP6BFQAPUU2KICQ7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 09:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>