<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:45:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:45:36 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，迪士尼接近达成将 Hulu + 直播电视业务并入 Fubo 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道称，华特迪士尼公司和流媒体服务提供商 FuboTV 即将达成一项交易，合并双方的在线直播电视业务。【原文：Walt Disney Co and streaming provider FuboTV are nearing a deal to combine their online live TV businesses, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-nears-deal-merge-hulu-live-tv-business-into-fubo-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTW2FGUI75JL5KPQJD4BNWJROQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司和日本钢铁公司向法院起诉拜登阻止 149 亿美元的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）阻止日本公司以 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁制造商后，美国钢铁公司和新日本制铁公司周一表示，他们已提起两起诉讼。【原文：U.S. Steel and Nippon Steel said on Monday they had filed two lawsuits after U.S. President Joe Biden blocked the $14.9 billion buyout of the American steelmaker by the Japanese company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-nippon-steel-file-two-lawsuits-after-biden-blocks-149-billion-deal-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S65MI5XCTJPNVGUA7F2J5UB7LU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[当地媒体报道，智利 Codelco 公司 2024 年铜产量 "略有 "增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的铜金属生产商智利科德尔科公司（Codelco）董事长马克西莫-帕切科（Maximo Pacheco）周一在接受当地一家报纸采访时说，2024 年该公司的铜产量与前一年相比 "略有增加"。【原文：Copper production at Chile's Codelco, the world's largest producer of the metal, was "slightly higher" in 2024 when compared to the previous year, Chairman Maximo Pacheco said in an interview with a local newspaper on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chiles-codelco-copper-production-slightly-increases-2024-local-press-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NIHY5OORZI4VGTYRS6YI5FGM4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:52:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片股上涨，期货走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货在上周尾盘反弹的基础上继续走高，投资者因对人工智能的持续乐观而买入科技股，并等待可能为美国货币政策路径定调的关键经济数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Monday, building on a late rally last week, as investors bought into technology stocks on continued optimism around AI and awaited crucial economic data that could set the tone for the U.S. monetary policy path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-higher-chip-stocks-rise-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTBT6KPE3JMKVA565NCVMAMCOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：特朗普上台前交易提振美国收益率，人民币走势震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUOXNJMWPRIPJI2NS2B2HRMHFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:23:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼、福克斯和华纳兄弟将请求法院解除对推出 Venu 体育服务的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[三家大型媒体公司将于周一请求美国上诉法院推翻阻止其 Venu 体育流媒体服务推出的裁决，并辩称地区法院法官以反垄断为由阻止其计划的首次亮相是错误的。【原文：Three major media companies will ask the U.S. Court of Appeals on Monday to reverse a ruling that blocked the launch of their Venu Sports streaming service, arguing that a district court judge was wrong to halt its planned debut on antitrust grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/disney-fox-warner-bros-ask-court-lift-ban-launch-venu-sports-service-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVUHUMJWYBOULPVFIQXUZGWCVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:17:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 和 WWE 旨在推动全球摔跤热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 下一次涉足现场直播节目是从周一开始的，届时该公司将播出第一集《Raw》，这是世界摔跤娱乐公司每周的精彩节目，三十年来一直是美国电视的主打节目。【原文：Netflix's next venture into live programming starts Monday when the company streams its first episode of "Raw," the weekly World Wrestling Entertainment spectacle that has been a staple of U.S. television for three decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/netflix-wwe-aim-fuel-wrestling-fervor-worldwide-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIC6VBQJF5ONVGM5KMIYLA2HNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯南克等人表示，特朗普的政策可能不会导致通货膨胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括历任美国总统顾问在内的一些知名经济学家一致认为，当选总统唐纳德-特朗普扩大关税、减税和遏制移民的计划可能不会像早期分析所认为的那样引发通货膨胀。【原文：A number of leading economists, including advisers to past U.S. presidents, have coalesced around the view that President-elect Donald Trump's plans to broaden tariffs, cut taxes and curb immigration may not prove as inflationary as early analysis had suggested.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-policies-may-not-prove-inflationary-bernanke-others-say-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOYHNDQ575P35MO2SYWMNJUYDE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受高价刺激，阿根廷人到国外寻找更便宜的耐克和巨无霸食品]]></title><description><![CDATA[在智利圣地亚哥的购物中心和巴西的海滩上，阿根廷人正在抢购服装、电子产品和 caipirinhas，因为以美元计算的国内成本因当地比索走强而飙升，阿根廷人正在利用海外价格便宜的优势。【原文：In the shopping malls of Santiago de Chile and the beaches of Brazil, Argentines are snapping up clothes, electronics and caipirinhas, taking advantage of cheaper prices overseas as domestic costs in dollar terms spike on a stronger local peso.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/stung-by-high-prices-argentines-seek-cheaper-nikes-big-macs-abroad-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNTRNBKEBZMN7GVPC5A43SBT5E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面对保守派的反弹，董事会多元化停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[2020 年乔治-弗洛伊德遇害后，投资者梅洛迪-霍布森（Mellody Hobson）回忆起《财富》500 强公司的董事们经常打电话来，要求推荐董事会中的多元化候选人。她说，现在这种情况 "非常零散"。【原文：In the aftermath of George Floyd's killing in 2020, investor Mellody Hobson recalls frequent calls from directors at Fortune 500 companies for references to diverse candidates for boards. Now, she says, it's "very sporadic."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boardroom-diversity-stalls-face-conservative-backlash-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCWITMYRGZNGJPGAULG34PMQ3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总理办公室称，意大利与 SpaceX 的会谈不是梅洛尼-特朗普会晤的主题]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利总理办公室表示，意大利总理乔治亚-梅洛尼周末访问美国期间，没有讨论罗马与埃隆-马斯克的 SpaceX 公司就可能提供 Starlink 服务一事进行的会谈。【原文：Italian Prime Minister Georgia Meloni did not discuss Rome's talks with Elon Musk's SpaceX over the possible supply of its Starlink services during her weekend visit to the United States, the PM's office said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/italys-talks-with-spacex-not-topic-meloni-trump-meeting-pm-office-says-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAH3WFO5HZNL3PKFHHD24YHK2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在冬季风暴后取消 1,300 多个航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一场冬季风暴给美国广大地区带来了冰雪和严寒，美国航空公司取消了 1300 多个航班。【原文：Airlines in the United States canceled more than 1,300 flights on Monday after a winter storm brought snow, ice and freezing temperatures to a broad swath of the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-cancel-over-1300-flights-after-winter-storm-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2HEWCAEYNJU5NV4BMCUL7GYEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国交易所要求大型基金经理限制股票抛售]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士称，中国的主要证券交易所要求一些大型共同基金在今年年初限制股票抛售，因为中国政府正试图在世界第二大经济体进入困难时期之际安抚市场。【原文：China's main stock exchanges asked some large mutual funds to restrict stock selling at the start of the year, three sources familiar with the matter said, as authorities sought to calm markets heading into a tricky period for the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-exchanges-ask-big-fund-managers-restrict-stock-selling-sources-say-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYANKZA3OBM5BHXFJ6JOH5YLYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 08:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：加元平静，特鲁多走向出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LC6QE32U4JOGTOT4O4OBCKGHOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国争相支撑下滑的人民币和股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，中国的证券交易所和中央银行慌忙为暴跌的人民币和下跌的股市辩护，试图安抚对唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫和中国政府重振经济的能力感到担忧的投资者。【原文：China's stock exchanges and central bank scurried to defend a tumbling yuan and falling stock markets on Monday, trying to soothe investors concerned about Donald Trump's return to the White House and Beijing's ability to revive the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-scrambles-shore-up-sliding-yuan-stock-markets-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2IKPHPMUZMGLAL2Q4TUYNICPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街银行退出气候组织令倡导者担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周，美国的贷款机构急于退出全球银行业顶级气候联盟之一，这招致了运动人士的嘲讽，他们担心该行业正在失去对化石燃料采取行动的决心。【原文：U.S. lenders have been rushing in recent weeks to leave one of the world's top banking sector climate coalitions, drawing scorn from campaigners who worry the industry is losing resolve to take action on fossil fuels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/exodus-by-wall-street-banks-climate-group-worries-advocates-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6ICLM4U6BIT7IRTSBU7CLIHJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 要求富士软对贝恩 "违反 NDA "申请禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权基金 KKR 周一表示，已致函富士软公司，要求其向法院提起诉讼，以制止贝恩资本在贝恩和 KKR 争夺这家软件制造商的过程中违反保密协议的行为。【原文：U.S. private equity fund KKR said on Monday it sent a letter to Fuji Soft asking it to make a court filing to stop what it said was Bain Capital's violation of a non-disclosure agreement amid Bain and KKR's acquisition battle for the software maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-asks-fuji-soft-file-injunction-against-bains-breach-nda-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5JFS2Y5ZVKHTMUYCQHCWBLGXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:46:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡数据中心公司 Digital Edge 融资逾 16 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于新加坡的数据中心公司 Digital Edge 周一表示，该公司已通过股权和债务融资相结合的方式筹集了超过 16 亿美元的新资金，为下一阶段的发展提供资金。【原文：Singapore-headquartered data centre company Digital Edge said on Monday it had raised over $1.6 billion in new capital via a combination of equity and debt financing to fund its next phase of growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/singaporean-data-centre-company-digital-edge-raises-over-16-billion-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56X3RJUAJVKRFD67NIAXH7DRTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国吉利控股公司的目标是到 2027 年年销量超过 500 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国吉利控股集团（GEELY.UL）周日表示，该公司的目标是到2027年汽车年销量超过500万辆，比2023年有大幅提升。【原文：China's Geely Holding Group (GEELY.UL) on Sunday said it aims to sell more than 5 million vehicles annually by 2027, a big jump from 2023, which it hopes to achieve by accelerating consolidation of its sprawling brands and improving efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-geely-holding-targets-over-5-million-units-annual-sales-by-2027-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZXJEP7LBFOOBNQ6FCVO3HT5DM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新服务业采购经理人指数显示，中国服务业活动创 7 个月新高，但美国贸易担忧削弱了乐观情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项私营部门调查显示，受国内需求激增的推动，中国服务业活动在12月份以七个月来最快的速度扩张，但来自国外的订单却出现下降，这反映出经济面临的贸易风险正在增加。【原文：China's services activity expanded at the fastest pace in seven months in December, driven by a surge in domestic demand, but orders from abroad declined, reflecting growing trade risks to the economy, a private sector survey showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-services-activity-hits-7-month-high-us-trade-fears-dent-optimism-caixin-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F56KNVEFVZPVBFAZSJUO6RTJ54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:54:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受寒冷天气和中国刺激政策影响，石油价格徘徊于 10 月以来最高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者关注北半球寒冷天气和中国政府经济刺激措施对全球燃料需求的影响，周一油价徘徊在10月份以来的最高点。【原文：Oil prices hovered at their highest since October on Monday as investors eyed the impact on global fuel demand from colder weather in the Northern Hemisphere and Beijing's economic stimulus measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-hovers-highest-since-oct-cold-weather-china-stimulus-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I36AHCC2Q5PQVKC3YTPKP6NT3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国 LG CNS 启动首次公开募股（IPO），募集资金高达 8.17 亿美元，条款表显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的一份条款书显示，韩国 IT 服务提供商 LG CNS 周一开始簿记建档，计划在首次公开募股（IPO）中融资最多 8.17 亿美元。【原文：South Korean IT services provider LG CNS started bookbuilding on Monday to raise up to $817 million in an initial public offering (IPO), according to a term sheet reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/south-koreas-lg-cns-launches-ipo-up-817-mln-term-sheet-says-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FO63AMISGBI7ZOJJF47F3L64R4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元维持在两年高点附近；人民币受到威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美元离两年高点不远，交易员们在等待本周发布的一系列美国经济数据，其中最重要的是 12 月份的非农就业报告，以寻找有关美联储利率前景的进一步线索。【原文：The dollar strayed not too far from a two-year peak on Monday as traders awaited a raft of U.S. economic data releases this week, headlined by December's nonfarm payrolls report, for further clues on the Federal Reserve's rate outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-holds-near-two-year-high-yuan-under-threat-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USFEPR25DVOZJPNWWMQP7GFYHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本服务业活动因需求稳健而扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项私营部门调查显示，受需求稳健和业务扩张的推动，日本服务业活动在 12 月份连续第二个月出现扩张。【原文：Japan's service activity expanded for a second straight month in December, buoyed by solid demand and business expansion, a private-sector survey showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-service-activity-expands-solid-demand-pmi-shows-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYMF22MPUJKRTG6AOOBLDSD6PA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市谨慎，美元在大量数据公布前上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市开局谨慎，因为本周将有大量经济新闻发布，这些新闻应会凸显美国股市的相对优异表现，并支持美元继续走牛。【原文：Asian share markets got off to a wary start on Monday ahead of a week brimming with economic news that should underline the relative outperformance of the United States and support the dollar's ongoing bull run.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNQIWSKVDJITJDHM6NHBMYVUI4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 NTV 报道，新日铁总裁称起诉美国政府是一种选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[据日本电视台周一报道，在美国总统拜登（Joe Biden）阻止新日铁收购美国钢铁公司的提议后，新日铁总裁今井忠志（Tadashi Imai）表示，对美国政府提起诉讼是 "重要选择之一"。【原文：Nippon Steel President Tadashi Imai said filing a lawsuit against the U.S. government is one of the "important options", Nippon Television reported on Monday, after President Joe Biden blocked its proposed purchase of U.S. Steel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steel-president-says-suing-us-government-is-an-option-ntv-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAGMKGLSZBOW5KTF4LP66MG5AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标中国两年期收益率有望跌破 1.00]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HI7LQXM47ZKMLDOK3ZPNXQKYPQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Insignia 公司获得 CC Capital 18 亿美元的出价，超过贝恩的出价]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，Insignia Financial 公布了美国投资管理公司 CC Capital Partners 提出的 28.7 亿澳元（17.8 亿美元）收购要约，超过了贝恩资本提出的 26.7 亿澳元收购要约，股价创下三年新高。【原文：Insignia Financial shares shot to a three-year high on Monday after it revealed a A$2.87 billion ($1.78 billion) takeover bid from U.S.-based investment manager CC Capital Partners, eclipsing a A$2.67 billion offer from Bain Capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/australias-insignia-financial-receives-18-billion-takeover-offer-cc-capital-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3C4ZVFGC6JMMZINEIWNBV4K5QY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:46:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，意大利正在就价值 15 亿美元的 SpaceX 安全服务交易进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周日报道，意大利正与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX 公司就该公司向政府提供安全电信服务的 15 亿欧元（15.5 亿美元）交易进行深入谈判。【原文：Italy is in advanced talks with Elon Musk's SpaceX over a 1.5 billion euro ($1.55 billion) deal for the company to provide secure telecommunications to the government, Bloomberg News reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italy-plans-15-bln-spacex-telecom-security-services-deal-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUWV44HQJBLOPKXUAPS3U6E7MM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 19:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件指控：竞争对手首席执行官向华尔街散布对新日铁交易前景的疑虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在新日铁公司面临拜登政府对其 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司这一注定失败的出价的怀疑时，它还面临着来自一个不可能的来源的阻力：该公司竞争对手的首席执行官一再向投资者对该交易的前景表示怀疑。【原文：Even as Nippon Steel faced skepticism of its doomed $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel from the Biden administration, it was also contending with headwinds from an unlikely source: the CEO of a rival bidder for the firm who repeatedly cast doubt on the deal's prospects to investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/rival-ceo-spread-doubt-about-nippon-steel-deal-prospects-wall-street-documents-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHOR4NXNIBJVXOSL7RK7RKVWWY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 19:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>