<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:39:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:39:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧元区采购经理人指数（PMI）显示：需求跃升，欧元区商业活动加速增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，欧元区 10 月份的商业活动出乎意料地加快了增长速度，企业获得新订单的速度为两年半以来最快，这表明该集团的经济在最后一个季度开始时获得了增长势头。【原文：Euro zone business activity unexpectedly grew at a faster pace in October as companies received new orders at the quickest rate in two-and-a-half years, suggesting the bloc's economy gained momentum at the start of the final quarter, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/euro-zone-business-activity-growth-accelerates-demand-jumps-pmi-shows-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFUVS35DC5O6VI47NDVULWUGSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 08:07:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 10 月份商业活动激增，创两年多新高，PMI 显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，受服务业活动强劲增长的推动，德国私营部门在 10 月份录得近两年半以来最强劲的增长。【原文：Germany's private sector recorded its strongest growth in nearly two-and-a-half years in October, buoyed by a robust rise in services activity, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/german-business-activity-surges-two-year-plus-high-october-pmi-shows-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7VLH477ANKBRHTOG2REIULNME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:33:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希腊指定雪佛龙和 Helleniq Energy 财团为海上天然气勘探的首选投标人]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊能源部周五表示，希腊已指定美国石油巨头雪佛龙（Chevron）和希腊最大的炼油厂 Helleniq Energy 组成的财团为南部近海区块天然气勘探的优先竞标者。【原文：Greece has named a consortium of U.S. oil major Chevron and Helleniq Energy, the country's biggest oil refiner, as preferred bidder for gas exploration in southern offshore blocks, the Greek energy ministry said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/greece-names-chevron-helleniq-energy-consortium-preferred-bidder-offshore-gas-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBE4NTUQBBOETFDYHI5EP45YLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金价格飙升，黄金基金创下单周资金流入纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行全球研究部（Bank of America Global Research）在一份援引 EPFR 数据的报告中称，截至本周三的一周内，黄金基金获得了有史以来最大的单周资金流入。【原文：Gold funds received their largest weekly inflow on record in the week to Wednesday, Bank of America Global Research said in a note citing EPFR data, a week in which the precious metal's price surged to a new record, before retreating sharply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-flows-bofa-urgent-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LN2VUX5CHVPXRFFG6H7X63O4N4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国需求疲软打击专业照明部门，Signify下调销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国商业和公共部门客户需求下降的影响，全球最大的灯具制造商 Signify 周五公布的第三季度销售额下降 8.4%，降幅超过预期，并下调了全年业绩指引。【原文：Signify , the world's biggest lights maker, reported a steeper than expected 8.4% drop in third-quarter sales and lowered its full-year guidance on Friday, hit by falling demand from commercial and public sector clients in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/signify-dims-sales-forecast-soft-us-demand-hits-professional-lighting-unit-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3EUHQODFVNENC2RFWCKNLKMSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲应对中国进口激增的压力与日俱增]]></title><description><![CDATA[二战结束后，一家位于德国汉堡北部小镇的百年轮胎翻新公司为英国占领区的卡车提供轮胎翻新服务。现在，它要与另一种新来者打交道：来自中国的大打折扣的轮胎。【原文：A century-old tyre retreading firm based in a small town north of Hamburg in Germany kept British occupation trucks rolling after World War Two. Now it deals with newcomers of a different kind: heavily discounted tyres from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/pressure-grows-europe-act-chinese-import-surge-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPYSM7D4GBIFXGODTANNMIB3PY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:35:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士总统对美国在 2025 年达成关税协议的前景持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士总统卡琳-凯勒-萨特（Karin Keller-Sutter）拒绝透露瑞士是否可能在今年与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普就关税问题达成协议。【原文：Swiss President Karin Keller-Sutter declined to say whether her country could this year strike a deal on tariffs with U.S. President Donald Trump, following trade tensions that have strained relations between the two nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/swiss-president-strikes-cautious-note-prospects-us-tariff-deal-2025-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTFY4OSH4VLKRLCOUCAWCH2BEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳新银行前首席执行官称银行解雇交易员是合理的]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳新银行集团前首席执行官谢恩-埃利奥特（Shayne Elliott）周五表示，该行解雇一名被控违反澳新银行行为准则、在工作中发送不当信息的前交易员是合理的。【原文：Former Australia and New Zealand Banking Group Chief Executive Shayne Elliott said on Friday the bank was justified in sacking a former trader accused of breaking ANZ's code of conduct by sending inappropriate messages at work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/anzs-former-ceo-says-bank-was-justified-sacking-trader-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGABUAFI2FIIXLNLQC5QJBW6NA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:25:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔第三季度利润超预期，股价上涨近 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，英特尔股价在法兰克福上涨近 10%，此前一天，该公司第三季度利润超出预期，得益于大幅削减成本措施。【原文：Intel shares rose nearly 10% in Frankfurt on Friday, a day after the company beat expectations for its third quarter profit helped by dramatic cost cutting measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-shares-up-nearly-10-after-third-quarter-profit-beat-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4NQUJTWBRO7LLAQKGAKA4DFXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 06:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国小米称存储芯片价格飙升推高智能手机成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国智能手机制造商小米周五表示，存储芯片价格飙升提高了手机制造成本，此前其新产品红米 K90 系列的定价引起了市场的失望。【原文：Chinese smartphone manufacturer Xiaomi on Friday said surging memory chip prices have raised the cost of making handsets, after pricing of its new Redmi K90 series drew market disappointment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinas-xiaomi-says-surging-memory-chip-prices-push-up-smartphone-costs-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D45F7EACZVKP7JGZE55RZPMHN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 05:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛峰集团第三季度喷气发动机服务业绩强劲，上调业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国航空航天集团赛峰集团周五上调了全年业绩预期，因为在核心喷气发动机部门的带动下，该集团第三季度收入高于预期。【原文：French aerospace group Safran raised full-year forecasts on Friday as it posted higher-than-expected third-quarter revenues, led by its core jet engine division.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/safran-hikes-forecasts-after-strong-q3-jet-engine-services-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKHZ4UTAHBMGXAUNJLQWCCZMFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 05:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷新任首席执行官将继承老问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[保时捷即将离任的首席执行官奥利弗-布卢姆（Oliver Blume）在结束其长达十年的任期之前，将于本周五提交一份季度报告。这份报告并不好看。【原文：Porsche's outgoing CEO Oliver Blume has one more quarterly report to deliver on Friday before his decade-long tenure comes to an end. It won't make for pretty reading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/porsches-new-ceo-will-inherit-old-problems-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARXAHEBLGZMWJCKDIEMTC5WPYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 05:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者利用互联网时代的游戏规则规避人工智能泡沫风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[主要投资者被人工智能的蓬勃发展所吓倒，但又害怕与之对赌，他们正在从被炒作的股票转向潜在的下一个赢家，重拾 20 世纪 90 年代网络时代的策略，这一策略曾帮助一些投资者躲过了股灾。【原文：Major investors, spooked by AI exuberance yet wary of betting against it, are shifting from hyped-up stocks into potential next-in-line winners, reviving a strategy from the 1990s dotcom era that helped some sidestep the crash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/investors-use-dotcom-era-playbook-dodge-ai-bubble-risks-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGTCDHL3RJOADMYAQ6EBN6ZH64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 05:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标在亚太经合组织旋风来临之前关注 CPI]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L56U3RQJ7JJKBGB6JTFZWSBR64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 04:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[9月份美国消费者物价在关税影响下可能继续上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于家庭为一些对关税敏感的商品支付了更多的费用，9月份美国消费者价格可能连续第二个月稳健上涨，但预计通胀走强不会阻止美联储下周再次降息。【原文：U.S. consumer prices likely rose solidly for a second straight month in September as households paid more for some tariff-sensitive goods, but firmer inflation was not expected to stop the Federal Reserve from cutting interest rates again next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-prices-likely-remained-higher-september-amid-tariff-pass-through-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJYUNXIYHFPUXBHWGGJ66CJ4DM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 04:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 关联公司收购印度联邦银行 9.99% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度联邦银行周五表示，美国私募股权投资巨头 Blackstone 的一家附属公司已通过优先股和认股权证以 619.7 亿卢比（7.0505 亿美元）的价格收购了印度联邦银行 9.99% 的股份。【原文：An affiliate of U.S. private equity major Blackstone has bought a 9.99% stake in India's Federal Bank via preferential equity shares and warrants for 61.97 billion rupees ($705.05 million), the Indian lender said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/blackstone-affiliate-buys-999-stake-indias-federal-bank-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEXJCF5LPVLTHPYEA75JEPCBSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西卡九个月销售额下降，计划裁员多达1500人]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士工业和建筑化学品生产商西卡周五公布了九个月销售额下降的报告，并表示将对持续疲软的市场进行结构性调整，包括裁员1500人。【原文：Swiss industrial and construction chemicals maker Sika reported a drop in nine-month sales on Friday and said it would implement structural changes in its persistently weak markets, including cutting up to 1,500 jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sika-posts-lower-9-month-sales-plans-up-1500-job-cuts-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7G54KBH55KYHHQJZZQ2C25WRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美官员在马来西亚就出口管制和特朗普关税威胁展开对峙]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国的高级经济官员将于周五抵达吉隆坡举行会谈，以防止贸易战升级，并使美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和中国国家主席习近平下周的会晤按计划进行。【原文：Top economic officials from the U.S. and China are due to arrive in Kuala Lumpur on Friday for talks to prevent a trade war escalation and keep next week's meeting between U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping on track.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-chinese-officials-face-off-export-controls-trump-tariff-threat-malaysia-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5NINWA3YJOLNK2SHCUGC6P3NQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称终止与加拿大的所有贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，在他所谓的前总统罗纳德-里根（Ronald Reagan）对关税发表负面言论的欺诈性广告之后，与加拿大的所有贸易谈判均已终止。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday that all trade talks with Canada were terminated following what he called a fraudulent advertisement in which former President Ronald Reagan spoke negatively about tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-all-trade-talks-with-canada-are-terminated-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HUABPHJVRKIZOJZ7VOGJ3MCYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:50:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市因中美贸易希望而上涨；石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于华尔街财报和中美关系解冻的迹象提振了投资者情绪，周五亚洲股市反弹，而油价则在美国对俄罗斯供应商实施新制裁后有所回落。【原文：Asian shares rallied on Friday as Wall Street earnings and signs of a thaw in U.S.-China relations boosted investor sentiment, while oil prices eased following fresh U.S. sanctions on Russian suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PO52PHGQINKOXBCU27DGRAUI4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:28:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）称，弱势美元的逆转可能考验亚洲抵御关税的能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织一位高级官员告诉路透社记者，如果美元反弹和低利率反弹导致金融条件收紧，亚洲抵御美国关税的能力可能会受到挑战。【原文：Asia may see its resilience to U.S. tariffs challenged if a rally in the dollar and a rebound in low interest rates lead to tighter financial conditions, a senior International Monetary Fund official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/reversal-weak-dollar-may-test-asias-resilience-tariffs-imf-says-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZIO3KRCXVJRZJCYL7YAF2J4J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织敦促亚洲削减贸易壁垒以抵御美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五敦促亚洲降低非关税壁垒，实现区域贸易一体化，以降低亚洲在美国关税和全球金融冲击面前的脆弱性。【原文：The International Monetary Fund on Friday urged Asia to lower non-tariff barriers and integrate regional trade to reduce its vulnerability to U.S. tariffs and global financial shocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/imf-urges-asia-cut-trade-barriers-beat-us-tariffs-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37IIW5W32JKL3ALHLJMXSGP7WE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员为美国通胀数据做准备，美元保持平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五持稳，兑主要对手的美元汇率有望在本周小幅上扬，因为投资者正在为延迟公布的通胀数据做准备，而这些数据不太可能阻止美联储下周降息。【原文：The U.S. dollar was steady on Friday, poised to eke out a small weekly gain against major rivals as investors braced for delayed inflation data that is unlikely to deter the Federal Reserve from lowering interest rates next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-calm-traders-brace-us-inflation-data-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APKARKYNRZKWRJ6L6FIB6WNPKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:38:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本百年企业藤仓借人工智能数据中心热潮成为日经一枝独秀]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本藤仓公司（Fujikura）在日经指数（Nikkei）红火的股价指数中一枝独秀，因为人们预期这家拥有百年历史的电线制造商将受益于使用其光纤的人工智能数据中心投资的增加。【原文：Japan's Fujikura has become a standout in the red-hot Nikkei share gauge on expectations the century-old wire maker will benefit from increased investment in artificial intelligence data centres that use its optical fibres.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-century-old-fujikura-rides-ai-data-centre-boom-become-nikkei-standout-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEE7AGHOIVNMZJCPEDLZ4ENE2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价大涨后回落，在供应担忧下仍有望实现周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国因乌克兰战争对俄罗斯最大的两家石油公司实施了新的制裁，加剧了市场对供应的担忧，周五早盘油价下跌，缩减了前一天的部分涨幅，但仍有望实现周线上涨。【原文：Oil prices dipped in early trade on Friday, trimming part of the previous day's surge but remaining on track for a weekly gain, as fresh U.S. sanctions on Russia's two biggest oil companies over the war in Ukraine fuelled supply concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-dip-after-surge-remain-track-weekly-gain-amid-supply-fears-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMVWJYMGOFIFNCMT3KUAVSANNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国第三季度经济温和增长，出口和消费保持弹性：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，在强劲的出口和家庭消费回升的支撑下，韩国经济在上个季度实现了小幅增长。【原文：South Korea's economy grew at a modest pace last quarter, supported by strong exports and a pickup in household consumption as government measures helped stimulate demand, a Reuters poll suggested.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-koreas-economy-grew-modestly-q3-exports-consumption-stay-resilient-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5AMATVQ5ZMLPLBNZO4NDYONDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 10 月份工厂活动创 19 个月新低（PMI]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五进行的一项私营部门调查显示，由于新订单大幅减少，日本制造业在10月份出现了19个月来最快的萎缩。【原文：Japan's manufacturing sector contracted in October at the fastest pace in 19 months due to a sharper decline in new orders, a private-sector survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-factory-activity-hits-19-month-low-october-pmi-shows-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U6VQ6BUW5MQ7PZ7U2P3KROAOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:34:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，作家协会计划反对派拉蒙与华纳兄弟合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引美国作家协会的一份电子邮件声明报道，代表编剧和新闻编辑的美国作家协会表示，将反对派拉蒙天舞公司与华纳兄弟发现公司的合并交易。【原文：The Writers Guild of America, which represents screenwriters and newsroom staffers, said it will oppose a deal combining Paramount Skydance and Warner Bros Discovery , Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing an emailed statement from the guild.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/writers-guild-plans-oppose-paramount-warner-bros-merger-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRUQDPLROVLMVIGE5QISGT3PIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司因燃料成本增加而下调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空集团（Alaska Air Group）周四下调了 2025 年的利润预期，原因是较高的燃料成本和包括恶劣天气在内的运营挑战影响了其利润率。【原文：Alaska Air Group lowered its 2025 profit forecast on Thursday as higher fuel costs and operational challenges, including adverse weather, weighed on its margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/alaska-air-cuts-annual-profit-forecast-higher-fuel-costs-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANQTKRY7YFJMZATNCCUALJOUQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 9 月核心通胀加速，保持在日本央行目标之上]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的数据显示，日本9月份核心消费者物价同比上涨2.9%，继续高于央行2%的目标，并保持了市场对近期加息的预期。【原文：Japan's core consumer prices rose 2.9% year-on-year in September, data showed on Friday, staying above the central bank's 2% target and keeping alive market expectations of a near-term interest rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-core-inflation-accelerates-september-stays-above-boj-target-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQ2ZMK3S3ZNHVGSQIKT6SLWBJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:47:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>