<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:19:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:19:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Tether称因涉犯罪活动冻结42亿美元稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于萨尔瓦多的稳定币发行商泰达币（Tether）表示，已冻结约42亿美元的加密货币代币，因其与"非法活动"有关联，这些活动主要发生在过去三年间。全球各地当局正努力打击加密货币相关的犯罪行为。【原文：El Salvador-based stablecoin issuer Tether said it has frozen about $4.2 billion of its crypto tokens over links to "illicit activity", mostly in the past three years, as authorities around the world try to crack down on crypto-related crime.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tether-says-it-has-frozen-42-billion-its-stablecoin-over-crime-links-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJI3MD7KONP6LGDD26DAPH5HMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞标：人工智能恐怖故事]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克·多兰和ROI团队本周末最期待阅读、观看和收听的内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPPEYVLDR5KVVFEQDXWOT2J4LA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货因人工智能担忧而走低，纳斯达克指数准备迎接大幅月度下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五下跌，因人工智能领域日益加剧的担忧拖累科技股，纳斯达克指数面临2025年3月以来最大月度跌幅，投资者正等待当日晚些时候公布的关键通胀数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slid on Friday as growing AI unease weighed on technology stocks, with the Nasdaq staring at its steepest monthly drop since March 2025, and investors awaited key inflation data later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-falter-ai-jitters-nasdaq-braces-steep-monthly-fall-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74PQCZJXFVJADDDNNPZH4FT63U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:43:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthpeak Properties旗下Janus Living公开提交美国IPO申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产投资信托公司Janus Living周五正式提交美国IPO申请文件，众多企业发行方正争相抢占三月上市窗口期。【原文：Real estate investment trust Janus Living publicly filed paperwork for a U.S. IPO on Friday, as corporate issuers line up to tap the March window.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthpeak-properties-janus-living-makes-us-ipo-filing-public-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQ734WN2B5MG7OH2GZBZSZ73O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师上调油价预期，因地缘政治风险；供应过剩担忧限制上涨空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[持续的地缘政治紧张局势引发的供应风险，促使分析师上调了今年的油价预测，尽管市场担忧供应过剩将持续对油价构成压力。【原文：Supply risks from ongoing geopolitical tensions have prompted analysts to raise their oil price forecasts for the year, despite concerns that an oversupply will continue to weigh on the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/analysts-hike-oil-outlook-geopolitical-risks-oversupply-concerns-limit-upside-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRXJLGH76RO4VG5EAW7NIN24SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通获利了结人民币升值行情]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通分析师表示，随着中国央行周五下调美元远期合约购买成本以抑制人民币近期升值势头，他们将平仓离岸人民币多头头寸。【原文：JPMorgan's analysts said they were closing their long offshore Chinese yuan position after the country's central bank cut the cost of buying dollar forwards on Friday in a bid to tame the yuan's recent rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-takes-profit-chinese-yuan-rally-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLC6ZVVMABJRBPD6IML723K3GI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据Axios报道，目标公司计划从谷物食品中去除人工色素]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Axios周五报道，塔吉特百货要求其销售的所有谷物产品必须在五月底前停止使用经认证的合成色素。【原文：Target will require every cereal it sells to be made without certified synthetic colors by the end of May, Axios reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/target-drop-synthetic-colors-cereals-axios-reports-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4DEA44LIBJPFM24ORUSG42FHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望：人工智能颠覆阴云笼罩市场，美国就业数据即将公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能颠覆各行业的前景，将在未来一周持续令美国股市保持紧张状态，华尔街正寻求更多洞见，以了解这项新兴技术将如何在经济领域引发连锁反应。【原文：Prospects for artificial intelligence to disrupt business sectors should keep the U.S. stock market on edge in the coming week, as Wall Street looks for more insight into how the emerging technology will reverberate through the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-ai-disruption-looms-over-markets-with-us-jobs-data-tap-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGK22SK7EZJXPCJQPL7S7D6IOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼人类学纷争：周五最后期限临近，销售额与人工智能战争悬而未决]]></title><description><![CDATA[五角大楼与顶尖人工智能实验室Anthropic之间的激烈争端即将达到顶点，争议焦点在于军方如何在战争中运用人工智能。【原文：An explosive feud between the Pentagon and top artificial intelligence lab Anthropic is set to come to a head over concerns about how the military could use AI at war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/pentagon-anthropic-feud-has-sales-ai-warfare-stake-friday-deadline-looms-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKFAA7NCXNKGZNKTAWZL5IPXK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着消费者寻求享受美食，餐饮业成为美国就业增长的亮点]]></title><description><![CDATA[纸面上看，美国消费者去年都在勒紧裤腰带，就连零售业巨头也步履维艰。但堂食餐厅和部分得来速连锁店却门庭若市，顾客们或为享受特别款待，或为品尝平价慰藉美食而纷至沓来。【原文：On paper, American consumers spent last year tightening their belts, and even retail heavyweights stumbled. But sit-down restaurants and some drive-through chains buzzed with patrons seeking a special treat or cheap comfort food.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/restaurants-emerge-bright-spot-us-job-growth-consumers-seek-treats-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIZX2AQCTBPAXN4VOCZ7COPJ7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[跳舞机器人为巴塞罗那老年人提供陪伴与支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴塞罗那居民艾琳·维格利森已有二十多年未曾跳舞，直到三个月前，一台机器人搬进了她的家。【原文：Barcelona resident Irene Veglison had not danced for more than two decades until a robot moved into her home three months ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/dancing-robots-bring-support-company-barcelona-elderly-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPSGUK6AQVOVZBKVOOES6UXLAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:49:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴斯夫正就其美国子公司提出的关税退还法律索赔展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴斯夫首席执行官表示，若该化工集团发现其美国子公司具备法律诉求，将在美国最高法院推翻特朗普总统多项关税措施后，就进口关税补偿问题提起诉讼。【原文：BASF's CEO said if the chemical group finds its U.S. subsidiary has a legal claim, it will sue for import tariff reimbursement after the U.S. Supreme Court quashed many of President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/basf-is-looking-into-legal-claims-by-us-unit-tariff-reimbursement-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSEKY6A7XJON5DODGTC5OZ375A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:42:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟收购战尘埃落定，奈飞、派拉蒙股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五盘前交易时段，奈飞股价飙升逾9%，投资者对其退出华纳兄弟探索公司收购战的决定表示欢迎；与此同时，派拉蒙股价上涨约10%，因其在争夺全球最珍贵影视资产的竞争中胜出。【原文：Netflix jumped more than 9% premarket on Friday as investors cheered its decision to exit the fight for Warner Bros Discovery, while Paramount rose about 10% on winning the race for some of the world's most prized TV and film assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/netflix-paramount-shares-jump-months-long-fight-warner-bros-ends-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQTPY7ACHVLR3OTU2WBTD23VT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚赌场运营商星娱乐集团上半年亏损收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚星娱乐集团周五公布，2026财年上半年亏损幅度有所收窄，得益于第二季度交易量在季节性因素推动下实现增长。【原文：Australia's Star Entertainment Group reported a smaller loss for the first half on Friday, supported by seasonally stronger trading volumes for the second quarter of fiscal 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-star-entertainment-narrows-first-half-loss-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJLERMLJQNKMZHCFRWMRX2PPRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解读：中国能采取哪些措施来抑制人民币升值？]]></title><description><![CDATA[人民币兑美元汇率正大幅升值，这得益于出口的强劲增长，同时美国利率下降和美元走软也助推了这一趋势。【原文：China's yuan is surging against the U.S. dollar, boosted by booming exports and aided by falling U.S. interest rates and the wobbly greenback.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/what-can-china-do-slow-down-its-rising-currency-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EF7WGNHH45N7LERNOOCYEFYZ6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瓦锡兰首席执行官寄望特朗普数据中心计划提振业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[芬兰能源公司瓦锡兰首席执行官向路透社表示，美国数据中心推动自建供电设施的举措将提振对该公司环保产品的需求，并助力未来两年服务人员招聘实现"两位数"百分比增长。【原文：A push for U.S. datacentres to use their own power will boost demand for Wartsila's more environmentally friendly products and help underpin a "double-digit" percentage increase in hiring of servicing staff over the next two years, the Finnish energy company's CEO told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/wartsila-ceo-eyes-boost-trump-datacenter-push-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NH56KCCPGRIF7D35JLKTM5BM4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Insta360制造商称将在美国国际贸易委员会裁决后"不受限制"地进口和销售产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于深圳的Arashi Vision公司（旗下拥有Insta360系列相机产品）周五表示，在美国际贸易委员会作出最终裁决后，该公司"将继续不受限制地向美国进口和销售现有产品"。【原文：Shenzhen-based Arashi Vision , which makes the Insta360 line of camera products, on Friday said it "will continue to import and sell existing products in the U.S. without restrictions" after a final ruling by USITC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/insta360-maker-says-it-will-import-sell-products-us-without-restrictions-after-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCOQYATJYBJUJLUWPRWOUBKHQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:41:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[European shares set for eighth straight month of gains, buoyed by earnings]]></title><description><![CDATA[European shares were steady on Friday and were set to log an eighth straight month of gains as better-than-expected corporate updates supported risk appetite despite lingering tariff and AI-disruption concerns.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-shares-set-eighth-straight-month-gains-buoyed-by-earnings-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTM5A7H63VMQ3K7G25PQXHWTHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CPP, Equinix to buy Nordic data center operator atNorth in $4 billion deal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canada Pension Plan Investment Board and Equinix have agreed to acquire Nordic data center operator atNorth from private equity firm Partners Group in a deal valued at about $4 billion, the companies said in a joint statement on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/cpp-equinix-buy-nordic-data-center-operator-atnorth-4-billion-deal-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7QMIWDE65ISXFIFJ4WM2AEMBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[起亚美国因座椅靠背框架问题召回约8.5万辆美国车辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kia America is recalling 85,448 vehicles in the U.S. over failure of a seat back frame failing to properly restrain an occupant during a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kia-america-recall-about-85000-us-vehicles-over-seat-back-frame-issue-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA4TUCHW55KKHKSMICRNKRSAXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度贸易部长表示，印度致力于与美国达成最优贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度贸易部长周五表示，印度希望与美国达成最有利的贸易协议，以确保在竞争中占据优势。此前，由于特朗普总统的关税政策被裁定无效，华盛顿敲定的协议命运仍不明朗。【原文：India wants to secure the best trade deal with the U.S. to ensure it has an edge over competitors, India's trade minister said on Friday, as the fate of deals finalised by Washington remain uncertain after President Donald Trump's tariffs were invalidated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-focused-getting-best-trade-deal-with-us-indian-trade-minister-says-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYC2ZUQYWVIBXMUVK2E2LRKYXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:19:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Poland plans social-media ban for children under 15, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰计划出台新法规，禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体，并将要求平台承担年龄核查责任。教育部长芭芭拉·诺瓦茨卡周五接受彭博新闻社采访时透露了这一消息。【原文：Poland plans to introduce new legislation to ban social media for children under 15 years of age and will hold platforms responsible for age verification, Education Minister Barbara Nowacka told Bloomberg News in an interview published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/poland-plans-social-media-ban-children-under-15-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3X7WNILBXNL3XFUPL642QGFMT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间要闻：人工智能困境与"公开战争"]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗基·斯威夫特带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGJ3VD2YNVJ3DG43DEOKDYMOVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:39:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯悦首席执行官称，未来五年内计划将印度业务规模扩大五倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯悦酒店集团首席执行官周五表示，未来五年该集团在印度的业务规模预计将扩大五倍。这家美国酒店运营商押注这个全球人口最多国家将迎来国内旅游热潮和消费支出增长。【原文：Hyatt Hotels expects to quintuple its India footprint over the next five years, its chief executive said on Friday, as the U.S. hotel operator bets on a surge in domestic travel and rising consumer spending in the world's most populous nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/hyatt-hotels-eyes-five-fold-expansion-india-over-next-five-years-ceo-says-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YRJ2ZFLJVPSRB4N2XSMZIWJEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:26:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国批准谷歌出口高精度地图数据的申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国周五表示，已批准谷歌将该国高精度地图数据出口至海外服务器的申请。这是二十年来首次批准该请求，标志着重大政策逆转，为这家美国科技巨头进入本土应用主导的市场扫清了障碍。【原文：South Korea said on Friday it had approved Google's request to export the country's high-precision map data to overseas servers, a major reversal after two decades of rejection that clears the way for the U.S. tech giant to enter a market dominated by local apps.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-approves-google-bid-export-high-precision-map-data-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPKKY5DY7RIQRAKIVRLNVZAIZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:09:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI boom will be no free pass for debt-laden major economies]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家表示，人工智能生产力革命若能实现，或许能为主要经济体争取更多时间来整顿其紧张的公共财政，但它无法承担最艰巨的任务。【原文：An AI productivity boom, if it materialises, may help buy major economies more time to clean up their strained public finances, economists say, although it won't do the heavy lifting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ai-boom-will-be-no-free-pass-debt-laden-major-economies-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGIQIMQ7G5PEVCJKUVAC57NY7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NTT数据公司高管称，今年将在印度增聘5000名员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本科技公司NTT Data计划今年在印度增加5000名员工，涉及软件编程、咨询和IT支持等领域，该公司一位高管向路透社透露。【原文：Japanese technology firm NTT Data plans to raise its India headcount by 5,000 employees this year across software programming, consulting and IT support, a senior executive told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/ntt-data-boost-india-headcount-by-5000-this-year-exec-says-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2I7X5QKZFIVXKOJ2PWIAWMY2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称任天堂计划通过京都银行等机构进行约19亿美元的股票发售]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位知情人士透露，任天堂计划逐步减持战略股权，包括三菱日联银行和京都银行在内的多家机构将出售这家"超级马里奥"制造商的股份。【原文：Nintendo plans an unwinding of strategic shareholdings that would see companies including MUFG Bank and the Bank of Kyoto selling shares of the "Super Mario" maker, according to three sources familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/nintendo-plans-around-19-billion-share-sale-by-kyoto-bank-others-sources-say-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBYTDCNRL5JGNNUTDUU3AHPCX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车集团将在韩国投资63亿美元建设人工智能数据中心和机器人工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国国土交通部周五表示，现代汽车集团与韩国政府签署协议，将在韩国西部沿海地区投资约9万亿韩元（62.6亿美元）建设人工智能数据中心、机器人制造工厂等项目。【原文：Hyundai Motor Group and South Korea on Friday signed a deal to invest about 9 trillion won ($6.26 billion) to build an AI data centre, a robot manufacturing factory and other developments in the country's western coastal region, the land ministry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-group-invest-63-bln-ai-data-centre-robot-factory-south-korea-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GMSGYRQFVK2JGT6BLBWHWIXEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚Appen公司表示，作为人工智能领域的"瑞士"，其人工测试需求正持续增长。]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚Appen公司是人工智能系统人工评估服务的主要供应商，该公司表示，日益高涨的技术保护主义将推动中美两国对其服务的采购需求——这些服务通过真人参与来训练和测试模型。【原文：Australia's Appen , a big supplier of human assessment of artificial intelligence systems, said rising technology protectionism would boost demand in the United States and China for its services that use real people to train and test models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-appen-says-being-switzerland-ai-boosts-demand-its-human-testing-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKM2L5OVGBPK5NHH4MPE274QAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>