<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:05:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:05:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[路透社/益普索民意调查显示，大多数美国人反对特朗普寻求的国内支出冻结措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社/益普索周二公布的最新民调显示，大多数美国人反对唐纳德-特朗普总统寻求的暂时冻结国内联邦支出，但对削减对外援助的支持率较高。【原文：Most Americans oppose a temporary freeze on domestic federal spending as sought by President Donald Trump, but support is higher for cutting foreign aid, according to a new Reuters/Ipsos poll released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/majority-americans-oppose-domestic-spending-freeze-sought-by-trump-reutersipsos-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7YXGAOIMRJ6FIRRZI2RFXYGH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:52:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果美国实施关税，加拿大跨山公司预计会对管道系统产生更多兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大输油管道运营商跨山公司表示，如果美国在一个月内对加拿大进口石油征收关税，该公司预计对其输油系统的兴趣会增加。【原文：Canadian pipeline operator Trans Mountain said it expects to see increased interest to ship on its system if the United States slaps tariffs on Canadian oil imports in a month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/canadas-trans-mountain-expects-more-interest-pipeline-system-if-us-implements-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YH2GXUG5SFPDNNU3ZAFAU4BHXU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易紧张局势和生物燃料政策为 ADM 2025 年前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球谷物贸易商阿彻-丹尼尔斯-米德兰公司（Archer-Daniels-Midland）周二表示，该公司正在削减成本和裁员，以应对因美国生物燃料政策的不确定性和酝酿中的贸易战而变得更具挑战性的大宗商品低迷。【原文：Global grains trader Archer-Daniels-Midland is slashing costs and cutting staff to weather a commodity downturn made more challenging by uncertainty about U.S. biofuels policies and a brewing trade war, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/adm-2025-outlook-clouded-by-trade-tensions-biofuel-policies-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRSQWWUOLRLTBAQPFMP64ICUCY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克效应？一月份特斯拉在欧洲五个市场的销量下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉 1 月份在包括英国和法国在内的五个欧洲国家的销售额下降，原因是电动汽车制造商的竞争对手们推出了更新的车型，而民意调查显示，公众舆论对首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的看法也在变坏。【原文：Tesla posted lower sales across five European countries in January, including the United Kingdom and France, as competitors with newer models gained on the electric vehicle maker and polls show public opinion souring on CEO Elon Musk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-effect-tesla-sales-slump-five-european-markets-january-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NG6FRMR7GNK53IWRBZA2VOYRNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:40:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[禽流感促使连锁餐厅华夫饼屋（Waffle House）对每个鸡蛋加收 50 美分的费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国连锁餐厅华夫饼屋（Waffle House）周一在其餐厅张贴的一份声明中说，该公司已对顾客点的每一个鸡蛋加收 50 美分的附加费。【原文：U.S. diner chain Waffle House has added a 50-cent surcharge for every egg in a customer’s order, the company said in a statement posted in its restaurants on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bird-flu-spurs-diner-chain-waffle-house-add-50-cent-fee-per-egg-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IALKU7FBPBKJ3GBBCXUTNZT7TM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:13:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，恩西诺公司的所有者正在考虑以 70 亿美元出售能源生产商并进行首次公开募股]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士透露，加拿大养老基金 CPP Investments 正在权衡各种战略选择，包括出售或首次公开募股，对 Encino Acquisition Partners 的估值可能高达 70 亿美元（包括债务）。【原文：Canadian pension fund CPP Investments is weighing strategic options, including a sale or initial public offering, for Encino Acquisition Partners that could value the U.S. oil and natural gas producer at as much as $7 billion, including debt, people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/encinos-owner-mulls-7-billion-sale-ipo-energy-producer-sources-say-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJI4HGCMMFPKBAVNFEIQ3PHYRA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国批准向埃及出售洛克希德和诺斯罗普-格鲁曼系统的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[五角大楼国防安全合作局周二表示，美国国务院已批准向埃及出售洛克希德-马丁公司和诺斯罗普-格鲁曼公司的防御系统。【原文：The U.S. State Department has approved the potential sale of Lockheed Martin and Northrop Grumman Corp's defense systems to Egypt, the Pentagon's Defense Security Cooperation Agency said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-approves-potential-sale-lockheed-northrop-grumman-systems-egypt-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6OT7AIQOBOKBCCAVXO5CWHOKM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国会将成立加密货币工作组]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院金融服务委员会主席、共和党人弗伦奇-希尔（French Hill）周二表示，国会参众两院的立法者将成立一个工作组，制定有利于数字资产发展的政策。【原文：U.S. Representative French Hill, a Republican who chairs the House Financial Services Committee, said on Tuesday lawmakers from both chambers of congress would form a working group to develop policy favoring development of digital assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-congress-form-cryptocurrency-working-group-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NJ7QGPRTJLTHFX2O23PYYXUNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:57:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Third Point 的勒布在信中表示，预计股票投资环境良好]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资人丹尼尔-勒布（Daniel Loeb）打赌，尽管特朗普政府在宣布和颁布新政策时采取了 "非常规 "的做法，但2025年将带来更有利的股票投资环境。【原文：Billionaire investor Daniel Loeb is betting 2025 will bring a more favorable stock investing environment despite the Trump administration's "unconventional" approach to announcing and enacting new policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/third-points-loeb-expects-favorable-stock-investment-environment-letter-says-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KPLAUVLW5N3BES42ALD4RMRL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:38:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，摩根士丹利将增加出售与马斯克 X 有关的贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，以摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）为首的一批银行将增加出售与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体平台 X 有关的贷款，因为投资者的需求强于预期。【原文：A group of Morgan Stanley-led banks is set to increase a sale of loans tied to Elon Musk's social media platform X after receiving stronger-than-expected demand from investors, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-increase-sale-loans-tied-musks-x-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4TPP5YA3ZLMVDXK3Q6NAQV23Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:38:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称高盛将请回技术银行家尼克-乔瓦尼]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周二看到的一份内部备忘录，高盛将重新启用尼克-乔瓦尼（Nick Giovanni），他之前在这家华尔街巨头工作了 20 多年。【原文：Goldman Sachs is bringing back Nick Giovanni, who spent more than 20 years at the Wall Street giant in a prior stint, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-bring-back-technology-banker-nick-giovanni-memo-says-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CKTWOALS3BKSJG3SJD6R37ZJ4M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:20:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音高管称供应商 Spirit Aero 拥有大量 737 机身库存]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司的主要供应商 Spirit AeroSystems 公司的一位高管周二在西雅图举行的一次航空航天会议上说，该公司拥有大量质量大幅提高的 737 机身库存，随时可以发货。【原文：Boeing's key supplier Spirit AeroSystems has a substantial inventory of 737 fuselages of significantly improved quality that are ready to ship, an executive with the planemaker told a Seattle aerospace conference on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-executive-says-supplier-spirit-aero-has-substantial-inventory-737-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZJIH3W5UFJQZDZE5FIEUSZZRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:17:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会代理主席重组该机构的执法部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会（CFTC）代理主席周二表示，该委员会将重组其执法部门的特别工作组，以结束 "执法监管"，转而专注于打击欺诈和帮助受害者。【原文：The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission will reorganize its Division of Enforcement's task forces to end "regulation by enforcement" and instead focus on combating fraud and helping victims, CFTC's acting chairman said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/acting-cftc-chair-restructures-agencys-enforcement-division-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUI4WCXPURP6LCXP3MLRLXPV3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国博彩协会称，美国人预计将在超级碗上合法投注 13.9 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国博彩协会（American Gaming Association）周二表示，本周日两届卫冕冠军堪萨斯城酋长队（Kansas City Chiefs）和费城老鹰队（Philadelphia Eagles）之间的超级碗对决，将在美国合法投注创纪录的 13.9 亿美元。【原文：A record $1.39 billion will be legally wagered in the United States on Sunday's Super Bowl match-up between the two-times defending champion Kansas City Chiefs and Philadelphia Eagles, the American Gaming Association said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/nfl/americans-expected-legally-bet-139-bln-super-bowl-aga-says-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUO6YQFUCNMSBLSZAGS3Y5GMIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税威胁不断演变，投资者提高警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者正在寻求保护投资组合免受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税计划可能带来的经济影响，尽管华尔街的许多人都怀疑这一局势是否会爆发一场导致资产瘫痪的持续贸易战。【原文：Investors are seeking to protect portfolios from the potential economic fallout from President Donald Trump's tariff plans even as many on Wall Street doubt the situation will erupt into a sustained trade war that cripples assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-guard-us-tariff-threats-evolve-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JUGJBNPDRJUXCDJPZTT4T2N3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 敦促美国监管机构为银行提供加密货币服务开辟道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase Global周二再次呼吁美国银行业监管机构澄清或修改其对银行提供加密货币服务以及可能与数字资产领域的公司进行合作的立场。【原文：Coinbase Global on Tuesday renewed its call for U.S. banking regulators to clarify or revise their position on banks offering cryptocurrency services as well as potentially doing tie-ups with companies in the digital assets sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/coinbase-urges-us-regulators-clear-path-banks-offer-crypto-services-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TK3XM5QZE5LI3BWSGINKLNRTYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉石油出口因雪佛龙公司的货物而增加，向中国供应更多石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据船只移动情况得出的数据显示，受美国大型企业雪佛龙公司（Chevron Corp）与委内瑞拉国家石油公司（PDVSA）的合资企业发货量增加以及更多货物运往中国的推动，委内瑞拉 1 月份的石油出口量增长了 15%，达到每天约 86.7 万桶。【原文：Venezuela's oil exports rose 15% to some 867,000 barrels per day in January, driven by an increase in shipments by U.S. major Chevron Corp from its joint ventures with state firm PDVSA, and more cargoes to China, data based on vessel movements showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/venezuela-oil-exports-rise-chevrons-cargoes-more-supply-china-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZUEPHOVFROT7PV4D6MFLVWAMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黎巴嫩总统希望道达尔能源公司尽快恢复石油和天然气勘探]]></title><description><![CDATA[黎巴嫩总统办公室发表声明称，黎巴嫩总统约瑟夫-奥恩（Joseph Aoun）周二告诉卡塔尔首相谢赫-穆罕默德-本-阿卜杜勒拉赫曼-阿勒萨尼（Sheikh Mohammed bin Abdulrahman Al Thani），他希望道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）尽快恢复在黎巴嫩沿海的石油和天然气勘探。【原文：Lebanon President Joseph Aoun on Tuesday told Qatari Prime Minister Sheikh Mohammed bin Abdulrahman Al Thani that he hopes TotalEnergies will soon resume oil and gas exploration off the coast of Lebanon, according to a statement from the president's office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/lebanon-president-says-he-hopes-totalenergies-will-resume-oil-gas-exploration-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RP6XEGLCSJIIXAQPCJORY5SNPQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:39:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CFTC 下达指令后，Robinhood 暂停超级碗博彩合约交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 周二表示，在收到美国商品期货交易委员会的要求后，该经纪公司已暂停超级碗博彩合约的交易。【原文：Robinhood said on Tuesday it had suspended trading in Super Bowl betting contracts after the brokerage received a request from the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/robinhood-receives-us-cftc-request-roll-back-super-bowl-prediction-contracts-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGMWNEHEIFMYLEXBGIE7ICXBTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:35:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克与 OpenAI 就非营利组织转制问题对簿公堂]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）和 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 的律师周二将在法庭上针锋相对，法官将听取马斯克关于停止 OpenAI 转为营利实体的诉讼的辩论。【原文：Lawyers for Elon Musk and ChatGPT maker OpenAI are set to butt heads in the courtroom on Tuesday as a judge will hear arguments on Musk’s lawsuit to halt OpenAI’s conversion to a for-profit entity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/elon-musk-openai-head-court-spar-over-nonprofit-conversion-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBNQINIK7VKLPAQVRJQZLAFZ2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车收购 Cruise 自主业务的全部所有权]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司周二宣布，已完成对 Cruise 自动驾驶汽车部门的全部收购，将专注于开发个人汽车技术，而不是机器人轴。【原文：General Motors has finalized the complete acquisition of its Cruise autonomous vehicle unit to focus on developing the technology for personal vehicles instead of on robotaxis, the company announced on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/general-motors-acquires-full-ownership-cruise-autonomous-business-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQYQ6OM3CZIRZJNOQ6DMSRV2HQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:29:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称摩根大通为其业务服务部门聘请了竞争对手高盛的高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周二看到的一份备忘录，摩根大通已聘请高盛高管乔纳森-斯劳特（Jonathan Slaughter）加入其商业服务部门，以扩大其在欧洲和中东地区的覆盖范围。【原文：JPMorgan &amp; Chase has hired Goldman Sachs's executive Jonathan Slaughter to join its business services group, in a bid to expand its coverage in Europe and the Middle East region, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jpmorgan-hires-rival-goldmans-executive-its-business-services-unit-memo-says-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVGF7KTZI5L4DG247SVW6BADC4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:24:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼迪更接近卫生部长职位，疫苗和包装食品库存下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的美国卫生部长人选小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：Shares of vaccine makers and packaged food companies fell on Tuesday after President Donald Trump's pick for U.S. health secretary, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., moved closer to the job after a favorable vote by a Senate panel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/vaccine-packaged-food-stocks-fall-kennedy-moves-closer-health-secretary-job-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UEUHY26GRLHTIKYIUVEQJOQNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 16:51:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储终止 2011 年对富国银行的两项执法行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周二宣布，已终止 2011 年对富国银行采取的一系列执法行动，但表示该银行的资产上限仍然有效。【原文：The Federal Reserve announced on Tuesday it had terminated a pair of enforcement actions imposed on Wells Fargo in 2011, but said the bank's asset cap remained in place.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-terminates-two-2011-enforcement-actions-against-wells-fargo-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRBE3MZB25LMHKLNGXRSTDL3NA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 16:40:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepSeek 和特朗普：对冲基金如何度过 2025 年动荡的开局]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，2025 年伊始，美国新总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政策的不确定性以及中国人工智能初创公司 DeepSeek 的出现导致科技股领头羊英伟达（Nvidia）股价暴跌，令市场波澜不惊，对冲基金受到提振。【原文：Hedge funds started 2025 buoyed by choppier markets driven by uncertainty on new U.S. President Donald Trump's policies and a tumble in tech-darling Nvidia as Chinese artificial intelligence startup DeepSeek emerged, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deepseek-trump-how-hedge-funds-navigated-turbulent-start-2025-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFDSC4EAFBPWLEDYZWXGPP7Z4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 16:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ADNOC 在美国的投资转移至国际分支 XRG]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿布扎比国家石油公司（ADNOC）首席执行官周二表示，阿布扎比国家石油公司在美国的投资目前归属于其新成立的国际投资部门XRG，该石油巨头正着手建立以低碳能源和化学品为重点的业务。【原文：Abu Dhabi National Oil Company's investments in the United States now sit within its new international investment arm XRG, ADNOC's CEO said on Tuesday, as the oil giant moves to build up a business focused on lower carbon energy and chemicals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/adnocs-us-investments-moved-international-arm-xrg-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNZLJ27C4NK7PMMTXAUVNTQQ7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:53:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月份工厂订单再次下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[受民用飞机预订量下降的影响，12 月份美国制成品的新订单有所下降，但其他地区的需求略显坚挺。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods dropped in December, pulled down by a decline in bookings for civilian aircraft, but demand elsewhere was marginally firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-factory-orders-decline-again-december-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y52ON7XUMBOHTEKZ4H4ZQFVDSA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月职位空缺大幅下降；裁员人数较少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 12 月份的职位空缺急剧下降，但低裁员率表明劳动力市场并未突然放缓。【原文：U.S. job openings dropped sharply in December, but low layoffs suggested that the labor market was not abruptly slowing down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-fall-sharply-december-layoffs-low-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BM3KV3KCAVOLBGFQFRSRFWDNIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:25:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税威胁笼罩着年轻的阿尔诺修复 LVMH 饮料部门的使命]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）面临发动贸易战的风险之际，亚历山大-阿尔诺（Alexandre Arnault）将在 LVMH 集团价值 60 亿美元的葡萄酒和烈酒业务中担任重要角色，这将使其扭亏为盈的努力变得更加复杂，而这可能决定这位 32 岁的年轻人在其父亲的帝国中的未来。【原文：Alexandre Arnault is taking a key role at LVMH's $6 billion wine and spirits business just as U.S. President Donald Trump risks unleashing a trade war, complicating a turnaround effort that could decide the 32-year-old's future in his father's empire.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trumps-tariff-threats-hang-over-young-arnaults-mission-fix-lvmh-drinks-unit-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4ZS2NKLPJPXVPRWUYQUW3EVVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股市和货币在关税风暴后的平静中找到立足点]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国和中国在关税问题上针锋相对，但在墨西哥和加拿大赢得最后一刻的缓和之后，周二股市和货币持稳，市场呈现出令人不安的平静。【原文：Stocks and currencies held steady on Tuesday as an uneasy calm settled on markets despite the United States and China going tit-for-tat on tariffs, a day after Mexico and Canada won a last-minute reprieve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-global-markets-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32OQ3JFOBFJ6XEEAKYYRV3GT2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:01:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>