<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 02:26:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 02:25:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[主要货币保持稳定，市场对 PPI 乐观程度和关税进行了评估]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元和主要货币周五保持稳定，因为交易商评估了华盛顿不会立即实施的对等关税的潜在影响，而美国生产者价格报告则缓解了对通货膨胀的担忧。【原文：The U.S. dollar and major currencies steadied on Friday, as traders assessed the potential impact of Washington's reciprocal tariffs which will not be immediately implemented, while a U.S. producer price report eased inflation concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/major-currencies-steady-markets-size-up-ppi-optimism-tariffs-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6I4APOYXZLJJDD4EMPQYULOPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国消费者监督机构将裁员范围扩大到试用期员工之外]]></title><description><![CDATA[据五位消息人士透露，美国消费者金融保护局周四又有一类员工收到了解聘通知，这表明特朗普政府在解雇联邦工作人员时，已经超出了试用期员工的范围。【原文：A new category of employees at the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau received termination notices on Thursday, according to five sources and termination letters, in a sign that the Trump administration was going beyond probationary employees as it looks to fire federal staff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-watchdog-broadens-layoffs-beyond-probationary-staff-sources-say-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RQ5FISWNEBKEBLEBEZJOUGKTIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报道巨人队希望出售球队有限股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《体育商业杂志》（Sports Business Journal）周四报道，纽约巨人队正在将球队的有限股份投入市场，这一过程很可能会创下 NFL 特许经营权估值的纪录。【原文：The New York Giants are putting a limited stake in the team on the market, with the process likely to set a record for an NFL franchise valuation, Sports Business Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/report-giants-looking-sell-limited-stake-team-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUQN5BDIMZOXDCY7BSXF2MNOEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称正就互惠关税计划与美国沟通]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府发言人周五表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令制定关税提案计划后，日本已开始与美国进行沟通。【原文：Japan has already initiated communication with the United States following President Donald Trump's order on formulating plans for tariff proposal, a government spokesperson said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-says-it-is-communicating-with-us-reciprocal-tariff-plan-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2AW2AMHKVK6BIFXHNDW73JWCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔出售部分 DaVita 股份，持股比例降至 45]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周四晚间表示，已出售 203,091 股 DaVita 公司股票，将其在这家肾透析服务提供商的持股降至约 3589 万股，持股比例为 45%，价值近 64 亿美元。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway said on Thursday night it sold 203,091 shares of DaVita , reducing its stake in the kidney dialysis services provider to about 35.89 million shares, a 45% stake worth nearly $6.4 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/berkshire-sells-some-davita-shares-cuts-stake-45-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAO5Z2DKRJMV7I6YYMFSKIAN3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 01:13:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：司法部长致函苹果公司后，苹果将恢复 TikTok 在美国应用商店的销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道称，根据美国司法部长帕姆-邦迪（Pam Bondi）的指示，苹果公司将于周四恢复字节跳动公司（ByteDance）旗下 TikTok 在美国应用商店的销售。【原文：Apple will restore ByteDance-owned TikTok on its U.S. App Store on Thursday following a directive from U.S. Attorney General Pam Bondi, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-restore-tiktok-us-app-store-after-attorney-generals-letter-bloomberg-news-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OO7C2STPNPRPMRVFTDBXJWLZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，汇丰银行将于 2 月 19 日公布 15 亿美元的年度成本节约计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，汇丰银行准备在 2 月 19 日报告其广泛重组计划所实施的变革每年可节约成本 15 亿美元。【原文：HSBC is preparing to report $1.5 billion of annual cost savings from the changes implemented under its broad restructuring initiatives on February 19, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-unveil-15-billion-annual-cost-savings-february-19-ft-reports-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2DJ3I2H3KRNUDHGHJFVVGN5RJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国卫生部长称应鼓励麦当劳在巨无霸中使用牛脂]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪周四告诉福克斯新闻，麦当劳在制作巨无霸汉堡时应该使用牛脂。【原文：U.S. Health and Human Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. told Fox News on Thursday McDonald's ought to be incentivized to use beef tallow when making its Big Mac burgers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-health-secretary-says-mcdonalds-should-be-incentivized-use-beef-tallow-big-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQU7TF7U4JP53EWNVEZA42DPR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:18:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼股票因买单过多而无法交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼公司周五在东京的早盘交易中，在这家科技和娱乐企业集团公布了其游戏和音乐部门的强劲业绩后，其股票在大量买单下没有成交。【原文：Sony's shares were untraded with a glut of buy orders in early trading in Tokyo on Friday after the technology and entertainment conglomerate reported strong results at its games and music divisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sony-shares-untraded-with-glut-buy-orders-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJLLRFLC6JOQNH744E5HPP67OA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司预测 2025 年核心利润高于分析师预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司周五预测，2025 年的核心利润将高于分析师的预期，因为这家加拿大最大的航空公司押注于稳定的国际旅游需求和商务预订的反弹。【原文：Air Canada forecast 2025 core profit above analysts' estimates on Friday, as the country's largest carrier bets on steady international travel demand and a rebound in business bookings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-canada-forecast-2025-core-profit-above-analysts-estimates-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBUVCOYB3RMFPDVHD5RQAKLG5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莫迪表示美印两国的目标是到 2030 年双边贸易额达到 5000 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪（Narendra Modi）周四表示，美国和印度已经制定了到2030年将双边贸易额翻番至5000亿美元的目标，并将致力于尽快达成互惠贸易协定。【原文：Indian Prime Minster Narendra Modi said on Thursday the United States and India have set a target of doubling their bilateral trade to $500 billion by 2030 and will work on concluding a mutually beneficial trade agreement very soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/modi-says-us-india-target-500-billion-bilateral-trade-by-2030-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEMDECL4DZI6TKROH6L6SSCIGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:34:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称印度同意购买更多美国石油和天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美国和印度已达成一项协议，其中包括印度进口更多的美国石油和天然气，以缩小两国之间的贸易逆差。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday the U.S. and India have struck an agreement that includes India importing more U.S. oil and gas to shrink the trade deficit between the two countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-says-india-agreed-purchase-more-us-oil-gas-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E77DUKPPVZMEJJB7NFTQ4QHAKA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:21:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络卡车车祸为特斯拉自动驾驶软件敲响警钟]]></title><description><![CDATA[在首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）表示将于今年推出付费机器人出租车服务几天后，本周发生了一起特斯拉 Cybertruck 在自动驾驶模式下撞车事故，引发了人们对该公司为该功能提供动力的软件的可靠性的担忧。【原文：A crash involving a Tesla Cybertruck in self-driving mode this week has sparked worries about the reliability of the company's software that powers the feature, days after CEO Elon Musk said he would roll out a paid robotaxi service this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/cybertruck-crash-raises-alarm-bells-about-teslas-self-driving-software-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBGJOYBOA5PY3EI45UJYMVPIMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络安全需求稳定，Palo Alto 上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks 公司周四上调了全年营收预期，原因是预计市场对该公司网络安全解决方案的需求将激增，以应对不断增加的网络威胁。【原文：Palo Alto Networks raised its full-year revenue forecast on Thursday, on expectations of a surge in demand for the company's cybersecurity solutions to tackle rising online threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/palo-alto-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-steady-cybersecurity-demand-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NM54UAJ5JZJEPAGGT57BG54GNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:13:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国出口商为 "老鼠赛跑 "做好准备，以摆脱美国的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国一家铝制品制造商的销售人员杰里米-方正（Jeremy Fang）正试图向亚洲、非洲和拉丁美洲市场出口更多产品，以抵消美国关税的影响。他说，问题是他的竞争对手也有同样的想法。【原文：Jeremy Fang, a sales officer at a Chinese aluminium products maker, is trying to export more to markets in Asia, Africa and Latin America to offset the U.S. tariffs' impact. The problem, he says, is that his competitors have the same idea.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chinese-exporters-brace-rat-race-shift-away-us-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPP4VI4J6JIHVM64W26HRCLQMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关于美国对等关税的新命令有哪些内容？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四提出废除美国几十年来的低关税税率，将其提高到与其他国家相同的水平，并抵消对美国商品设置的其他壁垒，以试图缩小去年高达1.2万亿美元的美国商品贸易逆差。【原文：President Donald Trump on Thursday moved to tear up decades-old low U.S. tariff rates, raising them to match those of other countries and counteract other barriers to American goods to try to shrink a U.S. goods trade deficit that topped $1.2 trillion last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/whats-trumps-new-order-reciprocal-us-tariffs-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7ASKZMFYFOA7KJ5K23J7GL2DY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:49:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求强劲，摩托罗拉预计季度调整后利润高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[安全和企业安保服务提供商摩托罗拉解决方案公司周四预计，受安全和安保服务需求增加的推动，第一季度调整后利润将高于华尔街预期。【原文：Safety and enterprise security services provider Motorola Solutions forecast first-quarter adjusted profit above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, driven by higher demand for its safety and security services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/motorola-forecasts-quarterly-adjusted-profit-above-estimates-strong-demand-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBIKZT54JJLMZD7T2BJVLRLW3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:28:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：Arm向客户招兵买马，计划销售自己的芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士和路透社查阅的一份文件显示，Arm 已开始从自己的客户中招兵买马，并与他们争夺交易，以推动销售自己的芯片。【原文：Arm has begun recruiting from its own customers and competing against them for deals as it pushes toward selling its own chips, according to people familiar with the matter and a document viewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/arm-recruits-customers-it-plans-sell-its-own-chips-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMSJM7LCYRMIXP62IOWRBHDIPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:24:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出口限制收紧，应用材料公司发布黯淡的季度收入预期；股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[应用材料公司（Applied Materials）周四预测第二季度营收低于市场预期，预计地缘政治紧张局势升级和消费电子产品内存芯片需求疲软将拖累其芯片制造设备的销售。【原文：Applied Materials forecast second-quarter revenue below market estimates on Thursday, expecting escalating geopolitical tensions and soft demand for memory chips used in consumer electronics to weigh on sales of its chipmaking equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/applied-materials-gives-dour-quarterly-revenue-forecast-export-curbs-tighten-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQRPKL3YCRND7GJW7BAM5PYEX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:50:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：华尔街反弹，因炙手可热的 PPI 表面看起来更冷淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLWFEVIEPBKKRHUVS7CBBSD3LA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:48:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉斯维加斯业务强劲，赌场运营商永利第四季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[赌场运营商永利度假村（Wynn Resorts）周四公布的第四季度利润和营收超出分析师预期，主要得益于拉斯维加斯和其他地区物业的强劲业务，该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨约 3%。【原文：Casino operator Wynn Resorts beat analysts' estimates for fourth-quarter profit and revenue on Thursday, driven by strong business in Las Vegas and other regional properties, sending its shares up about 3% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/casino-operator-wynn-beats-fourth-quarter-estimates-strength-las-vegas-business-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4CWTAO27VP77AOQR4YO2MI6PI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:44:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会起诉加密货币交易所 Binance 的案件被搁置]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿特区的一名联邦法官周四将美国证券交易委员会对 Binance 的民事诉讼搁置 60 天，批准了该监管机构和全球最大加密货币交易所的联合请求。【原文：A federal judge in Washington, D.C., on Thursday put the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's civil lawsuit against Binance on hold for 60 days, granting a joint request by the regulator and the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sec-case-against-crypto-exchange-binance-put-hold-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALX3U66T2NIY3MG52YBLGYZQIA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，新西兰制造业活动两年来首次出现扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，新西兰制造业活动近两年来首次出现扩张，生产和新订单的关键分项指数结果均为正值。【原文：Manufacturing activity in New Zealand expanded for the first time in nearly two years, with key sub-index results for both production and new orders in positive territory, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/new-zealand-manufacturing-activity-expands-first-time-two-years-survey-shows-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5WTIOLY3BLVBCBINKPT2BU3IM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利首席执行官泰德-皮克 2024 年的薪酬定为 3400 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份文件显示，摩根士丹利首席执行官泰德-皮克（Ted Pick）2024 年的薪酬定为 3400 万美元，这是他上任后的第一年。【原文：Morgan Stanley CEO Ted Pick's compensation was set at $34 million for 2024, his first year in the top job, a filing showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-sets-compensation-34-million-ceo-ted-pick-2024-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBOHHOEPQ5IK3CJ5MCAUFM2F34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:31:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员再次提出允许在全国范围内全年销售 E15 的法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员周四再次提出一项两党法案，允许在全国范围内全年销售乙醇含量更高的汽油，该计划得到了一个主要石油贸易集团的支持。【原文：U.S. senators reintroduced a bipartisan bill on Thursday that would allow nationwide sales of gasoline with a higher blend of ethanol year-round, a plan that has the support of a leading oil trade group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-senators-reintroduce-bill-allow-year-round-nationwide-e15-sales-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQZJHE6LXRJGTM2G2XRJLBM53M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普计划就数字服务税对加拿大和法国征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，他计划就加拿大和法国对美国科技巨头征收数字服务税一事对两国征收关税，这一直是一个长期的刺激因素。【原文：President Donald Trump on Thursday said he planned to impose tariffs on Canada and France over their digital services taxes on U.S. technology giants, which has been a long-standing irritant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-plans-tariffs-canada-france-over-digital-services-taxes-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RTG4YBYDFI7RMWRXFHAEMKLQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:18:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 公布第四季度利润因加密货币上涨而增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Coinbase 周四报告称，受美国大选后比特币和其他代币交易量增加的推动，第四季度利润大幅增长。【原文：Crypto exchange Coinbase reported a steep rise in fourth quarter profit on Thursday, driven by higher trading volumes in bitcoin and other tokens following the U.S. election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/coinbase-reports-strong-fourth-quarter-profit-crypto-rally-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIBV66J5D5K3TLQHGIJFNHWRVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广告销售强劲，Roku 季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受强劲的用户增长和强劲的广告销售推动，Roku 周四公布的第四季度营收超出华尔街预期。【原文：Roku topped Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter revenue on Thursday, driven by robust subscriber growth and strong advertising sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/rokus-quarterly-revenue-beats-estimates-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4JXR2RBXVONVGGEDA2HYC5TRI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飞机交付延迟导致航空租赁公司收入减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空租赁公司（Air Lease Corp）周四公布的季度收入下降，原因是尽管旅游需求强劲，但租赁商仍要面对波音和空中客车公司推迟交付商用飞机的问题。【原文：Air Lease Corp on Thursday reported lower quarterly revenue as lessors wrestle with delays in taking deliveries of commercial jets from planemakers Boeing and Airbus despite strong travel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-lease-corp-reports-lower-revenue-jet-delivery-delays-bite-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6STMOAIVKVNVROUQ3FRHWWZCUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airbnb因外汇逆风和复活节时机调整第一季度业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[度假屋租赁公司 Airbnb 周四公布，由于国际旅游需求依然强劲，该公司的季度营收有所增长，但由于艰难的同比比较和美元走强，该公司预计第一季度的增长将有所放缓。【原文：Vacation home rentals company Airbnb posted higher quarterly revenue on Thursday as international travel demand remained strong, although it forecast slower growth for the first quarter due to tough year-over-year comparisons and a stronger dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/airbnb-tempers-first-quarter-forecast-fx-headwinds-easter-timing-2025-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MK5CMEUBY5I7PFW3WMYT6KJFBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>