<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 06:09:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 06:09:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价特朗普回来了，波动性也回来了]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XS6LTALFANLTFD5UVUVFO4FNVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 05:33:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴宝莉投资者关注销售好转迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者对巴宝莉寄予厚望，希望该英国奢侈品牌在本周五公布关键节日季的销售报告时，开始显示出扭亏为盈的迹象。【原文：Investors have high hopes for Burberry to start showing signs of progress in its turnaround when the British luxury brand reports sales for the crucial festive season this Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/burberry-investors-watch-signs-sales-turnaround-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UBLCO2NVFIV3H2UO3XLBGRJLI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 05:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球企业可能受到特朗普承诺的关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统特朗普表示，他可能从2月1日起对加拿大和墨西哥征收25%的关税，这使得多家亚洲汽车制造商和电池公司的股价在周二的交易中走低。【原文：U.S. President Trump said he could impose 25% tariffs on Canada and Mexico from Feb. 1, sending shares of several Asian automakers and battery firms lower in trading on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-companies-likely-be-affected-by-trumps-promised-tariffs-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4G674R7TNKO5FBDQPT6ADSXAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 05:03:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[冬季风暴来袭，得克萨斯州港口和飞行员暂停部分作业]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于天气寒冷，德克萨斯州的港口和协助船只在港口航行的领航员周一暂停了部分作业。【原文：Texas ports and pilots, who assist in moving vessels around ports, suspended some operations on Monday as frigid weather conditions hit the state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/texas-ports-pilots-suspend-some-operations-winter-storm-hits-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7ZYUJOWSBMNDNWPEPRYKREIIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 04:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020 年签署的中美第一阶段贸易协定是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）已指示联邦机构评估中国在第一阶段贸易协定下的表现。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has directed federal agencies to assess China's performance under the Phase 1 trade deal that he signed with Beijing in 2020 during his first term at the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/whats-us-china-phase-1-trade-deal-signed-2020-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DRZMPLZKRKDVPXRE7EC5CQCXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 03:37:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普推迟加征关税，中国股市谨慎走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的就职政策表明他将通过谈判而不是立即对贸易伙伴征收高额关税，周二中国股市开盘走高，人民币汇率走强。【原文：Chinese stocks opened higher and the yuan strengthened in a cautious start to Tuesday, as U.S. President Donald Trump's inaugural policies suggested he will negotiate rather than immediately impose hefty tariffs on trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-stocks-cautiously-higher-after-trump-delays-tariffs-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOLL5NNLZZOAFCWJZNREHPQGAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 02:59:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上台后，亚洲汽车和电池制造商受到冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，日本汽车制造商和韩国电池制造商的股票受到打击，此前美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他可能很快对加拿大和墨西哥征收关税，并撤销了上届政府关于电动汽车的行政命令。【原文：Shares of Japanese automakers and South Korean battery makers were hit on Tuesday, after U.S. President Donald Trump said he could impose tariffs on Canada and Mexico soon and revoked the previous administration's executive order on electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asian-car-battery-makers-hit-trump-gets-work-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRIFLUWXKVLW3FCLXKGDIRR7XQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 02:35:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税计划引发股市和国债波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在唐纳德-特朗普宣布对邻国征收贸易关税的计划后，全球股市和美国国债走势震荡，扭转了盘初唐纳德-特朗普就任新总统后最初几个小时的短暂宽松反弹。【原文：Global shares and U.S. Treasuries were volatile on Tuesday, reversing a brief relief rally from early in the session in the first few hours of Donald Trump's new presidency after he announced plans for trade tariffs on neighbouring countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-tv-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4WSFO666NOWHGB7GWZIZIRHUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 02:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提出普遍征收关税的想法，但表示美国尚未做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一提出了普遍征收关税的想法，但表示美国尚未准备好采取这一步骤。【原文：Republican U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday floated the idea of universal tariffs but said the United States was not yet ready for such a step.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-floats-idea-universal-tariff-says-us-not-ready-it-yet-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXUDN2TLVROGRPQXIYRSIV7HOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署承诺的 TikTok 命令，推迟对应用程序的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一签署命令，推迟对流行短视频应用 TikTok 的禁令，该应用原定于 1 月 19 日关闭。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday signed an order to delay a ban of popular short-video app TikTok that was slated to be shuttered on Jan. 19.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-signs-promised-tiktok-order-delaying-ban-app-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZYFRLDYQJMZNLVY62E2C5NYGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:18:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国第四季度经济勉强增长；韩国央行将于二月降息：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对经济学家进行的一项调查显示，韩国经济在上个季度几乎没有增长，原因是政治混乱拖累了消费者支出。【原文：The South Korean economy barely grew last quarter as political chaos weighed on consumer spending, according to a Reuters poll of economists who expect the Bank of Korea to cut interest rates next month following a surprise hold last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/south-korea-economy-barely-grew-q4-bok-cut-rates-february-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HTTGFDJLFL6VMTWEWDXMP577U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称考虑对墨西哥和加拿大征收 25% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他正在考虑对从加拿大和墨西哥进口的商品征收 25% 的关税，因为这两个国家允许许多人以及芬太尼越境。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he was thinking of imposing 25% tariffs on imports from Canada and Mexico because they were allowing many people to cross the border as well as fentanyl.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-says-hes-thinking-25-tariffs-mexico-canada-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TY2GOB4INJPD5KZ33J7PZQSY2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:08:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普撤销拜登关于 2030 年电动汽车占比 50%目标的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周一撤销了其前任乔-拜登签署的 2021 年行政命令，该命令旨在确保 2030 年销售的所有新车中有一半是电动汽车。【原文：President Donald Trump on Monday revoked a 2021 executive order signed by his predecessor Joe Biden that sought to ensure half of all new vehicles sold in 2030 were electric.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-revokes-biden-order-that-set-50-ev-target-2030-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VW3ZO73VZ5PHLIROTQUYZD4WUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令联邦工作人员全职返岗]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统下令联邦工作人员每周五天返回办公室，并于周一在华盛顿首都第一体育馆欢呼的支持者面前签署了一项行政命令。【原文：President Donald Trump has ordered federal workers to return to the office five days a week, signing an executive order in front of cheering supporters at Washington's Capital One Arena on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-orders-federal-workers-back-office-full-time-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBRXZ5WDZFNAVCCQP5DCYW2QOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普撤销拜登关于应对人工智能风险的行政命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一撤销了一项由乔-拜登签署的 2023 年行政令，该行政令旨在降低人工智能对消费者、工人和国家安全造成的风险。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday revoked a 2023 executive order signed by Joe Biden that sought to reduce the risks that artificial intelligence poses to consumers, workers and national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/trump-revokes-biden-executive-order-addressing-ai-risks-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NF6X6BP3DNLUFK2S646GR3M46Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普贸易备忘录草案针对美国贸易逆差和中国购买美国出口商品问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份白宫贸易备忘录草案，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正在命令联邦机构 "调查和补救 "美国持续存在的贸易赤字，并解决其他国家的不公平贸易行为和货币操纵问题。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is ordering federal agencies to "investigate and remedy" persistent U.S. trade deficits, and address other countries' unfair trade practices and currency manipulation, according to a draft White House trade memo seen by Reuters that stops short of ordering immediate new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/draft-trump-trade-memo-targets-us-trade-deficit-china-purchases-us-exports-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUXO5HFMRVJLTP2BPUWNVTSC4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登联邦贸易委员会主席汗将在未来几周内辞去委员会职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[莉娜-汗（Lina Khan）曾在前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）的领导下领导美国联邦贸易委员会，直到本周一，她在一份备忘录中告诉工作人员，她将在未来几周内辞去该委员会的职务。【原文：Lina Khan, who headed the U.S. Federal Trade Commission under former President Joe Biden until Monday, will resign from the commission in the coming weeks, she told staff in a memo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/biden-ftc-chair-khan-resign-commission-coming-weeks-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IPTASLMWFMF3K7RFNI6ICR2FI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普计划提高化石燃料产量，美国原油期货每桶下跌 1 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普总统上任并宣布通过宣布国家紧急状态来最大限度提高美国石油和天然气产量的计划之后，美国油价在周二的亚洲早盘交易中每桶下跌超过1美元。【原文：U.S. oil prices fell by more than $1 a barrel in early Asian trading on Tuesday after President Donald Trump took office and announced a plan to maximise U.S. oil and gas production by declaring a national emergency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-futures-down-1-barrel-trump-plan-boost-fossil-fuel-output-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3EDRBZEYVLGVNXSITGUIXQDBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：中国商飞为越南提供喷气式飞机表明中国在推动国际市场发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位了解会谈和文件情况的人士称，中国正加大力度利用中国商飞公司的国产喷气式飞机打入外国航空市场，并努力说服越南批准其飞机进入越南市场。【原文：China's drive to break into foreign aviation markets with its homegrown COMAC jets has intensified, with a push to persuade Vietnam to authorise its planes in the country, according to two people with knowledge of the talks and documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/comac-jets-vietnam-show-chinas-push-international-market-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AR26VFDY55OONGIOMYISLQRCNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：特朗普关税警告重挫美元，提振股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SHZB4I5FNI5DBHSDQLKDUPTTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 21:49:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的新加密货币引发道德担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[道德专家和业内人士表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在周一就职典礼前不久推出了一种加密代币，这引发了新的利益冲突问题。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's launch of a crypto token shortly before his inauguration on Monday creates new conflict-of-interest concerns, ethics experts and industry insiders said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-new-crypto-coin-sparks-ethics-concerns-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZJGA4R6UNKATDEVHR3KMX2UJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称特朗普任命共和党人植田为美国证券交易委员会代理主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周一表示，新宣誓就职的唐纳德-特朗普总统已任命美国证券交易委员会共和党成员马克-植田（Mark Uyeda）担任该机构代理主席。【原文：Newly sworn-in President Donald Trump has tapped Mark Uyeda, a Republican member of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, to be acting chair of the agency, the White House said Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-taps-republican-uyeda-acting-sec-chair-white-house-says-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QM2YBCPVHROTXA36DIQUQFVAAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:39:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，特朗普任命特拉维斯-希尔为联邦存款保险公司代理主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，新宣誓就职的总统唐纳德-特朗普周一任命联邦存款保险公司副主席特拉维斯-希尔代理领导该机构。【原文：Newly sworn-in President Donald Trump on Monday appointed Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation vice chair Travis Hill to lead the agency on an acting basis, the White House said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-appoints-travis-hill-fdic-acting-chair-white-house-says-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJNPPPBSKVNKLAYHVGZD4TFYMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:32:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[米莱伊就任总统第一年，阿根廷贸易顺差达到创纪录的近 190 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一公布的官方数据，阿根廷 2024 年的贸易顺差达到创纪录的 189 亿美元，这与自由派总统哈维尔-米莱伊上任后的第一个完整年度基本吻合。【原文：Argentina posted a record $18.9 billion trade surplus for 2024, according to official data released on Monday, that largely coincides with libertarian President Javier Milei's first full year on the job.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-marks-record-trade-surplus-nearly-19-bln-mileis-first-year-president-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64JUWGSKNFPTRKZMWV3AASD6UM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:27:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易、关税、能源--市场对特朗普就职演说的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，他将对各国征收关税和税收，以让美国人致富，并将全面改革贸易体系和宣布国家能源紧急状态，此后美元延续跌势，而原油价格则收敛跌幅。【原文：The dollar extended its slide while crude prices curtailed their losses after U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he would tariff and tax countries to enrich Americans, overhaul the trade system and declare a national energy emergency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trump-quotes-instant-view-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H43MKM4UY5MZLAIRTWX7L3EZTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 19:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会代理主席范大为承诺 "与所有利益相关者合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党人卡罗琳-范周一被新上任的总统唐纳德-特朗普任命为美国商品期货交易委员会代理主席，她承诺将与所有利益相关者开展建设性的合作。【原文：Republican Caroline Pham, named acting chair on Monday of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission by newly installed President Donald Trump, pledged to work constructively with all stakeholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/acting-us-cftc-chair-pham-pledges-work-with-all-stakeholders-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOTRSDIQXFN6HNHKQQ2AASNV5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 18:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣誓就职，马克龙警告欧洲不能只依赖美国武器]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙（Emmanuel Macron）周一警告说，纳税人用于欧洲军事预算的数十亿欧元不应只用于购买美国武器，他还推动对本土国防工业进行更多投资。【原文：French President Emmanuel Macron warned on Monday that the billions of euros of taxpayer money spent on Europe's military budgets should not be used to buy only American weapons, pushing for more investment in home-grown defence industries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-is-sworn-macron-warns-europe-it-cant-depend-only-us-weapons-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M54VASOCFJNJJMNA4XIQRUC2RM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道努班克首席执行官考虑将注册地迁至英国，并在美国扩展业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nu Holdings Ltd 是一家金融科技公司，它创建了拉丁美洲最有价值的 Nubank 贷款公司，其创始人兼首席执行官大卫-维莱斯（David Velez）告诉路透社，该公司正在考虑在全球扩张（可能包括美国）之前，将其合法注册地迁往英国。【原文：Nu Holdings Ltd , the fintech that created Latin America's most valuable lender in Nubank, is considering moving its legal domicile to Britain ahead of a global expansion that may include the United States, its founder and CEO David Velez told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nubank-ceo-considers-moving-domicile-britain-expanding-us-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XF7446D2BISJODGP2YMGCVPEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示：首席执行官对全球经济增长持乐观态度，但风险依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球调查显示，生成式人工智能的进步并未导致就业机会的减少。【原文：The global survey showed advancements in generative AI had not led to a reduction in employment opportunities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/ceos-optimistic-about-global-growth-risks-remain-survey-shows-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O53FDYEWLNNKJPGPQ5PCNDG2DM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比利时任命调查法官调查刚果冲突矿产案]]></title><description><![CDATA[刚果（金）的一名律师周一表示，刚果（金）于 12 月提起刑事诉讼，指控苹果公司的子公司在供应链中使用所谓的冲突矿产，比利时已任命一名调查法官。【原文：An investigating magistrate has been appointed in Belgium after Democratic Republic of the Congo in December filed criminal complaints accusing Apple subsidiaries of using so-called conflict minerals in their supply chain, a lawyer for Congo said Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/investigating-magistrate-appointed-belgium-congo-conflict-minerals-case-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROJNB2IBFJO4FGQEC7X6QCAIXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:43:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>