<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:33:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:33:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席珀利鼓励企业使用常备回购机制]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行一位负责执行货币政策的官员周四表示，该央行正在鼓励使用一种关键的流动性工具，迄今为止，这种工具在很大程度上处于休眠状态。【原文：A Federal Reserve Bank of New York official responsible for implementing monetary policy said on Thursday the central bank is encouraging usage of a key liquidity tool that thus far has been largely dormant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-perli-encourages-firms-use-standing-repo-facility-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMIBLMAT5FIPZC46AZI3SLDBIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，Impactive Capital 或将参与 WEX 的代理权争夺战，寻求 11 位董事中的 4 位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉此事的人士和路透社看到的一份文件称，激进投资者 Impactive Capital 正在为金融科技公司 WEX Inc 的董事会斗争做准备，并可能在明年的年会上提名至少四名董事。【原文：Activist investor Impactive Capital is gearing up for a boardroom fight at financial technology company WEX Inc , and may nominate at least four directors at next year's annual meeting, according to a person familiar with the matter and a document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/impactive-capital-may-run-proxy-fight-wex-seeking-4-11-directors-source-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXISY5DRJVMUBF3HV2LYJAUU2A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尚未完成：美国参议院共和党人计划修改众议院的特朗普减税法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院共和党人周四表示，他们将寻求对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的全面税收和支出法案进行实质性修改，此前该法案在众议院以微弱优势获得批准，这表明该方案仍面临重大障碍。【原文：U.S. Senate Republicans said on Thursday they will seek substantial changes to President Donald Trump's sweeping tax and spending bill after it narrowly won approval in the House of Representatives, in a sign that significant hurdles remain for the package.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/not-done-yet-us-senate-republicans-plan-changes-houses-trump-tax-cuts-bill-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDSTVHQXT5PG3E4BDRPP4WAA34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:06:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件显示，美国联邦贸易委员会就马斯克抵制 X 的言论对 Media Matters 进行调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周四看到的一份文件显示，美国联邦贸易委员会要求 Media Matters 提供文件，说明可能与被埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）指控帮助策划广告商抵制 X 的其他媒体监督机构进行的协调。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission has demanded documents from Media Matters about possible coordination with other media watchdogs accused by Elon Musk of helping orchestrate advertiser boycotts of X, according to a document seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ftc-probes-media-matters-over-musks-x-boycott-claims-document-shows-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FC6HWM4RQVOJHI4Z4CULPHAPWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tinder 首席执行官伊奥索塔鲁诺将于七月卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tinder 首席执行官菲-伊奥索塔鲁诺（Faye Iosotaluno）周四表示，她将于 7 月份卸任，因为该交友软件的目标是吸引更多用户。【原文：Tinder CEO Faye Iosotaluno said on Thursday that she would step down in July, as the dating app aims to attract more users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tinder-ceo-iosotaluno-step-down-july-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPCZTENFZFJGHC52MNO7PMYDTU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁工人工会敦促特朗普阻止新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社首次报道，美国钢铁工人联合会周四敦促美国总统唐纳德-特朗普阻止新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司，尽管这家日本钢铁巨头承诺向这家美国标志性企业投资 140 亿美元。【原文：The United Steelworkers union urged U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday to block Nippon Steel's bid for U.S. Steel despite a pledge by the Japanese steel giant to invest $14 billion in the iconic American company, as first reported by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-steelworkers-union-urges-trump-block-nippon-steels-bid-us-steel-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPMLDMGYCFNAXHKJZ75NNDBQOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:31:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葛兰素史克的哮喘药物获 FDA 批准用于治疗 "吸烟者肺病]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国制药商葛兰素史克公司周四表示，美国食品和药物管理局已批准该公司生产的哮喘药物用于治疗部分慢性肺病患者，这种慢性肺病通常被称为 "吸烟者之肺"。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has approved British drugmaker GSK's asthma drug to treat some patients with a chronic lung disease commonly known as "smoker's lung", the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/gsks-asthma-drug-nucala-wins-fdas-approval-treat-smokers-lung-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UN7UK2N26FMNNPVMSU7TMNWURQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，阿迪达斯和彪马预计将跟随耐克提高运动服装价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和投资者周四表示，由于美国对进口商品征收关税导致零售商成本上升，阿迪达斯和彪马很可能效仿耐克，在美国提高跑步鞋和运动服的价格。【原文：Adidas and Puma are likely to hike prices for running shoes and sportswear in the United States, following Nike's lead, analysts and investors said on Thursday, as U.S. tariffs on imports drive costs up for retailers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-puma-expected-hike-sportswear-prices-following-nike-us-tariffs-hit-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B55KCYH3P5LGTAOFCAQZPIJT5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[初创公司 Anthropic 称其新型人工智能模型可一次编码数小时]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能实验室 Anthropic 周四发布了其最新的顶级技术 Claude Opus 4，称该技术可以连续数小时自主编写计算机代码。【原文：Artificial intelligence lab Anthropic on Thursday unveiled its latest top-of-the-line technology, Claude Opus 4, which it says can write computer code autonomously for hours at a time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/startup-anthropic-says-its-new-ai-model-can-code-hours-time-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGYFH3IUJRLGLKU3UBM677MKZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球债券市场发出信号，各国政府必须支付更多的长期借款]]></title><description><![CDATA[从乏善可陈的债务拍卖到长期债券价格的暴跌，投资者正在向各国政府发出一个明确的信息：在当前不确定的环境下，他们需要为未来几十年的借贷付出更多的代价。【原文：From ho-hum debt auctions to plunging long-term bond prices, investors are sending a clear message to governments that in the current climate of uncertainty they need to pay more to borrow for decades ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-bond-markets-signal-governments-must-pay-more-borrow-long-term-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2WWTDI7BZMPHOX7HDXBBGKLII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广告技术平台 MNTN 在纳斯达克首秀表现抢眼，涨幅超过 31]]></title><description><![CDATA[由瑞安-雷诺兹（Ryan Reynolds）担任首席创意官的互联网电视广告平台 MNTN 周四在纽约证券交易所上市，股价上涨了 31.25%，估值达到 16.2 亿美元，表明 IPO 市场继续保持复苏势头。【原文：MNTN , an advertising platform for internet-connected TVs which has Ryan Reynolds as its chief creative officer, secured a valuation of $1.62 billion after its shares gained 31.25% in its New York Stock Exchange debut on Thursday, signaling continued momentum in the recovering IPO market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/adtech-platform-mntn-gains-over-31-stellar-nasdaq-debut-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JXUINRMKJMWNGMOSF42HWCXKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓广泛物色新任首席执行官，与必和必拓的强大阵容形成鲜明对比]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，在力拓寻找新首席执行官的过程中，由于可能的内部候选人名单非常短，该矿商将广泛撒网，这与其主要竞争对手必和必拓（BHP）专注的继任计划形成了鲜明对比。【原文：As Rio Tinto , searches for a new CEO, the miner will cast a wide net due to a very short list of possible internal candidates, sources said, in contrast with laser-focused succession planning at its main rival BHP.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rio-hunts-broadly-new-ceo-contrast-with-strong-bhp-bench-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMYO5UQUANLENDIBOSICPB4JWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯立法者主张有权无视西方公司回购方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯立法者正在推动制定新规则，赋予国内公司无视与离开俄罗斯的西方公司达成的任何回购协议的权利，以控制战略部门并促进国内生产。【原文：Russian lawmakers are pushing for new rules to give domestic companies the right to ignore any buyback options they agreed with Western firms that left the country, to keep a grip on strategic sectors and promote domestic production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/russian-lawmakers-push-right-ignore-western-company-buyback-options-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGCB7Q7MIBKPDP6DTOB6QHA2UA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:14:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际清算银行数字货币中心负责人提前离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[领导国际清算银行数字货币工作的前瑞典央行行长塞西莉亚-斯金斯利（Cecilia Skingsley）将提前两年离开这个总部设在瑞士的伞式机构，回国担任政府工作。【原文：The former Swedish central banker leading the Bank for International Settlements' work on digital currencies, Cecilia Skingsley, is to leave the Switzerland-based umbrella body two years early to take a government job back in her homeland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/head-bis-digital-currency-hub-leaves-post-early-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBI6BCWJK5LIVO2FQ3N4I4WO6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博法律报道，谷歌因人工智能技术交易面临司法部调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博法律周四援引知情人士的话报道，美国司法部正在调查 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌与人工智能初创公司 Character.AI 达成的协议是否违反了反垄断法，该协议允许这家科技巨头使用聊天机器人制造商的技术。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department is probing whether Alphabet's Google violated antitrust law in its agreement with AI startup Character.AI that allows the tech giant to use the chatbot maker's technology, Bloomberg Law reported on Thursday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-faces-doj-probe-over-deal-ai-tech-bloomberg-law-reports-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRWFAS2CIFOAJBM7BFPMSZWTW4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，埃及正在就购买 40-60 船液化天然气进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士告诉路透社，埃及正在与能源公司和贸易公司洽谈购买 40-60 船液化天然气（LNG）的事宜，因为在夏季需求高峰到来之前，埃及的能源紧缺状况正在恶化。【原文：Egypt is in talks with energy firms and trading houses to buy 40-60 cargoes of liquefied natural gas (LNG) amid a worsening energy crunch ahead of peak summer demand, three sources aware of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/egypt-talks-buy-40-60-lng-cargoes-amid-energy-crunch-sources-say-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XMPISCEUBNR7J7CKSAFFP6ZVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局（FAA）批准太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）的 "星际飞船 "火箭复飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周四表示，已批准太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）的 "星际飞船"（Starship）在三月份的爆炸测试事故后复飞，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空公司最快可在下周从得克萨斯州发射火星火箭的第九次试飞。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration on Thursday said it approved SpaceX's Starship to return to flight after its explosive testing mishap in March, allowing Elon Musk's space company to launch the Mars rocket's ninth test flight from Texas as soon as next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/faa-approves-return-flight-spacexs-starship-rocket-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQQCBJGR6VJDHAOQSJRTZUL47Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利相信美欧贸易协定将呼应美英协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利经济部长吉安卡洛-乔盖蒂（Giancarlo Giorgetti）周四表示，意大利相信美国将同意与欧盟达成一项类似于华盛顿已经与英国达成的贸易协议。【原文：Italy is confident the United States will agree to a trade deal with the European Union similar to the one Washington has already struck with Britain, Economy Minister Giancarlo Giorgetti said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italy-confident-us-eu-trade-accord-will-echo-us-uk-deal-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NM3A2N3QE5L5NINB555AVMPA2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:33:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院投票否决加州 2035 年电动汽车法规]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院周四投票决定禁止加利福尼亚州到 2035 年停止销售纯汽油车的里程碑计划，该计划已被代表美国三分之一汽车市场的其他 11 个州采纳。【原文：The U.S. Senate on Thursday voted to bar California's landmark plan to end the sale of gasoline-only vehicles by 2035 that has been adopted by 11 other states representing a third of the U.S. auto market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-senate-votes-block-california-2035-electric-vehicle-rules-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHRS7YBH2JKWDKI4TEZI3WUP6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛与塔吉特：关税凸显财富鸿沟日益扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税正在扩大市场领导者沃尔玛和塔吉特（Target）之间的差距，两家公司的最新季报显示，这凸显了美国较小零售商在经济不确定性中的失策。【原文：President Donald Trump's tariffs are widening the gap between market-leader Walmart and Target, the companies' latest quarterly reports show, underscoring missteps at the smaller U.S. retailer amid economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/walmart-vs-target-tariffs-highlight-growing-divide-fortunes-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FLAMHOUYJLDJOZNRRT6MTGIYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广告技术公司 MNTN 和投资者在美国首次公开募股中融资 1.872 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[营销技术公司 MNTN 和一些投资者周三表示，该公司在美国首次公开募股中募集到了 1.872 亿美元，为在 "解放日 "市场低迷中被推迟的另一次备受关注的上市创造了条件。【原文：Marketing tech firm MNTN and some investors raised $187.2 million in a U.S. initial public offering, the company said on Wednesday, setting the stage for another closely watched listing that was delayed amid the "Liberation Day" market downturn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/adtech-mntn-investors-raise-1872-million-us-ipo-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">635T3SB23VOUNCKMN4PMXESWUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织称美国国债抛售仍有序进行]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）发言人周四表示，美国国债市场保持有序，美国政府债券仍是流动性较好的避险资产。【原文：The U.S. Treasury market remains orderly and U.S. government bonds remain liquid safe-haven assets, a spokesperson at the International Monetary Fund said on Thursday, adding the Fund was monitoring tax plans taking shape in Congress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasuries-sell-off-remains-orderly-imf-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHDP2HCYLZKXTDNHZ5MDA2OX6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构投票决定禁止被认为存在安全风险的中国实验室测试美国电子产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（Federal Communications Commission）周四以4比0的投票结果最终确定了禁止被认为对美国国家安全构成威胁的中国实验室在美国测试智能手机、照相机和电脑等电子设备的规定。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission voted on Thursday 4-0 to finalize rules barring Chinese labs deemed risks to U.S. national security from testing electronic devices such as smartphones, cameras and computers for use in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-agency-votes-bar-chinese-labs-deemed-security-risks-testing-us-electronics-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFI5RWHLVBJ7XGDYAG5O4E2GC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:08:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新的人工智能更新让 Alphabet 创下近三个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者对谷歌母公司的人工智能更新（包括向所有美国用户推出 "人工智能模式"）表示欢迎，Alphabet 股价周四大涨 4%，连续第二天上涨。【原文：Alphabet shares jumped 4% on Thursday, rising for a second straight day, as investors cheered the Google parent's artificial intelligence updates including the rolling out of "AI Mode" to all its U.S. users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/alphabet-hits-near-three-month-high-new-ai-updates-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYA4FIJ73NIT5K7WETYXJETJYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[众议院预算法案有效扼杀了美国清洁能源的蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[众议院预算法案在周四清晨的投票中以微弱优势获得通过，该法案将有效遏制美国因 2022 年颁布的税收减免政策而掀起的清洁能源生产热潮。【原文：The House budget bill that narrowly passed in an early morning vote on Thursday would effectively put the brakes on a clean energy production boom in the United States spurred by tax credits enacted in 2022.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/house-budget-bill-effectively-kills-us-clean-energy-boom-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJXXXVXW4VJ27GENYHCIPI6XAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥经济增长乏力，五月通胀率上升，为经济敲响警钟]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，分析人士对墨西哥经济敲响了警钟，因为新数据显示墨西哥第一季度经济增长乏力，而通胀率今年首次飙升至央行目标范围之外。【原文：Analysts sounded alarms over Mexico's economy on Thursday after new data showed feeble growth in the first quarter while inflation spiked outside the central bank's target range for the first time this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-inflation-rises-past-central-bank-target-early-may-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMTON4QX7NOITMAVIALH7XQDAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:51:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[律师称美国应就 737 MAX 欺诈案起诉波音公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些遇难者家属的律师说，美国司法部应就两起致命的 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故引发的刑事欺诈案对波音公司进行审判，并拒绝接受允许该飞机制造商免于起诉的临时协议。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department should take Boeing to trial in a criminal fraud case stemming from two fatal 737 MAX crashes and reject a tentative deal to allow the planemaker to avoid prosecution, a lawyer for some of the victims' families said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-should-take-boeing-trial-737-max-fraud-case-lawyer-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEAXCO3FEVNWTNGR7GVM2F72L4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国有望在贝莱德气候案中支持共和党各州的观点]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，美国联邦反垄断执法人员预计将于周四对共和党各州提出的指控资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock）、先锋（Vanguard）和道富（State Street）通过气候激进主义合谋减少煤炭产量的论点表示支持。【原文：U.S. federal antitrust enforcers were expected to express support on Thursday for arguments wielded by Republican states that accuse asset managers BlackRock , Vanguard and State Street of conspiring through climate activism to decrease coal output, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-expected-support-republican-states-argument-blackrock-climate-case-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XK5F4YBLIROOFJNG5QPOWVKDHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：七国集团草案承诺应对全球经济 "过度失衡]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周四援引一份公报草案报道称，七国集团财政部长和央行行长承诺解决全球经济 "过度失衡 "问题。【原文：Finance ministers and central bank governors from the Group of Seven nations pledged to address "excessive imbalances" in the global economy, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing a draft communique.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/g7-draft-pledges-tackling-excessive-imbalances-global-economy-bloomberg-news-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FU7U4477PNIDLNHUDDVCCLYBBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[发动机供应商赛峰集团称波音已恢复 "动态 "生产模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音737 MAX客机发动机制造商和主要供应商赛峰集团（Safran）负责人周四表示，在经历了多年737 MAX客机受挫的不确定性之后，美国飞机制造商波音公司已经恢复了更具 "活力 "的生产计划。【原文：U.S. planemaker Boeing has returned to a more "dynamic" production profile after years of uncertainty surrounding setbacks to its 737 MAX passenger jet, the head of engine maker and key Boeing supplier Safran said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-back-dynamic-production-mode-engine-supplier-safran-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2O6P7ZCNVBMDNPLPXC6MRVKFCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>