<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 15:35:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 15:35:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[密歇根大学称 11 月美国消费者信心指数上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，11月初美国消费者情绪升至七个月来的最高点，衡量家庭对未来预期的指标升至三年多来的最高点。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment rose to a seven-month high in early November, with a measure of households' expectations for the future climbing to the highest in more than three years, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-rises-november-umich-says-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PSDNMMDOVIVZMQJSHW2GM7SNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 15:25:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，欧洲央行推动瑞丰银行和联合信贷银行持有俄罗斯风险资本]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，欧洲中央银行正在推动莱弗森银行和联合信贷银行持有部分资本，以缓冲其俄罗斯业务带来的潜在风险。【原文：The European Central Bank is pushing Raiffeisen and UniCredit to hold some capital as a buffer against potential risks stemming from their Russia businesses, two sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecb-pushes-raiffeisen-unicredit-hold-capital-russia-risk-sources-say-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3GFHS6C5VPT5OPCAK5AAU55AA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 14:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NRG 能源公司第三季度核心利润超预期，上调全年预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，NRG 能源公司的第三季度核心利润超出预期，原因是其服务区域的供应成本降低，并上调了 2024 年的利润展望，使其股价在收盘前上涨超过 3%。【原文：NRG Energy beat third-quarter core profit estimates on Friday due to lower supply costs across its service territories, and raised its 2024 profit outlook, sending its shares up over 3% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nrg-energy-posts-q3-core-profit-beat-raises-annual-forecast-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPQ5ZHMICNOODJ4ZU3PJVG5VD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:51:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PNC 新增 5 亿美元投资，加倍推进分行扩张计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[PNC 银行周五表示，将增加 5 亿美元的分行扩张投资，开设 100 多家新分行，翻新 200 家现有分行，加倍努力通过实体网点接触客户。【原文：PNC Bank said on Friday it will increase its investment in branch expansion by an additional $500 million to open over 100 new locations and renovate 200 existing ones, doubling down on efforts to reach customers through physical locations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/pnc-doubles-down-branch-expansion-plan-with-additional-500-mln-investment-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOV5PC323BO37CFUISH2DZSTDA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:51:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球货币市场基金因选举谨慎而大量流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月6日的一周内，全球货币市场基金吸引了大量资金流入，原因是投资者在美国总统大选和美联储政策会议前寻求安全。【原文：Global money market funds attracted sharp inflows in the week to Nov. 6 as investors sought safety ahead of the U.S. presidential election and the Federal Reserve's policy meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMV2O7MMB5MGFK6NJVFIWC43JQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲银行迎接特朗普 2.0 带来的更激烈竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲银行要缩小与美国竞争对手的盈利差距，面临着更加艰巨的任务，因为华尔街正等待着唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）再次担任总统后放松金融监管的新时代。【原文：European banks face an even tougher task to close an earnings gap on U.S. rivals, as Wall Street awaits a new era of financial deregulation under a second Donald Trump presidency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/europes-banks-brace-tougher-competition-under-trump-20-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWL6MVXJGVNCFM5RFGKH34HPQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:32:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大选前美国货币市场基金需求旺盛]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月6日的一周内，美国投资者将大量资金转移到安全的货币市场基金，因为他们在谨慎地等待美国总统大选结果和美联储的政策决定。【原文：U.S. investors moved large amounts of money to the safety of money market funds in the week to Nov. 6 as they cautiously awaited the U.S. presidential election outcome and the Federal Reserve's policy decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-money-market-funds-saw-significant-demand-before-us-elections-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUEPZKICENNKBJBD3SIPVWDRAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:21:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加剧内斗阻碍欧盟提升竞争力]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普在大选获胜前不久警告说，27 国集团将不得不为没有购买足够的美国出口产品而 "付出巨大代价"。【原文：Trump warned shortly before his election victory that the 27-nation bloc will have to "pay a big price" for not buying enough American exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-adds-internal-strife-hindering-eu-competitiveness-push-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CJSJZ2OFJOAFLXEJYTSSEC3L4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第三季度利润不佳，预期下调，CNH 工业股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于需求疲软和经销商库存需求减少，这家农用和建筑设备制造商第三季度利润未达预期，并下调了 2024 年的利润预期。【原文：Shares of CNH Industrial fell more than 10% premarket on Friday, after the farm and construction equipment maker missed third-quarter profit estimates and cut its 2024 profit forecast due to weak demand and reduced dealer inventory requirements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cnh-industrial-shares-fall-after-third-quarter-profit-miss-forecast-cut-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOJA7HMJVZNX3BWAOVUA47IC3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 12:46:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国最新刺激政策低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，希望中国宣布为正在准备迎接唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）再次担任总统的经济提供额外财政缓冲的投资者们失望了。【原文：Investors hoping China would announce extra fiscal buffers for an economy girding for another Donald Trump presidency were disappointed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-latest-stimulus-falls-short-expectations-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R33UVAEGYVKJ5ATXF5HV4AALUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 12:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司因票房疲软、有线电视业务下滑而未能实现销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司周五公布的季度营收不及预期，原因是票房缺乏爆款以及有线电视业务的下滑抵消了其流媒体服务在 NFL 内容回归后好于预期的用户增长。【原文：Paramount Global missed quarterly revenue estimates on Friday as a lack of big hits at the box office and declines in its cable business outweighed better-than-expected subscriber growth at its streaming service after the return of NFL content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-global-misses-revenue-estimates-weak-box-office-cable-tv-declines-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBFJPYRZQRO6JL2FPLJYCH242E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 12:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宜家报告利润增加，尽管降价导致收入减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大家具品牌宜家家居（Inter IKEA）的所有者报告称，尽管在 BILLY 书柜等一系列产品降价后收入急剧下降，但由于利息支出减少，2024 年的利润增加了。【原文：Inter IKEA, the owner of the world's biggest furniture brand, reported higher profits for 2024 thanks to lower interest payments, despite a sharp decline in revenues after it cut prices across its range of products like BILLY bookcases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ikea-reports-higher-profit-despite-revenue-hit-price-cuts-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSL6RQJUENOXHDNWXRSXNNBZOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 12:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管金价高企，历峰集团仍对提高珠宝价格持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，历峰集团高管表示，尽管近几个月来黄金价格飙升，但卡地亚的所有者历峰集团计划在提高珠宝价格方面坚持谨慎的态度，目前还没有计划在未来几个月内提价。【原文：Cartier owner Richemont plans to stick to its cautious approach to raising prices of jewellery despite the soaring price of gold in recent months, and has no plans yet for price increases in the upcoming months, executives said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/richemont-remains-cautious-raising-jewellery-prices-despite-high-gold-prices-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZSXDNNOJRNB7KNXFEJUYYBKYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 11:32:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社/益普索民调显示，大多数美国人预计特朗普将增加美国债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社/益普索（Reuters/Ipsos）最新民调显示，大多数美国人认为当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将在新任期内把美国政府推向更深的债务困境，尽管大多数共和党人并不像民主党人那样对他的财政管理感到担忧。【原文：Most Americans believe President-elect Donald Trump will push the U.S. government deeper into debt in his new term, though most Republicans do not share Democrats' concerns over his fiscal stewardship, according to a new Reuters/Ipsos poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/most-americans-expect-trump-increase-us-debt-reutersipsos-poll-finds-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP5LBFBB3VM5TCT4LUC27ITZOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 11:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间交易大选后华尔街因美联储减息和中国刺激而繁荣]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPHNIM4DFZNRPCSAATR4LZ3JWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 11:08:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛将为独立驾驶员提供新的节日奖金，与亚马逊一决高下]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛告诉路透社，该零售商将向独立送货司机支付新的经济奖励，鼓励他们在假日期间到美国商店收取在线订单并将其送到购物者手中。【原文：Walmart will pay independent delivery drivers new financial incentives to pick up online orders at its U.S. stores and deliver them to shoppers during the holiday season, the retailer told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-offer-independent-drivers-new-holiday-bonuses-battle-with-amazon-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">663CIELNANMIXBYU2XLAQOCALU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 11:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，台积电将从下周一起暂停为中国生产先进的人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引三位知情人士的话报道称，台湾半导体制造公司已通知中国芯片设计公司，从下周一起暂停生产其先进的人工智能芯片。【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company has notified Chinese chip design companies that it is suspending production of their advanced AI chips from Monday, Financial Times reported on Friday, citing three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/tsmc-suspend-production-advanced-ai-chips-china-monday-ft-reports-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O42PCYLFOBOPHH4DTQFTMQFGJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 11:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司第三季度利润增至 2.07 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）在周五提交的一份证券文件中称，该公司第三季度调整后净利润从去年同期的 1.67 亿雷亚尔飙升至 11.8 亿雷亚尔（约合 2.073 亿美元）。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer's third-quarter adjusted net profit soared to 1.18 billion reais ($207.30 million) from 167 million reais a year earlier, it said in a securities filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazilian-planemaker-embraers-third-quarter-profit-soars-207-mln-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMAL26E3TZIIBCRSM2MQLS2PAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:41:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 中国提高地方政府债务上限以振兴经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最高立法机构周五批准了一项法案，允许地方政府在三年内发行6万亿元人民币（约合8,388亿美元）债券，用于置换表外债务或 "隐性 "债务，以刺激疲软的经济。【原文：China top legislative body approved a bill on Friday to allow local governments to issue 6 trillion yuan ($838.8 billion) in bonds to swap for off-balance sheet or "hidden" debt over three years, as policymakers sought to spur the sluggish economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/view-china-raises-local-government-debt-ceilings-revive-economy-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5I4QPNDRNOSJAB2NIWKFJNJJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[结交新朋友，促进招聘：中国芯片业计划如何应对特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）担任美国总统后的四年里，中国的半导体行业正在加紧采购外国芯片制造设备，并寻找机会聘用海外人才和建立新的联盟，从而为未来四年的战斗做好准备。【原文：China's semiconductor industry is readying itself for four more combative years under Donald Trump as U.S. president by ramping up purchases of foreign chipmaking equipment and looking out for opportunities to hire overseas talent and forge new alliances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/make-new-friends-boost-hiring-how-chinas-chip-industry-plans-deal-with-trump-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKI5VYVOUBO2HLNVTM627ORNM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:12:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[成本上升导致新加坡航空公司半年利润减少近一半]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡航空公司（SIA）周五公布的半年报显示，利润同比减少近一半，反映出市场竞争加剧，加上燃油成本和费用增加。【原文：Singapore Airlines (SIA) reported a half-year profit on Friday that nearly halved year-on-year, reflecting intensifying market competition coupled with higher fuel costs and expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/singapore-airlines-posts-slump-half-year-profit-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSUENSLOSZPWTLWZJN65AZOF6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金发女郎不在了？新兴市场在特朗普治下前途未卜]]></title><description><![CDATA[在全球加息多年之后，投资者希望新兴市场在 2025 年迎来 "金鸡独立 "的时刻，但在唐纳德-特朗普即将重返白宫之前，投资者正面临着巨大的不确定性。【原文：Investors hoping for a "Goldilocks" moment for emerging markets in 2025 following years of global interest rate hikes are grappling with significant uncertainty ahead of Donald Trump's impending return to the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/is-goldilocks-gone-emerging-markets-face-uncertain-path-under-trump-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTQZIJKT7NNH3DMZQVWX67JEN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:27:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国钢铁企业准备应对特朗普关税的间接打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国钢铁业已经在产能过剩和国内需求疲软的困境中挣扎，如果美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对中国商品（如用合金制造的制成品）征收 60% 的关税，中国钢铁业将面临间接打击。【原文：China's steel industry, already struggling with overcapacity and weak domestic demand, faces an indirect hit if U.S. President-elect Donald Trump pursues 60% tariffs on Chinese goods such as manufactured items made from the alloy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-steelmakers-gird-indirect-trump-tariffs-hit-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7AOAJ7455JKBJC27FJZNL37MM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔 500 指数期货突破 6000 点大关，股市因特朗普获胜而走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，追踪基准 S&amp;P 500 指数的期货交易突破了 6000 点大关，股市在唐纳德-特朗普重新夺回美国总统宝座和美联储降息的这一周中以乐观的态势收尾。【原文：Futures tracking the benchmark S&amp;P 500 were trading above the 6,000-point mark on Friday, with equity markets set for an upbeat end to an action-packed week that saw Donald Trump recapture the U.S. presidency and the Federal Reserve cut rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sp-500-futures-cross-6000-mark-equities-ride-higher-trumps-victory-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMTJ6AARXNIILIAJHKFDJMLZSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[东南亚为逃离特朗普对华关税的工厂做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[该地区的工业园区开发商表示，由于预计唐纳德-特朗普重掌白宫后将对中国政府征收高额关税，企业纷纷将工厂从中国迁往东南亚。【原文：Companies have been moving factories from China to Southeast Asia, anticipating Donald Trump would slap high tariffs on Beijing if he regained the White House, a move set to accelerate with his election win, industrial park developers in the region say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/southeast-asia-prepares-factories-fleeing-trump-tariffs-china-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2HXWRUP7ZOWXCQI3KMQGKDDLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄牙目标 2025 年出售 TAP 航空公司，超过 12 家潜在买家表现出兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[葡萄牙基础设施部长表示，葡萄牙政府计划在 2025 年恢复出售国旗航空公司葡萄牙航空（TAP），此前已有十多家潜在买家对此表示出兴趣。【原文：Portugal's government plans to resume the sale of flag carrier TAP in 2025, the country's infrastructure minister said, after receiving interest from more than a dozen potential buyers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/portugal-targets-2025-tap-sale-more-than-12-potential-buyers-show-interest-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4ITXTFF6NNGLORCOZGGX23HLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 08:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[历峰集团预计，随着大选不确定性的消除，美国市场将回暖]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周总统大选投票后，大选前的不确定性已经消除，历峰集团在美国的业务可能会得到提振，但现在就断言唐纳德-特朗普可能提高关税会对这家奢侈品公司产生怎样的影响还为时尚早。【原文：Richemont's U.S. business could get a boost now that pre-election uncertainty following this week's presidential poll is out of the way, although it is too early to say how possible tariff hikes under Donald Trump would affect the luxury company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/richemont-expects-pick-up-us-with-election-uncertainty-now-out-way-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56DJZAJY55LXXCY2AG7ZDVMJR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 08:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国、英国和瑞典纷纷降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国、英国和瑞典本周都下调了利率，尽管唐纳德-特朗普赢得美国大选带来了新的不确定性因素，因为有可能提高关税。【原文：The United States, Britain and Sweden all cut interest rates this week, even as Donald Trump's U.S. election win introduced a fresh element of uncertainty given the threat of higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/global-markets-central-banks-graphic-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52XHJS5LYFJCRF23RPPGHYZFTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 08:19:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国通过地方政府债务置换启动 1.4 万亿美元财政支持计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，中国启动了新一轮财政支持计划，以缓解地方政府的偿债压力，同时财政部长蓝佛安也表示将采取进一步的刺激措施。【原文：China kicked off a fresh round of fiscal support on Friday for its sputtering economy with a package that eases debt repayment strains for local governments, with Finance Minister Lan Foan signalling further stimulus in the pipeline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-unveils-steps-tackle-hidden-debt-local-goverments-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XKJVT7325N6LHEYBTZMNEYMWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 08:18:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰的财政命运突然与特朗普的经济议程联系在一起]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）兑现选前承诺，那么爱尔兰独特的低税收商业模式对美国的影响可能会使其公共财政面临重大风险。【原文：The unique exposure of Ireland's low-tax business model to the United States could place its public finances at significant risk under a Donald Trump presidency - if he follows through on pre-election promises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/irelands-fiscal-fortunes-suddenly-tied-trumps-economic-agenda-2024-11-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWDAKH5J2JJM3IHRZAEEOUGH4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 07:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>