<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:06:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:06:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[尽管有特朗普的命令，但放弃 DEI 可能会让公司陷入法律纠纷]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家表示，那些为避免特朗普政府审查而缩减工作场所多元化努力的美国公司，可能会使自己面临更多工人歧视诉讼。【原文：U.S. companies that scale back workplace diversity efforts to avoid scrutiny from the Trump administration may be exposing themselves to more discrimination lawsuits by workers, experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/despite-trump-order-abandoning-dei-could-land-companies-legal-trouble-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7VQHKB7QZLYVOA2VCWMDW6WWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月消费者信心下滑；12 个月通胀预期上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对劳动力市场的担忧，以及如果唐纳德-特朗普总统的新政府继续推进对进口商品征收关税的计划，商品价格可能会上涨，美国消费者情绪在1月份出现了六个月来的首次疲软。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment weakened in January for the first time in six months amid worries about the labor market and potential higher prices for goods if President Donald Trump's new administration presses ahead with planned tariffs on imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-ebbs-january-12-month-inflation-expectations-rise-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXSOQTX5LZLC3BUKDLTFBMUKVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:45:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马与中国电动汽车制造商一起向欧盟法院提起关税诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[据欧盟法院网站上的一份文件显示，宝马已联合中国生产商向欧盟法院（CJEU）提起诉讼，反对欧盟对中国生产的电动汽车（EV）征收关税。【原文：BMW has joined Chinese producers in filing a challenge at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) against EU tariffs on China-made electric vehicles (EVs), according to a filing on the court's website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-joins-chinese-ev-makers-filing-eu-court-challenge-tariffs-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PO3BQMOXGRI5NI2J7YGSNI43NM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Venture Global 股票开盘价可能比首次公开发行价高出最多 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Global LNG 的股票周五在纽约证券交易所首次开盘时将比发行价高出 6%。【原文：Venture Global LNG's shares were set to open up to 6% above their offer price in their debut on the New York Stock Exchange on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/venture-global-shares-likely-open-up-6-above-ipo-price-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICESV7DBEBM5ZAUC54UXGLHACQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:29:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月成屋销售升至 10 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国现房销售在 12 月份增至 10 个月来的最高点，但进一步的增长可能会受到抵押贷款利率和房价上涨的限制，这使得许多潜在购房者保持观望。【原文：U.S. existing home sales increased to a 10-month high in December, but further gains are likely to be limited by elevated mortgage rates and house prices, which are keeping many prospective buyers on the sidelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-existing-home-sales-rise-10-month-high-december-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I43XQJBOZVOUDK4ZQOKV6NHQAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际纸业公司获得欧盟批准，以 72 亿美元收购 DS Smith]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部设在美国的国际纸业公司以 58 亿英镑（72 亿美元）收购英国竞争对手 DS Smith，并承诺出售资产以解决竞争问题，获得欧盟批准。【原文：U.S.-based International Paper secured EU clearance for its 5.8-billion-pound ($7.2 billion) acquisition of UK rival DS Smith with a pledge to sell assets to address competition concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/international-paper-gains-eu-nod-72-bln-ds-smith-buy-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXWXVPCMPBKDJBODOLJ54YDNAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的首个政策举措让加密货币市场失去动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[即使在唐纳德-特朗普总统下令成立一个新的工作小组，负责提出新的加密货币规则并探索美国加密货币储备的可能性之后，加密货币市场周五仍保持稳定，低于近期高点。【原文：Crypto markets steadied on Friday, still holding below recent highs even after President Donald Trump ordered the creation of a new working group, tasked with proposing new crypto rules and exploring the possibility of a U.S. cryptocurrency stockpile.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-markets-lose-steam-after-trumps-first-policy-move-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJCQ6HQ6FRLDNB7X3OQAA6HO4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月商业活动创九个月新低；招聘加速]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于物价压力上升，1月份美国商业活动放缓至第九个月低点，但企业报告称增加了招聘，这支持了美联储今年降息的谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. business activity slowed to a ninth-month low in January amid rising price pressures, but firms reported boosting hiring, supporting the Federal Reserve's cautious approach to cutting interest rates this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-activity-nine-month-low-january-hiring-accelerates-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WKJTFGDHROPNO4ISVL3WBYFSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:51:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道OpenAI 面临印度全球出版商的新版权案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度图书出版商及其国际同行已在新德里对 OpenAI 提起版权诉讼，一位代表周五表示，这是一系列寻求阻止 ChatGPT 聊天机器人访问专有内容的全球案件中的最新一起。【原文：Indian book publishers and their international counterparts have filed a copyright lawsuit against OpenAI in New Delhi, a representative said on Friday, the latest in a series of global cases seeking to stop the ChatGPT chatbot accessing proprietary content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-faces-new-copyright-case-global-publishers-india-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJQ3PSC22JKRDA2N64BTQDJKBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:46:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府审查美国自动紧急制动规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家汽车安全机构周五表示，它正在重新考虑前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）政府制定的一项具有里程碑意义的规定，即要求到2029年，几乎所有的新车和卡车都必须配备先进的自动紧急制动系统。【原文：A U.S. auto safety agency said Friday it is reconsidering a landmark rule from the administration of former President Joe Biden requiring nearly all new cars and trucks by 2029 to have advanced automatic emergency braking systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-administration-reviewing-us-automatic-emergency-braking-rule-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I6UXF7CGRMOFENJQBIK7PAR3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美达今年资本支出投资高达 650 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 首席执行官马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）周五在 Facebook 发布的一篇文章中表示，2025 年将投资 600 亿至 650 亿美元用于资本支出。【原文：Meta Platforms will invest $60 billion to $65 billion in capital expenditure in 2025, CEO Mark Zuckerberg said in a Facebook post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-invest-up-65-bln-capital-expenditure-this-year-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ANT6UQ77VMJLOYHYO22IF7EYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:14:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta、TikTok 和 X 将加入欧盟对德国大选的压力测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟发言人周五表示，欧盟委员会将于下周对大型社交媒体平台进行压力测试，以了解这些平台在下月德国大选前是否采取了足够措施来应对虚假信息。【原文：The European Commission will hold a stress test with large social media platforms next week to see whether they have done enough to counter disinformation in the run-up to next month's German election, an EU spokesperson said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-tiktok-x-join-eu-stress-test-german-election-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GISKOCBLR5J4TJ3UGAKNPFXL54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AT&T 通过向 Reign Capital 出售-回租房地产获得 8.5 亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[AT&amp;T 周五表示，已通过向房地产开发公司 Reign Capital 售后回租其闲置的中央办公设施（容纳其传统铜缆网络）的方式，获得了 8.5 亿美元的资金。【原文：AT&amp;T said on Friday it has secured $850 million through the sale-leaseback of its underused central office facilities that house its legacy copper networks to real estate development firm Reign Capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/att-secures-850-mln-sale-leaseback-real-estate-reign-capital-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IU4RF7U2FM6HK36W4KZ64OJXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:23:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HCA 医疗保健公司预计 2025 年利润高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[HCA 医疗保健公司周五预测 2025 年的利润将高于预期，预计医疗程序的需求将增加，成本将降低。【原文：HCA Healthcare on Friday forecast 2025 profit above estimates, expecting elevated demand for medical procedures and lower costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hca-healthcare-forecasts-2025-profit-above-estimates-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QE7GPP3ISZJQTC7ERY4UFEI73Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普商务部主管人选霍华德-卢特尼克公布财务信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的商务部领导人选霍华德-卢特尼克周五在参议院举行听证会确认他担任商务部领导之前，披露了他的财务控股和资产情况。【原文：Howard Lutnick, President Donald Trump's nominee to lead the Commerce Department, on Friday disclosed his financial holdings and assets ahead of a Senate hearing to confirm him for the role.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/howard-lutnick-trumps-pick-run-commerce-department-releases-financial-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3URWZ34ZVP7BFYZX4YTBAHRIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Signify 首席执行官表示，可以应对美国可能征收的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰照明公司 Signify 首席执行官周五表示，预计美国可能征收的新进口关税不会对公司造成很大的财务影响。【原文：Dutch lighting company Signify does not expect a big financial impact from possible new U.S. import tariffs, its chief executive said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/signify-can-cope-with-possible-us-tariffs-ceo-says-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTI67HJV3BIZHAGCRVPAQRFY2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+尚未对特朗普呼吁降低油价做出反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+"尚未对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普要求降低油价的呼吁做出反应，该组织的代表指出，已经制定了一项计划，从四月份开始提高石油产量。【原文：OPEC+ has yet to react to a call from U.S. President Donald Trump for lower oil prices, with delegates from the group pointing to a plan already in place to start raising oil output from April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-yet-react-trump-call-lower-oil-prices-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKJ7RYQMO5IRJGLCHS4VQGAJOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IPO 市场卷土重来：近期美国主要上市公司业绩如何]]></title><description><![CDATA[在商业友好型的唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫、利率下降和股市风险情绪重燃的推动下，美国首次公开募股市场预计将在2025年迎来井喷。【原文：The U.S. IPO market is expected to see a blowout 2025, fueled by the return of business-friendly Donald Trump to the White House, declining interest rates and a renewed risk-on sentiment in equity markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ipo-market-comeback-how-recent-major-us-listings-fared-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYFI3BHHUBJ3FOPYE3FXPEVQGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:47:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行力推数字欧元以应对特朗普的加密货币政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行董事会成员皮埃罗-西波隆（Piero Cipollone）周五表示，欧元区银行需要一种数字欧元来应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普推动推广稳定币（一种通常与美元挂钩的加密货币）的举措。【原文：Euro zone banks need a digital euro to respond to U.S. President Donald Trump's push to promote stablecoins, a type of cryptocurrency typically pegged to the U.S. dollar, European Central Bank board member Piero Cipollone said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ecb-pitches-digital-euro-response-trumps-crypto-push-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGCNGGUK4VNAVM2WRZ4K4UOY7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:42:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于 5G 支出巨大，Verizon 预测年度自由现金流和利润均将下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，威瑞森通信公司（Verizon Communications）预测年度自由现金流和利润将低于华尔街预期，因为这家美国电信巨头斥巨资扩大高速互联网服务，并在日趋饱和的无线市场上吸引客户。【原文：Verizon Communications forecast annual free cash flow and profit below Wall Street estimates on Friday, as the U.S. telecom major spends heavily to expand high-speed internet services and attract customers in a saturating wireless market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/verizon-forecasts-downbeat-annual-free-cash-flow-profit-heavy-5g-spending-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KGARIAACJMKZCI7ZZ3KGD63ZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[假日消费旺季使美国运通利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国运通公布第四季度利润大增 12%，原因是假日期间有更多消费者刷卡旅游和网购。【原文：American Express reported a 12% jump in fourth-quarter profit on Friday, as more consumers swiped cards during the holiday season for travel and online shopping.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/amex-profit-jumps-resilient-credit-card-spending-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UU6K6UEMWZO5TD4A3EX2VKV7QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investcorp 可能考虑在 3-5 年内上市，着眼于美国的退休储蓄]]></title><description><![CDATA[Investcorp 副董事长周五表示，Investcorp 可能考虑在未来三到五年内公开上市，这家中东最大的另类投资公司的目标是将其管理资产翻一番，达到 1,000 亿美元。【原文：Investcorp could consider a public listing in the next three to five years, its vice chairman said on Friday, as the Middle East's biggest alternative investment firm targets a doubling of its assets under management to $100 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investcorp-could-consider-listing-3-5-years-eyes-us-retirement-savings-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDZC7FU2IBMPLLXSI3574ZHOXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:37:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政策的不确定性导致期货下跌；等待数据和收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于唐纳德-特朗普总统贸易政策的不确定性占据上风，同时投资者也在等待可能揭示经济状况的数据和企业财报，美国股指期货周五下跌。【原文：U.S. stock index futures dipped on Friday, as uncertainty about President Donald Trump's trade policies prevailed, while investors also awaited data and corporate earnings reports that could throw light on the state of the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-dip-trump-policy-uncertainty-data-earnings-awaited-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHHPW2VPLRMJXEGPGB64VUVQCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:26:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国举报人称万事达卡和维萨卡未能阻止为 OnlyFans 上的儿童性虐待材料付款]]></title><description><![CDATA[万事达卡和威士卡未能阻止它们的支付网络对热门网站 OnlyFans 上的儿童性虐待材料和性交易收益进行洗钱，据此前未披露的举报人向美国财政部金融犯罪部门提交的指控称。【原文：Mastercard and Visa failed to stop their payment networks from laundering proceeds from child sexual abuse material and sex trafficking on the popular website OnlyFans, according to allegations in a previously undisclosed whistleblower complaint filed with the U.S. Treasury’s financial crimes unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-whistleblower-says-mastercard-visa-failed-stop-payments-child-sex-abuse-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BI56BC5GX5JMLHASJH6QXRXDZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球风险投资公司首次亮相，测试特朗普政策转向后的能源 IPO 胃口]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Global LNG 将于本周五首次公开募股，其首次公开募股估值大幅降低至 605 亿美元，但仍将成为美国最大的上市能源公司之一。【原文：Venture Global LNG will debut on public markets on Friday after sharply lowering its IPO valuation to $60.5 billion, but still set to be one of the largest U.S.-listed energy companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/venture-global-debut-test-appetite-energy-ipos-after-trumps-policy-pivot-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y7I4AYWORJMBKWWBPGDZ5I3HI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[进入特朗普新时代，美国立法者对加密货币态度冷淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府有望迎来加密货币的繁荣时期，但路透社的一项调查显示，即将上任的国会议员中很少有人投资比特币或其他数字货币。【原文：President Donald Trump’s administration is expected to usher in a boom time for crypto but a Reuters review shows very few members of the incoming congress are invested in bitcoin or other digital currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-lawmakers-are-light-crypto-heading-into-new-trump-era-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKNJZMDU5RK7DKHWKWULVPKZ5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美联储降息观点将考验美股反弹势头]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储将于下周召开的 2025 年首次会议将对美国股市的回升构成考验，因为投资者将衡量未来几个月更有利于股市的降息幅度。【原文：The Federal Reserve's first meeting of 2025 in the coming week stands to test the resurgence in U.S. stocks as investors gauge the extent of more equity-friendly interest rate cuts in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-feds-rate-cut-view-set-test-resurgent-us-stocks-rally-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVMRQDU4QVIJFLFYFDMDOGKJNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：航空航天供应商争相缓解特朗普关税迫在眉睫的打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大直升机零部件供应商 Optima Aero 已经开始将库存转移到边境以南，以尽量降低美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提出的潜在关税风险。【原文：Canadian helicopter parts supplier Optima Aero is already moving inventory south of the border to minimize the risk from potential tariffs proposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aerospace-suppliers-scramble-cushion-blow-looming-trump-tariffs-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXGQR566W5KEBBWD2VWPSI2N2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 日本央行加息、欧元区经济增长、人民币升值，美元大幅下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWZ2L66YIZNNBESDE4QARNAVMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储暂时按兵不动，关注就业强劲和通胀放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[在 12 月份的上次会议上，美国联邦储备委员会的官员们担心通胀率会超过 2% 的目标，并目睹了就业岗位的增加在似乎正在出现的下滑中摇摆不定。【原文：At their last meeting in December, U.S. Federal Reserve officials were worried about inflation getting stuck above their 2% target and had watched job gains seesaw in what seemed an emerging decline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-hold-now-eyes-strong-jobs-easing-inflation-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VIGOBCIGZRPGRKZY7EV43L34KE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>