<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:05:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:05:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国旨在禁止在海底电信电缆中使用中国技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（Federal Communications Commission）周三表示，计划通过相关规定，禁止公司将包含中国技术或设备的海底通信电缆连接到美国。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission said on Wednesday it plans to adopt rules to bar companies from connecting undersea submarine communication cables to the United States that include Chinese technology or equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-aims-ban-chinese-technology-submarine-cables-ft-reports-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWJ5URMKHFJ6DBBVSRXM6CX54M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:24:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储称美国经济活动增长但前景悲观]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三表示，最近几周美国经济活动略有增长，但前景为中性至略微悲观，因为企业报告称特朗普政府提高关税给价格带来了上涨压力。【原文：U.S. economic activity increased slightly in recent weeks, but the outlook was neutral to slightly pessimistic, the Federal Reserve said on Wednesday, as businesses reported the Trump administration's higher tariffs were putting upward pressure on prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economic-activity-up-outlook-pessimistic-fed-says-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SQFFLSWEFIU3DBMBON3GOS2GQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:21:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国将坚持对日本征收 25% 的关税，可能很快与印度达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普继周二宣布与印尼达成协议后，周三又表示，美国很可能将与日本就关税问题 "照章办事"，并可能与印度达成另一项贸易协议。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Wednesday the U.S. will probably "live by the letter" on tariffs with Japan and may have another trade deal coming up with India, following his announcement of an accord with Indonesia on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/trump-says-us-will-stick-25-tariff-japan-may-have-deal-with-india-soon-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UE2H2HIRO5OTHODLK2TYS3BJNI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普团队因宗教原因放宽联邦雇员在家办公禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周三表示，联邦雇员可以获准在家工作或调整工作时间，以适应宗教斋戒和祈祷的需要，此前政府曾要求工人全时到办公室报到。【原文：Federal employees can get permission to work from home or adjust their hours to accommodate religious fasts and prayers, the Trump administration said on Wednesday, after previously demanding that workers report to offices full time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/trump-team-relaxes-work-from-home-ban-federal-employees-religious-reasons-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDYQUIMBBFIDNATH4RW3WBGJ7Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司明年开始在美国工厂生产中型 SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典沃尔沃汽车公司周三表示，将从2026年底开始在美国南卡罗来纳州的工厂生产XC60中型SUV。【原文：Sweden's Volvo Cars said on Wednesday it would start producing its XC60 mid-size SUV in its plant in South Carolina, United States from late 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-start-mid-size-suv-production-us-plant-next-year-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PKV3ADJYJKSVB4YOVF5W3MTMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的 "世界自由 "加密代币将可交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界自由金融公司（World Liberty Financial）是唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）家族的加密企业之一，该公司发行的数字代币的持有者周三投票决定让这些代币可以交易，为它们的广泛销售和购买铺平了道路--这有可能提升总统所持代币的价值。【原文：Holders of the digital tokens issued by World Liberty Financial, one of the crypto ventures of the family of Donald Trump, voted on Wednesday to make them tradeable, paving the way for their wide sale and purchase -- potentially boosting the value of the president's holdings of them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-world-liberty-crypto-tokens-become-tradable-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGYNH5C7NBJDHM2M7IPYGAGUZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:53:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗聘请摩根大通资深银行家加强融资业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周三看到的一份内部备忘录，花旗集团已从摩根大通聘请了两名高级管理人员，以加强其领导团队并拓展融资业务。【原文：Citigroup has hired two senior executives from JPMorgan to strengthen its leadership team and expand its financing business, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-hires-senior-jpmorgan-bankers-strengthen-financing-business-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXQ4RN4WWRM5DCIMA2CXFMFKYU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:39:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 NDTV 报道，印度航空公司完成波音 787 飞机燃油控制开关检查，未发现问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度广播公司 NDTV 周三援引一位官员的话说，印度航空公司已经完成了对波音 787 飞机燃油控制开关的检查，没有发现任何问题。【原文：Air India has completed the inspection of fuel control switches on Boeing 787 planes with no issues being found, Indian broadcaster NDTV said on Wednesday, citing an official.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-india-completes-fuel-control-switches-inspection-boeing-787-planes-no-issues-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBOTNQSEKZP4FHFFCUWSRAWO74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德克萨斯州调查 M&M 制造商玛氏公司抵制去除合成染料的情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[得克萨斯州总检察长周三表示，他已开始调查玛氏公司，该公司生产 M&amp;M's 和 Skittles 糖果，据称该公司拒绝从其产品中去除合成食品染料。【原文：Texas' attorney general said on Wednesday he has begun investigating Mars, which makes M&amp;M's and Skittles candies, for its alleged refusal to remove synthetic food dyes from its products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/texas-probes-mm-maker-mars-resistance-removing-synthetic-dyes-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QU3XATWJZMOHHEAWDMJ2BIBLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院通过加密货币立法的程序性障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党控制的美国众议院周三通过了一项关键的程序性障碍，为几项加密货币法案的可能通过创造了条件，而就在一天前，唐纳德-特朗普总统还出面挽救了这一举措。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives cleared a key procedural hurdle Wednesday, setting the stage for likely passage of several cryptocurrency bills a day after President Donald Trump intervened to save the initiative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-house-clears-procedural-hurdle-cryptocurrency-legislation-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTJIQVD2GBO6XL7AS7BUFAPZAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:27:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，英国 NCC 集团考虑出售网络安全部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻周三援引消息人士的话报道，总部位于英国的全球网络安全专家 NCC 集团已开始进行战略审查，可能会出售其主要的网络安全部门。【原文：UK-based global cybersecurity specialist NCC Group has begun a strategic review that could entail a sale of its primary cybersecurity division, Sky News reported on Wednesday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uks-ncc-group-weighs-sale-cybersecurity-arm-sky-news-reports-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5X6H4Y7D5ROC5ARHZOZNBHLA7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提高关税后，巴西敦促与美国进行贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布自8月起对巴西商品征收50%的关税后，巴西周三敦促美国对其5月提交的贸易提案作出回应，重申巴西对达成一项 "双方都能接受的 "协议持开放态度。【原文：Brazil on Wednesday urged the U.S. to respond to a trade proposal submitted in May, reaffirming its openness to a "mutually acceptable" deal after U.S. President Donald Trump announced a 50% tariff on Brazilian goods starting in August.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-urges-trade-talks-with-us-after-trump-tariff-hike-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RB2R72SWJ5JIJBXXATUT742WVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:48:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在全球范围内对涉嫌与俄罗斯有关联的黑客发出七张逮捕令]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国和西班牙对一个亲俄黑客组织的七名嫌疑成员发出逮捕令，该组织被指控对关键基础设施、军火制造商、电力公司和公共当局实施网络攻击。【原文：Germany and Spain issued arrest warrants for seven suspected members of a pro-Russian hacking group accused of carrying out cyber attacks against critical infrastructure, arms makers, power companies and public authorities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/seven-arrest-warrants-issued-global-swoop-suspected-russia-linked-hackers-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCFJUB6C2FMN3HE3FCMRHQE5FQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡尼称美国尚未达成对加拿大有利的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周三表示，解决与软木木材相关的问题是正在进行的与美国贸易谈判的重中之重，但一项有利于加拿大工人的协议尚未摆上桌面。【原文：Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney on Wednesday said working through issues related to softwood lumber is a top priority in ongoing trade negotiations with the U.S., but a deal that works for Canadian workers isn't yet on the table.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carney-says-us-deal-that-works-canada-isnt-table-yet-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNWE7Y2CEJJ3DHUSYRUX5KB74U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trendyol、Baykar 首席执行官、ADQ 和蚂蚁国际将在土耳其开发金融科技平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其 Trendyol 集团、Baykar 首席执行官 Haluk Bayraktar、阿布扎比主权基金 ADQ 和蚂蚁金服国际公司周三表示，已同意探讨在土耳其成立一家提供数字金融服务的潜在金融科技合资企业。【原文：Turkey's Trendyol Group, Baykar CEO Haluk Bayraktar, Abu Dhabi’s sovereign fund ADQ and Ant International have agreed to explore a potential joint fintech venture offering digital financial services in Turkey, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/trendyol-baykar-ceo-adq-ant-international-develop-fintech-platform-turkey-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2MNUTR5VZMIPOR6FUXQE5WYG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:19:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局不考虑用马斯克的 "星链 "取代 L3Harris 和 Verizon 的合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局告诉立法者，它不考虑用埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX 公司的 Starlink 卫星部门取代目前与 L3Harris 或 Verizon Communications 公司签订的电信合同。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration told lawmakers it is not considering replacing its current telecommunication contracts it holds with L3Harris or Verizon Communications with Elon Musk's SpaceX's Starlink satellite unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-faa-not-considering-replacing-l3harris-verizon-contracts-with-musks-starlink-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQLJQWJJ3VOHJJ4ZDBQPWYFHYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:13:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 在 Downdetector 报告全球大面积故障后调查错误原因]]></title><description><![CDATA[在 Downdetector.com 显示全球有超过 10 万用户报告了社交媒体平台的问题后，社交媒体平台 Reddit 表示正在调查错误率升高的问题。【原文：Social media platform Reddit said it was looking into elevated error rates, after Downdetector.com showed more than 100,000 users globally had reported issues with the social media platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/reddit-down-thousands-us-users-downdetector-shows-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SYGXHQWGRJCRFJFVCT2FNH5ZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易部长格里尔表示希望美国贸易逆差走下坡路]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周三表示，他的贸易政策目标是使美国1.2万亿美元的贸易逆差走上下降通道，并阻止美国先进制造业能力的流失。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Wednesday that his trade policy goal was to put the $1.2 trillion U.S. trade deficit on a downward path and to stem the loss of U.S. advanced manufacturing capacity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-trade-chief-greer-says-wants-us-trade-deficit-downward-path-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VV7J6RVUTVMVXIWQPTXAMKITKE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普对解雇美联储主席鲍威尔持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周三告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔持开放态度。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is open to the idea of firing Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, a source told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-open-idea-firing-fed-chair-powell-source-says-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSKZ4Q3SSJM6XHE7K7WRH6AWKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将解雇美联储主席鲍威尔的报道引发美元和国债价格暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社援引一位不愿透露姓名的白宫官员的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普很可能很快解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔，此后美元周三大幅下跌。【原文：The dollar fell sharply on Wednesday after Bloomberg, citing an unidentified White House official, reported U.S. President Donald Trump is likely to fire Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/view-dollar-treasury-prices-tumble-after-report-trump-fire-feds-powell-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAN77G5TP5MI3ITRN2R4Y4V7TU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员加大对美联储降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，唐纳德-特朗普总统可能很快解雇美联储杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell），交易商目前押注从9月开始降息，到12月至少再降息一次，此后美国短期利率期货周三上涨。【原文：Short-term U.S. interest-rate futures rose on Wednesday after a report that President Donald Trump is likely to fire Federal Reserve Jerome Powell soon, with traders now betting on rate cuts starting in September and at least one more by December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/traders-boost-bets-fed-rate-cuts-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUWTKWCMZVKYJHTT4BYOQJXASI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:50:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大宣布对进口钢铁征收新关税以保护国内产业]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周三表示，加拿大将对与之签订自由贸易协定的国家（美国除外）实行关税配额，以保护国内钢铁行业。加拿大还将在 7 月底前对从所有非美国国家进口的含有在中国熔化和浇铸的钢材的钢材征收 25% 的额外关税。【原文：Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney on Wednesday said that Canada will introduce a tariff rate quota for countries with which it has free trade agreements, excluding the United States, to protect the domestic steel industry. Canada will also implement additional tariffs of 25% on steel imports from all non-U.S. countries containing steel melted and poured in China before the end of July.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/canada-announces-new-tariff-measures-imported-steel-protect-domestic-industry-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRNJOGFC3RKERM5V6JTHWGAME4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前英国国家犯罪署官员因从暗网毒贩处窃取比特币而入狱]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国国家犯罪署的一名官员从非法暗网市场的经营者那里窃取了加密货币，周三被判处 5-1 年半监禁。【原文：An officer with Britain's National Crime Agency who stole cryptocurrency from the operator of an illegal dark web marketplace was jailed on Wednesday for 5-1/2 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/ex-uk-national-crime-agency-officer-jailed-stealing-bitcoin-dark-web-drug-dealer-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JGSVGTPQFJDDOCPVCNOJVTIPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发出关税威胁后，墨西哥计划加强与加拿大的贸易合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆周三表示，她已与加拿大总理马克-卡尼进行了交谈，双方同意加强贸易合作，特别是考虑到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于8月1日开始征收关税。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Wednesday that she had spoken with Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney and that the two had agreed to strengthen trade collaboration, particularly in light of the tariffs from U.S. President Donald Trump set to go in effect on August 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-plans-stronger-trade-collaboration-with-canada-after-trump-tariff-threats-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2S6MHXAP5OKZIO7HQK36RR3XA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:42:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，XAI 正在讨论在沙特阿拉伯租赁数据中心容量的事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三报道，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的xAI公司正在沙特阿拉伯洽谈租赁数据中心的事宜，这是该公司在提供廉价能源和政治善意的地区扩大基础设施的努力的一部分。【原文：Elon Musk's xAI is in talks to lease data center capacity in Saudi Arabia, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, as part of an effort to expand its infrastructure in regions offering cheap energy and political goodwill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/xai-discussions-lease-data-center-capacity-saudi-arabia-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">373ISOILZVIDVFHIB5VNR2NK5Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，OpenAI 正在开发 ChatGPT 内的支付结账系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周三援引多位熟悉该计划的人士的话报道称，OpenAI 正计划通过在聊天机器人中集成支付结账系统，从通过 ChatGPT 进行的在线产品销售中分一杯羹。【原文：OpenAI is planning to take a cut from online product sales made through ChatGPT by integrating a payment checkout system into the chatbot, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday, citing multiple people familiar with the proposals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-working-payment-checkout-system-within-chatgpt-ft-reports-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKBWS57K4ZOQ5ECYRJK6GOZFLY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:25:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国削减公共假期的计划可能无助于经济发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国政府认为，为了自身利益，法国有太多的休息日，但其削减部分公共假日的提议可能不会产生太大的经济效益。【原文：The French government thinks the country has too many days off for its own good, but its proposal to cull some public holidays may not produce much of an economic benefit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/frances-plan-cull-public-holidays-may-not-help-economy-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3NSL4UIJZI4JLBZPSAR32JQKM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道：特朗普可能很快解雇美联储主席鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周三援引一位不愿透露姓名的白宫官员的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普很可能很快解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is likely to fire Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell soon, Bloomberg reported on Wednesday, citing an unidentified White House official.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-indicated-republican-lawmakers-he-will-fire-feds-powell-cbs-reports-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLKYMFB5LNONZFV7UZS6CYXZCM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行有望推出稳定币，摩根士丹利也在考虑使用稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行首席执行官布莱恩-莫伊尼汉（Brian Moynihan）周三表示，美国银行与业内其他公司一样，一直在研究稳定币，投资者可以期待该银行在这方面取得进展，但没有给出时间表。【原文：Bank of America has been working on stablecoins like the rest of the industry and investors can expect the lender to move forward on this, CEO Brian Moynihan said on Wednesday, without giving a timeline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-expects-launch-stablecoins-morgan-stanley-weighs-use-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSJWELP3HBOBBLINAMUHO7OTMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟冯德莱恩称新预算适合 "新时代]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）周三宣布，她提出的 2028-2034 年欧盟 2 万亿欧元新预算是为新时代设计的"。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen declared on Wednesday that her proposed new 2 trillion euro budget for the European Union from 2028-2034 had been designed for a new era".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eus-von-der-leyen-unveils-budget-new-era-with-step-change-direct-eu-revenue-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2TYH5P3HRNJKZOGNGNA5GNV2WI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:44:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>