<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:34:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:34:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贸易部长称肯尼亚力争年底前与美国达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯尼亚贸易部长告诉路透社记者，肯尼亚预计将在年底前与美国达成一项贸易协议，如果本月到期的现有地区贸易安排不再续约，此举将缓解肯尼亚对这一关键市场的出口。【原文：Kenya expects to conclude a trade deal with the United States by year-end, its trade minister told Reuters, a move that could cushion its exports to a key market if an existing regional trade arrangement that expires this month is not renewed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/kenya-seeks-strike-us-trade-deal-by-year-end-trade-minister-says-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFLUFAKAUBLWXIMAOUMI2T3FM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:06:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果利用人工智能开发出手表中的新血压通知功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五上市的 Apple Watch Series 11 型号可以通知用户他们可能有高血压，这是公司利用人工智能而不是血压计提供的一项功能。【原文：Apple Watch Series 11 models that go on sale on Friday can notify users that they may have high blood pressure, in a feature the company has powered using artificial intelligence rather than a blood pressure monitor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/apple-used-ai-uncover-new-blood-pressure-notification-feature-watch-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YENECRS5KRNSRKXSVQFS6JSHKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德与 Vanguard 因新指导意见而缩减公司会谈规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[披露的信息显示，全球最大的两家资产管理公司今年大幅缩减了与公司老板举行会议的次数，因为新的指导意见增加了讨论气候变化和多元化等话题的难度。【原文：The world's two biggest asset managers sharply scaled back the number of meetings held with company bosses this year, disclosures show, as new guidance made it harder to discuss topics like climate change and diversity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/blackrock-vanguard-scale-back-company-talks-new-guidance-bites-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DADNN4NA3BOT3GGXIQILZKHRN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储卡什卡利认为，考虑到劳动力市场风险，今年再降息两次可能是合适的]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周五表示，他支持本周将美国基准短期利率下调四分之一个百分点的决定，并认为在美联储今年的最后两次会议上，每次下调相同幅度的利率都是合适的。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis President Neel Kashkari on Friday said he supported this week's decision to cut the U.S. benchmark short-term interest rate by a quarter of a percentage point, and feels that same-sized rate cuts at each of the Fed's final two meetings of the year will be appropriate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-kashkari-sees-two-more-rate-cuts-this-year-likely-appropriate-given-labor-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3EBF3XTHFPGLG4ZZVKCZ24Q7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标央行红利]]></title><description><![CDATA[看看《投资回报率》责任编辑安娜-西曼斯基（Anna Szymanski）和《投资回报率》团队的其他成员周末要阅读、观看和聆听的内容。【原文：Check out what ROI Editor-in-Charge Anna Szymanski and the rest of the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AH526Y3VQVK5ZKKQ3TCZE25WF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:41:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟部长寻求就独立于维萨卡和万事达卡的数字欧元达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟各国财长将于周五就如何建立一种数字欧元货币达成共同立场，这种数字欧元货币可以替代目前占主导地位的美国维萨卡和万事达卡系统。【原文：European Union finance ministers will seek to reach a common position on Friday on how to set up a digital euro currency that could become an alternative to the now dominant U.S.-based Visa and Mastercard systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eu-ministers-seek-agreement-digital-euro-be-independent-visa-mastercard-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3ATQ4JLNNPVVL4K3YF4FTOUFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的联邦通信委员会主席卡尔用新方法利用旧权力约束媒体公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高媒体监管机构布兰登-卡尔（Brendan Carr）向华特-迪士尼（Walt Disney）施压，要求其停止播出一档深夜脱口秀节目，这引发了民主党议员和其他批评人士的愤怒，并要求他辞职。【原文：Top U.S. media regulator Brendan Carr has sparked outrage and calls for his resignation from Democratic lawmakers and other critics after he pressured Walt Disney to stop running a late-night talk show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trumps-fcc-chair-carr-uses-old-powers-new-ways-rein-media-companies-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFH557JSJVLDVC7TNSZAPX622E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股期货持稳，股指将实现周线上涨；联邦快递上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货趋于稳定，在上一交易日主要股指升至纪录高位后有所停顿，而包裹递送公司联邦快递（FedEx）在超出季度盈利预期后上涨。【原文：U.S. stock index futures stabilized on Friday, pausing after the main indexes rallied to record highs in the previous session, while parcel delivery company FedEx rose after beating quarterly earnings expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-steady-indexes-set-weekly-gains-fedex-up-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V55FTNXMAVIK5NJIJ6AGFWJMBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：奢侈品牌的巨大挑战：了解 Z 世代]]></title><description><![CDATA[来自法国的 Fleur Arbel 和 Christophe Kairouz 最近被路易威登纽约旗舰店入口处的彩色长颈鹿和鸵鸟雕塑所吸引。【原文：Fleur Arbel and Christophe Kairouz, both from France, were lured into Louis Vuitton's New York flagship recently by a colorful sculpture of a monogrammed giraffe and ostrich above the store's entrance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/luxury-brands-big-challenge-figuring-out-gen-z-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2M77I2MCLVM2NL7K3DFIZYFXHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大海斯拉人如何成为世界上第一个土著液化天然气业主]]></title><description><![CDATA[海斯拉原住民的新首领莫琳-奈斯（Maureen Nyce）戴上了硬礼帽，穿上了安全背心，于八月前往锡达液化天然气管道现场视察，她这样做并不是以来访政要或文化使者的身份，而是以业主的身份。【原文：When Maureen Nyce, the new chief of the Haisla First Nation, donned a hard hat and safety vest for an August visit to the site of the Cedar LNG pipeline, she did so not as a visiting dignitary or cultural emissary - but as an owner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/how-canadas-haisla-became-worlds-first-indigenous-lng-owners-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNDMZTXHYJKKRK77Z24IVKU54A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:08:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻：美联储重启降息，美国房股大放异彩]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国联邦储备委员会重启降息，住房股是股市中可能受益的领域之一，最近几周，随着市场对更多宽松货币政策的定价，住房股已经跃跃欲试。【原文：As the U.S. Federal Reserve restarts interest rate cuts, housing shares are one of the areas of the stock market that may benefit, and they have perked up in recent weeks as markets priced in more monetary easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-st-week-ahead-us-housing-shares-shine-fed-restarts-rate-cuts-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SY6RJ77HJP2LOU3ZYAF5ONR3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:06:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国汽车行业机构将对美国芯片发起歧视调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车工业协会（CAAM）周五发表声明称，该协会已就美国芯片贸易政策对汽车行业的影响展开反歧视调查。【原文：The China Association of Automobile Manufacturers (CAAM) has launched an anti-discrimination probe into the impact on the auto industry of U.S. trade policy over chips, the association said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-auto-industry-body-launch-discrimination-probe-into-us-chips-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIA3RJCV2RP65OAOUPSGPX3ZJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:36:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递股价上涨，华尔街在贸易不确定性中欢呼利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递的股价在周五的盘前交易中攀升了 5%，投资者对这家包裹递送巨头在关税相关不确定性和低价值货运 "微不足道 "豁免终止的背景下实现季度利润和收入增长感到高兴。【原文：Shares of FedEx climbed 5% in premarket trading on Friday, as investors cheered the parcel delivery major's quarterly profit and revenue beat against a backdrop of tariff-related uncertainty and the end of the "de minimis" exemption on low-value shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/fedex-shares-rally-wall-street-cheers-profit-beat-amid-trade-uncertainties-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCBEVZHA7BNDPI2IPBQJFTFKPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储重启宽松政策，其他主要央行按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会自 12 月以来首次降息，与其他大多数主要央行维持利率不变的做法不同。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve has delivered its first rate cut since December, diverging from most other major central banks that have kept interest rates unchanged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-cenbank-graphic-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRCIR5TRNZI4JKJRZGRQHHNQ7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》报道，美国议员计划提出两党法案以取消咖啡关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周五援引立法草案副本报道，美国众议员唐-培根（Don Bacon）和罗-卡纳（Ro Khanna）计划提出两党立法，规定咖啡产品在2025年1月19日之后免于征收任何关税。【原文：U.S. Representatives Don Bacon and Ro Khanna plan to introduce bipartisan legislation that would exempt coffee products from any tariffs imposed after Jan. 19, 2025, the Washington Post reported on Friday, citing a copy of the draft legislation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-lawmakers-plan-introduce-bipartisan-bill-kill-coffee-tariffs-washington-post-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYUZEWJSTBKXJBZV5CYT76MHYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:24:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔与英伟达的交易对亚洲芯片制造商来说喜忧参半]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia 对英特尔的 50 亿美元投资对台积电等亚洲芯片制造商来说是一把双刃剑，因为英特尔的复兴可以减轻美国对其外国竞争对手的审查，尽管从长远来看会促进竞争。【原文：Nvidia's $5 billion investment in Intel is a double-edged sword for Asian chipmakers such as TSMC as an Intel revival could ease U.S. scrutiny on its foreign rivals although it can boost competition in the long term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/intels-nvidia-deal-expected-be-mixed-blessing-asian-chipmakers-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIWTFXG7IZKFVJMGTRSW47X43Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达探索向英国自动驾驶初创公司 Wayve 投资 5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国自动驾驶技术集团 Wayve 周四表示，美国芯片设计商英伟达（Nvidia）已签署意向书，可能在下一轮融资中投资 5 亿美元。【原文：U.S. chip designer Nvidia has signed a letter of intent for a possible $500 million investment in the next funding round at Britain's Wayve, the autonomous driving technology group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nvidia-explores-500-million-investment-uk-self-driving-startup-wayve-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDDQ747CKVICHOH5BQIEYZ4CKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 08:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 SMBC 将所持杰富瑞股份增至 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[三井住友金融集团（Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group）旗下的银行部门日本三井住友银行（Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corp）周五发表声明称，将向美国投资银行杰富瑞（Jefferies）再投资1,350亿日元（约合9.1284亿美元）。【原文：Japan's Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corp, the banking arm of Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group , will invest a further 135 billion yen ($912.84 million) in U.S. investment bank Jefferies , the companies said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japans-smbc-raises-stake-jefferies-about-20-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SB46NGOGIVKE5JLNISPOTO5JSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 08:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，福特因车门饰板脱落风险召回逾 10 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，福特汽车公司将在美国召回10万多辆金牛座（Taurus）汽车，原因是该车存在缺陷，可能导致车门饰板在行驶过程中脱落。【原文：Ford Motor is recalling more than 100,000 Taurus vehicles in the United States due to a defect that could cause door trim to detach while driving, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/ford-recalls-over-100000-vehicles-over-risk-door-trim-detachment-nhtsa-says-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRO77WRYGJKZLP3ZC2LOOJEIYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 07:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：伊拉克未能获得美国批准通过伊朗进口土库曼斯坦天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国的压力下，伊拉克试图通过邻国伊朗从土库曼斯坦输送天然气来缓解其长期电力短缺问题的努力失败了，这使得巴格达不得不争相寻找替代方案来维持电力供应。【原文：Iraq's attempt to ease its chronic power shortage with gas from Turkmenistan routed through neighbouring Iran has failed under U.S. pressure, leaving Baghdad scrambling for alternatives to keep the lights on.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/iraq-fails-win-us-approval-import-turkmen-gas-via-iran-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZTN4LKV5JK5DKVTKSA6LP6KQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 07:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主要券商预计英国央行 9 月暂停降息后 2025 年不再降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[在英国央行维持关键利率不变之后，包括高盛、花旗集团和摩根大通在内的主要券商预计英国央行今年不会再降息。【原文：Major brokerages including Goldman Sachs, Citigroup and J.P.Morgan expect no more interest rate cuts by the Bank of England this year after the British central bank kept its key rate on hold.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/major-brokerages-expect-no-more-boe-rate-cuts-2025-after-september-pause-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DYSQBAH6NJK3F6QCKIXVP7OHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 07:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田在新闻发布会上的讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五维持利率稳定，但决定开始出售其持有的风险资产，在逐步退出大规模刺激计划残余部分方面又迈出了一步。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady on Friday but decided to start selling its holdings of risky assets, taking another step forward in phasing out remnants of its massive stimulus programme.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/boj-governor-uedas-comments-news-conference-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSRKCUZXSVIG3CY4P4AIWCU5KE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 06:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息称中国在与加拿大发生贸易争端后抢购澳大利亚油菜籽]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位贸易消息人士告诉路透社，在中国政府上个月对从传统供应国加拿大进口的油菜籽征收初步反倾销税之后，中国国有贸易公司中粮集团已经购买了多达九批 60,000 公吨的澳大利亚油菜籽。【原文：Chinese state trading firm COFCO has bought up to nine 60,000-metric-ton cargoes of Australian canola, three trade sources told Reuters, after Beijing last month imposed preliminary anti-dumping duties on imports of the oilseed from traditional supplier Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-snaps-up-australian-canola-after-trade-spat-with-canada-sources-say-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UJRFSP7B5MCXLFFPUCRSL2TUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 06:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国交易平台 IG 集团收购澳大利亚加密货币交易所]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国在线交易平台 IG 集团周五表示，它已以 1.78 亿澳元（1.1741 亿美元）的价格收购了澳大利亚加密货币交易所 Independent Reserve，从而扩大了其在亚太地区的数字产品和业务。【原文：British online trading platform IG Group said on Friday it had acquired Australian cryptocurrency exchange Independent Reserve for A$178 million ($117.41 million), expanding its digital offerings and presence in the Asia-Pacific region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/uk-trading-platform-ig-group-buys-australian-crypto-exchange-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33BNXYRWEVKKJCAAYAKRZMYQHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 06:31:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，通用电气医疗集团正在探索出售中国业务部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士周五透露，美国医疗设备制造商通用电气医疗集团（GE Healthcare）正在与顾问合作，探讨其中国业务的各种选择，包括直接出售。【原文：U.S. medical device maker GE Healthcare is working with advisers to explore options for its China unit including an outright sale, a person with knowledge of the discussions said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/ge-healthcare-exploring-sale-china-unit-source-says-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHVFKZUKB5IGJJJPOX7KNIZJGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 06:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美联储放宽政策，中国仍将维持基准贷款利率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项调查显示，在美国联邦储备委员会降息后，中国央行保持关键政策利率稳定，预计下周一中国将连续第四个月维持基准贷款利率不变。【原文：China is expected to leave benchmark lending rates unchanged for the fourth month in a row next Monday, a Reuters survey showed, after the central bank kept a key policy rate steady following the U.S. Federal Reserve's rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/china-expected-leave-benchmark-lending-rates-unchanged-despite-fed-easing-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XATSNS5LPJPIRD2OAEF6WK4WA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 06:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果 iPhone 17 发布会吸引数百人在北京专卖店排起长队]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五是 iPhone 17 上市日，数百人在北京的苹果旗舰店排起了长队，这表明该系列手机在世界第二大经济体的销售有了一个良好的开端。【原文：Hundreds of people lined up at Apple’s flagship store in Beijing on the launch day of the iPhone 17 on Friday in a sign that sales of the series are off to a promising start in the world's second largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/apples-iphone-17-launch-draws-hundreds-long-queue-its-beijing-store-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEAOPXMQRVPVFJWSUCRBFNFYYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:11:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球经济暂时从容应对特朗普冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普总统上任后的头八个月里，全球经济秩序面临的威胁来势汹汹--从大规模关税冲击到美联储控制权争夺战，甚至还有一种新兴的美国国家资本主义形式。【原文：Threats to the global economic order have come at a furious pace during President Donald Trump's first eight months in office - from a massive tariff shock to a battle for control of the Federal Reserve and even an emerging form of U.S. state capitalism.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-economy-takes-trump-shocks-stride-now-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOIGRGCED5OQXC2A62HHYEWIF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道记录显示，FDA尼古丁袋试点将减轻制造商的研究负担]]></title><description><![CDATA[内部会议记录显示，美国食品和药物管理局将根据一项新的试点计划放宽对尼古丁袋制造商的要求，这是特朗普领导的白宫对吸烟替代品采取更柔和立场的第一个明显迹象。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration will ease requirements on nicotine pouch manufacturers under a new pilot program, internal meeting transcripts show, in the first clear sign of a softer stance on smoking alternatives under Trump's White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/fda-nicotine-pouch-pilot-ease-manufacturers-research-burden-transcript-shows-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OM7NVBX2BK6NIDG555XFOQ24M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：日本央行按兵不动，偏向鹰派]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPZBG6JZ2BKFBGKUKBAFDXHTJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 04:47:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>