<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:12:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:12:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[在SEC寻求法院批准送达传票后，阿达尼集团旗下公司市值蒸发125亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团旗下公司周五市值蒸发125亿美元，此前美国市场监管机构向法院申请协助向创始人高塔姆·阿达尼及集团高管萨加尔·阿达尼送达传票，指控其涉嫌欺诈及2.65亿美元贿赂案。【原文：India's Adani group firms shed $12.5 billion in market cap on Friday, after a U.S. markets regulator asked a court for help in serving summonses upon founder Gautam Adani and group executive Sagar Adani over alleged fraud and a $265 million bribery scheme.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/adani-group-firms-shed-125-billion-market-cap-after-sec-seeks-court-nod-serve-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OP3PPZATQ5OZZIIU4SYNG7QJX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:42:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西速溶咖啡行业寻求澄清美国维持50%关税的决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西商业协会向路透社透露，该国速溶咖啡行业正寻求了解详情，以弄清为何其产品仍面临50%的美国关税，尽管美国已取消了对该南美国家其他咖啡出口产品的大部分进口关税。【原文：Brazil's instant coffee industry is seeking details on why it continues to face a 50% U.S. tariff, even after import charges were lifted on most of the South American country's other coffee exports, business associations told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-instant-coffee-sector-seeks-clarity-us-decision-keep-50-tariff-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z2SD3YNGDBPDZOXFW36ADABIGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:29:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员称国会必须调查TikTok交易，批评缺乏细节]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员埃德·马基周五表示，国会应调查TikTok中国母公司字节跳动达成的一项协议。该协议旨在建立一家美国控股的合资企业，以确保美国数据安全，从而避免美国禁止这款社交媒体应用。【原文：Democratic Senator Ed Markey said on Friday Congress should investigate a deal by TikTok's Chinese owner ByteDance to establish a majority American-owned joint venture that would secure U.S. data in a bid to avoid a U.S. ban on the social media app.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/senator-says-congress-must-investigate-tiktok-deal-faults-lack-details-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMHDUV5NMBIX3I4ST6VSKTNYBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:08:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官驳回DoorDash和优步阻止纽约市小费法规的申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官驳回了DoorDash和优步科技公司要求颁布禁令的请求，该禁令旨在阻止纽约市实施一项法律。该法律要求外卖应用程序在顾客付款时提供向配送员支付小费的选项。【原文：A federal judge rejected DoorDash's and Uber Technologies' request for an injunction to block New York City laws that would require food delivery apps to provide customers an option to tip delivery workers when paying.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/judge-rejects-doordash-uber-bid-block-new-york-city-tipping-laws-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCCEAQT5PBOEDPD2YWS4X4WNPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金因地缘政治担忧遭遇资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月21日当周，美国股票基金遭遇资金外流，因投资者担忧特朗普总统就格陵兰问题对欧洲国家发出的关税威胁而降低风险敞口。【原文：U.S. equity funds faced outflows in the week through January 21 as investors reduced risk ​exposure on concerns about President Donald Trump's tariff threats ‌against European nations over Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-outflows-geopolitical-worries-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55RLA2KK6VKAPPKKL26XD5C7KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:29:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者信心指数1月份有所改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者信心在1月份全面改善，但对高物价和劳动力市场的担忧依然存在，周五公布的一项调查显示。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment improved across the board in January, though concerns about high ​prices and the labor market lingered, a ‌survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-improves-january-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZB74RYKY5NKDFSXNOTGOZ5CZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股市资金流入放缓，因地缘政治不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月21日当周，全球股票基金投资规模出现萎缩，因美国总统特朗普威胁重启与欧洲的格陵兰岛贸易争端，抑制了投资者的风险偏好。【原文：Investments in global equity funds shrank in the week to January 21 as U.S. President Donald Trump's threats of reigniting a trade dispute with Europe over Greenland curbed investor appetite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-flows-corrected-graphic-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F44DAU3FMFPH3I4SX6MPOISIQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:11:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA["就业、就业、就业"——达沃斯论坛上，随着担忧情绪退居次席，人工智能成为新的口号]]></title><description><![CDATA[刺骨的寒冷、政治紧张局势以及对人工智能的疑虑，都未能浇灭达沃斯商界领袖们对技术创造就业机会的热情。【原文：Biting cold, political tensions and doubts about artificial intelligence did nothing to curb the enthusiasm of business leaders in Davos over technology's ability to create jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/jobs-jobs-jobs-ai-mantra-fears-take-back-seat-davos-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKZTO2NFGRLHNBINT34XUVM36M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国1月商业活动保持稳定；价格压力持续存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国1月份商业活动保持平稳，调查显示，新订单的改善被疲软的劳动力市场和企业对进口关税导致成本上升的持续担忧所抵消。【原文：U.S. business activity was steady in January as an improvement in new orders was ​offset by a lackluster labor market and lingering concerns among firms over higher costs because of ‌import tariffs, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-business-activity-stable-january-price-pressures-persist-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDWAIF7SNBKK7OI3K3B7TIMHSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士称，特朗普政府解雇了其部门曾禁止中国车辆的官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，特朗普政府已撤换一名商务部官员，该官员的部门曾以国家安全为由，实质上禁止了几乎所有中国汽车进入美国市场。【原文：The Trump administration has pushed out a Commerce Department official whose office effectively barred nearly all Chinese cars from the U.S. market for national security reasons, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-administration-pushes-out-official-whose-unit-banned-chinese-vehicles-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42PZIFA7ZROJ3HJ6QQ536YVGGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:44:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将暂停对美930亿欧元报复性贸易措施六个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五表示，将提议再暂停六个月针对美国的价值930亿欧元（1091.9亿美元）的欧盟报复性贸易措施，这些措施原定于2月7日启动。【原文：The European Commission said on Friday it would propose suspending for another six months an ​EU package of retaliatory trade measures against the ‌U.S. worth 93 billion euros ($109.19 billion) that would otherwise kick in on February 7.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-suspend-93-billion-euro-retaliatory-trade-package-against-us-6-months-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGJCSSDHYJK7BCGPQJFPRSU6EQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:11:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺沃制药的Wegovy减肥药首周处方量达18,410份，开局表现令人鼓舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[据分析师援引IQVIA数据显示，诺和诺德的口服减肥药Wegovy在美国上市后的首个完整周内，开具处方达18,410次，为该类口服减肥药市场开局带来积极信号。【原文：Novo Nordisk's Wegovy pill was prescribed 18,410 times in the U.S. in the first full week after its launch in an encouraging ​start to the oral weight-loss drug race, according to analysts that cited IQVIA data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novos-wegovy-pill-tracks-18410-prescriptions-first-full-week-since-launch-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OEJQS3GRBL5XBHCRKW6QFH63U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，瑞银正为部分私人银行客户探索加密货币投资业务。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，瑞银集团正计划向部分私人银行客户提供加密货币投资选项，消息人士透露了这一情况。【原文：UBS is planning to offer cryptocurrency investment options to some private banking clients, Bloomberg ​News reported on Friday, citing people familiar ‌with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-explores-crypto-investing-select-private-banking-clients-bloomberg-news-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFOE2MM4DRKFVBYK77CZFYMLAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SLB季度利润超预期，计划向股东返还40亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[SLB周五公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，这家全球领先的油田服务公司受益于收购ChampionX，并宣布今年将向股东返还40亿美元。【原文：SLB beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Friday, as the world's top oilfield services provider benefited ​from the ChampionX acquisition and unveiled plans to return $4 billion ‌to shareholders this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/slb-beats-fourth-quarter-profit-estimates-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2GM57PZONOONDGGPHVT5ZD4RM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：我的反弹有多绿色？]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克·多兰和ROI团队本周末最期待阅读、观看和收听的内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLGCOYCRGVLTZEVGEAHQSIBJXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:42:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称花旗集团将于三月裁员更多员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，花旗集团在3月份预计将裁减更多员工，此前该集团本月已裁减约1000个岗位。【原文：Citigroup is expected to lay off more employees in March following a round of about 1,000 job cuts this month, according to two sources with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/citigroup-lay-off-more-employees-march-sources-say-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NM5XM6UMXZMPXLVC7XUJQCTOOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:33:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货下跌，英特尔股价暴跌，地缘政治担忧持续发酵]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周五走低，预示标普500指数和纳斯达克指数将连续第二周下跌。英特尔因业绩预期不及预期导致股价暴跌，而持续的地缘政治紧张局势也令市场情绪承压。【原文：U.S. stock futures dipped on Friday, signaling ​a second consecutive week of declines for the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq, as Intel's shares ‌plunged after disappointing forecasts, while lingering geopolitical tensions weighed on sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-dip-intel-plunges-geopolitical-concerns-linger-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47FSGASQQ5KITAWXHPGT5UPMX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国调查Meta公司对WhatsApp数据请求的合规情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国通信监管机构Ofcom周五表示，已就Meta Platforms在某项市场审查中提供的WhatsApp相关信息展开调查。【原文：British regulator Ofcom said on Friday it had opened an investigation into Meta Platforms over the information it had provided relating to WhatsApp for one of its market reviews.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-investigates-metas-compliance-with-whatsapp-data-requests-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7HU27TLKJOF3OEX6H3I7V4C64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:16:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联想首席财务官表示，公司正寻求与多个AI模型建立合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[联想首席财务官表示，该公司正寻求与全球多家大型语言模型建立合作关系，为其设备提供支持，旨在确立其作为全球人工智能参与者的地位。【原文：Lenovo is seeking partnerships with multiple large language models around the world to power its devices as it aims to establish itself as a global AI player, the company's chief financial officer said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/lenovo-looking-partner-with-multiple-ai-models-cfo-says-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCM7C2YWIBK3VHZD42S3QMB2CU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星链：航空公司的必备品，还是昂贵的附加服务？]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克与瑞安航空首席执行官迈克尔·奥利里在社交媒体上就安装星链WiFi服务的成本展开争执，这重新点燃了航空业长期存在的争论：究竟谁真正需要在3万英尺高空使用互联网——而谁又愿意为此买单？【原文：A social-media feud between Elon Musk and Ryanair boss Michael O'Leary over the cost of fitting Starlink's WiFi service has reignited a long-running debate in aviation: who really needs internet at 30,000 feet - and who is willing to pay for it?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/elon-musks-starlink-must-have-airlines-or-costly-perk-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XVFDWR2KRJZ7PRWKQAS4AT7OE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部协助的海外合同额在2025年跃升至2440亿美元，得益于波音公司订单的增长。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部国际贸易管理局周五表示，2025年在该部门协助下，美国企业签署了价值2440亿美元的外国政府采购合同，较2024年增长近三倍。波音公司客机订单量大幅攀升是主要推动因素。【原文：U.S. companies signed foreign government procurement contracts worth $244 billion in 2025 with assistance from the U.S. Commerce Department, nearly triple the total in 2024 as Boeing logged a massive increase in jetliner orders, the agency's International Trade Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-commerce-assisted-foreign-contracts-jump-244-billion-2025-boeing-order-gains-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46JL23NCCBKOZHB42QA2PMRJ4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望：美联储决议与财报大周临近，全球紧张局势令市场前景蒙尘]]></title><description><![CDATA[年初以来被地缘政治动荡所困扰的投资者，下周可能将关注焦点转向人工智能相关盈利前景及利率走向，届时将迎来大批财报发布和美联储会议。【原文：Investors who have been consumed by geopolitical turmoil to start the year may switch focus in the coming week to prospects for artificial intelligence-related profits ​and the path for interest rates, with a huge crop of earnings reports and a Federal Reserve meeting on tap.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-fed-big-earnings-week-loom-markets-global-tensions-muddy-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AH5VYNZREZP7NMCVMSAOVRXRPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道明证券称，全球股票基金遭遇创纪录资金外流，因美国和中国撤资激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[道明证券策略师周五在分析EPFR数据的报告中指出，全球股票基金创下史上最大规模资金流出纪录，因美国和中国市场的巨额赎回抵消了其他地区相对强劲的表现。【原文：Global equity funds recorded their largest outflows on record, as heavy withdrawals from the U.S. and China outweighed a relatively strong showing in other regions, TD Securities strategists said in a Friday note analysing EPFR data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-flows-urgent-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBD6CCTC4VL33FCOBWV627ZBQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希思罗机场新式安检仪终结令人厌烦的液体和笔记本电脑翻查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在欧洲最繁忙的希思罗机场，乘客通过安检时将不再被迫翻找随身行李中的洗发水、水瓶和笔记本电脑，这得益于新型专用扫描仪的投入使用。【原文：Passengers will no longer be forced to dig around in their hand luggage to extract shampoos, water bottles and laptops when travelling through security at Heathrow, Europe's busiest airport, thanks to new specialist scanners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/heathrows-new-scanners-end-dreaded-rummage-liquids-laptops-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4J6EBGITRPHZBTVZRNAEODSSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯联邦储蓄银行入股Element公司，普京推动技术主权建设]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯最大银行转型的科技集团俄罗斯联邦储蓄银行（Sberbank）已收购领先电子产品制造商Element的大部分股权。此举正值莫斯科推动在乌克兰战争所需高科技组件生产领域实现自主权之际。【原文：Sberbank, Russia's biggest bank turned technology conglomerate, has taken a major stake in leading electronics producer Element, as Moscow pushes for sovereignty in the production of the high-tech components needed for the war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/russias-sberbank-takes-stake-element-putin-pushes-tech-sovereignty-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCS3GEYJB5JYBCG32CV57EHFRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递将在法国裁员最多500人；重组运营业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递周五表示，计划裁减多达500个岗位，并投入高达7800万欧元（约合9158万美元）资金，作为其在该国国内业务重大重组计划的一部分。【原文：FedEx said on Friday that it planned to cut up to 500 jobs and invest as much as 78 million euros ($91.58 million) as part of a major overhaul to its domestic operations in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/fedex-cut-up-500-jobs-france-restructures-operations-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFXWALNKDNKIFI67HCI5PXQAUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果和戴尔的供应商和硕集团预计其美国工厂将于三月底前完工。]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾电子代工巨头和硕集团总裁兼首席执行官郑光志周五表示，该集团在得克萨斯州的首家美国工厂预计将于3月底完工，试产工作将在3月底或4月启动。【原文：Taiwanese contract electronics manufacturer Pegatron's first U.S. factory, in Texas, is expected to be ​completed by the end of March, with trial ‌production to begin around then or April, President and CEO Kuang-Chih Cheng said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-us-plant-be-completed-by-end-march-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4TLEZWUYFJ53NF6FIHI3OQFMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾期待亚利桑那州增加芯片投资，总统表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾期待亚利桑那州对半导体产业投入更多投资，以加强与美国的联系。台湾总统赖清德周五向到访的该州参议员如是表示。【原文：Taiwan looks forward to even more semiconductor investment in Arizona to bolster ties with the United States, President Lai Ching-te ​told a visiting senator from the state on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-looks-forward-more-chip-investment-arizona-president-says-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULP3RYOB3VMSROCYFCG2EKPNP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:24:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Euro zone business activity expands more slowly than expected in January]]></title><description><![CDATA[Euro zone business activity expanded more slowly than expected this month as weaker growth in the dominant services industry offset milder factory contraction, according to a survey, while price pressures picked up.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/euro-zone-business-activity-expands-more-slowly-than-expected-january-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XL36OIBZ5VPBXPQ5S4ZKUXRBIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CK Hutchison explores split sale of global ports, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[CK Hutchison is exploring a restructured sale of dozens of ports to a global consortium by breaking the transaction into smaller parcels with differing ownership structures, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ck-hutchison-explores-split-sale-global-ports-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4JFIK5S2VI5BEYEVYLR2RLUKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>