<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 17:04:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 17:04:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据美国全国公共广播电台（NPR）报道，特朗普政府在马阿拉歌晚宴后放弃了对 Nvidia H20 芯片的打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国全国公共广播电台（NPR）周三援引两位知情人士的话报道，在首席执行官黄仁勋上周出席了玛拉歌（Mar-a-Lago）晚宴之后，白宫改变了遏制英伟达（Nvidia）H20 芯片的方针。【原文：The White House has reversed course on curbs on Nvidia's H20 chips after CEO Jensen Huang attended a Mar-a-Lago dinner last week, NPR reported on Wednesday, citing two sources with knowledge of the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-administration-backs-off-nvidias-h20-chip-crackdown-after-mar-a-lago-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIABMSARC5NW5CDL5D7YGEP6QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 17:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员采取行动阻止国际货币基金组织（IMF）因石油基金争端对中非提供支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国立法者提出了一项立法，可能会阻止国际货币基金组织（IMF）对一些中非国家的支持，以保护石油公司必须留出用于环境恢复的数十亿美元。【原文：U.S. lawmakers have introduced legislation that could block International Monetary Fund (IMF) support for some Central African countries, in an effort to guard billions of dollars that oil companies must set aside for environmental restoration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/us-lawmakers-move-block-imf-central-africa-support-over-oil-fund-dispute-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXW26YXFOVN27O2XI2XHZRQLIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 JD Sports 支持耐克战略，称双方关系良好]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国体育用品零售商 JD Sports 是耐克最大的客户之一，该公司周三表示，尽管面临贸易和关税方面的挑战，但该公司对耐克品牌的发展方向和双方的关系感觉 "非常好"。【原文：British sportswear retailer JD Sports , one of Nike's largest customers, said on Wednesday it felt "really good" about the direction of the brand and their relationship despite trading and tariff challenges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-jd-sports-backs-nike-strategy-says-relationship-good-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BECURMOPWFOTNJUI4ALOWQIPIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:40:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴斯夫起诉伯克希尔的金霸王公司，指控其窃取电池机密]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的电池制造商金霸王公司（Duracell）被巴斯夫公司（BASF）起诉，指控其窃取了这家德国化学公司的锂离子电池技术相关商业机密。【原文：Duracell, the battery maker owned by Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway , has been sued by BASF for allegedly stealing trade secrets related to the German chemical company's lithium ion battery technology, court documents showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/basf-sues-berkshires-duracell-allegedly-stealing-battery-secrets-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27CB36XOMRJDZP3YAETZOQ4TCA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国企业债券市场再次因特朗普关税波动而关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国企业债券市场在周二仅开盘发售了一只债券后再次关闭，因为在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布解放日关税后的一周内，利差扩大幅度达到了自2023年地区银行业危机以来的最大值。【原文：The U.S. corporate bond market has shut again after opening for just one bond offering on Tuesday, as spreads in the week after President Donald Trump's Liberation Day tariffs have widened the most since 2023's regional banking crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-corporate-bond-market-shuts-again-trump-tariffs-volatility-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75SYVIEH5RKI3MDNM4WV7ORVPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油厂不太可能斥巨资加工更多国内石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业消息人士和分析师表示，美国炼油厂不打算进行大笔投资，以加工更多的国内原油，减少来自主要供应国加拿大和墨西哥的石油，这是特朗普总统提高石油产量计划的一个障碍。【原文：U.S. refiners are not planning to make big-ticket investments to process more domestic crude and less oil from top suppliers Canada and Mexico, industry sources and analysts said, an obstacle to President Trump's plan to boost oil output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refiners-unlikely-spend-big-process-more-domestic-oil-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPDM5DONARP5BERMGY55DUQQTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[长江和记在巴拿马投资 17 亿美元，超额完成任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于香港的长江和记控制的一家公司周三表示，已在巴拿马运河附近的两个港口投资 17 亿美元，超过了合同规定的金额，巴拿马当局正在对该合同进行审计。【原文：A company controlled by Hong Kong-based CK Hutchison has invested $1.7 billion in two ports near the Panama Canal, it said on Wednesday, surpassing the amount required under its contract, which is being audited by Panamanian authorities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ck-hutchison-invested-17-bln-panama-surpassing-obligations-it-says-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UINU3AK36JNOHBTDQKCYHH6CWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司三月份交付 71 架喷气式飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司周三证实，3月份交付了71架喷气式飞机，使第一季度的交付量从去年同期的142架下降到136架。【原文：Airbus delivered 71 jets in March, the planemaker confirmed on Wednesday, bringing first-quarter deliveries to 136, down from 142 a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-delivers-71-jets-march-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQIZHJBSVRLS3C6JCMIPTAMC4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈斯 F1 车队称关税不会影响车队所有者的业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国哈斯一级方程式车队表示，尽管老板吉恩-哈斯（Gene Haas）的机床业务因唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的贸易关税而出现 "需求大幅下降"，但车队仍在正常运营。【原文：The U.S.-owned Haas Formula One team said they were carrying on as normal despite owner Gene Haas's machine tools business reporting a 'dramatic decrease in demand' as a result of President Donald Trump's trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/formula1/haas-f1-say-no-impact-tariffs-hitting-owners-business-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LF2G3IWYFVMJ5N5R4EJ7P2UQYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:46:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰铁路迄今已恢复一半受网络攻击影响的 IT 服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰最大的货运公司--乌克兰国家铁路公司（Ukrzaliznytsia）周三表示，在 3 月底遭受的大规模网络攻击中，该公司仅成功恢复了约一半的 IT 服务。【原文：Ukrainian state railways Ukrzaliznytsia, the country's largest cargo carrier, said on Wednesday that it had managed to restore only about half of its IT services hit by a large-scale cyber attack in late March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ukraines-railways-restore-half-it-services-hit-by-cyber-attack-so-far-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNDBEGWVPZK3ZPFECKRMCIQBDU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储穆萨莱姆认为经济增长低于趋势，通胀风险加大]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆说，随着企业和家庭适应新进口关税导致的价格上涨，美国经济增长可能会 "实质性地 "低于趋势，失业率将在年内上升。【原文：U.S. economic growth will likely slip "materially" below trend and the unemployment rate will rise over the year as firms and households adjust to prices driven higher by new import tariffs, St. Louis Fed President Alberto Musalem said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-musalem-sees-growth-slipping-below-trend-higher-inflation-risk-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLBWZIDLWVLZZBFJLQMIOSIYIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:25:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称特朗普有望签署美国造船业行政令]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的消息人士称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普预计可能在周三签署一项行政命令，旨在重振美国造船业，削弱中国对全球航运业的控制。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is expected to sign an executive order potentially on Wednesday aimed at reinvigorating U.S. shipbuilding and reducing China's grip on the global shipping industry, three sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-expected-sign-executive-order-us-shipbuilding-sources-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWMSZHYC6ZIFZPDGYBTMCKXCJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:23:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 数据显示，美国原油库存增加，出口量创 1 月份新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周三称，上周美国原油库存增加，原因是进口增加，出口降至1月份以来的最低点，同时汽油和馏分油库存减少。【原文：U.S. crude oil stockpiles rose last week as imports increased and exports fell to their lowest since January, while gasoline and distillate inventories drew down, the Energy Information Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-stockpiles-rise-exports-hit-jan-lows-eia-data-shows-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LGK5Q4TERL4VBOX2X3XK4OXR4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从果汁到珠宝：欧盟将对哪些美国商品征收关税？]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟将从下周二开始对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收钢铝关税采取反制措施，对210亿欧元（约合230亿美元）的美国进口商品征收额外关税。【原文：The European Union will launch countermeasures from next Tuesday against U.S. President Donald Trump’s steel and aluminium tariffs with extra duties on 21 billion euros ($23 billion) of U.S. imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/juice-jewellery-which-us-goods-will-eu-hit-with-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWCEPGW3YRO57JZFQS7UGYLJOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lightmatter 展示可减少人工智能能耗的新型计算机芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[硅谷初创公司 Lightmatter 周三透露，它已开发出一种新型计算机芯片，既能加快人工智能工作的速度，又能在此过程中减少用电量。【原文：Silicon Valley startup Lightmatter revealed on Wednesday it had developed a new type of computer chip that could both speed up artificial intelligence work and use less electricity in the process.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/lightmatter-shows-new-type-computer-chip-that-could-reduce-ai-energy-use-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDONQTO4AZLVNBEARVNF6YJLDA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发的股市暴跌余震中的企业信贷震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[关税冲击和经济衰退的担忧在上周使全球股市陷入低迷，这种担忧正在蔓延到企业融资市场，提高了借贷成本，甚至扰乱了低风险公司的融资计划。【原文：The tariff shock and recession fears that have sent world stocks into a tailspin over the last week are rolling into corporate funding markets, raising the cost of borrowing and disrupting financing plans even for lower-risk companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-credit-analysis-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KU2IQKO2M5N3XKKNRTAJQ3Q4B4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canalys 称关税焦虑推动第一季度个人电脑出货量增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司Canalys周三表示，今年第一季度全球个人电脑出货量增长了9.4%，原因是个人电脑制造商因预期美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将全面征收关税而增加了对美国的发货量。【原文：Global shipments of personal computers rose 9.4% in the first quarter of this year as PC makers boosted consignments to the United States in anticipation of President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs, research firm Canalys said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tariff-anxiety-boosted-first-quarter-personal-computer-shipments-canalys-says-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXPIZZGIVJMQNPHZBWSSOKOJAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法案设立基金对俄罗斯幽灵舰队实施石油制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[来自美国两党的两位参议员于周三提出了一项立法，建立一个基金，以对俄罗斯为逃避西方对其乌克兰战争的制裁而依赖的所谓 "幽灵 "油轮船队实施制裁。【原文：Legislation from two U.S. senators from both parties introduced on Wednesday establishes a fund to enforce sanctions on the so-called ghost fleet of tankers Russia relies on to carry oil to avoid Western sanctions over its war on Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-bill-creates-fund-enforce-oil-sanctions-russias-ghost-fleet-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JPD42P34FNB3DCBS5RTIUIRO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:57:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟关税将抑制美国玉米进口，大豆风险暂时较低]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商和行业代表表示，欧盟从下周开始对美国商品征收反关税，这将阻止大量美国玉米流向欧洲，并提高寻求替代饲料谷物供应的买家的成本。【原文：European Union counter-tariffs on U.S. goods starting next week are set to halt a large flow of U.S. corn to Europe and raise costs for buyers chasing alternative supplies of the feed grain, traders and industry representatives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/eu-tariffs-curb-us-corn-imports-soy-lower-risk-now-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWHT27VUTZJETOTI7BXSKGFT3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士总统与特朗普谈贸易，希望尽快解决问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士总统卡琳-凯勒-萨特（Karin Keller-Sutter）周三表示，她已就贸易问题与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普通了电话，并期待在瑞士被征收比欧盟邻国更高的进口关税后达成协议。【原文：Swiss President Karin Keller-Sutter said on Wednesday she had spoken to U.S. President Donald Trump by telephone about trade and was looking forward to reaching agreements after Switzerland was hit with bigger import tariffs than its EU neighbours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/swiss-president-talks-trade-with-trump-hopes-fixes-soon-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45MKDJ4Q25J4XFGQQYFERRJGUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:43:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院小组投票决定推举特朗普提名的 420 亿美元政府宽带互联网基金监管人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商务委员会周三以 15-13 的党派票数通过了特朗普政府提名的人选，该人选将负责监督一项价值 420 亿美元的政府基金，该基金旨在将高速宽带互联网引入美国未得到服务的地区。【原文：The U.S. Senate Commerce Committee voted 15-13 along party lines Wednesday to advance the Trump administration's nominee to oversee a $42 billion government fund to bring high-speed broadband internet to unserved parts of America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-senate-panel-votes-advance-trump-nominee-oversee-42-billion-government-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJUN3DGFJ5KSLC3R2UML4AH4SE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油价格跌破 60 美元，美国生产商面临增长和资本回报的艰难抉择]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师们表示，贸易战升级导致油价跌破每桶60美元，可能会引发整个美国油区的焦虑情绪，从而可能迫使企业加倍采取措施，包括削减股票回购和资本支出。【原文：A plunge in oil prices below $60 per barrel due to an escalating trade war may trigger anxiety across the U.S. oil patch, likely forcing companies to double down on measures including cuts to share buybacks and capital expenditures, analysts have said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-producers-face-tough-choices-growth-capital-returns-oil-falls-below-60-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPHOG5WHPRKCZGXCJA3276COHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:14:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源部长将在访问阿联酋期间讨论安全问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据阿联酋国家通讯社周三报道，美国能源部长克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）表示，他对阿联酋的访问将包括就加强全球能源安全进行讨论。【原文：United States Energy Secretary Chris Wright said his visit to the United Arab Emirates will include discussion on enhancing global energy security, the UAE state news agency reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-energy-secretary-discuss-security-during-uae-visit-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSYTHMMBBFLV5CWPVMKLSAFR6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，亚马逊考虑 150 亿美元的仓库扩建计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，亚马逊公司正在考虑一项价值 150 亿美元的仓库扩建计划，将在美国城市和农村地区新建约 80 个物流设施。【原文：Amazon.com is considering a $15 billion warehouse expansion plan for about 80 new logistics facilities in U.S. cities and rural areas, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazoncom-considers-15-billion-warehouse-expansion-plan-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6H3YBOANXJKAZCHQ7UACCMTN3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴基斯坦求助于比特币矿工和人工智能数据中心以利用剩余电力]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴基斯坦加密委员会负责人兼财政部长顾问周三表示，巴基斯坦计划将部分剩余电力分配给比特币挖矿和人工智能数据中心，并补充说，巴基斯坦已与几家挖矿公司举行了会谈。【原文：Pakistan plans to allocate part of its surplus electricity to Bitcoin mining and AI data centres, the head of Pakistan's Crypto Council and adviser to the finance minister said on Wednesday, adding it had held talks with several mining firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/pakistan-turns-bitcoin-miners-ai-data-centers-use-surplus-power-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BPASAPT5JLSNMCDFYSWRYPX24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将于周二开始对美国关税进行报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟成员国周三一致同意，欧盟将于下周启动针对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关税的首个反制措施，与中国和加拿大一道采取报复行动，并使全球贸易冲突升级。【原文：The European Union will launch its first countermeasures against U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs next week, the bloc's members agreed on Wednesday, joining China and Canada in retaliating and escalating a global trade conflict.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-start-retaliating-against-us-tariffs-tuesday-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVUT2UYYZRN5NASIYSLSY2F534</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税动荡让投资者无处藏身]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的对等关税会对经济造成影响，投资者正在抛售他们在动荡时期通常青睐的美国资产，从而动摇了对传统避风港的信心。【原文：Investors are dumping U.S. assets they usually favour in times of turmoil as fear over the economic impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's reciprocal tariffs shakes confidence in traditional safe-havens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tariff-turmoil-leaves-investors-with-few-hiding-places-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAJPCHPYWFLKRPCXLPY2SDSVG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:36:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示特朗普有可能与美国盟友达成关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，他认为特朗普政府可以与美国的盟友达成关税协议，因为他准备在未来几周领导与70多个国家的谈判，但由于中国的报复行为，中国仍然是一个例外。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that he thinks the Trump administration can reach tariff deals with U.S. allies as he prepares to lead negotiations with over 70 countries in the coming weeks, but China remains an outlier due to its retaliation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-says-trump-can-likely-reach-tariff-deals-with-us-allies-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNDJJJ3UNBI3PB4M5CXW7R3PFM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nuro 在最新一轮融资中估值 60 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动驾驶技术初创公司 Nuro 周三表示，公司在最新一轮融资中筹集了 1.06 亿美元，估值达 60 亿美元。【原文：Autonomous driving technology startup Nuro said on Wednesday it was valued at $6 billion after raising $106 million in its latest funding round.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nuro-valued-6-billion-latest-funding-round-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAUQ6FWM6ZM57HAXBJ2HMQCGT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普下令审查新日铁的竞购后，激进分子 Ancora 放弃了美国钢铁公司的竞选活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令重新审查日本新日铁对美国钢铁公司的收购后，激进投资者 Ancora 周三表示，将撤回对美国钢铁公司董事会董事候选人的提名。【原文：Activist investor Ancora said on Wednesday it is withdrawing its nominations for director candidates on the board of U.S. Steel after President Donald Trump ordered a fresh review of Japan's Nippon Steel's bid for the domestic steelmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/activist-ancora-drops-us-steel-campaign-after-trump-orders-review-nippon-steel-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42A3I3IGIJNJZM7KNBMZE22YMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>