<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 04:05:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 04:05:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[读卖新闻》称，Seven & i 可能为非核心资产成立控股公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《读卖新闻》周四报道，Seven &amp; i Holdings 正在探讨为其超市、餐饮部门和非核心资产成立一家中间控股公司，以吸引外部投资，并专注于便利店业务。【原文：Seven &amp; i Holdings is exploring establishing an intermediate holding company for its supermarket, restaurant arms and non-core assets to attract external investment and focus on its convenience store operations, the Yomiuri newspaper reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/seven-i-may-establish-holding-company-non-core-assets-says-yomiuri-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M33VO2KSLROAJJ4N7PWBVFLORE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 03:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊在美国将 Apple TV+ 添加到 Prime Video 流媒体服务中]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周三表示，Apple TV+ 将于本月晚些时候在美国的 Prime Video 上推出，月费 9.99 美元。【原文：Amazon said on Wednesday that Apple TV+ will become available on Prime Video later this month in the U.S. for $9.99 per month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/amazon-adds-apple-tv-its-prime-video-streaming-service-us-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAJ3LSSTTNKQZKNMNORHNQOQKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 03:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国股市攀升；美元在美国通胀测试前持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中国央行启动了 5000 亿元人民币的融资机制以刺激资本市场，周四亚洲股市从中国股市中获得提振，而美元则在当天晚些时候美国通胀数据公布前徘徊在两个月高点附近。【原文：Asian stocks got a lift on Thursday from Chinese stocks as China's central bank kicked off its 500 billion yuan facility to spur capital markets, while the dollar lingered near a two-month high ahead of U.S. inflation data later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLOMTME3DZMY7K4UGNHPAOEDIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:55:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞前高管未参与 Starboard 针对制药商的竞选活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[辉瑞公司前首席执行官兼董事长伊恩-雷德（Ian Read）和前首席财务官弗兰克-达梅利奥（Frank D'Amelio）在一份声明中表示，他们不会参与激进投资者 Starboard Value 的投资，Starboard Value 希望这家美国制药巨头做出改变，扭转业绩。【原文：Pfizer's former CEO and Chair Ian Read and ex-CFO Frank D'Amelio said in a statement that they will not be involved with activist investor Starboard Value, which wants the U.S. drug giant to make changes to turn its performance around.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/former-pfizer-executives-not-involved-starboards-campaign-against-drugmaker-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSEQA4NK5ZLM5FEJ4CEBPWBZLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受飓风米尔顿影响，130 多万佛罗里达用户停电]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 PowerOutage.us 提供的数据，由于飓风米尔顿以 3 级风暴登陆佛罗里达州，周三有 130 多万户家庭和企业停电。【原文：More than 1.3 million homes and businesses in Florida were without power on Wednesday, as Hurricane Milton made landfall as Category 3 storm, according to data from PowerOutage.us.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/over-13-million-florida-customers-without-power-due-hurricane-milton-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQE3GTYWJJL5PGV5VHX2GDYJMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:44:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度监管改革可加速即将上市的初创企业回家进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家、律师和投资者认为，印度取消一个耗时的合规步骤，将加快在国外注册的印度初创企业回国参与该国上市热潮的步伐。【原文：India's scrapping of a time-consuming compliance step will accelerate the pace at which Indian startups domiciled abroad shift back home to participate in the country's listing boom, according to bankers, lawyers and investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-regulatory-reform-could-hasten-homecoming-ipo-bound-startups-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7VIOVY22FP2TH6LRGFXPQVTRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[条款表显示，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司在债券交易中融资 19 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周四查阅的一份条款书显示，沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）在一项七期日元债券交易中筹集了 2818 亿日元（19 亿美元）。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway has raised 281.8 billion yen ($1.9 billion) in a seven-tranche yen-denominated bond deal, according to a term sheet reviewed by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-hathaway-raises-19-bln-bond-deal-term-sheet-shows-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LNESQG2HRIEVL6A3B3VP7CCJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 01:55:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列-伊朗冲突担忧和美国风暴导致油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，油价在亚洲早盘交易中上涨，原因是人们担心中东可能出现供应中断，以色列计划打击石油生产国伊朗，以及一场大风暴肆虐佛罗里达州导致燃料需求激增。【原文：Oil prices rose in early Asian trade on Thursday on concerns about potential supply disruptions in the Middle East, with Israel planning to strike oil-producer Iran, and on spikes in fuel demand as a major storm barreled into Florida.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-israel-iran-conflict-fears-us-storm-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JVB76PICNKNPE4LIQMZBUBLCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 01:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元徘徊在两个月高位附近，美联储宽松政策押注在通胀数据公布前消退]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑主要货币周四接近两个月来的峰值，因为市场对美联储进一步放宽货币政策的耐心态度越来越有信心，即使当天晚些时候即将公布一份关键的通胀报告。【原文：The U.S. dollar traded near a two-month peak against major peers on Thursday as markets grew more confident about a patient approach from the Federal Reserve to further monetary easing, even as a key inflation report loomed later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-hovers-near-two-month-peak-fed-easing-bets-ebb-before-inflation-data-2024-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQLX3TLBMZIGTA336D5RU2GZ5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：道明银行在美国和解协议中面临 30 亿美元罚款和发展限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，作为与监管机构和检察官达成的和解协议的一部分，道明银行预计将支付约 30 亿美元的罚金，并接受对其在美国发展的限制。【原文：TD Bank is expected to pay about $3 billion in penalties and accept limits on its growth in the United States as part of a settlement with regulators and prosecutors over charges it failed to properly monitor money laundering by drug cartels, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/td-bank-faces-3-bln-penalties-growth-restrictions-us-settlement-wsj-reports-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P76DBMFOBVICBBU625KOSTLMRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 23:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席戴利认为今年还将降息一到两次]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周三表示，她 "完全 "支持美国央行上个月降息半个百分点，并称如果经济发展如她所料，今年很可能再降息一到两次。
"戴利在博伊西州立大学接受 KTVB 主播卡罗琳-霍利（Carolyn Holly）采访时说："劳动力市场已经下行。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly on Wednesday said she "fully" supported the U.S. central bank's half-of-a-percentage-point interest-rate cut last month, and said one or two more rate cuts this year are likely if the economy evolves as she expects.
"The labor market has downshifted," Daly said in an interview with KTVB anchor Carolyn Holly at Boise State University, adding sh】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-daly-sees-one-or-two-more-interest-rate-cuts-this-year-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCWP7ZWIM5LGZOOZ6IEQRPLGSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：佛罗里达州的基金经理为飓风米尔顿做好准备，但仍致力于该州的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[佛罗里达州的阳光和低税率吸引了许多对冲基金和其他金融专业人士南迁。现在，又一场大规模飓风使这种情结面临考验，但许多大牌经理人承诺在可预见的未来继续留在 "南方华尔街"。【原文：Florida's sun and low taxes enticed many hedge funds and other financial professionals to move south. Now another massive hurricane is putting that love affair to the test, but many big-name managers are committed to remaining in "Wall Street South" for the foreseeable future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/florida-based-fund-managers-brace-hurricane-milton-remain-committed-state-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VR333ERKFJNOBDJ4DZ2XGURN7U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:56:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉表示，多边银行在评级下调之前最多可再贷款 4800 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉（Fitch）在周三的一份报告中称，在对其超国家机构评级标准进行审查后，十几家最大的多边开发银行在面临评级下调之前，可以合计再贷款 5 万亿美元。【原文：A dozen of the largest multilateral development banks could collectively lend a further half-trillion dollars before facing rating downgrades, Fitch said in a Wednesday report, following a review of its criteria for rating supranational institutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/multilateral-banks-could-lend-up-480-billion-more-before-rating-downgrades-fitch-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYFHAT2FQRKDFIM2BX2TJKPVGE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:55:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲 对中国股市的现实检验，美元大幅走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBXRQLHPQ5LILI5S6PHFG7IVIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:46:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飓风米尔顿临近，佛罗里达州化肥厂和谷物加工厂关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[佛罗里达州的化肥厂、牲畜饲料厂和至少一家大型面粉厂周三关闭，准备应对飓风米尔顿带来的破坏性狂风、暴雨和致命的风暴潮。【原文：Fertilizer plants, livestock feed facilities and at least one large flour mill in Florida closed on Wednesday in preparation for Hurricane Milton's destructive winds, heavy rain and deadly storm surge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/florida-fertilizer-plants-grain-mills-close-hurricane-milton-nears-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZ5TRPUK7BNCTBY3VFYY4RIJWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，Azul 与出租商达成的协议对巴西航空工业公司是个好消息]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西阿苏尔航空公司（Azul）与其出租人之间达成的以 5 亿多美元债务换取股权的交易对飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）来说是个好消息，分析师说，这减少了人们对一个重要客户债务负担的担忧。【原文：A deal between Brazilian airline Azul and its lessors to swap more than $500 million in obligations for an equity stake is good news for planemaker Embraer , analysts say, as it reduces concerns about the debt load of a key customer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/azul-deal-with-lessors-good-news-planemaker-embraer-analysts-say-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVVC5QGAQZO4LDHFOCS3H2L3AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西的土著群体：碳信用额未征求我们的意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西帕拉州的原住民组织称，政府在与跨国公司签署一项协议，出售碳抵消额度以支持该州亚马逊雨林的保护工作之前，并未征求他们的意见。【原文：Indigenous organizations in the Brazilian state of Para said they were not consulted by the government before it signed a deal with multinational companies to sell carbon offset credits to support conservation of the Amazon rainforest in the state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/indigenous-groups-brazil-we-were-not-consulted-carbon-credits-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47YDXPBLPFIKRF47D7V4ZZD2OI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:10:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大选不确定性下美国债券期限溢价再次转正]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国国债 10 年期溢价（衡量投资者持有长期政府债务证券所需补偿的指标）重回正值，原因是美国经济的韧性打破了激进降息的预期，而大选的不确定性又对长期债券构成了压力。【原文：The U.S. Treasury 10-year term premium, a measure of the compensation investors demand to hold long-term government debt securities, moved back into positive territory this week as U.S. economic resilience defied expectations of aggressive interest rate cuts and election uncertainty weighed on long-term bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-bond-term-premium-turns-positive-again-amid-election-uncertainty-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSWFUZHDH5LF5J65CEXHDEC5PY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国指控 18 人和公司涉嫌加密货币欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[四家加密货币公司和 14 名个人受到指控，美国检察官周三表示，这是首次对金融服务公司在加密货币领域操纵市场和虚假交易的刑事起诉。【原文：Four cryptocurrency companies and 14 individuals have been charged in what U.S. prosecutors on Wednesday said was the first criminal prosecution of financial services firms for market manipulation and sham trading in the crypto sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-charges-18-people-companies-cryptocurrency-fraud-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPVXHWHJ4BM6DJLHZUZNMVYRC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飓风米尔顿迫近，迪士尼世界将关闭奥兰多主题公园]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪斯尼乐园周三表示，其位于佛罗里达州的主题公园周四将继续关闭，与奥兰多其他主要景点一起准备应对飓风米尔顿，预计飓风将于周四登陆佛罗里达州。【原文：Walt Disney World said on Wednesday its theme park in Florida would remain closed on Thursday, joining other major Orlando attractions preparing for Hurricane Milton, which is expected to make landfall in the state on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/disney-world-close-orlando-theme-park-hurricane-milton-looms-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LJ2RBILJBI3NKKWXIEZVE7FAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:40:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航空业敦促采取措施防止飞机使用未经批准的零部件]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空业联盟周三发布了一份报告，呼吁采取新措施，帮助防止未经批准的零部件进入航空供应链。【原文：A report issued by an aviation industry coalition on Wednesday called for new steps to help prevent future unapproved parts from entering the aviation supply chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aviation-industry-urges-steps-prevent-unapproved-parts-airplane-use-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6FBQTPYMNNRTEOYONRPTIFZOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:36:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌在美国搜索、应用和广告案件中的反垄断困境加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周的两天时间里，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司被法院勒令向竞争对手开放其应用程序商店 Play，并获悉美国司法部可能很快会要求法官拆分该公司，以限制其对在线搜索的控制。【原文：In the span of two days this week, Alphabet's Google was hit with a court order to open up its app store Play to rivals and learned that the U.S. Justice Department may soon ask a judge to split up the company to limit its hold over online searches.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/googles-antitrust-woes-mount-us-cases-over-search-apps-ads-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HA4G6JV7ZNNO5C6CJJDRHBAX6M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，Stellantis 首席执行官计划对管理层进行重大调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，Stellantis 首席执行官卡洛斯-塔瓦雷斯（Carlos Tavares）正计划对管理层进行深度调整，以应对汽车制造商的利润预警。【原文：Stellantis CEO Carlos Tavares is planning a deep management reshuffle amid the automaker's profit warning, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-ceo-plans-major-management-changes-bloomberg-reports-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRSINOEKNVN7LJ2ONWOORRC5UQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[会议纪要显示，"绝大多数 "美联储成员赞成在 9 月份大幅减息]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据刚刚公布的为期两天的会议纪要，在美联储 9 月份的会议上，"绝大多数 "美联储官员支持通过大幅降息半个百分点来开启一个宽松货币政策的时代，但似乎有更广泛的共识，即最初的举措不会使美联储承诺在未来采取任何特定的降息步伐。【原文：A "substantial majority" of U.S. Federal Reserve officials at the central bank's September meeting supported beginning an era of easier monetary policy with an outsized half-point rate cut, but there appeared even broader agreement that the initial move would not commit the Fed to any particular pace of rate reductions in the future, according to just-released minutes of the two-day session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/substantial-majority-fed-favored-large-cut-sept-minutes-show-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HO2YFH3CABPYBH74IA3CKPLIRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期抵押贷款利率跃升至 6.36%，创 15 个月来最大单周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，最受欢迎的美国住房贷款利率升至 6.36%，创下一年多来的最大单周升幅，此前好于预期的经济数据导致金融市场减少了对美联储进一步降息的押注。【原文：The interest rate for the most popular U.S. home loan rose to 6.36% last week, marking the biggest weekly increase in more than a year after better-than-expected economic data caused financial markets to scale back bets on further Federal Reserve interest-rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-mortgage-rate-jumps-636-biggest-weekly-gain-15-months-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UXU5Y4REJLIBECJWDSF42BTFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德公司任命新的 F-35 战斗机项目负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司周三宣布任命Chauncey McIntosh为F-35 "闪电II "项目副总裁兼总经理，自12月1日起生效。【原文：Lockheed Martin announced on Wednesday that Chauncey McIntosh been appointed vice president and general manager of the F-35 Lightning II Program, effective Dec. 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-names-new-f-35-fighter-jet-program-leader-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KUY2J5F6BOTXASN6SD5UVLQJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:50:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行看好强劲增长指标，美国邮轮股上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于券商花旗（Citi）看好包括挪威邮轮公司（Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings）在内的美国邮轮运营商的长期前景，这些公司的股票在周三午盘交易中大涨。【原文：Shares of U.S. cruise operators, including Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings , surged in midday trading on Wednesday as brokerage Citi gets bullish on the companies' long-term prospects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-cruise-stocks-rise-citi-upbeat-about-strong-growth-indicators-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7XOZV5N3ZOMFDVOJGYCZ45O5Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉债券持有人提出并行索赔，花旗银行拍卖岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[委内瑞拉数十亿美元债券和票据的持有者在最后一刻成为美国法院一案的主角，该案将决定炼油企业 Citgo Petroleum 的所有权，这有可能破坏为十多家公司未偿还债务和被该国征用而进行的补偿拍卖。【原文：Holders of billions of dollars in Venezuelan bonds and notes have emerged as last-minute protagonists in a U.S. court case set to decide the ownership of oil refiner Citgo Petroleum, threatening to derail an auction to compensate more than a dozen companies for unpaid debts and expropriations by the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/citgo-auction-jeopardy-venezuela-bondholders-pursue-parallel-claims-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBQTRNQCXBOTJDQAN5ZJCUGLK4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:15:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月份批发库存修正后有所下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于机动车库存增长速度大幅放缓，8 月份美国批发库存的增幅低于最初的预期，这种趋势如果持续下去，可能会削弱人们对第三季度经济强劲增长的预期。【原文：U.S. wholesale inventories rose less than initially thought in August amid a sharp moderation in the pace of increase in motor vehicle stocks, a trend that if sustained could temper expectations for robust economic growth in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-wholesale-inventories-revised-lower-august-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDYV3VG2SZKI7A4224IGN4WGZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葛兰素史克就美国州法院审理的善达（Zantac）案达成高达 22 亿美元的和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[葛兰素史克公司周三表示，该公司已与十家原告公司达成协议，最高赔偿金额为22亿美元，这十家原告公司占美国州法院Zantac产品责任诉讼案件的93%。【原文：GSK said on Wednesday it had reached agreements with ten plaintiff firms, representing 93% of U.S. state court Zantac product liability cases pending against the drugmaker, for up to $2.2 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/gsk-reaches-up-22-billion-settlement-zantac-us-state-court-cases-2024-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5JKC3OHJBMU3CGRRWEKQR3YJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>