<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:07:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:07:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Canalys 称关税焦虑推动第一季度个人电脑出货量增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司Canalys周三表示，今年第一季度全球个人电脑出货量增长了9.4%，原因是个人电脑制造商因预期美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将全面征收关税而增加了对美国的发货量。【原文：Global shipments of personal computers rose 9.4% in the first quarter of this year as PC makers boosted consignments to the United States in anticipation of President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs, research firm Canalys said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tariff-anxiety-boosted-first-quarter-personal-computer-shipments-canalys-says-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXPIZZGIVJMQNPHZBWSSOKOJAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法案设立基金对俄罗斯幽灵舰队实施石油制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[来自美国两党的两位参议员于周三提出了一项立法，建立一个基金，以对俄罗斯为逃避西方对其乌克兰战争的制裁而依赖的所谓 "幽灵 "油轮船队实施制裁。【原文：Legislation from two U.S. senators from both parties introduced on Wednesday establishes a fund to enforce sanctions on the so-called ghost fleet of tankers Russia relies on to carry oil to avoid Western sanctions over its war on Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-bill-creates-fund-enforce-oil-sanctions-russias-ghost-fleet-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JPD42P34FNB3DCBS5RTIUIRO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:57:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟关税将抑制美国玉米进口，大豆风险暂时较低]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商和行业代表表示，欧盟从下周开始对美国商品征收反关税，这将阻止大量美国玉米流向欧洲，并提高寻求替代饲料谷物供应的买家的成本。【原文：European Union counter-tariffs on U.S. goods starting next week are set to halt a large flow of U.S. corn to Europe and raise costs for buyers chasing alternative supplies of the feed grain, traders and industry representatives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/eu-tariffs-curb-us-corn-imports-soy-lower-risk-now-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWHT27VUTZJETOTI7BXSKGFT3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士总统与特朗普谈贸易，希望尽快解决问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士总统卡琳-凯勒-萨特（Karin Keller-Sutter）周三表示，她已就贸易问题与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普通了电话，并期待在瑞士被征收比欧盟邻国更高的进口关税后达成协议。【原文：Swiss President Karin Keller-Sutter said on Wednesday she had spoken to U.S. President Donald Trump by telephone about trade and was looking forward to reaching agreements after Switzerland was hit with bigger import tariffs than its EU neighbours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/swiss-president-talks-trade-with-trump-hopes-fixes-soon-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45MKDJ4Q25J4XFGQQYFERRJGUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:43:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院小组投票决定推举特朗普提名的 420 亿美元政府宽带互联网基金监管人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商务委员会周三以 15-13 的党派票数通过了特朗普政府提名的人选，该人选将负责监督一项价值 420 亿美元的政府基金，该基金旨在将高速宽带互联网引入美国未得到服务的地区。【原文：The U.S. Senate Commerce Committee voted 15-13 along party lines Wednesday to advance the Trump administration's nominee to oversee a $42 billion government fund to bring high-speed broadband internet to unserved parts of America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-senate-panel-votes-advance-trump-nominee-oversee-42-billion-government-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJUN3DGFJ5KSLC3R2UML4AH4SE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油价格跌破 60 美元，美国生产商面临增长和资本回报的艰难抉择]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师们表示，贸易战升级导致油价跌破每桶60美元，可能会引发整个美国油区的焦虑情绪，从而可能迫使企业加倍采取措施，包括削减股票回购和资本支出。【原文：A plunge in oil prices below $60 per barrel due to an escalating trade war may trigger anxiety across the U.S. oil patch, likely forcing companies to double down on measures including cuts to share buybacks and capital expenditures, analysts have said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-producers-face-tough-choices-growth-capital-returns-oil-falls-below-60-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPHOG5WHPRKCZGXCJA3276COHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:14:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源部长将在访问阿联酋期间讨论安全问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据阿联酋国家通讯社周三报道，美国能源部长克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）表示，他对阿联酋的访问将包括就加强全球能源安全进行讨论。【原文：United States Energy Secretary Chris Wright said his visit to the United Arab Emirates will include discussion on enhancing global energy security, the UAE state news agency reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-energy-secretary-discuss-security-during-uae-visit-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSYTHMMBBFLV5CWPVMKLSAFR6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，亚马逊考虑 150 亿美元的仓库扩建计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，亚马逊公司正在考虑一项价值 150 亿美元的仓库扩建计划，将在美国城市和农村地区新建约 80 个物流设施。【原文：Amazon.com is considering a $15 billion warehouse expansion plan for about 80 new logistics facilities in U.S. cities and rural areas, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazoncom-considers-15-billion-warehouse-expansion-plan-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6H3YBOANXJKAZCHQ7UACCMTN3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴基斯坦求助于比特币矿工和人工智能数据中心以利用剩余电力]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴基斯坦加密委员会负责人兼财政部长顾问周三表示，巴基斯坦计划将部分剩余电力分配给比特币挖矿和人工智能数据中心，并补充说，巴基斯坦已与几家挖矿公司举行了会谈。【原文：Pakistan plans to allocate part of its surplus electricity to Bitcoin mining and AI data centres, the head of Pakistan's Crypto Council and adviser to the finance minister said on Wednesday, adding it had held talks with several mining firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/pakistan-turns-bitcoin-miners-ai-data-centers-use-surplus-power-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BPASAPT5JLSNMCDFYSWRYPX24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将于周二开始对美国关税进行报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟成员国周三一致同意，欧盟将于下周启动针对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关税的首个反制措施，与中国和加拿大一道采取报复行动，并使全球贸易冲突升级。【原文：The European Union will launch its first countermeasures against U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs next week, the bloc's members agreed on Wednesday, joining China and Canada in retaliating and escalating a global trade conflict.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-start-retaliating-against-us-tariffs-tuesday-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVUT2UYYZRN5NASIYSLSY2F534</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税动荡让投资者无处藏身]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的对等关税会对经济造成影响，投资者正在抛售他们在动荡时期通常青睐的美国资产，从而动摇了对传统避风港的信心。【原文：Investors are dumping U.S. assets they usually favour in times of turmoil as fear over the economic impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's reciprocal tariffs shakes confidence in traditional safe-havens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tariff-turmoil-leaves-investors-with-few-hiding-places-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAJPCHPYWFLKRPCXLPY2SDSVG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:36:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示特朗普有可能与美国盟友达成关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，他认为特朗普政府可以与美国的盟友达成关税协议，因为他准备在未来几周领导与70多个国家的谈判，但由于中国的报复行为，中国仍然是一个例外。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that he thinks the Trump administration can reach tariff deals with U.S. allies as he prepares to lead negotiations with over 70 countries in the coming weeks, but China remains an outlier due to its retaliation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-says-trump-can-likely-reach-tariff-deals-with-us-allies-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNDJJJ3UNBI3PB4M5CXW7R3PFM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nuro 在最新一轮融资中估值 60 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动驾驶技术初创公司 Nuro 周三表示，公司在最新一轮融资中筹集了 1.06 亿美元，估值达 60 亿美元。【原文：Autonomous driving technology startup Nuro said on Wednesday it was valued at $6 billion after raising $106 million in its latest funding round.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nuro-valued-6-billion-latest-funding-round-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAUQ6FWM6ZM57HAXBJ2HMQCGT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普下令审查新日铁的竞购后，激进分子 Ancora 放弃了美国钢铁公司的竞选活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令重新审查日本新日铁对美国钢铁公司的收购后，激进投资者 Ancora 周三表示，将撤回对美国钢铁公司董事会董事候选人的提名。【原文：Activist investor Ancora said on Wednesday it is withdrawing its nominations for director candidates on the board of U.S. Steel after President Donald Trump ordered a fresh review of Japan's Nippon Steel's bid for the domestic steelmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/activist-ancora-drops-us-steel-campaign-after-trump-orders-review-nippon-steel-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42A3I3IGIJNJZM7KNBMZE22YMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官戴蒙预期经济衰退和违约，敦促贸易谈判尽快取得进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米-戴蒙（Jamie Dimon）周三在福克斯财经频道（Fox Business）的 "与玛丽亚共度的早晨"（Mornings with Maria）节目中表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）实施的全面关税可能会导致经济衰退和借款人违约。【原文：JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon said on Wednesday that sweeping tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump will probably lead to a recession and defaults by borrowers, he told Fox Business’ Mornings with Maria.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/jpmorgan-ceo-dimon-expects-recession-defaults-urges-quick-progress-trade-talks-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMOFU3XLZFKNRJUZMFEFPJQUVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国科技初创企业 1Komma5 与 Klarna 一起搁置美国 IPO 计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统特朗普的可再生能源和贸易政策扰乱了市场，德国独角兽企业 1Komma5 Grad 与瑞典的 Klarna 公司一道，重新评估了在美国上市的计划。【原文：German unicorn 1Komma5 Grad has joined Sweden's Klarna in reassessing plans for a U.S. float as President Trump's renewable energy and trade policies have roiled markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/german-tech-startup-1komma5-joins-klarna-shelving-us-ipo-plans-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3MTXHB2AZPL3EMR2UBSIXHEHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:49:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示美国财政部将在银行监管中发挥更大作用，减轻不当负担]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，财政部将在银行业监管方面发挥更大作用，以更好地平衡成本与收益，确保贷款人能够为美国经济增长提供资金。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday his department will play a greater role in banking regulation to better balance costs and benefits and ensure that lenders can finance growth in the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bessent-says-us-treasury-take-stronger-role-bank-regulation-easing-undue-burdens-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVUTZJUDWNKZJASOZBFY5K36PM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:46:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌推出新型铁木芯片，加速人工智能应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 周三发布了名为 "铁木 "的第七代人工智能芯片。【原文：Alphabet's on Wednesday unveiled its seventh-generation artificial intelligence chip named Ironwood, which the company said is designed to speed the performance of AI applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-launches-new-ironwood-chip-speed-ai-applications-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKKIDAEAUVK7XGWIIR7PKS7QZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:12:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税忧虑引发印尼盾和股市暴跌，印尼人抢购黄金]]></title><description><![CDATA[数以百计的印尼人蜂拥购买金条，押注贵金属的价值可以使他们在这个东南亚最大经济体的货币和股市暴跌时免受未来更艰难的经济时期的影响。【原文：Hundreds of Indonesians are flocking to buy gold bars, betting that the precious metal's value could shield them from tougher economic times ahead as the currency and the stock market tumble in South East Asia's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/indonesians-rush-gold-rupiah-stocks-plunge-amid-us-tariff-worries-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LI2D52P2W5KYZH7V2QMGPGXDTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Verizon称谷歌人工智能客服人员带动销售额跃升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Verizon 称，该公司利用谷歌模型为客户服务代表打造的人工智能助理缩短了通话时间，使他们有时间向客户销售产品，从而导致销售额激增。【原文：Verizon said an AI assistant for the company's customer service representatives built using Google models had cut down on call times and freed them up to sell products to customers, leading to a surge in sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/verizon-says-google-ai-customer-service-agents-has-led-sales-jump-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GIJQCGBZ5PQNI3LBY5IEWMYA4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 JD Sports 未受关税影响，利润增长乏力]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国体育用品零售商 JD Sports 周三预测，即使在美国关税的潜在影响尚未显现之前，今年的利润增长也将微乎其微，主要市场的贸易环境预计将 "动荡不安"。【原文：British sportswear retailer JD Sports on Wednesday forecast little or no profit growth this year, even before any potential impact from U.S. tariffs, with the trading environment in its key markets expected to be "volatile".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-jd-sports-flags-little-profit-growth-before-any-tariff-hit-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BS5PAMP4ZPE7JEFPRQGP2347E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长称中国贸易升级是不幸的，也是他们的损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，中国对美国征收84%报复性关税的举动对中国政府来说是不幸的，也是一个失败的主张。【原文：China's move to impose 84% retaliatory tariffs against the United States is unfortunate and a losing proposition for Beijing, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-trade-escalation-unfortunate-loss-them-us-treasury-secretary-says-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7NVKWONFFPN5GYCAXL6NEDVGA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰硝基化学公司签署 3.1 亿美元协议，为美国军方供应 TNT]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰国防部副部长说，波兰炸药制造商硝化公司（Nitro-Chem）周三签署了一项协议，将向一家美国公司供应价值 12 亿兹罗提（约合 3.1 亿美元）的炸药，供美国军方使用。【原文：Polish explosives maker Nitro-Chem signed a deal on Wednesday to supply explosives worth 1.2 billion zlotys ($310 million) to a U.S. firm, intended for the U.S. military, the deputy defence minister said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/polands-nitro-chem-signs-310-mln-deal-supply-tnt-us-military-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JDSY7YF3NJIBBI76BQEXXOP6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:40:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将美国公司列入出口管制不可靠实体名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据中国商务部的声明，中国商务部周三将12家美国公司列入出口管制名单，将6家美国公司列入不可靠实体名单，并于周四生效。【原文：China's commerce ministry on Wednesday added 12 U.S. companies to its export control list and six to its unreliable entities list, effective Thursday, according to ministry statements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-adds-us-companies-lists-export-control-unreliable-entities-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2VOFKKTTJJ4XFKCO5KPVIUDRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在世贸组织对特朗普 "鲁莽 "征收关税表示 "严重关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周三告诉世界贸易组织，美国决定对北京征收所谓的对等关税，这有可能进一步破坏全球贸易的稳定。【原文：China told the World Trade Organization on Wednesday that the United States' decision to impose what it has called reciprocal tariffs on Beijing threatens to further destabilise global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-expresses-grave-concern-wto-about-reckless-trump-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMZ3OXAETBOYNI5TWO2BT4KFPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:25:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士称，在美国提高关税之际，印度正在权衡出口支持措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位政府消息人士称，在美国提高关税后全球不确定性增加的情况下，印度正在考虑采取延长银行贷款利息补贴和提供奖励等措施，以帮助出口商实现多样化。【原文：India is considering measures such as extending interest subsidies on bank loans and offering incentives to help exporters to diversify amid rising global uncertainty after the U.S. tariff hikes, two government sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-weighs-export-support-measures-amid-us-tariff-hike-say-government-sources-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3LEH6CFSRKGDN7DN4XIYXYMFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:17:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在沙特的首次亮相中，特斯拉面临着沙漠高温、充电桩数量少的问题，但马斯克没有提出抗议]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周四开始在沙特阿拉伯销售汽车，在该国连接首都利雅得和圣城麦加的一条东西向主干道上，长达 900 公里（559 英里）的路段上没有一个充电站。【原文：Tesla starts selling cars in Saudi Arabia on Thursday, a country where on a 900-kilometre (559 mile) stretch of its main east-west highway linking the capital Riyadh and the holy city of Mecca there isn't a single charging station.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/saudi-debut-tesla-faces-desert-heat-few-chargers-no-musk-protests-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLVZXP5FEZKAFOQRSA4AHP623E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期抵押贷款利率上周下降，申请量激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，最受欢迎的美国住房贷款利率降至 6.61%，为 10 月份以来的最低利率，从而推动了抵押贷款申请，即使在唐纳德-特朗普总统决定对全球贸易伙伴征收全面关税导致全球股市暴跌的情况下也是如此。【原文：The interest rate for the most popular U.S. home loan dropped to 6.61% last week, the lowest rate since October, giving a boost to mortgage applications even as global stocks tumbled in the wake of President Donald Trump's decision to impose sweeping tariffs on trading partners the world over.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-mortgage-rate-dropped-last-week-applications-surged-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CJUAWWEMZPCVFG5BNHJZXEK4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛重申年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛在周三的投资者日之前表示，将坚持其年度销售额和营业收入增长预期。【原文：Walmart is sticking to its annual sales and operating income growth forecast, the retailer said ahead of its investor day on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-reaffirms-annual-sales-forecast-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQIH4GRKDJO4TEEPP5GUEQGJB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普取消了圣诞节？中国装饰品制造商报告没有美国订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[塑料圣诞树和其他节日装饰品的中国生产商说，美国客户的订单对他们的业务至关重要，现在应该已经开始收到订单了。但由于进口关税激增，它们还没有收到订单。【原文：Chinese producers of plastic Christmas trees and other festive decorations say orders from U.S. clients, which are crucial for their business, should have started to come in by now. But because of surging import tariffs, they haven't.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/has-trump-cancelled-christmas-chinas-decorations-makers-report-no-us-orders-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBEFCKWFZ5O6TPPEO63R4AY5IU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>