<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 02:46:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 02:46:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称美国最早可能在 1 月 14 日达到新的债务限额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周五在一封信中告诉立法者，美国财政部最早可能需要在1月14日之前采取 "非常措施"，以防止美国出现债务违约。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department may need to take "extraordinary measures" by as early as Jan. 14 to prevent the United States from defaulting on its debt, Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen told lawmakers in a letter on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-may-hit-new-debt-limit-early-jan-14-yellen-says-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSM2NL55I5OJ7JRJU2BQTKTCPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 23:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求最高法院暂停执行可能禁止 TikTok 的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）敦促美国最高法院暂停联邦TikTok法律，该法律将禁止这一流行的社交媒体应用程序或迫使其出售，这位共和党美国当选总统认为，他在上任后应该有时间寻求 "政治解决 "这一问题。【原文：Donald Trump has urged the U.S. Supreme Court to pause a federal TikTok law that would ban the popular social media app or force its sale, with the Republican U.S. President-elect arguing that he should have time after taking office to pursue a "political resolution" to the issue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trump-asks-supreme-court-pause-law-that-could-ban-tiktok-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSOV4EENKVJ2ZPGH4XWJNBNRXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 22:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝索斯的蓝色起源公司首次发射新格伦火箭获得联邦航空局许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周五表示，已为杰夫-贝索斯（Jeff Bezos）的火箭公司蓝色起源（Blue Origin）的 "新格伦"（New Glenn）发射项目颁发了商业航天发射许可证。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said on Friday that it has issued a commercial space launch license for Blue Origin's — Jeff Bezos' rocket company — New Glenn launch.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/bezos-blue-origin-gets-faa-license-its-first-new-glenn-rocket-launch-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSV3TT732JPHTDPQTXCG7K57YY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 21:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦存款保险公司与 Vanguard 达成被动协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦存款保险公司周五表示，它已与 Vanguard 达成了被动协议。【原文：The Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation said on Friday it has struck a passivity agreement with Vanguard.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fdic-strikes-passivity-deal-with-vanguard-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFRL27BIRVJP5JIUOMPPQGZHHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 21:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解释器：为什么 OpenAI 计划转型为公益公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周五制定了一项计划，将其营利性部门转型为特拉华州公益公司（PBC），以帮助其筹集资金，并在与谷歌等公司的高成本人工智能竞赛中保持领先地位。【原文：OpenAI on Friday laid out a plan to transition its for-profit arm into a Delaware public benefit corporation (PBC) to help it raise capital and stay ahead in the costly AI race against companies such as Google.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/why-openai-plans-transition-public-benefit-corporation-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTPTF6IVPBNVBFCHENC5SWF2YU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 21:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在遭中国支持的 "台风盐 "网络攻击的公司名单中增加第 9 家电信公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫一位高级官员周五表示，在与中国有关的被称为 "盐台风"（Salt Typhoon）的大规模网络间谍行动中受到攻击的实体名单中，美国官员又增加了第九家电信公司。【原文：U.S. officials have added a ninth telecommunications company to the list of entities compromised by a sweeping Chinese-linked cyberespionage operation known as Salt Typhoon, a top White House official said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-adds-9th-telcom-list-companies-hacked-by-chinese-backed-salt-typhoon-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCQC4K2R2BMD7BDNV5KDJQ2BII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜克能源公司申请追回 11 亿美元飓风成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于美国的公用事业公司杜克能源周五表示，它已向佛罗里达州公共服务委员会提交了一份计划，以收回与公司紧急启动和应对飓风黛比、海伦和米尔顿有关的约 11 亿美元的直接费用。【原文：U.S.-based utility Duke Energy said on Friday it had filed a plan with the Florida Public Service Commission to recover about $1.1 billion in direct costs associated with the company's emergency activation and response to hurricanes Debby, Helene and Milton.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/duke-energy-files-recover-11-bln-hurricane-costs-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4M4UGNZ2CZMXDN2ZCKJKT5QL6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[言论自由倡导者告诉最高法院，美国的 TikTok 法律让人联想到独裁统治]]></title><description><![CDATA[言论自由倡导者周五告诉最高法院，美国针对中国拥有的 TikTok 的法律让人联想到美国专制敌人建立的审查制度。【原文：A U.S. law against Chinese-owned TikTok evokes the censorship regimes put in place by the United States' authoritarian enemies, free-speech advocates told the Supreme Court on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/free-speech-advocates-tell-supreme-court-us-tiktok-law-reminiscent-dictatorships-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLDLO5L3OJJZ7O6YYS6HOS6GDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国劳资关系委员会的案件中，星巴克就咖啡师被解雇一案提出的上诉基本败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦上诉法院周五基本驳回了星巴克对全国劳工关系委员会认定该咖啡连锁店非法解雇两名费城咖啡师的上诉，因为这两名咖啡师想组织工会。【原文：A federal appeals court on Friday largely rejected Starbucks' appeal of a National Labor Relations Board finding the coffee chain illegally fired two Philadelphia baristas because they wanted to organize a union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/starbucks-largely-loses-appeal-over-baristas-firing-nlrb-case-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JOWJJI4NRNXRLP2WWGRXGKWXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最新年度数据显示，美国无家可归者人数增加了 18%，创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国住房和城市发展部周五表示，受住房负担不起、高通胀、系统性种族主义、自然灾害和移民增加等因素的影响，去年美国无家可归者人数上升了18%，创下历史新高。【原文：There was a record 18% rise in homelessness in the U.S. in the last year, driven by factors like unaffordable housing, high inflation, systemic racism, natural disasters and rising immigration, the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-homelessness-rose-by-record-18-latest-annual-data-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQPCMMTLLBJR5PCWWDGWXHXZ6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 18:24:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[年末交易清淡，股市在税收抛售和获利了结中下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周五，科技股和成长股拖累华尔街主要股指走低，本周假期缩短，市场在传统强势期的预期推动下表现乐观。【原文：Tech and growth stocks dragged Wall Street's main indexes lower on Friday, at the end of an upbeat holiday-shortened week that was driven by expectations around a traditionally strong period for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/stocks-drop-thin-year-end-trade-amid-tax-selling-profit-taking-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UEHMPXBAJLMRK7Y3Z7W6Y66LQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 16:51:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准百时美施贵宝的 Opdivo 可注射剂型]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周五表示，它已批准了百时美施贵宝公司（Bristol Myers Squibb）大片抗癌药 Opdivo 的注射剂版本。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Friday that it has approved an injectable version of Bristol Myers Squibb's blockbuster cancer drug, Opdivo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-injectable-form-bristol-myers-opdivo-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSTUON4LUJLIHB4KIV2WEBMAFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 16:35:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[声明称数据丢失防护公司 Cyberhaven 遭到漏洞攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据保护公司 Cyberhaven 在一份分发给客户并经路透社审查的声明中说，黑客入侵了该公司的一名员工，并利用该员工的访问权限可能窃取了该公司用户的敏感信息。
声明称，黑客于周三早些时候向该公司用户推送了 Cyberhaven 的 Chrome 浏览器扩展的破解版本。该扩展【原文：Hackers compromised an employee of the data-protection company Cyberhaven and used the worker's access to potentially steal sensitive information from the firm's users, the company said in a statement distributed to customers and reviewed by Reuters.
The hackers pushed a compromised version of Cyberhaven's Chrome browser extension to the company's users early on Wednesday, the statement said. The】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/data-loss-prevention-company-cyberhaven-hit-by-breach-statement-says-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPTDVPPMLJMRTIZETEQYFGEE2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 16:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院裁定，诺华必须面对为推广多发性硬化症药物而支付回扣的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周五恢复了一起举报人诉讼，该诉讼指控瑞士制药商诺华公司向医生支付非法回扣，诱使他们推销其多发性硬化症治疗药物吉仑雅（Gilenya）。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Friday revived a whistleblower lawsuit accusing the Swiss drugmaker Novartis of paying illegal kickbacks to doctors to induce them to promote its blockbuster multiple sclerosis drug Gilenya.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/novartis-must-face-claims-it-paid-kickbacks-promote-ms-drug-us-appeals-court-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LFOS77TP5LEHBF3T6ILNVYZTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 16:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月商品贸易逆差扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于进口反弹，11 月份美国商品贸易逆差的扩大幅度超出预期，这为本季度贸易是否会在一年来首次为经济增长添砖加瓦蒙上了阴影。【原文：The U.S. goods trade deficit widened more than expected in November on a rebound in imports, clouding the picture over whether trade might add to economic growth this quarter for the first time in a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-goods-trade-gap-widens-november-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGGDSPWTXRNGFGB6ID5LOERJOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 15:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上周原油和产品库存可能下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二进行的一项调查显示，上周美国原油和燃料库存预计将下降。【原文：U.S. crude oil and fuel stockpiles are expected to have fallen last week, an extended Reuters poll showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-product-inventories-likely-fell-last-week-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5E3IUS36RM4ZMHCH7XPY4QPV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 提出向新营利结构转型的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周五制定了一项计划，将于明年对其公司结构进行改革，并表示将成立一家公益公司来管理其不断增长的业务，并放宽其当前非盈利母公司施加的限制。【原文：OpenAI on Friday laid out a plan to revamp its corporate structure next year, saying it would create a public benefit corporation to manage its growing business and ease the restrictions imposed by its current non-profit parent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-lays-out-plan-shift-new-for-profit-structure-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWYLRI3WQBIW7M332ELNFQQJLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:47:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，Jana Partners 在推动兰姆-威斯顿公司变革的过程中签下了第六位高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的一份监管文件显示，Jana Partners 正与第六位高管合作推动兰姆-韦斯顿公司（Lamb Weston）的变革，这表明这位激进投资者可能会寻求更换这家薯条生产商的大部分董事会成员。【原文：Jana Partners is working with a sixth executive to push for changes at Lamb Weston, signaling the activist investor may seek to replace the majority of the french fry maker's board, according to a regulatory filing made on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jana-partners-signs-up-sixth-executive-it-pushes-changes-lamb-weston-filing-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HDYGOBQS5LHNFT7PMDINZWALI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:45:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HomeStreet 银行将向美国银行出售 9.9 亿美元的多户住宅贷款组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[HomeStreet 银行周五表示，已同意向美国银行出售近 9.9 亿美元的多户商业房地产贷款。【原文：HomeStreet Bank said on Friday it has agreed to sell nearly $990 million of its multifamily commercial real estate loans to Bank of America .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/homestreet-bank-sell-990-mln-multifamily-loan-portfolio-bofa-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYFFL4JHJJJVBLQG5M4PRVBVLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:35:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院停止执行反洗钱法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院已停止执行一项反洗钱法，该法要求公司实体在大多数公司向美国财政部披露其真实受益所有人身份的最后期限之前披露。【原文：A U.S. appeals court has halted enforcement of an anti-money laundering law that requires corporate entities to disclose the identities of their real beneficial owners to the U.S. Treasury Department ahead of a deadline for most companies to do so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-appeals-court-halts-enforcement-anti-money-laundering-law-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAE2OWPTKJJ5DDVIMOFJTGMJ5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:35:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BioNTech 就 COVID 疫苗特许权使用费问题与美国代理机构和宾夕法尼亚大学达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[BioNTech 公司在周五提交的文件中表示，该公司已与美国国立卫生研究院和宾夕法尼亚大学就其 COVID-19 疫苗的版税支付问题分别达成了两项和解协议。【原文：BioNTech has entered into two separate settlement agreements with the U.S. National Institutes of Health and the University of Pennyslvania over the payment of royalties related to its COVID-19 vaccine, the company said in filings on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/biontech-enters-settlement-with-us-agency-upenn-over-covid-vaccine-royalties-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VH37I2SQNLLJHZ6FOXIER33DI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司向未披露的客户出售两架 C-390 军用飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周五表示，该公司已经签署了一份合同，向一家未公开的客户出售两架 C-390 千禧型军用货机。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer has signed a contract to sell two C-390 Millennium military cargo aircraft to an undisclosed client, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/embraer-sells-two-c-390-military-aircraft-undisclosed-client-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YAWU2LE3BML7N6O57NE3YPFTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:25:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾科学部警告说，削减开支可能会影响芯片和人工智能的资金投入]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾科学部周五警告说，在反对党通过要求削减经济和技术支出的法律后，明年用于半导体、人工智能和航空航天等领域的资金可能会减少200亿新台币（约合6.0911亿美元）。
在议会中占多数的台湾反对党上周通过立法，要求将中央政府的支出转到地方政府。【原文：Taiwan’s science ministry warned on Friday that funding for areas such as semiconductors, AI and aerospace could be reduced by T$20 billion ($609.11 million) for next year after opposition parties passed laws requiring cuts to economic and technology spending.
Taiwan’s opposition parties, which hold a majority in parliament, passed legislation last week to redirect spending from the central govern】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-science-ministry-warns-spending-cuts-could-hit-chips-ai-funding-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANBJ3PXEKZIJ7K5MNWQLKPAQYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:33:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 和 Amedisys 放弃终止合并协议的权利]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五提交的一份文件显示，UnitedHealth 和 Amedisys 放弃了在特定日期前终止合并协议的权利。【原文：UnitedHealth and Amedisys waived the right to terminate their merger agreement until a certain date, a filing showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/unitedhealth-amedisys-waive-right-terminate-merger-agreement-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FRYQX3AKBPPNB7I524XEG7UGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡港务局称壳牌关闭石油加工厂调查泄漏事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡海事与港务管理局（MPA）和国家环境局（NEA）周五表示，壳牌已关闭了其位于布干礁（Pulau Bukom）设施的一个石油加工装置，以调查一起疑似泄漏事件。【原文：Shell has shut down an oil processing unit at its Pulau Bukom facility to investigate a suspected leak, Singapore's Maritime and Port Authority (MPA) and National Environment Agency (NEA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-shuts-down-oil-processing-unit-investigate-leak-singapores-port-authority-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDGW26ZTXJIETHCNLHKYIX253Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[方舟的凯茜-伍德（Cathie Wood）在 "特朗普冲击 "中呼吁明确税制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技投资者凯茜-伍德（Cathie Wood）告诉路透社记者，她呼吁唐纳德-特朗普即将上任的政府通过将承诺的企业和个人减税政策追溯到2025年1月1日来促进经济增长和政策确定性。【原文：U.S. tech investor Cathie Wood is calling on Donald Trump's incoming administration to boost economic growth and policy certainty by backdating promised corporate and personal tax cuts to Jan. 1, 2025, she told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/arks-cathie-wood-calls-tax-clarity-she-rides-trump-bump-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OQM3D7EFBKT7M3NBO7IU3B4WE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 特朗普的首次行动和就业数据将在一月考验市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国股市今年的辉煌业绩收官之后，投资者预计将乘着季节性的势头进入 1 月中旬，届时一系列经济数据和华盛顿的权力交接可能会让市场蠢蠢欲动。【原文：After closing the books on a banner year for U.S. stocks, investors expect to ride seasonal momentum into mid-January when a slew of economic data and a transition of power in Washington could send markets moving.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-trumps-first-actions-job-data-test-market-january-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRSRRXEZDBLN3HQW563Z73ASTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:04:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货走软，假期缩短的一周强势收官]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货下跌，华尔街主要股指在节假日缩短的一周结束时表现乐观，市场对传统强势期的预期推动了股指的上涨。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Friday at the end of an upbeat holiday-shortened week for Wall Street's main indexes that was driven by expectations around a traditionally strong period for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-futures-ease-strong-holiday-shortened-week-draws-close-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSXA273TGRM2ND6WDTHVMV5QO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 10:41:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金因通胀降温、融资法案和假日反弹而获得大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 12 月 25 日的一周内，美国股票基金吸引了大量资金流入，从前一周的抛售中恢复过来，这主要是受到冷淡的通胀报告、避免政府停摆的临时拨款法案以及所谓的 "圣诞老人 "反弹的推动。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted significant inflows in the week to Dec. 25, recovering from a prior-week sell-off, buoyed by a cooler inflation report, a stopgap funding bill averting a government shutdown and a so-called "Santa Claus" rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-receive-big-inflows-cool-inflation-funding-bill-holiday-rally-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5K2TNSGR7RPF7BXUXRMC7NHYSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 10:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀缓解，全球股票基金重获资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至12月25日的一周内，全球股票基金资金大幅流入，从上一周的大量净卖出中反弹，这主要是受到美国通胀报告向好以及华盛顿避免了政府关门的影响，这恢复了投资者对风险资产的信心。【原文：Global equity funds witnessed sharp inflows in the week through Dec. 25, rebounding from significant net sales the previous week, buoyed by a benign U.S. inflation report and relief that Washington had averted a government shutdown, which restored investor confidence in risk assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGAE25T455J7TENCEQIRND2BVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 09:57:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>