<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 13:37:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 13:37:11 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[博世将裁员 5,550 人，德国汽车业再遭重创]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗伯特-博世（ROBG.UL）周五表示，公司计划裁员多达5550人，这是德国汽车行业陷入困境的最新迹象。【原文：Robert Bosch (ROBG.UL) said on Friday the company plans to cut up to 5,550 jobs, the latest sign of struggle in Germany's creaking auto sector, which is grappling with competition from cheaper Chinese rivals and weak demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bosch-axe-5550-jobs-latest-blow-german-auto-sector-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AR4F36NH5NSVGTFLKBPIZXIKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 13:33:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车劳工代表投票决定从 12 月初开始举行有限罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据地区 IG Metall 工会周五发表的一份声明，大众汽车的劳工代表已投票决定从 12 月初开始举行有限罢工。【原文：Volkswagen labour representatives have voted for limited strikes from early December, according to a statement from regional IG Metall trade union on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-labour-representatives-vote-limited-strikes-early-december-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIMHPN22SVN3FB2SRX656SBWIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 13:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔将以 13.3 亿美元出售个人防护设备业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔周五表示，将以约 13.3 亿美元的现金向 Protective Industrial Products 公司出售其个人防护设备业务。【原文：Honeywell said on Friday it would sell its personal protective equipment business to Protective Industrial Products for about $1.33 billion in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/honeywell-sell-personal-protective-equipment-business-133-billion-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5VTUI6FLYJNDXEWOATPNJ73KHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 12:41:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁是破产的 Northvolt 债权人？]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电动汽车电池制造商 Northvolt 在美国申请破产保护，负债 58 亿美元，现金只有 3000 万美元。【原文：Northvolt, the Swedish maker of battery cells for electric vehicles, filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the United States with debts of $5.8 billion and only $30 million in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/who-are-bankrupt-northvolts-creditors-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJZTICNEENOETLOJI2KU44BXWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 12:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国新制裁可能意味着欧盟通过俄罗斯天然气工业银行支付能源费用的终结]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯经济学家周五表示，美国对莫斯科的新制裁可能会关闭欧洲客户支付俄罗斯天然气的唯一途径，增加俄罗斯外汇市场的波动性，并将莫斯科推向中国政府的轨道。【原文：New U.S. sanctions on Moscow may shut down the only way European customers can pay for Russian gas, increase volatility on Russia's FX market and push Moscow closer to Beijing's orbit, Russian economists said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-us-sanctions-probably-spell-end-eu-energy-payments-through-russias-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKHBJ4EW3NKJFONX32A5R6CSWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 12:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国调查摩根大通与伊朗对冲基金的联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，美国财政部正在调查摩根大通与一家对冲基金的关系，据说该对冲基金是伊朗石油交易商侯赛因-沙姆哈尼（Hossein Shamkhani）网络的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department is looking into JPMorgan Chase's relationship with a hedge fund that is said to be a part of Iranian oil trader Hossein Shamkhani's network, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-probes-jpmorgans-links-with-iranian-hedge-fund-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPTZWS2LUBMM3E62MOSFKNLYR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构将考虑调查苹果和谷歌的移动浏览器]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国竞争监管机构的一份报告称，苹果可能阻碍了智能手机浏览器的创新，该机构建议利用其新权力调查苹果和谷歌在移动生态系统中的双头垄断。【原文：Apple could be holding back innovation in smartphone browsers, according to a report by Britain's competition regulator, which recommended that Apple's and Google's duopoly in mobile ecosystems should be investigated with its new powers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-regulator-will-consider-probing-apples-googles-mobile-browsers-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICVPOQ6KWBJ4VBBVXSF2JTJOA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:46:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在商业活动数据和地缘政治紧张局势面前，期货市场因谨慎而下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在商业活动调查和乌克兰与俄罗斯之间日益紧张的地缘政治局势前保持谨慎，美国股指期货周五下滑，但华尔街主要股指有望实现周线上涨。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Friday as investors remain cautious ahead of a business activity survey and increasing geopolitical tensions between Ukraine and Russia, but Wall Street's main indexes were poised for weekly gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-slip-caution-ahead-business-activity-data-geopolitical-tensions-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5G73YLVWNIWXFRKF3BN6DCOQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:33:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投诉撤销后，欧盟监管机构取消了对苹果电子书规则的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在投诉人撤回对 iPhone 制造商的投诉后，欧盟反垄断监管机构于周五结束了对苹果公司针对电子书和有声读物应用程序开发商的竞争规则长达四年之久的调查。【原文：EU antitrust regulators on Friday closed a four-year long investigation into Apple's rules for competing e-book and audiobook apps developers after the complainant withdrew its complaint against the iPhone maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-regulators-scrap-probe-into-apples-e-book-rules-after-complaint-was-withdrawn-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDSLHVMYSVLOPEGSFHQ4PS64AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gap 股价大涨，因乐观的销售预期预示着假日季的良好开端]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gap 股价周五盘前飙升 15%，原因是其四个品牌在近两年后都恢复了增长，这促使该服装零售商在假日购物季的强劲开端上调了年度销售预期。【原文：Gap shares soared 15% premarket on Friday, as a return to growth at all four of its brands after nearly two years encouraged the apparel retailer to lift its annual sales forecast in a robust start to the holiday shopping season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/gap-shares-surge-upbeat-sales-expectations-signal-promising-start-holiday-season-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDQTDFUB7JKFFLCCTFGWLZRMPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：欧元/美元逼近平价，比特币盯上 10 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5JO4DCZKBOXLPNT55CIPZ6XMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国 FDA 发现广泛使用的哮喘药物会影响大脑]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社审查的一份科学报告，美国政府研究人员发现，默克公司（Merck &amp; Co）最初销售的一种广泛处方的哮喘药可能与一些患者的严重精神健康问题有关。【原文：U.S. government researchers have found that a widely prescribed asthma drug originally sold by Merck &amp; Co may be linked to serious mental health problems for some patients, according to a scientific presentation reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-finds-widely-used-asthma-drug-impacts-brain-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JKITC5AVJOPJMQKKOZO6ZDW4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金连续第三周获得资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月20日，美国投资者连续第三周抢购股票基金，这主要是受企业盈利预期上升的乐观情绪提振，不过由于美联储对利率前景持谨慎态度以及俄罗斯与西方之间的地缘政治紧张局势，投资者的资金流入受到了抑制。【原文：U.S. investors snapped up equity funds for a third successive week through Nov. 20, buoyed by optimism over rising corporate earnings expectations, although the inflows were restrained due to a cautious Federal Reserve rate outlook and geopolitical tensions between Russia and the West.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-gain-inflows-third-week-row-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YRPUG7KMVLU3P2LEG64K6KJSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车因驱动力损失召回超过 14.5 万辆美国电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，由于驱动力损失，韩国现代汽车公司将在美国召回约145235辆电动汽车。【原文：South Korean carmaker Hyundai Motor is recalling about 145,235 electrified vehicles in the United States due to a loss of drive power, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-recalls-over-145000-electrified-us-vehicles-loss-drive-power-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFMOWT6XSBP5BGVIQNAGWCK5DQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治紧张局势导致全球股票基金每周资金流入放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至11月20日的一周里，由于俄罗斯与西方之间的地缘政治紧张局势，全球股票基金的资金流入放缓，投资者还对美国明年的利率政策前景感到焦虑。【原文：Inflows into global equity funds slowed in the week ending Nov. 20 due to geopolitical tensions between Russia and the West, with investors also anxious about the U.S. interest rate policy outlook for next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPVLTKSMH5JR5HTSVCZHPRNXHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿达尼公司的贿赂丑闻引发了市场对公开披露缺失的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年 3 月，阿达尼集团的企业财务负责人给其一家贷款机构写了一封邮件，称媒体关于该集团涉嫌在美国进行贿赂调查的报道 "毫无根据"。这封邮件还标注了最高财务主管萨加尔-阿达尼（Sagar Adani）的名字。【原文：In March, Adani Group's head of corporate finance wrote an email to one of its lenders, calling as "baseless" a media report on the group's alleged bribery investigation in the United States. That email was also marked to top finance executive Sagar Adani.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/adanis-bribery-scandal-raises-concern-market-public-disclosure-lapses-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KO7F2PZDWVLKHOUNNTJMGBAAJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Northvolt 申请破产后首席执行官下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电动汽车电池制造商 Northvolt 首席执行官彼得-卡尔松（Peter Carlsson）周五表示，在该集团申请美国破产保护一天后，他将下台。【原文：Northvolt's CEO Peter Carlsson is stepping down, the Swedish maker of battery cells for electric vehicles said on Friday, one day after the group filed for U.S. Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/northvolt-ceo-steps-down-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWJ23GIZNVLCBFPJH4SBG6OILQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 08:45:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于阿达尼在美国的贿赂起诉，您需要了解什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因涉嫌参与一项价值 2.65 亿美元的贿赂印度官员计划而被美国检方起诉，这在他同名的价值 1,420 亿美元的从港口到大豆的商业集团中引起了震动。【原文：Indian billionaire Gautam Adani has been indicted by U.S. prosecutors for his alleged role in a $265 million scheme to bribe Indian officials, sending shockwaves across his eponymous $142 billion ports-to-soybeans business conglomerate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/what-you-need-know-about-adanis-us-bribery-indictment-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LP4SUEPHCJK7VDRL2KB7HC35JM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 08:08:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从澳大利亚到以色列，阿达尼集团的项目遍布全球]]></title><description><![CDATA[在阿达尼集团创始人高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因涉嫌参与一项价值 2.65 亿美元的贿赂计划而被美国检察官起诉后，阿达尼集团在肯尼亚的两个主要项目被取消。【原文：Two major Adani Group projects in Kenya were scuttled after its founder Gautam Adani was indicted by U.S. prosecutors over his alleged role in a $265 million bribery scheme - allegations that his conglomerate has denied.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-israel-adani-group-projects-span-globe-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2UDA7WFQBPQFJIRUU42EIXV7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 08:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币屡创新高，目标直指 10 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，比特币触及历史新高，目标直指 100,000 美元大关，这是对唐纳德-特朗普政府执政后监管环境将更加友好的预期引发的加密货币大涨。【原文：Bitcoin touched a fresh record high on Friday, with its sights set firmly on the $100,000 barrier, in a stellar rally for the cryptocurrency sparked by expectations of a more friendly regulatory environment under a Donald Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-record-highs-sets-sights-100000-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3ZJJFZHBNOXDK7CSS26HHUBRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 07:59:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州州长下令州政府机构剥离中国资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[得克萨斯州共和党州长格雷格-阿博特（Greg Abbott）以金融和安全风险为由，下令州政府机构停止将州政府资金投资于中国，并在第一时间出售。【原文：Republican Governor of Texas Greg Abbott ordered state agencies to cease investing state funds in China and sell at the first available opportunity, citing financial and security risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/texas-governor-orders-state-agencies-divest-china-assets-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGHNYKD3HFOL3FMRX3NTI2JK5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 07:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国起诉后全球银行考虑停止向印度阿达尼公司提供新贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，在美国检察官以欺诈罪起诉印度阿达尼集团的亿万富翁创始人高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）后，一些全球银行正在考虑暂时停止向该集团提供新的信贷，但继续保留现有贷款。【原文：Some global banks are considering temporarily halting fresh credit to India's Adani Group but staying put with existing loans following U.S. prosecutors' indictment of its billionaire founder Gautam Adani for fraud, sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-banks-weigh-halting-fresh-credit-indias-adani-after-us-indictment-say-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z2KKTFNCMVKTNOOGF7OYTUTZLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 07:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩支持的 Kioxia 将在首次公开募股中融资 6.46 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周五提交的一份监管文件，贝恩资本（Bain Capital）支持的 Kioxia 将在该芯片制造商的首次公开募股中募集 1000 亿日元（约合 6.4545 亿美元），不包括超额配售。【原文：Bain Capital-backed Kioxia is to raise 100 billion yen ($645.45 million) excluding overallotment in the chipmaker's initial public offering, according to a regulatory filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bain-backed-kioxia-raise-646-mln-ipo-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3W235T3ZNZL3XFT7IWLBVRPI6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 07:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿达尼澳大利亚煤炭公司面临人权投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团（Adani Group）的亿万富翁董事长因欺诈被美国检察官起诉，在一个原住民团体向该国人权委员会提出投诉后，该集团在澳大利亚的煤炭部门正面临种族主义指控。【原文：India's Adani Group, whose billionaire chairman has been indicted for fraud by U.S. prosecutors, is facing accusations of racism at its Australian coal unit after an Aboriginal group filed a complaint with the country's Human Rights Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/adanis-australian-coal-unit-faces-human-rights-complaint-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IAR3Y4H2ROWLNHMPMS6OIZYB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 05:52:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价PMI迫在眉睫，比特币观望会持续升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYE5E7AHBVJO5IXFL3WSR635JE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 05:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利在新加坡设立新的东南亚总部]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）表示，本周在新加坡繁华的市中心商业区开设了新的东南亚总部。【原文：Morgan Stanley said it opened its new Southeast Asia headquarters in Singapore's swanky downtown business district this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/morgan-stanley-opens-new-southeast-asia-headquarters-singapore-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXOLOUKX2JKRZLSDYTK7RZGH3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 05:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉阿达尼创始人后，标普下调阿达尼旗下三家公司评级展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P 全球评级公司周五将阿达尼集团三家实体的评级展望从 "稳定 "下调至 "负面"，理由是该集团的亿万富翁、创始人高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因贿赂指控被美国起诉后，融资渠道面临风险。【原文：S&amp;P Global Ratings lowered its outlook on three Adani Group entities to negative from stable on Friday, citing risks to funding access following a U.S. indictment of the conglomerate's billionaire founder, Gautam Adani, on bribery charges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/sp-lowers-outlook-three-adani-units-after-us-indictment-founder-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGA6VG22F5PP7PVNR2Z4QU2IIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 04:57:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多数分析师表示，随着日元走软和特朗普的回归，日本央行将在 12 月加息：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，超过半数的经济学家认为，日本央行将在 12 月的会议上再次加息，原因是经济走强和对日元贬值的担忧促使决策者采取行动。【原文：The Bank of Japan will raise interest rates again at its December meeting as a strengthening economy and concerns over the depreciating yen prompt policymakers to act, according to just over half of economists in a Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-hike-rates-dec-yen-weakens-trump-returns-majority-analysts-say-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74JTEGBXMNN7LD64KYGLNLLY2U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 04:21:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，F1 与 ESPN 就下一份美国媒体转播权协议展开谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四称，在现有合同还剩一年的情况下，一级方程式赛车已开始与转播商 ESPN 就下一份美国媒体转播权协议进行谈判。【原文：Formula One has opened negotiations with broadcaster ESPN over its next U.S. media rights deal with one year left on the existing contract, the Financial Times said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/f1-espn-open-talks-over-next-us-media-rights-deal-ft-reports-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EM7V3KDIJZMVDJQ5L33L4ETKEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 04:12:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉后阿达尼集团公司股价连续第二个交易日下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿达尼集团公司的股价周五连续第二天下跌，此前美国检方指控这家印度企业集团的亿万富翁董事长涉嫌贿赂和欺诈。【原文：Adani Group companies' shares fell for a second straight day on Friday after U.S. prosecutors charged the Indian conglomerate's billionaire chairman in an alleged bribery and fraud scheme.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/adani-group-firms-shares-fall-second-session-after-us-indictments-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMTNAMHSPJJCZC6QRO6GKQ5QA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 04:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>