<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:40:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:40:43 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Primark 老板 Paul Marchant 在 "判断失误 "后辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国联合食品公司（Associated British Foods）称，其 Primark 服装业务的老板 Paul Marchant 已辞职，辞职立即生效，因为有个人指控他在社交环境中对她的行为。【原文：Associated British Foods said the boss of its Primark clothing business, Paul Marchant, has resigned with immediate effect following an allegation made by an individual about his behaviour towards her in a social environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/primark-boss-paul-marchant-resigns-after-error-judgement-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2SNVUO3XRJR3N5G3Q64MNDD5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯顿-马丁再获 6800 万美元融资，将出售 F1 车队股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯顿-马丁周一表示，董事长劳伦斯-斯特罗尔（Lawrence Stroll）的紫杉集团（Yew Tree Consortium）将向这家豪华汽车制造商再投资5250万英镑（6798万美元），并将持股比例增至约33%。【原文：Aston Martin said on Monday Chairman Lawrence Stroll's Yew Tree Consortium would invest a further 52.5 million pounds ($67.98 million) in the luxury carmaker and increase its stake to about 33%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/aston-martin-says-chairman-invest-further-68-million-carmaker-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIWH2ITQL5P23PEZOW6EREBGUE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:09:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：特朗普吹嘘对所有人征收关税，风险资产遭践踏]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EU7O7Q2UBRJKDG6AUV73IBOUHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:35:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道老兄，我的车呢？在混合动力车热潮中，丰田买家面临漫长等待]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位熟知内情的人士透露，丰田汽油-电力混合动力汽车需求的飙升已使供应商难以跟上步伐，导致零部件短缺，购车者需要等待数月之久。【原文：Soaring demand for Toyota's gasoline-electric hybrids has left suppliers struggling to keep pace, leading to shortages of parts and months-long waits for car buyers, according to four people familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/dude-wheres-my-car-toyota-buyers-face-long-waits-amid-hybrid-boom-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5KVSVIV3VME7KQQ6DTSABFASY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:28:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚央行董事会可能恢复减持，新成员首次亮相]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管面临通胀压力和财政困难，哥伦比亚中央银行董事会周一仍将在新董事会成员的支持下恢复基准利率的下调。【原文：Colombia's central bank board looks set on Monday to resume cuts to its benchmark interest rate with the support of new board members, despite inflation pressures and a difficult fiscal situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/colombia-central-bank-board-likely-resume-cuts-new-members-debut-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKUKRYX4M5P3TDSHHUJUHAJ4WE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国风险溢价缩减，更多现金流入欧洲]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者持有美国国债比持有德国国债所享有的溢价将创下多年来的最大季度跌幅，大西洋两岸财政政策的结构性转变预计将进一步缩小这一差距，从而吸引更多现金流向欧洲。【原文：The premium investors enjoy from holding U.S. government debt over that of Germany is set for its biggest quarterly drop in years, with tectonic fiscal policy shifts on both sides of the Atlantic expected to shrink this gap further, luring more cash to Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/shrinking-us-risk-premium-divert-more-cash-into-europe-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4BOFJOPWVIFTFMOAZP2YFA23Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油市场静观特朗普威胁征收俄罗斯石油关税是否虚张声势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，石油市场对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁要对俄罗斯石油买家征收关税的言论无动于衷，因为白宫发出的一系列威胁所带来的震撼已开始让厌倦的交易商们感到厌倦。【原文：Oil markets on Monday shrugged off U.S. President Donald Trump's threat to hit buyers of Russian oil with tariffs as the shock value of the barrage of threats from the White House begins to wear thin with jaded traders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-markets-wait-see-if-trumps-russian-oil-tariff-threat-is-bluff-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36UA44YTZBN5PGLUDOYAEIDKEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国智璞人工智能公司推出免费人工智能代理，加剧国内技术竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创公司智普人工智能（Zhipu AI）周一发布了一款免费的人工智能代理，加入了中国竞争日益激烈的人工智能市场的类似发布浪潮。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence startup Zhipu AI unveiled a free AI agent on Monday, joining a wave of similar launches in China's increasingly competitive AI market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinas-zhipu-ai-launches-free-ai-agent-intensifying-domestic-tech-race-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AO3YENGMIJOUNFVKS2RQQE5V3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:02:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电在海外扩张的同时，在台湾新建国内晶圆厂，确认对台湾的承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[台积电周一表示，其新建的国内晶圆厂将为台湾经济增加 7000 个技术岗位，并将继续在台湾扩张。【原文：TSMC said on Monday that its newly built domestic fab would add 7,000 tech jobs to the island's economy and that it will continue to expand in Taiwan, following concern that its investment in the U.S. will dilute its presence at home.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-affirms-commitment-taiwan-with-new-domestic-fab-amid-overseas-expansion-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6HQ2X5J7FJN25K36FIMRRBSJQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛预计美国联邦储备委员会 2025 年将降息三次]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）以关税不确定性为由，目前预计美国联邦储备委员会今年将降息三个季度点。
这家华尔街经纪公司在周日的一份说明中表示，预计今年将在7月、9月和11月连续降息三次，而之前的预测是在6月和12月降息两次。【原文：Goldman Sachs now expects the U.S. Federal Reserve to deliver three quarter point interest rate cuts this year, citing tariff uncertainty.
The Wall Street brokereage expects three consecutive cuts this year in July, September, and November, compared to its previous forecast of two cuts in June and December, it said in a note on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-expects-us-fed-deliver-three-rate-cuts-2025-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4K77HJIGJJ7ROBVJNIEZNE7UI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[让欧洲再次伟大 "的贸易正获得牵引力]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个更加独立、不那么依赖美国的欧洲正在形成，投资者在这个被长期回避的地区感受到的机会不仅仅是抢购国防股票。【原文：A more independent, less U.S.-reliant Europe is taking shape and investors sense opportunities in a long-shunned region that go beyond just snapping up defence shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/make-europe-great-again-trades-are-gaining-traction-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLNBDI5CO5K6XPV26RRDLR62M4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:04:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对中国和美国公司而言，特朗普的贸易战这次更可怕]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国供应商和他们的美国客户现在正在面对严峻的现实，即这场贸易战将在 2018 年给特朗普的第一个任期带来更严重的冲击。【原文：Chinese suppliers and their American clients are now coming to grips with the grim reality that this trade war will hit harder than in Trump's first term in 2018.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/china-us-inc-trumps-trade-war-feels-much-worse-this-time-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DP7SLJTHWNNMFHXBG62CWXPJRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战困境推动黄金屡创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税计划会引发全球贸易战和经济后果，投资者纷纷转向避险资产，黄金周一触及历史新高，突破了3,100美元的水平。【原文：Gold touched an all-time high on Monday, breaching the $3,100 level, as investors turned to the safe-haven asset amid concerns that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff plans would stoke a global trade war and economic fallout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trade-war-woes-propel-gold-record-highs-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPLWV4WGK5MNZKI6DHPGJQPTXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:24:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本财务大臣称将就外汇问题与美国密切沟通]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣加藤胜信周一表示，他将与美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）就外汇问题进行密切沟通，并指出密切对话对市场稳定非常重要。【原文：Japan Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato said on Monday that he would communicate closely with U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on foreign exchange, pointing out that close dialogue is important for market stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-finance-minister-says-he-will-closely-communicate-with-us-forex-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FWPZ4KAKFP47GBEPO6FYNKCRE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税和不确定性推动避险资金流入，黄金飙升突破 3100 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，金价首次飙升至每盎司 3100 美元以上，原因是对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税和潜在经济影响的担忧，以及对地缘政治的担忧，推动了新一轮对避险资产的投资热潮。【原文：Gold prices on Monday soared above $3,100 per ounce for the first time as concerns around U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs and the potential economic fallout, combined with geopolitical worries, drove a fresh wave of investments into the safe-haven asset.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-surges-past-3100-us-tariffs-uncertainty-propel-safe-haven-flows-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5MXEG3G7NPLVE7AAIVCJAPU4U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾总统在美国可能征收关税前听取简报]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾总统赖清德办公室周一表示，赖清德总统周日晚会见了高级官员，讨论了美国关税可能带来的影响，并听取了应急计划的最新进展。【原文：Taiwan President Lai Ching-te met senior officials on Sunday night to discuss the possible impact of U.S. tariffs and receive an update on contingency plans, his office said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-president-briefed-ahead-possible-us-tariffs-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4L46IGUVSRPAFOGKCGE6SCLCT4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:11:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[订单强劲，中国制造业创 12 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项工厂调查显示，中国制造业活动在 3 月份以一年来最快的速度扩张，新订单促进了生产，使这个世界第二大经济体在应对愈演愈烈的美国贸易战时得到了一些缓解。【原文：China's manufacturing activity expanded at the fastest pace in a year in March, a factory survey showed on Monday, with new orders boosting production, giving the world's No.2 economy some reprieve as it deals with an intensifying U.S. trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-manufacturing-activity-picks-up-march-pmi-shows-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANIG3ZLQ6BOANF3ODV677ODKJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:42:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国有媒体批评港口交易，长江和记股价下跌 4.5%]]></title><description><![CDATA[长江和记 0001.HK 股价周一最多下跌了 4.7%，此前中国国家媒体批评了这家香港企业集团的巴拿马港口交易，消息人士称，预计于 4 月 2 日签署的交易将被推迟。【原文：Shares of CK Hutchison 0001.HK fell as much as 4.7% on Monday after China state media criticised the Hong Kong conglomerate's Panama port deal and sources said the deal, which was expected to be signed on April 2, would be delayed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ck-hutchison-shares-set-open-down-45-china-state-media-blasts-port-deal-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZO6TKIJAJM6TFLOVE7YKHR7WI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:34:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元上涨，黄金创历史新高，关税忧虑点燃避险需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于交易商担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策将引发通货膨胀并抑制经济增长，避险货币日元周一上涨，而黄金则升至历史新高。【原文：The safe-haven Japanese yen rose on Monday while gold pushed to a fresh all-time peak as traders worried that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs will ignite inflation and crimp economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yen-gains-gold-record-high-tariff-angst-ignites-haven-demand-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6MZ3J46MROFJC3EQ4MU64QEEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管特朗普警告可能对俄罗斯买家征收关税，但油价仍有所松动]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普警告说，如果他认为莫斯科阻碍了他结束乌克兰战争的努力，他可能会对俄罗斯石油的买家征收二级关税，但周一油价仍有所回落，有望实现季度微跌。【原文：Oil prices eased on Monday, heading for a slight quarterly loss despite a warning by U.S. President Donald Trump that he may impose secondary tariffs on buyers of Russian oil if he feels Moscow is blocking his efforts to end the war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-ease-despite-trump-warning-possible-tariffs-russian-buyers-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57OLEXU5NBLIJO43L3VOFRYK2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新华社：中国海洋石油总公司在南海发现亿吨级油田]]></title><description><![CDATA[据新华社周一报道，中国海洋石油总公司（中海油）在南海发现了一个探明储量超过 1 亿吨的油田。【原文：The China National Offshore Oil Corporation (CNOOC) has discovered an oilfield in the South China Sea with proven reserves exceeding 100 million tonnes, Xinhua news agency reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-cnooc-discovers-100-mln-ton-oilfield-south-china-sea-xinhua-says-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KOVL7FSDVICFO6CGEB3Y72EMU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港长江和记表示尚未决定电信公司分拆事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港企业集团长江和记董事会周一表示，针对媒体有关其全球电信业务可能分拆上市的报道，该公司尚未作出任何决定。【原文：The board of Hong Kong conglomerate CK Hutchison said on Monday it has not made any decision on its global telecommunications business, in response to media reports about a potential spin-off listing of the assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/hong-kongs-ck-hutchison-says-no-decision-made-telco-spin-off-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2DNLEAGNFFJT5PDX7PXHUUZHJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中银航空将购买 120 架波音和空客飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于新加坡的中银航空周一表示，已与波音公司达成协议，购买 50 架波音 737-8 飞机，具体价格未透露。【原文：Singapore-based BOC Aviation said on Monday it has entered into an agreement with Boeing to purchase 50 Boeing 737-8 aircraft for an undisclosed sum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boc-aviation-buy-120-boeing-airbus-aircraft-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQIC2KE4MNLVNA4KLQSEGVQNZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税倒计时，股市下滑，债券反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市跟随华尔街期货走低，因为投资者在对美国即将征收关税的形式和范围知之甚少的情况下，难以对即将到来的关税风险进行定价。【原文：Asia stocks followed Wall Street futures lower on Monday as investors struggled to price in the risk of imminent U.S. tariffs with so little still known about what form or scope the levies will take.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKWEKZBOPFILFGZFPVB5FNYEBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:22:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥克兰机场在监察机构批评后削减旅客收费]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰奥克兰国际机场周一表示，在该国竞争监督机构称机场运营商向航空公司和旅客多收费用后，该机场将削减航空公司的旅客收费。【原文：New Zealand's Auckland International Airport said on Monday it will cut airline passenger charges after the country's competition watchdog said the airport operator was overcharging airlines and travellers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/auckland-airport-cuts-passenger-charges-after-watchdogs-criticism-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCVRAEG4X5KANAJW46WFORRMIM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称对等关税将针对所有国家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周日表示，他将于本周宣布的互惠互利关税将包括所有国家，而不仅仅是由 10 到 15 个国家组成的小集团。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday reciprocal tariffs he is set to announce this week will include all nations, beyond just a smaller group of 10 to 15 countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-says-reciprocal-tariffs-will-target-all-countries-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RR3J44K2UVNHNHCNFSVSD3ZKWM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:11:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 TikTok 出售协议将在周六截止日期前达成]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，将在周六截止日期前与 TikTok 的中国母公司字节跳动达成协议，出售这款有 1.7 亿美国人使用的短视频应用。【原文：President Donald Trump said a deal with TikTok's Chinese parent ByteDance to sell the short video app used by 170 million Americans would be struck before a deadline on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-says-tiktok-sale-deal-come-before-saturday-deadline-2025-03-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6GTL6H6WRO53K36AOO7KT7HYU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WiseTech Global 任命 Chris Charlton 和 Andrew Harrison 为独立非执行董事]]></title><description><![CDATA[慧科全球（WiseTech Global）周一表示，已任命克里斯-查尔顿（Chris Charlton）和安德鲁-哈里森（Andrew Harrison）为董事会独立非执行董事，此举旨在使其审计与风险委员会符合交易所规定。【原文：WiseTech Global said on Monday it has appointed Chris Charlton and Andrew Harrison as independent non-executive directors to its board, in a move to make its audit and risk committee compliant with exchange regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wisetech-global-appoints-chris-charlton-andrew-harrison-independent-non-2025-03-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CO2EYOSN5JCHFGAFYH7S5UMKE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 22:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《澳大利亚金融时报》报道，维珍澳大利亚公司高管将与投资者会面，商讨在澳大利亚证券交易所重新上市事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《澳大利亚金融评论报》（AFR）周日晚间报道，贝恩资本控股的维珍澳大利亚公司将在 2020 年退市后重返澳大利亚证券交易所。【原文：Bain Capital-owned Virgin Australia is set to return to the Australian stock exchange after delisting in 2020, the Australian Financial Review (AFR) reported late on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/virgin-australia-executives-set-meet-investors-relisting-asx-afr-reports-2025-03-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUF5MFUE5RMFTAZ3UEC36CYKHY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国肖尔茨表示欧盟已准备好在贸易关税问题上回应美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理奥拉夫-肖尔茨（Olaf Scholz）周日表示，欧洲希望与美国合作，但如果华盛顿在别无选择的情况下对钢铁和铝征收关税，欧盟已做好统一应对的准备。【原文：Europe wants to cooperate with the United States but the EU is ready to respond as one if Washington leaves it no choice by imposing tariffs on steel and aluminium, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eu-ready-respond-us-trade-tariffs-says-germanys-scholz-2025-03-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VO4LMDDVCBKNNJNPYJ4HIADLOE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:18:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>