<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:33:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:33:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨勒姆称CPI数据降温 "令人鼓舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周四表示，当天早些时候公布的消费者物价数据正朝着正确的方向发展。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis President Alberto Musalem said on Thursday that consumer price data released earlier in the day is moving in the right direction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-musalem-says-cooler-cpi-data-is-encouraging-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTAV47PP3FMTBCHNBXIVT6TUQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:31:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求复苏乏力，Conagra Brands 预计全年销售额和利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[康奈格拉品牌公司（Conagra Brands）周四预测的年度收入和利润低于分析师的预期，原因是资金紧张的消费者转而选择价格更低廉的家庭主食。【原文：Conagra Brands forecast annual revenue and profit below analysts' estimates on Thursday, as cash-strapped consumers turned to cheaper pantry staples for their at-home meals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/conagra-brands-projects-lower-annual-sales-profit-tepid-demand-recovery-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEHZU74KJZNVRN3CGAO6A2F7UI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:25:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员希望波音公司首席执行官在准备新的 FAA 立法时出庭作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商务委员会主席玛丽亚-坎特韦尔（Maria Cantwell）周四表示，她希望波音公司首席执行官戴夫-卡尔霍恩（Dave Calhoun）在她准备立法加强联邦航空管理局对飞机制造商的监督时出席她的委员会。【原文：U.S. Senate Commerce Committee chair Maria Cantwell said Thursday she wants Boeing CEO Dave Calhoun to appear before her committee as she prepares legislation that would boost Federal Aviation Administration oversight of planemakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/senator-wants-boeing-ceo-testify-she-prepares-new-faa-legislation-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIGPMO6QUJPANGIQ3UKDC2CW7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:47:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织认为美国联邦储备委员会有望在今年晚些时候降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五表示，该组织仍然认为美联储可能会在今年晚些时候开始降息，并应保持谨慎，即使美国6月份消费者价格的下跌提高了提前降息的预期。【原文：The International Monetary Fund said on Friday it continues to believe that the Federal Reserve could start cutting interest rates later this year and should stay cautious, even as a fall in U.S. June consumer prices raises expectations for an earlier rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/imf-sees-us-fed-position-cut-interest-rates-later-this-year-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAD4W55ASBKNJCZZGSUS77OMYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，美国联邦贸易委员会将在埃克森仲裁期间推迟对雪佛龙-赫斯交易做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，美国联邦贸易委员会计划推迟决定是否阻止雪佛龙公司以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司，直到与埃克森美孚公司的仲裁案得到解决。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission plans to delay its decision whether to block Chevron's $53 billion takeover of Hess until after an arbitration case with Exxon Mobil is settled, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-ftc-delay-decision-chevron-hess-deal-during-exxon-arbitration-bloomberg-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZ3WG53ZFVNMNL7LHLMGM363GA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利称 "很可能 "需要调整政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周四表示，近期较低的通胀读数让人 "松了一口气"，她预计物价压力和劳动力市场将进一步放缓，从而有理由降息。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly on Thursday said that recent cooler inflation readings are a "relief" and she expects further easing in both price pressures and the labor market to warrant interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-daly-says-policy-adjustments-likely-warranted-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJWW5ZN46ZPLFGXRFJX56OMPJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:21:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪：私人信贷增长的新时代引发担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪评级公司（Moody's Ratings）的最新报告指出，由于缺乏监督和透明度，私人信贷借贷的快速增长超出了其传统市场，给美国经济带来了潜在的未来风险。【原文：The rapid growth of private credit lending beyond its traditional market presents potential future risks to the U.S. economy due to lack of oversight and transparency, according to a new Moody's Ratings report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/new-era-private-credit-growth-raises-concerns-moodys-says-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAYM3AKA5FMCDHLUFWB2PSBWZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:09:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约欺诈案庭审结束，律师称 Ozy Media 的卡洛斯-沃森被撒谎的联合创始人出卖了]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在前新闻主播欺诈案的结案陈词中，一名辩护律师说，Ozy Media 的联合创始人卡洛斯-沃森（Carlos Watson）遭到了一名高级副手的背叛，这名副手向投资者撒谎并伪造文件，以掩盖这家初创公司糟糕的财务状况。【原文：Ozy Media co-founder Carlos Watson was betrayed by a top deputy who lied to investors and forged documents to hide the startup’s dire finances, a defense lawyer said on Thursday during closing arguments in the former news anchor’s fraud trial.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ozy-medias-carlos-watson-was-betrayed-by-lying-co-founder-lawyer-says-new-york-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UD4AOUNK4ZLCFFOSXBEK3OVPIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特斯拉将机器人出租车的推出时间从 8 月推迟到 10 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引熟悉这一决定的人士的话报道，特斯拉正将其Robotaxi的推出时间从8月推迟到10月。【原文：Tesla is delaying the launch of its Robotaxi to October from August, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-delays-robotaxi-launch-october-august-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3C7C2RUZRNRVADGETHQ74NYRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:58:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[低收入消费者的经济压力蔓延，百事公司倍感压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事公司首席执行官拉蒙-拉瓜尔塔（Ramon Laguarta）周四表示，美国各收入群体而不仅仅是低收入消费者对价格的敏感度 "要高得多"，这凸显了百事公司对消费者需求广泛变化的敏感性。【原文：PepsiCo CEO Ramon Laguarta said Thursday there is "much more price sensitivity" across U.S. income groups and not just low-income consumers, highlighting its sensitivity to broad shifts in consumer demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pepsico-feels-squeeze-financial-pressure-spreads-low-income-consumers-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOWFW34XU5LUZB6DPIJ6LXQPU4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:55:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着经济危机加深，古巴加大对私营企业的压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[古巴正在收紧对新兴私营企业的监管，控制利润并加强监督，因为政府正在努力研究如何以最佳方式管理这个由共产党统治的国家中快速增长的私营企业。【原文：Cuba is tightening regulations on fledgling private businesses, reining in profits and beefing up oversight as the government wrestles with how best to manage fast-growing private enterprise in the communist-run country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/cuba-ratchets-up-pressure-private-business-economic-crisis-deepens-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7A27O2LXFM75IKRRPKKNUEBVQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[野兽男孩就 "破坏 "广告起诉辣椒餐馆老板]]></title><description><![CDATA[Beastie Boys 在纽约联邦法院起诉餐厅所有者布林克国际公司（Brinker International），称布林克公司在未经他们许可的情况下，使用这支传奇说唱三人组 1994 年创作的歌曲 "Sabotage "来宣传 Chili's 连锁餐厅。【原文：The Beastie Boys have sued restaurant owner Brinker International in New York federal court, saying Brinker used the legendary rap trio's 1994 song "Sabotage" to promote the Chili's chain without their permission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/beastie-boys-sue-chilis-owner-over-sabotage-ads-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HA7FN43ZO5J27O6SAD33CXQ454</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:39:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车将投资 9 亿美元改造密歇根汽车厂以生产电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长詹妮弗-格兰霍姆（Jennifer Granholm）周四表示，通用汽车公司计划投资至少 9 亿美元对密歇根州兰辛的一家汽车厂进行改造，以生产电动汽车。【原文：General Motors plans to invest at least $900 million to retool a Lansing, Michigan auto plant to build electric vehicles, Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-invest-900-million-retool-michigan-auto-plant-build-evs-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAHYG3HILZLT3I6XAICUU3P6SM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院委员会投票决定公布 TikTok 诉讼案闭门听证记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院一个委员会周四投票决定公布 3 月份闭门听证会的记录，内容涉及 TikTok 在为司法部辩护时对司法部构成的威胁，司法部试图通过法律迫使 TikTok 的中国所有者剥离这款热门应用在美国的资产。【原文：A U.S. House committee on Thursday voted to release a transcript of a closed-door hearing in March on threats posed by TikTok to the Justice Department in its defense of a law that seeks to force its Chinese owner to divest the popular app's U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-house-committee-votes-release-closed-door-hearing-transcript-tiktok-lawsuit-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5TSS6IKTJJMVLLI6EDBQIMPV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:18:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[信中称，共和党议员对微软与 G42 的人工智能交易深表担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党议员要求拜登政府就微软向阿联酋人工智能公司 G42 投资 15 亿美元一事进行情报通报，理由是他们对敏感技术的转让以及该协议缺乏规则或国会监督深表关切。【原文：Republican lawmakers are seeking an intelligence briefing from the Biden administration on Microsoft's $1.5 billion investment in UAE-based artificial intelligence firm G42, citing deep concerns over the transfer of sensitive technology and the lack of rules or congressional oversight regarding the agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/republican-lawmakers-deeply-concerned-over-microsoft-g42-ai-deal-letter-says-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIE77ZKIDZMHTBJ7OIEPHIV4XI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰富瑞称，美国法院推翻 "雪佛龙尊重原则 "可能会限制对电动汽车和更安全化学品的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰富瑞（Jefferies）分析师表示，美国最高法院最近决定推翻 1984 年的一项先例，即允许政府机构解释不明确的法律，这可能会抑制对电动汽车的投资和用于制造业的更安全化学品的开发。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court's recent decision to overturn a 1984 precedent, which allowed government agencies to interpret unclear laws, could curb investments in electric vehicles and the development of safer chemicals used in manufacturing, according to a Jefferies analyst.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-courts-reversal-chevron-deference-may-limit-investments-evs-safer-chemicals-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4TEW6D3QVO6NNIVVOZ2BSTRVQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:38:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[温和的美国 6 月 CPI 为美联储宽松政策铺平道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 6 月份消费者物价意外下降，年增幅为一年来最小，这强化了通货紧缩趋势重回正轨的观点，使美联储距离降息又近了一步。【原文：U.S. consumer prices unexpectedly fell in June and the annual increase was the smallest in a year, reinforcing views that the disinflation trend was back on track and drawing the Federal Reserve another step closer to cutting interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-tame-us-june-cpi-smoothes-path-fed-ease-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZD7WDHBGJJBXCVE5HKAX5CWFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷神公司赢得 12 亿美元合同，向德国提供更多爱国者防空导弹防御系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[RTX 旗下的雷神技术公司（Raytheon Technologies）周四表示，该公司已获得一份价值 12 亿美元的合同，将为德国提供更多的 "爱国者 "防空和导弹防御系统。【原文：RTX's Raytheon Technologies said on Thursday that it has been awarded a $1.2 billion contract to supply Germany with additional Patriot air and missile defense systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/raytheon-wins-12-bln-contract-additional-patriot-air-missile-defense-systems-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DQZ4YY25RJKHNJH455FTQ5RBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩资本将以 45 亿美元收购金融软件供应商 Envestnet]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融软件供应商 Envestnet 周四表示，私募股权公司贝恩资本（Bain Capital）将以 45 亿美元的价格收购 Envestnet，贝莱德（BlackRock）和富达投资（Fidelity Investments）等一批投资者也将提供支持。【原文：Private equity firm Bain Capital will buy Envestnet in a $4.5 billion deal, with backing from a cohort of investors, including BlackRock and Fidelity Investments, the financial software vendor said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-capital-buy-financial-software-vendor-envestnet-45-bln-deal-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LOQWQSBSFPGDMRDRMR4BFHXO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，区块投资者需要更多信息来衡量加密货币部门的盈利潜力]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰克-多西（Jack Dorsey）领导的支付技术公司布洛克（Block）可能会成为加密货币挖矿行业的强大参与者，但分析师表示，华尔街需要了解利润率方面的详细信息，以衡量这项业务带来的盈利尾风。【原文：Jack Dorsey-led payments technology firm Block could become a formidable player in the crypto mining industry, but Wall Street will need details on profit margins to gauge the earnings tailwind from this business, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/block-investors-need-more-gauge-crypto-units-earnings-potential-analysts-say-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WC6RE3AJ5FJQRLA2CLJGOPQJNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:05:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数降幅超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量降幅超过预期，但由于汽车制造商闲置工厂进行改造，每年这个时候都会出现波动，因此很难对劳动力市场做出准确判断。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits dropped more than expected last week, but volatility around this time of the year as automobile manufacturers idle plants for retooling makes it harder to get a clean read on the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-more-than-expected-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVJ3RHRO2RJYNCS42UWM6OGBQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:43:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CPI数据公布后，交易员加大对美联储9月降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在一份政府报告显示6月份通胀率下降后，交易员们加大了对美联储将于9月份开始降息的押注。
利率期货价格显示，美联储在9月份会议上降息的可能性约为85%，而在报告公布前，降息的可能性约为70%。交易商还【原文：Traders on Wednesday boosted bets that the Federal Reserve will start cutting rates in September after a government report showed inflation receding in June.
Interest-rate futures prices reflected about an 85% chance of a rate cut at the Fed's September meeting, compared with about a 70% chance seen before the report, which showed consumer prices unexpectedly fell last month from May. Traders also】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/traders-boost-bets-fed-rate-cut-sept-after-cpi-data-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WX5DYUESSRIQBN3UNUHY4GQ6RA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:39:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月消费者价格意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者物价意外下降，年增幅为一年来最小，这强化了通货紧缩趋势重回正轨的观点，使美联储距离降息又近了一步。【原文：U.S. consumer prices unexpectedly fell and the annual increase was the smallest in a year, reinforcing views that the disinflation trend was back on track and drawing the Federal Reserve another step closer to cutting interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-prices-unexpectedly-fall-june-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USIIV6BBFZKIDK5WFKAKTHO5JA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:35:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，投资组合经理预计第三季度信贷状况恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际信贷组合经理协会的一项调查显示，全球最大金融机构的投资组合经理预计未来三个月信贷状况将恶化。【原文：Portfolio managers at the world's largest global financial institutions expect credit conditions to worsen over the next three months, according to a survey by the International Association of Credit Portfolio Managers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/portfolio-managers-expect-worse-credit-conditions-q3-survey-shows-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVFWEHCTYNMKFDB35KTCSJ33MM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于需求不振，Conagra Brands 预计全年有机销售额低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[康奈格拉品牌公司（Conagra Brands）周四预计全年营收低于预期，原因是生活成本居高不下继续拖累销售量，导致资金紧张的购物者转而选择更便宜的家庭用餐替代品。【原文：Conagra Brands forecast annual revenue below estimates on Thursday, as cash-strapped shoppers turned to cheaper alternatives for their at-home meals as high living costs continued to weigh on sales volumes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/conagra-brands-forecasts-annual-organic-sales-below-estimates-tepid-demand-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27RH2KINGVM3JLF4HWSOLT5NQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:39:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易公司从英国石油公司和壳牌石油公司吸引顶尖人才]]></title><description><![CDATA[多位消息人士周四告诉路透社，最近几周，几位知名的能源交易员从石油巨头公司辞职，转投贸易公司，因为资产易手后人才流失，贸易公司也在增加奖金。【原文：Several high-profile energy traders have in recent weeks quit oil majors for trading houses, multiple sources told Reuters on Thursday, as talent follows assets swapping hands and as trading houses ramp up bonuses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trading-houses-lure-top-talent-bp-shell-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7V4T27DKFOXJDVPLMVHLJXOMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车通过 QuantumScape 交易提高固态电池产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司与美国初创公司 QuantumScape 周四表示，大众汽车将大幅提高与 QuantumScape 合作开发的固态电池的产量，因为这家德国汽车制造商的目标是将这种技术应用到更多的汽车上。【原文：Volkswagen will massively ramp up production of solid-state batteries developed with U.S. startup QuantumScape , both companies said on Thursday, as the German carmaker aims to bring the technology into more vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-ramp-up-solid-state-battery-production-quantumscape-deal-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZJ73HO2GJOQ3MHMKWSCGJDQFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空盈利前景弱于华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周四预计，本季度利润将低于分析师预期，原因是低端市场面临折扣压力。【原文：Delta Air Lines on Thursday forecast lower profits in the current quarter than analysts had expected, with the carrier citing discounting pressure in the low end of the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-earnings-outlook-weaker-than-wall-street-forecast-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPEQA7KBRFKCNKUK7KZ2ILVW3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 10:39:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通旨在积累 15%的美国消费者存款，提高信用卡份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的银行希望变得更大。【原文：The biggest U.S. bank wants to get even bigger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-aims-amass-15-us-consumer-deposits-boost-credit-card-share-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6C3EHQL7PVICRBAVURWVB3XLCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 10:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在通胀数据考验涨势之前，期货走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街期货周四下滑，因为市场正在为一项关键的美国通胀数据做准备，该数据可能会增强美国联邦储备委员会放宽政策的预期，并使股市继续保持破纪录的上涨势头。【原文：Wall Street futures slipped on Thursday as markets braced for a key U.S. inflation print that could bolster expectations of policy easing from the U.S. Federal Reserve and keep equities on their record-breaking run.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-lower-ahead-rally-testing-inflation-data-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLDWHJMDPJINLK5COBZUFTKP4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 10:24:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>