<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 20:37:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 20:37:11 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[外国投资者增加对美股投资组合的美元套期保值]]></title><description><![CDATA[海外资产管理公司和养老金正在增加对美元走软的保护，因为他们担心美国货币分散其美国股票投资组合的能力会下降。【原文：Overseas asset managers and pensions are adding protection against a weakening dollar, concerned about the U.S. currency's diminishing ability to diversify their U.S. equity portfolios.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/foreign-investors-increase-dollar-hedges-us-stock-portfolios-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFSMDIDTBNN4TIXRI24YKQVCCA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 19:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[云计算设计师平台 Figma 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[基于云计算的设计师平台 Figma 周二在美国申请首次公开募股。【原文：Cloud-based designer platform Figma filed for an initial public offering in the U.S. on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cloud-based-designer-platform-figma-files-us-ipo-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKLYKGPN7BMTXF42RVIQ2NP7IE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 19:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示不会延长 7 月 9 日的贸易最后期限，并对日本协议表示怀疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，他不考虑延长各国与美国谈判贸易协议的7月9日最后期限，并继续对能否与日本达成协议表示怀疑。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Tuesday he was not thinking of extending the July 9 deadline for countries to negotiate trade deals with the U.S., and continued to express doubt that an agreement could be reached with Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-he-wont-extend-july-9-trade-deadline-expresses-doubt-japan-deal-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6N5RE234VJLNVG7PGJXY5CUUDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 19:20:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于欧盟对碳排放的罚款，Stellantis 可能关闭工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯特兰蒂斯公司（Stellantis）欧洲区负责人周二表示，由于不遵守二氧化碳排放目标，该公司可能面临欧盟巨额罚款的风险，因此可能不得不关闭工厂。【原文：Stellantis may have to close factories due to the risk of hefty European Union fines for not complying with CO2 emission targets, the head of the Franco-Italian automaker for Europe said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/stellantis-may-close-factories-due-eu-fines-carbon-emissions-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QPVNLFA3FKRDLKOODQ6X3IEO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 18:34:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔称美元互换额度仍是重要工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔周二表示，美国央行没有计划改变向其他官方实体提供美元流动性的方式。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said Tuesday the U.S. central bank has no plans to change how it offers dollar liquidity to other official entities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-powell-says-dollar-swap-lines-remain-important-tool-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSWRQMAVBZPPXNFRTWK3WBNLPQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 18:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：瑞银从摩根士丹利聘请泰勒-亨里克斯（Taylor Henricks）担任美洲并购部主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，瑞银集团聘请泰勒-亨里克斯（Taylor Henricks）担任美洲并购业务主管，以拓展在美国的投资银行业务。【原文：UBS hired Taylor Henricks as its head of mergers and acquisitions in the Americas as it seeks to expand investment banking in the U.S., according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-hires-taylor-henricks-head-ma-americas-morgan-stanley-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGVRNRFBEVOXVC2LSRCVA2RH54</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美国参议院在最后一刻做出了修改，但该法案还是对可再生能源造成了沉重打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业倡导者和立法者表示，尽管取消了一些有争议的条款，但周二通过的美国参议院大规模预算法案将加大风能和太阳能项目的开发难度。【原文：The U.S. Senate's massive budget bill that passed on Tuesday will make it harder to develop wind and solar energy projects, despite the removal of some contentious provisions, industry advocates and lawmakers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/despite-last-minute-changes-senate-bill-deals-big-blow-renewable-energy-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFD3KWKLCZPVFGT7K5XUBE4NLQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 投资者对美国参议院通过特朗普大型税收法案的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党控制的美国参议院周二通过了唐纳德-特朗普总统的全面减税和支出法案，该法案被称为 "美丽的大法案"。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. Senate passed President Donald Trump's sweeping tax-cut and spending bill termed the "big, beautiful bill" on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/view-investors-react-us-senate-passes-trumps-big-tax-bill-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKLZOTJB3RJOHKMREWZDPSMIII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于工厂检修，美国 6 月液化天然气出口量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融公司 LSEG 的初步数据显示，由于美国一些最大出口设施的维护工作影响了产量，6 月份美国液化天然气出口量降至年内第二低的月度水平。【原文：U.S. liquefied natural gas exports fell to their second lowest monthly level for the year in June, as maintenance work at some of the country's largest export facilities hurt output, according to preliminary data from financial firm LSEG.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-lng-exports-fall-june-due-plant-maintenance-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXDUZSPAAVMJLBCVPSSFVOYKKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:16:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISDA 称第一季度针对英国违约的保护交易猛增]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际掉期及衍生品协会周二的一份报告显示，为投资者提供英国公司违约保护的衍生品合约交易额在2025年第一季度跃升近50%，达到2万多亿美元。【原文：Trading of derivatives contracts that provide investors with protection against UK company defaults jumped almost 50% in the first quarter of 2025 to more than $2 trillion, an International Swaps and Derivatives Association report showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trading-protection-against-uk-defaults-jumped-q1-says-isda-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGJFZ5H4M5POJEYCW2XISX6R44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定中国华为必须面对美国刑事指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官周二驳回了华为技术公司（Huawei Technologies）要求驳回大部分联邦起诉书的请求，这些起诉书指控这家中国电信公司试图窃取美国竞争对手的技术机密，并就其在伊朗的工作误导银行。【原文：A U.S. judge on Tuesday rejected Huawei Technologies' bid to dismiss most of a federal indictment accusing the Chinese telecommunications company of trying to steal technology secrets from U.S. rivals, and misleading banks about its work in Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/chinas-huawei-must-face-us-criminal-charges-judge-rules-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7IDSNJXGFPPJGPP3CKHFEJOAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国 6 月汽车注册量下降 6.7%，特斯拉销量下降 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国汽车机构PFA周二公布的数据显示，6月份法国新车注册量为169,504辆，同比下滑6.7%。【原文：New car registrations in France slid 6.7% in June from a year earlier to 169,504 vehicles, data from French car body PFA showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/france-car-registrations-down-67-june-tesla-sales-drop-10-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73ODIU7Z6ZKALPV2P6PRVH6OWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:26:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共和党人无视债务担忧，推进特朗普减税法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的共和党人正在推进一项全面的减税和支出法案，无党派分析人士称，该法案可能会在未来十年内使国家债务增加 3.3 万亿美元。【原文：As President Donald Trump's Republicans push ahead on a sweeping tax-cut and spending bill that nonpartisan analysts say could add $3.3 trillion to the nation's debt over the next decade, they're taking a new approach - denying there is anything to worry about.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/republicans-ignore-debt-worry-they-push-forward-trump-tax-cut-bill-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UY5CNRHX4VJ6JGZ7H3HTHD6B4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[央行行长称，挑战美元霸主地位尚需时日]]></title><description><![CDATA[在葡萄牙度假胜地辛特拉参加年度会议的各国央行行长周二表示，美元作为世界首选储备货币的地位不会很快受到重大挑战。【原文：There is no prospect of a major challenge to the dollar's status as the world's reserve currency of choice any time soon, central bankers gathered for an annual conference in the Portuguese resort of Sintra said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/challenge-dollar-supremacy-long-way-off-central-bankers-say-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMPI4NW2DJO5ZBHQINFKBAXZPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[发言人称波音将收购 Spirit 北爱尔兰工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spirit 公司发言人周二表示，波音公司将接管 Spirit AeroSystems 公司位于北爱尔兰贝尔法斯特的工厂，此前该公司曾试图为该工厂寻找买家，但最终未能如愿。【原文：Boeing is set to take over Spirit AeroSystems' facility in Belfast, Northern Ireland, after attempts to find a buyer for the site fell through, a Spirit spokesperson said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-set-acquire-spirits-northern-ireland-plant-spokesperson-says-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P4GFRPDMWFPFDIN5FRQA5LM5RI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田第二季度美国汽车销量增长 7.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司北美分公司周二公布，受轿车和 SUV 需求的推动，第二季度美国汽车销量有所增长。【原文：Toyota Motors' North American unit reported higher second-quarter U.S. vehicle sales on Tuesday, helped by demand for its sedans and SUVs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyotas-second-quarter-us-auto-sales-rise-72-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UWWY6XIJBJMJGO5IRDAK5YRUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:04:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[YPF 公司营业额的裁决为阿根廷页岩油的前景蒙上阴影，外汇]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法院作出了一项戏剧性的裁决，命令阿根廷交出其持有的国有能源公司 YPF 51% 的股份，这给阿根廷开发其巨大的瓦卡穆埃尔塔页岩层的计划和重返全球市场的希望蒙上了阴影。【原文：A dramatic ruling by a U.S. court ordering Argentina to hand over the 51% stake it holds in state energy firm YPF has cast a shadow over the country's plans for its huge Vaca Muerta shale formation and hopes to return to global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ypf-turnover-ruling-casts-shadow-over-argentina-shale-hopes-fx-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E42VNVCKGNJBNNH3IJU46VARZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:49:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英超联赛与微软建立为期五年的人工智能合作伙伴关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，英格兰足球超级联赛和微软宣布了一项为期五年的合作伙伴关系，这家云计算巨头将把其人工智能 Copilot 引入联赛的数字平台，以提供有关比赛的快速事实和统计数据。【原文：The English Premier League and Microsoft on Tuesday announced a five-year partnership where the cloud giant will infuse its artificial intelligence Copilot into the league's digital platforms to provide quick facts and statistics about matches.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/premier-league-forms-five-year-ai-partnership-with-microsoft-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLTWP5G2FVL4BDES2PIWKXS4JU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:41:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯为外国投资者推出提款担保账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据弗拉基米尔-普京总统周二签署的一项法令，俄罗斯推出了一种包含提款担保的新型投资账户，莫斯科希望借此吸引外国投资者进入俄罗斯股市。【原文：Russia has launched a new type of investment account that contains withdrawal guarantees, according to a decree signed by President Vladimir Putin on Tuesday, as Moscow looks to attract foreign investors to the Russian stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/russia-launches-accounts-with-withdrawal-guarantees-foreign-investors-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XK57KQ6OENL6NA6XD567P72LY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:39:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁 H&M 创始家族加速收购股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的监管文件显示，亿万富翁佩尔松家族加快了对其创立的 H&amp;M 时尚帝国的股份收购步伐，这可能会加剧人们对该公司最终可能被私有化的猜测。【原文：The billionaire Persson family has picked up the pace of share purchases in the H&amp;M fashion empire it founded, regulatory filings showed on Tuesday, potentially boosting speculation the company may eventually be taken private.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/billionaire-hm-founding-family-speeds-up-share-purchases-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQ3FNK3JPRJL5GV7IVJZSZNNDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:36:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，AQR 资本管理公司年中实现两位数回报]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，一位消息人士称，亿万富翁投资者克里夫-阿斯内斯（Cliff Asness）的 AQR 资本管理公司（AQR Capital Management）旗下的几只基金在今年上半年取得了正收益。【原文：Billionaire investor Cliff Asness's AQR Capital Management finished the first half of the year with positive returns in several of its funds, said a source on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aqr-capital-management-reaches-mid-year-with-double-digit-returns-source-says-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SUE7B36DJN2BKFSOKG4V5BRJQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:35:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车第二季度美国汽车销量增长 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司周二公布，受经济型跨界 SUV 需求的推动，第二季度美国汽车销量有所增长。【原文：General Motors reported higher second-quarter U.S. sales on Tuesday, aided by demand for its affordable crossover SUVs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gms-second-quarter-us-auto-sales-rise-7-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOTT5WBOJFMT7IYAEXAHBQL46Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:35:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泛欧交易所洽谈以 4.7 亿美元收购雅典证券交易所]]></title><description><![CDATA[泛欧交易所（Euronext）正在洽谈收购雅典证券交易所最多 100%的股份，交易金额为 3.99 亿欧元（4.7 亿美元），这将是该集团最近的一次收购，该集团已在法国和荷兰等国运营证券市场。【原文：Euronext is in talks to buy up to 100% of the Athens Stock Exchange in a 399 million euro ($470 million) all-share deal that would be the latest for a group that already operates stock markets in countries including France and the Netherlands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/euronext-talks-acquire-athens-stock-exchange-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7USPU2QF65IXLEMCGE7F7CREZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:26:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，Scale AI 的更大竞争对手 Surge AI 寻求最高 10 亿美元的融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，与 Scale AI 竞争的数据标签公司 Surge AI 已聘请顾问，准备在该公司历史上的首次融资中筹集多达 10 亿美元的资金。【原文：Surge AI, a data-labeling firm that competes with Scale AI, has hired advisors to raise as much as $1 billion in the first capital raising in the firm's history, sources told Reuters, as it seeks to capitalize on growing user demand amid Scale AI's recent customer exodus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/scale-ais-bigger-rival-surge-ai-seeks-up-1-billion-capital-raise-sources-say-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34PVWE22D5MRHITZH53N2MFV6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:23:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《泰晤士报》报道，阿斯利康首席执行官希望在美国市场上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《泰晤士报》周二援引多位消息人士的话报道，阿斯利康首席执行官帕斯卡尔-索里奥（Pascal Soriot）正在考虑将该公司的股票市场迁往美国。【原文：AstraZeneca chief executive Pascal Soriot is considering moving the company's stock market listing to the United States, The Times reported on Tuesday, citing multiple sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-ceo-eyes-us-market-listing-times-reports-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EY2XNDHP7NIMJPSMFQYNQXK2TY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球红利基金因降息希望和市场恐慌而吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在应对地缘政治和经济紧张局势的同时寻求收益稳定的资产，投资于分红股票的全球基金在经历了两年不温不火的投资者需求之后，今年吸引了大量资金流入。【原文：Global funds that invest in dividend-paying stocks are drawing strong flows this year, following two years of tepid investor demand, as investors seek assets with a stable income while they navigate geopolitical and economic tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/global-markets-dividendfunds-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FEG22E7KONJVBOUVUGDUMMVNGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国五月建筑支出再次下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于抵押贷款利率上升和库存增加对独户住宅项目造成压力，5 月份美国建筑支出下降。【原文：U.S. construction spending fell in May as higher mortgage rates and rising inventory weighed on single-family housing projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-construction-spending-falls-again-may-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW54VVE3T5OUTBHSFIX3EKYPNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:33:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月职位空缺意外增加，招聘人数下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国5月份的职位空缺出乎意料地增加，但招聘人数的下降加剧了劳动力市场转入低速增长的迹象，因为特朗普政府对进口商品征收关税的不确定性，为期90天的提高互惠关税的暂停期即将结束。【原文：U.S. job openings unexpectedly increased in May, but a decline in hiring added to signs that the labor market had shifted into lower gear amid uncertainty over the Trump administration's tariffs on imports, with a 90-day pause on higher reciprocal duties drawing to an end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-job-openings-unexpectedly-rise-may-hiring-falls-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NLMLAN4GJMR3OLBMIPFT5APK4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔不排除 7 月降息可能后，美联储降息押注上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在被问及 7 月考虑降息是否为时过早时表示，他 "不能说"，但决定将取决于经济数据，随后金融市场对美联储最快本月开始降息的押注上升。【原文：Financial market bets rose that the Federal Reserve could start interest-rate cuts as soon as this month after Fed Chair Jerome Powell, asked if July was too soon to consider rate cuts, said he "can't say" but that the decision would depend on the economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-rate-cut-bets-rise-after-powell-doesnt-rule-out-july-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUGJSWLONRNKTLDLFCZSK5WJFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制造业受关税影响陷入疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[6 月份，美国制造业依然低迷，新订单低迷，投入品价格攀升，这表明特朗普政府对进口商品征收关税继续阻碍了企业提前规划的能力。【原文：U.S. manufacturing remained sluggish in June, with new orders subdued and prices paid for inputs creeping higher, suggesting that the Trump administration's tariffs on imported goods continued to hamper businesses' ability to plan ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-manufacturing-mired-weakness-tariffs-bite-2025-07-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6GJH752DRPT5N44VXHTMEBNDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>