<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:35:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:35:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[市场困境可能导致数万亿美元资产寻求货币保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着唐纳德-特朗普重新定义全球贸易的宏伟计划对美元造成冲击，持有价值数万亿美元货币资产的投资者可能会在数十年来首次寻求保护这些资产价值的方法。【原文：As Donald Trump's grand plan to redefine global trade whipsaws the U.S. dollar, investors who hold tens of trillions' worth assets in the currency may for the first time in decades be seeking ways to protect the value of those holdings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/global-markets-dollar-hedging-analysis-pix-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6CZSS7AAZOQDNVREXTHAA6Y3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国大幅加征关税，美股期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五下跌，此前中国将对美国进口商品征收的关税提高至125%，贸易战升级，可能扰乱全球贸易并引发经济衰退。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Friday after China increased its tariffs on U.S. imports to 125%, escalating a trade war that could disrupt global trade and trigger an economic downturn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-stock-futures-fall-china-strikes-back-with-steep-tariffs-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNAFWHGI7JLT3JYU4NFOCAMZSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电子产品公司 Anker 开始在亚马逊上提价]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的Anker公司是亚马逊最大的销售商之一，提供从电源箱到手机壳等产品，自周四以来，该公司在美国平台上五分之一的产品提高了价格，这表明对中国商品征收的关税正在转嫁给美国购物者。【原文：China's Anker, one of Amazon's largest sellers offering products from power banks to phone cases, has raised prices on a fifth of its products on the U.S. platform since Thursday, in a sign that tariffs on Chinese goods are being passed on to U.S. shoppers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-electronics-company-anker-starts-raising-prices-amazon-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWXCR7AJ75LK3D6RDZVFBK67ZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:09:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯律师称花旗银行在俄客户收到部分被冻结资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据俄罗斯律师事务所援引其客户的话称，美国花旗银行俄罗斯子公司的经纪客户已开始收到因西方制裁而在欧洲被冻结的证券的息票付款。【原文：Brokerage customers of the Russian subsidiary of U.S. bank Citi have started receiving coupon payments on securities frozen in Europe by Western sanctions, according to Russian law firms, citing their clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-clients-russia-receiving-some-frozen-funds-russian-lawyers-say-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXWLZUWNL5IA3OHBRC3MP3DMKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:54:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世贸组织前任和现任领导人要求迅速改革，以保持全球自由贸易的活力]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织的一位前负责人表示，受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面保护主义关税影响，未来的全球贸易条件可能会在这个已有 30 年历史的国际监督机构之外决定，除非它迅速进行自我改革。【原文：A former World Trade Organization boss has said the future terms of global trade, rocked by U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping protectionist tariffs, could be decided outside the 30-year-old international watchdog unless it reforms itself fast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wto-chiefs-past-present-demand-rapid-reform-keep-global-free-trade-alive-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6SMHDZ4DJIFLEBXQPEHTMDXX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外国投资者一周内抛售 65 亿美元美国股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[博雅全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）周五称，由于关税引发的市场动荡，外国投资者在截至周三的五个交易日内抛售了65亿美元的美国股票。【原文：Foreign investors dumped $6.5 billion of U.S. equities in the five trading sessions ending Wednesday, BofA Global Research said on Friday, as tariff induced turmoil gripped markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-bofa-urgent-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSEA6LE57VPALC23ECMEPVGSYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:34:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国回击特朗普加征关税，将美国商品关税提高至 125]]></title><description><![CDATA[北京周五将美国进口商品的关税提高至125%，以回击美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将中国商品关税提高至145%的决定，从而提高了贸易战的赌注，这场贸易战有可能终结全球供应链。【原文：Beijing on Friday increased its tariffs on U.S. imports to 125%, hitting back against U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to hike duties on Chinese goods to 145%, raising the stakes in a trade war that threatens to up-end global supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-increase-tariffs-us-goods-125-up-84-finance-ministry-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAPMKQGO3FL7DKOJMYQV4ONIKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发贸易动荡，强势美元倍感压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对朋友和敌人征收混乱的关税，破坏了数十年来人们对世界储备货币的信任，美元在短短一周内从避风港变成了投资者的鞭打对象。【原文：In just a week, the dollar has gone from a safe haven to investors' whipping boy as U.S. President Donald Trump's chaotic tariffs on friend and foe alike undermine decades of trust in the world's reserve currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/mighty-us-dollar-feels-heat-trumps-tariffs-spark-trade-turmoil-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBHDCLJF5ZKEHBCA2G7VSFXCPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[倍耐力表示没有在美国投资的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[倍耐力轮胎制造商周五表示，目前没有计划在美国投资，这与一家意大利报纸的报道相矛盾。【原文：Pirelli is not planning investments in the United States at the moment, the tyre maker said on Friday, contradicting a report in an Italian newspaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/pirelli-says-it-has-no-plans-invest-united-states-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KUL2X42UBO77AIDMBHYRIZARU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:52:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾 Vanguard 加快新加坡晶圆厂的建设步伐]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾芯片制造商万古国际半导体（Vanguard International Semiconductor）周五表示，由于地缘政治风险，该公司将加快其位于新加坡的12英寸晶圆厂的建设速度，因为客户正在寻求更多在中国以外生产芯片的选择。【原文：Taiwan chip maker Vanguard International Semiconductor said on Friday it will speed construction of its 12-inch fab in Singapore because of geopolitical risks, as customers seek more options to make chips outside China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-vanguard-hasten-construction-singapore-fab-plant-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KF6G3BZ4RLGNBNS5LML7AP36Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通分析师表示，他现在会缓和对美国关税的公开评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通资产管理公司（JPMorgan Asset Management）的一位资深投资策略师表示，由于担心自己的全部观点会对同事和华尔街银行造成影响，他对美国关税问题的一些公开评论有所保留。【原文：A senior JPMorgan Asset Management investment strategist said he has held back on some of his public comments on U.S. tariffs due to concerns about the impact his full opinions would have on his colleagues and on the Wall Street bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/jpmorgan-analyst-says-he-now-tempers-public-comments-us-tariffs-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPKEXYPQXVOEJMH5TLZWRRBJAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:40:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid 收购位于亚利桑那州的部分尼古拉设施和资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于加利福尼亚州的 Lucid 集团周五表示，将收购亚利桑那州的部分设施和资产，这些设施和资产以前属于破产的电动和氢动力卡车制造商尼古拉公司（Nikola Corp .【原文：California-based Lucid Group on Friday said it will acquire select Arizona-based facilities and assets previously belonging to bankrupt electric and hydrogen-powered truckmaker Nikola Corp .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lucid-acquire-select-arizona-based-nikola-facilities-assets-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B72NKOY3Y5MC7C4E5HH7HUOAHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:18:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车旗下斯堪尼亚收购破产的 Northvolt 重工业电池组部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车旗下卡车制造商斯堪尼亚（Scania）周五表示，已同意收购破产的 Northvolt 公司为重工业生产电池组的部门，重启了 2 月份首次提出的交易，具体价格未透露。【原文：Volkswagen's truckmaker Scania said on Friday it had agreed to buy bankrupt Northvolt's division that makes battery packs for heavy industry, reviving a transaction first presented in February, for an undisclosed price.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagens-scania-buys-bankrupt-northvolts-heavy-industry-battery-packs-unit-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VW6JQLV2KNP7XE3EJ7ICGNUYKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典海克斯康公司称北美和中国经济增长乏力影响第一季度盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典工业技术集团海克斯康（Hexagon）周五表示，由于北美和中国的增长逊于预期，该公司第一季度调整后营业利润下降了约 8%，股价下跌了 6%。【原文：Swedish industrial technology group Hexagon said on Friday its adjusted operating profit fell around 8% in the first quarter due to weaker than expected growth in North America and China, sending its shares 6% lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/swedens-hexagon-says-weak-namerica-china-growth-hit-q1-earnings-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QFIAWPJRZNU7FDTXQHBIWEYHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 06:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 3 月出口可能在特朗普新关税生效前获得前置性提升]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管与美国不断扩大的贸易战令经济前景暗淡，但由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本月将全面征收关税，中国的工厂赶在关税之前发货，因此 3 月份中国的出口可能加快了步伐。【原文：China's exports likely picked up pace in March, as factories rushed out shipments ahead of U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs this month, though the broadening trade war with the United States has darkened the economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-march-exports-likely-got-front-loading-lift-before-trumps-new-tariffs-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZMYRFOJJ5PYBAMRIAREUEIVQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 06:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，申银万国伦敦上市获英国批准，正等待中国点头]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，在线快速时尚零售商 Shein 已获得英国金融行为监管局（FCA）的批准，计划在伦敦进行首次公开募股。【原文：Online fast-fashion retailer Shein has secured approval from Britain's Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) for its planned initial public offering in London, according to two sources with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shein-gains-uk-approval-london-ipo-awaits-china-nod-sources-say-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">77QSC6JTJFOMFI32J6CXYFT6IY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 06:08:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 第一季度出货量同比下降 9]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 周五表示，其第一季度的出货量与去年同期相比下降了 9%，估计为 120 万辆。【原文：Stellantis said on Friday its first-quarter shipments were down 9% compared to last year, to an estimated 1.2 million vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-first-quarter-shipments-fall-9-yy-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWLVRQTVXVJZ5P5WWHSSBPQFIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道虚假账户为杜特尔特点赞，现在又瞄准菲律宾大选]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲律宾前总统罗德里戈-杜特尔特（Rodrigo Duterte）因血腥的毒品战争被送往国际刑事法院接受指控后，一个复杂的虚假社交媒体账户网络慷慨激昂地为他辩护。【原文：A sophisticated network of fake social media accounts sprang to the impassioned defence of former Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte after he was sent to the International Criminal Court to face charges over his bloody drug war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fake-accounts-drove-praise-duterte-now-target-philippine-election-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A25DJ55W4VNQZM7FLSQAOW5TYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 05:44:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国总统马克龙：特朗普暂停加征关税只是 "脆弱的暂停]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙（Emmanuel Macron）周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周决定暂停对各国征收关税90天，这只为 "脆弱的暂停 "提供了空间。【原文：French President Emmanuel Macron said on Friday that U.S. President Donald Trump's decision this week for a 90-day suspension on tariffs he had imposed on countries gave room for only a 'fragile pause'.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/frances-macron-trump-tariff-suspension-only-provides-fragile-pause-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CW3A6TR2QJMQFCUWZHOKPPZWK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 05:18:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场持续波动，投资者正努力应对关税带来的经济威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，希望结束市场剧烈波动的投资者意识到，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普不断变化的关税计划所带来的后果仍对盈利和经济构成威胁，并可能对股市造成更多惩罚。【原文：Investors hoping for an end to wild market swings were reminded on Thursday that fallout from U.S. President Donald Trump's shifting tariff plans remains a threat to earnings and the economy, and could deal yet more punishment to equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-grapple-with-tariff-driven-economic-threat-market-swings-persist-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFAQ3XUSJ5OCLNKYIX77U3CQI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 05:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税混乱可能导致飞机交付陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[在过去几个月里，由于白宫时好时坏的关税政策，汽车、消费品和工业设备时常在港口延误、滞留在铁路车辆上、在仓库里徘徊。【原文：Cars, consumer goods, and industrial equipment have been delayed at ports, stuck on rail cars, and languished in warehouses at times over the last few months due to the White House's on-again, off-again tariff policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trumps-tariff-confusion-could-leave-aircraft-deliveries-limbo-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBDGHYS3CBIMBOEHV5BGG5BCG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 05:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，谷歌在安卓和 Pixel 集团裁员数百人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周五援引一位知情人士的话报道，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌周四裁掉了平台和设备部门的数百名员工，该部门主要负责安卓软件、Pixel 手机和 Chrome 浏览器。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Thursday laid off hundreds of employees in its platforms and devices unit, which works on Android software, Pixel phones and the Chrome browser, The Information reported on Friday, citing a person with direct knowledge of the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-lays-off-hundreds-employees-android-pixel-group-information-reports-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CI3I7YA7FFMH3HJR34VIXALRMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 04:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价市场重回白刃战]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XQWTKTN4NLZ7M6OFIZWA2LOLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 04:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着 90 天窗口期的开启，欧盟就如何应对美国关税集思广益]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国将提高关税的时间推迟了 90 天，欧盟各国财长将在周五集思广益，商讨如何利用这段时间与华盛顿达成贸易协议，以及在无法达成贸易协议的情况下如何协调各方努力以应对更高的关税。【原文：With higher U.S. tariffs postponed by 90 days, European Union finance ministers will brainstorm on Friday how to use that time to get a trade deal with Washington and how to coordinate their efforts to handle higher tariffs if they do not.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-brainstorms-how-brace-us-tariffs-90-day-window-opens-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3B3KRHMNG5LT7IQS24GUVZVIPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 04:07:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉暂停在中国网站接受 Model S 和 Model X 的新订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五的核查，特斯拉已暂停在其中国网站上接受 Model S 和 Model X 汽车的新订单。【原文：Tesla has suspended taking new orders for Model S and Model X vehicles on its Chinese website, according to checks made by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-suspends-taking-new-orders-model-s-model-x-chinese-website-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SV6HU5OMPBNIXHWAXKDV476LFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 04:06:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济衰退风险挥之不去，特朗普暂停加征关税缓解效果甚微]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策引发的一周动荡在周五几乎没有缓解的迹象，市场再次暴跌，外国领导人正试图找出如何应对世界贸易秩序瓦解的办法。【原文：A week of turmoil unleashed by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs showed little sign of easing on Friday, with markets again tumbling and foreign leaders trying to work out how to respond to a dismantling of the world trade order.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trumps-tariff-pause-brings-little-relief-recession-risk-lingers-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AFKO4QJ65JZFO5SJ5IMERNRQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道面对特朗普关税，越南着眼于打击部分对华贸易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的人士和路透社看到的一份政府文件称，为了避免美国的惩罚性关税，越南准备打击经由其领土运往美国的中国商品，并将加强对敏感的对华出口产品的控制。【原文：In hope of avoiding punishing U.S. tariffs, Vietnam is prepared to crack down on Chinese goods being shipped to the United States via its territory and will tighten controls on sensitive exports to China, according to a person familiar with the matter and a government document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/facing-trump-tariffs-vietnam-eyes-crackdown-some-china-trade-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7URP36ZT2BMCPNL2CBNFZO4OUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:27:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元下滑，避险资金流入，黄金突破 3,200 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美元走软和贸易战升级的推动，投资者纷纷涌向避险资产，黄金在上周五首次突破3200美元/盎司的关键水平，创下新高。【原文：Gold breached the key $3,200/oz level for the first time to scale a new peak on Friday, fuelled by a weaker dollar and an escalating trade war that sent investors rushing toward safe-haven assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-bolts-past-3200-dollar-slide-safe-haven-flows-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6GTSMDRWFN7DH6WNP4PCP75PM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战搅动市场，股市、美元下挫，债券再遭重创]]></title><description><![CDATA[这种焦虑引发了对避风港的抢购，使得瑞士法郎兑美元汇率飙升至十年来的新高，黄金也达到了新的峰值。【原文：The anxiety has sparked a rush into safe havens, sending the Swiss franc soaring to a decade high against the dollar, and gold to a new peak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1pix-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBR4U5HGXVIN7PMFIBD5TGQHMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 02:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在美国推出全新 Cybertruck 车型，售价 69,990 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周四表示，已在美国推出新版 Cybertruck，售价为 69,990 美元。【原文：Tesla on Thursday said it has launched a new version of Cybertruck in the United States, priced at $69,990.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-launches-new-cybertruck-variant-us-priced-69990-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64545LKAI5M6NEOGFQXYUHNENM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 02:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>