<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:05:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:05:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国针对亚马逊的反垄断案将继续推进]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，美国联邦贸易委员会指控亚马逊扼杀在线零售业竞争的案件将继续审理，但与该机构一同起诉的一些州的诉讼请求已被驳回。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission's case accusing Amazon of stifling competition in online retail will move forward, though some of the states that sued alongside the agency had their claims dismissed, court documents showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-antitrust-case-against-amazon-move-forward-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJAQUMCLZVJSZGHL45QYZDDKDA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 17:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[密尔顿逼近佛罗里达州，港口限制航行，部分石油设施关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着飓风米尔顿的迅速加强，美国墨西哥湾至少有一个石油和天然气平台于周一关闭，佛罗里达州的港口也对船只航行实施了限制。【原文：At least one oil and gas platform in the U.S. Gulf of Mexico was shut on Monday and Florida ports imposed restrictions on vessel navigation as Hurricane Milton rapidly intensified.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ports-restrict-navigation-some-oil-facilities-shut-milton-approaches-florida-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RC5L32MAABPQHKHANPMV6WJQCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:55:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飓风季节带来损失，美国财险公司业绩下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在飓风米尔顿向佛罗里达州西海岸袭来的途中，飓风强度增强为四级，标志着该行业今年要承保的又一场代价高昂的灾难，美国财产和人身保险股周一大幅下挫。【原文：U.S. property and casualty insurance stocks tanked on Monday after Hurricane Milton intensified into a category 4 on its path toward Florida's western coast, marking yet another costly disaster for the industry to cover this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-property-casualty-insurers-slump-hurricane-season-brings-losses-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4E46KWMVOFNLLBF4VVO7T664B4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:50:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能热潮推动 GPU 季度出货量达 10 万台，超微股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[超微计算机公司（Super Micro Computer）周一表示，该公司目前每季度的图形处理器出货量超过 10 万台，并推出了一套新的液体冷却产品，这使得这家人工智能服务器制造商的股价在经历了长达数周的暴跌后上涨了约 14%。【原文：Super Micro Computer said on Monday it is currently shipping more than 100,000 graphics processors per quarter and unveiled a new suite of liquid cooling products, sending the AI server maker's shares up about 14% following a weeks-long slump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/super-micro-shares-surge-ai-boom-drives-100000-quarterly-gpu-shipments-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRFRNBENKNK3JP6VIZ2JJZ33GE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车在飓风相关供应商问题后恢复生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）周一表示，由于飓风海伦（Helene）对供应商造成的影响，该公司上周暂时停止了位于得克萨斯州和密歇根州的两家装配厂的生产。【原文：General Motors said Monday it is resuming production at two assembly plants in Texas and Michigan after it temporarily halted production at the plants last week because of impacts to its suppliers due to Hurricane Helene.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-resumes-production-after-hurricane-related-supplier-issue-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5K3D7BXRZJO75N53VSRD2BLHVY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利检察官发现为波音公司制造的缺陷部件威胁飞机安全]]></title><description><![CDATA[检察官周六表示，调查人员发现，两家意大利分包商在为波音公司的 787 Dreamliner 制造某些部件时，使用了更便宜且不符合要求的钛和铝，从而节省了大量资金，但却威胁到了飞机的安全。【原文：Investigators have found that two Italian sub-contractors used cheaper and non-compliant forms of titanium and aluminium to make certain parts for Boeing's 787 Dreamliner, saving significant sums of money and threatening plane safety, prosecutors said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/flawed-parts-made-boeing-threatened-plane-safety-italian-prosecutors-find-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCLMFVOBGJJC3ENMERQEN6I3RE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预算组织称，特朗普的税收和支出计划将比哈里斯的计划增加两倍的债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一家关注预算问题的智库周一估计，共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普的税收和支出计划所产生的新债务将是副总统卡马拉-哈里斯计划的两倍多。【原文：Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump's tax and spending plans would produce more than twice as much new debt as the plans from Vice President Kamala Harris, a budget-focused think-tank estimated on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-tax-spending-plans-would-add-twice-much-debt-harris-budget-group-says-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QZNDFP4DFLITEY2BSDI4C2B7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，高盛持有价值 6.7% 的联合信贷银行衍生品头寸]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛周一提交的一份监管文件显示，截至 9 月 30 日，高盛在意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）持有的衍生品头寸相当于该银行 6.7% 的股份，其中大部分是掉期和期货合约以及看涨期权。【原文：Goldman Sachs has derivative positions in UniCredit equivalent to a 6.7% stake in the Italian bank as of Sept. 30, mostly swap and future contracts as well as call options, a regulatory filing showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-has-derivatives-positions-worth-67-stake-unicredit-filing-shows-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5HXUOHNXJNTHEZY7LPCCW22GE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:21:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：联合利华高管称正在全面调整欧洲家庭护理供应链]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华的一位高级管理人员告诉路透社，联合利华正在斥资超过 1.5 亿欧元（1.65 亿美元）改造其欧洲家庭护理业务的供应链，旨在弥补多年来的业绩不佳，并开发年轻的、大流行后的购物者。【原文：Unilever is spending over 150 million euros ($165 million) to revamp its European homecare business' supply chain, a senior executive told Reuters, aiming to make up for years of underperformance and tap into young, post-pandemic shoppers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-overhauling-european-homecare-supply-chain-executive-says-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IJCPMKAQVMZ7NPXUW2U2CTSV4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:40:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟支持对中国电动汽车征收关税表明柏林的影响力正在减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理奥拉夫-肖尔茨（Olaf Scholz）拒绝欧盟对中国电动汽车征收关税，但未能阻止欧盟其他成员国投赞成票，这暴露了分裂的柏林是如何努力推动欧盟政策的。【原文：German Chancellor Olaf Scholz's rejection of EU tariffs on Chinese electric vehicles failed to stop fellow European Union members voting in favour, exposing how a divided Berlin is struggling to drive EU policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-backing-china-ev-tariffs-shows-berlins-waning-influence-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PRWM3MSDJLFDK2ZKVJMBQ2TNA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:13:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回优步和 Lyft 为避免加州司机起诉而提出的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一拒绝审理优步（Uber）和 Lyft 代表司机对加利福尼亚州提起的诉讼提出的质疑，这些司机签署了协议，在关于其承包商身份的法律纠纷中，不与打车公司发生法律纠纷。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Monday to hear a challenge by Uber and Lyft to lawsuits by the state of California on behalf of drivers who signed agreements to keep legal disputes with the ride-hailing companies out of court in a legal fight over their status as contractors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-rebuffs-uber-lyft-bid-avoid-california-driver-suits-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ILQ2QRL7MVJPRDSJXI73FR7DFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥反垄断监管机构裁定格鲁玛公司可以操纵玉米饼市场价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥反垄断监督机构 Cofece 周一认定，玉米粉和玉米饼生产商 Gruma 可以操纵市场价格，并在调查后得出结论，在这一关键食品领域不存在竞争条件。【原文：Mexico's antitrust watchdog Cofece on Monday determined that corn flour and tortilla-maker Gruma can fix prices in the market, concluding following an investigation that competitive conditions in the key food segment do not exist.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mexico-antitrust-watchdog-rules-gruma-can-fix-tortilla-market-prices-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPVBPNDQPRLZBARTJOK4AWTUR4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:20:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回 "医药兄弟 "马丁-什克里（Martin Shkreli）对处罚的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一拒绝审理前制药公司首席执行官马丁-什克里（Martin Shkreli）对法官判处的 6460 万美元罚款提出的异议，因为他将一种救命药物的价格提高了 4000% 以上。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Monday to hear former pharmaceutical company CEO Martin Shkreli's challenge to a $64.6 million financial penalty imposed by a judge after he raised a lifesaving drug's price by more than 4,000%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-rejects-pharma-bro-martin-shkrelis-appeal-penalties-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQOYH7T5RVJH7HDGF2IJVTWYLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本日产汽车公司将投资汽车技术公司 ChargeScape]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本日产汽车公司周一表示，将向 ChargeScape 公司投资，具体金额未透露，并在美国和加拿大向其电动汽车驾驶员推广这家电池充电技术公司的服务。【原文：Japan's Nissan Motor said on Monday it would invest an undisclosed amount in ChargeScape and roll out the battery charging technology company's services to its electric-vehicle drivers across the United States and Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japans-nissan-invest-auto-tech-firm-chargescape-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQ4WV5S62VPNDDQE3OVZSLBCPQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[截至 10 月 2 日的一周，美国货币市场基金吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 2 日的一周内，美国货币市场基金出现大量资金流入，原因是在中东地缘政治忧虑加剧的情况下，投资者在关键的就业报告公布前谨慎行事，寻求更安全的资产。【原文：U.S. money market funds saw massive inflows in the week to Oct. 2 as investors sought safer assets on caution ahead of a key payrolls report amid heightened geopolitical concerns in the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-money-market-funds-draw-sharp-inflows-week-oct-2-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INLVUE34KRLX3BF375NSPH22A4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[截至 10 月 2 日的一周，全球货币市场基金吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 2 日的一周内，全球货币市场基金吸引了大量资金流入，原因是投资者在关键的美国非农就业报告公布前持谨慎态度，以及中东地缘政治紧张局势加剧，这些因素刺激了对更安全资产的需求。【原文：Global money market funds attracted large inflows in the week to Oct. 2 as investor caution ahead of a key U.S. payrolls report and heightened geopolitical tensions in the Middle East boosted demand for safer assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3ZIUQD4VVLYXHTTX6PFKTAZS4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[价格折扣刺激需求，Lucid 季度交付量超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，Lucid 集团第三季度交付量超出市场预期，原因是在经济不确定的情况下，其豪华电动汽车的折扣和更便宜的融资方案刺激了需求。【原文：Lucid Group beat market expectations for third-quarter deliveries on Monday, as discounts and cheaper financing options for its luxury electric vehicles boosted demand in an uncertain economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lucid-beats-quarterly-deliveries-estimate-price-discounts-boost-demand-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXXXEG7R35M3PFFB4LBLL5BF7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:07:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔格林任命 Optum 的 Jason Stenta 为首席商务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔格林博姿联盟周一任命前 Optum 高管 Jason Stenta 为公司首席商务官。【原文：Walgreens Boots Alliance named ex-Optum executive Jason Stenta as the company's chief commercial officer on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/walgreens-names-optums-jason-stenta-chief-commercial-officer-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DU7QHZ6KBN57GMVPXXUTUSRSM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 对联合汽车工人工会提起新诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[克莱斯勒母公司斯特兰蒂斯公司周一表示，该公司已对美国汽车工人联合会和 23 个地方工会提起另外八项诉讼，称该工会因公司推迟计划投资而威胁罢工，从而违反了合同。【原文：Chrysler parent Stellantis said Monday it has filed eight additional lawsuits against the United Auto Workers and 23 union locals, saying the union has violated its contract by threatening to strike over the company's delays in planned investment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-files-new-suits-against-united-auto-workers-union-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSQNKY4DYFKNPGVHRXIT6JIQ7E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:29:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄酒制造商 Duckhorn 将被 Butterfly Equity 以 19.5 亿美元收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[顶级奢华葡萄酒制造商 Duckhorn Portfolio 周一表示，该公司将被 Butterfly Equity 以价值 19.5 亿美元的全现金交易方式私有化。【原文：Premier luxury wine maker Duckhorn Portfolio said on Monday it would be taken private by Butterfly Equity in an all-cash deal worth $1.95 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/wine-maker-duckhorn-be-acquired-by-butterfly-equity-195-bln-deal-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYBLA5HY6ZMUZI2YAFESVKIAHY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 11:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易商 IXM 称电动汽车对铜的需求保持不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[大宗商品贸易商 IXM 的精炼金属主管表示，尽管电动汽车销售放缓引发了疑虑，但对电动汽车所用铜等金属的需求上升趋势依然完好，但由于市场在不断变化，因此很难估计数字。【原文：The uptrend in demand for metals such as copper used in electric vehicles is intact despite doubts raised by the slowdown in EV sales, but estimating numbers is difficult as the market is evolving, commodity trader IXM's head of refined metal said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/copper-demand-electric-vehicles-is-intact-trader-ixm-says-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELSGTPFN4JLGXHZFUSJ7Y2EXOY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:47:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CAMP4 Therapeutics 在美国首次公开募股中寻求最高 2.83 亿美元的估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[由医疗保健巨头凯撒医疗集团（Kaiser Permanente）支持的生物制药公司CAMP4 Therapeutics周一表示，其在美国首次公开募股的目标估值高达2.83亿美元。【原文：CAMP4 Therapeutics, a biopharmaceutical company backed by healthcare giant Kaiser Permanente, said on Monday it was targeting a valuation of up to $283 million in its initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/camp4-therapeutics-seeks-up-283-mln-valuation-us-ipo-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76GM7LXYH5L7BBEARNJYZDZBKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:31:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价巨额薪资令 10 年期国债收益率突破 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T67PTAGIJFNEND4GVWXLZIACLI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:20:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下滑，市场在繁忙的一周前重新评估利率走势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周一下滑，原因是在关键的通胀数据、政策制定者的言论以及本周晚些时候开始的第三季度财报季到来之前，投资者减少了对美联储今年降息幅度的押注。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Monday as investors dialed back bets on the scope of the Federal Reserve rate cuts this year, ahead of key inflation data, policymakers' comments and the third-quarter earnings season that starts later this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-futures-slip-markets-reprice-rate-path-ahead-busy-week-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHS7KSHWCVOIVD6BOTXVW3UOSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Equinor 收购 Orsted 9.8% 股份，价值 25 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威 Equinor 公司周一表示，已收购丹麦可再生能源集团 Orsted 9.8% 的股份，价值约 25 亿美元，成为仅次于丹麦政府的第二大股东。【原文：Norway's Equinor said on Monday it has bought a 9.8% stake in Danish renewable energy group Orsted valued at around $2.5 billion, making it the second largest shareholder after the government of Denmark.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/equinor-buys-98-stake-orsted-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MROBPQUVAJKEPGPCTMGECBQKSY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛上调标普 500 指数年底及未来 12 个月的目标值]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）上调了基准 S&amp;P 500 指数在今年年底和未来 12 个月的目标值，原因是预期企业公司的利润率会有更高的增长，而且到 2025 年宏观经济前景稳定。【原文：Goldman Sachs has raised its target for the benchmark S&amp;P 500 index for the year-end and the next 12 months on expectations of higher margin growth for corporate companies and a steady macroeconomic outlook through 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-lifts-sp-500-index-target-year-end-next-12-months-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJ2FUZTZ75JE7HUWDLW22ULWLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 09:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道三星电子称无意分拆代工业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子董事长李在镕（Jay Y. Lee）周一告诉路透社，三星电子无意分拆其合约芯片制造业务和逻辑芯片设计业务。【原文：Samsung Electronics is not interested in spinning off its contract chip manufacturing business as well as its logic chip designing operation, its chairperson Jay Y. Lee told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-electronics-says-it-is-not-interested-spinning-off-foundry-business-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFK3V77E2NJFLB7UZG75UMRRQ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 09:23:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙将向加拿大自然资源公司剥离价值 65 亿美元的资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙周一表示，将以 65 亿美元的价格向加拿大自然资源公司（Canadian Natural Resources）出售其在阿萨巴斯卡油砂项目（Athabasca Oil Sands project）中的非经营性权益和在杜弗奈页岩项目（Duvernay shale）中的经营性权益，这两个项目均位于加拿大阿尔伯塔省。【原文：Chevron said on Monday it would sell its non-operated interest in the Athabasca Oil Sands project and its operated interest in Duvernay shale, all located in Alberta, Canada, to Canadian Natural Resources for $6.5 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/chevron-sell-interests-athabasca-oil-sands-duvernay-shale-canadian-natural-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSY2PDPYEVJ5FMLATTKFZFFVWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 09:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加纳野猫式金矿开采蓬勃发展，毒害人类和自然]]></title><description><![CDATA[在加纳的一个无证金矿，身着 T 恤、短裤和胶靴的男子蹚过一滩滩掺杂着水银的泥水，徒手掏出石头，操作摇摇晃晃的水闸，寻找珍贵的矿石。【原文：At an unlicensed gold mine in Ghana, men in t-shirts, shorts and rubber boots wade through pools of muddy water laced with mercury, pull out rocks with bare hands and operate a rickety sluice as they search for the precious ore.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ghanas-wildcat-gold-mining-booms-poisoning-people-nature-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">253YN6ENPRJ4TGSJ3U2KVIWZ7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 08:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业报告好于预期，高盛将美国经济衰退概率降至 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[在最新的就业报告显示数据好于预期之后，高盛（Goldman Sachs）将美国在未来 12 个月内陷入衰退的几率下调了 5 个百分点，降至 15%。【原文：Goldman Sachs has lowered the odds of the United States slipping into a recession in the next 12 months by five percentage points to 15%, following the latest employment report that showed better-than-expected data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-lowers-odds-us-recession-15-after-better-than-expected-jobs-report-2024-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7BR7DD7PZJLPEVVXGJ22U3WLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 06:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>