<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:34:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:34:40 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[监管文件显示，D.E. Shaw 看空拜耳 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国一份监管文件显示，对冲基金 D.E. Shaw 周二对德国拜耳公司下了 10.2 亿欧元（10.8 亿美元）的空头赌注，此前拜耳公司发布的财报使其股价跌至 20 年来的最低点。【原文：Hedge fund D.E. Shaw took an 1.02 billion euro ($1.08 billion) short bet against Germany's Bayer on Tuesday following an earnings presentation that sent its shares to a 20-year low, a regulatory filing in Germany showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/de-shaw-takes-1-bln-short-bayer-regulatory-filing-shows-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEPDVQFD3JLRTNIZSY7OKZ6DOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国高管权衡特朗普关税提案带来的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[许多美国公司的高管们正在为当选总统唐纳德-特朗普兑现其提高关税的竞选承诺所带来的影响做准备，此举可能会扰乱供应链并加剧通胀压力。【原文：Top executives at many U.S. companies are preparing for the impact from President-elect Donald Trump fulfilling his campaign promise of raising tariffs, a move that could disrupt supply chains and worsen inflationary pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-executives-weigh-risks-proposed-trump-tariffs-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYF4T4ZMIVOCRL6ILMQLBVQEFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创企业吸引投资者，CoreWeave 完成 6.5 亿美元的二次销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能云计算初创公司 CoreWeave 周三表示，该公司已完成一笔 6.5 亿美元的少数股权投资，领投方包括 Jane Street、Magnetar、富达管理公司（Fidelity Management）和麦格理资本（Macquarie Capital）。【原文：AI cloud startup CoreWeave said on Wednesday it has closed a $650 million minority investment led by Jane Street, Magnetar, Fidelity Management and Macquarie Capital, as investors look to capitalize on the generative AI boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/coreweave-closes-650-mln-secondary-sale-ai-startups-lure-investors-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VYGFHEYQBPKHL4DDZOUW32UNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州唯一一家使用人工智能帮助应对新的许可挑战的核电厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州仅存的一家核电站计划使用人工智能工具来帮助它遵守新的许可要求，以保持这座拥有几十年历史的核电站继续运行。【原文：California's only remaining nuclear power plant plans to use artificial intelligence tools to help it comply with new licensing requirements to keep the decades-old facility running.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/californias-only-nuclear-plant-use-ai-help-comply-with-new-licensing-challenges-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGAXWICTTNMQRNMC2ZRE4RM6PU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴尔的摩在起诉阿片类药物经销商一案中胜诉 2.66 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴尔的摩市在指控顶级药品分销商 McKesson 和 Cencora 助长了阿片类药物成瘾在美国的流行的诉讼中赢得了 2.66 亿美元的赔偿，预计该市将在下一阶段的诉讼中要求赔偿数十亿美元。【原文：The city of Baltimore won $266 million in its lawsuit accusing top drug distributors McKesson and Cencora of fueling an epidemic of opioid addiction in the U.S., and is expected to seek billions more in the next phase of the case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/baltimore-wins-266-million-opioid-case-against-distributors-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBRW3T7WDRNTRG44NWMH3QCTRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:57:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普胜选后，印度阿达尼集团将向美国能源领域投资 100 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团（Adani Group）董事长高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）周三在社交媒体平台 X 上发文称，该集团将向美国的能源安全和基础设施项目投资 100 亿美元，旨在创造多达 15000 个就业机会。【原文：India's Adani Group will invest $10 billion in US energy security and infrastructure projects, aiming to create up to 15,000 jobs, chairman Gautam Adani said in a post on social media platform X on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/indias-adani-group-invest-10-bln-us-energy-following-trump-win-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDYBXSWKTVIUXMAU6GQNUXMZAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:53:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司本周起发布裁员通知]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周三表示，从本周开始，公司将向受该计划影响的工人发出裁员通知，这家负债累累的飞机制造商将在全球范围内裁员17000人，占其全球员工总数的10%。【原文：Boeing said on Wednesday it is issuing layoff notices starting this week to workers impacted by a broader plan by the heavily indebted planemaker to cut 17,000 jobs, or 10% of its global workforce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-starts-issuing-layoff-notices-starting-this-week-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIOJBAL76VPBRK7HGOXCXLJJJM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小型股面临特朗普提振和通胀风险之间的微妙平衡]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）赢得总统大选后，美国小盘股飙升至接近历史高点，但一些投资者对追涨持谨慎态度，因为他们担心特朗普的政策可能会推动通胀回升，从而损害对利率敏感的行业。【原文：U.S. small-cap stocks have surged to near record highs following Donald Trump's presidential election win, but some investors are wary of chasing the rally as they fear his policies could drive a resurgence in inflation, hurting the rate-sensitive sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/small-cap-stocks-face-delicate-balance-between-trump-boost-inflation-risks-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHARAYBNCRIFBJVMEWTRMXEEOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储称第三季度家庭债务上升，收入增加减轻债务负担]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备委员会在周三发布的一份报告中说，收入水平的提高帮助美国人在第三季度控制住了不断扩大的债务负担，尽管一些压力迹象有所增加。【原文：Rising income levels helped Americans manage their expanding debt loads during the third quarter, even as some signs of stress mounted, the New York Federal Reserve said in a report released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ny-fed-says-household-debt-up-third-quarter-rising-incomes-ease-debt-burden-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCHFM7RTABJTRAR2QHHCEA2X2I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Frontier 股东批准与 Verizon 的 96 亿美元交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[前沿通信公司（Frontier Communications）股东已批准以 96 亿美元的价格出售给威瑞森公司（Verizon），该公司周三表示，尽管一些大型投资者寻求获得更高的价格。【原文：Frontier Communications shareholders have approved a $9.6 billion sale to Verizon , the company said on Wednesday, even as a number of large investors sought to get a higher price.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/frontier-shareholders-approve-96-billion-deal-with-verizon-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KN3GTN73WFKMVEIEFCJL7LOLYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:58:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙电信公司称，哥伦比亚政府在仲裁中被判赔偿 3.8 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙电信公司 Telefonica 周三表示，作为仲裁程序的一部分，世界银行国际投资争端解决中心（ICSID）已命令哥伦比亚政府向其支付 3.8 亿美元。【原文：Spanish telecoms company Telefonica said on Wednesday that the World Bank's International Centre for Settlement of Investment Disputes (ICSID) had ordered the Colombian government to pay it $380 million as part of an arbitration process.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/telefonica-awarded-380-million-colombian-government-arbitration-company-says-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYSV455AOFJOHOSB7EXWPCWIKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前证券交易委员会（SEC）主席称，特朗普执政期间可能会出台加密货币立法]]></title><description><![CDATA[前华尔街最高监管者、可能的政治任命者杰伊-克莱顿（Jay Clayton）周三表示，美国国会很可能在当选总统唐纳德-特朗普执政期间通过管理加密货币的立法。【原文：Congress is likely to adopt legislation governing cryptocurrencies during President-elect Donald Trump's administration, Jay Clayton, a former top Wall Street regulator and potential political appointee, said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/crypto-legislation-likely-coming-under-trump-ex-sec-chief-says-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JB2OGLNJHNK2LGVPWTRIA4ODSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:45:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊在美国推出低成本电子商务服务，挑战特姆公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周三表示，该公司为美国部分客户推出了一项名为 "亚马逊购物"（Amazon Haul）的低成本电子商务服务，为他们提供20美元或更低价格的精选商品，以应对中国企业申银万国和PDD控股公司旗下的特姆公司的挑战。【原文：Amazon.com launched a low-cost ecommerce service called Amazon Haul for some customers in the United States giving them a selection of products at $20 or less, the online retailer said on Wednesday, as it looks to take on Chinese firms Shein and PDD Holdings' Temu.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-launches-low-cost-ecommerce-service-challenge-temu-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUIF4JWEUFJ3PGC4NZZ2VQTMM4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:35:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普和中国问题成为芯片制造商 ASML 投资者日的关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，这家领先的计算机芯片设备制造商将在一年两次的 "投资者日 "上提供新的中长期财务指导，届时美国将进一步限制 ASML 向中国的销售。【原文：The threat of further U.S.-led restrictions on ASML's sales to China will hang over the leading computer chip equipment maker on Thursday when it offers up new medium- and long-term financial guidance at its biannual Investor Day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-china-loom-over-chipmaker-asmls-investor-day-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODJLXUCFMBIUBKZK7LEZ7XNZAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛根：美联储应在降息问题上 "谨慎行事]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周三表示，美国央行应谨慎推进进一步降息，以免无意中重燃通胀。【原文：The U.S. central bank should proceed cautiously on further interest rate cuts to keep from inadvertently reigniting inflation, Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-should-proceed-with-caution-rate-cuts-logan-says-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGQIP2ETM5LHJBIL4E5J7I7DEI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 14:49:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币因特朗普的兴奋而升至 90,000 美元以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币周三冲破了 90,000 美元的关口，由于人们预期唐纳德-特朗普担任美国总统及其政府将对加密货币有利，比特币的持续涨势丝毫没有放松的迹象。【原文：Bitcoin charged past the $90,000 level on Wednesday, as its relentless rally showed no signs of easing on expectations that Donald Trump as U.S. president and his administration will be a boon for cryptocurrencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bitcoin-rises-above-90000-trump-euphoria-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U6USSFGUNM4BJEYV23COSGL3Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 14:40:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将因收购 Instagram 和 WhatsApp 面临反垄断审判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国华盛顿的一名法官周三裁定，Facebook 的所有者 Meta Platforms 必须在美国联邦贸易委员会要求其解散的诉讼中出庭受审，该诉讼声称 Meta Platforms 收购 Instagram 和 WhatsApp 是为了打压社交媒体领域的新兴竞争。【原文：Facebook owner Meta Platforms must face trial in a U.S. Federal Trade Commission lawsuit seeking its break up over claims that it bought Instagram and WhatsApp to crush emerging competition in social media, a judge in Washington ruled on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/meta-will-face-antitrust-trial-over-instagram-whatsapp-acquisitions-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7TB6FPYJRMFVEMNAWN5YWRY2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 14:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：欧元为何下跌，会跌至 1 美元吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元跌至一年来的低点，重新引发了该货币可能触及 1 美元大关的言论。唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在美国大选中获胜引发了加征关税的前景，这可能会对欧元区经济造成新的打击。【原文：The euro has fallen to one-year lows, reviving talk the currency could hit the $1 mark. Donald Trump's U.S. election win raises the prospect of a hike in tariffs that could deal a fresh blow to the euro zone economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/why-is-euro-falling-could-it-hit-1-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6LT2YJJVZON3ACJDFVN7QIY4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 14:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[10 月 CPI 通胀率小幅上升，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，美国消费者物价如期上涨，自今年年中以来，降低通胀的进展有所放缓，这可能导致美联储明年的降息次数减少。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased as expected in October, and progress toward bringing inflation down has slowed since mid-year, which could result in fewer interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-oct-cpi-inflation-up-modestly-expected-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDNXFAPMDVJQBIYEN3UORCXGBY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀数据公布后，交易员押注美联储 12 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在一份政府报告显示 10 月份消费者通胀率上升符合经济学家预期之后，以美联储政策利率为结算基准的合约交易商开始倾向于认为央行在下个月的会议上再次降息四分之一点的可能性更大。【原文：Traders of contracts that settle to the Federal Reserve's policy rate moved Wednesday to price in a firmer chance of another quarter-point interest-rate cut at the central bank's meeting next month, after a government report showed consumer inflation rose in October in line with economist expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/traders-bet-fed-december-rate-cut-after-inflation-data-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWX5EREJ2NNITL44LGDNRFNA5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:47:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普胜选一周后，华尔街银行家们收敛了乐观情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，华尔街的金融家们齐聚曼哈顿市中心，他们对当选总统唐纳德-特朗普放松监管议程的乐观情绪因其人事和政策的不确定性而有所收敛。【原文：As Wall Street financiers gathered in downtown Manhattan on Wednesday, their optimism about President-elect Donald Trump's deregulatory agenda was tempered by uncertainty over his personnel and policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-bankers-temper-optimism-week-after-trump-victory-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U44CTUUW4RJ6VENJJMJMABATO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:45:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份消费者价格如期上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份美国消费者物价如期上涨，自今年年中以来，低通胀的进展有所放缓，这可能导致美联储明年的降息次数减少。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased as expected in October, and progress towards low inflation has slowed since mid-year, which could result in fewer interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-prices-rise-expected-october-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OD2ABJYXP5P4ZOOKHGRUPRSA4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:36:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士金融监管机构将定期审查对瑞银的监管方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士金融监管机构 FINMA 周三表示，随着瑞士当局准备全面修订监管法规，使银行业更加稳健，该机构今后将定期审查对瑞银集团的监管方式。【原文：Swiss financial regulator FINMA said on Wednesday it will in future regularly review how it oversees UBS as the country's authorities prepare to overhaul regulations to make the banking sector more robust.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swiss-financial-watchdog-regularly-review-how-it-oversees-ubs-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTGEV4KO2ZPSVE3FWT7CW27GBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国金融公司寻求 "大胆 "改革以对抗华尔街的崛起]]></title><description><![CDATA[在伦敦金融超级大国地位面临新挑战之际，英国金融业寄希望于政策制定者对规则进行改革，将增长放在首位，并阻止业务流失到全球竞争对手手中。【原文：Britain's finance sector is counting on policymakers to deliver a rulebook revamp that prioritises growth and stops business slipping away to global rivals, amid fresh challenges to London's financial superpower status.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/uk-finance-firms-seek-bold-reforms-counter-wall-st-ascendancy-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZQP3X7C25MZHK3TA7E7D6WONM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:11:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海上风电电缆制造商耐克森称可能将美国工厂改造成出口中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克森公司（Nexans）周三表示，如果唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）第二次担任总统后，海上风电行业受到挑战，该公司将把位于美国的工厂转变为出口中心。【原文：Nexans said on Wednesday it would turn its U.S.-based plant into an export hub if the offshore wind sector was challenged under Donald Trump's second stint as president.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/offshore-wind-cable-maker-nexans-says-it-might-turn-us-plant-into-export-hub-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQFA5NK4ERN7XIOMYLGNCSLIQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:10:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺基亚从 Rapid 收购全球最大的应用程序接口中心，以在 5G 领域套现]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺基亚周三表示，它已从美国公司 Rapid 手中收购了全球最大的应用编程接口（API）中心和市场，以提高其 5G 和 4G 网络的收入。【原文：Nokia said on Wednesday it had bought the world's largest application programming interface (API) hub and marketplace from U.S. company Rapid as it seeks to boost revenues from its 5G and 4G networks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nokia-buys-worlds-largest-api-hub-rapid-cash-5g-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QD6ASDZGXJL4FIVFFP5U5WO3SE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普胜选后，通胀忧虑再次困扰债券策略师]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，唐纳德-特朗普赢得总统大选迫使债券策略师们对较长期国债收益率的前景做出重大调整，因为美国通胀回升的风险正在升级。【原文：Donald Trump's presidential election win has forced bond strategists to make a material change in their outlook towards higher longer-dated Treasury yields, a Reuters poll found, as the risk of a U.S. inflation resurgence escalates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/inflation-worries-come-back-haunt-bond-strategists-after-trump-victory-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3NBLLNL5VLFRBS3HVW5P25TY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡瓦因牛排和皮塔饼需求再次上调年销售额预期，业绩大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[连锁餐厅卡瓦的股价在周三的盘前交易中飙升近 17%，达到 169.40 美元，此前该公司第三季度的盈利超出预期，原因是对皮塔饼和烤牛排等地中海美食的需求强劲。【原文：Restaurant chain Cava's stock soared nearly 17% to $169.40 in premarket trading on Wednesday, after it exceeded third-quarter earnings estimates on strong demand for its Mediterranean fare such as pita chips and grilled steak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/cava-jumps-after-raising-annual-sales-forecast-again-demand-steak-pita-chips-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAFZVIHSARNAJOGQGWMAIKY2BY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 12:44:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游艇制造商 Ferretti 在确认美国订单前下调全年指导计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利豪华游艇制造商法拉帝公司（Ferretti）周三下调了调整后核心利润（EBITDA）和收入的全年指导目标，以待其 "复合型 "游艇部门的美国订单得到确认。【原文：Italian luxury yacht maker Ferretti on Wednesday reduced its full-year guidance for adjusted core profit (EBITDA) and revenue pending confirmation of U.S. orders for yachts in its "composite" segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/yacht-maker-ferretti-cuts-full-year-guidance-pending-confirmation-us-orders-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2DXQJCY4BVLYVMMZQJV5N74HO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西服务业 9 月份创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 9 月份服务业活动的增长超过预期，并创下历史新高，这是在巴西央行启动货币紧缩周期以对抗通胀之后出现的经济强劲迹象。【原文：Services activity in Brazil grew more than expected in September and hit a record high, a sign of economic strength that comes after the central bank kicked off a monetary tightening cycle to fight inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/brazils-service-sector-hits-fresh-record-high-september-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6THOBDS5TVL5BHMGEIGWTKVNKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 12:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>