<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:39:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:39:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[参议院批准 Pulte 担任房利美和房地美监管机构职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院周四投票确认威廉-普尔特（William Pulte）担任负责监管房利美和房地美的监管机构的下一任主管。【原文：The U.S. Senate voted Thursday to confirm William Pulte to serve as the next director of the regulator charged with overseeing housing giants Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/senate-approves-pulte-fannie-freddie-regulator-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6QCF2ZLTJOIJDV7N6FRLFOPTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学学生被捕后，抗议者占领特朗普大厦]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，数十人涌入纽约市特朗普大厦大厅，抗议逮捕和拘留哥伦比亚大学学生马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil）。【原文：Scores of people poured into the lobby of Trump Tower in New York City on Thursday to protest the arrest and detention of Columbia University student Mahmoud Khalil, whom the Trump administration aims to deport over his pro-Palestinian activism.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/protesters-occupy-trump-tower-following-arrest-columbia-student-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGEVV6SOYFI7JPLSWBTAOTD2HE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:15:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称白宫指示各机构避免解雇网络安全人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封电子邮件称，白宫正在敦促联邦机构不要裁减其网络安全团队，因为他们正在争分夺秒地遵守周四提交大规模裁员计划以削减预算的最后期限。【原文：The White House is urging federal agencies to refrain from laying off their cybersecurity teams, as they scramble to comply with a Thursday deadline to submit mass layoff plans to slash their budgets, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-instructs-agencies-avoid-firing-cybersecurity-staff-email-says-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TM52ZPNLNFJKXIATQSATFU2HVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国邮政与埃隆-马斯克的 DOGE 团队签署援助协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国邮政总局局长路易斯-德乔伊（Louis DeJoy）告诉国会，他与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 DOGE 政府改革团队签署了一项协议，在这个亏损的机构努力解决 "大问题 "的过程中，为其提供援助。【原文：U.S. Postmaster General Louis DeJoy told Congress he signed an agreement with Elon Musk's DOGE government reform team to provide assistance to the money-losing agency as it works to address "big problems."】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usps-signs-agreement-with-elon-musks-doge-team-assistance-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFFPABDOLBISDOP5VQWRKHQGXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称纽约州州长霍邱尔将于周五与特朗普会晤]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普周四告诉记者，纽约州州长凯西-霍楚尔（Kathy Hochul）将于周五上午来华盛顿与唐纳德-特朗普总统会面。【原文：New York Governor Kathy Hochul will come to Washington to meet with President Donald Trump on Friday morning, Trump told reporters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ny-governor-hochul-meet-with-trump-friday-trump-says-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZAQZNG4YBJAXFJ5JV3H437TAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院备忘录显示，特朗普医疗保险提名人近年来可能 "严重 "少缴医疗保险税款]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据参议院财政委员会民主党工作人员起草的一份备忘录，被唐纳德-特朗普总统提名监督医疗保险和医疗补助计划的名医麦赫麦特-奥兹博士近年来似乎少缴了社会保险和医疗保险税。【原文：Dr. Mehmet Oz, the celebrity physician nominated by President Donald Trump to oversee Medicare and Medicaid, appears to have underpaid his social security and Medicare taxes in recent years, according to a memo drafted by Democratic staffers on the Senate Finance Committee.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-medicare-nominee-may-have-significantly-underpaid-his-medicare-taxes-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIWZNYZY4ZI63EEL7ZH55PCSXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:14:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农民起诉特朗普政府扣留 IRA 资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，几位美国农民和非营利组织对特朗普政府提起诉讼，称其非法扣留农业部通过《通货膨胀削减法》（Inflation Reduction Act）资助的拨款。【原文：Several U.S. farmers and nonprofits filed a lawsuit against the Trump administration on Thursday, arguing it is illegally withholding Department of Agriculture grants funded by the Inflation Reduction Act.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-farmers-sue-trump-administration-withheld-ira-funds-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLOZIDKL5VNVPANVBAXD6Q4T4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官命令特朗普政府恢复数千名被解雇工人的工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州的一名联邦法官周四命令六家美国机构恢复数千名新近被解雇的员工的工作，这些员工是唐纳德-特朗普总统清理联邦员工队伍行动的一部分。【原文：A California federal judge on Thursday ordered six U.S. agencies to reinstate thousands of recently-hired employees who were fired as part of President Donald Trump's purge of the federal workforce.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-extend-block-trump-administration-ordering-mass-firings-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAONQK2Q4NNA5AUSYBVNVSCYTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:22:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员敦促农业部恢复被取消的地方食品计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封信的副本，美国参议院的民主党人将要求农业部撤销已向学校和食品银行采购了 20 多亿美元当地食品的项目。【原文：Democrats in the U.S. Senate will ask the Department of Agriculture to reverse the cancellation of programs that have funneled more than $2 billion for local food purchases to schools and food banks, according to a copy of a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senators-urge-usda-reinstate-canceled-local-food-programs-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IVQHB4FHSBNRDMZ27NJTSJW2AI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国许多鸟类物种被认为已达到数量 "临界点]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份新的报告称，由于栖息地丧失和气候变化等因素，美国鸟类数量正在经历惊人的下降，该报告确定了 112 个已达到 "临界点 "的物种，其中包括 42 个数量极低并呈急剧下降趋势的物种。【原文：U.S. bird populations are experiencing alarming declines due to factors such as habitat loss and climate change, according to a new report identifying 112 species that have reached a "tipping point," including 42 with perilously low numbers and steep downward trends.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/environment/many-us-bird-species-seen-reaching-population-tipping-point-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2MUN5S7WZOBTAM47VQ2VVNKXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国许多鸟类物种被认为已达到数量 "临界点]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份新的报告称，由于栖息地丧失和气候变化等因素，美国鸟类数量正在经历惊人的下降，该报告确定了 112 个已达到 "临界点 "的物种，其中包括 42 个数量极低并呈急剧下降趋势的物种。【原文：U.S. bird populations are experiencing alarming declines due to factors such as habitat loss and climate change, according to a new report identifying 112 species that have reached a "tipping point," including 42 with perilously low numbers and steep downward trends.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/environment/many-us-bird-species-seen-reaching-population-tipping-point-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2MUN5S7WZOBTAM47VQ2VVNKXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院小组对喷气式直升机相撞事故展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院监督小组委员会周四表示，它正在调查 1 月份一架陆军黑鹰直升机与一架美国航空公司支线喷气式飞机在华盛顿里根国家机场附近相撞造成 67 人死亡的事件。【原文：A U.S. House of Representatives oversight subcommittee said Thursday it is investigating the collision in January between an Army Black Hawk helicopter and an American Airlines regional jet that killed 67 people near Washington Reagan National Airport.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-panel-opens-investigation-into-fatal-jet-helicopter-collision-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HU4JYHQPPVO55P53DP4F3MWA5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 首席律师希拉里-珀金斯（Hilary Perkins）上任两天即辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局首席法律顾问希拉里-珀金斯（Hilary Perkins）周四在社交媒体平台 X 上发文称，美国食品和药物管理局首席法律顾问希拉里-珀金斯（Hilary Perkins）已经辞职，这距离她的任命宣布仅过去了两天。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration's chief counsel, Hilary Perkins, has resigned, the federal agency said in a post on social media platform X on Thursday, just two days after her appointment was announced.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fdas-top-lawyer-hilary-perkins-resigns-two-days-into-role-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAM2MSIUMVMNBLDO7JVFBBBAGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府试图驳回哥伦比亚大学学生对逮捕的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府敦促法官驳回哥伦比亚大学学生马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil）对其移民逮捕提出的质疑，或者将此案移出纽约，因为这位亲巴勒斯坦活动人士的律师正在为他的获释而斗争。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration has urged a judge to dismiss Columbia University student Mahmoud Khalil's challenge to his immigration arrest, or alternatively move the case out of New York, as the pro-Palestinian activist's lawyers fight for his release.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-seeks-toss-columbia-students-challenge-arrest-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFPJLVNQAZJNVEOXI275SFTGUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:14:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布蒂吉格表示不会竞选密歇根州州长和美国参议员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前交通部长皮特-巴蒂吉格（Pete Buttigieg）周四表示，他将不会竞选明年的密歇根州州长或美国参议院参议员。【原文：Former U.S. Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg said on Thursday that he will not run for governor in Michigan or U.S. Senate next year.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/buttigieg-says-he-will-not-run-michigan-governor-us-senate-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AR5Q2QVLPRJHLKH6UU3W42O2LE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布蒂吉格表示不会竞选密歇根州州长和美国参议员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前交通部长皮特-巴蒂吉格（Pete Buttigieg）周四表示，他将不会竞选明年的密歇根州州长或美国参议院参议员。【原文：Former U.S. Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg said on Thursday that he will not run for governor in Michigan or U.S. Senate next year.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/buttigieg-says-he-will-not-run-michigan-governor-us-senate-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AR5Q2QVLPRJHLKH6UU3W42O2LE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官命令 DOGE 和马斯克提供削减成本的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名法官命令埃隆-马斯克和他的政府效率部回答有关他们削减联邦开支的问题。【原文：A judge has ordered Elon Musk and his Department of Government Efficiency to answer questions describing their efforts to slash federal spending.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-orders-doge-musk-produce-cost-cutting-records-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MOJ5R7KLQVP73JWQV3CK2XY52U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:51:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党领导的各州起诉阻止特朗普解散美国教育部]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群民主党州检察长周四提起诉讼，寻求阻止共和党美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府解散美国教育部，并阻止其裁员近一半。【原文：A group of Democratic state attorneys general on Thursday filed a lawsuit seeking to block Republican U.S. President Donald Trump's administration from dismantling the U.S. Department of Education and halt it from laying off nearly half of its staff.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-led-states-sue-block-trump-dismantling-us-education-department-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZVS2SIHHFIQPMBW452ZAVROPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Axios 报道，白宫撤回特朗普的疾控中心人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Axios 周四报道，白宫正在撤换唐纳德-特朗普总统提名的美国疾病控制和预防中心领导人戴夫-韦尔登（Dave Weldon），就在提名人即将在美国参议院接受确认之际。【原文：The White House is pulling President Donald Trump's nominee to lead the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Dave Weldon, Axios reported on Thursday just as the nominee was set to appear before the U.S. Senate for confirmation.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/white-house-withdraws-trumps-pick-cdc-axios-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEMDNK4GNFJZLCGFOJHVLJSGDE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 12:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降，劳动力市场保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济的美国人数有所下降，但政府大幅削减开支和贸易战升级威胁着劳动力市场的稳定。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell last week, but sharp government spending cuts and an escalating trade war threaten labor market stability.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-amid-labor-market-stability-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AK2JAUIPNINNKALEENEG32POM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 12:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克裁员缩减了帮助实现特朗普能源主导议程所需的员工队伍]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社采访的州政府官员、立法者和机构代表称，特朗普政府大规模裁减联邦工作人员，导致政府许可一些新能源项目的能力放缓，唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "钻井，宝贝，钻井 "议程可能因此受挫。【原文：The Trump administration’s mass layoffs of federal workers have slowed the government’s ability to permit some new energy projects in a potential setback to President Donald Trump’s ‘drill, baby, drill’ agenda, according to state officials, lawmakers and agency representatives interviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/musks-layoffs-shrink-workforce-needed-help-realize-trumps-energy-dominance-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZDCRGZRCRJW3AXRAXQACVWP5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 10:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国各机构提交大规模裁员计划的截止日期为周四]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四是政府机构提交第二波大规模裁员和削减预算计划的截止日期，唐纳德-特朗普总统缩减美国联邦政府的潜在规模可能会变得更加清晰。【原文：The potential scale of President Donald Trump's efforts to shrink the U.S. federal government could become clearer on Thursday, the deadline for government agencies to submit plans for a second wave of mass layoffs and to slash their budgets.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-agencies-face-thursday-deadline-submit-mass-layoff-plans-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6JQRF42KJIC7KOWLV7HOBSRWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 10:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的疾控中心人选韦尔登将面临禽流感和麻疹威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[疫苗评论家戴夫-韦尔登（Dave Weldon）是唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统选中领导美国疾病控制和预防中心（U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention）的人选，他将在这个已经因裁员和公众对 COVID-19 大流行病的不信任而陷入动荡的机构面临麻疹病例上升和禽流感的威胁。【原文：Vaccine critic Dave Weldon, President Donald Trump's pick to lead the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, will face rising measles cases and bird flu threats at an agency already in turmoil from staff cuts and public distrust over the COVID-19 pandemic.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trumps-cdc-pick-weldon-face-bird-flu-measles-threats-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGP5GLZIVNKUTN42V7PF5HHCTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 10:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：美国服装生产为何不可能发生重大转变]]></title><description><![CDATA[几位高管本周告诉路透社，唐纳德-特朗普总统推动的 "美国制造 "正在促使一些美国服装零售商扩大从T恤衫到大衣和西装等各种产品的国内生产。【原文：President Donald Trump's Made in America push is prompting some U.S. clothing retailers to expand domestic production of everything from T-shirts to coats and suits, several executives told Reuters this week.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/why-major-shift-us-clothing-production-is-unlikely-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CAY4HBL3ZOYNOV534VGD56C2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 09:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[警方称美国最高法院法官巴雷特的妹妹成为炸弹威胁目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[当地警方周三表示，保守派美国最高法院大法官艾米-科尼-巴雷特（Amy Coney Barrett）的妹妹本月初在南卡罗来纳州查尔斯顿的家中遭到炸弹威胁。【原文：A sister of conservative U.S. Supreme Court Justice Amy Coney Barrett was the target of a bomb threat at her home in Charleston, South Carolina, earlier this month, local police said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/sister-us-supreme-courts-barrett-target-bomb-threat-police-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIUFZDTVBJLWTFEYB7ZZWWKW5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报道称美国司法部正在调查纽约移民酒店]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，美国司法部周三开始调查纽约市酒店作为移民庇护所的运营情况。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department on Wednesday opened an investigation into the operation of New York City hotels as migrant shelters, according to media reports.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-justice-department-investigating-new-york-migrant-hotels-reports-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JS37A3QHKFPWXJEHRATA3Z3LJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人权组织称特朗普在提到舒默时使用了 "巴勒斯坦人 "这一蔑称]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国穆斯林和犹太人权益组织周三批评唐纳德-特朗普总统将参议院民主党最高级别的参议员查克-舒默称为巴勒斯坦人，这些组织称总统使用该词是一种污蔑。【原文：U.S. Muslim and Jewish advocacy groups criticized President Donald Trump on Wednesday for referring to the top Senate Democrat, Senator Chuck Schumer, as a Palestinian, with the organizations saying the president used the term as a slur.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/rights-groups-say-trump-used-term-palestinian-slur-reference-schumer-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGYP2KQHOBNDRAYEUYSQJW6CAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道被捕哥伦比亚大学学生的妻子说，她天真地以为他是安全的]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国特工逮捕马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil）的前两天，这位哥伦比亚大学学生和巴勒斯坦活动家问他的妻子，如果移民局特工上门，她知道该怎么办吗？【原文：Two days before U.S. agents arrested Mahmoud Khalil, the Columbia University student and Palestinian activist asked his wife if she knew what to do if immigration agents came to their door.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/wife-arrested-columbia-student-says-she-was-naive-believe-he-was-secure-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BP3KHLF6WRPXPIPIUCNIVQQ3ZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:06:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙德克萨斯炼油厂脚手架倒塌致工人受伤--消息人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉工厂运作的人士说，雪佛龙公司位于得克萨斯州帕萨迪纳的炼油厂周三发生脚手架倒塌事故，造成三名工人受伤。【原文：A scaffolding collapse on Wednesday at Chevron Corp's Pasadena, Texas, refinery injured three workers, people familiar with plant operations said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/scaffolding-collapse-injures-workers-chevron-texas-refinery-sources-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4TLBZLFTZPCBPQWBQNGR3KLGY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）取消了原定回收被困宇航员的宇航员航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）周三取消了向国际空间站发射由四名宇航员组成的替代机组人员的计划，该计划将启动美国宇航员布奇-威尔莫尔（Butch Wilmore）和苏尼-威廉姆斯（Suni Williams）期待已久的回家之旅，他们已在国际空间站滞留了九个月。【原文：SpaceX on Wednesday scrubbed the expected launch of a replacement crew of four astronauts to the International Space Station that would have set in motion the long-awaited homecoming of U.S. astronauts Butch Wilmore and Suni Williams, who have been stranded on the station for nine months.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/space/spacex-nasa-set-astronaut-flight-that-will-retrieve-stuck-astronauts-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VHWCCK7FZLFNINA2HXRKPHHOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>