<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:07:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:07:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Investcorp 可能考虑在 3-5 年内上市，着眼于美国的退休储蓄]]></title><description><![CDATA[Investcorp 副董事长周五表示，Investcorp 可能考虑在未来三到五年内公开上市，这家中东最大的另类投资公司的目标是将其管理资产翻一番，达到 1,000 亿美元。【原文：Investcorp could consider a public listing in the next three to five years, its vice chairman said on Friday, as the Middle East's biggest alternative investment firm targets a doubling of its assets under management to $100 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investcorp-could-consider-listing-3-5-years-eyes-us-retirement-savings-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDZC7FU2IBMPLLXSI3574ZHOXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:37:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政策的不确定性导致期货下跌；等待数据和收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于唐纳德-特朗普总统贸易政策的不确定性占据上风，同时投资者也在等待可能揭示经济状况的数据和企业财报，美国股指期货周五下跌。【原文：U.S. stock index futures dipped on Friday, as uncertainty about President Donald Trump's trade policies prevailed, while investors also awaited data and corporate earnings reports that could throw light on the state of the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-dip-trump-policy-uncertainty-data-earnings-awaited-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHHPW2VPLRMJXEGPGB64VUVQCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:26:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国举报人称万事达卡和维萨卡未能阻止为 OnlyFans 上的儿童性虐待材料付款]]></title><description><![CDATA[万事达卡和威士卡未能阻止它们的支付网络对热门网站 OnlyFans 上的儿童性虐待材料和性交易收益进行洗钱，据此前未披露的举报人向美国财政部金融犯罪部门提交的指控称。【原文：Mastercard and Visa failed to stop their payment networks from laundering proceeds from child sexual abuse material and sex trafficking on the popular website OnlyFans, according to allegations in a previously undisclosed whistleblower complaint filed with the U.S. Treasury’s financial crimes unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-whistleblower-says-mastercard-visa-failed-stop-payments-child-sex-abuse-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BI56BC5GX5JMLHASJH6QXRXDZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球风险投资公司首次亮相，测试特朗普政策转向后的能源 IPO 胃口]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Global LNG 将于本周五首次公开募股，其首次公开募股估值大幅降低至 605 亿美元，但仍将成为美国最大的上市能源公司之一。【原文：Venture Global LNG will debut on public markets on Friday after sharply lowering its IPO valuation to $60.5 billion, but still set to be one of the largest U.S.-listed energy companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/venture-global-debut-test-appetite-energy-ipos-after-trumps-policy-pivot-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y7I4AYWORJMBKWWBPGDZ5I3HI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[进入特朗普新时代，美国立法者对加密货币态度冷淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府有望迎来加密货币的繁荣时期，但路透社的一项调查显示，即将上任的国会议员中很少有人投资比特币或其他数字货币。【原文：President Donald Trump’s administration is expected to usher in a boom time for crypto but a Reuters review shows very few members of the incoming congress are invested in bitcoin or other digital currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-lawmakers-are-light-crypto-heading-into-new-trump-era-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKNJZMDU5RK7DKHWKWULVPKZ5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美联储降息观点将考验美股反弹势头]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储将于下周召开的 2025 年首次会议将对美国股市的回升构成考验，因为投资者将衡量未来几个月更有利于股市的降息幅度。【原文：The Federal Reserve's first meeting of 2025 in the coming week stands to test the resurgence in U.S. stocks as investors gauge the extent of more equity-friendly interest rate cuts in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-feds-rate-cut-view-set-test-resurgent-us-stocks-rally-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVMRQDU4QVIJFLFYFDMDOGKJNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：航空航天供应商争相缓解特朗普关税迫在眉睫的打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大直升机零部件供应商 Optima Aero 已经开始将库存转移到边境以南，以尽量降低美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提出的潜在关税风险。【原文：Canadian helicopter parts supplier Optima Aero is already moving inventory south of the border to minimize the risk from potential tariffs proposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aerospace-suppliers-scramble-cushion-blow-looming-trump-tariffs-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXGQR566W5KEBBWD2VWPSI2N2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 日本央行加息、欧元区经济增长、人民币升值，美元大幅下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWZ2L66YIZNNBESDE4QARNAVMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储暂时按兵不动，关注就业强劲和通胀放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[在 12 月份的上次会议上，美国联邦储备委员会的官员们担心通胀率会超过 2% 的目标，并目睹了就业岗位的增加在似乎正在出现的下滑中摇摆不定。【原文：At their last meeting in December, U.S. Federal Reserve officials were worried about inflation getting stuck above their 2% target and had watched job gains seesaw in what seemed an emerging decline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-hold-now-eyes-strong-jobs-easing-inflation-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VIGOBCIGZRPGRKZY7EV43L34KE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储在不稳定时刻保持利率稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）的政策制定者们预计将在下周的会议上继续按兵不动，但更大的事件将是该央行如何面对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的早期举措，这些举措可能会影响今年的经济，包括要求美联储继续降低借贷成本。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve policymakers meeting next week are expected to keep interest rates on hold but the larger story unfolding will be how the central bank confronts early moves by President Donald Trump that are likely to shape the economy this year, including demands the Fed continue lowering borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-hold-rates-steady-an-unsteady-moment-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZKRTRDBU5O6LPYVXHCBR7TRMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁格奥尔基耶娃：世界通胀尚未完全被打败]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）在达沃斯表示，全球政策制定者在不引发经济衰退的情况下应对通货膨胀方面取得了显著进展，但仍有一些工作要做。【原文：Global policymakers have made remarkable progress in tackling inflation without inducing a recession, but some work remains to be done, International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said in Davos.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/world-inflation-not-fully-defeated-yet-imfs-georgieva-says-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EE64MQASUFIYDMBN6WCYLHOGHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:44:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民意调查：中国 1 月份制造业活动连续第四个月扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[1 月份，中国的工厂活动可能连续第四个月扩张，这凸显了这个世界第二大经济体的供应方实力，而中国正在为美国提高关税做准备，这可能会进一步削弱国内需求并加剧通货紧缩压力。【原文：China's factory activity likely expanded for a fourth month in January, highlighting the supply-side strength of the world's No.2 economy, which is bracing for U.S. tariff hikes that could further weaken domestic demand and fuel deflationary pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/poll-china-jan-manufacturing-activity-seen-expanding-fourth-month-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNLBFY2LPJO2DHI6YN2FACSGCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:40:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：日本 JERA 计划扩大美国液化天然气采购量，以实现能源供应多元化]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高级管理人员告诉路透社，日本最大的顶级液化天然气买家 JERA 计划增加从美国购买液化天然气，以实现供应多样化，满足数据中心和人工智能刺激的需求增长。【原文：Japan's biggest top LNG buyer, JERA, plans to increase its purchases of liquefied natural gas from the United States to diversify its supply and meet demand growth spurred by data centres and AI, a senior executive told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/japans-jera-plans-expand-us-lng-purchases-diversify-energy-supply-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDPE4UKXSBNODJ3ZBOGOKEM7NE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息希望重燃，美国股票基金流出缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 1 月 22 日的一周，美国股票基金的资金流出量降至三周以来的最低水平，这主要是受到美国核心通胀报告利好股市后，市场对暂停降息的预期发生变化的影响。【原文：Outflows from U.S. equity funds cooled to the lowest in three weeks in the week to Jan. 22, buoyed by shifting expectations for a pause in rate cuts after a benign U.S. core inflation report bolstered equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-fund-outflows-ease-renewed-hopes-fed-rate-cuts-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4GIMAJ45VPFZBF2EW5QNXOXVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:32:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯 STC 寻求进入西班牙电信董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯最大的电信运营商 STC 集团在一份文件中向美国市场监管机构表示，将在西班牙电信公司意外更换首席执行官六天后，寻求在该公司董事会中占有一席之地。【原文：Saudi Arabia's largest telecoms operator, STC Group , will seek a seat on Telefonica's board, it told the U.S. markets regulator in a filing, six days after the Spanish company unexpectedly replaced its chief executive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/saudi-arabias-stc-seeks-seat-telefonica-board-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCSEVIFSPRPKDH3ZYHYABED5GY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:27:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达沃斯-贝莱德的芬克说，也许是时候重返欧洲投资了]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）周五在达沃斯世界经济论坛上表示，欧洲存在太多悲观情绪，现在可能是重新投资该地区的时候了。【原文：There is too much pessimism around Europe and it could be time to investing back in the region, BlackRock CEO Larry Fink said at the World Economic Forum in Davos on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/davos-blackrocks-fink-says-probably-time-be-investing-back-europe-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQHSVZ6X25NDBLIMCS52VJUTTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 2024 年财政收入增长 1.3%，低于去年同期的 6.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[财政部周五公布的数据显示，2024 年中国财政收入同比增长 1.3%，增幅低于 2023 年的 6.4%。【原文：China's fiscal revenue in 2024 rose 1.3% year on year, narrowing from 6.4% expansion in 2023, finance ministry data showed on Friday, as a property market slump and slowing domestic demands weighed on the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-2024-fiscal-revenue-grows-13-down-64-year-earlier-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKU3443ZRVLOLB2PDFXXJSKFLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金因美联储降息希望和特朗普的人工智能计划而获得资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至1月22日的一周里，全球股票基金五周来第四次获得资金流入，这主要是受到美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）在通胀降温后降息的乐观预期，以及唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统提出的大规模人工智能基础设施支出计划的刺激。【原文：Global equity funds gained a fourth weekly inflow in five weeks in the week through Jan. 22 spurred by optimism for U.S. Federal Reserve rate cuts following cooling inflation and President Donald Trump's plans for extensive AI infrastructure spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSQXGUQRJVK3LLNXEXFHT5PBVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PMI显示，欧元区企业在2025年伊始温和恢复增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项调查显示，欧元区企业在新年伊始适度恢复增长，1 月份服务业活动稳定，制造业长期低迷的态势也有所缓解。【原文：Euro zone business began the new year with a modest return to growth as stable services activity in January was complemented by an easing of the long-running downturn in manufacturing, a survey showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-businesses-start-2025-with-modest-return-growth-pmi-shows-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBJD6SKGTJL63G6FZZ2E3HCZS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 09:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 1 月份商业活动趋于稳定，PMI 显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的一项调查显示，由于服务业的增长抵消了制造业产出的持续下降，1 月份德国私营部门的商业活动趋于稳定，结束了连续六个月的萎缩。【原文：Business activity in Germany's private sector stabilised in January, marking an end to a six-month contraction as services growth offset a continued decline in manufacturing output, according to a survey published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-business-activity-stabilises-january-pmi-shows-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXZI5ZMGIVNGPHNKBRUBKE7RTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 08:42:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NTT DATA 老板在达沃斯呼吁制定人工智能监管的全球标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本 IT 公司 NTT DATA 首席执行官表示，人工智能（AI）监管方面的全球标准将降低这一快速发展技术的开发风险。【原文：The chief executive of Japanese IT company NTT DATA said global standards in regulation of artificial intelligence (AI) would reduce risks in the development of the fast-emerging technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ntt-data-boss-calls-global-standards-ai-regulation-davos-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJ6UUOYXSZJMJP2ALRZ55IXQTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 08:41:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[销售额超出预期，巴宝莉股价上涨 13]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国奢侈品零售商巴宝莉（Burberry）第三季度销售额降幅低于预期，周五开盘股价飙升超过 13%。【原文：Shares in British luxury retailer Burberry soared by more than 13% in opening trade on Friday after its third-quarter sales fell by less than forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/burberry-shares-rise-13-after-sales-beat-expectations-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODL2CDFURJI3FBWP4WTNE4VYHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 08:40:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行称在提出具体报价前不会与裕信银行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行周五重申，在收到意大利联合信贷银行的具体建议之前，不会与该银行进行正式讨论。【原文：Commerzbank reiterated on Friday that it will not meet with UniCredit for formal discussions until it receives a specific proposal from the Italian bank, which has ruffled feathers in Berlin with its interest in a merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/commerzbank-says-no-talks-with-unicredit-until-specific-offer-made-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGUMZWSQEBLFTIY23YAEPIVV7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 08:19:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管机构称特斯拉将修复 120 多万辆进口和中国制造汽车的软件问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门表示，特斯拉将修复部分进口Model S和X以及中国制造的Model 3和Y汽车存在安全隐患的软件，总计修复数量超过120万辆。【原文：Tesla will fix software for some imported Model S and X, and China-made Model 3 and Y cars over safety hazards, totalling more than 1.2 million units, China's market regulator said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-fix-software-over-12-million-imported-china-made-cars-says-regulator-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZIWH663GRPQXA3SMOVGHENH34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 08:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股息激增预示着中国市场的文化转变]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国政府的授意下，一些公司回购股票，并向等待回暖的投资者支付创纪录的股息，中国疲惫不堪的股市正在出现新的资本主义色彩。【原文：New shades of capitalism are emerging in China's tuckered out stock market as companies, at Beijing's behest, buy back their shares and pay record dividends to investors lying in wait for a so-far evasive rebound.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/dividend-surge-signals-culture-shift-chinas-markets-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HA6WV4OSSJJERI2ND2FOW33RYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利银行业争夺战中的谁主沉浮]]></title><description><![CDATA[被救助的意大利银行业巨头锡耶纳银行（MPS）周五向 Mediobanca 提出了 133 亿欧元（139 亿美元）的全股收购要约，这是意大利银行业复杂传奇的最新意外转折。【原文：Bailed-out lender Monte dei Paschi di Siena (MPS) launched on Friday a 13.3 billion euro ($13.9 billion) all-share buyout offer for Mediobanca , in the latest surprise twist of a complex Italian banking saga.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/who-owns-what-italys-banking-battles-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5P6G7WRTZPMFG5MHFNHGAW6DQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解释器：-美国比特币战略储备如何运作？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四下令成立一个数字资产工作组，其任务之一是探索美国加密货币储备。【原文：President Donald Trump ordered the creation of a digital asset working group on Thursday which, among other things, would be tasked with exploring a U.S. cryptocurrency stockpile.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/how-would-us-bitcoin-strategic-reserve-work-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROD5L3EARVL5TNR3TKWURE5SKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈利-波特》出版商布鲁姆斯伯里与亚马逊达成供货协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈利-波特》出版商布鲁姆斯伯里出版公司周五表示，已与亚马逊达成新的长期供货协议。【原文：Harry Potter publisher Bloomsbury Publishing said on Friday it has reached a new long-term supply agreement with Amazon .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/harry-potter-publisher-bloomsbury-strikes-supply-agreement-with-amazon-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JOFR4KJQFVKAVKVK6E2Q2J2YCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:21:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国购物者为巴宝莉带来假日促销效应]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，英国奢侈品牌巴宝莉（Burberry）发布报告称，受美国假日季强劲需求的帮助，该公司季度可比店面销售额下降了4%，降幅小于预期，这是该公司扭亏为盈过程中令人鼓舞的一步。【原文：British luxury brand Burberry reported a smaller than expected 4% drop in quarterly comparable store sales on Friday, helped by stronger holiday season demand in the United States, an encouraging step in the company's turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/burberrys-quarterly-sales-drop-less-than-feared-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23F2ZPAXOVOFBIMFUPC4WEGVME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:10:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱立信第四季度营收和核心利润因美国需求复苏而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电信设备制造商爱立信周五公布，由于其主要的北美市场恢复增长，第四季度收入和调整后营业利润均有所增长。【原文：Swedish telecom equipment maker Ericsson reported on Friday a rise in fourth-quarter revenue and adjusted operating profit as its mainstay North American market returned to growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ericssons-q4-core-profit-rises-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LVA67WU7VITXJ45FFLS635MQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 06:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>