<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:45:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:45:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国就美国新关税向世贸组织提出申诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国表示已于周五向世界贸易组织正式投诉美国的新关税措施，称这些措施违反了世贸组织规则，并要求进行磋商。【原文：China said it had opened a formal complaint against the new U.S. tariffs with the World Trade Organization on Friday, saying the measures violate WTO rules and requesting consultations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-files-complaint-with-wto-over-new-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUQXQVFWKVP4BLTDBYH7V5MGOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 中国在全球贸易战中采取报复行动后，石油暴跌 8]]></title><description><![CDATA[继美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周早些时候全面征收关税之后，中国周五又对美国商品征收 34% 的额外关税，从而使全球贸易冲突升级。【原文：China escalated the global trade conflict on Friday by imposing an additional 34% tariff on U.S. goods, following President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/view-oil-tumbles-8-after-china-retaliates-global-trade-war-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKI3AEPUDFMHFI67XBXO62N5ZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月份就业增长超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份美国经济新增就业岗位远超预期，但在商业信心下滑和股市大跌的背景下，唐纳德-特朗普总统全面征收进口关税可能会在未来数月考验劳动力市场的韧性。【原文：The U.S. economy added far more jobs than expected in March, but President Donald Trump's sweeping import tariffs could test the labor market's resilience in the months ahead amid sagging business confidence and a stock market selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-growth-beats-expectations-march-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RMQBBFGV5RPGZLHS6MIKCBWIWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:38:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，汽车制造商 INEOS 调整定价]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于伦敦的英力士汽车公司周五表示，由于新的25%汽车进口关税，该公司正在提高其高档汽车的价格。【原文：London-based INEOS Automotive is increasing prices on its premium vehicles as a result of the new 25% tariff on auto imports, the company said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/automaker-ineos-adjusts-pricing-result-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J3MM4W3HLFINJOQBY2ZDKWEQS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:38:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年，Spotify 向尼日利亚和南非艺术家支付的版税激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[音频流媒体巨头 Spotify 去年向尼日利亚和南非（其最大的两个非洲市场）艺人支付的版税飙升至约 5900 万美元，因为艺人对非洲大陆音乐的兴趣与日俱增。【原文：Audio streaming giant Spotify's royalty payments to artists from Nigeria and South Africa - its two biggest African markets - spiked to around $59 million last year as performers rode a wave of growing interest in music from the continent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/spotify-royalty-payouts-nigerian-south-african-artists-boom-2024-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GL6TQPHN6RIH5LEDCUG2T5OAKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国报复特朗普关税，科技股和银行股首当其冲]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国政府对美国商品征收34%的额外关税进行报复之后，美国科技重镇、银行和石油巨头周五扩大了跌幅，这加剧了投资者对全球贸易战升级的担忧，而贸易战升级又加剧了对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. tech heavyweights, banks and oil majors extended losses on Friday after Beijing retaliated with additional duties of 34% on U.S. goods, amplifying investor concerns over an escalating global trade war that has stoked fears of a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tech-bank-stocks-bear-brunt-china-retaliates-trump-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMP5O5K4WZJYJGWSL7PPOCVCAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司 SandboxAQ 新增英伟达和谷歌为支持者，再融资 1.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[利用量子计算技术为企业开发定量人工智能模型的初创公司 SandboxAQ 表示，该公司已从包括谷歌、英伟达（Nvidia）和法国巴黎银行（BNP Paribas）在内的新投资者那里筹集了 1.5 亿美元。【原文：SandboxAQ, a startup drawing on quantum computing techniques to develop quantitative artificial intelligence models for enterprises, said it has raised $150 million from new investors including Google, Nvidia and BNP Paribas .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-startup-sandboxaq-adds-nvidia-google-backers-raises-additional-150-million-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGAYSYO5V5KDVATPYBNVDJVZNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:08:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税担忧升级，投资者逃离美国股票基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月2日的一周里，美国股票基金出现资金外流，原因是投资者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收贸易关税可能会推高成本、给企业利润带来压力并加剧经济衰退风险的担忧与日俱增，因而抛售风险资产。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw outflows in the week ending April 2 as investors shed risky assets on growing concerns that President Donald Trump's sweeping trade tariffs could drive up costs, pressure corporate profits and heighten recession risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/investors-flee-us-equity-funds-escalating-tariff-concerns-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4HEO4SUSZL2ZPQX4WLDF2RCTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:58:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国以稀土出口管制回击美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为对唐纳德-特朗普总统一揽子关税计划的回应，中国周五对一些稀土元素实施了出口限制，这可能会切断美国与从智能手机到电动汽车电池等各种产品所需的重要矿产的联系。【原文：China placed some rare earth elements under export restrictions on Friday as part of its response to President Donald Trump's tariff package, potentially cutting the U.S. off from critical minerals vital to everything from smartphones to electric car batteries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-hits-back-us-tariffs-with-rare-earth-export-controls-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5MBLZPRMROYRMDMRW5Y27UJGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:53:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发美国经济衰退担忧，印度 IT 企业做好应对准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，印度价值 2830 亿美元的 IT 行业未来一年将面临严峻考验，因为关税可能会刺激其主要美国市场的通货膨胀，并迫使客户削减支出。【原文：India's $283-billion IT sector should brace for a rough year ahead as tariffs are likely to stoke inflation in its key U.S. market and force clients to cut spending, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indian-it-firms-brace-impact-tariffs-fan-us-recession-fears-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CZYMEEGC5NKZOMYTPC6HUZ4AE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道德国为欧洲通信卫星公司在乌克兰的互联网提供资金，马斯克紧张局势加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[柏林一直在为乌克兰接入法国欧洲通信卫星公司（Eutelsat）运营的卫星互联网网络支付费用，因为欧洲正在寻求埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 "星际链路"（Starlink）的替代方案。【原文：Berlin has been paying for Ukraine's access to a satellite-internet network operated by France's Eutelsat , as Europe seeks alternatives to Elon Musk’s Starlink.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/germany-funds-eutelsat-internet-ukraine-musk-tensions-rise-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKPZB7SYSJK4TOY7GMOATZ62GI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:37:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北约代表吕特表示，美国关税并未违反北约条约]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，北约秘书长马克-吕特（Mark Rutte）在布鲁塞尔与北约外长会晤后表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统宣布的美国全面新关税并未违反北约条约。【原文：The sweeping new U.S. tariffs announced by President Donald Trump do not violate NATO treaties, the military alliance's Secretary-General Mark Rutte said on Friday after meeting NATO foreign ministers in Brussels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-tariffs-dont-violate-nato-treaty-says-natos-rutte-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5SPBWZYXVKHRIZQRHPBTKNYOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易关税引发经济放缓担忧，全球货币市场资金流入激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月2日的一周里，全球货币市场基金出现大量资金流入，原因是投资者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的激进贸易政策越来越谨慎，这些政策加剧了对全球经济放缓的担忧，并促使一些经济学家上调了对经济衰退的预测。【原文：Global money market funds saw massive inflows in the week ending April 2 as investors grew cautious over U.S. President Donald Trump's aggressive trade policies, which are heightening fears of a global slowdown and prompting some economists to revise their recession projections upward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMGBRPKSQRPGBPK6BWNCXVHZLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税冲击后，评级机构标普将审查所有全球预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评级巨头S&amp;P Global表示，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周大规模征收世界贸易关税之后，该公司正在审查其所有宏观经济预测，此举可能会加剧人们对信用评级再次下调的担忧。【原文：Credit ratings giant S&amp;P Global has said it is reviewing all its macro economic forecasts in the wake of Donald Trump's sweeping world trade tariffs this week, a move likely to fuel concerns of a renewed wave of credit score downgrades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/ratings-agency-sp-review-all-global-forecasts-after-us-tariff-shock-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3G7EUVU4KRKDZBODFYDSZYGJ3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start Campus 计划投资 93.5 亿美元建设葡萄牙数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国投资基金 Davidson Kempner 和英国的 Pioneer Point Partners 计划到 2030 年投资 85 亿欧元（93.5 亿美元）在葡萄牙建设一个数据中心枢纽，以满足大型科技和人工智能公司日益增长的需求。【原文：U.S. investment fund Davidson Kempner and Britain's Pioneer Point Partners plan to invest 8.5 billion euros ($9.35 billion) by 2030 in a data centre hub in Portugal to serve a growing demand from major tech and artificial intelligence companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/start-campus-plans-invest-935-billion-portugal-data-hub-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5R6SG2DIPVOU3K5IHLLFUNHYUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:10:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储经济衰退警报之一发出 2008 年式信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储首选的经济衰退指标之一本周的恶化速度与 2008 年一样快，这是一个最新迹象，表明债券投资者正在为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税政策导致经济急剧放缓做好准备。【原文：One of the Federal Reserve's preferred recession indicators has this week deteriorated as fast as it did in 2008, the latest sign that bond investors are bracing for a sharp economic slowdown as a result of U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/one-feds-top-recession-alarms-sends-2008-style-signal-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IK3A6MPHCZKPDOEQKMSWCAAWXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 投资者对中国对美国商品征收报复性关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五宣布对美国商品征收 34% 的额外关税，以报复美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周实施的全面关税措施，这些措施加剧了市场对经济衰退的担忧，并引发了全球股市暴跌。【原文：China announced additional tariffs of 34% on U.S. goods on Friday, retaliating to President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs this week that have fed fears of a recession and triggered a global stock market rout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/view-investors-react-chinas-retaliatory-tariffs-us-goods-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4FFV6UWYJN73HQTWPIJRO7V3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税将削弱印度钻石业，损害就业和出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国的高额关税可能会破坏印度的宝石和珠宝出口，危及成千上万工人的生计，一股焦虑情绪笼罩着印度的钻石抛光中心苏拉特。【原文：A wave of anxiety has gripped India's diamond polishing hub of Surat, as hefty U.S. tariffs threaten to undermine the country's gem and jewellery exports, putting at risk the livelihoods of thousands of workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-tariffs-set-cripple-indias-diamond-industry-hurting-jobs-exports-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UE7Q74QKTVI3FINU2PND6I56PY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:56:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国垃圾债券利差因贸易战担忧飙升至 17 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至周四晚些时候，美国高收益公司债券利差飙升至401个基点，创下2023年11月以来的新高，原因是全球市场担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的进口关税计划将引发贸易战。【原文：U.S. high yield corporate bond spreads surged to 401 basis points as of late Thursday, their highest since November 2023, as global markets swooned over fears that U.S. President Donald Trump's plan for import tariffs would kick off a trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-junk-bond-spreads-surge-17-month-high-trade-war-fears-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJICXFQYRZNURMV5MNZ3O7DHNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:48:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利总理称与美国的谈判应以取消所有关税为目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利总理乔治亚-梅洛尼（Giorgia Meloni）周五表示，美国与欧盟之间的关税谈判应以取消所有关税为目标。【原文：Italian Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni on Friday said negotiations on tariffs between the U.S. and the European Union should aim at lifting all of them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/italy-pm-says-negotiations-with-us-should-aim-removing-all-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQMZCEF56JLUZJD2WRL3EWL32A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:45:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inditex 在美国开设更多门店仍有商机]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zara 所有者 Inditex 公司首席执行官 Oscar Garcia Maceiras 周五表示，尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布征收贸易关税，但该公司相信自己将有机会在美国发展，并计划在美国开设更多门店。【原文：Zara owner Inditex believes it will have opportunities to grow in the United States where it plans to open more stores, despite trade tariffs annouced by President Donald Trump, Chief Executive Officer Oscar Garcia Maceiras said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/inditex-still-sees-opportunities-us-with-more-stores-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HF2JY2VVIFMG3AVQHKN2ODTWFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美洲 "壮丽 "熊]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORQ7ALWLDJNHJOIBBKZAPR3UDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国贸易机构称，美国加征关税可能导致日本汽车出口损失 170 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际贸易中心周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普决定对汽车行业征收25%的关税后，日本可能失去170亿美元的汽车出口潜力。【原文：Japan could lose $17 billion in car export potential in the U.S. following President Donald Trump's decision to introduce 25% tariffs on the automotive sector, the International Trade Centre said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japan-could-lose-17-billion-car-exports-due-us-tariffs-says-un-trade-agency-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U7JY3PAT5PH5ATNCFRX742P2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:29:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对美国加征关税进行报复后，华尔街期货失守]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周五大幅下跌，预示着华尔街将遭受更多损失，因为在特朗普政府全面征收关税导致美国股市缩水2.4万亿美元的一天之后，中国采取了新的关税报复措施。【原文：U.S. stock futures fell sharply on Friday, signaling more losses on Wall Street, after China retaliated with fresh tariffs a day after the Trump administration's sweeping levies knocked off $2.4 trillion from U.S. equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-futures-lose-ground-after-china-retaliates-against-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76DS4WZQTRICTHQCBS56HHRUVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼集团高管称，石油巨头受困于欧佩克+增产，而非美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃尼公司（Eni）的高层管理人员弗朗切斯科-加泰伊（Francesco Gattei）周五表示，在欧佩克+国家（OPEC+）的八个成员国意外同意在五月增加石油产量之后，石油巨头们的日子不好过，而美国政府征收的关税对石油行业的影响不大。【原文：Oil majors are suffering after eight OPEC+ countries unexpectedly agreed to increase oil output in May, while tariffs imposed by U.S. administration had a muted effect on the sector, Eni's top executive Francesco Gattei said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-majors-suffering-opec-output-hike-not-us-tariffs-eni-exec-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWJ6ETAK3ZLSPPUC7KHX354K4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:21:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在全球贸易战中实施报复，对美国商品全面征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五宣布对美国商品征收 34% 的额外关税，这是与唐纳德-特朗普总统贸易战的最严重升级，加剧了人们对经济衰退的担忧，并引发了全球股市暴跌。【原文：China announced additional tariffs of 34% on U.S. goods on Friday, the most serious escalation in a trade war with President Donald Trump that has fed fears of a recession and triggered a global stock market rout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/europe-prepares-response-trump-tariffs-global-markets-plunge-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOKNK2JOLFOSXM2FBM4RBVGJGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将从 4 月 10 日起对所有美国商品加征 34% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国财政部周五表示，将从4月10日起对所有美国商品征收34%的额外关税，作为对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收全面关税的反制措施。【原文：China's finance ministry said on Friday it will impose additional tariffs of 34% on all U.S. goods from April 10 as a countermeasure to sweeping tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-impose-tariffs-34-all-us-goods-april-10-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PZJJBMRMRJFFEJYG4CBPUHNOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:14:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁期限临近，西班牙对委内瑞拉石油的进口量增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府设定的关键制裁期限的临近，西班牙 1 月和 2 月从委内瑞拉进口的原油量同比增长了约 59%。【原文：Spain's crude oil imports from Venezuela in January and February rose roughly 59% from a year earlier as a key sanctions deadline set by U.S. President Donald Trump's administration approaches.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/spains-imports-venezuelan-oil-rise-us-sanctions-deadline-approaches-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3L3B7YQGFKWHBVROOFBQZZ6W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税、经济不确定性助推首席执行官与激进分子达成更多和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要对中国征收关税，Yeti Holdings 的股价在 12 月和 3 月再次暴跌。【原文：Shares of Yeti Holdings tumbled in December and again in March when President Donald Trump threatened tariffs against China, where the company had some of its biggest factories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-economic-uncertainty-fuel-more-settlements-between-ceos-activists-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAGL4EE27JMFLKJT2HTXKIRVHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件称越南越捷航空公司将与波音公司签署飞机融资协议并加强合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部日程表，越南廉价航空公司 VietJet 将于下周在华盛顿与投资基金 KKR 的合作伙伴签署一份 2 亿美元的飞机融资协议，飞机制造商波音公司也将出席会议。【原文：Vietnamese budget airline VietJet is set to sign a $200 million aircraft finance deal with a partner of investment fund KKR at a meeting in Washington next week attended by planemaker Boeing, according to an internal schedule seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietnams-vietjet-sign-aircraft-finance-deal-boost-cooperation-with-boeing-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2D63VMBRZJI7HA2Y6KE3PG2GFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>