<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 17:04:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[上诉法院裁定亚马逊必须面对华盛顿特区的反垄断诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿特区的一家上诉法院周四恢复了该地区对亚马逊公司（Amazon.com Inc）的诉讼，称其合理地声称这家在线零售商的定价政策非法扼杀了竞争。【原文：An appeals court in Washington, D.C. revived the district's lawsuit against Amazon.com Inc on Thursday, saying it plausibly claimed the online retailer's pricing policies illegally stifle competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/amazon-must-face-dcs-antitrust-lawsuit-appeals-court-rules-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJVLLFMJYFNBVKT2GAXE7LKYOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：CME 和标准普尔探讨出售合资企业 OSTTRA]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，衍生品交易所 CME 集团和金融信息公司 S&amp;P Global 正在权衡出售合资企业 OSTTRA 的事宜。【原文：Derivatives exchange CME Group and financial information company S&amp;P Global are weighing a sale of joint venture OSTTRA, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/cme-sp-explore-sale-joint-venture-osttra-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGTLDOXUIVOVPG3XKSPMMW4DF4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:52:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓制定应急计划，最大限度减少加拿大铁路停运造成的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓矿业公司（Rio Tinto）周四告诉路透社记者，该公司预计工人与加拿大两大铁路网络管理层之间的劳资纠纷将影响其在加拿大多个地点接收原材料并向北美客户运输产品的能力。【原文：Rio Tinto expects the labor dispute between the workers and the management of Canada's two biggest rail networks will affect its ability to receive raw materials at several sites across Canada and ship products to customers in North America, the miner told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/rio-tinto-has-contingency-plans-minimize-impact-canada-rail-stoppage-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDU6WJ5JWFMJFBA2BIDEDCO4JQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:35:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工统计局因最新数据失误再次受到审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工统计局本应于周三公开发布的就业市场数据莫名其妙地被推迟，但在该局发布数据之前，这些数据仍然出现在了社交媒体平台上，美国劳工统计局因此再次受到审查。【原文：The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics is once again under scrutiny after closely watched job market data due for public release on Wednesday was inexplicably delayed but still found its way onto social media platforms before the agency posted it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-bureau-labor-statistics-under-scrutiny-again-latest-data-misstep-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGAQ2AVAO5PPZONLBO2F4TU7J4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司飞行员投票批准罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司飞行员工会周四表示，加航飞行员投票赞成授权罢工。【原文：Air Canada pilots voted in favor of authorizing a strike, the Air Line Pilots Association union said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/air-canada-pilots-vote-authorize-strike-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSNMQ5GIXRLT7G7YZONDHRE6DM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:22:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢公司由资深员工弗莱克斯接替首席执行官施奈德的职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司周四表示，将由服务多年的高管洛朗-弗莱克西（Laurent Freixe）接替首席执行官马克-施耐德（Mark Schneider），这是全球最大食品制造商的一次重大变动。【原文：Nestle is replacing Chief Executive Mark Schneider with long-serving executive Laurent Freixe, the company said on Thursday, a big change at the world's biggest foodmaker which has struggled with the cost of living crisis hitting customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nestle-names-laurent-freixe-new-ceo-mark-schneider-leaves-company-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MG2LLVULTZIQFIBEEX5IQ4WN3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:17:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果将更新欧盟浏览器选项，使更多应用程序可删除]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四表示，将改变欧盟地区用户选择浏览器选项的方式，增加一个专门用于更改默认应用程序的部分，并使更多应用程序可删除。【原文：Apple will change how users choose browser options in the European Union, add a dedicated section for changing default apps, and make more apps deletable, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-update-eu-browser-options-make-more-apps-deletable-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPXLMLESNZKXXCEEHEU33BKXJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期固定利率抵押贷款降至 2023 年 5 月以来最低水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国流行的 30 年期固定利率抵押贷款平均利率降至 2023 年 5 月以来的最低水平，但可能还需要进一步下降，住房市场的需求才会出现明显改善。【原文：The average rate on the popular U.S. 30-year fixed-rate mortgage ticked down this week to the lowest level since May 2023, but may need to fall further for the housing market to see significant improvement in demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-fixed-rate-mortgage-slips-lowest-level-since-may-2023-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QLXXFAVU5L63PV4LDRKXYJKGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:09:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，宝马在欧洲电动汽车销量首次超过特斯拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场研究公司 JATO Dynamics 的数据显示，宝马首次击败美国汽车制造商特斯拉，领跑欧洲电池电动汽车（BEV）市场。【原文：BMW led the European battery electric vehicle (BEV) market for the first time, beating U.S. automaker Tesla , according to market research firm JATO Dynamics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-overtakes-tesla-european-ev-sales-first-time-report-says-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIBVURMKVROYFEY4ZAUZK5JOSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 15:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大铁路网络关闭，马士基关注应急计划，仍接受预订]]></title><description><![CDATA[在加拿大两大货运铁路公司因劳资纠纷而关闭网络之后，马士基航运公司周四表示，该公司正在评估在加拿大的应急战略。【原文：Shipping company Maersk is evaluating contingency strategies in Canada, the company said on Thursday after the country's two main freight rail companies shut down their networks over a labour dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/maersk-eyes-contigency-plans-canada-rail-networks-close-still-takes-bookings-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33D4ATQEKZIAFBOSSFSGEXI664</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 15:50:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香奈儿收购瑞士小众制表商 MB&F 25% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国奢侈品牌香奈儿周四表示，香奈儿收购了瑞士高端制表商 MB&amp;F 公司 25% 的股份，该公司以奇特的手表设计而闻名，香奈儿补充说，这是香奈儿扩大制表业务战略的一部分。【原文：Chanel has bought a 25% stake in high-end Swiss watchmaker MB&amp;F, known for its quirky watch designs, the French luxury house said on Thursday, adding it was part of strategy to increase its presence in watch-making.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/chanel-buys-25-stake-niche-swiss-watchmaker-mbf-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OW2NTXRWXJP53MSRPVWILMZHMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迈克-林奇（Mike Lynch）是英国科技界的开拓者，他在美国被无罪释放后死于海上]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克-林奇（Mike Lynch），这位在豪华游艇沉没于西西里岛附近海域时丧生的科技大亨，用了十多年的时间创建了英国最大的软件公司，又用了几乎同样长的时间来对抗关于他夸大公司价值以确保数十亿英镑出售的指控。【原文：Mike Lynch, the tech tycoon who died when his luxury yacht sank off Sicily, spent more than a decade building Britain's biggest software company and almost as long again fighting charges he had inflated its value to secure a multi-billion-pound sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/obituary-mike-lynch-british-tech-trailblazer-who-died-sea-after-us-trial-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43EIDFNVJJONVLFQGKNK77TWDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储决策者认为就业市场是决定降息的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储决策者周四表示，随着通胀率从高位大幅回落，他们正在密切关注美国劳动力市场，以判断何时开始降息，其中一位决策者表示应该 "很快 "行动。【原文：Federal Reserve policymakers on Thursday said that with inflation well down from its highs they are paying close attention to the U.S. labor market to gauge when to begin reducing interest rates, with one saying they should move "soon."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-policymakers-see-job-market-key-rate-cut-decision-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UBGURK5ZJOCRPYXVVJ2I5HQ7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:10:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月成屋销售增幅高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份成屋销售增幅超过预期，扭转了连续四个月下降的趋势，因为供应量的增加和抵押贷款利率的下降为未来几个月的活动反弹带来了希望。【原文：U.S. existing home sales rose more than expected in July, reversing four consecutive monthly declines, as improving supply and declining mortgage rates offered hope that activity could rebound in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-existing-home-sales-rise-more-than-expected-july-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2WS5PRQCBIYHGZTA4M2UIWAFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[申银万国加强供应商审计，披露童工案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[快速时尚零售商希恩（Shein）在其 2023 年可持续发展报告中称，去年在其供应商中发现了两起童工案例，该公司在计划上市前加强了对中国制造商的审计，以平息对其低成本商业模式的批评。【原文：Fast fashion retailer Shein found two cases of child labour at its suppliers last year, it said in its 2023 sustainability report, as it stepped up audits of manufacturers in China to assuage criticisms of its low-cost business model ahead of a planned flotation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shein-reveals-child-labour-cases-it-steps-up-supplier-audits-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJ6TTGDJSZNZ5MSXOFZKXBHYB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商业活动走低，定价能力进一步减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 8 月份的商业活动降至 4 个月来的最低点，企业继续努力将更高的价格转嫁给消费者，这使得通胀在未来几个月内保持下降趋势的可能性增大。【原文：U.S. business activity fell to a 4-month low in August and firms continued to struggle to pass on higher prices to consumers, bolstering the likelihood that inflation will stay on a downward trend over the coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-activity-edges-lower-pricing-power-ebbs-further-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZLEMPRLMNO4XFHZ2O5PYMSLCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 13:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席哈克准备有条不紊地启动降息进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联邦储备银行行长帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）周四表示，只要数据表现符合他的预期，他就同意 9 月份降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia President Patrick Harker said Thursday he was on board with a September rate cut as long as the data performs as he expects it to.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-harker-is-ready-start-methodical-course-rate-cuts-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFOWKSP3RFOL3KXEZEYLQDFIZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 13:49:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上海交割规则变化导致卖方卖空]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟知内情的消息人士称，上海期货交易所（ShFE）的电池金属铅潜在卖家被迫寻找海外供应，或在规格发生变化后将他们希望平仓的远期合约展期。【原文：Would-be sellers of battery metal lead on the Shanghai Futures Exchange (ShFE) have been forced to search for overseas supplies or roll forward contracts they hoped to close following a change in specifications, four sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/lead-sellers-caught-short-by-shanghai-delivery-rule-change-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V62VMXT77BOY7PHYWOZEL4JF4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 13:24:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯：很快将适宜降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联储主席苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周四表示，美联储很快将适宜开始降息周期，这表明她可能支持美国央行在下个月的政策会议上降息。【原文：It will soon be appropriate for the Federal Reserve to begin a rate-cutting cycle, Boston Fed President Susan Collins said on Thursday, signaling her likely support for a rate cut at the U.S. central bank's policy meeting next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-collins-will-soon-be-appropriate-cut-interest-rates-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24NW6SXAXZO7BPLO7YXDCA556M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 13:11:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒂姆-德雷珀领投加密货币初创公司 Ark Labs 250 万美元融资轮]]></title><description><![CDATA[方舟实验室（Ark Labs）是一家成立三个月的初创公司，致力于开发加快比特币交易速度并降低成本的解决方案，该公司已在一轮种子轮融资中筹集到 250 万美元，本轮融资由亿万富翁投资者蒂姆-德雷珀（Tim Draper）领投。【原文：Ark Labs, a three-month old startup developing solutions to speed up bitcoin transactions and lower costs, has raised $2.5 million in a pre-seed funding round led by billionaire investor Tim Draper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tim-draper-leads-25-mln-funding-round-crypto-startup-ark-labs-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5EJVLKTORLAVJAQ5CU32VFJDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 13:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国企业高管大选言论增多凸显政策不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于候选人卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）和唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）之间更广泛的政策分歧引发了有关税收、关税和定价权的问题，美国公司高管们对即将到来的总统大选的讨论比四年前要多得多。【原文：U.S. company executives are talking much more about the upcoming presidential election than they did four years ago as a wider policy rift between candidates Kamala Harris and Donald Trump raises questions around taxes, tariffs and pricing power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/rise-election-talk-us-execs-highlights-policy-uncertainty-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJBADIRTDFKTTO4CTG2S5YAXVQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最近一周申请失业救济人数上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近一周，新申请失业救济金的美国人数有所增加，但这一水平仍表明劳动力市场逐步降温的趋势没有改变。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits rose in the latest week, but the level still suggested a gradual cooling of the labor market remains intact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-jobless-claims-rise-latest-week-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYWN5SHYZVPKDADERCQSNQOUKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 12:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德表示对 9 月降息持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储银行行长杰夫-施密德（Jeff Schmid）是美国央行中较为鹰派的决策者之一，他在周四表示，他正在仔细研究失业率上升背后的动态，并将根据数据来决定是否支持下个月降息。【原文：Kansas City Fed Bank President Jeff Schmid, one of the U.S. central bank's more hawkish policymakers, said on Thursday he was taking a closer look at the dynamics behind the rise in the unemployment rate and would let data guide him on whether to support a rate cut next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-schmid-signals-open-mind-september-rate-cut-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NH3S4AH4JNPTGV642BAZDTYMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 11:59:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据共同社报道，软银正在洽谈对夏普的投资，但可行性尚不明确]]></title><description><![CDATA[据共同社周四报道，日本电信公司软银公司（SoftBank Corp）正在洽谈向电子产品制造商夏普公司（Sharp Corp）投资约1000亿日元（约合6.84亿美元），但该交易的可行性仍不明确。【原文：Japanese telecom company SoftBank Corp is in talks to invest about 100 billion yen ($684 million) in electronics maker Sharp Corp , but the feasibility of the deal remains unclear, Kyodo news agency reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/softbank-talks-invest-sharp-feasibility-unclear-kyodo-reports-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64KMCAWELBMP5OKSAIZHUFCSUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 11:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行决策者将 9 月作为降息重点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）7月17-18日会议的记录显示，该行决策者在上个月开会时并不急于降息，他们认为9月份是审查是否回调政策的下一个最佳时机。【原文：European Central Bank policymaker were in no rush to cut interest rates when they met last month and saw September as the next best opportunity to review whether to dial back policy, the accounts of their July 17-18 meeting showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ecb-policymakers-put-september-into-rate-cut-focus-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJRMTN6MDVJAPMW7LZTGHTXMNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 11:45:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金下跌抵消了美国降息的希望，多伦多证券交易所（TSX）期货走势低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，与加拿大主要股票指数挂钩的期货市场表现平淡，因为金价下跌抵消了投资者对美国 9 月份降息的乐观预期。【原文：Futures linked to Canada's main stock index were muted on Thursday as losses in gold prices countered investor optimism around U.S. rate-cut hopes in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tsx-futures-muted-losses-gold-offset-us-rate-cut-hopes-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAMBNURZSJMAJFMWXEBZ7MKSUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 11:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton 预测 2025 年订购量低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，Peloton Interactive 预测 2025 年的订户数将低于分析师的预期，预计其健身器材需求疲软，订户数增长乏力，因为持续的通胀抑制了可自由支配的支出。【原文：Peloton Interactive forecast 2025 subscriptions below analysts' estimates on Thursday, anticipating weak demand for its exercise equipment and sluggish subscriber additions as sticky inflation keeps discretionary spending in check.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/peloton-forecasts-2025-subscriptions-below-estimates-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ABHRZ5YNBISNC5LPHP6RHUTBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 11:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险公司 Aegon 因美国死亡率上升损失 4 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰保险公司 Aegon 周四表示，将在 2024 年上半年计提约 4 亿美元的费用，以反映其主要美国市场与死亡相关的保险索赔增加。【原文：Dutch insurer Aegon booked a charge of around $400 million in the first half of 2024 to reflect higher death-related insurance claims in its key U.S. market, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/insurer-aegon-books-400-mln-hit-higher-us-mortality-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYIUDYV4U5PZ5EU4XUMD6DM46E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 11:10:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年美国新 ETF 的推出速度创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[晨星直接公司（Morningstar Direct）的数据显示，2024 年美国市场上新发行的交易所交易基金数量有望再创新高，平均每月将有 50 只交易所交易基金首次亮相。【原文：The number of new exchange-traded funds hitting the U.S. market is on track to set another record in 2024, according to data from Morningstar Direct, with an average of 50 ETFs making their debut monthly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/new-us-etfs-being-launched-record-pace-2024-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EMQ2SJAWZOVBL4ASR54UBTCLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 11:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛与汉堡王合作为会员提供折扣优惠]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛周四表示，它已与 Restaurant Brands 旗下的汉堡王公司合作，为其会员客户提供打折餐饮优惠，这家零售巨头希望提高其服务的吸引力，以便更好地与亚马逊的 Prime 展开竞争。【原文：Walmart said on Thursday it has partnered with Restaurant Brands' Burger King to offer discounted meal benefits to its membership customers as the retail giant looks to make its services more attractive to compete better with Amazon's Prime.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-partners-with-burger-king-offer-discounted-deals-members-2024-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBZ4O5WKMJLQZG4VQ7NK4FJF7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 10:59:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>