<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:04:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:04:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Azul 公司批准利用尼勒曼投资增资]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Azul 航空公司周四晚些时候表示，作为庭外重组的一部分，该公司董事会已批准增资，让出租人以股权代替近 5.5 亿美元的债务。【原文：Brazilian airline Azul's board of directors has approved a capital increase as part of an out-of-court restructuring that gave lessors equity in lieu of nearly $550 million in obligations, the company said late on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-azul-approves-capital-increase-with-neeleman-investment-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMEL4I5ENNNWFBJ5N3I7JQ5HMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:56:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税、联邦政府削减开支抑制美国商业活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对进口商品征收关税和联邦政府大幅削减开支的担忧日益加剧，2 月份美国商业活动几乎停滞，唐纳德-特朗普总统赢得大选后取得的所有收益都被抹去。【原文：U.S. business activity nearly stalled in February amid mounting fears over tariffs on imports and deep cuts in federal government spending, erasing all the gains notched in the aftermath of President Donald Trump's election victory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tariffs-federal-government-spending-cuts-restrain-us-business-activity-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7XFQ5LRHZMO7K6SKOT7U7EYVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 在英国就安全气囊和安全带卡特尔提起的 8.07 亿美元诉讼被驳回]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，伦敦一家法庭驳回了 Stellantis 公司对两家安全设备制造商提出的 7.71 亿欧元（8.0762 亿美元）的诉讼。【原文：Stellantis' 771 million euro ($807.62 million) lawsuit against two safety equipment makers was dismissed by a London tribunal on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-807-million-uk-lawsuit-over-airbag-seatbelt-cartels-dismissed-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGQFY3OGL5J7TPASHH75JEFKG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称美国向伊拉克施压要求恢复库尔德石油出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[八位直接了解此事的消息人士告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府正在向伊拉克施加压力，要求伊拉克允许库尔德人重新开始石油出口，否则将与伊朗一起面临制裁。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is piling pressure on Iraq to allow Kurdish oil exports to restart or face sanctions alongside Iran, eight sources with direct knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-piles-pressure-iraq-resume-kurdish-oil-exports-sources-say-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EPQ5F6JEMZKG5KXQEQZRXFOK7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 称诺和诺德减肥药短缺问题已解决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局网站周五显示，丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司广受欢迎的减肥药和糖尿病药物Wegovy和Ozempic的短缺问题已经解决。【原文：A shortage of Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk's popular weight-loss and diabetes drugs, Wegovy and Ozempic, has been resolved, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's website showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-says-shortage-novos-weight-loss-drug-resolved-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXMOFFJOOFJCRDZSFHIREPBA7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，作为乌克兰战争解决方案的一部分，俄罗斯可能让出 3,000 亿美元的冻结资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士告诉路透社，俄罗斯可能同意将冻结在欧洲的 3,000 亿美元主权资产用于乌克兰重建，但将坚持把部分资金用于莫斯科军队控制的乌克兰五分之一领土。【原文：Russia could agree to using $300 billion of sovereign assets frozen in Europe for reconstruction in Ukraine but will insist that part of the money is spent on the one-fifth of the country that Moscow's forces control, three sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-could-concede-300-bln-frozen-assets-part-ukraine-war-settlement-sources-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZB4D6F27ZVJQXD7W6VMC52GJ3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，人工智能初创公司 Genspark 融资 1 亿美元，欲与谷歌竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，搜索初创公司 Genspark 在 A 轮融资中筹集了 1 亿美元，估值达 5.3 亿美元。【原文：Search startup Genspark has raised $100 million in a series A funding round, valuing the startup at $530 million, according to a source familiar with the matter, as the race to use artificial intelligence to disrupt Google’s stranglehold on the search engine market heats up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-startup-genspark-raises-100-million-compete-with-google-source-says-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDQOZ6WZVBMJRCMMKQGM4RV4IM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通分析师认为阿美今年不会派发特别股息]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）周五在一份研究报告中表示，沙特阿美石油公司（Saudi Aramco）预计今年将不派发与业绩挂钩的股息，而在此之前的 2024 年现金周期将更加平衡。【原文：Saudi Aramco is forecast to have no performance-linked dividend this year after a more balanced 2024 cash cycle following earlier bumper results that backed the special payout, JPMorgan said in a research note on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/jpmorgan-analysts-see-no-special-aramco-dividend-this-year-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YFGG3FJM5L4LC6ES7GNATA3DY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:52:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holcim 北美业务分拆后将更名为 Amrize]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士 Holcim 公司周五表示，已将其北美建材公司命名为 Amrize，并计划于今年上市。【原文：Holcim has given the name Amrize to its North American building materials company, which it plans to list this year, the Swiss firm said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/holcims-north-american-business-be-called-amrize-after-spin-off-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJYMXYU55VMX7DSHXC32HEF5JA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:22:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[当地新闻报道称，Equinor 计划出售阿根廷陆上资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mas Energia》在线刊物援引未具名消息人士的话报道，挪威石油天然气公司埃奎诺（Equinor）正寻求出售其在阿根廷瓦卡穆埃尔塔地区的陆上资产。【原文：Norwegian oil and gas firm Equinor is looking to sell its onshore assets in Argentina's Vaca Muerta region, the Mas Energia online publication reported, citing unnamed sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/equinor-plans-sale-onshore-assets-argentina-local-news-report-says-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IK4BARC5AFIV7CT7ZWEZSQQ4KA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:18:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易所称美国证券监管机构将撤销对 Coinbase 的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase 周五表示，美国证券监管机构计划撤回对该加密货币交易所的诉讼，从而结束了这场长达数年、一度被认为对该交易平台乃至整个行业都具有决定性意义的诉讼。【原文：Coinbase said on Friday the U.S. securities regulator planned to withdraw its lawsuit against the crypto exchange, ending a contentious years-long legal battle once considered existential for the trading platform and the broader sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-securities-regulator-drop-lawsuit-against-coinbase-exchange-says-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZDQMCYRAJI7LLU75CZIJH4S5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:09:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蓝鸟生物将在资金紧张的情况下被凯雷和 SK Capital 私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[基因疗法生产商蓝鸟生物周五表示，将被凯雷和 SK Capital Partners 私有化，从而结束了该公司因资金严重短缺而在公开市场上挣扎的动荡历程。【原文：Gene therapy maker Bluebird bio said on Friday it would be taken private by Carlyle and SK Capital Partners, ending its tumultuous journey in the public markets as it struggled with a severe cash crunch.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bluebird-bio-be-taken-private-by-carlyle-sk-capital-amid-cash-crunch-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKZX5RYQTFLYBGFIKS4NI6W2OA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[支出放缓使 BNPL 的扩张成为焦点，导致布洛克公司股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于支出增长放缓加剧了投资者的担忧，支付公司布洛克的股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌了8%，这也让人们开始关注其在2025年通过 "先买后付 "贷款来推动利润增长的赌注。【原文：Payments firm Block's shares fell 8% in premarket trading on Friday as a slowdown in spending growth fueled investor concerns, turning the spotlight to its bet on buy-now, pay-later lending to drive profits in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/block-shares-drop-spending-slowdown-puts-bnpl-expansion-focus-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2CXSSW56FI6LP5ICMCBBYEBOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:39:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀缓解、盈利乐观，美国股票基金吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 2 月 19 日的七天里，美国股票基金三周来首次吸引资金流入，这主要是受到通胀担忧缓解和第四季度企业盈利强劲提振风险偏好的影响。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted inflows for the first time in three weeks in the seven days to February 19, buoyed by easing inflation concerns and strong fourth-quarter corporate earnings that boosted risk appetite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-attract-inflows-inflation-relief-earnings-optimism-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Y3D4756GBJF5JM2AID7SMF4NE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡宣布退税和 37 亿美元计划提振股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡周五宣布了一系列振兴其股票市场的措施，包括对首次上市实行 20% 的退税，以及一项 50 亿新元（37.4 亿美元）的计划，重点投资于国内股票。【原文：Singapore announced on Friday a set of measures to rejuvenate its equities market, including a 20% tax rebate for primary listings and a S$5 billion ($3.74 billion) program that focuses on investing in domestic stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/singapore-announces-tax-rebates-37-billion-program-boost-stock-market-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSJXH6SQHNOOFJ2RPJBYJE636I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:27:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普停止拨款后，液化空气集团只能继续建设美国六个氢气中心中的两个]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国液化空气公司（Air Liquide）周五表示，在唐纳德-特朗普总统冻结清洁能源项目资金后，他们之前为美国能源部（DoE）授予的六个氢气项目中只有两个可能会继续推进。【原文：France's Air Liquide said on Friday that only two out of their six previously awarded hydrogen projects for the U.S. Department of Energy (DoE) might move forward after President Donald Trump froze funding on clean energy projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/air-liquide-could-pursue-just-two-out-six-us-hydrogen-hubs-after-trump-halts-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK7VI3MMJZNARBT5ZOGARYBZDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，司法部对 UnitedHealth 的医疗保险收费行为展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，美国司法部近几个月来对 UnitedHealth 的医疗保险收费行为展开了调查。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department has launched an investigation into UnitedHealth's Medicare billing practices in recent months, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/doj-investigates-medicare-billing-practices-unitedhealth-wsj-reports-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYVWTLGRZBMLBOMC2A37ND5PXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普为何将增值税卷入贸易对峙？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普说，美国与世界其他国家近万亿美元的贸易逆差主要归咎于增值税。170多个征收增值税的国家--包括美国在欧洲的主要贸易伙伴--坚称增值税没有影响。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump says value-added taxes carry a lot of blame for America's near trillion dollar trade deficit with the rest of the world. The 170-plus countries who charge VAT - including top U.S. trade partners in Europe - insist they have no impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/why-trump-has-thrown-vat-into-trade-stand-off-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHCDCOCR4BKJFBE7FHUWODXWNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:54:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业机构称印度制药商即使征收关税也能保持在美国的主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家由政府支持的贸易机构表示，即使美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收高额关税，印度制药公司仍能保持其在美国销售仿制药的主导市场份额，因为它们 "极具竞争力"。【原文：Indian pharmaceutical companies will be able to retain their dominant market share in the U.S. in selling generic drugs even if President Donald Trump imposes high tariffs because they are "highly competitive", a government-backed trade body said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/indian-drugmakers-can-retain-us-dominance-even-with-tariffs-says-industry-body-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDMJNPC6WZPQDNPTRECKO47GDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：沃尔玛夹击华尔街，欧元关注德国投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BONM7LBTKRPMDFMUQH4NHRLZA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:09:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 英伟达将提供人工智能交易实况检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）下周的利润报告可能会引导美国股市的走向，因为投资者希望确认，在上个月由中国初创公司 DeepSeek 引发的恐慌性抛售之后，两年来推动股市的人工智能驱动型投资趋势是否完好无损。【原文：Nvidia's profit report next week could steer the U.S. stock market's course, as investors seek confirmation that the AI-driven investment trend, which has powered equities for two years, is intact after last month's panic-selling triggered by the Chinese startup DeepSeek.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-nvidia-offer-ai-trades-reality-check-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GMFRLIHUNO6FCV6GFPWRPXL3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，富士康已要求本田建立合作伙伴关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周五报道，台湾富士康已提议与日本本田汽车建立合作伙伴关系，旨在建立一个包括竞争对手日产汽车和三菱汽车在内的合作框架。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn has proposed forming a partnership with Japan's Honda Motor , aiming to create a tie-up framework that also includes rival carmakers Nissan Motor and Mitsubishi Motors , the Nikkei newspaper reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/foxconn-has-asked-honda-form-partnership-nikkei-reports-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDTKACWHDBJL5NMLURUZXN5O6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:54:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[周四下跌后期货持平，市场等待美联储和关税线索]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者对唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税威胁和美联储的利率前景感到担忧，美国股指期货在上一交易日下跌后，周五基本持平。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were largely flat on Friday after declining in the previous session when investors fretted over President Donald Trump's tariff threats and the Federal Reserve's interest rate outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-flat-after-thursdays-fall-markets-await-fed-tariff-cues-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UTCAFLB3VJ57KNFBU3HRBHTZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:43:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国科技股因盈利惊喜和基金轮动创下五年来最佳赢利纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[在香港上市的中国科技股周五走高，创下自2020年以来的最佳单周连胜纪录，原因是盈利惊喜和对人工智能行业的乐观情绪吸引了全球投资者将资金轮流投入该行业。【原文：Chinese tech stocks listed in Hong Kong advanced on Friday for their best weekly winning streak since 2020, as earnings surprises and optimism about the artificial intelligence sector drew global investors rotating funds into the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-tech-stocks-cap-best-winning-run-five-years-earnings-surprises-fund-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWX2FKOY2BIAVJTQ3P4W5M42AI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院通过共和党边境安全法案，特朗普未减税]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管特朗普倾向于众议院版本的法案，其中包括数万亿美元的减税措施，但美国参议院还是在周五凌晨通过了一项共和党法案，以推动唐纳德-特朗普总统的移民、能源和国防政策。【原文：The U.S. Senate passed a Republican bill promoting President Donald Trump's immigration, energy and defense policies in the early hours of Friday morning, despite Trump's preference for a House of Representatives version of the bill that would include trillions of dollars in tax cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-passes-republican-border-security-bill-without-trump-tax-cuts-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MZ7BISKXFNGHJM4YB4JFSJBPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特因安全带隐患在美国召回超过 24 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，福特汽车公司将在美国召回240,510辆存在安全带隐患的汽车。【原文：Ford Motor is recalling 240,510 vehicles in the U.S. over potential seat belt issues, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-over-240000-vehicles-us-over-potential-seat-belt-issues-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSEAYTCBCBLDJCKJHI3IK7VO4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称 Rivian 将召回超过 17,000 辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周五表示，Rivian Automotive 公司因前大灯问题在美国召回 17,260 辆汽车，该问题可能会降低能见度并增加撞车风险。【原文：Rivian Automotive is recalling 17,260 vehicles in the United States due to a headlight issue that can reduce visibility and increase the risk of a crash, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-recall-over-17000-us-vehicles-nhtsa-says-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEZWCYDXDJOXTCANG5XANPDT34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧股上涨、美国通胀降温导致全球股票基金流入增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球股票基金继续保持强劲的资金流入，其中大部分流入欧洲股票基金，欧洲股票基金创下历史新高，原因是乌克兰有望实现和平，以及预期军费开支增加导致国防部门资金激增。【原文：Global equity funds continued to see robust inflows, with the majority directed to European equity funds, which hit record highs fueled by hopes for peace in Ukraine and a surge in the defense sector due to anticipated increases in military spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJCW5DRIMBOZRM7XOLO4VXKKBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:18:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉因动力转向问题在美国召回 38 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周五表示，由于动力转向辅助系统故障，该公司将在美国召回近38万辆汽车，该故障可能会增加转向力度，尤其是在低速行驶时，从而增加撞车风险。【原文：Tesla said on Friday it was recalling nearly 380,000 vehicles in the United States due to a power steering assist failure that could increase steering effort, particularly at low speeds, raising the risk of a crash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-recalls-380000-vehicles-us-over-power-steering-issue-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRF6V2FVJNLWVHELONSQ7E4NMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯坦查特承诺减少与石油和天然气债券相关的排放]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周五承诺减少其为石油和天然气公司出售的债券的相关排放，并将继续推进其净零排放战略，这与其他正在重新评估其气候计划的贷款机构形成了鲜明对比。【原文：Standard Chartered on Friday pledged to cut the emissions linked to the bonds it sells for oil and gas companies and will press ahead with its net-zero strategy, in contrast with other lenders who are reassessing their climate plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/stanchart-pledges-cut-emissions-linked-oil-gas-bonds-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDFTINPENRLZDDVBKS3HYKZ3RQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>