<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:33:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:33:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府寻求取消律师事务所案法官的资格]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周五要求负责监督针对律师事务所帕金斯-科伊（Perkins Coie）的特朗普行政命令挑战案的联邦法官让位，称她的公正性 "可能会受到合理质疑"。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration on Friday asked the federal judge overseeing a challenge to Trump's executive order targeting law firm Perkins Coie to step aside from the case, saying her impartiality "might reasonably be questioned."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-seeks-disqualify-judge-law-firm-case-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26X3KHEDFZMN7GOXCP3UHRLVZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普计划整顿监管，美国证券交易委员会举行加密货币工作组圆桌会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会加密货币工作组周五与专家们举行了首次公开会议，重点讨论了在特朗普政府寻求全面修订加密货币法规之际，证券法可能如何适用于数字资产。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's crypto task force held its first public meeting with experts on Friday, focusing on how securities laws might apply to digital assets as the Trump administration looks to overhaul cryptocurrency regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-holds-crypto-task-force-roundtable-trump-plans-regulatory-revamp-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGROTJPMKJKJJCLMUPYTZ2YHPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着数百人接受特朗普的收购提议，美国证券交易委员会将出现人员外流现象]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位熟知内情的人士告诉路透社，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统和埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）努力重塑美国政府的背景下，数百名员工已同意接受辞职，华尔街的最高监管机构正面临关键部门人员外流的问题。【原文：Wall Street's top regulator is facing an exodus of staff across key departments as hundreds of employees have agreed to take resignation offers amid President Donald Trump and Elon Musk's efforts to remake the U.S. government, five people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-see-exodus-hundreds-take-trumps-buyout-offers-sources-say-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZ5CKTJ4AVPSNJ2ZW4OMML4HJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:57:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[致命碰撞事故发生后，美国议员敦促削减华盛顿地区的军事训练航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[在今年 1 月一架美国航空公司支线飞机与一架美国陆军直升机在空中相撞造成 67 人死亡之后，十名美国众议院民主党议员周五敦促五角大楼减少在华盛顿特区的军事训练飞行。【原文：Ten U.S. House of Representatives Democratic lawmakers on Friday urged the Pentagon to reduce military training flights in the Washington, D.C., area after a January midair collision between an American Airlines regional jet and a U.S. Army helicopter killed 67 people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-lawmakers-urge-cut-washington-area-military-training-flights-after-fatal-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWROOJEXRNM43GTLUSQFSFVWZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:53:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司创始人在美国承认操纵市场计划罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家加密货币金融服务公司的创始人周五承认了美国对他的指控，即他参与了一个大范围的计划，代表客户公司操纵数字代币市场。【原文：The founder of a cryptocurrency financial services firm pleaded guilty on Friday to U.S. charges that he participated in a wide-ranging scheme to manipulate the market for digital tokens on behalf of client companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cryptocurrency-firm-founder-pleads-guilty-us-market-manipulation-scheme-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YY7YBEHK75LWZODWEIYLAQGGFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学的研究因特朗普削减经费而立即受到冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学本月突然被关闭了数百万美元的联邦拨款，这已经扰乱了该校的医学和科学研究，因为该校将在周五的最后期限前屈服于政府的要求，对如何处理校园内的异议进行全面改革。【原文：The sudden shutdown of millions of dollars in federal funding to Columbia University this month is already disrupting medical and scientific research at the school as it confronts a Friday deadline to bow to government demands for sweeping changes in how it deals with dissent on campus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/columbia-research-takes-immediate-hit-trump-funding-cuts-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXHXOSZFBFPU7IA3IZMSM4AGSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:45:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与保罗-韦斯律师事务所的交易引发律师界恐慌]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街强大的律师事务所保罗-魏斯（Paul Weiss）周五因与白宫达成交易以逃避危及该事务所业务的行政命令而遭到猛烈抨击，尽管一些律师表示该事务所几乎没有其他选择。【原文：Powerful Wall Street law firm Paul Weiss faced heavy criticism on Friday over a deal it struck with the White House to escape an executive order imperiling the firm's business, even as some lawyers said the firm faced few other options.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trumps-deal-with-law-firm-paul-weiss-sparks-alarm-among-lawyers-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWT4IK5GLRJV7FK6EANLWJB4RI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国发布变性人禁军令指南，寻求取消法院命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防部周五发布了关于如何执行唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统关于军队中变性人禁令的新指南，并要求联邦法官取消她最近下达的阻止该禁令的命令。【原文：The U.S. Department of Defense on Friday released new guidance on how it will enforce President Donald Trump's ban on transgender people in the military, and asked a federal judge to lift her recent order blocking the ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-releases-guidance-transgender-military-ban-seeks-lift-court-order-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUTR2W3V7ZIYRGHMOXJPDUQTFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部采取行动保护特朗普免受 1 月 6 日诉讼的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部已采取行动，保护唐纳德-特朗普总统免受警方和民主党议员的民事诉讼，这些诉讼要求特朗普总统对其支持者于 2021 年 1 月 6 日袭击美国国会大厦期间发生的暴力事件负责。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department has moved to shield President Donald Trump from civil lawsuits by police and Democratic lawmakers seeking to hold him responsible for violence during the January 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol by his supporters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-justice-department-moves-protect-trump-january-6-lawsuits-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSJEQONPBBN3HJNSMJ47UEA35A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院驳回特朗普切断教师备课补助资金的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[在联邦上诉法院周五拒绝允许唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府取消对八个民主党领导的州的教师准备项目的拨款后，美国教育部必须继续为这些项目提供资金支持。【原文：The U.S. Department of Education must continue funding grants supporting teacher preparation programs in eight Democratic-led states after a federal appeals court on Friday declined to allow President Donald Trump's administration to cancel them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-appeals-court-rejects-trump-bid-cut-off-teacher-preparation-grant-funding-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDUIL3EFKNPFXCGPKDBBZL2NQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院驳回特朗普切断教师备课补助资金的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[在联邦上诉法院周五拒绝允许唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府取消对八个民主党领导的州的教师准备项目的拨款后，美国教育部必须继续为这些项目提供资金支持。【原文：The U.S. Department of Education must continue funding grants supporting teacher preparation programs in eight Democratic-led states after a federal appeals court on Friday declined to allow President Donald Trump's administration to cancel them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-appeals-court-rejects-trump-bid-cut-off-teacher-preparation-grant-funding-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDUIL3EFKNPFXCGPKDBBZL2NQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称小企业管理局将处理联邦学生贷款组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他的政府将把联邦政府学生贷款组合的责任从教育部移交给小企业管理局。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday said his administration is will transfer responsibility for the federal government's student loan portfolio from the Department of Education to the Small Business Administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-small-business-administration-will-handle-federal-student-loan-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IA2KOGHXVRO4ZK65BJTLMFA4OY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官将权衡延长对特朗普政府递解出境的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法官曾根据 1798 年的一项法律暂时阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府驱逐被指控的委内瑞拉帮派成员，他将于周五就是否维持该禁令举行听证会，同时还将考虑官员们是否违反了该命令。【原文：The U.S. judge who temporarily blocked President Donald Trump's administration from deporting alleged Venezuelan gang members under a 1798 law will hold a hearing on Friday over whether to maintain the ban while also considering whether officials violated the order.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-weigh-extending-block-trump-administrations-deportations-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYGXPADCBJIWZN3FVEBRIDCQ7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克呼吁起诉向《纽约时报》泄密的五角大楼工作人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）称，在《纽约时报》报道这位亿万富翁将听取美国军方对任何可能与中国爆发的战争的计划简报后，与该报记者交谈的五角大楼工作人员应受到起诉。【原文：Elon Musk said Pentagon staff who spoke to reporters at the New York Times should be prosecuted, after the newspaper reported the billionaire was due to be briefed about the U.S. military's plan for any war that might break out with China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/elon-musk-calls-prosecutions-pentagon-staff-who-leaked-new-york-times-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUYNWSFOYVO6NE74SBU6VKNH64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:45:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克抵达五角大楼听取简报]]></title><description><![CDATA[马斯克乘坐车队抵达，并迅速上楼与国防部长皮特-黑格塞斯会面。【原文：Musk arrived in a motorcade and quickly moved upstairs to meet Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/elon-musk-arrives-pentagon-briefings-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUMINLDJFZNARNJUJMHHOEZZHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鉴于经济不确定性，美联储官员支持谨慎的政策方针]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，鉴于经济面临诸多不确定性，美国央行的货币政策正处于正确的位置，并指出目前并不急于对利率做出任何调整。【原文：New York Federal Reserve President John Williams said on Friday the U.S. central bank's monetary policy is in the right place given the myriad uncertainties facing the economy, noting that there's no urgency to make any changes to interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-williams-says-monetary-policy-right-place-amid-notable-uncertainty-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZGIC6WQR5J2PKYGLCLS3MBKFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令，指示各机构允许官员查阅记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五签署了一项行政命令，指示政府机构负责人允许联邦官员访问非机密的机构记录、数据和系统，以制止浪费和欺诈行为。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday signed an executive order directing the heads of government agencies to grant federal officials access to unclassified agency records, data and systems to stop waste and fraud, the White House said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-signs-order-directing-agencies-grant-officials-access-records-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3O3QIG3SY5NELFHPCVMAYGTKMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党参议员称，特朗普政府逮捕哈利勒时滥用了移民法]]></title><description><![CDATA[由八名民主党参议员组成的小组周五指责特朗普政府滥用美国移民法，逮捕哥伦比亚大学学生马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil），因为他参加了支持巴勒斯坦的抗议活动。【原文：A group of eight Democratic Senators on Friday accused the Trump administration of abusing the country's immigration laws in arresting Columbia University student Mahmoud Khalil over his participation in pro-Palestinian protests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-abused-immigration-laws-with-khalils-arrest-democratic-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3N44KHDKJ5LORPSM5H5K3WYVL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道联邦调查局缩减国内恐怖主义调查的人员编制和追踪范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的消息人士透露，联邦调查局已经削减了一个专注于国内恐怖主义的办公室的人员编制，并取消了一个用于追踪此类调查的工具，这一转变可能会削弱执法部门打击白人至上主义者和反政府极端分子的能力。【原文：The FBI has cut staffing in an office focused on domestic terrorism and has scrapped a tool used to track such investigations, in a shift that could undermine law enforcement’s ability to counter white supremacists and anti-government extremists, according to sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fbi-scales-back-staffing-tracking-domestic-terrorism-probes-sources-say-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VEU7H7Y6ZIPNB53PYSB6LLDRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:11:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普横行国会，选民对民主党的反应感到沮丧]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党选民希瑟-奥格登（Heather Ogden）对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统攻击联邦官僚机构的行为感到愤怒，她希望自己的政党能表现出更多的战斗力。【原文：Democratic voter Heather Ogden is furious at President Donald Trump's assault on the federal bureaucracy - and she wishes her party would show more fight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/voters-frustrated-with-democrats-response-trump-runs-roughshod-over-congress-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRWZJ7MY6VMCBIFZ5NHRQZCSRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普以大刀阔斧的行动考验美国宪法秩序]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）重返白宫后大刀阔斧地行使权力，这是对 18 世纪建立的美国宪法制衡体系的考验，因为总统几乎没有遇到国会的抵制，与联邦司法机构的紧张关系也在升级。【原文：Donald Trump's sweeping assertion of power since returning to the White House is testing the U.S. constitutional system of checks and balances established in the 18th century as the president faces scant resistance from Congress and tensions with the federal judiciary escalate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/with-sweeping-actions-trump-tests-us-constitutional-order-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTSD6I6YXJLXPFVXD6PZRZ3GME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫审查联邦机构第二轮大规模裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，白宫官员正在审查联邦机构的裁员计划，预计此举将导致在未来几周内大规模解雇数千名政府工作人员。【原文：White House officials are reviewing federal agencies' downsizing plans, a move expected to result in the mass firing of thousands of government workers within the coming weeks, two sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-begins-review-federal-agency-plans-second-round-mass-layoffs-sources-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXCE2XQOCFOJNPNHWUTYL6YZA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普国家税务总局高管声称国税局技术预算可节省 15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[受特朗普政府委托负责审查美国国内税收署技术现代化项目的科技初创企业高管周四表示，他已经取消了税务机构预算中价值约 15 亿美元的合同。【原文：The tech startup executive charged by the Trump administration with reviewing the Internal Revenue Service's technology modernization program said on Thursday that he has canceled contracts worth about $1.5 billion from the tax agency's budget.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-doge-executive-claims-15-billion-savings-irs-technology-budget-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46GZZZ7S3FO6FF2AK4CSGAIBJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州大学洛杉矶分校因 2024 年暴徒袭击亲巴勒斯坦抗议者而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份法庭文件显示，加州大学洛杉矶分校周四因 2024 年暴徒袭击支持巴勒斯坦的抗议者而被起诉，当时正值美国校园抗议以色列加沙战争运动的高峰期。【原文：The University of California, Los Angeles, was sued on Thursday over a 2024 mob attack on pro-Palestinian protesters at the height of the U.S. campus protest movement against Israel's war in Gaza, a court filing showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ucla-sued-over-2024-mob-attack-pro-palestinian-protesters-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PA5W5UZQIZKG5CX3UPTBW2HAYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 02:56:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，五角大楼将向马斯克介绍可能与中国开战的绝密计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周四援引美国官员的话报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的亲密盟友、亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周五将听取五角大楼关于美国军方应对可能与中国爆发的任何战争的计划的简报。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk, U.S. President Donald Trump's close ally, is due to be briefed on Friday by the Pentagon on the U.S. military's plan for any war that might break out with China, the New York Times reported on Thursday, citing U.S. officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-brief-musk-top-secret-plan-potential-war-with-china-nyt-reports-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2QAKQXIDWNPQJDGUAW46KAZXQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 02:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称五角大楼将授予美国空军下一代战斗机合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[据了解该计划的消息人士称，五角大楼最快将于本周五宣布其关于下一代战斗机合同的决定，该合同最初价值超过 200 亿美元，尽管早些时候人们对预算限制和优先事项转移表示担忧。【原文：The Pentagon is set to announce its decision on a next-generation fighter jet contract initially worth more than $20 billion as soon as Friday, despite earlier concerns about budget constraints and shifting priorities, sources briefed on the plan said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-set-award-us-air-forces-next-generation-fighter-jet-contract-sources-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L27K3SOFGZPFXA67FYSQHQQNYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普撤回针对保罗-魏斯律师事务所的行政命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，他将撤回针对纽约律师事务所保罗-魏斯-里夫金-沃顿-加里森（Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison）的行政命令。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday he is withdrawing an executive order targeting New York law firm Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-withdraws-executive-order-targeting-paul-weiss-law-firm-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66OAJVZ3RVONZO7UR6ZKGLTRTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 23:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特斯拉以旧换新在马斯克的反弹中再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃德蒙兹（Edmunds）的数据显示，在抗议首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）担任美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）顾问的浪潮中，本月特斯拉电动汽车的交易量创下历史新高。【原文：Motorists have traded in a record number of Tesla electric vehicles this month, Edmunds data showed, amid a wave of protests against CEO Elon Musk's work as an adviser to U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-trade-ins-pace-record-high-amid-musk-backlash-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22DOJTRRRBOMLBZ32RZSGKGU3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 22:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国疫苗咨询会议改在四月举行]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部发言人周四在一封电子邮件中说，一个为美国疾病控制中心提供建议的免疫专家小组将于四月召开会议，此前的一次会议曾被推迟。【原文：A panel of immunization experts that advises the U.S. Centers for Disease Control will convene in April after a previous meeting had been postponed, a spokesman for the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services said in an email on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-vaccine-advisory-meeting-rescheduled-april-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GHCZSZTFJOM5BYZYRVRLZMJLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 22:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准 Alnylam 治疗罕见心脏病的药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四批准了 Alnylam 公司治疗一种罕见致命心脏病的药物，从而允许一种新型药物进入由辉瑞公司的大片药物 Vyndaqel 占据的市场。【原文：U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved Alnylam's drug to treat a rare and deadly heart disease on Thursday, allowing the entry of a new type of medicine in a market dominated by Pfizer's blockbuster Vyndaqel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-alnylams-drug-rare-heart-condition-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6F4B6RSL7ZLWLHQ4RXIW2FHQR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>