<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 01:32:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 01:32:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行上田称美国关税不确定性急剧上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田一夫周五表示，围绕美国政策，尤其是关税政策的不确定性最近急剧上升。【原文：Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda said on Friday uncertainty surrounding U.S. policy, particularly that on tariffs, has heightened sharply recently.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/bojs-ueda-says-us-tariff-uncertainty-heightening-sharply-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIGEZI3YOBJ53HLVYBN4UFAGIE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 01:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元滑向复活节周末]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑日元汇率从七个月低点回升，原因是美日贸易谈判迄今未就货币问题进行任何讨论。【原文：The dollar looked set to notch a fourth straight weekly loss on Thursday as tariffs drive investors from U.S. assets, though it lifted off a seven-month low against the yen as U.S.-Japan trade talks have so far steered clear of any currency discussion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-slides-towards-easter-weekend-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45NJRLQUXVKNBNFBIWSPBTAHGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 01:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税加剧经济风险，韩国维持利率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国央行周四一如预期维持政策利率不变，这一决定旨在帮助疲软的韩元，因为华盛顿试图通过征收全面关税来调整全球贸易秩序，这有可能损害经济增长。【原文：South Korea's central bank left its policy interest rate unchanged as expected on Thursday, a decision designed to aid a wobbly won as Washington's attempts to reorder global trade by imposing sweeping tariffs threaten to damage economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/south-korea-holds-rates-trump-tariffs-heighten-economic-risks-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72R4JXTJCRMMHD7PH6FRGFVCPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 01:07:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国增加对伊朗的制裁，欧佩克减产，油价每周上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，油价延续涨势，原因是在华盛顿实施进一步制裁以遏制伊朗石油贸易之后，供应有望趋紧，而且一些欧佩克产油国承诺进一步减产，以弥补超过商定配额的抽油量。【原文：Oil prices extended gains on Thursday on the prospect of tighter supply after Washington imposed further sanctions to curb Iranian oil trade and as some OPEC producers pledged further output cuts to compensate for pumping above agreed quotas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-heads-weekly-rise-us-adds-sanctions-iran-opec-cuts-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4XBQEUS5JM27B46DRFDFKY2HI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:55:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瓦莱罗公司计提 11 亿美元减值损失，可能闲置加州炼油厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[瓦莱罗能源公司（Valero Energy Corp）周三表示，将对其加州炼油厂计提 11 亿美元的税前减值，并告知州监管机构，将在 2026 年 4 月底之前永久关闭或重组其位于加州贝尼西亚的旧金山地区炼油厂。【原文：Valero Energy Corp said on Wednesday it was taking a $1.1 billion pre-tax impairment related to its California refineries and told state regulators it would permanently shut or restructure its San Francisco-area refinery in Benicia, California by the end of April 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/valero-books-11-bln-impairment-may-idle-california-refinery-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWV2EUBREBMM7DECHZEZSUWOPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:48:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德称需要耐心等待关税结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联邦储备银行行长杰夫-施密德（Jeff Schmid）周三表示，美联储的政策决策面临着复杂的局面，他指出，虽然他听到了农业部门对关税的紧张情绪，但近期能源价格的下跌可能会带来一剂 "强心针"，在一定程度上限制通胀。【原文：The Federal Reserve faces a complicated picture for policy decisions, Kansas City Federal Reserve Bank President Jeff Schmid said on Wednesday, noting that while he is hearing nervousness about tariffs in the agricultural sector, a recent decline in energy prices may deliver an offsetting "shot in the arm" that could somewhat limit inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-schmid-says-patience-needed-see-how-tariffs-play-out-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOXRIV62IZM4PEXXZY5RLZAGV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Insignia 延长贝恩和 CC Capital 竞购的排他性窗口期]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Insignia Financial 公司周四表示，该公司已将其竞标者贝恩资本（Bain Capital）和 CC Capital Partners 的排他性期限延长了四周，以便他们考虑收购这家财富管理公司的建议。【原文：Australia's Insignia Financial said on Thursday that it has extended the exclusivity period by four weeks for both its bidders, Bain Capital and CC Capital Partners, to consider their proposals to acquire the wealth manager.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/australias-insignia-financial-extends-exclusivity-period-bain-cc-capital-bids-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWHM2KPMVFI6BIURRBM4W6H2KA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:23:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 3 月份出口在美国加征关税前扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的数据显示，日本 3 月份出口连续第六个月增长，原因是美国全面关税的威胁促使日本公司增加了汽车和电子零部件的出货量。【原文：Japan's exports rose for a sixth straight month in March, data showed on Thursday, as the threat of sweeping U.S. tariffs drove Japanese companies to ramp up shipments of cars and electronic parts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-exports-expand-march-ahead-us-tariffs-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJY5BPWAZ5JTNALUYUJYN5SSBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:13:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税紧张局势下习近平访柬，柬埔寨期待中国提供更多帮助]]></title><description><![CDATA[柬埔寨政府发言人表示，中国国家主席习近平将于本周四结束东南亚三国之行访问柬埔寨，柬埔寨希望得到中国更多的财政支持，包括基础设施方面的支持。【原文：Cambodia is betting on more financial support from China, including for infrastructure, as President Xi Jinping visits the country on Thursday at the end of a three-nation trip in Southeast Asia, a Cambodian government spokesman said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/cambodia-eyes-more-china-help-xi-visits-amid-us-tariff-tensions-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLHX5N6CFBKMXJ7QIYJNQNMRPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 3 月出口同比增长 3.9]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务省周四公布的数据显示，日本 3 月份出口同比增长 3.9%，连续第六个月增长。【原文：Japanese exports rose 3.9% year-on-year in March, up for a sixth straight month, data from the Ministry of Finance showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-exports-rise-39-yy-march-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YF47RHWD3RLV7OKPKSN4NIMFTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚桑托斯公司第一季度销售收入下降 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚石油和天然气生产商桑托斯公司（Santos）周四公布的第一季度销售收入下降了7%，原因是原油销售量下降，以及国内天然气和与石油挂钩的液化天然气销售合同的实际价格疲软。【原文：Australian oil and gas producer Santos posted a 7% fall in first-quarter sales revenue on Thursday, hurt by lower crude sales volumes and weak realised prices for domestic gas and oil-linked LNG sales contracts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australias-santos-posts-7-fall-first-quarter-sales-revenue-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPD7HT6VYJLG5JLOB3BANHUDQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 23:38:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在外国大米成为关税话题之前，越来越多的日本人开始接受外国大米]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，严重的大米短缺导致日本大米价格飞涨，东京餐馆老板平野 Arata 做了一件以前看来不可思议的事：他改用美国品种的大米。【原文：When a severe rice shortage sent prices skyrocketing in Japan last year, Tokyo restaurant owner Arata Hirano did what had once seemed unthinkable: he switched to an American variety.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/more-japanese-embracing-foreign-rice-even-before-it-became-tariff-topic-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOGT5RTR55KJHNRZAC74SYCNNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 23:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铝业公司预计第二季度将遭受 9000 万美元的关税打击，对华关税将增加年度成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铝业公司（Alcoa）周三表示，预计美国对从加拿大进口的铝征收关税将在本季度给该公司造成约 9000 万美元的损失。【原文：Alcoa said on Wednesday it expects U.S. tariffs on aluminum imports from Canada to cost the company about $90 million in the current quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/alcoa-expects-90-million-tariff-hit-second-quarter-sees-duties-china-raising-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITOKFXQRJBLH5JZYQUCEZQCXKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 22:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：CFPB 将减少对企业的处罚力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》记者 X 日发布的一份备忘录称，消费者金融保护局首席法律官马克-保莱塔（Mark Paoletta）周三表示，该局将重点解决 "有形伤害 "问题，直接把钱退还给消费者，而不是对公司进行处罚。【原文：Consumer Financial Protection Bureau Chief Legal Officer Mark Paoletta said on Wednesday the bureau will focus on redressing "tangible harm" by getting money back directly to consumers rather than imposing penalties on companies, according to a memo posted by a Wall Street Journal reporter on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/cfpb-focus-less-imposing-penalties-companies-wsj-reports-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKLZJ2TUX5LD7IUKOOJ3MMYXZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 22:48:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，由于关税终止了中国的廉价运输，特姆优、希恩削减了数字广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业数据显示，美国社交媒体上最大的两家广告商--中国在线市场特步和快时尚零售商Shein正在大幅削减其在美国的数字广告支出，这对Meta's Facebook和YouTube等科技公司是一个打击。【原文：Chinese online marketplace Temu and fast-fashion retailer Shein, two of the biggest advertisers on U.S. social media, are sharply cutting their U.S. digital ad spending, industry data show, in a blow to tech companies such as Meta's Facebook and YouTube.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/temu-shein-slash-digital-ads-tariffs-end-cheap-shipping-china-data-show-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YH6OQ3DXMVMKLKZW5XKDKRZPMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 22:39:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税伤害的股市并未因鲍威尔的言论而有所好转]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者可能一直希望美联储能够帮助受关税影响的市场，但周三美联储总裁却发出了一个不受欢迎的信息：美联储可能陷入困境。【原文：Investors who may have been hoping the Federal Reserve is poised to come to the aid of tariff-rattled markets took away an unwelcome message from the central bank's chief on Wednesday: the Fed may be in a bind.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tariff-wounded-stocks-find-no-balm-with-powell-remarks-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2AP6OHUAZKV7KHKB434GIED2U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 22:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第一季度利润将大幅增长，但特朗普政策为其前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[台积电（TSMC）是全球人工智能应用领域先进芯片的主要生产商，该公司将于本周四公布第一季度利润增长 57% 的报告，但也可能会指出美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易政策所带来的风险。【原文：TSMC , the main global producer of advanced chips used in artificial intelligence applications, is set to report a 57% leap in first-quarter profit on Thursday, though it is also likely to flag risks from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-q1-profit-set-jump-trumps-policies-cloud-its-future-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UH72TWW2IRK6DK3JFFLG6B3Q7A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 22:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普贸易战波及商界，股市再遭重创]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全球贸易战的连锁反应正越来越多地同时在众多行业中显现，周三再次对美国股市造成压力，而美国股市已被其反复无常的贸易政策扰动了数周。【原文：The ripple effects of Donald Trump's global trade war are increasingly being felt across numerous industries all at once and on Wednesday were once again exerting pressure on U.S. stock markets that have been roiled for weeks by his erratic trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-trade-war-ripples-through-business-world-hits-stocks-again-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYADEIF32RONLFKPNXVIL4BFKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 21:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[煤炭收入下降，铁路运营商 CSX 季度业绩不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[铁路运营商 CSX 周三公布的第一季度收入和利润低于华尔街预期，原因是联运业务的增长被煤炭收入和燃料附加费的下降所抵消。【原文：Railroad operator CSX reported first-quarter revenue and profit below Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, as gains in intermodal were offset by a decline in coal revenue and fuel surcharge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/railroad-operator-csx-misses-quarterly-estimates-coal-revenue-falls-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKVLQ7EBGZM6PKSYYPVPXNKW7Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 21:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，前 CISA 负责人 Chris Krebs 在特朗普施压下离开 SentinelOne]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，前网络安全和基础设施安全局局长克里斯托弗-克雷布斯（Christopher Krebs）迫于唐纳德-特朗普总统的压力，即将离开网络安全公司 SentinelOne。【原文：Ex-Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency chief Christopher Krebs is leaving cybersecurity company SentinelOne following pressure from President Donald Trump, according to two sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ex-cisa-chief-chris-krebs-leaving-sentinelone-following-trump-pressure-sources-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H362QIOTCNMVXIDVS6UK4BB7PA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 21:08:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 当筹码减少时]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-graphics-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHKHWAESL5NA3IXVOSLMQ62IYI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 21:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔认为特朗普的劳工委员会解雇案不适用于美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国中央银行行长周三表示，最高法院正在审理的唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇联邦劳工委员会两名民主党人的法律案件不太可能适用于美联储。【原文：The legal case before the Supreme Court over President Donald Trump's firing of two Democrats from federal labor boards does not likely apply to the Federal Reserve, the head of the U.S. central bank said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/powell-does-not-think-trumps-labor-board-firings-case-will-apply-fed-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJ57ND6V6ZP5ZJEK7ZO6Q6U56I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国下令停止建设 Equinor 纽约海上风电项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国内政部长道格-伯格姆（Doug Burgum）周三表示，他将指示其机构停止在纽约海岸附近建设 Equinor 的 Empire Wind 海上风电项目。【原文：U.S. Interior Secretary Doug Burgum said on Wednesday he was directing his agency to halt construction on Equinor's Empire Wind offshore wind project off the coast of New York.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-orders-halt-construction-new-york-offshore-wind-project-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHC5QP5ZONOQFPIBAHEZAVVXMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外汇管制放松后阿根廷比索收复失地，米莱排除干预可能]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷比索周三收盘上涨 6.6%，收复了本周早些时候阿根廷取消资本管制导致比索暴跌的失地。【原文：Argentina's peso closed 6.6% higher on Wednesday, regaining ground lost after the currency tumbled on a lifting of capital controls earlier in the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/argentine-peso-recoups-lost-ground-after-fx-control-ease-milei-rules-out-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFDA4AOAEVPQLNEPUF74S7B72Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对印度的棉花出口因价格下跌和关税不确定性而增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家表示，在全球关税冲突、美国棉价下跌以及南亚国家需求上升的推动下，过去几个月美国对印度的陆地棉出口有所增加。【原文：U.S. upland cotton exports to India have risen in the past few months fueled by global tariff conflicts, declining American prices and rising demand in the South Asian country, industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-cotton-exports-india-rise-lower-prices-tariff-uncertainties-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GRIIND6TJJCTGXSUFYT524FN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：英特尔向中国客户出口人工智能芯片需要许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，美国芯片制造商英特尔已通知中国客户，它将开始需要许可证才能销售其部分先进的人工智能处理器。【原文：American chipmaker Intel has informed Chinese clients it will start needing a license to sell some of its advanced artificial intelligence processors, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-will-need-license-export-ai-chips-chinese-clients-ft-reports-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5A7K46EWZPJJPEDLAOTVOHQRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示，成千上万用户的缩放比例下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 的数据，周三有数千名用户的视频会议平台 Zoom Communications 服务出现故障。【原文：Video-conferencing platform Zoom Communications services were down for thousands of users on Wednesday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/zoom-down-thousands-users-downdetector-shows-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OHG4JFZ6FL4BOASWZT2UXBVCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[管道运营商金德摩根第一季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受产品管道业务疲软和成本上升的影响，美国管道和码头运营商金德摩根公司（Kinder Morgan）第一季度利润略低于华尔街预期。【原文：U.S. pipeline and terminal operator Kinder Morgan narrowly missed Wall Street expectations for first-quarter profit on Wednesday, hurt by weakness in its products pipelines segment and higher costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pipeline-operator-kinder-morgan-misses-first-quarter-profit-estimates-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7X2YC2EPN5PGRGEYVYPOJRLIN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:11:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2 月份外国持有的美国国债增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三公布的数据显示，2月份外国持有的美国国债增加了3.4%，其中最大的两个持有国--日本和中国分别增持了美债。【原文：Foreign holdings of U.S. Treasuries rose 3.4% in February, data from the Treasury Department showed on Wednesday, with the two largest owners, Japan and China, each building up their U.S. debt holdings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/foreign-holdings-us-treasuries-rise-february-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYQE7EQP7ROBZACH6V2R756QIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《美国汽车新闻》报道，如果特朗普继续征收汽车关税，福特汽车可能在 5 月份提价]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国《汽车新闻》周三援引一份给经销商的备忘录报道，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的汽车关税政策不放松，福特汽车可能会在五月份提高新车价格。【原文：Ford Motor may raise prices of its new vehicles in May if U.S. President Donald Trump's auto tariffs are not eased, Automotive News reported on Wednesday, citing a memo to dealers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-motor-may-hike-prices-may-if-trumps-auto-tariffs-persist-automotive-news-2025-04-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2OBBIKW2VJL3NYU2H4ZFHGODU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 19:41:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>