<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:04:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:04:34 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司波音航班客舱起火，联邦航空局将展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司一架从佛罗里达飞往纽瓦克机场的波音737航班上的机组人员报告机舱内起火，美国联邦航空管理局周四表示将对此展开调查。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration on Thursday said it will investigate after the crew on a United Airlines-operated Boeing 737 flight from Florida to Newark airport reported a fire in the cabin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-investigate-after-fire-reported-cabin-united-airlines-boeing-flight-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2WQWRMRFFNSVIQE274QHXCOYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AppLovin 竞购中国以外所有市场的 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[营销平台 AppLovin 周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普规定的为 1.7 亿美国人使用的短视频应用寻找非中国买家的 4 月 5 日最后期限到来之前，它已提交了一份对 TikTok 在中国以外资产的竞购书。【原文：Marketing platform AppLovin said on Thursday it has submitted a bid for TikTok assets outside of China, ahead of the April 5 deadline set by the U.S. President Donald Trump to find a non-Chinese buyer for the short video app used by 170 million Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/applovin-bids-tiktok-all-markets-outside-china-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B37UHKSGRFKXFCFRZOKPO57RJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，海莉-比伯正在探索出售其彩妆品牌 Rhode]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟知内情的人士透露，名模海莉-比伯（Hailey Bieber）正在探索出售其彩妆品牌 Rhode，价值可能超过 10 亿美元。【原文：Model Hailey Bieber is exploring a sale of her makeup brand Rhode that could be worth more than $1 billion, according to three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hailey-bieber-explores-sale-her-makeup-brand-rhode-sources-say-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMWJQJKLH5ITNBPRXFRGAOGNO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：特朗普火力全开，全球市场关税化]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量。【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUYENLLYKNI3ZKJ6T63B26JTJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称，如果中国批准嘀嗒出行协议，将获得关税减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，他将考虑就 TikTok 达成一项交易，即中国批准出售该短视频应用，以换取美国对中国进口产品关税的减免。
特朗普说，Tiktok的交易已经接近尾声，有多个投资者参与其中。
TikTok面临着在4月5日最后期限前达成协议，找到一个非中国买家，否则将面临被禁止进入美国的威胁。【原文：President Donald Trump on Thursday said he would consider a deal for TikTok where China approves the sale of the short video app in exchange for relief from U.S. tariffs on Chinese imports.
Trump said that a deal is close on Tiktok, with multiple investors involved.
TikTok faces an April 5 deadline to reach a deal to find a non-Chinese buyer under threat of being banned from the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-says-china-could-get-tariff-relief-if-it-approves-tiktok-deal-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EC56B6K25KYDO7XQJHO4TRCL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:51:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行将于 9 月推出 Pix 分期付款功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行周四表示，一项允许用户通过其广受欢迎的即时支付系统 Pix 分期支付交易的新功能将于 9 月份推出。【原文：Brazil's central bank said on Thursday that a new feature allowing users to pay for transactions in installments through its widely popular instant payment system, Pix, is set to become available in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-central-bank-launch-pix-installment-feature-september-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WM7C2HMROBNCZPHMSISGR7F2YY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普 500 指数市值损失 2.4 万亿美元，创 2020 年以来最大单日跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[在华尔街周四的大跌中，S&amp;P 500 指数公司的股票市值共损失了 2.4 万亿美元，这是自 2020 年 3 月 16 日新出现的冠状病毒大流行导致全球市场陷入低迷以来的最大单日市值损失。【原文：S&amp;P 500 companies lost a combined $2.4 trillion in stock market value in Thursday's selloff on Wall Street, their biggest one-day loss in value since the emerging coronavirus pandemic sent global markets into a tailspin on March 16, 2020.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/sp-500-loses-24-trillion-market-value-biggest-one-day-loss-since-2020-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVIPRUHI4JKYDNBU33BVRLGPYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾伯维因收购支出下调 2025 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯维周四下调了2025年调整后利润预期，因为该制药商预计将产生2.48亿美元与里程碑付款相关的收购费用以及研发成本。【原文：AbbVie on Thursday cut its 2025 adjusted profit forecast as the drugmaker expects to incur $248 million in acquisition expenses related to milestone payments as well as research and development costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/abbvie-cuts-2025-profit-forecast-acquisition-expenses-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z54ZKHZ5UZOGXBER7F77RZBBHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发布行政命令后，法官批准美国终止外国贿赂案的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官同意让美国司法部结束对 Cognizant Technology Solutions 两名前高管的起诉，这是自唐纳德-特朗普总统停止执行一项重要的反贿赂法律以来，司法部首次公开放弃一起外国贿赂案。【原文：A federal judge agreed to let the U.S. Department of Justice end its prosecution of two former Cognizant Technology Solutions executives, the first time the department publicly abandoned a foreign bribery case since President Donald Trump halted enforcement of a key anti-bribery law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-grants-us-request-end-foreign-bribery-case-following-trump-executive-order-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7A2SYOSTJJP53DTMTJKD2RXM5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行将于 4 月 9 日下调现金利率，进一步放宽政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社调查显示，新西兰储备银行将于4月9日降息25个基点，经济学家们维持此前的利率展望，因为预计通胀仍将受到控制。【原文：The Reserve Bank of New Zealand will cut interest rates by 25 basis points on April 9, according to economists polled by Reuters, who have held to their previous rate outlook as inflation is expected to remain under control.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/rbnz-set-cut-cash-rate-april-9-flags-further-easing-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLKIAUIYHZMGRNZZUVPPPBENLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:09:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国进口鸡蛋旨在降低价格，但可能会受到关税打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部长布鲁克-罗林斯（Brooke Rollins）周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的新关税可能适用于为缓解供应短缺而进口的鸡蛋。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's new tariffs could apply to eggs being imported to ease a supply shortage, Agriculture Secretary Brooke Rollins said on Thursday, a move that industry experts said could boost prices just as they have started to decline from record highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-egg-imports-meant-drive-prices-down-could-be-hit-by-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMW2U4BC7RO2ZILOPPWZDJZZQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库克出席活动的网络视频中出现色情和纳粹图片]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）在一所大学发表演讲的互联网流媒体遭到黑客攻击，观看屏幕上充斥着种族主义言论、纳粹标志和色情图片，导致在线访问被切断。【原文：An internet stream of a speech at a university by Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook was hacked on Thursday as racist remarks, Nazi symbols and pornographic images peppered the viewing screen, prompting online access to be cut off.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/online-feed-event-with-feds-cook-hit-with-porn-nazi-images-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LZR2VGD5RKABH5S3WS6LFOPF4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，巴西 Banco Master 银行正在等待 BTG Pactual 提出并购建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，巴西贷款机构 Banco Master 正在推进与投资银行 BTG Pactual 的谈判，以出售国有控股银行巴西商业银行收购其大部分资本后剩余的资产。【原文：Brazilian lender Banco Master is advancing in talks with investment bank BTG Pactual to sell assets left over after a deal in which state-controlled bank BRB acquired most of its capital, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/brazils-banco-master-awaits-ma-proposal-btg-pactual-sources-say-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XL7VWJLL2RPJBFUR4TBMGKPTBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:56:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，KKR 退出寻求收购 Gerresheimer 的财团]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道称，KKR 已放弃与私募股权财团讨论收购 Gerresheimer AG 事宜。【原文：KKR has abandoned a private equity consortium discussing a takeover of Gerresheimer AG , Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kkr-drops-out-consortium-seeking-gerresheimer-takeover-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UAKFI3WIJJTHGHS2WTXV2K6XI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:54:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，世界经济论坛创始人克劳斯-施瓦布将辞去受托人主席一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，世界经济论坛创始人克劳斯-施瓦布（Klaus Schwab）将 "启动 "卸任论坛董事会主席一职的程序。【原文：The founder of the World Economic Forum, Klaus Schwab, will "start the process" of stepping down as chair of its board of trustees, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-economic-forum-founder-klaus-schwab-step-down-chair-trustees-ft-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5U5RT6I6RNILM4PBYZ3C37FEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:37:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥与美国的自由贸易或将继续，因为特朗普免于征收新关税，但打击了竞争对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "解放日 "似乎将终结北美自由贸易和墨西哥进入美国的特权。【原文：President Donald Trump's "Liberation Day" appeared set to end North American free trade and Mexico's privileged access to the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-free-trade-with-us-may-survive-trump-spares-it-new-tariffs-hits-rivals-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGUV4UPKDRNCRFG7JA7OBMA7EI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资级信用风险指数创 2023 年 11 月以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国全面征收关税引发的市场动荡中，作为信用风险指标的一篮子信用违约掉期的Markit CDX北美投资级指数周四扩大至2023年11月以来的最高点。【原文：The Markit CDX North American Investment Grade Index , a basket of credit default swaps that serves as a gauge of credit risk, widened to its highest since November 2023 on Thursday amid market turmoil fueled by U.S. sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-tariffs-credit-urgent-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7MXYBH2HFMXJE7VY6ACSAP4LA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股票多空对冲基金在市场下跌中抹去了年内收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府宣布全面征收关税后，股市暴跌，全球股票多空对冲基金周四抹去了今年以来的涨幅。【原文：Global equity long/short hedge funds erased their gains for the year on Thursday as stocks plunged after the Trump administration announced sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/equity-longshort-hedge-funds-wipe-out-year-gains-market-rout-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z2SUZ7B5KZJ35GYNPRUR23X35I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:17:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔与台积电初步同意组建芯片制造合资企业，信息报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《信息时报》周四援引两位参与部分讨论的人士的话报道，英特尔公司和台湾半导体制造股份有限公司的高管最近达成了一项初步协议，将组建一家合资企业来运营这家美国公司的芯片制造设施。【原文：Executives from Intel and Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co recently reached a preliminary agreement to form a joint venture to operate the U.S. firm's chipmaking facilities, the Information reported on Thursday, citing two people involved in some of the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-tsmc-tentatively-agree-form-chipmaking-joint-venture-information-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRQD7EDIGFJDJBCJ5YQYHEFNMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准安进公司的 Uplizna 首次用于治疗罕见免疫性疾病]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四表示，该局已批准扩大安进公司药物Uplizna的使用范围，以帮助降低一种罕见的免疫系统相关疾病患者的复发风险。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has approved expanded use of Amgen's drug, Uplizna, to help reduce the risk of flares in patients with a rare immune system-related condition, the regulator said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-expanded-use-amgens-rare-disease-drug-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIMOP3CXR5KKDJBPG3BV3MQTNY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:49:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储库克表示，在高度不确定的情况下，美联储是时候观察数据了]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）周四表示，在高度不确定性的情况下，央行现在应该慢慢观察数据的变化，然后再改变货币政策的设定。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook said Thursday that amid high levels of uncertainty now is a time for the central bank to take its time to watch how the data comes in before it changes the setting of monetary policy again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-cook-says-amid-high-uncertainty-time-fed-watch-data-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNNEL7SUPBN2BLP6LFFAD7EFQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:33:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 NTSB 敦促 FAA 要求对波音 757 飞机门闩进行检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会周四敦促联邦航空管理局要求航空公司在2023年田纳西州联邦快递一架航班紧急撤离后检查波音757飞机舱门的锁扣，并在必要时进行更换。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board on Thursday urged the Federal Aviation Administration to require airlines to inspect latches on Boeing 757 airplane doors after a 2023 emergency evacuation of a FedEx flight in Tennessee, and to replace them if needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-ntsb-urges-faa-require-boeing-757-airplane-door-latch-inspections-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUAKBJUOB5PZLBXJYZN2LPRDNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛：美国关税威胁冲击经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）警告说，美国全面征收关税将拖累全球经济增长，并促使美联储比之前预期的更积极地降息。【原文：Goldman Sachs warned sweeping U.S. tariffs will weigh on global growth and prompt the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates more aggressively than previously expected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-tariffs-threaten-growth-shock-goldman-sachs-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NM3LSU2QMJI65C464BZTDLZQZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咖啡进口税对已经面临高价的美国烘焙商造成压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[自殖民时代以来，美国首次对咖啡进口征收关税，这将增加进口商和烘焙商的成本和复杂性，而他们已经在应对接近创纪录的价格。【原文：The first U.S. tariffs on coffee imports since colonial times will increase costs and complexity to importers and roasters already dealing with near-record prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/import-tax-coffee-pressures-us-roasters-already-facing-high-prices-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXHWALHZE5L5HFFTICND2YXMCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资者对关税深度措手不及，将面临更多痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三宣布全面征收新关税，投资者对此早有心理准备，但许多人表示，现在的情况是市场最坏的情况。他们的信息是系好安全带，做好心理准备。【原文：Investors had been prepared for a shock heading in to U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of sweeping new tariffs on Wednesday, but many said that what played out was the worst-case-scenario for markets. Their message: Buckle up and brace yourself.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-tariffs-funds-pix-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BH42JSVWXVNUHMMLTR7R7NV53U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉下调西南航空公司评级至负面]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周四将西南航空公司的评级展望从之前的 "稳定 "下调至 "负面"，理由是该航空公司可能会转向不太保守的资本分配和财务政策。【原文：Fitch Ratings on Thursday downgraded Southwest Airlines to a "negative" outlook from its earlier "stable" rating, citing the carrier's possible shift to a less conservative capital allocation and financial policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-downgrades-southwest-airlines-outlook-negative-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIWXYEPN4RNA5F6FZUPRROSBSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，Capital One 以 350 亿美元收购 Discover 的交易通过了美国司法部的审核]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周四报道，Capital One 金融公司收购发现金融服务公司（Discover Financial Services）的提议获得了美国司法部的批准，因为司法部告诉其他负责调查该并购案的监管机构，它认为没有足够的竞争问题来阻止该交易。【原文：Capital One Financial Corp got a greenlight from the Justice Department for its proposed acquisition of Discover Financial Services after the DOJ told other regulators looking into the merger that it doesn't see sufficient competition concerns to block the deal, the New York Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/capital-ones-35-billion-deal-discover-clears-us-doj-hurdle-nyt-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4U7UDXMSXNIDFLRN36PH5CZAO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:51:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嗨得更高特朗普关税将提高美国大麻价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[考虑通过吸烟来摆脱关税阴霾？再想想吧。【原文：Contemplating smoking your way out of the tariff gloom? Think again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/high-just-got-higher-trump-tariffs-raise-prices-us-cannabis-users-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGVU4NSZMJMNBEZVKKQWBOXZJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亨特公司番茄生产商 Conagra 首席执行官表示，可能会提高价格以抵消关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chef Boyardee生产商Conagra Brands首席执行官肖恩-康诺利（Sean Connolly）周四表示，Conagra Brands可能不得不提高价格，以抵消对可可、橄榄油、棕榈油和一种用于罐头食品的钢材等原料征收关税的成本。【原文：Chef Boyardee maker Conagra Brands may have to hike prices to offset the cost of tariffs on ingredients like cocoa, olive oil, palm oil and a type of steel used for its canned food products, CEO Sean Connolly said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hunts-tomato-maker-conagra-may-hike-prices-offset-tariffs-ceo-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4DEH4BPM5MRHE5HZDK7ZDZP3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西枪支制造商金牛座认为美国工厂是最大限度减少关税冲击的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西枪支制造商金牛座阿玛斯公司首席执行官 Salesio Nuhs 告诉路透社，该公司在美国的生产线有望帮助其最大限度地减少美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三征收关税的影响。【原文：Brazilian gunmaker Taurus Armas expects its production line in the United States to help it minimize the impact of tariffs imposed on Wednesday by U.S. President Donald Trump, its chief executive Salesio Nuhs told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-gunmaker-taurus-sees-us-plant-key-minimizing-tariff-hit-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q57HHJSSVZIFPHJTHTYT3CXSWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>