<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:41:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:41:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[意大利伦巴第选矿集团利用 Starlink 测试卫星通信服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利伦巴第大区周四在一个试点项目中选择了一个使用星链（Starlink）低轨道卫星星座的企业联盟，以了解天基连接是否是提高该国高速互联网普及率的可行解决方案。【原文：Italy's Lombardy region on Thursday picked a consortium of firms using Starlink's low-orbit satellite constellation in a pilot project to see if space-based connectivity is a viable solution to boost high-speed internet penetration in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/italys-lombardy-picks-group-using-starlink-test-satcom-services-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVQVA4VSAJLU7NOTT75RLUOVOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利佩科里诺奶酪生产商力争避免美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[佩科里诺罗马诺奶酪是意大利最著名的出口食品之一，其生产商正在游说美国不要对其征收新的关税，因为这可能会抬高消费者的价格，并从其出口市场中分一杯羹。【原文：Producers of Pecorino Romano cheese, one of Italy's best known food exports, are lobbying to be spared new U.S. tariffs that could raise consumer prices and take a chunk out of their export market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italian-pecorino-producers-press-avoid-us-tariffs-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJI66T33CJLJFDQGNRCPKL4ARE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前美联储理事沃什称财政部与央行需要达成新协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[前美联储理事凯文-沃什（Kevin Warsh）被视为美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）的潜在继任者。【原文：Former Federal Reserve Governor Kevin Warsh, seen as a potential successor to Fed Chair Jerome Powell, said on Thursday there needs to be a new accord between the Treasury Department and U.S. central bank, referencing a 1951 pact that separated federal debt management from monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ex-fed-governor-warsh-says-new-accord-between-treasury-central-bank-needed-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWIRLDOHINNJTNHN6QC7KVAC2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛墨西哥业务部第二季度利润率疲软，市值缩水 33 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四上午，沃尔玛墨西哥和中美洲分公司（Walmex）股价下跌 6%，市值减少 609 亿比索（32.5 亿美元），此前该公司公布的利润率低于预期。【原文：Shares in Walmart's Mexico and Central America unit, known as Walmex , slid 6% on Thursday morning, wiping off 60.9 billion pesos ($3.25 billion) from the firm's market capitalization after posting weaker-than-expected margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmarts-mexico-unit-wipes-33-billion-off-market-value-after-weak-q2-margins-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICCFQRIXKFLTTFY66SDSQ6GMXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:59:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局敦促沃尔沃车主紧急召回制动器]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周四要求瑞典汽车制造商沃尔沃（Volvo）部分车辆的车主紧急完成因刹车失灵问题的安全召回。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) on Thursday asked owners of some vehicles of Swedish automaker Volvo to urgently complete a safety recall over a brake failure issue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/nhtsa-urges-volvo-owners-complete-urgent-brake-recall-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FINBT6KD4RNJ5P5LUWKM55YMZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，在特朗普忧虑之际，英国央行对贷款人进行美元风险审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士称，英国央行已要求一些贷款机构测试其抵御潜在美元冲击的能力，这是特朗普政府的政策正在削弱人们对美国作为金融稳定基石的信任的最新迹象。【原文：The Bank of England has asked some lenders to test their resilience to potential U.S. dollar shocks, three sources said, the latest sign of how the Trump administration's policies are eroding trust in the U.S. as a bedrock of financial stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bank-england-scrutinizes-lenders-dollar-risk-amid-trump-worries-sources-say-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWRP6DVKG5NLLP2PRZSX5GTV3M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:47:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，高盛任命哈利勒为中间市场集团全球主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四看到的一份备忘录显示，高盛任命其资深银行家 Aasem Khalil 为其全球业务主管，主要负责中型市场银行业务的客户覆盖。【原文：Goldman Sachs named its senior banker Aasem Khalil as global head of its business focused on client coverage in middle-market banking, a memo seen by Reuters on Thursday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-sachs-names-khalil-global-head-middle-market-group-memo-says-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SURRVHPBBFLR5ASLF7EWIJ4ZG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：亚马逊 AWS 云计算部门裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊发言人在路透社调查后证实，亚马逊网络服务云计算部门周四裁员。AWS内部有多个部门受到了影响。【原文：Amazon cut jobs in its Amazon Web Services cloud computing unit Thursday, a spokesperson confirmed following a Reuters inquiry. Several groups within AWS were impacted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazons-aws-cloud-computing-unit-cuts-jobs-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNJITWIV7ZMD5CDGRN7NRBPEDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:26:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机器人出租车竞争白热化，Waymo 扩大德克萨斯州奥斯汀的覆盖范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[这家软件巨头的自动驾驶部门周四表示，Alphabet 旗下的 Waymo 正在将其在得克萨斯州奥斯汀的服务范围从之前的 37 平方英里扩大到 90 平方英里，以保护其在该市的领先地位，免受特斯拉等竞争对手的冲击。【原文：Alphabet's Waymo is expanding its service in Austin, Texas, to 90 square miles from 37 square miles earlier, the software giant's self-driving unit said on Thursday, seeking to protect its top position in the city from rivals such as Tesla.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/waymo-expands-coverage-austin-texas-robotaxi-competition-heats-up-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6TMEXMXTBI3BOVNQE4JCE4MZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月商业库存保持不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份，美国企业库存连续第二个月保持不变，这表明库存可能会在第二季度减少国内生产总值。【原文：U.S. business inventories were unchanged for a second straight month in May, suggesting that inventories could subtract from gross domestic product in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-business-inventories-unchanged-may-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LT4HGVPAQVMXDFHIXDPTVTIFEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车安全机构裁员超过 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社向国会提供的数据，美国汽车安全机构正在根据特朗普政府提出的离开政府的经济激励计划裁减超过25%的员工。【原文：The U.S. auto safety agency is shedding more than 25% of its employees under financial incentive programs to depart the government offered by the Trump administration, according to data provided to Congress seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-auto-safety-agency-shedding-more-than-25-employees-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXBYUTZ5FBO3ZM6GLC6MNITVEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:54:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国 Mistral 公司新增人工智能功能，与美国聊天机器人一较高下]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国初创公司Mistral周四宣布了其人工智能聊天机器人Le Chat的新功能，试图在美国和中国主导的全球人工智能竞赛中占据一席之地。
Mistral经常被称为法国和欧洲的人工智能冠军，它与OpenAI和Alphabet旗下的谷歌等美国巨头竞争，但在市场份额或收入方面却落后于它们。
"Mistral 在一篇博文中说："我们将通过一系列强大的新功能，让 Le Chat 变得更强大、更直观、更有趣，帮助你更深入地研究，更自然地表达，并让你的互动（文字、语音和图像）在上下文中井井有条。【原文：French start-up Mistral announced new features to its AI chatbot Le Chat on Thursday as it tries to carve out a place for itself in a global AI race dominated by the United States and China.
Often presented as France's and Europe's AI champion, Mistral competes with American giants such as OpenAI and Alphabet's Google, but lags behind in terms of market share or revenues.
"We're making Le Chat even more capable, more intuitive — and more fun — with a collection of powerful new features to help you research more thoroughly, express yourself more naturally, and keep your interactions — text, voice, and images — organized in context", said Mistral in a blog post.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/frances-mistral-adds-new-ai-features-rival-us-chatbots-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7BEIKDA7RO2ZGU2AB7ULQGOPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称摩根大通任命北美企业银行部新领导人]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部备忘录，摩根大通已任命 Mike Lister 和 Brennan Spry 为北美企业银行业务联席主管。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has appointed Mike Lister and Brennan Spry as co-heads of North America corporate banking, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-appoints-new-leaders-its-north-america-corporate-banking-unit-memo-says-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37MTXYXVPBMPXL5LY5JITK52PY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:42:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定，起诉 Anthropic 的美国作家可联合起来提起版权集体诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州一名联邦法官周四裁定，起诉人工智能初创公司 Anthropic 侵犯版权的三位作家可以代表 Anthropic 涉嫌盗版以训练其人工智能系统的全国作家。【原文：A California federal judge ruled on Thursday that three authors suing artificial intelligence startup Anthropic for copyright infringement can represent writers nationwide whose books Anthropic allegedly pirated to train its AI system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-authors-suing-anthropic-can-band-together-copyright-class-action-judge-rules-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHLPFPVA35KQJPCAPHLXAPC7DA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯储蓄银行为俄罗斯加密资产提供托管服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯最大的国有银行储蓄银行（Sberbank）周四表示，希望为俄罗斯加密货币资产提供托管服务，寻求在俄罗斯数字资产发展中发挥主导作用。【原文：Russia's largest lender Sberbank wants to offer custody services for Russian cryptocurrency assets, the state-owned bank said on Thursday, seeking a leading role in Russia's development of digital assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/russias-sberbank-offers-custody-services-russian-crypto-assets-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UD37ACVTTZLI3IGES7STGVJIKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:39:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，FDA 授权 Juul 电子烟在美国销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟知内情的消息人士周四告诉路透社，美国食品和药物管理局已授权销售 Juul 的烟草和薄荷口味的电子烟设备和笔芯。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has authorized the sale of Juul's e-cigarette device and refill cartridges in tobacco and menthol flavors, a source familiar with the matter told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/fda-authorizes-juuls-e-cigarettes-sale-us-source-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OCJBOYEOFK2NOBG6OZFA3RI3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帝亚吉欧新任首席执行官需要行动，而不仅仅是言辞]]></title><description><![CDATA[帝亚吉欧的新任临时首席执行官尼克-贾汉阿尼（Nik Jhangiani）以其冷静自信和清晰的沟通方式吸引了投资者，相比之下，他的前任在短期任期内难以赢得公司股东的青睐。【原文：Diageo's new interim CEO Nik Jhangiani has charmed investors with his cool confidence and clear communication, in contrast to his predecessor who struggled to win over the company's shareholders during her short term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/diageos-new-ceo-needs-actions-not-just-words-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZL5CT2USNM7HNTH42Y5ZKT6NE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:30:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会和马斯克寻求更多时间让亿万富翁回应美国证券交易委员会的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）和埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）再次达成协议，给予这位亿万富翁更多的时间来回应监管机构的民事诉讼，该诉讼指控马斯克在 2022 年披露其在推特（Twitter）的巨额股份时等待了太长时间。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission and Elon Musk have again agreed to give the billionaire more time to respond to the regulator's civil lawsuit accusing him of waiting too long in 2022 to reveal his large stake in Twitter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-sec-musk-seek-more-time-billionaire-respond-secs-lawsuit-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP7E63G7ERIDJPUESPYB2FHVBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 "加密周 "大戏之后，美国众议院准备向特朗普提交稳定币法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[经过两天紧张的谈判，美国众议院似乎准备在周四通过关键的加密立法，包括为与美元挂钩的加密代币--稳定币--建立监管框架。【原文：The U.S. House of Representatives appeared poised to pass key crypto legislation on Thursday, including the creation of a regulatory framework for U.S.-dollar-pegged cryptocurrency tokens known as stablecoins, after two days of fraught negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-house-poised-send-stablecoin-bill-trump-after-crypto-week-drama-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TVOHF62RC5PM7KAP3QLT7N2O7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:17:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司采取期权策略，在美元回升时保护欧元收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些美国公司正在利用更有吸引力的欧元期权定价，以保护它们预期从欧洲获得的收入免受损失，因为它们担心共同货币可能已经走强得有点过头了。【原文：Some U.S. companies are taking advantage of more attractive pricing in euro options to protect the revenues they expect from Europe against losses, fearing the common currency may have strengthened a bit too far.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-companies-adopt-options-strategies-shield-euro-revenues-case-dollar-recovers-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4GLSXFABNNCJDGB2G4L3PJASE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:53:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗聘请高盛老将弗里德兰加强投资银行团队]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四在一份内部备忘录中看到，花旗集团最高主管维斯-拉加万（Vis Raghavan）宣布，花旗集团已聘请大卫-弗里德兰（David Friedland）担任北美投资银行业务联席主管。【原文：Citigroup has hired David Friedland as co-head of North America investment banking coverage, its top executive Vis Raghavan announced in an internal memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/citi-hires-goldman-veteran-friedland-boost-investment-banking-team-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXWROYFAZZIIZFNHQ3HI65WPOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BWX 技术公司获得价值高达 26 亿美元的海军核反应堆组件合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[BWX Technologies 公司周四表示，该公司已获得价值 26 亿美元的合同，包括未来的选择权，为美国海军制造核潜艇和航空母舰的部件。【原文：BWX Technologies said on Thursday it has secured contracts worth $2.6 billion, including future options, to manufacture components for nuclear submarines and an aircraft carrier for the U.S. Navy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/bwx-technologies-secures-naval-nuclear-reactor-component-contract-worth-up-26-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7E7RMFMZ5NIQNMV5R5XBM6RSWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 投资者与扎克伯格达成和解，结束 Facebook 隐私诉讼案的审判]]></title><description><![CDATA[起诉马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）和其他公司领导人的 Meta Platforms 股东的一名律师周四告诉特拉华州法官，双方已达成和解协议，结束了因 Facebook 侵犯用户隐私权而耗资 80 亿美元的诉讼。【原文：A lawyer for Meta Platforms shareholders who were suing Mark Zuckerberg and other company leaders told a Delaware judge on Thursday that the parties had reached a settlement agreement, ending a $8 billion trial over Facebook’s user privacy violations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-investors-zuckerberg-reach-settlement-end-trial-over-facebook-privacy-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDWFMMKZOZNJDOZ432MQ52P5U4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：富国银行美国籍银行家退出中国受阻]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国富国银行一位从事贸易融资的银行家最近在中国旅行后被禁止离开中国。【原文：A U.S.-based Wells Fargo banker who works in trade financing has been blocked from leaving China after traveling there recently, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-based-wells-fargo-banker-blocked-exiting-china-wsj-reports-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTV7EK747RL4DO4P2PTFNAY2JE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月进口价格小幅上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于能源产品价格下降，6 月份美国进口价格小幅反弹，但消费品成本上升与关税导致的通胀上升相一致。【原文：U.S. import prices rebounded marginally in June amid cheaper energy products, but higher costs for consumer goods were consistent with a tariff-driven increase in inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-import-prices-rise-marginally-june-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4HDTXOTSFJY5LOSCEXMIYYPJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:22:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒关税影响价格，一段时间内不会降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周四表示，随着特朗普政府关税的影响开始传导至消费者价格，美国联邦储备委员会 "在一段时间内 "不应降息，需要采取紧缩的货币政策来抑制通胀心理。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve should not cut interest rates "for some time" as the impact of Trump administration tariffs begin passing through to consumer prices, with tight monetary policy needed to keep inflationary psychology in check, Federal Reserve governor Adriana Kugler said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-kugler-no-rate-cut-some-time-tariffs-pass-through-prices-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBBOXPXK5FIGTMRUXJITJ4PFYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司 Bitcoin Standard 将通过与 Cantor 支持的 SPAC 达成交易上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币公司比特币标准财务公司（Bitcoin Standard Treasury Company）周四表示，该公司的目标是通过与坎托-菲茨杰拉德（Cantor Fitzgerald）支持的空头支票工具合并，在纳斯达克上市。【原文：Crypto firm Bitcoin Standard Treasury Company is aiming to list on the Nasdaq through a merger with a Cantor Fitzgerald-backed blank check vehicle, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/crypto-firm-bitcoin-standard-go-public-through-deal-with-cantor-backed-spac-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7VFLKVM6FONDIBEDRVYSRS2RY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行员工在布鲁塞尔表达对联合信贷银行交易的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周四社交媒体上的一篇帖子和两位知情人士透露，德国商业银行的一个员工代表代表团会见了欧洲议会议员，表达了他们对联合信贷银行可能收购德国商业银行的担忧。【原文：A delegation of employee representatives from Commerzbank met with members of the European Parliament to voice their concerns about a possible takeover by UniCredit , according to a social media post on Thursday and two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commerzbank-employees-voice-unicredit-deal-concerns-brussels-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6K6UHPWWTRISPN52RSBVAUAPEE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降；7 月份就业增长趋于稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量有所下降，表明 7 月份就业稳步增长，尽管由于招聘放缓，一些下岗工人经历了长时间的失业。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for jobless benefits fell last week, pointing to steady job growth in July, though some laid off workers are experiencing long spells of unemployment because of a moderation in hiring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-job-growth-appears-steady-july-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGLBGYVVAZPTFOX3OMZH6NUUBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月零售销售超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 6 月份零售额的反弹幅度超过预期，但部分增幅可能反映了受关税影响的一些商品的价格上涨。【原文：U.S. retail sales rebounded more than expected in June, but some of the increase likely reflected higher prices for some goods exposed to tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-retail-sales-beat-expectations-june-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTGX3S2WMBPHDK42IHCS6HF3XE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>