<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 17:34:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 17:34:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国要求欧盟反垄断负责人澄清约束大科技公司的规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院司法委员会主席吉姆-乔丹（Jim Jordan）周日要求欧盟反垄断负责人特雷莎-里贝拉（Teresa Ribera）澄清她是如何执行欧盟约束大科技公司的规则的，称这些规则似乎是针对美国公司的。【原文：U.S. House Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan on Sunday demanded EU antitrust chief Teresa Ribera clarify how she enforces the European Union's rules reining in Big Tech, saying they appear to target U.S. companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-demands-eu-antitrust-chief-clarify-rules-reining-big-tech-2025-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N55MCFYV2VPULPCHLI6OSLYGRM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 17:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普特使称，如果达成和平协议，美国公司可在俄罗斯开展业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的特使史蒂夫-威特科夫（Steve Witkoff）周日表示，如果俄乌战争达成和平协议，美国公司有望在俄罗斯开展业务。【原文：President Donald Trump's special envoy Steve Witkoff said on Sunday that there would be an expectation that U.S. firms may do business in Russia in the event of a peace deal in the Russia-Ukraine war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-envoy-says-us-firms-may-do-business-russia-case-peace-deal-2025-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKH3HNRVZNPQZCASNRIL47AEME</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:39:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡塔尔与 Scale AI 签订协议，利用人工智能提升政府服务水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[Scale AI 公司的一位高管周日告诉路透社，卡塔尔政府已与人工智能数据公司 Scale AI 签署了一份为期五年的协议，将部署人工智能驱动的工具和培训，以推动改善这个海湾阿拉伯国家的政府服务。【原文：Qatar's government has signed a five-year deal with AI data company Scale AI to deploy AI-powered tools and training in a push to improve government services in the Gulf Arab state, a senior Scale AI executive told Reuters on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qatar-signs-deal-with-scale-ai-use-ai-boost-government-services-2025-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DD26YA3QKZJFFAVQOHXZ2ND3LQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:34:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚对 Telegram 延迟回答虐待儿童和恐怖问题处以罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚网络安全监管机构周一对消息平台 Telegram 处以约 100 万澳元（64 万美元）的罚款，原因是该公司迟迟没有回答有关该应用为防止虐待儿童和暴力极端主义材料传播而采取的措施的问题。【原文：Australia's online safety regulator on Monday fined messaging platform Telegram about A$1 million ($640,000) for its delay in answering questions about measures the app took to prevent the spread of child abuse and violent extremist material.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-fines-telegram-delay-answering-child-abuse-terror-questions-2025-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OD2ACLTPHVMENOKTRRKFRM36Y4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:08:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国 "非常接近 "与乌克兰达成矿产协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六表示，作为结束乌克兰战争努力的一部分，美国正与乌克兰就分享乌克兰矿产收入达成一项协议。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Saturday the United States is close an agreement with Ukraine on sharing revenue from Ukrainian minerals as part of efforts to end the Ukraine war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-us-pretty-close-minerals-deal-with-ukraine-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQV2MK7DPRK2NHGFCB2AXPPQBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 20:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司从年度报告中删除多样性和包容性内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周六加入了越来越多的美国公司的行列，这些公司公开改变了讨论其对多元化和包容性承诺的方式。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway on Saturday joined a growing list of American companies to publicly change their approach to discussing their commitment to diversity and inclusion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/berkshire-hathaway-removes-diversity-inclusion-annual-report-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2F2PSOGHWZP3LJK75ZFKZTURYY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 19:55:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示经济伙伴关系将保护乌克兰人和美国纳税人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）在周六为《金融时报》撰写的一篇评论文章中写道，乌克兰和美国之间的经济伙伴关系将使两国受益。【原文：An economic partnership between Ukraine and the U.S. would benefit both countries, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent wrote in an opinion piece for the Financial Times on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bessent-says-economic-partnership-will-protect-ukrainians-us-taxpayers-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3W3NEXMR2RJUTKTXOIINJO7SKA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 18:54:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[草案显示欧盟将缩减企业可持续发展规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份文件草案显示，欧盟委员会计划减少面临欧盟可持续发展报告要求的公司数量，这是其减少企业繁文缛节举措的一部分。【原文：The European Commission plans to cut back the number of companies facing EU sustainability reporting requirements, as part of its drive to cut red tape for businesses, a draft document seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/eu-pare-back-sustainability-rules-companies-draft-shows-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBGCSWPTAZOKTKERMIEKAP2OFU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 18:31:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马表示将重新考虑在英国生产电动迷你车的时间安排]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝马公司周六表示，正在重新考虑在英国生产全电动迷你汽车的时间表，理由是该行业面临着不确定性。【原文：BMW said on Saturday it is rethinking its timetable for manufacturing all-electric Mini cars in Britain, citing uncertainties facing the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-says-it-will-review-timing-electric-mini-production-uk-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZAGH3WWRNKBHOIG2GUBTXKAVU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 17:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔将加大对日本贸易公司的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）周六表示，他的企业集团伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）可能会增持其持有的五家日本贸易公司的股份。【原文：Warren Buffett said on Saturday that his conglomerate Berkshire Hathaway will likely increase its ownership in the five Japanese trading houses it holds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/berkshire-boost-investments-japanese-trading-houses-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGQW2UNZYRKABCVTENIZMX4H3E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 17:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰副总理称波兰为乌克兰订购星链支付费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰周六表示，尽管有消息称美国可能会考虑切断乌克兰对卫星互联网系统的使用，但波兰一直在为乌克兰的星链订购支付费用，并将继续这样做。【原文：Poland said on Saturday it has been paying for Ukraine's Starlink subscription and will continue to do so despite sources saying the United States could consider cutting Ukraine's access to the satellite internet system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/poland-is-paying-ukraines-starlink-subscription-its-deputy-pm-says-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KGSXGUT2BJ33D7BZ6I7UABCMU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 16:56:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特称美国应 "明智消费"，计划增加对日本的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[94 岁高龄的巴菲特在年度信函中也承认了自己的高龄，他告诉股东们，他现在使用拐杖，在 5 月份的伯克希尔年度会议上回答股东们问题的时间会减少。【原文：The 94-year-old Buffett also acknowledged his advanced age in his annual letter, telling shareholders he now uses a cane and will spend less time fielding their questions at Berkshire's annual meeting in May.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/warren-buffett-says-us-should-spend-wisely-plans-increase-investment-japan-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LD6VBP7OLJOPDNYRIIDKK3UEQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴菲特的伯克希尔公司因保险和投资实现创纪录利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周六公布了连续第三个创纪录的年度营业利润，这主要得益于其保险业务承保盈利和投资收益的大幅增长。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway on Saturday posted its third straight record annual operating profit, bolstered by large increases in underwriting earnings and investment income in its insurance businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/buffetts-berkshire-posts-record-profit-insurance-investments-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7SJL3QS65JV5IMNQSCRDGM4LQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 13:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，Stellantis公司因后视摄像头图像问题召回27354辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周六表示，由于后视摄像头图像无法显示，Stellantis公司将在美国召回27354辆玛莎拉蒂汽车。【原文：Stellantis is recalling 27,354 Maserati vehicles in the U.S over concerns of a rearview camera image that does not display, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-recalls-27354-us-vehicles-over-rearview-camera-image-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XTVSONUMJM7NNJ5J533ABP2PA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 10:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[媒体称 Seven & i Holdings 选择贝恩作为资产出售的首选买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体周六报道，7-Eleven 连锁便利店运营商日本 Seven &amp; i 控股公司已选择贝恩资本作为其非核心资产股份的首选买家。【原文：Japan's Seven &amp; i Holdings , operator of the 7-Eleven convenience store chain, has picked Bain Capital as its preferred buyer for a stake of its non-core assets, local media reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/seven-i-holdings-picks-bain-preferred-buyer-asset-sale-media-say-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVPJXX3CJZPBXKV5C3TI7BZ4RQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 10:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行维勒鲁瓦重申今年夏天存款利率可能达到 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国央行行长兼欧洲央行决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）在周六发表的一篇访谈中表示，欧洲央行可能在今年夏天之前将存款利率下调至 2%。【原文：The European Central Bank could cut its deposit rate down to 2% by this summer, said Bank of France head and ECB policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau in an interview published on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecbs-villeroy-reaffirms-deposit-rates-could-be-2-by-this-summer-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFVD57YAKRJEPORDWHOZWPQTZA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 07:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示波音首席航空安全官即将退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份备忘录，波音公司首席航空航天安全官迈克-德莱尼（Mike Delaney）将于今年晚些时候退休。【原文：Boeing's chief aerospace safety officer, Mike Delaney, will retire later this year, according to memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-chief-aerospace-safety-officer-retire-air-current-editor-says-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4GZQO6SFVOUDIPAFQEYYEKVZA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西法官在 "审查 "纠纷后暂停 Rumble 平台运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西最高法院周五以美国视频共享平台 Rumble 未遵守法院命令为由，下令暂停其在巴西的业务，这与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 公司去年面临的情况类似。【原文：Brazil's Supreme Court on Friday ordered the suspension of U.S. video-sharing platform Rumble in the country, citing its failure to comply with court orders, in a similar path to the one faced by Elon Musk's X last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-supreme-court-orders-rumble-suspension-country-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFNNQW7DRRJ4VP6OBICI3KCOVI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，特朗普征收 10%的石油关税可能导致外国生产商每年损失 100 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）周五表示，由于替代买家和加工能力有限，加拿大和拉丁美洲的重质原油仍然依赖于美国炼油厂，因此拟议中的 10%美国石油关税可能会使外国生产商每年损失 100 亿美元。【原文：Goldman Sachs said on Friday a proposed 10% U.S. oil tariff could cost foreign producers $10 billion per year, as Canadian and Latin American heavy crudes remain reliant on U.S. refiners due to limited alternative buyers and processing capabilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-10-oil-tariff-could-cost-foreign-producers-10-billion-annually-goldman-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKLHON545FPS5OYYRDRI3DUF7Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:28:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称美国可能因矿产问题切断乌克兰使用星链互联网服务的渠道]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，美国谈判代表向基辅施压，要求乌克兰获得关键矿产，并提出了切断该国使用埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）重要的星链（Starlink）卫星互联网系统的可能性。【原文：U.S. negotiators pressing Kyiv for access to Ukraine's critical minerals have raised the possibility of cutting the country's access to Elon Musk's vital Starlink satellite internet system, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-could-cut-ukraines-access-starlink-internet-services-over-minerals-say-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEJUIMHFYJLUHIMET7UXML3QEA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年利润水平较低，CVS 削减奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 周五表示，由于去年利润水平较低，该公司已经削减了部分员工的奖金，因为这家医疗保健集团正在努力应对其医疗保险计划成本上升的问题。【原文：CVS Health said on Friday it has cut bonuses for some employees because of its low profit levels last year, as the healthcare conglomerate grapples with higher costs across its Medicare plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-cuts-bonuses-after-low-profit-levels-2024-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZSMOP3LQRM4VLQBBVBXRS6JQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普的领导下，消费者监督机构撤销了对在线贷款机构的起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）已着手废除美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau），该局周五向法院表示，将撤销对在线借贷平台 Solo Funds 的诉讼，该机构此前曾指控 Solo Funds 在贷款成本方面欺骗借款人。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, which President Donald Trump has moved to abolish, told a court on Friday it was dropping a lawsuit against the online lending platform Solo Funds, which the agency had earlier accused of deceiving borrowers about the cost of loans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/under-trump-consumer-watchdog-drops-case-against-online-lender-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSJUVARTARJNPGBWSUAMXC3WBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称考虑将美国邮政局与商务部合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周五表示，他正在考虑将美国邮政局与美国商务部合并，民主党人称此举将违反联邦法律。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday he was considering merging the U.S. Postal Service with the U.S. Commerce Department, a move Democrats said would violate federal law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-is-considering-merging-us-postal-service-with-commerce-department-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TL62IISZIFOPXKWPOZVVQ6OARM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普媒体提议在佛罗里达州重新注册公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的特朗普媒体&amp; 科技集团（Trump Media &amp; Technology Group）周五表示，将在 4 月底举行的年会上提议在佛罗里达州重新注册公司。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's Trump Media &amp; Technology Group said on Friday it will propose reincorporating the company in Florida at its annual meeting in late April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-media-propose-reincorporation-florida-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVMYNHJZYNILTKXTNF35GMEU4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将对数字税征收报复性关税，可能在周五实施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他将签署一份备忘录，对向美国科技公司征收数字服务税的国家征收关税。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday that he would sign a memorandum to impose tariffs on countries that levy digital service taxes on U.S. technology companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-impose-retaliatory-tariffs-digital-taxes-may-come-friday-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYXQTS6AHBO43HB32T5BWZFLGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街巨头摩根士丹利在年度报告中更加强调多元化]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）在周五发布的最新年度报告中淡化了对多元化的强调，这表明随着企业适应唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统政府领导下不断变化的现实，摩根士丹利正在进行重新调整。【原文：Morgan Stanley toned down its emphasis on diversity in its latest annual report published on Friday, signaling a recalibration as businesses adapt to a changing reality under President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-giant-morgan-stanley-eases-diversity-emphasis-annual-report-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCC6H5JPLBNJZF2SIUAKPKBOJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:21:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受经济和关税担忧影响，华尔街运输类股受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于投资者对疲软的经济数据做出反应并担心关税问题，运输类股票大幅反转，经济风向标道琼斯运输平均指数下跌超过2.6%，创下自12月18日以来的最大单日跌幅，也是连续第三次下跌。【原文：Transportation stocks went sharply in reverse on Friday with the economic bellwether Dow Jones Transport average index falling more than 2.6% in its steepest daily loss since December 18 and its third consecutive decline, as investors reacted to weak economic readings and worried about tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/transport-stocks-take-hit-wall-street-economic-tariff-fears-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTXFQIRE5JIV5FQXJXBGEIN5ZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富兰克林邓普顿申请 Solana ETF，加密货币的兴趣已超越比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[富兰克林邓普顿公司（Franklin Templeton）周五申请了一只交易所交易基金，该基金将跟踪索拉纳的现货价格，这反映出资产管理公司对从比特币以外的加密货币的受欢迎程度中获利的兴趣日益浓厚。【原文：Franklin Templeton filed for an exchange-traded fund on Friday that will track the spot price of Solana , reflecting the growing interest among asset managers to profit from the popularity of cryptocurrencies beyond bitcoin .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/franklin-templeton-files-solana-etf-crypto-interest-expands-beyond-bitcoin-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THA2ZAPXA5JBVGOXGNTTKOOE4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫官员称，特朗普将利用外国投资委员会限制中国在战略领域的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统将于周五签署一份备忘录，指示美国外国投资委员会限制中国在战略领域的投资。【原文：President Donald Trump will sign a memorandum on Friday that will direct the Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States to restrict Chinese investments in strategic areas, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-use-cfius-restrict-chinese-investments-strategic-areas-white-house-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR3VTWQIKNLCZOLWLFUDNK22KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储暂停量化宽松政策，财政部债务计划或为美债带来短暂宽松]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储缩减资产负债表的速度可能放缓，财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）也保证不会立即增加长期债务，这些都能在短期内缓解债券市场对财政问题的担忧。【原文：A potential slowdown of the Federal Reserve's balance sheet drawdown and Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent's assurance against imminent long-term debt hikes could offer relief in the near term to bond market jitters as fiscal concerns linger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-qt-pause-treasurys-debt-plans-may-offer-fleeting-relief-us-bonds-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6AF4A5INROG7FXG7M3RFDSMUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:12:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>