<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:39:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:39:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[PayPal 和 Venmo 用户将提前使用 Perplexity 的 Comet AI 浏览器]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字支付公司Perplexity周三表示，美国和部分全球市场的贝宝（PayPal）和Venmo用户将通过为期12个月的Pro订阅试用，提前获得Perplexity新推出的人工智能Comet浏览器。【原文：PayPal and Venmo users in the U.S. and some global markets will receive early access to Perplexity's new AI-powered Comet browser through a 12-month trial of the startup's Pro subscription, the digital payments company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/paypal-venmo-users-gain-early-access-perplexitys-comet-ai-browser-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJLINGGWPVJRVPDUYAU6Q3F5Z4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SoFi 推出以人工智能为主题的新 ETF，质疑声与日俱增]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，SoFi Technologies 公司近两年来首次推出交易所交易基金，押注零售投资领域最热门的人工智能。【原文：SoFi Technologies jumped back into the exchange-traded fund business on Wednesday with its first launch in nearly two years, betting on artificial intelligence, the hottest theme in retail investing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sofi-launches-new-ai-themed-etf-skepticism-grows-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4IZ67TZSVNBFES4TY6ZCODTOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨莱姆称政策到位，警告就业市场风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆周三表示，鉴于当前的经济数据，美国央行的货币政策正处于正确的位置。【原文：St. Louis Federal Reserve President Alberto Musalem said on Wednesday the U.S. central bank's monetary policy is in the right place given current economic data, in remarks that did not give a clear signal whether he supports an interest rate cut later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-musalem-says-policy-right-place-warns-job-market-risks-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAENKKTBHJL6RB47CBP6SLG2XM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融犯罪监察机构呼吁各国对空壳公司作出澄清]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球金融犯罪监察机构负责人呼吁各国公开空壳公司的使用情况，称其为犯罪分子的 "逃亡之车"，并表示这一问题将成为新一轮国家评估的关键部分。【原文：The head of the global financial crime watchdog has called on countries to come clean on the use of shell companies, calling them the "getaway car" for criminals, and said the problem would be a key part of a new round of national assessments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/financial-crime-watchdog-calls-countries-come-clean-shell-companies-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53SDAYD2YVOUVC2P54UE6X2OMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列 Cato Networks 收购 Aim Security，再融资 5000 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列网络安全公司 Cato Networks 周三表示，它将收购网络初创公司 Aim Security，这是该公司有史以来的首次收购，并将在一轮私人融资中再筹集 5000 万美元。【原文：Israeli cyber security firm Cato Networks said on Wednesday it was buying cyber startup Aim Security, its first ever acquisition, and raising another $50 million in a private funding round.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israels-cato-networks-buys-aim-security-raises-another-50-million-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4OXTKOGWJIFDFEECPBXJUMVEE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行调查显示，美国工人的财务压力越来越大]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行的一项调查显示，美国工人对不断增加的个人债务和财务健康状况的压力越来越大。【原文：U.S. workers are becoming more stressed about their rising personal debts and financial health, a Bank of America survey showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-workers-are-becoming-more-stressed-about-finances-bofa-survey-shows-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDTZR2T26FPWHJ3OR3JCXH2OTE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:12:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ID.me 在最新融资中估值突破 20 亿美元，推动打击人工智能驱动的欺诈行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[ID.me 周三表示，它在最新一轮融资中筹集了 3.4 亿美元，加上投资公司 Ribbit Capital 主导的信贷融资，数字身份钱包的估值超过 20 亿美元。【原文：ID.me said on Wednesday it had raised $340 million across its latest funding round, combined with a credit facility, led by investment firm Ribbit Capital, valuing the digital identity wallet at over $2 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/idme-tops-2-billion-valuation-latest-fundraise-amid-push-combat-ai-driven-fraud-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBPIH34GUBL6HO3YTYVJAE5ZSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Bancorp 恢复机构比特币托管服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（U.S. Bancorp）在暂停比特币托管服务三年多之后，将重新启动比特币托管服务，因为特朗普政府支持加密货币的姿态鼓励传统金融机构深入研究数字资产。【原文：U.S. Bancorp is restarting its bitcoin custody service after a more than three-year pause, as the Trump administration's pro-crypto posture has encouraged traditional financial institutions to delve deeper into digital assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-bancorp-revives-institutional-bitcoin-custody-service-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGCX5RLQPZKKRN2VMNJGCIHZWI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芬兰 IQM 量子计算机公司在新一轮融资中募集 3.2 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于芬兰的 IQM 量子计算机公司周三表示，该公司在新一轮融资中筹集了 3.2 亿美元，欧洲正努力跟上美国在该领域的全球领导者的步伐。【原文：Finnish-headquartered company IQM Quantum Computers has raised $320 million in a new funding round, the company said on Wednesday, as Europe tries to keep pace with global leaders in the field from the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/finlands-iqm-quantum-computers-raises-320-million-new-funding-round-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SDNFN7KAZOCZHIKH2EXDBTCXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技股盈利强劲，汇丰银行上调标普 500 指数年底目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行将 S&amp;P 500 指数的年末预期从 6400 点上调至 6500 点，理由是第二季度盈利强于预期，宏观形势也很有弹性，科技和金融行业推动了增长势头。【原文：HSBC raised its year-end S&amp;P 500 forecast to 6,500 from 6,400, citing stronger-than-expected Q2 earnings and resilient macro conditions, with tech and financials driving momentum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hsbc-lifts-sp-500-year-end-target-strong-tech-earnings-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IB5UHXZJZFNFLPFJFPNXB4PYBY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[努文与猎人角和淡马锡合作推动私人信贷发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资管理公司纽维恩（Nuveen）的私人债务部门周三表示，该公司已与猎人点资本（Hunter Point Capital）和淡马锡（Temasek）建立了合作伙伴关系，从而进一步推动其进入快速增长的企业融资市场。【原文：Investment manager Nuveen's private debt arm has partnered with Hunter Point Capital and Temasek, the company said on Wednesday, as it furthers its push into the fast-growing slice of corporate financing market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nuveen-partners-with-hunter-point-temasek-private-credit-push-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIZ4ARWPDBNJ3JUVZBUCMD4RNE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:42:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HappyRobot 融资 4400 万美元，为货运运营商拓展人工智能代理业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[HappyRobot是一家人工智能初创公司，为货运运营商提供自动化通信服务，包括费率谈判和预约，该公司在Base10 Partners领投的一轮融资中筹集了4400万美元。【原文：HappyRobot, an artificial intelligence startup that automates communications including rate negotiation and appointment booking for freight operators, has raised $44 million in a funding round led by Base10 Partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/happyrobot-raises-44-million-expand-ai-agents-freight-operators-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZGVTCZDONIM5EGJH2YYO5RZRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:35:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰国际集团（ING）称，欧元全球地位提升的早期迹象正在显现]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰国际集团（ING）在周三发表的一份报告中说，有早期证据表明，债券发行人和投资者正在更多地利用欧元，以纪念欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）表示欧元可能成为一种可行的美元替代货币的 100 天。【原文：There is early evidence that bond issuers and investors are making greater use of the euro, ING said in a report published on Wednesday to mark 100 days since ECB chief Christine Lagarde said the euro could become a viable dollar alternative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/early-signs-emerging-euros-beefed-up-global-status-ing-says-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJ7MQJ4TX5OUPJPTXEFAJJCAKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:26:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储援助受质疑，敦促各国央行汇集美元储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家颇具影响力的智库负责人表示，鉴于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的攻击无法保证美联储的帮助，欧洲中央银行及其全球同行应集中储备美元流动性。【原文：The European Central Bank and its peers around the world should pool their reserves for U.S. dollar liquidity as Federal Reserve help cannot be guaranteed given President Donald Trump's attacks, the head of an influential think tank said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/central-banks-urged-pool-dollar-reserves-fed-help-questioned-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IT5IJXGHBNIZ3FAOHZQNNICUNQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税压力和需求放缓的影响，金宝公司对 2026 财年的预测不高]]></title><description><![CDATA[受零食和即食餐需求疲软以及关税导致成本上升的影响，金宝公司周三预计全年销售利润低于华尔街预期。【原文：Campbell's Co forecast annual sales profit below Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, pressured by weak demand for snacks and ready-to-eat meals as well as higher costs from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/campbells-forecasts-muted-fiscal-2026-tariff-pressures-slow-demand-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CS7QHRSFENOD3KZOIJUU43QWQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[怡安将在 27 亿美元的交易中剥离 NFP 大部分财富管理业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Aon 周三表示，将把 NFP 财富业务的大部分出售给私募股权公司 Madison Dearborn Partners，交易价值约为 27 亿美元。【原文：Aon said on Wednesday it will sell the majority of NFP's wealth business to private equity firm Madison Dearborn Partners in a deal valued at about $2.7 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/aon-divest-majority-nfps-wealth-business-27-billion-deal-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUGAGJF37JO7JJ4R5DF4CMCEIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:09:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于关税和定价压力，电动汽车制造商 Polestar 季度亏损扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 周三公布第二季度亏损扩大，原因是美国关税和不断加剧的价格压力导致其旗舰车型 Polestar 3 计提减值费用。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Polestar reported a wider loss for the second quarter on Wednesday, after U.S. tariffs and intensifying price pressure led to an impairment charge of its flagship model, Polestar 3.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestar-posts-wider-quarterly-loss-tariffs-pricing-pressure-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPG42FRTCNIKVIEX5PQRVFSHPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅西百货上调年度预期，扭亏为盈初见成效]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅西百货公司（Macy's）周三上调了年度销售额和利润预期，这得益于包括布鲁明戴尔百货公司（Bloomingdale's）和蓝水星连锁店（Bluemercury）在内的各品牌需求的恢复，该零售商的扭亏为盈计划正在成形。【原文：Macy's raised its annual sales and profit forecasts on Wednesday, helped by resilient demand across banners including Bloomingdale's and Bluemercury chains as the retailer's turnaround plan takes shape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/macys-lifts-annual-forecasts-turnaround-efforts-start-paying-off-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJFLYWYXVJKABHROFQGXNLJ5X4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标美国长期债券收益率再次测试 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRK3T5RPOZIU7O5XEIGAPSTD6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:52:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息和对独立性的怀疑使美元持续承压：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三对外汇策略师进行的一项调查显示，由于市场参与者在思考美联储未来的独立性以及美联储可能还会进行多少次降息，未来几个月美元将走软。【原文：The U.S. dollar will weaken over coming months as market participants ponder the Federal Reserve's future independence and how many more rate cuts it may deliver, a Reuters survey of foreign exchange strategists showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-rate-cuts-doubts-over-independence-keep-us-dollar-under-pressure-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POP73LPKARKEXOAZBL5CAHHETE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元树公司上调年度目标，因廉价商品需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dollar Tree 周三上调了年度销售额和利润预期，原因是越来越多不同收入类别的美国人在其门店购买更便宜的食品杂货、服装和家居装饰用品。【原文：Dollar Tree raised its annual sales and profit forecasts on Wednesday as more Americans across income categories shop for cheaper groceries, apparel and home decor items at its stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dollar-tree-raises-annual-targets-resilient-demand-cheaper-goods-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUDYYW4HK5K5NKDPI3CV5676ZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公交技术公司 Via Transportation 在美国 IPO 的目标估值高达 35 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[公交技术制造商 Via Transportation 公司周三表示，其首次公开募股的目标估值高达 35 亿美元，加入了今年秋季在美国交易所上市的公司行列。【原文：Transit technology maker Via Transportation said on Wednesday it was targeting a valuation of up to $3.50 billion in its initial public offering, joining a wave of companies aiming to list their shares on U.S. exchanges this fall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/transit-tech-firm-via-transportation-targets-up-35-billion-valuation-us-ipo-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SROKKA6T3NMHDNRGFXETAFNDDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:37:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海王保险申请在美国上市，IPO窗口重新开启]]></title><description><![CDATA[洪水保险供应商海王星公司周三提交了美国首次公开募股申请，成为利用投资者对新股的新需求的最新一家公司。【原文：Flood insurance provider Neptune filed for a U.S. initial public offering on Wednesday, becoming the latest company to tap into renewed investor demand for new stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/neptune-insurance-files-us-listing-ipo-window-reopens-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5HA3V2U6ZMWTPTUIJ25ZTUTNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:32:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官将听取对允许波音公司避免因坠机事件被起诉的协议的反对意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，一名美国法官将就是否批准司法部与波音公司达成的一项协议举行听证会，该协议允许波音公司避免因两起造成 346 人死亡的 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故而被起诉。【原文：A U.S. judge on Wednesday will hold a hearing on whether to approve a deal between the Justice Department and Boeing that allows the planemaker to avoid prosecution on a charge stemming from two fatal 737 MAX plane crashes that killed 346 people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-judge-hear-objections-deal-that-allows-boeing-avoid-prosecution-over-crashes-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFIAMJQ6XBID5FKZORIHF3CBPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:06:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌的人工智能竞争对手从数据共享令中获益，但科技巨头远未溃败]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二的一项反垄断裁决命令 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司与竞争对手共享其宝贵的搜索数据，这将使一批新兴的人工智能公司从中获益。【原文：A rising group of artificial intelligence companies stand to gain from an antitrust ruling on Tuesday that ordered Alphabet's Google to share its invaluable search data with competitors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/googles-ai-rivals-get-boost-data-sharing-order-tech-giant-far-routed-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEZSY7OFVFNGBIOPNTL7KFYSSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将请求最高法院挽救关税，但面临棘手的法律问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在下级法院两次受挫后，即将要求保守派占多数的最高法院确认其广泛的紧急关税措施有效，但他的政府在推进后备计划时将面临棘手的法律问题。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is set to imminently ask the conservative-majority Supreme Court to validate his broad emergency tariffs after two setbacks at lower courts, but will face tough legal questions as his administration presses ahead with backup plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-ask-supreme-court-save-tariffs-faces-tough-legal-questions-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXW23NF56JNBVAW7IBDJ3B5QNI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元匮乏，委内瑞拉货币交易所转向加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[十几位消息人士称，由于美国对石油出口的限制减少了可用的外汇，委内瑞拉政府正在慢慢允许私营部门在货币兑换中使用与美元挂钩的加密货币。【原文：Venezuela's government is slowly allowing the use of dollar-tied cryptocurrencies in currency exchanges for the private sector, a dozen sources said, as U.S. restrictions on oil exports reduce available foreign currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/with-dollars-scarce-venezuela-currency-exchanges-turn-crypto-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CI5XPJJJVBIB7PMJJTJBBCTE6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[边疆航空公司高管称，该公司的新福利以竞争对手的忠诚会员为目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[据超低成本航空公司边疆航空公司（Frontier Airlines）的一位高层管理人员称，该公司正试图通过提供新的旅行奖励措施来吸引其他航空公司的高端乘客，因为他们可能会对目前的忠诚度福利感到不满。【原文：Frontier Airlines is seeking to lure premium flyers of other airlines, who may feel dissatisfied with their current loyalty perks, by offering new travel incentives, according to a top executive of the ultra-low-cost carrier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frontier-airlines-new-perks-target-loyalty-members-rivals-exec-says-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTOPGIKDAFPBBF3QDGWNNMFHKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:02:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件显示，美国交易公司简街对印度市场监管机构提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社查阅的一份案件文件，简街公司周三对印度市场监管机构提起诉讼，指控这家美国高频交易巨头操纵市场。【原文：Jane Street on Wednesday filed a case against India's markets regulator which has accused the U.S. high-frequency trading giant of market manipulation, according to a case document reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-trading-firm-jane-street-files-case-against-india-markets-regulator-document-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSZDX6VYVJPWDAKMVRWYFVLGWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:55:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zalando 将对欧盟法院驳回其挑战欧盟技术规则的裁决提起上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的在线零售公司 Zalando 周三表示，将对欧盟法院驳回其对具有里程碑意义的欧盟技术规则的挑战的裁决提起上诉。【原文：Zalando will appeal an EU court ruling dismissing its challenge against landmark EU tech rules, Europe's biggest online retail company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/zalando-appeal-eu-court-ruling-rejecting-its-challenge-against-eu-tech-rules-2025-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPRTWWCV6NKERPHUQLGSR7BIYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:55:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>