<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:38:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:38:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[澳新银行调查显示，新西兰商业信心达到30年来的最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳新银行（ANZ Bank）周五的一项调查显示，新西兰12月份的商业信心指数飙升至30年来的最高水平，前瞻性活动指标再次回升，部分指标达到数十年来的新高。【原文：New Zealand's business confidence surged in December to hit its highest level in 30 years, with forward-looking activity indicators lifting again with some reaching multi-decade highs, an ANZ Bank survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-business-confidence-hits-highest-level-30-years-anz-survey-shows-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PHQ4MZILJM4RJ2Y6UPQ4VU2TI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cannabis companies face hurdles accessing big banks despite reclassification, experts say]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump's move to relax marijuana regulations could ease some burden for cannabis companies, but will likely keep doors to access capital from big banks closed, experts said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/cannabis-companies-face-hurdles-accessing-big-banks-despite-reclassification-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATO67UKGRJKZTM2EJTLBYH32WI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japan's core inflation steady in November, stays above BOJ target]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's core consumer prices rose 3.0% in November from a year earlier, data showed on Friday, staying above the central bank's 2% target for the 44th straight month.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-core-inflation-steady-november-stays-above-boj-target-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4T7OPKEXVJIHIAMJRQXRYF6VQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wanxiang to pay $53 million to resolve US probe into imported Chinese auto parts, DOJ says]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，已与中国汽车零部件供应商万向集团的美国分公司就五年内对从中国进口的轮毂总成和其他零部件征收进口关税一事达成和解。【原文：The Justice Department said Thursday it had reached a settlement with the U.S. arm of Chinese auto parts supplier Wanxiang over import tariffs owed on wheel hub assemblies and other parts imported from China over a five-year period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/wanxiang-pay-53-million-resolve-us-probe-into-imported-chinese-auto-parts-doj-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6PCOQR76BMV7LXKS7ZM6VFIPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:21:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑莓因网络安全需求上调年度收入预期下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[黑莓公司（BlackBerry）周四上调了 2026 财年收入预期的下限，表明随着企业加大支出以应对日益复杂的网络攻击，对其网络安全软件的需求强劲。【原文：BlackBerry on Thursday raised the lower end of its fiscal 2026 revenue forecast, signalling strong demand for its cybersecurity software as companies ramp up spending to counter increasingly sophisticated cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackberry-lifts-lower-end-annual-revenue-forecast-cybersecurity-demand-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKCUZJMDBFIWHK2KTGJTS3HINM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦监督员报告后，UAW 总裁办公室主任将离开工会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车工人联合会（UAW）的一位重要战略家和工会 2023 年汽车厂罢工的策划者即将离开该工会组织，因为负责监督 UAW 的联邦监督员在一份报告中认为他
 
 他参与了一场不当解除另一位工会领导人职务的运动。【原文：A key United Auto Workers strategist and architect of the union’s 2023 auto-factory strike is leaving the labor group, after a report by the federal monitor overseeing the UAW concluded that he
 
 was part of a campaign to improperly remove duties from another union leader.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/uaw-presidents-chief-staff-leave-union-following-federal-monitor-report-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYDDX4PSBJKN3ARJKH2AWNVS44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok signs deal to sell US unit to American investor-led venture]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份 TikTok 首席执行官的备忘录，字节跳动旗下的 TikTok 已签署协议，将其美国实体出售给一家由美国投资者控制的合资企业。【原文：ByteDance's TikTok has signed a deal to sell its U.S. entity to a joint venture controlled by American investors, according to a memo from TikTok CEO seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/american-investor-consortium-acquire-tiktok-us-entity-axios-reports-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2RA7QD745MLRNVGHPRSIBM6OI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚桑托斯公司任命内部人士拉克兰-哈里斯为财务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[Santos said on Friday it has appointed insider Lachlan Harris as its CFO, as the Australian gas producer navigates a transition period tied to its key Barossa and Pikka projects.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-santos-names-insider-lachlan-harris-finance-boss-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2OK6GE4NJPAXH3DYTRXKTILS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国主要交易所将于 12 月 24 日和 26 日继续营业]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令联邦政府在12月24日和12月26日两天关闭数小时后，美国主要证券交易所周四表示，它们将在这两天如期开市。【原文：Major U.S. stock exchanges said on Thursday they will remain open as scheduled on December 24 and December 26, hours after President Donald Trump ordered the federal government to be closed on those days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nyse-says-stock-market-remain-open-dec-24-dec-26-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AULCCDQ3IFIG5IAY6VZ3SVUYEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trading Day: Three cheers for 'whacky' inflation]]></title><description><![CDATA[这将是本年度最后一期定期 "交易日 "通讯。感谢您的支持和反馈，我们期待 2026 年同样精彩纷呈。正常服务将于 1 月 5 日星期一恢复。节日快乐【原文：This will be the last regular 'Trading Day' newsletter of the year. Thank you for all your support and feedback, and we look forward to an equally eventful and rewarding 2026. Normal service will be resumed on Monday, January 5. Happy holidays.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDO4XNYMNJNK5KDC3HG5GPXXU4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将把利率上调至 30 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五将把利率上调至三十年来的最高点，并表示准备在明年以后进一步加息，这凸显了日本央行坚信持续的工资增长将使通胀率持久地保持在2%的目标附近。【原文：The Bank of Japan is set to raise interest rates on Friday to a three-decade high and signal its readiness to eye further hikes beyond next year, underscoring its conviction that sustained wage gains will keep inflation durably around its 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bank-japan-set-raise-interest-rates-30-year-high-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6P2C3IN3VNJTNDO3BQ4AK6V344</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比在接受福克斯财经采访时对最新通胀数据表示欢迎，并称可能会有更多降息举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago President Austan Goolsbee said on Thursday “there’s a lot to like” in the latest consumer price index data, and if it can be sustained, it will help open the door for more interest rate cuts next year.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-goolsbee-fox-business-interview-welcomes-latest-inflation-data-says-more-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AEH6YZMKNIQRBC3STSPQT2HGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:50:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Starbucks supplier Cuisine Solutions hires Morgan Stanley and Rothschild for potential sale, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[食品公司 Cuisine Solutions 为星巴克（Starbucks）生产鸡蛋饼，为好市多（Costco）生产草饲西冷牛肉，据熟悉内情的人士透露，该公司已聘请投资银行探讨明年的出售事宜，这家家族式私营公司的估值可能超过 20 亿美元。【原文：Food company Cuisine Solutions, which makes egg bites for Starbucks and sous vide grass-fed beef sirloin for Costco , has hired investment banks to explore a sale next year that could value the private, family-owned company at over $2 billion, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/starbucks-supplier-cuisine-solutions-hires-morgan-stanley-rothschild-potential-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4H3QTMBL5N6ZHVSDW7EJ2LPR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克利润率下滑为第二季度收入增长蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司周四的季度收入超过了华尔街的预期，但关税和这家运动服装巨头以折扣方式清理陈旧库存的努力损害了利润率。【原文：Nike on Thursday edged past Wall Street expectations for quarterly revenue, but tariffs and the sportswear giant's efforts to clear out aged inventory at discounts hurt margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nike-edges-past-quarterly-revenue-expectations-resilient-demand-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RFL3423EVNGZKHL4GZHFEBIQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递发布乐观季度业绩，上调 2026 年利润预期下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递周四公布的第二季度利润和收入均高于华尔街预期，并上调了全年盈利展望的下限，原因是旺季定价行动和成本削减努力帮助抵消了货运量的疲软。【原文：FedEx posted second-quarter profit and revenue above Wall Street's estimates on Thursday and lifted the low end of its full-year earnings outlook, as peak-season pricing actions and cost-cutting efforts helped offset softer shipment volumes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fedex-posts-higher-quarterly-results-raises-low-end-full-year-profit-forecast-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJYL2PJD7VJXHP5SAES4K5UXBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，墨西哥石油公司生产部门负责人将在未来几天内下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexico's state oil company Pemex is preparing to replace the head of its exploration and production arm, just months after he returned to the post, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters, as the company struggles to stem a decline in crude output.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/head-pemexs-production-arm-step-down-coming-days-sources-say-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMPV2LQGRJOOPCGLIKMIQQ33LA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资经理被控在 Anduril 上市前欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[A New York investment manager has been indicted for allegedly defrauding millions of dollars from investors in a sham pre-IPO scheme tied to U.S. drone-maker Anduril Industries, highlighting the risk of fraud as private tech firms grow more prominent and valuable.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-investment-manager-charged-with-anduril-pre-ipo-fraud-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JV4WHBCTTJN2JNZB4P2JTDZF54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:54:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Finalists for top Fed job want to cut rates, but diverge from there]]></title><description><![CDATA[到目前为止，唐纳德-特朗普总统面试过的三位候选人都希望在明年 5 月接替美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔，但他们在货币政策的其他方面存在分歧，而且背景各不相同。【原文：The three candidates interviewed by President Donald Trump so far to replace Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell next May share a desire to cut interest rates, but diverge on other aspects of monetary policy and come from different backgrounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/finalists-top-fed-job-want-cut-rates-diverge-there-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YACHDOHMERMW7CCYQ43DL3VAQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Energy Department taps Big Tech for AI-powered research push]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部周四表示，它已与包括微软、谷歌和 Nvidia 等科技巨头在内的 24 家组织签署了协议，以推进创世任务。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy said on Thursday it has signed agreements with 24 organizations, including tech giants such as Microsoft , Google and Nvidia , to advance the Genesis Mission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-energy-department-taps-big-tech-ai-powered-research-push-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTI4GTDKT5NIPM75SVSPNGTQBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛认为到 2026 年 12 月黄金价格为 4,900 美元，预计油价将下跌；铜仍是最受欢迎的工业金属]]></title><description><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs sees gold prices climbing 14% to $4,900 per ounce by December 2026 in its base case, it said in a note on Thursday, while citing upside risks to this view due to a potential broadening of diversification to private investors.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-sees-gold-4900-by-december-2026-projects-oil-price-decline-copper-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQ65DRSMNVJJTFJKS4VPF25CMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:47:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利 Nexi 拒绝 TPG 对数字银行资产的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利金融科技公司 Nexi 周四表示，将不会接受美国私募股权基金 TPG 收购其数字银行部门的提议。【原文：Italian fintech company Nexi said on Thursday it will not proceed with U.S. private equity fund TPG's offer to buy its digital banking unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italys-nexi-rejects-tpg-offer-digital-banking-assets-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUQXRDL5HJOLPFJJITK7Z5RZXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:33:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The pain points and bright spots in a patchy US inflation report]]></title><description><![CDATA[久拖不决的 11 月份消费者物价指数报告让特朗普政府提前感受到了美国人对物价高涨和攀升的热议。【原文：The long-delayed Consumer Price Index report for November offered some early holiday cheer for a Trump administration feeling the heat from Americans over high and climbing prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pain-points-bright-spots-patchy-us-inflation-report-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGDFBPEIK5MRPJN5W6AE7O5YGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instacart 将支付 6000 万美元，以了结美国联邦贸易委员会对其欺骗购物者的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周四在旧金山提交的法庭文件，Instacart 已同意支付 6000 万美元，以了结美国联邦贸易委员会对该在线食品杂货配送平台在 Instacart+ 会员资格和免费配送服务方面欺骗消费者的指控。【原文：Instacart has agreed to pay $60 million to settle the U.S. Federal Trade Commission's allegations that the online grocery delivery platform deceived consumers about its Instacart+ membership and free delivery offers, according to court documents filed in San Francisco on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-nominates-joshua-rudd-director-national-security-agency-pentagon-says-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDMDNIIE5ZIELKWCDQ24GJUTWY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:49:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗通过另一监管障碍，解决长期存在的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团向解决其长期存在的合规问题又迈出了一步，周四宣布美国银行监管机构已取消了要求该银行解决其问题的部分严厉处罚。【原文：Citigroup took another step toward fixing its longstanding compliance problems, announcing on Thursday that a U.S. bank regulator had removed part of a sweeping punishment requiring the bank to tackle its issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/citi-clears-another-regulatory-hurdle-fix-longstanding-problems-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7DEXDX4TZJJHGTF3N7YNW4B6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:44:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源监管机构指示 PJM 制定人工智能连接规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源监管机构周四指示美国最大的电网运营商 PJM Interconnection 制定有关连接人工智能驱动的数据中心和其他位于发电厂旁边的大型电力负载的规则。【原文：The U.S. energy regulator on Thursday directed the largest U.S. grid operator, PJM Interconnection, to establish rules on the connection of artificial intelligence-driven data centers and other large electricity loads located next to power plants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-energy-regulator-directs-pjm-launch-rules-ai-connections-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4EKWO5VRRMHNKYGRNWUIKQIDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥反垄断机构称谷歌不能强制移动设备制造商使用安卓系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥反垄断委员会周四表示，已经解决了一起因安卓系统相关商业行为导致移动操作系统市场缺乏竞争的案件。【原文：Mexico's antitrust commission said on Thursday it had resolved a case over a lack of competition in the mobile operating system market stemming from business practices related to Android.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/mexicos-antitrust-commission-resolves-android-competition-case-orders-google-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YK7FVRHFMBKR5DCAOCHXBSJA3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ben & Jerry's 董事会称 Magnum 解除董事长和董事职务未经授权]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ben & Jerry's 独立董事会周三晚些时候在一份文件中称，其新公司所有者 Magnum 冰激凌公司无权罢免包括主席 Anuradha Mittal 在内的董事。【原文：Ben & Jerry's independent board late on Wednesday said in a filing that its new corporate owner, the Magnum Ice Cream Company, was not authorized to remove directors including Chair Anuradha Mittal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/ben-jerrys-board-says-magnums-removal-chair-directors-is-unauthorized-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72R6C6JHSJP2RFKAHMJIBSNSSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰-美国基金批准投资政策，预计 2026 年开展首批项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责监督乌克兰-美国重建基金的美国政府机构表示，作为两国 4 月签署的矿产协议的一部分而成立的乌克兰-美国重建基金周四批准了其资产政策，并准备在 2026 年开始审查其首个投资机会。【原文：The Ukraine-U.S. reconstruction fund, established as part of the minerals deal the two countries signed in April, on Thursday approved its asset policies and is poised to begin reviewing its first investment opportunities in 2026, the U.S. governmental body overseeing the fund said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ukraine-us-fund-approves-investment-policies-it-eyes-first-projects-2026-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R76R5LFM7ROK3JDX2EEU23V7RY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，欧洲央行决策者认为明年利率将保持稳定，但不会降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士告诉路透社，欧洲央行决策者预计明年将保持利率稳定，但他们尚未准备好降息，因为前景太不确定。【原文：European Central Bank policymakers expect to keep interest rates steady next year but they are not yet ready to take a rate cut off the table because the outlook is too uncertain, three sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ecb-policymakers-see-steady-rates-next-year-cut-not-off-table-sources-say-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZCI554ALZKYZOF2M6QLJTNGBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:30:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众管理层将继续削减成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司首席执行官奥利弗-布卢姆（Oliver Blume）周四承诺继续削减欧洲最大汽车制造商的成本，因为该公司正努力在全行业的挑战中保持竞争力。【原文：Volkswagen's Chief Executive Oliver Blume pledged continued cost cutting at Europe's largest carmaker on Thursday, as the company seeks to remain competitive amid industry-wide challenges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/vw-management-continue-cost-cutting-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAIDWNPBFZJHDHCA75M2ZHTFS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:17:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>