<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:36:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:36:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商 AMD 预测第二季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[AMD 周二预测第二季度营收将高于华尔街预期，即使贸易紧张局势给全球经济前景蒙上阴影，该公司仍将人工智能芯片的强劲需求作为赌注。【原文：AMD forecast second-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, betting on robust demand for its artificial-intelligence chips even as trade tensions cloud the global economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chipmaker-amd-forecasts-second-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYQT4SDLKZMV3HQULSVNISYOIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EA 预计新游戏 "战地 "的年度预订额将超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子艺界（Electronic Arts）周二预测，2026 财年的账面收入将高于华尔街预期，这家电子游戏发行商看好其体育游戏的强劲表现和新游戏《战地》（Battlefield）的推出。【原文：Electronic Arts forecast fiscal 2026 bookings above Wall Street expectations on Tuesday, as the videogame publisher bets on the strong performance of its sports titles and the launch of a new "Battlefield" game.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ea-forecasts-annual-bookings-above-estimates-with-new-battlefield-game-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IIBAFBSHFNJJIFU44T2H336VE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:18:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[超微公司下调年度收入预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[超微计算机公司（Super Micro Computer）周二下调了 2025 财年的营收预期，这加剧了人们对这家服务器制造商在人工智能市场地位的担忧，此前一系列内部问题曾导致该公司可能退市。【原文：Super Micro Computer trimmed its fiscal 2025 revenue expectation on Tuesday, adding to concerns around the server maker's position in the AI market after a litany of internal issues had brought on a potential delisting】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/super-micro-cuts-annual-revenue-forecast-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQEU3AD55JPYHO3VG4TXZIDEQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:16:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价下跌导致德文郡能源公司第一季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受油价下跌影响，德文能源公司周二未能实现第一季度利润预期。【原文：Devon Energy missed first-quarter profit estimates on Tuesday, hit by lower oil prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/devon-energy-misses-first-quarter-profit-estimates-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIFY566R6VOWXBJ3BHOXGP3LFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:14:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税影响需求，Rivian 下调年度交付量预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国对进口汽车和汽车零部件征收关税可能会扰乱经济，并损害对其电动 SUV 和皮卡的需求，Rivian 公司周二下调了 2025 年的交付预期。【原文：Rivian lowered its deliveries forecast for 2025 on Tuesday as U.S. tariffs on imported vehicles and auto parts threaten to unsettle the economy and hurt demand for its electric SUVs and pickup trucks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-slashes-annual-deliveries-forecast-us-tariffs-seen-hitting-demand-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IU5COB7RTBNTRPFFL7T2OMAER4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:09:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即使关税问题对汽车制造商造成冲击，Lucid 仍坚持年产量预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管关税威胁迫使许多汽车制造商撤回目标，但Lucid周二仍坚持其2025年的产量预测，同时这家豪华电动汽车制造商公布的第一季度营收低于分析师预期。【原文：Lucid stuck to its 2025 production forecast on Tuesday despite the threat of tariffs forcing many automakers to pull back targets, while the luxury electric-vehicle maker reported first-quarter revenue below analysts' expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lucid-sticks-annual-production-forecast-even-tariff-woes-hit-automakers-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWQEPWMFV5PDPNV534JABVBDNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局任命该机构批评家维奈-普拉萨德（Vinay Prasad）为最高疫苗官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周二表示，该局已任命曾批评过 FDA 领导层和 COVID-19 授权的肿瘤学家 Vinay Prasad 担任生物制品评估与研究中心主任。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has named Vinay Prasad, an oncologist who has previously criticized FDA leadership and COVID-19 mandates, as the director of its Center for Biologics Evaluation and Research, the agency said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-names-agency-critic-vinay-prasad-top-vaccine-official-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4MCS2IJLRKI5CY3EET2NOTXEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国受压企业四月份债务重组增多]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）周二的数据显示，由于企业面临关税上涨、通货膨胀和资本市场波动的压力，4月份财务状况紧张的美国企业进行的债务重组增加了近60%。【原文：Debt restructuring by financially stressed U.S. companies rose nearly 60% in April, data from JPMorgan showed on Tuesday, as businesses faced pressure from rising tariffs, inflation and capital markets volatility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stressed-us-companies-restructured-more-debt-april-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPUDA4NOIFKPNGU5ZNGS6MPARQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:36:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制药商寻求规避关税，3月份美国进口药品激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于制药商在美国可能对其产品征收关税前备货，3 月份对美国的药品进口激增。【原文：Pharmaceutical imports to the U.S. surged in March as drugmakers stocked up ahead of potential U.S. tariffs on their products, which have historically been exempt from such fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pharma-imports-us-surged-march-drugmakers-look-avoid-tariffs-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7JETZQX22ZNBXKJCTCHVE6REVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税影响外出就餐欲望，巴菲特的 Dairy Queen 保持警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的 Dairy Queen 首席执行官表示，有迹象表明消费者减少了外出就餐的次数，但相信美国的特许经营商能够承受经济压力，包括关税带来的压力。【原文：Dairy Queen, owned by Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway , has seen signs that consumers are dining out less, but believes American franchisees can withstand economic pressures, including from tariffs, its chief executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/buffetts-dairy-queen-guard-tariffs-weigh-desire-dine-out-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVZALQ55TJMFRPZ2FKGIQAKVVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德称，尽管基调乐观，但美国部分信贷市场仍闪现警告信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德集团（BlackRock）的一位高管表示，尽管市场普遍希望关税带来的动荡已经平息，但美国企业债务市场的一些地区正在闪现出警告信号，即经济降温正在挤压最脆弱的借款人。【原文：Pockets of the U.S. corporate debt market are flashing warning signs that a cooling economy is squeezing the most fragile borrowers, a BlackRock executive said, despite broader market hopes that the turbulence from tariffs has subsided.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pockets-us-credit-markets-flash-warnings-despite-upbeat-tone-says-blackrock-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZFFPJ56HRLGLCDYBPGYMFTJIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称欧佩克+产量增加、关税不确定性加剧油价波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（U.S. Energy Information Administration）周二表示，石油市场参与者对欧佩克+产量增加导致供过于求的看法，以及关税对经济影响的不确定性，加剧了短期油价波动。【原文：Perceptions of oversupply among oil market participants from increasing OPEC+ output and uncertainty about the economic impact of tariffs have raised short-term oil price volatility, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/higher-opec-output-tariff-uncertainty-raising-oil-price-volatility-eia-says-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DE4XMPXQTBKKDHSXJFPY2FMLOM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称国税局技术预算削减 20 亿美元不会造成中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，特朗普政府已从美国国税局信息技术预算中削减了 20 亿美元，且未造成业务中断，并打算通过自动处理纸质表格再节省数亿美元。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Tuesday said the Trump administration has cut $2 billion from the IRS information technology budget without operational disruptions and intends to save hundreds of millions more by automating processing of paper forms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bessent-says-2-billion-cut-irs-technology-budget-without-disruptions-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IS6XMKFUYVKX7F6KPZ257V5NDU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟计划在 2027 年底前逐步淘汰俄罗斯天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周二表示，将于下月提出法律措施，在 2027 年底前逐步停止欧盟进口所有俄罗斯天然气和液化天然气。【原文：The European Commission will next month propose legal measures to phase out the EU's imports of all Russian gas and liquefied natural gas by the end of 2027, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/eus-plan-phase-out-russian-gas-by-end-2027-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76GXYYHTOZOSNFUOUCAFKHNFCQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊机器人出租车部门 Zoox 在拉斯维加斯自动驾驶车祸后召回车辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）的自动驾驶部门 Zoox 同意召回 270 辆无人驾驶汽车，因为一辆无人驾驶机器人出租车 4 月 8 日在拉斯维加斯与一辆乘用车相撞。【原文：Amazon.com's self-driving unit Zoox agreed to recall 270 driverless vehicles after an unoccupied robotaxi was involved in an April 8 crash with a passenger car in Las Vegas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazons-robotaxi-unit-zoox-recalls-vehicles-after-self-driving-las-vegas-crash-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZGZXU6I7RJHXC33YOMJIBN6GE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党议员破坏关键听证会，特朗普的加密货币投资引发紧张局势泡沫化]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国国会山因唐纳德-特朗普总统的各种加密货币投资项目而出现的紧张局势升级，并有可能破坏数字资产行业在今年年底前立法的希望，因为一位民主党高级立法者阻止了就一项法案进行辩论的努力。【原文：Tensions on Capitol Hill over President Donald Trump's various cryptocurrency ventures escalated on Tuesday and threatened to derail the digital asset sector's hope of legislation by the end of this year as a top Democratic lawmaker stalled efforts to debate a bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trumps-crypto-ventures-cause-tensions-bubble-over-democratic-lawmaker-scuttles-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIMU4JLSL5JB3NFWTHZK33SVRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:13:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[思科展示量子网络芯片并开设新实验室]]></title><description><![CDATA[思科系统公司周二展示了一款用于将量子计算机联网的原型芯片，并表示将在加利福尼亚州圣莫尼卡开设一个新实验室，以进一步研究量子计算。【原文：Cisco Systems on Tuesday showed a prototype chip for networking quantum computers together and said it is opening a new lab in Santa Monica, California, to further pursue quantum computing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cisco-shows-quantum-networking-chip-opens-new-lab-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5XILGW6J5LZ7IVRU54EF452ME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:53:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔股东批准股权激励计划和新 CEO 薪酬]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔股东周二批准了一项公司措施，旨在充实股票储备，以吸引和留住新员工，并为新任首席执行官陈立武提供补偿。【原文：Intel shareholders on Tuesday approved a company measure aimed at topping up share reserves to attract and retain new employees and compensation for new CEO Lip-Bu Tan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/intel-shareholders-approve-equity-incentive-plan-new-ceo-pay-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4G4CILDYRKBPAI4HS77FPEPPE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将在未来几周评估贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，他和政府高层官员将在未来两周内审查潜在的贸易协议，以决定接受哪些协议。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that he and top administration officials will review potential trade deals over the next two weeks to decide which ones to accept.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-says-china-wants-negotiate-meet-right-time-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOIGWYUYWFOWRE44ZAFPMHHAHY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:32:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会结束对摩根士丹利现金清算计划的调查，未采取任何执法行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街银行摩根士丹利在周一提交的一份文件中表示，美国证券交易委员会已结束对摩根士丹利咨询账户现金清算计划的调查，不会采取执法行动。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has ended its investigation into Morgan Stanley's cash sweep program for advisory accounts and will not pursue enforcement action, the Wall Street bank said in a filing dated Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-sec-ends-inquiry-into-morgan-stanleys-cash-sweep-program-with-no-enforcement-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52HUVMEGFVIVPORE2PKXFXJ77Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Constellation 重新关注并网人工智能数据中心电力项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[星座能源公司（Constellation Energy）高管周二表示，该公司正日益关注与美国电网连接的潜在数据中心项目，这与该公司之前强调直接从其发电厂为巨型服务器仓库提供燃料的做法有所不同。【原文：Constellation Energy is increasingly focused on potential data center projects that connect to the U.S. electrical grid in a pivot away from the company's previous emphasis on fueling the giant server warehouses directly from its power plants, company executives said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/constellation-refocusing-grid-connected-ai-data-center-power-projects-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUTMFBEAS5LWPMNAR46EXS2FKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称美国本周可能宣布与一些国家达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，特朗普政府最早可能在本周宣布与美国最大的一些贸易伙伴达成贸易协议，但没有透露涉及哪些国家的详细情况。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Tuesday said the Trump administration could announce trade agreements with some of the United States' largest trade partners as early as this week, but gave no details on which countries were involved.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-says-us-could-announce-trade-deals-with-some-countries-this-week-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEWPKUNU3NPZBEKZLX5RZ3TN3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:35:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉堡王必须面对有关 Whopper 广告的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[汉堡王（Burger King）必须面对一桩诉讼，该诉讼称汉堡王在广告中误导顾客，使其 Whopper 三明治和其他产品看起来比实际尺寸大。【原文：Burger King must face a lawsuit claiming it misleads customers with advertisements that make its Whopper sandwich and other products appear larger than they are.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/burger-king-must-face-lawsuit-over-whopper-ads-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXXCRMFX5BNFPB4IXYLQ2SHDGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:26:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税影响，零售商寻求在欧洲实现增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[越来越多的零售商和消费品牌正在将重点从美国转向欧洲和其他市场，因为他们预计美国关税将引发价格上涨，从而导致美国消费者需求下降。【原文：Growing numbers of retailers and consumer brands are shifting their focus to Europe and other markets from the United States, as they expect U.S. tariffs to spark price hikes that will drive American consumer demand down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spooked-by-us-tariffs-retailers-look-growth-europe-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z56NBHWKJ5IOFMTQ3MMHD3VV3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:21:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储发现四月份供应链压力有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管全球各经济体急于应对特朗普政府大规模和不断变化的贸易关税的影响，但供应链压力在上个月仍有所缓解。【原文：Supply chain pressures eased last month even as economies around the world rushed to position themselves for the impact of massive and shifting trade tariffs by the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/new-york-fed-finds-easing-supply-chain-pressure-april-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">542PUH4OZFOW7PHR535TSIXHWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 xAI 加入 TWG Global 和 Palantir，共同推动金融领域的人工智能发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的人工智能公司xAI与Palantir Technologies和投资公司TWG Global周二表示，双方已建立合作伙伴关系，共同发掘金融服务业日益增长的人工智能需求。【原文：Elon Musk's artificial intelligence company xAI has partnered with Palantir Technologies and investment firm TWG Global, the companies said on Tuesday, as they look to tap growing AI demand in the financial services industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-xai-joins-twg-global-palantir-ai-push-financial-sector-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZA3LIUCVERMGXLCOEHRIPQIT7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:24:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国与印度在特朗普关税 "新时代 "达成重要贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）引发的关税动荡迫使双方加快努力增加威士忌、汽车和食品贸易之后，英国和印度周二达成了一项觊觎已久的自由贸易协定。【原文：Britain and India clinched a long-coveted free trade pact on Tuesday after tariff turmoil sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump forced the two sides to hasten efforts to increase their trade in whisky, cars and food.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-uk-conclude-talks-over-free-trade-pact-pm-modi-says-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGABSVEFPNK7HFWPLDXIPJELBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软推出搭载高通芯片的低价人工智能笔记本电脑]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周二表示，它将以比以往更低的价格发布采用高通公司芯片的新款笔记本电脑和平板电脑，旨在向更广泛的客户提供新的人工智能功能。【原文：Microsoft on Tuesday said it will release a new laptop and tablet with chips from Qualcomm at lower prices than before, aiming to get new AI features to a broader set of customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-launches-lower-priced-ai-laptops-with-qualcomm-chips-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2VPGY74QZLNTD3ZY7MDIHSAWU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[严格削减成本后，Gartner 上调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，技术研究公司 Gartner 的季度利润超出预期，并上调了全年盈利预期，这表明尽管关税导致经济不确定性，但严格的成本控制有助于公司保持弹性。【原文：Technology research firm Gartner topped quarterly profit expectations on Tuesday and bumped up its full-year earnings forecast, signaling that tight cost controls were helping it stay resilient despite tariff-driven economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gartner-raises-annual-profit-forecast-after-strict-cost-cuts-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUU43HGVOZMJJKU6CDFAUKY52Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能驱动云安全需求，Datadog上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[云安全公司 Datadog 周二上调了全年营收预期，季度销售额超过预期，这主要得益于大客户和人工智能驱动的工作负载的增长。【原文：Cloud security firm Datadog raised its annual revenue forecast and beat the estimate for quarterly sales on Tuesday, thanks to growth in large customers and AI-driven workloads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/datadog-lifts-annual-revenue-forecast-ai-driven-cloud-security-demand-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQBTN7JK65OYTCEQ4YJKSBF3RY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>