<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:04:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:04:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国喷气式飞机与直升机相撞后，NTSB 紧急提出安全建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封信称，美国国家运输安全委员会将于周二宣布，它将提出一项紧急安全建议，防止在华盛顿里根国家机场使用两条跑道时进行直升机作业。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board will announce on Tuesday it is making an urgent safety recommendation to prevent helicopter operations when two runways are being used at Washington Reagan National Airport following a mid-air collision in January that killed 67 people, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ntsb-making-urgent-safety-recommendations-after-american-jet-collision-with-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOPSV5X3ZFMDLKMAJAFAN3IYRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[犹他州有望成为首个禁止在公共供水系统中使用氟化物的州]]></title><description><![CDATA[在犹他州州长斯宾塞-考克斯（Spencer Cox）表示将签署相关立法后，犹他州将成为美国第一个禁止在公共供水系统中使用氟化物的州。【原文：Utah is set to become the first U.S. state to ban the use of fluoride in public water systems after Utah Governor Spencer Cox said he would sign legislation to that effect.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/utah-poised-become-first-state-ban-fluoride-public-water-system-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUABFICQBZJSTC5E7WESQTZUEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 分析 美国电力需求激增之际小型核电举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[从美国能源部长到大型科技公司，每个人都将小型模块化核反应堆作为应对蓬勃发展的电力需求的潜在方案，但由于成本和监管障碍，该技术正努力实现商业化。【原文：Everyone from the U.S. energy secretary to Big Tech touts small modular nuclear reactors as a potential answer to booming power demand, but the technology is struggling to become commercial due to costs and regulatory hurdles.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-analysis-small-nuclear-power-struggles-cusp-us-electricity-demand-boom-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQACXBZRO5I6NDUDT7TFFXTSAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学巴勒斯坦裔学生抗议者向美国联邦法院提出逮捕异议]]></title><description><![CDATA[关于一名被捕的巴勒斯坦活动人士和哥伦比亚大学学生的法律之争已成为特朗普政府移民政策的导火索，将在联邦法院展开，美国政府将于周二就此案的下一步行动提出建议。【原文：A legal battle over an arrested Palestinian activist and Columbia University student that has become a flashpoint of the Trump administration’s immigration policy will play out in federal court, with the U.S. government set to propose the next steps in the case on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/palestinian-columbia-student-protestors-challenge-arrest-turns-us-federal-court-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGFNY4GSWRPIVOYNTUNDKMHG3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[州卫生局称，得克萨斯州麻疹病例比 3 月 7 日增加 25 例]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州卫生部门周二报告了该州 223 例麻疹病例，比 3 月 7 日增加了 25 例，而在此之前近两周，一名未接种疫苗的儿童死于麻疹，这是美国十年来爆发的最大规模的麻疹疫情之一。【原文：The Texas health department reported 223 measles cases in the state on Tuesday, an increase of 25 cases from March 7, nearly two weeks after an unvaccinated child died of the disease amid one of the largest outbreaks the U.S. has witnessed in a decade.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/measles-cases-rise-223-texas-state-health-department-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS7R7TG3YZI7LC6N23NLA3R5EA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:18:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱德华-蒙克肖像在伦敦新展中展出]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，一场新的爱德华-蒙克肖像画展在伦敦拉开帷幕，展示了这位挪威画家作品和生活的一个重要方面。【原文：A new exhibition of portraits by Edvard Munch opens in London this week, shining a light on an important aspect of the Norwegian painter's work and his life.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/lifestyle/portraits-by-edvard-munch-go-show-new-london-exhibition-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOG6TPKSAJKKFFZHW77RECZSOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:59:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将对加拿大金属征收的关税加倍至 50]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二将他计划对所有从加拿大进入美国的钢铁和铝产品征收的关税提高了一倍，使关税总额达到 50%，以回应安大略省对进入美国的电力征收 25% 的关税。【原文：President Donald Trump on Tuesday doubled his planned tariff on all steel and aluminum products coming into the United States from Canada, bringing the total to 50%, in response to the province of Ontario placing a 25% tariff on electricity coming into the U.S.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-says-he-will-raise-tariffs-canada-metals-50-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ONVWMUI5RNCXEIIGNJPI3E4SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:10:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月份职位空缺增加；裁员人数下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 1 月份的职位空缺有所增加，但由于人们担心进口关税的不确定性和政府积极削减开支可能会导致经济活动急剧放缓，未来几个月的劳动力需求可能会走软。【原文：U.S. job openings increased in January, but demand for labor is likely to soften in the months ahead amid concerns that uncertainty over import tariffs and aggressive government spending cuts could cause a sharp slowdown in economic activity.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-increase-january-layoffs-decline-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERZUABQTINP4BG233FOQ4MY6N4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[女童子军因饼干中含有重金属和杀虫剂被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[女童子军被消费者起诉，指控其广受欢迎的薄荷糖和其他饼干中含有 "重金属 "和杀虫剂。【原文：The Girl Scouts have been sued by consumers over the alleged presence of "heavy metals" and pesticides in its popular Thin Mints and other cookies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/girl-scouts-sued-over-alleged-heavy-metals-pesticides-cookies-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJBEVV5R7FOFLOI6OJJQJAKCWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:48:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[周一大跌后的最新美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[股市抛售已使上个月的 S&amp;P 500 指数峰值损失了 4 万亿美元。【原文：A stock market sell-off has wiped out $4 trillion from the S&amp;P 500’s peak last month.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/latest-us-markets-after-mondays-selloff-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMTKGI474BHIXFA2RVDKVZCRB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会（NTSB）将发布华盛顿州喷气机与直升机致命相撞事故的初步报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会计划于周二发布一份初步报告，调查 1 月 29 日一架直升机与一架美国航空公司喷气式飞机在华盛顿里根国家机场附近相撞，造成 67 人死亡的事故。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board plans to issue a preliminary report on Tuesday into the Jan. 29 collision between a helicopter and an American Airlines jet that killed 67 people near Washington Reagan National Airport.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ntsb-release-preliminary-report-into-fatal-washington-jet-helicopter-collision-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYUAHDMUWNNLNOHSSFGTUSSENM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 12:52:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克在北卡罗来纳州开设疫苗生产厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司周二表示，该公司已在北卡罗来纳州的工厂开设了一家价值 10 亿美元的工厂，面对唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税威胁，这家制药商正努力提升其在美国的制造业。【原文：Merck said on Tuesday it has opened a $1-billion facility at its North Carolina site, as the drugmaker seeks to boost its U.S. manufacturing in the face of President Donald Trump's tariff threats.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-opens-vaccine-manufacturing-facility-north-carolina-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7W7GKIFAFMAFB35ULKNOVMFOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:57:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普削减夏威夷世界领先的温室气体观测站经费]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普政府正在考虑取消一个著名的夏威夷气候研究站支持办公室的租约，这让人们对追踪碳排放对全球变暖影响的关键工作的未来感到担忧。【原文：The Trump administration is considering cancelling the lease of the support office for a renowned Hawaiian climate research station, sources said, raising fears for the future of key work tracking the impact of carbon emissions on global warming.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-cuts-target-world-leading-greenhouse-gas-observatory-hawaii-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MOE7MSBFV5OVZAWH66OCEL2BOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普会见美国企业界人士，经济担忧打压股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计总统将与约 100 位首席执行官发表讲话。【原文：The president is expected to speak with around 100 CEOs.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-meets-corporate-america-economic-fears-nip-stocks-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KMTLLA3KRO45FH73UHOVY3CB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:06:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税给威斯康星州的工厂车间带来了 "狂野的西部"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里恩斯公司（AriensCo）是一家生产鲜艳橙色吹雪机的公司，自 11 月份以来，该公司一直在为关税寒流做准备。【原文：AriensCo - a manufacturer of bright orange snowblowers - has braced for the cold blast of tariffs since November.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-tariffs-create-wild-west-wisconsins-factory-floors-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34BORXCWXRISZH4ONOWDG6IUFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院在民主党反对声中就政府拨款问题进行激烈投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[控制美国国会的共和党人将于周二试图推动立法，以避免政府在周末关门，而对唐纳德-特朗普总统大幅裁员感到震惊的民主党人预计将反对立法。【原文：Republicans who control the U.S. Congress will try on Tuesday to advance legislation that would avert a weekend government shutdown, while Democrats alarmed by President Donald Trump's dramatic downsizing effort were expected to oppose it.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-tees-up-close-vote-government-funding-face-democratic-opposition-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHFKKGRM4FJSFPXXWCEJU2XJX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:03:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莫斯科无人机袭击最新消息：乌克兰袭击俄罗斯首都]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰官员稍后将在沙特阿拉伯与美国团队会面，讨论可能的和平谈判。【原文：Ukrainian officials are due to meet a U.S. team in Saudi Arabia later to discuss possible peace talks.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/europe/moscow-drone-attack-latest-russian-capital-targeted-by-ukraine-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZEJBTIQM5DN5FHLQLMWKNDR3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将购买 "新特斯拉 "以示对马斯克的支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，他将购买一辆新的特斯拉汽车，以示对这家电动汽车制造商的掌门人及其盟友埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的支持。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday said he will buy a new Tesla car to show support for the electric carmaker's chief and his ally Elon Musk amid recent "Tesla Takedown" protests and the slump in the company's stock price.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-buy-new-tesla-show-support-musk-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25P5CHB4BNO45P3U6YLXKXQ3EY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 05:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国私募基金要求美国证券交易委员会重新考虑詹斯勒时代的规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募基金行业组织管理基金协会（Managed Funds Association）敦促美国证券交易委员会（SEC）改革或撤销过去四年来出台的法规。【原文：The Managed Funds Association, a private fund industry group, has urged the U.S. Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) to reform or withdraw regulations introduced over the past four years.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/us-private-funds-ask-sec-rethink-gensler-era-rules-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWBYHNNPCNPAZFODPUQTGBBRBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 04:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[权益组织称，以色列-加沙战争是美国反穆斯林事件创新高的幕后推手]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个穆斯林权益组织周二表示，由于美国盟友以色列在加沙发动的战争以及由此引发的大学校园抗议活动导致伊斯兰恐惧症加剧，2024 年针对美国穆斯林和阿拉伯人的歧视和攻击上升了 7.4%。【原文：Discrimination and attacks against American Muslims and Arabs rose by 7.4% in 2024 due to heightened Islamophobia caused by U.S. ally Israel's war in Gaza and the resulting college campus protests, a Muslim advocacy group said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/israel-gaza-war-behind-record-high-us-anti-muslim-incidents-advocacy-group-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIO6UHSDXNPOHAPQSMCW7ELDIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 04:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官命令特朗普政府恢复教师备课补助金]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一名联邦法官命令美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府暂时恢复八个州的教师培训补助金。【原文：A federal judge on Monday ordered U.S. President Donald Trump's administration to temporarily restore grants for teacher preparation in eight states that it nixed as part of its efforts to eradicate diversity, equity and inclusion initiatives.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-orders-trump-administration-restore-teacher-preparation-grants-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3LHYIO4DNIQ5DFDEOSO75Z3DY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:14:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部削减超过 10 亿美元的学校和当地食品采购资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一个学校组织称，美国农业部削减了两项联邦计划，这两项计划每年花费超过10亿美元帮助学校和食品银行从当地农场和牧场购买食品。【原文：The U.S. Agriculture Department has cut two federal programs that spent over $1 billion annually to help schools and food banks buy food from local farms and ranches, according to a school group and a Politico report on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-cuts-over-1-billion-funding-schools-local-food-purchases-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDQTTCESL5IBBDBSIKYQRZILAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:36:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官称马斯克的 DOGE 必须公布 "秘密 "运营的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周一下令，由美国总统唐纳德-特朗普创建、亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）带头的政府缩编团队必须公开有关其运作的记录，他说该团队的运作一直处于 "非同寻常的保密状态"。【原文：A federal judge on Monday ordered the government-downsizing team created by U.S. President Donald Trump and spearheaded by billionaire Elon Musk to make public records concerning its operations, which he said had been run in "unusual secrecy."】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-says-musks-doge-must-release-records-operations-run-secrecy-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2PU6Z6N6JK5TFBKYKRP5U2HCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:12:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官不会命令特朗普政府恢复被取消的对外援助合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周一拒绝命令唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府恢复自总统上任以来取消的数千份对外援助合同和赠款，但他认为政府必须加快支付已完成工作的近 20 亿美元。【原文：A federal judge on Monday declined to order President Donald Trump's administration to restore thousands of foreign aid contracts and grants that have been canceled since the president took office, though he found that the administration must speed up payments of close to $2 billion for already completed work.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/judge-will-not-order-trump-administration-restore-canceled-foreign-aid-contracts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNMQO5IWQRJZTFRXK6KPDE5VNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 01:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工人拆除华盛顿特区黑人生命事件广场壁画以避免资金削减]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，建筑工人开始拆除华盛顿特区黑人生命事务广场的壁画，此前市长穆里尔-鲍泽（Muriel Bowser）承诺将重新设计该广场，以应对共和党威胁削减该市交通资金，除非该广场重新命名。【原文：Construction workers began removing Washington, D.C.'s Black Lives Matter Plaza mural on Monday, after Mayor Muriel Bowser pledged to redesign the plaza in response to Republican threats to cut the city's transportation funding unless it was renamed.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/workers-remove-dc-black-lives-matter-plaza-mural-avoid-funding-cuts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3FALWUFRFOXVF7VC7LZJGKKTA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:20:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国交通部长将与波音公司就安全工作举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）计划于周四参观位于华盛顿州的波音工厂，以确保美国飞机制造商保持最高的安全水平。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy plans to visit a Boeing factory on Thursday in Washington State to ensure the U.S. planemaker is maintaining the highest level of safety.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transportation-chief-meet-with-boeing-safety-efforts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JBTKOWVFRJK3O7TD3LHQCYYHE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国交通部长将与波音公司就安全工作举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）计划于周四参观位于华盛顿州的波音工厂，以确保美国飞机制造商保持最高的安全水平。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy plans to visit a Boeing factory on Thursday in Washington State to ensure the U.S. planemaker is maintaining the highest level of safety.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transportation-chief-meet-with-boeing-safety-efforts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JBTKOWVFRJK3O7TD3LHQCYYHE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特朗普寻求在五角大楼基地提炼矿物以提高美国产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名高级政府官员告诉路透社记者，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的目标是在五角大楼军事基地上建造金属精炼设施，作为他促进国内关键矿产生产和抵消中国对该行业控制的计划的一部分。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump aims to build metals refining facilities on Pentagon military bases as part of his plan to boost domestic production of critical minerals and offset China's control of the sector, two senior administration officials told Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-seeks-minerals-refining-pentagon-bases-boost-us-output-sources-say-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACASFGTJCZJZJEMFNBABRLYF3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 23:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员指责特朗普削弱乌克兰国防，驳斥马斯克 "叛徒 "的侮辱性言论]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位刚刚访问过乌克兰的美国民主党参议员周一表示，特朗普政府暂停情报共享的做法削弱了基辅对俄罗斯的防御能力，并驳斥特朗普顾问埃隆-马斯克称他为 "叛徒"。【原文：A Democratic U.S. senator who just visited Ukraine said on Monday the Trump administration's suspension of intelligence-sharing had lessened Kyiv's defenses against Russia, and dismissed Trump advisor Elon Musk calling him a "traitor."】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senator-accuses-trump-weakening-ukraines-defense-dismisses-musk-traitor-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3DD6HA3ZNPPDGS32X4KSCA42M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府计划限制奥巴马医保的注册期]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责监督奥巴马医改计划的机构在一份新闻稿中说，特朗普政府的目标是在 12 月 15 日结束奥巴马医改健康保险计划的注册期，比目前的截止日期提前一个月。【原文：The Trump administration aims to close the enrollment period for Obamacare health insurance plans on December 15, one month earlier than the current deadline, the agency that oversees the program said in a press release.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-plans-restrict-obamacare-enrollment-period-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICSYOO6425NWLIR5OGNY47IYWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>