<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:11:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:11:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家：贝森特称美国下周可能解除更多委内瑞拉制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特向路透社表示，美国对委内瑞拉的额外制裁最早可能于下周解除，以促进石油销售。他同时透露，下周将与国际货币基金组织和世界银行的负责人会晤，商讨重启与委内瑞拉的合作事宜。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent has told Reuters that additional U.S. sanctions on Venezuela could be lifted as soon as next week to facilitate oil sales, and that he will also meet next week with the heads of the International Monetary Fund and World Bank on their re-engagement with Venezuela.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-may-lift-more-venezuela-sanctions-next-week-bessent-says-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YX3YXRNEJVNUFACVRQXYLOVGMQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的X平台将在七天内开源新算法]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克周六表示，社交媒体平台X将在七天内向公众开放其新算法，包括所有自然推荐和广告推荐的代码。【原文：Elon Musk said on Saturday that social media platform X will open its new algorithm, including all code for organic and advertising post recommendations, to the public in seven days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/musks-x-open-source-new-algorithm-seven-days-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VS5EMJ7EFJMIVF7OVZWJVQQ2L4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能研究人员称，尽管存在诸多限制，中国正在逐步缩小与美国的科技差距。]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国顶尖人工智能研究人员周六表示，尽管先进芯片制造工具的缺乏正制约着该行业的发展，但随着风险承担和创新能力的增强，中国有望缩小与美国的科技差距。【原文：China can narrow its technological gap with the U.S. driven by growing risk-taking and innovation, though the lack of advanced chipmaking tools is hobbling the sector, the country's leading artificial intelligence researchers said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-is-closing-us-technology-lead-despite-constraints-ai-researchers-say-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6FYB52LORL6LGBOEVLT3U2VGQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：力拓收购嘉能可计划给必和必拓带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓集团与嘉能可的收购谈判可能催生全球行业新领头羊，这将推动铜矿需求旺盛的采矿业加速整合，并给全球最大矿业公司必和必拓带来巨大压力，迫使其作出回应。【原文：Rio Tinto's , talks to buy Glencore and create a new global industry leader could spur consolidation efforts across the copper-hungry mining sector and heap pressure on BHP, currently the world's biggest miner, to respond.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/rio-tintos-bid-glencore-piles-pressure-bhp-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6WD4DODTZKRFB7GIEQJMZWRRM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度尼西亚因性化图像暂时封禁Grok访问权限]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚周六暂时封禁了埃隆·马斯克的Grok聊天机器人，原因是该人工智能工具存在生成色情内容的风险，成为首个禁止使用该人工智能工具的国家。【原文：Indonesia temporarily blocked Elon Musk's Grok chatbot on Saturday due to the risk of AI-generated pornographic content, becoming the first country to deny access to the AI tool.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/indonesia-temporarily-blocks-access-grok-over-sexualised-images-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUHDH2P55JMGFKXOL23ZWTJPQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 07:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普呼吁将信用卡利率上限设定为10%，有效期为一年。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周五表示，他将呼吁从1月20日起对信用卡利率实施为期一年的10%上限，但他并未说明该计划如何落实，也未阐明如何确保企业遵守规定。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he was calling for a one-year cap on credit card interest rates at 10% starting January 20 but he did not provide details on how his plan will come to fruition or how he planned to make companies comply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-calls-one-year-cap-credit-card-interest-rates-10-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEA5KX7QM5MNZAQAWWP2I4DOPQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:47:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛将取代阿斯利康进入纳斯达克100指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克周五宣布，美国零售巨头沃尔玛将取代英国制药公司阿斯利康，于2026年1月20日起正式纳入纳斯达克100指数。【原文：Nasdaq on Friday said U.S. retailer Walmart will replace British drugmaker Astrazeneca in the Nasdaq-100 Index effective on January 20, 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/walmart-replace-astrazeneca-nasdaq-100-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW3BWKA25RJM3ASPJ22A3SYNTI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示美国财政部可轻松承担任何关税退还款项]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五向路透社表示，若最高法院裁定特朗普总统的紧急关税措施无效，美国财政部拥有充足资金支付任何关税退还款项，但退款过程可能持续数周甚至长达一年。【原文：The U.S. Treasury has more than adequate funds to pay any tariff refunds ordered if the Supreme Court rules against President Donald Trump's emergency tariffs, but any repayments would be spread out over weeks or even a year, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/bessent-says-us-treasury-can-easily-cover-any-tariff-refunds-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPB3GC4MV5O3DHDMKOJEIYYB7E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称澳大利亚、印度获邀参加七国集团关键矿产会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特表示，澳大利亚及其他若干国家将参加他于周一在华盛顿主持的七国集团（G7）财长会议，共同商讨关键矿产问题。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said Australia and several other countries would join a meeting of finance ministers from the Group of Seven advanced economies that he is hosting in Washington on Monday to discuss critical minerals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-australia-india-invited-g7-meeting-critical-minerals-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3UEOOHM3ZIW5AP6XYK2OBJVZQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:28:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，如果人们能证明资金来源，海外汇款是可行的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五对路透社表示，美国财政部加强海外资金转移审查的计划，不应损害那些能证明资金并非来自社会福利金的人。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department's plan to increase scrutiny of overseas transfers of money should not harm people who can prove the funds did not come from social service payments, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bessent-says-overseas-money-transfers-are-fine-if-people-can-prove-origin-funds-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2JTFVLBFFJSPHARVAFQPUJ5WA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:24:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：MBS购买的目标是匹配美联储的资产缩减]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五表示，特朗普政府启动抵押贷款支持证券购买计划的目标，是使购买规模大致与这些债券从美联储资产负债表上滚出的速度相匹配。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Friday said the goal of the Trump administration's launch of mortgage-backed securities purchases is to roughly match the rate at which those bonds are rolling off the Federal Reserve's balance sheet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bessent-goal-mbs-buys-is-match-fed-run-off-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBT6VZSDONMYHARXRVYXJMRSXA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源部长称雪佛龙公司已找到途径，可使委内瑞拉产量提升50%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯·赖特周五表示，雪佛龙公司已找到将委内瑞拉产量提升50%的途径。此前特朗普总统就该南美国家问题与多家石油公司举行了会晤。【原文：U.S. Energy Secretary Chris Wright said on Friday that Chevron saw a pathway to grow its Venezuela production by 50%, with his comments coming after a meeting that President Donald Trump had with oil companies on the South American nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-sees-pathway-grow-venezuela-production-by-50-us-energy-secretary-says-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMS24L6S5NPYVFZMLYY3CVQQVE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，多家公司正争相确保船只并组建团队，以转移委内瑞拉石油。]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉相关操作的消息人士称，在委内瑞拉总统尼古拉斯·马杜罗下台后，多家石油公司正争相参与委新出口原油至美国的业务。这些公司正紧急商讨租用油轮事宜，并筹备相关操作，以确保原油能从船只和破败不堪的委内瑞拉港口安全转运。【原文：Oil companies aiming to participate in new exports of Venezuelan crude to the U.S. following the ouster of President Nicolas Maduro are in hasty discussions to find tankers and put together operations to transfer the crude safely from vessels and dilapidated Venezuelan ports, four sources familiar with the operations said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/companies-scramble-secure-ships-assemble-operations-transfer-venezuelan-oil-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNIKDPLXX5IY3NQBBJIRZDE7XI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Boeing's biggest 737 MAX model moves to next stage in certification but still faces hurdles]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Aviation Administration has approved Boeing's largest variant of its best-selling 737 MAX jet, the MAX 10, to move to the second phase of flight testing on the plane's long-delayed certification campaign, according to a source familiar with the program.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-biggest-737-max-model-moves-next-stage-certification-still-faces-hurdles-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SIAUEBXX5PKVMH3KPEBEB4HVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:50:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FCC approves SpaceX plan to deploy additional 7,500 Starlink satellites]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Communications Commission said on Friday it has approved SpaceX's request to deploy another 7,500 second-generation Starlink satellites as it works to boost internet service worldwide.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fcc-approves-spacex-plan-deploy-additional-7500-starlink-satellites-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UY2ZCMHDZOT5PIQ3WCFNBX6FY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:33:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Casino operator Wynn CFO Julie Cameron-Doe retires]]></title><description><![CDATA[Casino operator Wynn Resorts said on Friday that CFO Julie Cameron-Doe would retire and that company insider Craig Jeffrey Fullalove would replace her as finance chief.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/casino-operator-wynn-cfo-julie-cameron-doe-retires-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNYODPERB5MCNEUOULETKQQZGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US SEC dismisses lawsuit against Rio Tinto ex-CFO]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday dismissed its lawsuit against a former Rio Tinto , chief financial officer, ending a long-running fraud case over a bad investment in a Mozambique coal project by one of the world's largest mining companies.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-sec-dismisses-lawsuit-against-rio-tinto-ex-cfo-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5JY7M2O5NKZ3ILKWYD4662SAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Commerce Department drops plan to impose restrictions on Chinese-made drones]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Commerce Department said on Friday it has withdrawn a plan to impose restrictions on Chinese drones to address national security concerns after an earlier crackdown on passenger cars and trucks.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-commerce-department-drops-plan-impose-restrictions-chinese-made-drones-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBNQK5YA7FPUVILPJLTZCYH3SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Supreme Court to hear suit claiming Cisco helped China pursue Falun Gong]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Supreme Court on Friday agreed to hear an appeal by Cisco Systems in which the tech company and President Donald Trump's administration are asking the justices to limit the reach of a federal law that has been used to hold corporations liable for human rights abuses committed abroad.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-hear-suit-claiming-cisco-helped-china-pursue-falun-gong-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JHXBYSQ2CNLQLBOTB42D5OOH6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:57:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Supreme Court to weigh FCC's power to fine wireless carriers]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Supreme Court agreed on Friday to hear a dispute involving fines imposed by the Federal Communications Commission on major U.S. wireless carriers for sharing customer location data without consent in the latest case to reach the justices challenging the powers of a U.S. regulatory agency.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-weigh-fccs-power-fine-wireless-carriers-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NOD32QWPRJRLEPFS37O25CQU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump's oil strategy for Venezuela leaves Citgo auction in limbo]]></title><description><![CDATA[As U.S. President Donald Trump moves quickly to put together a $100 billion effort to revive Venezuela's oil industry, the administration has yet to finalize the fate of the crown jewel of the country's foreign assets, U.S. refining company Citgo Petroleum, sources close to the matter said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trumps-oil-strategy-venezuela-leaves-citgo-auction-limbo-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEP2S64JGVMJZEN6WG46EREAZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US FTC wins ruling blocking Edwards Lifesciences' acquisition of JenaValve]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission won a ruling on Friday blocking Edwards Lifesciences' acquisition of JenaValve Technology, court records showed.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/ftc-wins-ruling-blocking-edwards-lifesciences-acquisition-jenavalve-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YG7UUG7AWNNAPGC2RCCGPIXRXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two Fed officials say key to fixing US housing more about supply than financing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two Federal Reserve officials on Friday expressed some skepticism that a Trump administration plan to lower housing costs by buying billions in mortgage-backed bonds will do much to lift the troubled sector.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/two-fed-officials-say-key-fixing-us-housing-more-about-supply-than-financing-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7IXQRYMBNM63D2YSIM3JOHAP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exxon CEO says prepared to evaluate reentering Venezuela]]></title><description><![CDATA[Exxon Mobil CEO Darren Woods said on Friday the U.S. oil major could hit the ground running in Venezuela and evaluate potentially returning to Venezuela.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-ceo-says-prepared-evaluate-reentering-venezuela-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UF6CHDQLYJK6TDXINTXOBJYS3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:48:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[California governor proposes $200 million in new state EV tax rebates]]></title><description><![CDATA[California Governor Gavin Newsom is proposing $200 million in new state electric-vehicle tax rebates after Congress earlier this year ended a federal $7,500 state tax deduction on new EVs, the state said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/california-governor-proposes-200-million-new-state-ev-tax-rebates-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVAMC3AEOVPYTBO7FAULNXD3VA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Musk's X sues music publishers over alleged licensing conspiracy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elon Musk's X Corp sued 18 major music publishers and a leading U.S. music industry trade association on Friday, alleging they conspired to block competition and force the social media platform to purchase licenses for musical works at inflated rates.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/musks-x-sues-music-publishers-over-alleged-licensing-conspiracy-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2PDXAD6EVJERAX35IRLSLUFPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:20:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump pushes 'drill baby drill' agenda to Venezuela, hurts producers at home]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. oil producers already reeling from low oil prices are facing renewed pressures, as President Donald Trump pushes them to boost output in Venezuela - a move that would weaken the oil market, cut revenues and hurt industry at home.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-pushes-drill-baby-drill-agenda-venezuela-hurts-producers-home-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4ZDAFDUGVPJBOPB5OBLTYL35M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI, SoftBank invest $1 billion in SB Energy as Stargate buildout expands]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI and SoftBank Group will jointly invest $1 billion in SB Energy, a SoftBank-owned provider of data-center and power infrastructure, as part of their $500 billion Stargate initiative aimed at building out AI infrastructure.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/openai-softbank-invest-1-billion-sb-energy-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSGQURZP7BIP5CVWGDHUM6NFHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:26:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis scraps US plug-in hybrid sales, citing weak demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chrysler parent Stellantis said on Friday it will stop selling plug-in hybrid versions of the Jeep Wrangler and Grand Cherokee, and the Chrysler Pacifica minivan, in the United States as it navigates soft demand and shifts its North American electrification strategy.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-scraps-us-plug-in-hybrid-sales-citing-weak-demand-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZ5TTPXMMVI77ELSRFZWBBGPSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:19:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed's Bostic says high inflation still central bank's main challenge -radio interview]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔·博斯蒂克周五在电台访谈中表示，通胀问题仍是其经济关切的核心焦点。他同时指出，在更广泛的不确定性背景下，就业市场仍处于低招聘、零裁员的状态。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic said on Friday in a radio interview inflation issues are still at the forefront of his economic concerns, in comments that added the job market continues to be in a low-hire, no-fire mode amid broader uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bostic-says-high-inflation-still-central-banks-main-challenge-radio-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JX2KM2CEQRJ5VP7LEIN2QVVWHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>