<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 06:06:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 06:06:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[泰国官员：目标是将对美贸易顺差降至 200 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国一位工业官员周五表示，泰国的目标是通过进口更多美国产品，将对美贸易顺差减少到 200 亿美元。【原文：Thailand is aiming to reduce its trade surplus with the United States to $20 billion by importing more U.S. products, an industry official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thailand-targets-reduction-trade-surplus-with-us-20-billion-official-says-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5LKYJ2T2ROBRHA7VFUNXKEZAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:47:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾称中国中芯国际涉嫌非法引诱技术工人]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾当局周五表示，他们正在调查中国最大的芯片制造商中芯国际是否在岛内一家伪装成萨摩亚人的空壳公司的掩护下非法诱骗台湾技术工人。【原文：Taiwan authorities said on Friday they were investigating whether China's largest chipmaker SMIC illegally lured Taiwanese tech workers under cover of a shell company on the island masquerading as Samoan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwan-says-chinas-smic-suspected-illegally-luring-tech-workers-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NH5KO4QPBZNM5M77SAIWSJKP4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标关税大屠杀仍在继续]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DK46A6EA3VNQBGYIP3NODZ2RPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:31:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普反复无常的关税政策动摇欧洲市场牛市信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲股市和欧元在第一季度表现抢眼，许多人担心这夸大了计划中的公共开支增长能以多快的速度重振该地区依然低迷的经济，并使其免受贸易战风险的影响。【原文：Investors are calling time on a rally in European stocks and the euro after a blistering first quarter that many fear has exaggerated how fast a planned public spending boom can revive the region's still sluggish economy and shore it up against trade war risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-erratic-tariff-policy-shakes-confidence-europes-market-bull-run-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V45736GQGVJ6NCAEJI5XBUZLVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普关税政策下，美国汽车买家面临价格上涨、选择减少的局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家表示，各大汽车制造商可以通过多种方式应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对美国进口汽车征收关税，但所有这些方式都会导致价格上涨、车型选择减少或限制消费者的功能。【原文：Major automakers can deal with President Donald Trump's tariffs on U.S. auto imports in a number of ways, but all of them lead to higher prices, fewer choices of models or limits on features for consumers, industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-car-buyers-face-higher-prices-less-choice-under-trumps-tariffs-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PCG2RYWYRIF5FYA2O7RKHR3VI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田汽车 2 月份全球产量连续第二个月增长，得益于稳健的日本销量]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周五表示，去年从日本国内市场的认证丑闻中恢复过来后，受日本产量增加和销售强劲的推动，2月份全球产量连续第二个月增长。【原文：Toyota Motor said on Friday its global production rose for the second consecutive month in February, driven by higher output and stronger sales in Japan after recovering from a certification scandal in its home market last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyotas-global-output-rises-second-month-february-solid-japan-sales-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPKUOBLWMBIA5JKTGS7W3WVHGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:32:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经过多年生存，中国华为重返收入高峰]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国华为公司有望在即将发布的年度业绩报告中宣布战胜美国制裁，这得益于其在软件方面的推进、芯片领域的进步以及帮助其走出 "生存模式 "的智能驾驶技术业务的蓬勃发展。【原文：China's Huawei is expected to claim triumph over U.S. sanctions at its upcoming annual results, bolstered by its software push, progress in chips and booming smart-driving technology business that has helped it move out of "survival mode".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/after-years-survival-chinas-huawei-returns-revenue-peak-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNFNUDGUMRN4RJWXGD5L6VDMUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 03:44:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新华社报道：中国国家主席习近平在北京会见全球首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[据新华社报道，中国国家主席习近平周五在北京会见了全球首席执行官，但未提供任何细节。【原文：Chinese President Xi Jinping met with global CEOs in Beijing on Friday, Xinhua reported, without providing any details.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-president-xi-meets-with-global-ceos-beijing-xinhua-reports-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUOBCGYCZFJRHNYBC55BRDIDCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 03:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面临关税风险，特朗普组织关注越南数十亿美元项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[该财团的一位发言人告诉路透社，特朗普组织及其在越南的合作伙伴正致力于在这个东南亚国家投资价值数十亿美元的高尔夫球场、酒店和房地产项目。【原文：The Trump Organization and its partner in Vietnam are working on multiple investments worth billions of dollars in golf courses, hotels and real estate projects in the Southeast Asian country, a spokesman for the consortium told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-organization-eyes-multi-billion-dollar-projects-vietnam-amid-tariff-risks-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5ZCQMAKUVJWDN3OTFSQFHTJH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 03:14:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油维持在一个月高位附近，在供应困境中将迎来第三周上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国对从委内瑞拉购买石油和天然气的国家征收关税并对伊朗石油贸易实施限制后，全球供应前景趋紧，油价周五维持在一个月高点附近，并有望实现第三次周线上涨。【原文：Oil prices held near one-month highs on Friday and were poised for a third weekly gain on a tightening global supply outlook after the U.S. imposed tariffs against countries buying oil and gas from Venezuela and placed restrictions on Iranian oil trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-holds-near-one-month-high-set-third-week-gains-amid-supply-woes-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7N4RUV5NY5OE7DJTFNY4TB5JII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 03:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，亚洲股市下滑，黄金创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市下跌，韩国和日本股市遭到大量抛售，而避险黄金则创下了历史新高，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最新的关税言论激起了投资者对全面贸易战的担忧。【原文：Asian stocks fell on Friday with heavy selling in South Korea and Japan while safe-haven gold hit a record high as the latest tariff salvo from U.S. President Donald Trump stoked investor worries of an all-out trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">423ETY4FTBMD5KXJYNQUNNDOJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达支持的 CoreWeave 以每股 40 美元的价格在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）支持的云计算公司 CoreWeave 周四表示，其首次公开募股的定价为每股 40 美元，而此前的定价区间为每股 47 美元至 55 美元。【原文：Nvidia-backed cloud computing firm CoreWeave said on Thursday it had priced its initial public offering at $40 per share, compared with the earlier range of $47 to $55 per share.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/nvidia-backed-coreweave-prices-downsized-us-ipo-40-per-share-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPWWBQAXU5MTPFYXWQBBFGJBF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:53:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元在 PCE 和关税冲击前徘徊不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对关税导致美国经济增长放缓的担忧推低了美国收益率、股市和美元汇率，美元汇率在上周五趋于平稳，并在下周出现季度性下跌。【原文：The dollar was headed for a steady week on Friday and a quarterly loss next week as concern about tariffs slowing U.S. growth has pushed down U.S. yields, stocks and the currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-hovers-ahead-pce-tariff-onslaught-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MC4GJ3SANLTPI7AFVTK6TVEME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Star Entertainment 的悉尼赌场执照暂停期延长至 9 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚陷入困境的赌场运营商 Star Entertainment 周五表示，根据新南威尔士州独立赌场委员会（NICC）的建议，其 Star Sydney 赌场的执照将至少暂停至 9 月 30 日。【原文：Australian embattled casino operator Star Entertainment said on Friday that its casino licence for Star Sydney will remain suspended until at least September 30, as advised by the New South Wales Independent Casino Commission (NICC).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/star-entertainments-sydney-casino-licence-suspension-extended-till-september-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZJ2A4PUV5OJ3J2252CYUT6XSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚竞争监督机构批准维珍航空与卡塔尔航空结盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚竞争监管机构周五表示，已授权维珍澳大利亚航空公司和卡塔尔航空公司以综合联盟的形式在多哈与悉尼、墨尔本、布里斯班和珀斯之间运营航班，为期五年。【原文：Australia's competition regulator said on Friday it had granted authorisation to Virgin Australia and Qatar Airways to operate flights between Doha and Sydney, Melbourne, Brisbane and Perth under an integrated alliance for five years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australias-competition-watchdog-authorises-virgin-qatar-airways-alliance-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C64KQSIBHZNWDAOBC3ZBZRI6FQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国正推动与乌克兰达成更广泛的矿产协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉正在进行的谈判的人士透露，路透社获得的一份提案草案摘要显示，特朗普政府已提议与乌克兰达成一项新的、范围更广的矿产协议。【原文：The Trump administration has proposed a new, more expansive minerals deal with Ukraine, according to three people familiar with the ongoing negotiations and a summary of a draft proposal obtained by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-is-pushing-more-expansive-minerals-deal-with-ukraine-sources-say-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BKAMWYARNZNQFO3WN2GND5PXUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Semafor 记者称，新日铁、美国钢铁公司正在积极洽谈每股 55 美元的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Semafor 记者罗汉-戈斯瓦米（Rohan Goswami）在 X 网站上发文称，新日铁和美国钢铁公司正在积极洽谈交易，美国钢铁公司将以每股 55 美元的价格收购新日铁。【原文：Nippon Steel and U.S. Steel are in active talks about a deal that would offer $55 per share to U.S. Steel, Semafor reporter Rohan Goswami said in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-us-steel-active-talk-55-per-share-deal-semafor-reporter-says-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4BJBCJQNVOOZFKCDD3EGRXUDE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:30:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴金关税下的汽车企业将在定价和利润率方面面临艰难抉择]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席汤姆-巴金（Tom Barkin）表示，他预计消费者不会完全受到特朗普政府对进口汽车征收 25% 税收的影响，但他补充说，企业在定价和利润率方面将面临艰难的选择。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Tom Barkin said he did not expect consumers to face the full brunt of the 25% tax the Trump administration has set on imported cars, but added firms will have difficult choices ahead on pricing and profit margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/feds-barkin-auto-firms-under-tariffs-will-face-tough-choices-pricing-margins-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SENLASXWNVOVLLNALWW3HSE22A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:20:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）和波音公司将开始测试 "星际客机"，计划于 2026 年初进行下一次飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）周四表示，在波音公司的CST-100 Starliner首次飞往国际空间站的任务因系统故障而被迫延长停留时间后，该局正朝着今年晚些时候或2026年初对其进行载人飞行认证的方向迈进。【原文：NASA said on Thursday it was moving toward certifying Boeing's CST-100 Starliner for crewed flights later this year or by early 2026 after its inaugural mission to the International Space Station was marred by a system fault, forcing an extended stay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/nasa-boeing-start-testing-starliner-next-flight-aimed-early-2026-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXGCWG5ACNI77NAPFZRPMKCNBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克称特斯拉员工和客户蒙受巨大损失 -福克斯新闻]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周三在福克斯新闻的 "布雷特-拜尔特别报道 "节目中被问及特斯拉在经销商处发生的纵火袭击等事件时说，特斯拉员工和客户受到了极大的伤害。【原文：Tesla Chief Executive Elon Musk said on Wednesday that a great wrong was being done to Tesla employees and customers when asked on Fox News' "Special Report with Brett Baier" about incidents at dealerships that include arson attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-says-great-wrong-is-being-done-tesla-staff-customers-fox-news-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFJGGZJXK5MSBJ6OIATH5ZR2SA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国太空部队授予火箭实验室和斯托克太空公司国家安全合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国太空部队太空系统司令部周四表示，已授予美国火箭实验室（Rocket Lab USA）和斯托克太空公司（Stoke Space）合同，以扩大其关键太空能力发射系统的产品组合。【原文：​The U.S. Space Force's Space Systems Command said on Thursday it had awarded contracts to Rocket Lab USA and Stoke Space to expand its portfolio of launch systems for critical space capability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/us-space-force-awards-national-security-contracts-rocket-lab-stoke-space-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBKOQCHYSNMTFHPMVPRSH3HI3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[内部备忘录称，亚马逊米高梅影业主管珍-萨尔克将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，Prime Video 和亚马逊美高梅在线娱乐官网工作室（Amazon MGM Studios）负责人迈克-霍普金斯（Mike Hopkins）在发给员工的一份内部备忘录中称，亚马逊美高梅在线娱乐官网工作室负责人珍-萨尔克（Jen Salke）将卸任，创办一家新的制作实体。【原文：Jen Salke, head of Amazon's MGM Studios, will step down from her role to start a new production entity, according to an internal memo sent to employees by Prime Video and Amazon MGM Studios head Mike Hopkins, as seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/amazon-mgm-studios-head-jen-salke-depart-internal-memo-says-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6BNGLBOQJIPVL46KBTYHQQC4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 22:54:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯表示，关税显然将在短期内推动通胀上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周四表示，特朗普政府的关税将推动美国通胀率上升，但目前尚不清楚这种上升压力的持续性如何。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said on Thursday that Trump administration tariffs will drive up U.S. inflation but it is unclear how persistent that upward pressure will be.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-collins-says-it-is-clear-tariffs-will-drive-inflation-up-near-term-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHVY65KB75P6XFBPZZTIGBAJZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 22:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liberty 首席执行官古塞克认为钢铁关税对油田服务的影响不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[自由能源公司（Liberty Energy）首席执行官罗恩-古塞克（Ron Gusek）周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）决定对进口钢铁征收关税，油田服务供应商的盈利将受到适度冲击。【原文：Oilfield service providers will face modest hits to earnings from U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to impose tariffs on steel imports, Liberty Energy Chief Executive Ron Gusek said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/liberty-ceo-gusek-sees-modest-impact-steel-tariffs-oilfield-services-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TW2EYKOJA5O2FHS3RLGNFKF46I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 21:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利政府高官加入意法半导体监事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士称，意大利打算任命负责管理国营企业和资产处置的经济部部门主管马尔切洛-萨拉（Marcello Sala）为芯片制造商意法半导体的监事会成员。【原文：Italy intends to appoint Marcello Sala, head of an economy ministry department that manages state-run firms and asset disposals, as a supervisory board member at chip maker STMicroelectronics , three sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italian-top-government-official-seen-joining-stmicroelectronics-supervisory-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWAAHQVLEVJPNHT352VHX3GY24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 21:13:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 投资者寻找谨慎的汽车动机]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTJEXJQYYFKF7P4E7U7RKAXVYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 21:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：Citgo拍卖重启出现新的债权人之争]]></title><description><![CDATA[委内瑞拉拥有的美国炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司的股份拍卖在重新启动后被建议以较低的起拍价进行，因此，一名试图推进拍卖的美国联邦法官正在处理债权人之间的新纠纷。【原文：A U.S. federal judge trying to move ahead with an auction of shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned U.S. refiner Citgo Petroleum is dealing with a fresh dispute between creditors after a lowball starting bid was recommended in a reboot of the sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-creditors-battle-emerges-citgo-auction-reboot-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGGRG37FOBLJPM7JHSQA7XVROQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 20:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴金广泛的不确定性可能打击需求，政策正处于良好状态，等待更多澄清]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席汤姆-巴尔金（Tom Barkin）周四表示，美联储目前的 "适度限制性 "货币政策适合于美国政府政策不确定性异常大且变化迅速的环境。【原文：The Federal Reserve's current "moderately restrictive" monetary policy is right for an environment with an abnormal amount of uncertainty and fast changes taking place in U.S. government policy, Richmond Fed President Tom Barkin said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-barkin-extensive-uncertainty-could-hit-demand-policy-good-place-awaiting-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OVAHJUOFPNPCHH45ZUDDYAJBYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 20:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自由欧洲电台称特朗普政府撤销了拨款终止令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府资助的自由欧洲电台/自由电台周四表示，其上级机构已经撤销了终止对其拨款的命令，此前该新闻机构曾就削减拨款一事起诉特朗普政府。【原文：U.S. government-funded Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty said on Thursday that its parent agency had rescinded an order terminating its grant funding, after the news outlet sued the Trump administration over the cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/radio-free-europe-says-trump-administration-rescinded-its-grant-termination-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASRIG3AL7JN5DDTRYWHQHLYJ2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 20:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lululemon 预测年度业绩低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lululemon Athletica 周四预测的年度收入和利润低于预期，原因是缺乏更新的款式，促使顾客寻找 Alo Yoga 和 Vuori 等竞争对手的产品。【原文：Lululemon Athletica forecast annual revenue and profit below estimates on Thursday, as the lack of newer styles has been pushing customers to look for products from competitors such as Alo Yoga and Vuori.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lululemon-forecasts-annual-revenue-below-estimates-2025-03-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THD3JLPDXFN2FJT5IWJQ2B4GWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 20:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>