<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:06:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:06:20 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 第三季度出货量增长 13%，达到 130 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 汽车制造商周五表示，第三季度全球出货量同比增长 13%，估计达到 130 万辆。【原文：Stellantis' global shipments rose 13% year-on-year in the third quarter to an estimated 1.3 million units, the automaker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-third-quarter-shipments-rise-13-13-million-vehicles-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2D2NFRTFVMMPHMZ3CFFBZWHGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：比尔-盖茨与泛美卫生组织考虑为低收入国家提供减肥药物的方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[盖茨基金会和泛美卫生组织告诉路透社，这两个全球健康组织都在研究如何让低收入国家更容易获得减肥药物，如诺和诺德的Wegovy和礼来的Mounjaro。【原文：The Gates Foundation and the Pan American Health Organization are both working on ways to make weight-loss drugs like Novo Nordisk's Wegovy and Eli Lilly's Mounjaro more accessible in lower-income countries, the global health groups told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bill-gates-paho-consider-ways-bring-weight-loss-drugs-lower-income-countries-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5UP7XSW25I5DINGA4AUNS5VNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美紧张局势的最新症结是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）和中国国家主席习近平将于本月访问首尔，在中美举行会谈之前，中国政府正在积累谈判筹码，宣布新的出口管制措施，以加强对高科技制造业供应链的控制。【原文：Beijing is stacking up its bargaining chips ahead of expected U.S.-China talks when Presidents Donald Trump and Xi Jinping visit Seoul this month, announcing new export controls to tighten its grip over high-tech manufacturing supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/what-are-latest-sticking-points-us-china-tensions-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RACNVINLSRIF7NZOKANWOUPVKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[基金经理薪酬飙升让艾斯勒资本公司损失惨重]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者和业内人士表示，由于员工成本飙升侵蚀了交易利润，艾斯勒资本公司决定关闭其旗舰多策略对冲基金，这暴露出总部位于伦敦的基金在试图快速发展和复制规模更大、根基稳固的美国公司时所面临的困难。【原文：Eisler Capital's decision to close its flagship multi-strategy hedge fund as soaring staff costs eroded trading profit exposes the difficulty London-based funds face when trying to grow rapidly and replicate bigger, entrenched U.S. players, investors and industry insiders say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/soaring-fund-manager-pay-cost-eisler-capital-dear-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INUU2NKUYVJX3KPJDLHWJVMJGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，软银正在洽谈由 Arm 股票支持的 50 亿美元保证金贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，软银集团公司（SoftBank Group Corp）正在商谈以其芯片部门 Arm Holdings 的股票为抵押，向全球银行借入 50 亿美元保证金贷款。【原文：SoftBank Group Corp is in talks to borrow $5 billion from global banks for a margin loan secured by shares of its chip unit Arm Holdings , Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-talks-5-billion-margin-loan-backed-by-arm-stock-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2KVQ6A6LBIQ3GRZL2LRIOGBJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:55:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国海关加大对英伟达人工智能芯片的打击力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，中国加大了对芯片进口限制的执行力度，旨在减少国内科技公司对美国产品的依赖，如英伟达（Nvidia）的人工智能处理器。【原文：China has ramped up enforcement of its chip import restrictions, aiming to reduce domestic technology companies' dependence on U.S. products such as Nvidia's artificial intelligence processors, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-steps-up-customs-crackdown-nvidia-ai-chips-ft-reports-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNIXKTYQ2RJXTJNX4LEABWO7HQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利：劳动力市场正处于 "令人担忧 "的地步]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周四表示，劳动力市场疲软和通胀放缓是上个月做出降息决定的原因，并促使美联储发出了未来可能进一步降息的信号。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly said on Thursday that a softening labor market and easing inflation were reasons behind last month's decision to cut rates, and prompted the Fed to signal the possibility of further rate cuts ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-labor-market-is-worrisome-point-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLBBHOWX2NPCHJ7ISJQ6Q2U5JE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大宗商品反弹后喘息，亚洲股市波澜不惊，日元成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于华尔街的跌势持续到早盘，亚洲股市在本周结束时摇摇欲坠，而大宗商品市场则在近期冲高后稍作喘息。【原文：Asian stocks limped towards the end of the week on a shaky footing on Friday as declines on Wall Street lingered into early trading, while commodity markets took a breather after their recent charge higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2H2MMHDXJMOXN3D24TVSCQXRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:51:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加息预期减弱，日元创一年来最大单周跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元将创下一年来的最大单周跌幅，因为投资者担心今年再次加息的可能性迅速减小，而日本下任首相的言论也未能安抚市场的不安情绪。【原文：The yen was set for its steepest weekly drop in a year on Friday, as investors fretted about fast-receding chances of another rate hike this year while comments from Japan's likely next prime minister failed to soothe market jitters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-heads-sharpest-weekly-fall-year-rate-hike-wagers-recede-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYYDH6XDXFNQHLN24CCHW3MX7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加沙协议达成后风险溢价消退，石油价格变化不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚市早盘，油价在上一交易日下跌超过1%后变化不大，原因是以色列和哈马斯就结束加沙战争的第一阶段计划达成一致后，市场的战争风险溢价减弱。【原文：Oil prices were little changed in early Asian trade on Friday after falling more than 1% in the previous session, as the market's war risk premium faded after Israel and Hamas agreed to the first phase of a plan to end the war in Gaza.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-little-changed-amid-fading-risk-premium-after-gaza-deal-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGOI62V2TFITFC2HUPVVMEHHPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:19:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通估计美国每周申请失业救济人数再次增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）周四估计，上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量再次增加，暗示与美国政府停摆有关的一些提前裁员现象。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased again last week, JPMorgan estimated on Thursday, hinting at some early layoffs related to the U.S. government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increased-again-jpmorgan-estimates-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJIWWPFPDRNWLMDJLCQPREIK7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国停摆阻碍关键农作物数据，农民和贸易商 "盲目飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[在联邦政府停摆期间，对全球谷物和大豆交易至关重要的美国数据已经失效，导致大宗商品交易商和农民在秋收高峰期无法获得作物产量预估、出口销售数据和市场报告。【原文：U.S. data vital to global grain and soybean trading has gone dark during the federal government's shutdown, leaving commodity traders and farmers without crop production estimates, export sales data and market reports during the peak of the autumn harvest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/farmers-traders-flying-blind-us-shutdown-blocks-key-crop-data-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLNLOQWWY5NT5PL5BRRJY3RBSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称殖民地管道公司将裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，美国最大的燃料运输系统运营商 Colonial 管道公司本周通知员工，该公司正计划裁员。【原文：The Colonial Pipeline Company, operator of the largest U.S. fuel transportation system, informed employees this week that it is planning to cut some jobs, according to two sources familiar with the matter and a company statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/colonial-pipeline-cut-jobs-sources-say-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHAFCK2RMFP3PCK5LRG2K2JTH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:05:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，美国前美联储理事拉里-林赛撤回美联储主席候选人提名]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国有线电视新闻网（CNBC）周四报道，前美国联邦储备委员会理事拉里-林赛（Larry Lindsey）已退出美国央行主席一职的竞选。【原文：Former U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Larry Lindsey has withdrawn his name from consideration for the position of chair of the U.S. central bank, CNBC reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/former-us-fed-governor-larry-lindsey-withdraws-name-fed-chair-cnbc-reports-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5DENUBMSRLLPIETBKV6V5ZVOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街监管机构在政府停摆期间放宽 IPO 通道]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街最高监管机构周四在其网站上发布公告，放宽了公司在联邦政府关门期间进行首次公开募股的条件。【原文：Wall Street's top regulator on Thursday eased the way for companies to proceed with initial public offerings during the federal government's shutdown, according to an announcement on its website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/wall-street-regulator-eases-ipo-path-during-government-shutdown-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMA3G7JJVRINLAU5DIO6SULXEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:52:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CVS 称超过 81% 的会员参加了 2026 年的高评级医疗保险优势计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 周四表示，其 Aetna 保险业务在 2026 年的医疗保险优势计划中，有超过 81% 的会员被评为 4 星级或更高。【原文：CVS Health said on Thursday that its Aetna insurance business has over 81% of members in Medicare Advantage plans that are rated 4 stars or higher for 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/cvs-says-over-81-members-are-high-rated-medicare-advantage-plans-2026-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBIEF3RANBNWTGBMDIRBBQW5OA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:50:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能需求推动数据中心增长，应用数字公司收入超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[应用数字公司（Applied Digital）周四公布的第一季度营收超出华尔街预期，主要原因是越来越多的客户扩大计算规模，以支持快速增长的生成式人工智能应用，从而导致对其数据中心服务的需求激增。【原文：Applied Digital topped Wall Street estimates for first-quarter revenue on Thursday, driven by surging demand for its data center services as more customers scale up computing to support fast-growing generative AI applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/applied-digital-beats-revenue-estimates-ai-demand-fuels-data-center-growth-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHIJO24YBRL6VF4ATQK4WMQWLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：能见度降低，华尔街和黄金趋冷]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量。【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZRF6THHGNICVJ7W554LSAUTC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道继通用汽车之后，福特撤销申请电动汽车税收抵免的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司（Ford Motor）周四表示，在9月30日联邦补贴到期后，该公司将收回一项允许经销商为电动汽车租赁提供7500美元税收抵免的计划。【原文：Ford Motor is walking back a program that would have allowed dealers to offer a $7,500 tax credit on EV leases after the federal subsidy expired September 30, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-reverses-plan-claim-ev-tax-credits-following-gm-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IR444NJCJMY5PNHTHVRCZNAMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国石油公司在与 Venture Global 公司关于液化天然气货物的仲裁案中胜诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Global 公司周四表示，英国石油公司在对 Venture Global 公司的仲裁案中胜诉，原因是这家美国供应商未能按照一项长期合同交付液化天然气，该合同本应于 2022 年底开始执行。【原文：BP has won its arbitration case against Venture Global over the U.S. supplier's failure to deliver liquefied natural gas under a long-term contract that was due to start in late 2022, Venture Global said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bp-wins-arbitration-case-against-venture-global-over-lng-cargoes-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR7Y23TY7RKURL74PDW4TT2UCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥在立法前将与中国和其他国家讨论提高关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）周四表示，墨西哥国会将暂缓批准对来自中国和其他亚洲国家的近1500种产品加征关税的提案，同时墨西哥将与这些国家举行会谈，并考虑对提案进行修改。【原文：Mexico's Congress will hold off approving proposed tariff hikes on nearly 1,500 products from China and other Asian countries while Mexico holds talks with those countries and considers changes to the proposal, President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mexico-discuss-tariff-hikes-with-china-others-before-making-law-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M45J2URU4NLWNBNH6KBHR33GSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部干预后，花旗做多阿根廷 BONTE 30 指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行周四表示，在美国财政部采取干预措施支撑阿根廷货币后，该行将做多阿根廷 BONTE 30 债券。【原文：Citi said on Thursday it was going long into Argentina's BONTE 30 bonds following intervention by the U.S. Treasury to shore up the country's currency, adding it saw room for local assets to continue gains ahead of a key legislative vote.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/citi-is-going-long-argentina-bonte-30-after-us-treasury-intervention-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDI7IODLMFOE7BFBJKYRXP6RXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[李维斯-斯特劳斯（Levi Strauss）上调年度销售额和利润预期，原因是牛仔布需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 周四上调了全年销售额和利润预期，原因是尽管关税提高，但欧洲和美洲市场对阔腿牛仔裤的需求强劲。【原文：Levi Strauss raised its full-year sales and profit forecasts on Thursday, banking on strong demand for wide-leg denim bottoms in Europe and the Americas despite higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-lifts-annual-sales-profit-forecasts-resilient-denim-demand-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JPJFAWVPZKX5IFIG5UFCBCR7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国资金外流对 "成长型 "股票基金打击最大，全球 "价值型 "基金倾斜加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[基金经理们表示，越来越多的全球投资者开始转向非美国的 "价值型 "股票，因为美国的估值捉襟见肘、财政紧张加剧以及现金流预测减弱，使得美国股市的涨势看起来相对不那么吸引人。【原文：More global investors are rotating into non-U.S. "value" stocks, fund managers say, as stretched U.S. valuations, rising fiscal strains, and weakening cash flow forecasts make rallying American equities look comparatively less attractive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-value-tilt-intensifies-us-outflows-hit-growth-stock-funds-hardest-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CFVRVFUNBMD5JTLZFJIITHI3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 向欧盟监管机构表达竞争关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周四表示，它上个月向欧盟当局提交的论据反映了其关于人工智能领域竞争的公开声明，尤其是在对 Alphabet 旗下谷歌公司进行反垄断调查的背景下。【原文：OpenAI said on Thursday the arguments it presented to EU authorities last month mirrored its public statements about competition in the AI space, particularly in the context of antitrust investigations into Alphabet's Google.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/openai-flags-competition-concerns-eu-regulators-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITIQUA7G4VLTDOOAJ3U4F5K3XA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:15:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司利润增长放缓，人工智能支出成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公司第三季度的盈利增长可能会比今年早些时候温和，部分原因是可能会受到关税打击，同时投资者也在寻找人工智能方面的大量支出正在得到回报的迹象。【原文：U.S. companies could report milder earnings growth in the third quarter than earlier this year, partly due to a likely tariff hit, while investors look for signs that heavy spending on artificial intelligence is paying off.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-companies-profit-growth-seen-softer-spotlight-ai-spending-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DU4WVLYYLNNNZJMI6ZBNLYPQAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：美国在高级财政官员会议后购买了阿根廷比索]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，本周两国高级财政官员在华盛顿举行会议后，美国购买了阿根廷比索，并与阿根廷中央银行敲定了一项价值 200 亿美元的货币互换框架。【原文：The United States purchased Argentine pesos and finalized a $20 billion currency swap framework with Argentina's central bank after a meeting between the two countries' top finance officials in Washington this week, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-purchased-argentine-pesos-after-top-finance-officials-meeting-bessent-says-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JA5VBMYMWNJK5AZKKW7FAF56TY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称今年万圣节美国巧克力价格仍将居高不下]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行农业食品研究所（Wells Fargo's Agri-Food Institute）周四发布的一份报告显示，由于可可成本自 2024 年初以来翻了一番多，美国巧克力消费者在即将到来的万圣节期间将面临巧克力价格上涨的问题。【原文：U.S. chocolate consumers will face elevated chocolate prices this coming Halloween period as cocoa costs have more than doubled since early 2024, according to a report released on Thursday by Wells Fargo's Agri-Food Institute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chocolate-prices-set-remain-high-this-halloween-us-report-says-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GHMPO7VFIZLHFP4GOFWON2IJAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:49:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示数千用户的 Microsoft 365 出现故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 的数据，周四有数千名用户的微软生产力软件套件出现故障。【原文：Microsoft's suite of productivity software was down for thousands of users on Thursday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-365-down-thousands-users-downdetector-shows-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HB3K4FPIU5LXDNV3MNCTQFLDTE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，美国司法部对 First Brands 倒闭展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引知情人士的话报道称，美国司法部已对破产汽车零部件制造商 First Brands 集团的倒闭展开调查。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice has launched an inquiry into the collapse of bankrupt auto parts maker First Brands Group, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-justice-department-opens-inquiry-into-first-brands-ft-reports-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIJGFICGLZIDRNAGMNMXQJBRTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:40:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>