<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:34:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:34:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 "关税人 "大展拳脚，市场畏缩不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGNDUHFJIJOJBAQ7ERICEYLK3M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[申诉称，特朗普解雇从事 DEI 工作的联邦工作人员是非法的]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群联邦雇员周三向美国劳工委员会提起集体诉讼，声称他们因参与实施多元化、公平和包容政策而被解雇，这侵犯了他们的宪法权利。【原文：A group of federal employees filed a class action complaint with a U.S. labor board on Wednesday claiming they were fired for their involvement in implementing diversity, equity and inclusion policies, in violation of their constitutional rights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-firings-federal-workers-with-dei-jobs-were-illegal-complaint-claims-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMM3WK25ZNJ33MDSXHDX4XSG3Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰富瑞利润因债券交易和股票承销疲软而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰富瑞银行周三发布报告称，由于美国贸易政策变化和地缘政治动荡引发的不确定性，债券交易疲软，股市交易停滞，该行第一季度利润下降近 15%。【原文：Jefferies' first-quarter profit fell nearly 15%, the bank reported on Wednesday, as bond trading weakened and stock market deals were stalled due to uncertainty sparked by shifting U.S. trade policy and geopolitical turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jefferies-profit-falls-weaker-bond-trading-equity-underwriting-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3OCQ56NZNKSXCJMITXM2JTP4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:23:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长告诉福克斯新闻：乌克兰可能在下周签署经济协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，乌克兰可能在下周签署一项经济协议，如果有必要，唐纳德-特朗普总统将毫不犹豫地加强对俄罗斯的制裁。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday Ukraine may sign an economic deal next week and President Donald Trump will not hesitate to raise sanctions on Russia if the need arises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/ukraine-may-sign-economic-deal-next-week-us-treasury-chief-tells-fox-news-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CDZDNTZFVI2FGZT6SYWK4Q5VI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[木薯科学公司必须面对有关阿尔茨海默氏症药物的恶意起诉诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[生物技术公司卡萨瓦科学公司（Cassava Sciences）周三未能结束医生和做空者对其即将停产的阿尔茨海默氏症试验性药物西姆非拉姆（simufilam）表示怀疑而提起的恶意诉讼。【原文：The biotechnology company Cassava Sciences failed on Wednesday to end a malicious prosecution lawsuit by doctors and short-sellers who expressed doubts about its experimental, soon-to-be-discontinued Alzheimer's drug simufilam.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cassava-sciences-must-face-malicious-prosecution-lawsuit-over-alzheimers-drug-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVUQLD7Y5BM7ZMWTFDIZ7RCBQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:49:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，OpenAI 预计到 2029 年才能实现现金流正增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三援引一位知情人士的话报道称，OpenAI 预计其现金流要到 2029 年才能转正。【原文：OpenAI is not expecting its cash flow to turn positive until 2029, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-does-not-expect-be-cash-flow-positive-until-2029-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEIHB4XYFZP35GKCZ763WMWT74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局今年将招聘 2000 名空中交通管制员，继续对波音公司进行严格监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）代理局长在周四向美国参议院一个小组提交的书面证词中表示，该局计划今年招聘 2000 名空中交通管制员学员，并对波音公司（Boeing BA.N）保持严格监管。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration plans to hire 2,000 air traffic controller trainees this year and maintain strict oversight of Boeing BA.N, the agency's acting administrator said in written testimony to be given to a U.S. Senate panel on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/faa-hire-2000-air-traffic-controllers-this-year-maintain-strict-boeing-oversight-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EJC27BR6FLCZBZEJFPJSZPIAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:55:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音-洛克希德公司的 "火神 "获准发射美国国家安全卫星]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国太空部队周三表示，已批准波音公司和洛克希德-马丁公司的火神火箭为美国发射国家安全卫星。【原文：The U.S. Space Force said on Wednesday it has cleared Boeing and Lockheed Martin's Vulcan rocket to launch national security satellites for the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/boeing-lockheeds-vulcan-cleared-launch-us-national-security-satellites-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRGUPA5CFNKWNOGPBHTKOKZ7IE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:54:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税阴影笼罩债务缠身的英国经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）成为笼罩在英国经济头上的最大威胁之一，英国的财政监督机构称，缓慢的经济增长和沉重的债务负担使英国特别容易受到他提议的关税的影响。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump emerged as one of the biggest threats hanging over the British economy on Wednesday, when the country's fiscal watchdog said slow growth and a heavy debt burden made it especially vulnerable to his proposed tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/trump-tariffs-loom-over-britains-debt-laden-economy-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVDG7JIUAFOQHJJDQO3JIWIXCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的证券交易委员会人选承诺制定 "合理 "的加密货币法规]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据参议院公开的准备证词，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）挑选的美国证券交易委员会主席保罗-阿特金斯（Paul Atkins）周三承诺，在他的领导下，监管将有利于加密货币行业，并防止政治 "扼杀 "资本形成。【原文：Paul Atkins, President Donald Trump's pick to run the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, pledged on Wednesday that regulations under his leadership would benefit the crypto sector and prevent politics from "stifling" capital formation, according to prepared testimony made public by the Senate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-sec-pick-pledges-rational-crypto-regulations-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6GN4JMJHRNWJC5R46KSNQ3IVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，收购公司围攻雀巢 50 亿欧元的水业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，PAI Partners 和贝恩资本是考虑竞购雀巢水业务的收购公司之一，该业务在交易中的估值可能约为 50 亿欧元（53.8 亿美元）或更高。【原文：PAI Partners and Bain Capital are among the buyout firms considering bidding for Nestle's water business, which could be valued at about 5 billion euros ($5.38 billion) or more in a deal, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/buyout-firms-circling-nestles-5-billion-euros-water-business-bloomberg-news-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DS6SQLGWXBKEFCT3M6CGSKVHPU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛的复活节套餐没有鸡蛋]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国零售业巨头沃尔玛周三表示，在禽流感疫情导致鸡蛋短缺、价格飙升的情况下，沃尔玛今年的复活节餐食将不提供鸡蛋。【原文：Walmart will be skipping eggs in its Easter meal offer this year, the U.S. retail giant said on Wednesday, in the midst of shortages and sky-high prices spiked by the bird flu outbreak among poultry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmarts-easter-meal-kit-leaves-out-eggs-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HWTVK7E7HBJH3EEJ4GHYCXZM74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:46:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑海协议不可能在短期内促进俄罗斯粮食出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和业内人士周三表示，一项被华盛顿和莫斯科吹捧为全球粮食安全福音的放宽俄罗斯进入国际农产品市场限制的潜在协议不太可能产生什么直接影响。【原文：A potential deal to ease restrictions on Russia's access to international agricultural markets, touted by Washington and Moscow as a boon for global food security, is unlikely to have much immediate impact, analysts and industry sources said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/black-sea-deal-unlikely-boost-russian-food-exports-short-term-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMADXOI7ZFNWDDJEKD375GB23U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:44:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，自马斯克收购以来，X 公司将首次实现年度广告收入增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司 Emarketer 周三提供的数据显示，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）旗下的社交媒体平台 X 自 2022 年被这位亿万富翁收购以来，今年将迎来广告收入增长的第一年。【原文：Elon Musk-owned social media platform X is poised for the company's first year of advertising revenue growth since its acquisition by the billionaire in 2022, data from research firm Emarketer showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/x-report-first-annual-ad-revenue-growth-since-musks-takeover-data-shows-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWVL5GBRTZITDNCHDFFVMXIQMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:43:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：欧盟高官预计特朗普将征收约 20% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，欧盟最高贸易谈判代表马罗什-谢夫乔维奇（Maroš Šefčovič）预计，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下周将对欧盟征收约20%的关税。【原文：The European Union's top trade negotiator Maroš Šefčovič expects U.S. President Donald Trump to hit the bloc with tariffs of about 20% next week, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/top-eu-official-expects-trump-tariffs-about-20-ft-reports-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIERJJXOLZP5BF2D3W52VIZKIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士政党计划遏制瑞银投资银行，以此作为资本规则的交换条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位资深立法者周三表示，作为旨在降低该行业风险的监管改革的一部分，瑞士的一个主要政党可能很快会提议对瑞银集团的投资银行活动设置上限。【原文：One of Switzerland's main political parties could soon propose capping UBS's investment banking activities as part of a regulatory overhaul aimed at making the sector less risky, a senior lawmaker said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swiss-party-plans-curb-ubs-investment-bank-trade-off-capital-rules-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7KLH2547RMTFIUKQ6SRDXYGTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储穆萨莱姆称关税可能引发更持久的通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周三表示，美国通胀率将停滞在美联储2%的目标之上，甚至在短期内进一步上升的风险已经增加，进口税的上升可能会引发更持久的物价压力。【原文：Risks have increased that U.S. inflation will stall above the Federal Reserve's 2% target or even rise further in the near term, with rising import taxes potentially triggering more persistent price pressures, St. Louis Fed president Alberto Musalem said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/st-louis-feds-musalem-says-tariffs-could-trigger-more-persistent-inflation-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAZPNFS2BJKFFFI5E4QVG6UJ3A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称可口可乐装瓶商遭到欧盟反垄断监管机构突袭]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位直接了解此事的人士说，可口可乐的装瓶商在本月早些时候遭到了欧盟反垄断监管机构的突袭。【原文：Coca Cola bottlers were raided by EU antitrust regulators earlier this month, a person with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coca-cola-bottlers-raided-by-eu-antitrust-regulators-source-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5J72XPYLZIIHPNZNYNT3Q5YHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普可能利用 2019 年的调查作为对汽车进口征收关税的理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业专家和前美国官员表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府很可能会利用他在第一个任期内完成的一项调查来为他所说的即将实施的汽车关税辩护。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is likely to use an investigation completed during his first term in office to justify auto tariffs that he says are imminent, industry experts and former U.S. officials said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-could-use-2019-investigation-justify-tariffs-auto-imports-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2QFBLPXE5KJDENYULU3W3WVAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:59:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称微软放弃在美国和欧洲租赁更多数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[道明证券（TD Cowen）分析师周三表示，由于供过于求，相对于当前的需求预测，微软在过去六个月中放弃了将在美国和欧洲使用 2 千兆瓦电力的数据中心项目。【原文：Microsoft has abandoned data center projects set to use 2 gigawatts of electricity in the U.S. and Europe in the last six months due to an oversupply relative to its current demand forecast, TD Cowen analysts said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-pulls-back-more-data-center-leases-us-europe-analysts-say-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3USLFKN45OTRKR4S3W3Y6QPIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于担心关税，意大利葡萄酒对美国的出口 "停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易集团Federvini周三表示，由于唐纳德-特朗普总统可能在未来几周内征收关税的不确定性，意大利葡萄酒和烈酒对美国的出口正在停滞。【原文：Italian wine and spirits exports to the United States are stalling due to the uncertainty over possible tariffs that President Donald Trump could impose in the coming weeks, trade group Federvini said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italian-wine-exports-us-at-standstill-due-tariff-fears-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5QJZ765NNK4BASIEL3YEGHK3M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普准备最快于周三宣布汽车关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）援引知情人士的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）准备最快于周三宣布有关汽车征税的消息。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is readying an announcement on auto levies as soon as Wednesday, Bloomberg News reported citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-is-preparing-auto-tariff-announcement-soon-wednesday-bloomberg-news-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5ZVMUR2LZMJPPKLNKHUZ63BGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表与中国副总理就贸易紧张局势表达 "坦率 "关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）准备进一步提高对中国进口商品的关税之际，美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）的办公室表示，格里尔在一次介绍性会晤中与中国国务院副总理何立峰就贸易问题进行了 "坦诚 "的会谈。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer held "candid" talks with Chinese Vice Premier He Lifeng on trade issues during an introductory meeting, Greer's office said as U.S. President Donald Trump prepares to raise tariffs on Chinese imports further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-trade-chief-chinese-vice-premier-express-candid-concerns-trade-tensions-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AF54MRMLDBMGRMYCA765NKJWSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:14:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席技术官就下一代喷气发动机的维护需求发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的航空公司之一的最高采购官员周三敦促通用电气航空航天公司和其他发动机制造商在设计下一代节油发动机时不要忽视耐用性。【原文：The top procurement official at one of Europe's largest airlines urged GE Aerospace and other engine makers on Wednesday not to overlook durability when it comes to designing the next generation of fuel-saving engines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lufthansa-cto-warns-over-maintenance-demand-next-jet-engines-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWHE2KTYDJPCTF4MW2KSF564GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:13:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：在具有里程碑意义的税务案件中，意大利要求 Meta、X 和 LinkedIn 缴税]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，四位直接了解此事的消息人士称，意大利已向 Meta、X 和 LinkedIn 提出税务要求，这是对美国科技巨头史无前例的增值税索赔的最后一个正式步骤，可能会对整个欧盟产生影响。【原文：Italy has handed tax demands to Meta , X and LinkedIn in the last formal step in an unprecedented VAT claim against the U.S. tech giants that could have repercussions across the European Union, four sources with direct knowledge of the matter said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italy-hands-vat-bill-meta-x-linkedin-landmark-tax-case-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZFAKC3S7VIUBKMZU3VZ22S2HI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡什卡利：美联储应在政策不确定的情况下长期按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周三表示，他对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税对美国经济的影响感到不确定，关税可能会推高物价，因此需要提高利率，而关税可能会减缓经济增长，因此需要降低借贷成本。【原文：Minneapolis Federal Reserve Bank President Neel Kashkari on Wednesday said he's uncertain about the effect of President Donald Trump's tariffs on the U.S. economy, with the possibility that they could push up prices arguing for higher interest rates, and the chance that they could slow economic growth calling for reducing borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-should-stay-put-extended-period-amid-policy-uncertainty-kashkari-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLDBREWBVVMLDACNSHYELEUNAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis的玛莎拉蒂在重新发布计划之前增加了定制选项]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利跑车制造商玛莎拉蒂是 Stellantis 集团旗下业绩最差的品牌之一，该公司周三表示，正在加强利润丰厚的定制服务，同时制定更广泛的扭亏为盈计划。【原文：Italian sports car maker Maserati, one of the worst performing brands within the Stellantis group, said on Wednesday it was boosting lucrative customisation services while working on wider turnaround plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-maserati-boosts-customisation-options-ahead-relaunch-plans-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VEXNTCC55O5ZHFCMYBAUX2SVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达拉斯联储称第一季度美国石油和天然气活动有所增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储周三的一项调查显示，2025 年第一季度美国石油和天然气行业的活动略有增加，但企业的不确定性和悲观情绪也有所上升。【原文：Activity in the U.S. oil and gas sector increased slightly in the first quarter of 2025, but uncertainty and pessimism among companies also rose, a Dallas Fed survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-gas-activity-edged-up-first-quarter-dallas-fed-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKQXBYQROBN6XO2GBKQEZGD7YU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:28:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富达投资公司测试与美元挂钩的稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国资产管理公司富达投资公司（Fidelity Investments）正在探讨是否推出自己的稳定币，这是主流投资者希望从加密货币兴趣复苏中套现的最新迹象。【原文：U.S. asset manager Fidelity Investments is exploring whether to launch its own stablecoin, in the latest sign of mainstream investors looking to cash in on a revival of interest in cryptocurrencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fidelity-investments-tests-dollar-pegged-stablecoin-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYPQVK4YIVNBLIZUQTSKHIT4PA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 月中旬纳斯达克指数短线兴趣上涨 2.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克交易所在周二晚些时候发布的一份声明中说，3 月中旬纳斯达克指数的空头利率上升了约 2.2%。【原文：Short interest on the Nasdaq rose about 2.2% in mid-March, the exchange said in a statement released late on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-short-interest-up-22-mid-march-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWHOOM3A5BLBVPJEQSJZZZBZKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:59:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>