<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:15:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:15:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对市场大跌的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者继续抛售高估值的科技股，周五亚洲和欧洲股市延续了全球股市的颓势，美国股票期货也显示华尔街开盘疲软。【原文：Asian and European shares extended a global rout on Friday and U.S. stock futures also pointed to a weak opening on Wall Street as investors continued to offload richly valued technology stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-selloff-quotes-instant-view-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WOYEHDO5VOVHGKCZOE7C4AD5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:54:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称 AIP 计划出售或上市法国铝厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位工会官员周五表示，美国投资公司 American Industrial Partners 计划出售法国最大的铝厂 Aluminium Dunkerque 或将其在股票市场上市。【原文：U.S. investment firm American Industrial Partners plans to sell or list on the stock market Aluminium Dunkerque, France's largest aluminium plant, a union official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/aip-plans-sale-or-listing-french-aluminium-plant-union-says-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46GM5WJGOZOHTDYFRAFFYH3WNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:49:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯称美联储仍可在 "近期 "降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，美国联邦储备委员会仍可在 "近期内 "降息，而不会使其通胀目标面临风险。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve can still cut interest rates "in the near term" without putting its inflation goal at risk, New York Fed president John Williams said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-williams-says-fed-can-still-cut-rates-near-term-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2E5N6OM2BK25FRF7MTT4ACHZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度和欧洲央行同意启动连接国内支付系统的初始阶段]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度储备银行（Reserve Bank of India）周五表示，印度和欧盟央行已同意启动国内支付系统联网的初始阶段。【原文：The central banks of India and the European Union have agreed to start the initial phase of linking domestic payments systems, the Reserve Bank of India said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-europe-central-banks-agree-start-initial-phase-linking-domestic-payment-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2KODRZJBFNZZICG5PM4SPXTOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业盈利乐观，全球股票基金连续第九周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球股票基金连续第九周吸引资金流入，原因是基金投资者受到第三季度整体强劲财报的鼓舞，消除了对科技股估值过高的担忧。【原文：Global equity funds attracted inflows for a ninth straight week as fund investors, encouraged by an overall strong third-quarter earnings season, brushed off concerns about lofty tech valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6ME45HSRJOT5LQUXHFSJ34EFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:09:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标信息交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克-多兰（Mike Dolan）和投资回报率团队周末兴奋阅读、观看和收听的一切。
编辑的话【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.
From the Editor】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENQBAZ3A3BODNITIVPHTRMBLRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普取消对巴西的关税后全球咖啡价格暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[面对美国消费者对食品成本高企日益增长的忧虑，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普取消了对包括咖啡和可可在内的巴西农产品征收 40% 的进口关税，导致周五全球咖啡价格暴跌。【原文：Global coffee prices plunged on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump removed 40% tariffs on imports of Brazilian agricultural products including coffee and cocoa in the face of growing angst from American consumers about high food costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-coffee-prices-plunge-after-trump-removes-tariffs-brazil-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYUZXY3BONNAXLULPTO4CASLII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[红十字会将裁员近 3000 人，缩减预算以应对捐赠疲劳症]]></title><description><![CDATA[红十字国际委员会周五在一份声明中说，它将把 2026 年的预算减少 17%，减至 18 亿瑞士法郎（约合 22.3 亿美元），并裁员 2900 人。【原文：The International Committee of the Red Cross will reduce its 2026 budget by 17% to 1.8 billion Swiss francs ($2.23 billion)and cut 2,900 jobs, it said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/red-cross-shed-nearly-3000-jobs-scale-back-budget-amid-donor-fatigue-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42HJ74GH2ZOIDMKXZ6WXU5BYFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VinFast 季度亏损因巨额支出而扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南 VinFast 公司周五公布的第三季度净亏损增加，原因是这家电动汽车制造商斥巨资扩大业务范围，并在激烈的竞争中提高销售额。【原文：Vietnam's VinFast reported a bigger third-quarter net loss on Friday as the electric vehicle maker spent heavily to expand its footprint and boost sales amid stiff competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vinfasts-quarterly-revenue-jumps-strong-deliveries-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBFD3BRI5FKCJD6UISFLWV75RE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[页岩钻机闲置，裁员人数增加，60 美元的油价考验二叠纪的抗压能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国得克萨斯州的页岩产业中心，石油产量正在不断攀升。但如果你和马克-沃特斯（Mark Waters）交谈，你就不会知道这一点，他拥有一家向石油公司销售工具和安全设备的商店。【原文：At the heart of the U.S. shale industry in Texas, oil production is climbing. But you wouldn't know that if you talked to Mark Waters, who owns a store that sells tools and safety equipment to oil firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shale-rigs-idle-layoffs-rise-60-oil-tests-resilience-permian-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O43FN2AJKRLTDEDCWVBEGZTLJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:10:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国各州瞄准数据驱动定价，以减轻消费者的痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在白宫试图推翻各州关于人工智能的法律之际，各州也在推行越来越多的法案，禁止技术驱动的定价行为，以减轻消费者的高成本负担。【原文：Even as the White House seeks to roll back state laws on artificial intelligence, states are pursuing an increasing number of bills to ban tech-driven pricing practices in an effort to bring consumers relief from high costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-states-take-aim-data-driven-pricing-ease-consumer-pain-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKV7LAMZ55JEFCBZ2FIUWBBDGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国两年来最大规模购买美国大豆提振价格，引发陷入困境的农民出售大豆]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周美国向中国出售了两年多来最大的大豆，这可能只是中国政府加速购买计划的开始，在此之前，由于与华盛顿的贸易战，这个世界第一大进口国已连续数月避开美国的供应。【原文：The largest U.S. soybean sales to China in more than two years this week could be just the beginning of an accelerated buying program by Beijing after the world's top importer shunned U.S. supplies for months due to a trade war with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-largest-us-soybean-buy-2-years-buoys-prices-triggers-sales-by-struggling-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGKAKNM2DBKM7EUVDXZKI7VMO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻：黑色星期五让坎坷市场聚焦消费支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国股市在本月陷入低迷，投资者将在未来一周寻找美国消费者走强的迹象，黑色星期五将成为假日购物季的焦点。【原文：With U.S. stocks in the midst of a grim month, investors will look in the coming week for signs of strength in the U.S. consumer with Black Friday putting the spotlight on the holiday shopping season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-black-friday-puts-focus-consumer-spending-rocky-markets-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHSQITHZYJIJPNFQKBAFMQSQT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普的 "金顶 "导弹防御系统面临延误和挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[八位熟悉情况的消息人士告诉路透社，唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "金色圆顶 "导弹防御计划正面临重大延误，原因是政府停摆43天，以及缺乏明确计划来使用今年夏天为该计划拨付的首批250亿美元资金。【原文：President Donald Trump's Golden Dome missile defense initiative is facing significant delays, hampered by the 43-day government shutdown and lack of a clear plan to spend the first $25 billion appropriated for the program this summer, eight sources familiar with the situation told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delays-setbacks-loom-over-trumps-golden-dome-missile-shield-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UO4RSZMIJNL5RBFZQ3XIFWHTDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[反垄断审判即将结束，谷歌希望避免广告业务被分拆]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国司法部的反垄断案接近尾声，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司将于周五在美国法院为避免其广告技术业务被分拆而提出最后的请求。【原文：Alphabet's Google will make its final plea to avoid a breakup of its advertising technology business in a U.S. court on Friday, as the Department of Justice's antitrust case draws to a close.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/google-aims-dodge-breakup-ad-business-antitrust-trial-wraps-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAGAMHAQ3FOX3ECFETDDCYQCWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国科技巨头纷纷涌入债券市场，人工智能支出引发的恐慌情绪将加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者越来越担心，用于为人工智能投资提供资金的公共债务迅速增加，可能会给美国企业债券市场带来压力，并最终削弱科技股的吸引力，尽管目前大多数大公司的杠杆率仍然很低。【原文：Investors are growing uneasy that the rapid rise in public debt used to bankroll AI investments could strain the U.S. corporate bond market and eventually dampen the appeal of tech stocks, despite leverage across most major companies remaining low for now.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/jitters-over-ai-spending-set-grow-us-tech-giants-flood-bond-market-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2LJ5UR6EZOJTAUCCCH5E7UM6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技股继续下挫，标普 500 指数和纳斯达克指数期货承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，纳斯达克和 S&amp;P 500 指数期货下跌，包括英伟达（Nvidia）在内的大多数科技股在前一交易日下挫后继续承压，原因是市场对该行业估值过高的担忧持续存在。【原文：Futures tied to the Nasdaq and the S&amp;P 500 fell on Friday, with most technology stocks, including Nvidia, remaining under pressure following a selloff in the previous session, as concerns over stretched valuations in the sector persisted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sp-500-nasdaq-futures-under-pressure-tech-selloff-continues-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MEW62RIJRIERLALIRHA2OQSH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国对俄罗斯石油巨头的制裁将如何影响卢布和经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对俄罗斯石油公司（Rosneft）和卢克石油公司（Lukoil）的制裁将于格林尼治标准时间周五17:01生效，以下是制裁可能对俄罗斯外汇市场产生的影响。【原文：Here is a look at how U.S. sanctions on Russian oil firms Rosneft and Lukoil, which take effect at 1701 GMT on Friday, may affect the Russian foreign currency market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-us-sanctions-russian-oil-majors-will-impact-rouble-economy-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APBWT3WA7JLW5F46QFYZXX55QA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:51:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行称，2025 年科技股仍将创下 750 亿美元的流入纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（BofA）周五发布的每周资金流向显示报告称，今年科技股仍有望实现创纪录的 750 亿美元资金流入，这凸显了市场对该行业的需求，即使该行业因估值过高而面临压力。【原文：Tech stocks remain on track for a record $75 billion inflow this year, BofA's weekly flow show note said on Friday, highlighting demand for the sector even as it comes under pressure from concerns about lofty valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-flows-bofa-urgent-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZLAOJXKUVM5LDMRC4D5EFXRJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:01:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长拉加德：欧盟可通过国内贸易打败特朗普的关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）周五表示，如果欧盟降低一些内部壁垒，就可以抵消美国贸易关税的影响。【原文：The European Union can offset the impact of U.S. trade tariffs if it knocks down some of its internal barriers, European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eu-can-beat-trumps-tariffs-with-domestic-trade-ecbs-lagarde-says-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHJSB7CQLNN3FMARJJRVAGY6O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元干预迫在眉睫，但未必奏效]]></title><description><![CDATA[日元的顽固疲软使日本濒临多年来第三次干预货币市场的边缘，但分析人士称，这很可能是无效的，当局必须谨慎行事，以避免引发新一轮抛售。【原文：A stubbornly weak yen has Japan on the cusp of intervening in the currency market for the third time in roughly as many years, but analysts say it's likely to be ineffective and authorities must tread carefully to avoid triggering a fresh selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-intervention-looms-large-it-may-not-work-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4XBCFFIONILNIA5HYBIRGBUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:24:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲军火制造商因乌克兰和平进程而跌至 9 月以来最低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在乌克兰总统沃洛德梅尔-泽连斯基（Volodymyr Zelenskiy）表示愿意就美国支持的结束战争计划开展诚实的工作后，欧洲国防股跌至 9 月初以来的最低水平。【原文：European defence shares fell to their lowest levels since early September on Friday, after Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said he was ready for honest work on a U.S.-backed plan to end the war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/european-arms-makers-stumble-ukraine-peace-push-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6YNKJNKBVLQNMLQUTL2Q7WATI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:18:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[育碧季度营收超预期，腾讯交易助其削减债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国视频游戏集团育碧周五公布的第二季度净预订额超过了其指导目标，并表示来自中国腾讯的 10 亿欧元（12 亿美元）投资将使其能够减少债务。【原文：French video game group Ubisoft reported second-quarter net bookings that exceeded its guidance on Friday, and said the 1-billion-euro ($1.2 billion) investment from China's Tencent would enable it to reduce its debt pile.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/ubisofts-quarterly-bookings-beat-guidance-tencent-deal-helps-cut-debt-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMEQW6A4SZK7DJGGGXCOINX6O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:51:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利在采取补救措施后结束对谷歌不正当使用个人数据的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利竞争管理机构周五表示，在网络搜索巨头谷歌采取补救措施后，该机构已结束了去年启动的对谷歌涉嫌在使用个人数据方面采取不公平商业行为的调查。【原文：Italy's competition authority said on Friday it had closed a probe it had launched last year over Google's alleged unfair commercial practices in the use of personal data after the online search giant adopted remedies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/italy-closes-google-probe-over-unfair-use-personal-data-after-remedies-adopted-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WK6H5MPH5NMVOVN4ON7L2TAV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:24:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Binance CEO Teng 称比特币波动与大多数资产类别一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[Binance 首席执行官理查德-滕（Richard Teng）周五表示，比特币在过去一个月的大幅下跌是投资者去杠杆化加密货币持有量和避险情绪的结果，这与大多数主要资产类别的情况一致。【原文：Binance Chief Executive Richard Teng said on Friday bitcoin's sharp drop in the past month was the result of investors deleveraging cryptocurrency holdings and risk aversion in line with that seen in most major asset classes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/binance-ceo-teng-says-bitcoin-volatility-line-with-most-asset-classes-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQBJ7XFUOBPR7MIY4F6EEZTHZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备受瞩目的美元套期保值热潮暂时放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在美国关税冲击美元的几个月后，海外投资者急于保护其持有的美国货币免受汇率下滑的影响的步伐急剧放缓，这是对美元投下的信任票，有助于美元从多年来最严重的颓势中恢复过来。【原文：Just months after a U.S. tariff shock whacked the dollar, a rush by overseas investors to protect U.S. holdings from the sliding currency has slowed sharply - a vote of confidence that's helping the greenback recover from its worst rout in years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/much-anticipated-dollar-hedging-rush-slows-now-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGGK2FBW7NM2BHZH3ABVAOSJKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国威立雅将以 30 亿美元收购有害废物处理集团 Clean Earth]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国水管理、废物管理和能源服务集团威立雅周五表示，已同意以 30 亿美元的价格收购美国有害废物公司 Clean Earth。【原文：French water management, waste management and energy services group Veolia said on Friday it had agreed to buy U.S.-based hazardous waste company Clean Earth for $3 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frances-veolia-buy-hazardous-waste-group-clean-earth-3-billion-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2H2N7E57Y5KZHCNZZZFNAAOYSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:33:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相顾问将在日本央行会议前的商业活动中发表讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新首相佐那江隆一的通货紧缩顾问将于 12 月 17 日在日本经济团体联合会（Keidanren）主办的一个小组讨论会上就新政府的经济强化战略发表演讲。【原文：Reflationist advisers of Japan's new prime minister Sanae Takaichi will speak on a panel hosted by Keidanren on December 17 on the new administration's strategy to strengthen the economy, the business lobby said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japan-premiers-advisers-will-speak-business-event-before-boj-meeting-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2WGAXJWB5PGHBSGCHAEGKHR5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币受到避险情绪的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，加密货币遭遇风险资产的广泛出逃，比特币和以太币跌至数月低点，原因是对高昂的科技估值的担忧持续存在，对美联储近期放松政策的押注也逐渐消退。【原文：Cryptocurrencies were caught in a broad flight from risk assets on Friday, sending bitcoin and ether to multi-month lows as worries persisted about lofty tech valuations and bets on near-term Federal Reserve policy easing faded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cryptocurrencies-whipped-by-flight-risk-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIR2FFAEG5MB5ASTJR42NGBACA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：科技股再度下挫，高市刺激政策落地，三把火齐发]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔-斯图尔特-亨特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HR57EP6SBJMOJHIO6PI34J4L4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:37:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>