<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 12:08:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 12:08:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Constellation Energy 将以 266 亿美元收购 Calpine]]></title><description><![CDATA[星座能源公司（Constellation Energy）周五表示，将以现金加股票的方式收购私人控股的地热和天然气能源公司 Calpine Corp，包括债务在内的交易价值为 266 亿美元。【原文：Constellation Energy said on Friday it would buy privately held Calpine Corp, a geothermal and natgas energy company, in a cash-and-stock deal valued at $26.6 billion including debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/constellation-energy-buy-calpine-266-bln-deal-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYN6QFA4E5I5TNLCLWJ5FZDXEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 12:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗预计全球股市涨势将延续至 2025 年，每股收益将增长 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周五表示，预计全球股市的涨势将延续到 2025 年，因为利率下降和通胀放缓可能有助于支撑企业盈利。【原文：Citigroup said on Friday it was expecting a rally in global equities to extend into 2025, as falling interest rates and easing inflation could help prop up corporate earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-expects-rally-global-stocks-extend-into-2025-sees-10-eps-growth-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUVIW4NZUBPHRM4NJESNQBFIHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛杉矶野火造成的损失不断增加，美国财产险和意外险保险公司业绩下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶野火肆虐，造成至少 10 人死亡，近 10,000 栋建筑被烧毁，其中五处大火已烧到第三天晚上。【原文：U.S. property and casualty insurance stocks fell in premarket trading on Friday after wildfires menacing Los Angeles killed at least 10 people and devoured nearly 10,000 structures, with five fires burning into a third night.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-property-casualty-insurers-slide-los-angeles-wildfire-losses-mount-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHSONY6AHVKGBK64QZV6CDIK4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空预测实现百年历史上最强劲的盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周五表示，预计 2025 年将成为该公司百年历史上盈利能力最强的一年，这主要得益于对高端旅行的强劲需求以及该行业定价能力的提高。【原文：Delta Air Lines said on Friday it expects 2025 to be the most profitable year in the company's 100-year history, thanks to robust demand for premium travel as well as the industry's improved pricing power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-forecasts-strongest-profit-its-100-year-history-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRJ65P4665LQTL56BUKEXVHWM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债券市场动荡，交易员对英镑信心大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据期权市场的数据，本周交易员对英镑的信心出现了自2022年英国预算危机以来的最大跌幅，原因是全球债券大跌加剧了对英国财政的不安，并使债券收益率升至16年来的新高。【原文：Traders' confidence in the pound has taken its biggest dive this week since the 2022 UK budget crisis, according to the options market, as a global bond selloff added to growing unease over Britain's finances and sent bond yields to 16-year highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/trader-confidence-sterling-takes-dive-bond-market-turmoil-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5KVDZP3UFPD5OTIC3IYBWFIP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关键薪资数据公布前，谨慎情绪导致期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在一份重要的劳动力市场报告公布之前，美国股指期货下滑，而此时，对通胀和即将上任的特朗普政府政策的担忧给美联储的货币政策前景蒙上了阴影。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Friday ahead of a crucial labor market report, at a time when concerns around inflation and the incoming Trump administration's policies have clouded the Federal Reserve's monetary policy outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-drop-caution-ahead-key-payrolls-data-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYED2FQP4BLDTK74UKCVFPZWRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:17:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价薪资水平提供现实检验，债券走势趋缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUOUV6QVKVLFJONJUAGNCZLXEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪推出全新紧凑型 SUV，加大欧洲市场拓展力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪周五表示，将于二月在欧洲推出新款 Atto 2 紧凑型 SUV，这将加剧欧洲电动汽车市场的竞争。【原文：BYD will launch its new Atto 2 compact SUV in Europe in February, the Chinese EV giant said on Friday, adding to competition in Europe's electric car market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-steps-up-europe-expansion-with-new-compact-suv-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V222TBYLABO3XGMZAT73ISYZIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:12:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期权市场认为美国 10 年期国债收益率短期内将达到 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[期货期权市场上的投资者押注基准美国 10 年期国债收益率在短期内将升至 5%，这反映出他们担心即将上任的特朗普政府的政策将增加本已臃肿的财政赤字并重振通胀。【原文：Investors in the futures options market are betting the benchmark U.S. 10-year Treasury yield is headed higher to 5% in the near term, reflecting worries that the incoming Trump administration's policies will increase an already bloated fiscal deficit and revive inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/options-market-positioned-us-treasury-10-year-yield-hit-5-near-term-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDLZTK6X6RNQFPSE4YGLXDOB4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院将审理美国即将对 TikTok 实施的禁令之争]]></title><description><![CDATA[面对美国迫在眉睫的禁令，TikTok 的命运将掌握在最高法院手中，该案将于本周五开庭审理，中国公司字节跳动（ByteDance）拥有的这款广泛使用的短视频应用程序将面临言论自由权与国家安全问题的对立。【原文：Facing a looming ban in the United States, TikTok's fate will be in the hands of the Supreme Court in a case being argued on Friday that pits free speech rights against national security concerns over the widely used short-video app owned by Chinese company ByteDance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/supreme-court-hear-fight-over-looming-us-ban-tiktok-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDD3AXYRW5ME5CFMDOV5RBSWSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:08:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝索斯的 "蓝色起源 "公司的 "新格伦 "号首次亮相，将对太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）构成期待已久的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰夫-贝索斯（Jeff Bezos）的蓝色起源公司（Blue Origin）将于本周日首次发射其巨型 "新格伦"（New Glenn）火箭，这是人们期待已久的首次跃入地球轨道，也是对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）的行业主导地位的最大挑战之一。【原文：Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin is set for an inaugural launch of its giant New Glenn rocket on Sunday, a long-awaited first leap to Earth orbit that sets up one of the biggest challenges yet to industry dominance enjoyed by Elon Musk's SpaceX.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/bezos-blue-origins-new-glenn-debut-pose-long-awaited-challenge-spacex-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ2VLTMZONLQRI6CVYUVYZ7HJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻：债券收益率攀升后，通胀报告可能引发市场震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的美国通胀数据可能会考验股票投资者的神经，进一步加剧对国债收益率上升和唐纳德-特朗普政策计划不确定性的担忧。【原文：U.S. inflation data in the coming week could test the nerves of stock investors and further inflame worries about rising Treasury yields and uncertainty over Donald Trump's policy plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-inflation-report-could-rattle-markets-after-bond-yields-climb-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74TZ4WLRNJOFZJF2XNPA4W74XY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行家希望 2025 年首次公开募股（IPO）复苏，因为高调上市的公司扎堆上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资银行家们正在为今年全球股票资本市场交易活动的回升做好准备，几家知名公司的首次公开募股预期前景看好，这将对全球股票资本市场的交易活动起到推动作用。【原文：Investment bankers are gearing up for a pickup in dealmaking activity in global equity capital markets this year, buoyed by a promising pipeline of anticipated initial public offerings of several high-profile companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bankers-hope-ipo-revival-2025-high-profile-listings-stack-up-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EP6CHSXID5MUNIM3OKIDZUYLQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因对美联储政策不确定性持谨慎态度，美国股票基金出现资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月8日的一周内，受美联储利率轨迹不确定性和即将上任的特朗普政府即将出台关税政策的影响，美国投资者撤出股票基金，转向安全的货币市场基金。【原文：U.S. investors pulled out of equity funds and moved to the safety of money market funds in the week to Jan. 8 driven by uncertainties about the Fed's interest rate trajectory and looming tariff policies by the incoming Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-outflows-caution-over-fed-policy-uncertainty-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSA4KCBCOFLRZDJ4Y3MK5KAIPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政治而非气候将推动 2025 年的可持续金融趋势]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）重返美国总统宝座，预示着从资金流动到法律案件和市场监管等各方面的地区分歧将进一步加大，可持续金融的动荡之年将在2025年继续。【原文：A turbulent year for sustainable finance is set to continue in 2025 as the return of Donald Trump as U.S. president heralds more regional divergence on everything from fund flows to legal cases and market regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/politics-not-climate-drive-sustainable-finance-trends-2025-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MO7CICMJRFJ2PFAZDOGVUJIEYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:32:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉因后视摄像头问题召回约 23.9 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周五表示，由于可能导致后视摄像头无法显示图像的问题，公司将召回约23.9万辆汽车，但可以通过空中软件更新解决。【原文：Tesla said on Friday it was recalling about 239,000 vehicles over an issue that could cause the rear-view camera to not display an image, but it could be resolved by an over-the-air software update.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-recalls-about-239000-vehicles-over-rear-view-camera-issue-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ4V4656MFOURGY2LAGYL5UDKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球货币市场基金因对潜在关税持谨慎态度而吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至1月8日的一周内，投资者纷纷涌入全球货币市场基金，原因是他们担心美国政府即将换届可能会提高关税，而且在一份可能会重塑美联储降息预期的重要就业报告公布之前，投资者也持谨慎态度。【原文：Investors piled into global money market funds in the week through Jan. 8, spurred by concerns over potential tariff increases with the upcoming change in the U.S. administration and caution ahead of a critical jobs report that could reshape expectations for Federal Reserve rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGGS2XEZOJJNXG7H2GP3SIGHRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 09:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国对美贸易顺差创历史新高，特朗普关税迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[统计局数据分析显示，就在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普抵达白宫之前，德国对美国的贸易顺差正朝着创纪录的水平迈进。【原文：The German trade surplus with the United States is heading towards a record level just before U.S. President-elect Donald Trump arrives at the White House, an analysis of statistics office data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/germanys-trade-surplus-with-us-reaches-record-high-trump-tariffs-loom-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2PJ6HAYPFIAVDQ5MFQNBYFVFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 09:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾预计特朗普对芯片出口征收关税影响不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾经济部长郭台铭周五表示，鉴于半导体技术的优越性，台湾预计美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的新政府对半导体出口征收的关税影响不大。【原文：Taiwan only expects a small impact from any tariffs imposed by the incoming government of U.S. President-elect Donald Trump on semiconductor exports given their technological superiority, Economy Minister Kuo Jyh-huei said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-expects-small-impact-trump-tariffs-chip-exports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEM5ULMBNZPJTASTHYJ32AEL3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 08:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰 2024 年汽车销量下滑，汽车制造商处境艰难]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国豪华汽车制造商梅赛德斯-奔驰（Mercedes-Benz）周五表示，2024年梅赛德斯-奔驰的核心汽车销量出现下滑，这对于汽车行业来说是艰难的一年，因为经济疲软导致需求减弱，尤其是在主要市场中国。【原文：Mercedes-Benz's core car sales fell in 2024, a tough year for the auto industry marked by waning demand in a weak economy, especially in key market China, the German luxury carmaker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-benz-2024-car-sales-fall-tough-year-automakers-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIDDOXLFV5KK3ICBAD7OMZDQJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 08:33:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱迪生否认与洛杉矶野火有关，保险公司要求其保留证据]]></title><description><![CDATA[南加州爱迪生公司（Southern California Edison）周四表示，它已收到保险公司的通知，要求保存与仍在洛杉矶燃烧的伊顿大火有关的证据，但表示没有消防机构指出该公司与大火有关。【原文：Southern California Edison said on Thursday it had received notices from insurance companies to preserve evidence related to the Eaton Fire that is still burning in Los Angeles, but said no fire agencies have pointed the utility's connection to the fire.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/edison-denies-la-wildfire-involvement-insurers-ask-it-preserve-evidence-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZBS66VCDNOGJORW6DOHPI7DFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 07:25:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国央行正加速迈向政策极限]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计中国央行今年将采取十年来最激进的货币政策，试图刺激经济并减轻美国即将加征关税的打击，但这样做有可能迅速耗尽其火力。【原文：China's central bank is expected to deploy its most aggressive monetary tactics in a decade this year as it tries to stimulate the economy and soften the blow of impending U.S. tariff hikes, but in doing so it risks quickly exhausting its firepower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-central-bank-is-moving-faster-towards-its-policy-limits-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F6JLO3SXVINBIDKBX5Z6KLLV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 07:24:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据每日报道，意大利普拉达公司考虑从卡普里控股公司手中收购范思哲]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《Il Sole 24 ore》日报周五报道，意大利普拉达公司正在考虑从美国卡普里控股公司（Capri Holdings）手中收购时装集团范思哲。【原文：Italy's Prada is considering buying fashion group Versace from U.S. Capri Holdings, daily Il Sole 24 ore reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/italys-prada-considering-buying-versace-capri-holdings-daily-reports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LZHUWFCLVLANCIGICDLZQCE6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 06:59:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holcim 任命主席 Jenisch 为北美分拆公司首席执行官兼主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士建筑材料制造商 Holcim 公司周五表示，该公司已任命其董事长兼前首席执行官 Jan Jenisch 担任其北美公司的董事长兼首席执行官。【原文：Holcim has named its chairman and former chief executive Jan Jenisch as chairman and CEO of its North American company following its multi-billion dollar spin-off, the Swiss building materials maker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/holcim-names-chairman-jenisch-ceo-chairman-north-american-spin-off-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MDS6W2VIBP6TC2ZOYCQKKHFWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 06:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业组织称，欧盟 2024 年新增风力发电能力不足气候目标所需发电量的一半]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲风能行业组织（WindEurope）上周五表示，去年风力发电提供了欧洲20%的电力消耗，但这一年的发电量还不到欧盟2030年能源和气候目标所需发电量的一半。【原文：Wind power provided 20% of the electricity consumed in Europe last year, but the capacity built during the year was less than half of what is needed to meet the European Union's 2030 energy and climate targets, industry group WindEurope said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eus-2024-new-wind-capacity-less-than-half-amount-needed-climate-goal-industry-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VN2ZCJU3AVL6DAARFWXOOAHNIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 06:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受益于人工智能需求，台积电第四季度营收大幅超出市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约芯片制造商台积电周五公布的第四季度财报显示，由于人工智能需求的推动，该公司第四季度营收轻松超过市场预期，并达到了自己的预期。【原文：TSMC , the world's largest contract chipmaker, reported on Friday fourth-quarter revenue that easily beat market forecasts and hit its own expectations as it reaped the benefit of artificial intelligence demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmcs-fourth-quarter-revenue-handily-beats-market-forecast-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYHNQ7AZLVKWPDNIIJPBJ4BDKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 05:39:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价迫在眉睫的非农就业让债券熊如饥似渴]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWLPZD3PJZIFNHJZFDURIHXMR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 05:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cryptoverse：下一波美国加密货币 ETF 已在筹备中]]></title><description><![CDATA[一年的变化真大。【原文：What a difference a year makes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cryptoverse-next-wave-us-crypto-etfs-already-pipeline-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HWRX7HVNLJJFNIVW6RK5LZYD4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 05:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月就业增长缓慢而稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[12 月份，美国的就业增长可能放缓至一个仍然健康的水平，而失业率则稳定在 4.2%，这强化了美联储今年降息的谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. job growth likely slowed to a still-healthy clip in December while the unemployment rate held steady at 4.2%, reinforcing the Federal Reserve's cautious approach toward interest rate cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/slow-steady-us-job-growth-seen-december-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4N7N6A4NRKFHFRBWEYQN5HNLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 05:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[产量下降，马来西亚 12 月棕榈油库存创 19 个月新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚棕榈油行业监管机构周五发布的数据显示，由于洪水导致产量下降，马来西亚棕榈油库存在12月份连续第三个月下降，创下自2023年5月以来的最低水平。【原文：Malaysia's palm oil stocks fell for a third consecutive month in December to hit their lowest since May 2023, as output dropped due to floods, data from the industry regulator showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/malaysia-end-december-palm-oil-stocks-fall-691-mpob-says-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WN5TKIXQTVICTN2B2PSC3C3FMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 04:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>