<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:11:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:11:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国法警局调查政府数字资产遭黑客攻击事件，彭博社报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法警局表示正在调查一起可能针对美国政府数字资产账户的黑客攻击事件，彭博新闻周三援引该机构的一封电子邮件报道称。【原文：The U.S. Marshals Service said it is investigating a possible hack of ​U.S. government digital-asset accounts, Bloomberg News ‌reported on Wednesday, citing an email from the agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-marshals-probe-possible-government-digital-asset-hack-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MBYNKHGSBKYBFAVX23PUYASBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储按预期维持利率不变，但认为通胀水平居高不下]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三如市场普遍预期般维持利率不变，称通胀水平依然居高不下，同时经济增长势头强劲。在最新政策声明中，美联储几乎未透露何时可能再次降息。【原文：The Federal Reserve held interest rates steady on Wednesday, as was widely expected, citing still-elevated inflation alongside solid economic growth, and giving little indication in its latest policy statement of when borrowing costs might fall again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-fed-holds-rates-steady-expected-sees-elevated-inflation-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3MAPWNUYFN2BBBGAFNT3ZH4LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储维持利率不变后，美元兑欧元和日元汇率保持涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元兑欧元和日元汇率维持升势。此前美国联邦储备委员会维持利率不变，称通胀率仍居高不下，经济增长稳健，且在最新政策声明中未透露何时可能再次降息。【原文：The U.S. dollar held gains against the euro and the yen on Wednesday after the U.S. Federal Reserve kept interest rates steady, citing still-elevated inflation alongside solid economic growth, and gave little indication in its latest policy statement of when borrowing costs might fall again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-holds-gains-against-euro-yen-after-fed-stands-pat-rates-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4MQ426RRFOZLF25H5CWFQFGWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：白宫将与银行及加密货币企业就立法分歧举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位知情人士透露，白宫将于周一与银行业和加密货币行业高管举行会晤，商讨具有里程碑意义的加密货币立法的推进路径。该立法因两大强势行业之间的冲突而陷入停滞。【原文：The White House on Monday will meet with ​executives from the banking and ‌cryptocurrency industries to discuss a path forward for landmark crypto legislation which has stalled due a clash between ‌the two powerful sectors, said ​three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/white-house-set-meet-with-banks-crypto-companies-legislation-clash-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQZOENPOCBLIZC6AGDPDLCA6OQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航运集团达飞海运将与石峰资本成立港口合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国航运集团达飞海运与美国投资公司石峰资本周三宣布，双方已达成协议，将成立一家估值近100亿美元的合资企业，共同运营并投资港口码头业务，包括在美国市场的相关投资。【原文：French shipping group CMA CGM and U.S. investment firm Stonepeak have agreed to create a joint ​venture valued at nearly $10 billion to operate and invest in port terminals, ‌including in the United States, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/shipping-group-cma-cgm-form-port-joint-venture-with-stonepeak-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74FJX2X2YNLQRHBSL4EVUIHLBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会提起诉讼，阻止联邦应急管理局裁减数千名雇员]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国政府雇员的工会组织已向联邦法官提出申请，要求阻止唐纳德·特朗普政府在联邦紧急事务管理局裁减逾1万个职位。【原文：Unions representing U.S. government workers have asked a federal judge to block President Donald Trump's administration from cutting more than 10,000 jobs at the Federal Emergency Management Agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/unions-sue-block-thousands-staffing-cuts-fema-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQDL5C4UBNOVZDODGHYHKTFFAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长称与特朗普就美联储主席人选进行了长时间交谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，他已就美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔继任人选的提名问题与唐纳德·特朗普总统进行了长时间的讨论，并称目前仍有四位"优秀"候选人参与角逐。【原文：Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Wednesday said he had spoken at length with President Donald Trump about the nomination of a successor for Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, saying there were still four "great" candidates in the running.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasury-chief-says-spoke-length-with-trump-about-fed-chair-candidates-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXEZKSMTBBPI7GJL7TU6JCCZPU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油商第四季度利润有望攀升，委内瑞拉成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源分析师表示，随着俄乌冲突持续推高产品利润率，美国主要炼油企业预计将公布更强劲的第四季度利润。【原文：Top U.S. oil refiners are expected to post stronger fourth-quarter profits as product margins spurred by the ongoing Russia-Ukraine war boosted earnings, energy analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refiners-poised-higher-q4-profit-venezuela-focus-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGIMVF5HUJKBPKNSHMIVCZJD2Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递计划在5月31日前恢复MD-11货运飞机运营，此前联合包裹服务公司发生事故]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递周三表示，正与波音公司及美国航空安全监管机构合作，计划在5月31日前恢复其停飞的MD-11货运飞机的运营。此前，联合包裹服务公司运营的一架该型号飞机于去年11月发生致命坠毁事故。【原文：FedEx said on Wednesday it is working with Boeing and U.S. aircraft safety regulators to return to service by May 31 the MD-11 cargo planes it grounded after the deadly crash of one of those jets operated by United Parcel Service in November.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fedex-plans-md-11-cargo-plane-return-by-may-31-following-ups-accident-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47TOWEMBCJJMHHMZ2WQN4RU2SQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克旗下Neuralink公司表示，已有21名参与者加入其试验项目。]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克旗下脑机接口公司Neuralink周三表示，自正式启动人体试验两周年之际，目前全球共有21名参与者加入试验。【原文：Elon Musk's brain implant company Neuralink said on Wednesday it now has 21 total participants enrolled in trials worldwide, as it completes two years since it officially began testing on humans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/elon-musks-neuralink-says-it-has-21-participants-enrolled-trials-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYEF2VPTRJNKFIHE7M6XQMFURA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司与印度炼油商续签价值逾31亿美元的石油协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国有石油公司巴西石油公司周三表示，已与印度国有炼油企业扩大并续签了石油销售合同。【原文：Brazil's state-run oil firm Petrobras said on Wednesday it has expanded and renewed oil sales contracts with Indian state-owned oil refiners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/petrobras-renews-oil-deals-with-indian-refiners-worth-more-than-31-bln-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4HGLC3XSRMFVGDGRYSDAGETVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:26:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员审视福特计划采用宁德时代技术生产电池]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院某委员会的共和党主席正密切审查福特汽车的计划。该计划拟将现有美国电池制造工厂改造为生产磷酸铁锂电池及电网级储能系统的基地，所用技术将从中国宁德时代（CATL）获得授权。【原文：The Republican chair of a U.S. House committee is scrutinizing Ford's plan to repurpose its existing U.S. battery manufacturing facilities to produce lithium iron phosphate cells and grid-scale energy storage systems using technology licensed from China's CATL .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-lawmaker-scrutinizes-ford-plan-produce-batteries-with-technology-catl-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTPXPSERBFJADHGTXY3KZDUFUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：风暴考验美国航空，滞留机组人员面临酒店短缺、救援漫长等待]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周席卷美国的冬季风暴不仅导致美国航空数千架次航班停飞，更使该航空公司的恢复系统不堪重负——从为机组人员寻找酒店房间到在连续数日航班取消后重建航班时刻表，各项工作都面临严峻考验。【原文：The winter storm that swept the U.S. last weekend did more than ground thousands of American Airlines flights. It strained the carrier's recovery system — from finding crews hotel rooms to rebuilding schedules after days of cancellations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/storm-tests-american-airlines-stranded-crews-face-hotel-shortages-long-waits-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I73FPA2RWVMWPNV5TZ5AHSQ7HI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:14:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与墨西哥同意就《美墨加协定》改革启动谈判，美国贸易代表办公室称]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔与墨西哥经济部长马塞洛·埃布拉德周三会晤时达成共识，将就《美墨加贸易协定》的潜在改革启动正式磋商，格里尔办公室表示。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer and ​Mexican Secretary of Economy ‌Marcelo Ebrard agreed during a meeting on Wednesday to ‌begin formal discussions on ​possible reforms to the United States-Mexico-Canada ‍trade agreement, Greer's office said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-mexico-agree-begin-talks-usmca-reforms-ustrs-office-says-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQQCENRQN5PU3HWSD7OJNE6MEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行行长称，对美联储独立性的威胁加剧了经济不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大央行行长蒂夫·麦克勒姆周三表示，美联储独立性面临的威胁正加剧全球经济不确定性。这是他迄今对美联储前景最严厉的表态。【原文：The threat to the independence of the U.S. Federal Reserve is boosting economic uncertainty around the world, Bank ​of Canada Governor Tiff Macklem said on Wednesday in his strongest ‌comments to date on the outlook for the Fed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/threat-feds-independence-boosts-economic-uncertainty-says-bank-canada-head-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVY7XMR43JLLXK3HD2KJRJGRLE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:42:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国寻求各州对核废料及再处理场址的兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周三表示，正就各州是否有意愿承接核废料储存、乏燃料再处理及核燃料制造设施征询意见，相关文件已在线发布。【原文：The U.S. said on Wednesday it is seeking input from U.S. states on any interest in hosting sites for storing nuclear waste, spent fuel reprocessing and nuclear fuel fabrication, according to a document posted online.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-seeks-interest-states-nuclear-waste-reprocessing-sites-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55PWBJFJXRITHGMTNAHCQSGQ4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称美国奉行强势美元政策，"绝对不会"干预支撑日元汇率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，美国奉行强势美元政策，这意味着要建立健全的经济基本面。他同时否认华盛顿正通过干预外汇市场来支撑日元汇率。【原文：The U.S. has a strong dollar policy and that means setting the right fundamentals, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday, while denying that Washington was intervening in currency markets to support the Japanese yen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bessent-says-us-has-strong-dollar-policy-absolutely-not-intervening-support-yen-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGHV4LM3NRIXXGKHJW5XARIGL4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行任命洛皮科洛接替马塔雷拉担任中国区负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周三发布的一份内部备忘录显示，该公司已任命维托·洛皮科洛担任意大利国家执行董事，接替即将从该公司退休的尼诺·马塔雷拉。【原文：Bank of America has appointed Vito Lo Piccolo as country executive ​for Italy, an internal memo ‌showed on Wednesday, replacing Nino Mattarella, who is retiring from the firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-appoints-lo-piccolo-country-head-replacing-mattarella-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6H4MB4S7NM2DKDHEREXAKSCIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:50:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空扩大冬季欧洲及拉丁美洲航线网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空周三宣布扩大其冬季航线网络至欧洲和拉丁美洲，押注于高端国际旅行需求的增长。【原文：Air Canada on Wednesday said it expanded its winter network to Europe and Latin America, betting on growing demand for premium international travel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-canada-expands-winter-routes-europe-latin-america-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJCVUG7SYBPDVN7767A2A2MATU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员多姆布罗夫斯基斯表示，欧盟需要推出数字欧元以摆脱对美国的依赖。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟经济事务专员瓦尔迪斯·东布罗夫斯基斯周三表示，欧盟需要迅速创建数字欧元，以减少该集团对主导性美国支付公司的依赖。【原文：The European Union needs to quickly create a digital euro to cut the bloc's dependence on dominant U.S. payment companies, Economic Commissioner Valdis Dombrovskis said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eu-needs-digital-euro-become-independent-us-says-eus-dombrovskis-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LX6G2OWUDJKARE7PHEFH4UODVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国的默茨：美国不应质疑与欧盟的贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希·梅尔茨周三表示，只要华盛顿履行其承诺，欧盟与美国之间贸易协定的批准基础就已具备。【原文：The foundations for the ratification of a trade deal between the EU and U.S. are in place as long as Washington honours its commitments, German Chancellor Friedrich Merz said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/germanys-merz-us-must-not-cast-doubt-trade-deal-with-eu-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KX7BKFCACVIXFOU5PZZZLLYB7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:56:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济学家称世界秩序已发生转变，但增长前景与一年前相同]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对经济学家的季度调查显示，2026年全球经济增长率将达到3%，与一年前的预测完全一致。这表明经济学家们并未受到美国贸易政策突变及其对待盟友方式剧变的影响。【原文：Global economic growth will be 3% in 2026, exactly as forecast a year ago, according to a quarterly Reuters poll of economists, suggesting they are unfazed by the abrupt and seismic shift in how the U.S. trades with others and treats its allies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/world-order-has-shifted-growth-outlook-same-year-ago-economists-say-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOFY73FLRJJFRAOK42GTZDQRJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称已有50万人注册"特朗普账户"，更多捐款正在涌入]]></title><description><![CDATA[财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，近日已有超过50万个家庭注册了特朗普政府的投资账户。此番表态是在一场活动前发表的，歌手妮琪·米娜将与总统唐纳德·特朗普共同出席该活动并发表演讲。【原文：More than 500,000 families ‌have signed up for the Trump administration's investment accounts in recent days, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday before an event at which singer Nicki Minaj will speak alongside President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/bessent-says-500000-have-signed-up-trump-accounts-more-donations-coming-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BDTIZIU7VK2DHGZVOMFW2Q4OY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:14:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银高级交易员称，为客户进行大规模美元对冲操作可能考验银行的承压能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团（UBS）一位高级交易员表示，投资者争相保护其美国资产免受美元贬值影响，这可能考验银行满足对冲需求的能力。瑞银是全球顶级货币交易商之一。【原文：Investors rushing to protect their U.S. assets against dollar ​depreciation could test banks' ability to meet demand for hedging, said ‌a senior trader at UBS , one of the world's top currency dealers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/big-hedging-dollars-clients-could-test-banks-capacity-senior-ubs-trader-says-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PFR64B6R5JNNA2RIL2W4UXYOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:10:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上游并购市场第四季度反弹，交易额达235亿美元，Enverus称]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析机构Enverus周三表示，美国上游并购市场在2025年下半年经历年中放缓后，于第四季度重拾增长势头，当季宣布交易额达235亿美元，推动全年并购总额攀升至650亿美元。【原文：The U.S. upstream mergers and acquisitions market regained momentum after a mid-year slowdown in the fourth quarter of 2025 reaching $23.5 ​billion in announced deals and pushing full-year activity to $65 billion, ‌analytics firm Enverus said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/us-upstream-ma-market-rebounds-q4-hits-235-billion-enverus-says-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FL2VJSVH2BLB3O3XESWHCQVJ3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌将支付1.35亿美元以解决安卓数据传输诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌将支付1.35亿美元，以解决智能手机用户提起的集体诉讼。这些用户指控谷歌在未经许可的情况下，通过其安卓操作系统收集用户手机数据。【原文：Google will pay $135 million to settle a proposed class action by smartphone users who accused Google of programming its Android operating system to collect their cellular data without permission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-pay-135-million-settle-android-data-transfer-lawsuit-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RMGKRNEE7FMWPLPFCZR3H34HIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈佛经济学家称美联储危机工具可能被武器化]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前国际货币基金组织首席经济学家肯尼思·罗格夫在被问及可能性时表示，美国央行在危机时期用于稳定全球金融市场的关键工具，可能被特朗普政府武器化。【原文：A key tool used by the U.S. central bank to stabilise global financial markets ​in times of crisis could be weaponised by the Trump administration, Kenneth Rogoff, a ‌former IMF chief economist said, when asked if that was a possibility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/fed-crisis-tool-could-be-weaponised-harvard-economist-says-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNOUDUYT5NIT5OZJVRYCERLDL4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:51:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行维持利率不变，称难以预测未来动向]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大央行周三如市场普遍预期般将政策利率维持在2.25%不变。行长蒂夫·麦克勒姆表示，当前高度不确定性使得预测下次利率调整的时间和方式变得困难。【原文：The Bank of Canada on Wednesday held its policy rate at 2.25%, as widely expected, and Governor Tiff Macklem said ​the high level of uncertainty made it difficult to predict when and how rates ‌might next change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-holds-rates-says-hard-predict-future-moves-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYW3SSH4OJM4FNFPVJF2TTUP4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:49:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普500指数首次突破7000点大关，人工智能乐观情绪助推]]></title><description><![CDATA[标普500指数周三首次突破7000点大关，这主要得益于市场对人工智能的持续乐观预期、科技巨头强劲财报的预期以及货币政策宽松的推动。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 breached the 7,000-point mark for the first time on Wednesday, driven by unrelenting optimism over artificial intelligence and ​expectations of strong Big Tech earnings as well as monetary policy easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/sp-500-crosses-7000-points-first-time-lifted-by-ai-optimism-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3CHE72P2FJTPIMCMAYQFZZC3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，巴西PicPay拟以最高定价区间进行纽约IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，巴西数字银行PicPay预计将于周三在美国首次公开募股（IPO）定价，定价区间为每股16至19美元，最终定价将处于区间上限。【原文：Brazilian digital bank PicPay is expected to price its ​U.S. initial public offering (IPO) on ‌Wednesday at the top of the indicated price range of $16 to $19 per share, a source familiar with the ‌matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/brazils-picpay-set-price-new-york-ipo-top-range-source-says-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BNRTQBCOBOTXO6A4YQ3E5XLBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>