<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:08:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:08:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，OpenAI将斥资约100亿美元向初创公司Cerebras购买计算能力。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，OpenAI已同意在三年内向Cerebras购买高达750兆瓦的计算能力，这笔交易价值超过100亿美元。【原文：OpenAI has agreed to purchase up to 750 megawatts of computing power over three years from Cerebras in a deal worth more than $10 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-buy-compute-capacity-startup-cerebras-around-10-billion-wsj-reports-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHSIBTKFKNLBXICSDMHAYMTGIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会称，波音公司于2011年针对MD-11飞机部件发布了服务通告。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会周三表示，去年11月在肯塔基州坠毁的UPS UPS.NMD-11货运飞机上发现裂纹的关键部件，正是2011年波音公司服务通告中提及的对象。该事故造成15人遇难。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board said on Wednesday that a key part of a UPS UPS.NMD-11 cargo jet that crashed in November in Kentucky, killing 15 people, that was found to have cracks was the subject of a 2011 Boeing service letter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ntsb-says-boeing-issued-service-advisory-2011-md-11-part-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3SFRP7TFRPBLOROLYP2GB5PEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛诺菲预计短期内美国疫苗需求疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[赛诺菲首席执行官保罗·哈德森周三表示，由于错误信息和现任政府加强监管，美国今年疫苗需求可能略有疲软。【原文：Sanofi chief executive Paul Hudson said on Wednesday the U.S. is likely to see a slight weakness in vaccine demand this year due to misinformation and heightened scrutiny under the current administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/sanofi-sees-softness-us-vaccine-demand-near-term-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2L2VVXRE5KANEPODWNBLLTV2I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:23:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储调查显示，美国经济活动在最近几周大多有所增长。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三在一份报告中称，美国大部分地区经济活动有所增长，近几周就业基本持平。这份报告在央行两周后召开会议前，可能难以改变政策制定者的利率预期。【原文：Economic activity increased in most parts of the U.S. and employment was mostly unchanged in recent weeks, the Federal Reserve said on Wednesday in a report that may do little to ​sway policymakers' interest rate views ahead of the central bank's meeting in two ‌weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economic-activity-mostly-increased-recent-weeks-fed-survey-shows-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3EKJRRDQMBOXVJO6D4WM6X3WXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储卡什卡里对2026年前景持乐观态度，预计通胀将趋缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔·卡什卡利周三表示，他对经济前景持乐观态度，并预计通胀将有所缓解，但具体降幅尚不明确。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of ​Minneapolis President Neel Kashkari said Wednesday he is optimistic about the economic outlook and expects inflation to ‌wane, but it is unclear by how much.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-kashkari-upbeat-2026-expects-inflation-moderate-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IM6CZS6BKZO5FPG5VSJCTRFVWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普批准英伟达向中国出口人工智能芯片，引发国会议员和前政府官员的强烈批评。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会议员和前政府官员周三质疑特朗普总统允许英伟达向中国出售其第二强人工智能芯片的决定，认为此举削弱了美国的AI优势，并可能助长北京的军事力量。【原文：U.S. lawmakers and former officials on Wednesday questioned President Donald Trump's decision to allow Nvidia to sell its second most powerful AI chips in China, arguing the move erodes America's AI edge and threatens to electrify Beijing's military.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-greenlight-nvidia-ai-chips-china-draws-fire-lawmakers-former-officials-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVFH4PD37ZPN7DEBVH7MBJUB4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌干达人、伊朗人转向多尔西的即时通讯应用Bitchat规避网络封锁]]></title><description><![CDATA[推特联合创始人杰克·多尔西推出的一款鲜为人知的离线通讯应用，已成为乌干达民众的重要生命线。在可能延长总统约韦里·穆塞韦尼四十年统治的争议性大选前夕，该国民众因互联网被切断而陷入孤立。【原文：A little-known offline messaging app launched by Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey has emerged as a key lifeline for Ugandans cut off from the internet ahead of a contentious election that could extend President Yoweri Museveni's four-decade rule.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ugandans-iranians-turn-dorseys-messaging-app-bitchat-web-crackdowns-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTETPS3UMBMM3E6KBW4KYI5AB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：奢侈品零售商萨克斯依靠房地产权利在破产期间维持营业]]></title><description><![CDATA[萨克斯全球公司拥有的优质房地产组合，可能成为这家遭受重创的奢侈品购物帝国在申请破产后进行重组时，与贷款方谈判的关键筹码。【原文：Saks Global's prime real estate portfolio could serve as a crucial bargaining chip with lenders as the hard-hit luxury shopping empire navigates its restructuring after filing for bankruptcy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/luxury-retailer-saks-leans-real-estate-rights-keep-doors-open-during-bankruptcy-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJU7BWG7OBJBXNPFFSGHNAJYNQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文因人工智能建设相关损失遭债券持有人起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，债券持有人对甲骨文公司提起诉讼，称因该公司未能披露其需要发行大量额外债务来建设人工智能基础设施，导致他们蒙受损失。该公司由亿万富翁拉里·埃里森担任董事长。【原文：Oracle was sued on Wednesday by bondholders ​who say they suffered losses because the company ‌chaired by billionaire Larry Ellison failed to disclose it needed to sell significant additional debt to build out its artificial intelligence infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/oracle-sued-by-bondholders-over-losses-tied-ai-buildout-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDGRKMJSDVMLXAP333Y4LVMQEE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:33:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visa加密货币负责人押注稳定币结算，预计交易量将增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[维萨公司正致力于将稳定币整合到现有支付系统中，其加密货币业务主管库伊·谢菲尔德向路透社表示，随着这些代币日益普及，维萨看到了维持市场领导地位的机会。【原文：Visa is working to integrate stablecoins into existing payment systems, seeing an opportunity to maintain its market leadership as these tokens gain traction, Visa's head of crypto, Cuy Sheffield, told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/visa-crypto-chief-bets-stablecoin-settlement-sees-volumes-growing-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGLUHQBKEVNAHEYDKHHV5LSRE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟文件显示，欧洲电信公司或将获得无限无线电频谱使用权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一份文件显示，欧盟委员会拟对电信规则进行改革，旨在促进投资。根据该改革方案，欧洲电信运营商可能获得不受时间限制的丰厚无线电频谱使用权。【原文：Europe's telecoms providers may be given the use of lucrative radio spectrum without a time limit under the European Commission's proposed revamp of telecoms rules aimed at boosting investment, according to a document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/european-telcos-may-get-unlimited-radio-spectrum-rights-eu-document-shows-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L23NAFUTPRJR5PUEORG5YIGOLQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interactive Brokers表示押注美国中期选举应能提振其平台增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国民众对11月中期选举的押注持续升温，Interactive Brokers创始人兼董事长托马斯·彼得菲表示，他预计该公司2024年推出的预测市场平台今年将加速增长。【原文：As Americans bet on U.S. midterm elections in November, Interactive Brokers founder and chairman Thomas Peterffy said he expects growth to accelerate this year for the prediction markets platform his company launched in 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/interactive-brokers-says-betting-us-midterm-elections-should-juice-growth-its-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VA7G6C52DRPEZPAWKVW64NWO6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Verizon网络在美国数千用户中出现故障，Downdetector数据显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[据故障追踪网站Downdetector.com显示，美国威瑞森通信公司（Verizon Communications）的网络于周三在美国境内数千名用户中出现故障。【原文：Verizon Communications' network was down for thousands of users in the U.S. on Wednesday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/verizons-network-down-thousands-users-us-downdetector-shows-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CF6HAT775LBJBAIQF56TEV5C4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州将就深度伪造内容对xAI展开调查，官员称]]></title><description><![CDATA[加州官员表示，他们正要求埃隆·马斯克旗下的xAI公司作出解释。此前该平台上非自愿性影像的传播引发全球关注。【原文：California officials said they were demanding answers from Elon Musk's xAI amid the spread of non-consensual sexual images on the platform that has prompted global scrutiny.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/california-investigate-xai-over-deepfake-content-officials-say-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DI5VFEQCFLGLN566USY4HEE2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟发言人表示，欧盟将仔细评估X公司承诺对Grok进行的改进。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人周三表示，该机构将仔细评估埃隆·马斯克旗下X平台宣布对其Grok聊天机器人所作的调整。【原文：The European Commission will carefully assess changes Elon Musk's platform X has said it would make to its Grok chatbot, a spokesperson said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/eu-will-carefully-assess-xs-promised-changes-grok-spokesperson-says-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KS6ZL4YADRIGPNCXO54X77QXXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:34:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文因人工智能建设相关损失遭债券持有人起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，债券持有人对甲骨文公司提起诉讼，称该公司因未能披露其需要出售大量额外债务来建设人工智能基础设施，导致投资者遭受损失。该公司由亿万富翁拉里·埃里森领导。【原文：Oracle was sued on Wednesday by bondholders who say they suffered losses because the company led by billionaire Larry Ellison failed to disclose it needed to sell significant additional debt to build out its artificial intelligence infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/oracle-sued-by-bondholders-over-losses-tied-ai-buildout-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4JXVZ5MVZI3ZFR2MVNBG4YWUM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[eBay公布首份气候计划，目标2045年实现净零排放]]></title><description><![CDATA[电商公司eBay周三公布了首份气候转型计划，宣布将加大运营和供应链脱碳力度，作为实现2045年净零排放目标的重要举措。【原文：E-commerce company eBay unveiled its first climate transition plan on Wednesday and said it would ramp up efforts to decarbonize its operations and supply chain as part of a plan to reach net-zero emissions by 2045.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/ebay-unveils-first-climate-plan-targets-net-zero-by-2045-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WALZIVYJ6RMLHFCWCQJAHIQ3VA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员米兰：外国央行对鲍威尔面临起诉威胁的评论不恰当]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会理事斯蒂芬·米兰周三在欧洲听众面前表示，外国央行为美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔辩护的言论不恰当，并驳斥了对美国金融机构韧性的担忧，称其为"博眼球的文章"。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran told a European audience ​on Wednesday that comments from foreign ‌central banks in defense of Fed Chair Jerome Powell were inappropriate, and dismissed concerns about the resilience of U.S. ‌institutions as "people writing things for clicks."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-miran-commentary-foreign-central-banks-powell-indictment-threat-not-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZES2PQKYORJVFKTS23DLUI4Y7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[古尔斯比称鲍威尔为"首轮当选的联邦储备委员会主席名人堂成员"，美国国家公共电台报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯坦·古尔斯比周三表示，美国央行的独立性对抑制通胀至关重要，而针对央行的攻击——例如特朗普政府对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的刑事调查——可能使这项任务更加困难。【原文：The independence of the U.S. central bank is critical to containing inflation, and attacks against it, such as the Trump ​administration's criminal probe into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, threaten to ‌make that task harder, Chicago Fed President Austan Goolsbee said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goolsbee-calls-powell-first-ballot-hall-of-fame-fed-chair-npr-says-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZUJXV2YUJMNDNS4AEDTYPJZSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西金融科技公司Agibank申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西金融科技公司Agibank周三向美国监管机构提交了首次公开募股申请。【原文：Brazilian fintech Agibank has filed for an initial public offering in the United States, a regulatory filing showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazilian-fintech-agibank-files-us-ipo-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LH54BASLBVOA5KAGDQY7IB4LEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CrowdStrike击败股东诉讼，涉重大软件故障事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官驳回了CrowdStrike股东提起的诉讼。这些股东指控这家网络安全公司通过隐瞒其不完善的软件测试和质量保证程序欺诈了他们——此前在2024年7月的一次系统故障中，全球超过800万台基于微软Windows的计算机因此瘫痪。【原文：A federal judge dismissed a ​lawsuit by CrowdStrike shareholders who said the cybersecurity company defrauded them by concealing ‌its inadequate software testing and quality assurance procedures, before a July 2024 outage crashed more than 8 million Microsoft Windows-based computers worldwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/crowdstrike-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-huge-software-outage-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44TSB3VDHVKJ5GFTVC7NMZYKXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国企业库存10月再度增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国企业库存10月在销售下滑的情况下进一步增加，这表明库存可能对第四季度国内生产总值产生贡献。【原文：U.S. business inventories increased further in October as sales dropped, suggesting inventories could contribute to gross domestic ​product in the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-business-inventories-increase-again-october-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZH4I2OIFVROE5EKMRJNECQYF34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员米兰表示，特朗普的放松监管政策将有助于降低通胀，为降息提供依据。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬·米兰周三表示，特朗普政府的放松监管举措将对通胀形成下行压力，这也是美国央行降息的又一理由。【原文：The Trump administration's deregulation effort will put downward pressure on inflation and is another reason for the U.S. central bank ​to cut interest rates, Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran said on ‌Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-miran-says-trumps-deregulation-will-help-lower-inflation-justifying-rate-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4KT5SMQ7ZNQ5D73P7US2JPDFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:31:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国监管机构突击搜查审计公司，作为反垄断调查的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国竞争监管机构周三表示，已突击搜查多家审计公司，作为反垄断调查的一部分。金融刊物《La Lettre》称，德勤、毕马威、安永和普华永道等"四大"审计公司均在被调查之列。【原文：France's competition watchdog has raided auditing firms as part of an anti-trust investigation, it said on Wednesday, while La Lettre financial publication said the "Big Four" firms Deloitte, KPMG, EY and PWC were among those targeted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/french-watchdog-raids-auditing-firms-part-antitrust-probe-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22AXXJ7B6JJXVI2JT2UKJ237QY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月成屋销售加速增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国12月成屋销售加速增长，得益于抵押贷款利率下降和房价涨幅放缓。【原文：U.S. existing home sales accelerated in December, boosted by lower mortgage rates and slow growth in house prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-existing-home-sales-accelerate-december-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7PNZSMSQZLF3IAT27VK7IJXTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:01:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储保尔森重申，在通胀趋缓后可能进一步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联邦储备银行行长安娜·保尔森周三重申，若经济符合其通胀放缓、就业市场趋稳的预期，央行可能在今年晚些时候下调短期利率。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia President Anna Paulson reiterated Wednesday her expectation that the central bank could lower short-term interest rates later this year if ​the economy meets her expectations of moderating inflation and job market stabilization.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-paulson-reiterates-more-rate-cuts-could-follow-moderating-inflation-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43CVIUVNNROVXCGO2WXLPYAZ3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:53:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿联酋加入人工智能供应链计划，加强与美国经济联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿拉伯联合酋长国周三加入了由美国主导的旨在保障人工智能和半导体供应链安全的倡议——"硅基和平"，此举进一步巩固了该国与美国的经济纽带。【原文：The United Arab Emirates on Wednesday joined a U.S.-led initiative to secure AI and semiconductor supply chains, dubbed Pax Silica, further strengthening economic ties with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/uae-bolsters-economic-ties-with-us-by-joining-ai-supply-chain-program-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNYDH35PXJMGJMU52LFVNGQMVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度经常账户赤字大幅收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经常账户赤字大幅收窄，因关税抑制了进口，同时初级收入激增。【原文：The U.S. current account deficit narrowed sharply as tariffs weighed on imports and primary ​income surged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-current-account-deficit-contracts-sharply-third-quarter-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6Z5HMK3XLFMODKLZZFRLWZRVMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克表示他并不知晓Grok生成未成年人的露骨图像]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克周三表示，他并不知晓xAI旗下Grok聊天机器人生成任何"未成年人裸体图像"，而全球对该人工智能工具的审查力度正在不断加强。【原文：Elon Musk said on Wednesday he was not aware of any "naked underage images" generated by xAI's Grok chatbot, as scrutiny of the AI tool intensifies worldwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/musk-says-unaware-grok-generating-explicit-images-minors-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWY3C6IC2JIWTEKLWE4TZHYZE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国11月生产者价格温和上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[11月美国生产者价格指数小幅回升，主要受汽油成本激增推动，但企业似乎正在吸收部分进口关税影响，贸易利润率因此受到挤压。【原文：U.S. producer prices picked up slightly in November amid a surge in the cost of gasoline, but businesses appeared to be absorbing some of the ​tariffs on imports, with trade margins compressing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-producer-prices-increase-moderately-november-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHBZGXURJNN2ZK6R5TAF577FKA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>