<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 15:35:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 15:35:25 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷债务风险指数再次下降，违约担忧减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者越来越看好亲市场的自由派总统哈维尔-米莱伊，阿根廷的国家风险指数（衡量投资者要求持有当地债券相对于等值美债的溢价）周二下跌了不到900个基点。【原文：Argentina's country risk index , a measure of the premium investors demand to hold local bonds versus equivalent U.S. debt, dropped under 900 basis points on Tuesday as investors grow more bullish on pro-market libertarian President Javier Milei.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/argentina-debt-risk-index-drops-again-default-fears-recede-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKR2R6NJQZOYTDM6SS5JWOX3HQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 15:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份消费者信心指数回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对劳动力市场的看法有所改善，10月份美国消费者信心指数升至9个月来的最高点。【原文：U.S. consumer confidence increased to a nine-month high in October amid improved perceptions of the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-confidence-rebounds-october-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICRFZWVUXBPKPDM5IGDMVDTVEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月职位空缺降至逾 3 年半低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 9 月份的职位空缺降至逾 3 年半以来的最低水平，上个月的数据也被下调，这表明劳动力市场状况大幅放缓。【原文：U.S. job openings fell to the lowest level in more than 3-1/2 years in September and data for the prior month was revised down, pointing to a considerable easing in labor market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-drop-more-than-3-12-year-low-september-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEXTBGSOANOYXG7DGYGKMEPU6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:29:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车旗下奥迪与潜在投资者洽谈布鲁塞尔生产基地事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司发言人周二表示，该公司的豪华车部门奥迪正在就其陷入困境的布鲁塞尔工厂与潜在投资者进行谈判。【原文：Volkswagen's luxury division Audi is in talks with a potential investor for its struggling Brussels plant, a company spokesperson said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagens-audi-talks-with-potential-investor-brussels-site-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HTFJ62TD5KXFEPTR2ZKNPF4PI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:58:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[廉价航空公司边疆航空第三季度亏损超预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，廉价航空公司边疆航空公司（Frontier Airlines）的母公司边疆集团（Frontier Group）公布的第三季度财报显示，由于国内航线运力过剩，该公司上半年的收入受到影响，第三季度的亏损额大于预期。【原文：Frontier Group , the parent of budget carrier Frontier Airlines, reported a bigger-than-expected loss in the third quarter on Tuesday, as overcapacity on domestic routes hit its revenue in the first half of the period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/no-frills-carrier-frontier-reports-bigger-than-expected-q3-loss-shares-fall-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JM3TPBTGMJNKLBRNR64GUHEH4E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲汽车安全机构冷落比亚迪 Atto 3 驾驶辅助系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲汽车安全机构对比亚迪 Atto 3 电动车所使用的驾驶辅助系统作出了 "不推荐 "评级，这对正在努力拓展欧洲市场的中国汽车制造商来说是一个打击。【原文：Europe's car safety agency has issued a "not recommended" rating to the driver assistance system used in BYD's Atto 3 EV, dealing a blow to the Chinese automaker as it strives to expand on the continent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-car-safety-agency-snubs-byds-atto-3-driver-assistance-system-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNK4UVUHRVK3DBXDYCNTD3HMUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:43:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[食品供应商 Sysco 因需求稳定，季度销售额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[食品分销商 Sysco 公司周二公布的第一季度营收超出预期，主要得益于其特色海鲜和鲜切肉类产品的稳定需求，但利润未达预期。【原文：Food distributor Sysco Corp beat first-quarter revenue estimates on Tuesday, helped by steady demand for its specialty seafood and fresh-cut meat products, but missed profit expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/food-supplier-sysco-beats-quarterly-sales-estimates-steady-demand-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3CKWTJ6URJFFJIXU2HM3J4BKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月份月度房价进一步上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份，美国独户住宅价格上涨，但供应依然紧张，加之抵押贷款利率升高，使潜在购房者仍持观望态度。【原文：U.S. single-family home prices increased in August amid still tight supply, which together with elevated mortgage rates continue to keep prospective buyers on the sidelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-monthly-house-prices-rise-further-august-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCD6DGXI5BJFNBA7IQDGVH5K2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid 下周开始接受 Gravity 电动 SUV 订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商Lucid集团周二表示，将于11月7日开始接受其Gravity SUV的订单，以刺激需求并吸引更广泛的客户。【原文：Electric-vehicle maker Lucid Group said on Tuesday it will open orders for its Gravity SUV on Nov. 7, as it looks to drum up demand and attract a wider swathe of customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lucid-open-orders-gravity-electric-suv-next-week-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VC63YIFMRMNPBCGI5SPYVGGII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月商品贸易逆差因进口而急剧扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于进口激增，9 月份美国货物贸易逆差急剧扩大，这表明贸易仍然拖累了第三季度的经济增长。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit in goods widened sharply in September amid a surge in imports, suggesting that trade remained a drag on economic growth in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-goods-trade-deficit-widens-sharply-september-imports-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNXYENYEUFNIPF6AS7WNMCMAXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[捷蓝航空全年收入预期低于预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）预计，由于美国大选在即，国内旅游需求放缓，2024 年的收入降幅将超过预期，导致其股价在周二收盘前下跌 4.5%。【原文：JetBlue Airways forecast a bigger-than-expected fall in 2024 revenue amid a moderation in domestic travel demand ahead of the upcoming U.S. elections, sending its shares down 4.5% before the bell on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/jetblues-full-year-revenue-forecast-misses-estimates-shares-fall-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CALPIIIQJROYXB4D2JZV5BEWAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:12:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康宁公司因光纤需求强劲而预测季度业绩乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[大猩猩玻璃制造商康宁公司周二公布的第四季度利润预期超出预期，原因是网络数据消耗量（包括用于生成式人工智能模型训练的数据消耗量）不断增加，对其光纤产品的需求也持续增加。【原文：Gorilla Glass maker Corning fourth-quarter profit forecast beat estimates on Tuesday, as rising consumption of data over networks, including for generative AI model training, continues to increase demand for its optical fiber products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/corning-forecasts-upbeat-quarterly-results-robust-demand-optical-fiber-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVR7GRUFI5MJJAZTY3QIED4A3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:53:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[D.R. Horton 2025 年收入和房屋交付量低于预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，D.R. Horton 预测 2025 年的收入和房屋交付量均低于预期，原因是抵押贷款利率的波动使一些购房者保持观望，而该建筑商保留了折扣以刺激需求。【原文：D.R. Horton forecast 2025 revenue and home deliveries below estimates on Thursday, as mortgage rate volatility kept some home buyers on the sidelines and the builder retained discounts to whip up demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dr-horton-sees-2025-revenue-home-deliveries-below-estimates-shares-fall-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRBAKO3XA5I7JIPC6M2G3JTZJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:40:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿布扎比的 CYVN Holdings 就收购迈凯轮汽车业务达成非约束性协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[两家海湾公司周二表示，总部位于阿布扎比的投资公司 CYVN Holdings 已达成一项非约束性协议，将从巴林主权财富基金 Mumtalakat 手中收购汽车制造商迈凯轮汽车业务 100% 的股份。【原文：Abu Dhabi-based investment vehicle CYVN Holdings has entered a non-binding agreement to buy 100% of carmaker McLaren's automotive business from Mumtalakat, the sovereign wealth fund of Bahrain, the two Gulf firms said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/abu-dhabis-cyvn-holdings-enters-non-binding-deal-buy-mclarens-automotive-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHXJP3QXHBMANJOFO76EIHMQRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:35:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱多斯公司因国防需求强劲而上调年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防承包商莱多斯控股公司（Leidos Holdings）周二上调了年度利润和收入预期，认为在地缘政治局势日益紧张的情况下，全球武器需求将保持强劲。【原文：U.S. defense contractor Leidos Holdings raised its annual profit and revenue forecasts on Tuesday, banking on strong worldwide weapons demand amid growing geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/leidos-lifts-annual-forecasts-robust-defense-demand-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UV4EOBSIINIYTOEVEEHZI4AAFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:29:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融产品需求增加，MSCI 第三季度利润强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[指数提供商摩根斯坦利资本国际公司（MSCI）周二发布报告称，由于对其产品和服务的需求强劲，公司第三季度利润有所增长。【原文：Index provider MSCI on Tuesday reported a rise in its third-quarter profit helped by robust demand for its products and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/msci-reports-strong-q3-profit-amid-increased-demand-financial-products-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSWK57BMORKRLCOX6FUDJTRGKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于燃料需求疲软，炼油商菲利普斯 66 公布第三季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 周二公布的季度利润下降，原因是燃料需求低迷导致利润率下滑。【原文：Phillips 66 posted a fall in quarterly profit on Tuesday, hurt by a slump in margins due to lackluster fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/refiner-phillips-66-reports-lower-third-quarter-profit-weak-fuel-demand-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBVFIXPYTBJOPBEJ5V3PEMSUDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求低迷，麦当劳全球销售额降幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦当劳周二公布的季度全球可比销售额降幅超过预期，主要市场的客流量疲软对其造成了影响，尽管麦当劳在数年涨价后加大了促销力度以吸引顾客。【原文：McDonald's on Tuesday posted a steeper-than-expected drop in quarterly global comparable sales, hurt by weaker traffic across its key markets even as it intensified promotions to woo back customers after several years of price hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mcdonalds-global-sales-fall-more-than-expected-muted-demand-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTVVJDGYOJJZ7JMIN5BCGV46EM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PayPal 预计第四季度营收低于预期，利润增长乏力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，PayPal 预测第四季度营收低于预期，原因是这家数字支付公司将重点从积极扩张转向利润率更高的业务，导致其股价在开盘前下跌 6.6%。【原文：PayPal forecast fourth-quarter revenue below estimates on Tuesday as the digital payments company shifts its focus to higher-margin businesses from aggressive expansion, sending its shares down 6.6% before the market open.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/paypal-forecasts-q4-revenue-below-estimates-profit-push-puts-growth-behind-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2G2LTSN5NVKMHM3F465HS3X7AE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特股价下跌 6%，原因是供应障碍和成本影响了利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司周二股价下跌 6%，此前该公司调低了全年利润预期，将原因归咎于产能过剩引发的全球价格战导致的供应商中断和保修成本。【原文：Ford Motor shares fell 6% on Tuesday after the automaker tempered its full-year profit forecast, blaming supplier disruptions and warranty costs amid a global price war fueled by overcapacity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-shares-fall-6-supply-snags-costs-hurt-profit-forecast-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TESJOK63EJMYFERYA5YQCY3BWQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞上调利润预期，第三季度业绩超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[辉瑞公司周二上调了全年盈利预期，此前其 COVID-19 疗法的销售好于预期，帮助其第三季度盈利超过了华尔街的预期。【原文：Pfizer raised its full-year profit forecast after better-than-expected sales of its COVID-19 treatment helped it beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter earnings on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pfizer-raises-profit-forecast-after-beating-third-quarter-estimates-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMCCRSDTQVOCJGP7SRINXNKYY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[皇家加勒比因邮轮需求强劲和价格上涨而上调年度盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[皇家加勒比公司周二第四次上调了今年的年度利润预期，这主要得益于该游轮运营商多次上调船票价格，以及对私人目的地和凉爽景点游轮的需求增加。【原文：Royal Caribbean on Tuesday raised its annual profit forecast for a fourth time this year, boosted by the cruise operator's multiple ticket price hikes and higher demand for cruises to private destinations and cooler spots.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/royal-caribbean-lifts-annual-profit-forecast-strong-cruise-demand-price-hikes-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LEJWBDRIRPBFAJTYBO5DXTD5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:48:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[不断恶化的写字楼贷款给美国地区性银行的 CRE 投资组合带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，随着远程工作的持续盛行，美国地区性银行仍在努力应对其办公楼贷款账面上的压力，但降息可能会缓解其他商业房地产（CRE）领域的压力，从而提供一些缓解措施。【原文：U.S. regional banks continue to grapple with pressures in their office loan books as remote work stays prevalent, but rate cuts may provide some relief by easing the strain on other commercial real estate (CRE) segments, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/deteriorating-office-loans-stress-us-regional-banks-cre-portfolios-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPHXWUKCYBPK5EAUQLG7SEDMEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于扭亏为盈计划初见成效，面包车所有者 VF Corp 的业绩飙升 22]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vans 制造商 VF Corp 在连续两个季度亏损后扭亏为盈，股价在周二的盘前交易中大涨 22%，促使投资者押注这家陷入困境的服装和鞋类制造商将以快于预期的速度扭亏为盈。【原文：Shares of Vans maker VF Corp surged 22% in premarket trading on Tuesday after turning a profit following two quarters of losses, prompting investors to bet on a faster-than-expected turnaround at the struggling apparel and footwear maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/vans-owner-vf-corp-soars-22-turnaround-plan-starts-pay-off-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOJKM7E3IJJDTCN5WEM4CQIOKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:33:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[倍耐力首席执行官称公司目前未计划关闭任何工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利轮胎制造商倍耐力公司首席执行官 Andrea Casaluci 在米兰举行的一次商业会议上表示，为应对汽车行业的危机，倍耐力公司不打算关闭任何工厂。【原文：Italian tyremaker Pirelli is not planning to close any of its factories as a response to the crisis of the automotive industry, CEO Andrea Casaluci said at a business conference in Milan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/pirelli-ceo-says-company-is-not-currently-planning-any-factory-closures-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDZOOLRVSZJBJLXMNKZHWDSFFE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：大选躁动的国债与巨型股的收益相得益彰]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNZYGVXIDNJJDBSR6C6ICANL2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究发现：到 2035 年，德国汽车业转型可能导致 18.6 万个工作岗位流失]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车工业协会（VDA）委托进行的一项研究周二公布，到 2035 年，德国汽车工业的转型可能导致 18.6 万个工作岗位流失，其中约四分之一已经流失。【原文：The transformation of the German car industry could lead to 186,000 jobs losses by 2035, of which roughly a quarter have already occurred, a study commissioned by the VDA auto industry association released on Tuesday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/german-car-industry-transformation-could-cost-186000-jobs-by-2035-study-finds-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S25VGBKTDBMEDLAEHPHOV7FOJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:21:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国利率期权为共和党扫荡定价，波动率飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在下周美国总统大选之前，利率期权投资者正在进行一些交易，如果利率保持高位，这些交易将获得回报，这表明市场正在为共和党的大选定价。【原文：Ahead of the U.S. presidential election next week, investors in interest rate options are putting on trades that will pay off if rates remain elevated, suggesting that the market is pricing in a sweep by the Republican party.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-interest-rate-options-price-republican-sweep-jump-volatility-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJM7Z2D2C5MKJACD6JLXEZRRPE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:19:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小米首席执行官在发布电动汽车前吹嘘纽博格林赛道纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，就在该公司举行活动揭晓其量产车型的几小时前，其制造商小米公司表示，中国的一款电动汽车原型在德国艰苦的纽伯格林赛道上创下了单圈时间纪录。【原文：A prototype Chinese electric vehicle has set a record lap time at Germany's grueling Nurburgring track, its maker Xiaomi said on Tuesday just hours before a company event expected to reveal the production model of the car.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/xiaomi-chief-touts-nurburgring-record-ahead-ev-launch-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBRM66FGAFMEHF4AFQZL7QGKNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:16:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场对 iPhone 的需求使苹果公司的收入创两年来最大增幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司预计将于本周四公布其两年来最大的季度收入增长，在该公司年度发布周期即将结束时，iPhone 的需求将好于近几年，尤其是在中国。【原文：Apple is expected to report its biggest quarterly revenue jump in two years on Thursday, with iPhone demand faring better than recent years toward the end of the company's annual release cycle, especially in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-set-biggest-revenue-jump-two-years-iphone-demand-china-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUVVZKHRJ5LLNM2ZS7BLBZSQAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>