<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:16:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:16:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员称，中国尚未收到任何英伟达H200芯片。]]></title><description><![CDATA[None of Nvidia's second most advanced AI chips, known as the H200, have been sold to Chinese customers so far, a U.S. Commerce Department official said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-has-not-yet-received-any-nvidia-h200-chips-us-official-said-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSCWUHKJPFLHXABN4WXPT7CKMU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为可能加剧焦虑的国情咨文演讲做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统周二晚间的国情咨文演讲正值投资者处于关键时刻——他们近月来饱受市场动荡冲击，亟需稳定局面。【原文：The State of the Union speech from President Donald Trump on Tuesday evening comes at a pivotal point for investors, sideswiped by market turbulence in recent months and craving stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-brace-state-union-speech-that-may-fuel-anxiety-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZ6EDZ3OCBL3RHAIDYF47ODP7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国液化天然气霸主地位持续巩固，首船货运十周年之际]]></title><description><![CDATA[自首船液化天然气（LNG）从得克萨斯州出口以来，十年的时间里，美国已迅速发展成为全球消费者最主要的超低温燃料供应国。【原文：In the ten years since the first export cargo of liquefied natural gas (LNG) left Texas, the United States has grown rapidly into the top supplier of the ultra-cooled fuel to world consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ten-years-after-first-cargo-us-lng-dominance-set-keep-growing-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTR32WYTZBMS3DUARWEREIZ7LY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能会计初创公司Basis以11.5亿美元估值完成1亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能会计初创公司Basis在B轮融资中筹集了1亿美元，公司估值达11.5亿美元。随着投资者纷纷向能够自主处理复杂任务的智能代理系统注入资金，该领域正迎来发展热潮。【原文：AI accounting startup Basis has raised $100 million in a Series B round valuing the company at $1.15 billion, as investors pour money into agentic AI systems designed to operate autonomously on complex tasks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-accounting-startup-basis-raises-100-million-115-billion-valuation-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PM2IBUPPRJLYXBMQU5VBYHW6D4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据Axios报道，赫格塞斯要求Anthropic在周五之前撤回其人工智能安全措施。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Axios周二报道，美国国防部长皮特·赫格塞斯已要求人工智能公司Anthropic在周五之前撤回其军用产品的安全保障措施。【原文：U.S. Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has given artificial intelligence company Anthropic until Friday to back down on safeguards for its products used by the military, Axios reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hegseth-gives-anthropic-until-friday-back-down-ai-safeguards-axios-reports-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4MNM7BKOVNA5OBZ7TT7XMRPFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:37:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银任命戈利亚领导美国财富管理顾问团队]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周二获得的一份内部备忘录显示，瑞银集团（UBS）于3月1日任命丽莎·戈利亚（Lisa Golia）领导其美国财富管理顾问团队，此前她已担任该业务首席运营官两年。【原文：UBS promoted Lisa Golia to lead its U.S. wealth management advisers in the field on March 1 after serving as chief operating officer for the business over the last two years, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-promotes-golia-lead-wealth-management-advisers-us-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHPVTTGH6VJGPKETADSGEDMYY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲人工智能芯片初创企业Axelera再获2.5亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[Axelera AI has secured $250 million in a funding round led by Innovation Industries that included BlackRock and SiteGround Capital as new investors, it said on Tuesday, marking one of the largest investments to date in a European AI chipmaking firm.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-ai-chip-startup-axelera-raises-additional-250-million-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZHIBFRRSROPJFC2DW3RVEERRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:16:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士央行行长表示，全球多数经济体应对关税的状况好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行行长马丁·施莱格尔周二表示，美国关税政策和不确定性因素已对全球经济增长构成压力，但经济诸多领域展现出超出预期的韧性。【原文：U.S. tariffs and uncertainty have weighed on global economic growth, but many parts of the economy have proved more resilient than expected, Swiss National Bank Chairman Martin Schlegel said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/much-world-economy-has-coped-better-than-expected-with-tariffs-snb-chairman-says-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHCRF2FKWNJDDKZGNQEIJ7NPHI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对印度、印尼和老挝的太阳能产品征收初步关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一宣布，对印度、印度尼西亚和老挝企业进口的太阳能电池和太阳能电池板征收反补贴税。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department on Monday announced anti-subsidy countervailing duties on solar cells and panels imported by companies in India, Indonesia and Laos.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-sets-preliminary-duties-solar-imports-india-indonesia-laos-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGRHQ3B4IRM4NOMBHSU5J2LQNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，资产管理公司纽伯格伯曼正探索保险业务，此举是行业推动的一部分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，纽伯格伯曼正考虑扩大其保险业务能力，这凸显了保险资产对寻求新收入来源和提升回报的资产管理公司持续具有吸引力。【原文：Neuberger Berman is exploring a potential expansion of its insurance capabilities, people familiar with the matter said, highlighting the ongoing allure of insurance assets for money managers seeking new revenue streams and boosted returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/money-manager-neuberger-berman-explores-insurance-venture-part-industry-push-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33EWPUIOMNOGLJ76PNWTM5U7RY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:42:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利监管机构禁止亚马逊物流部门使用员工个人数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利隐私监管机构周二表示，已禁止亚马逊意大利物流公司（AMZN.O）使用其位于罗马东北部帕索科雷塞物流中心1800名员工的个人信息。【原文：Italy's privacy authority said on Tuesday it had banned Amazon Italia Logistica AMZN.O from using personal information of 1,800 workers at its Passo Corese logistics centre, north-east of Rome.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/italy-watchdog-bans-amazon-unit-using-staff-personal-data-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KINUQAIOARMT3PDEHJGJSXLGCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普500指数有望年底前上涨10%，但贸易和人工智能颠覆性影响的担忧依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，尽管市场持续担忧美国总统特朗普的贸易政策及人工智能带来的冲击，但受强劲盈利和经济稳步增长推动，标普500指数将在今年剩余时间内上涨约10%。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 stock index will gain about 10% between now and the end of the year, driven by strong earnings and steady economic growth despite ongoing worries about U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies and disruption from artificial intelligence, according to a Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sp-500-poised-gain-10-by-year-end-trade-ai-disruption-concerns-persist-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQ3LV6LZ3NP5BCG5EWNIUJXUDU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大会在校园枪击案后向OpenAI安全官员施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府部长表示，在发现ChatGPT开发商OpenAI未就其封禁的涉嫌大规模枪击案嫌疑人账户向警方通报后，加拿大将于周二就安全协议问题向OpenAI官员施压。【原文：Canada will press OpenAI officials on Tuesday about their safety protocols after it emerged the ChatGPT maker did not contact police about an account it banned belonging to an alleged mass shooter, a government minister said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-press-openai-safety-officials-wake-school-shooting-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNHLUCCTUZJNPNB3ETH6EFSECY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:11:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[铝业巨头美国铝业公司寻求将10处厂区出售给数据中心运营商]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铝业公司（Alcoa Corp）首席执行官周二表示，该公司正计划向数据中心行业出售10处已关闭或缩减产能的工厂，首笔交易将于6月底前完成。【原文：U.S. aluminium company Alcoa Corp is looking to sell 10 of its closed or curtailed sites to the data centre industry, with the first sale set to be completed by the end of June, its CEO said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/aluminium-maker-alcoa-seeks-sell-10-sites-data-centres-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SH74CRSMJNMVZHZTGKNHRYKRAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国坚信其与美国的贸易协议依然有效，尽管特朗普政府最新采取了关税措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[British trade minister Peter Kyle said he was confident the trade deal Britain struck last year with the United States would still stand despite U.S. President Donald Trump's latest move to apply a 10% global import tariff.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-confident-its-trade-deal-with-us-still-stands-despite-latest-trump-tariff-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRY2P6CFWNKZRL25HCN4DGXH4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空公司与贷款方达成协议，成功脱离破产保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司周二表示，已与贷款方达成协议，这将帮助其在今春晚些时候或初夏摆脱破产困境。【原文：Spirit Airlines said on Tuesday it has reached an agreement with its lenders that will help it emerge from bankruptcy by late spring or early summer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spirit-airlines-seals-deal-with-lenders-emerge-bankruptcy-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYLC3LZQLZO4XAZ4NDHZEIEDFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:55:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[若价格僵局持续，科特迪瓦未售可可库存将激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业专家和全球贸易高管表示，除非政府下调国家监管的农民收购价以促进农民向贸易商销售，否则到3月底主要可可作物收成结束时，科特迪瓦将积压约20万吨未售出的可可。【原文：Ivory Coast will have accumulated about 200,000 metric tons of unsold cocoa by end-March when its main crop concludes unless the government cuts state-regulated farmer prices in order to unlock sales from farmers to traders, industry experts and global trading executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/ivory-coast-unsold-cocoa-stocks-set-soar-if-price-standoff-persists-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDJFRTGIEZLRFFBEBAUCQHKS7Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:53:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国软件股上涨，Anthropic公告引发市场反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shares of U.S. software companies that entered into partnerships with AI startup Anthropic on Tuesday helped lead a rebound in the sector that has been hammered by fears about the disruptive impact of artificial intelligence.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-software-stocks-climb-anthropic-announcement-sparks-relief-rally-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OU7JHEIJ2FKVFAJOE3RHUT4WJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:46:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员称，在特朗普加征关税后，欧盟将面临与美国的过渡期]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员马罗什·谢夫乔维奇周二表示，在特朗普总统实施新的进口附加费后，欧盟与美国的关系将面临为期数月的"过渡期"，这可能危及双方去年达成的贸易协议。【原文：The European Union is facing a "transitional period" of a few months in relations with the U.S. after President Donald Trump's new import surcharge, which threatens to undermine the trade deal the two sides struck last year, European Trade Commissioner Maros Sefcovic said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-faces-transition-period-with-us-after-trump-tariff-move-says-eu-trade-chief-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYLGJGWJT5NWBI6IIX2RCMDYCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:42:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉被控招聘存在反美偏见，美国法官裁定必须应诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官拒绝驳回指控特斯拉在招聘中歧视美国公民、以便支付更低薪资给外国工人的诉讼，但表示对提起诉讼的软件工程师能否胜诉持怀疑态度。【原文：A U.S. judge has refused to dismiss a lawsuit accusing Tesla of discriminating against American citizens in hiring so it can pay less to foreign workers, but said he was skeptical that the software engineer who sued would prevail.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/tesla-must-face-lawsuit-alleging-anti-american-bias-hiring-us-judge-rules-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERVAA7DF4NKDDFXSDOLHVW7254</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果股东否决要求提交中国业务关联报告的股东提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司股东周二否决了一项提案，该提案要求公司披露其对中国的依赖程度——中国制造了该公司大部分产品。【原文：Apple shareholders on Tuesday rejected a proposal to report on the company's dependence on China to manufacture a bulk of its products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/apple-shareholders-reject-shareholder-proposal-asking-report-china-entanglements-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOFD4WP2XZL4PLZ5QQSKJ3CF2E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:22:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司宣布推出普雷托尔公务机新机型]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司周二宣布推出其Praetor公务机的新型号，旨在把握全球对公务机需求激增的机遇。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer announced on Tuesday new variants of its Praetor business jets as it seeks to capitalize on heated global demand for executive aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-announces-new-variants-praetor-business-jets-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6R2XLNXZBLLLA327IJT2PQAJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州寻求禁令以阻止亚马逊涉嫌压制价格竞争的行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州周二要求州法官阻止亚马逊公司通过所谓胁迫商家不得在其他平台低价销售商品的手段，抬高消费者购买商品的价格。【原文：California asked a state judge on Tuesday to stop Amazon.com from inflating prices for consumers through an alleged campaign to bully merchants not to sell goods more cheaply elsewhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/california-seeks-injunction-stop-amazons-alleged-stifling-price-competition-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2R3EQPLW7RNPDJH5QX52AN53CM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic发布新插件后分析师评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能实验室Anthropic周二公布了10种新方案，帮助企业客户将其技术应用于关键业务领域。此前数周，该公司的其他产品发布曾引发传统软件公司股票的激进抛售。【原文：Artificial intelligence lab Anthropic on Tuesday unveiled 10 new ways for business customers to plug in its technology to key areas of their work, weeks after other releases sparked an aggressive selloff of traditional software company shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/analysts-comments-after-anthropic-unveils-new-plug-ins-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTH3VEYBAJOWTASASN6F6TEAEI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:45:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月批发库存小幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周二公布的数据显示，12月批发库存小幅上升，同时销售额实现强劲增长。【原文：U.S. wholesale inventories increased marginally in December amid strong sales growth, government data showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-wholesale-inventories-increase-marginally-december-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPSLVJN3FJJXLBGKQVMTWXT6K4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者信心指数在2月份有所改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二公布的一项调查显示，随着家庭对劳动力市场的看法好转，美国消费者信心指数在2月份出现超预期反弹。【原文：U.S. consumer confidence rebounded more than expected in February amid an improvement in households' perceptions of the labor market, a survey showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-confidence-improves-february-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7N4SR3XLNOWVESDZR7IFJTZRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:22:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大交通部在特朗普争执后认证湾流G700和G800喷气机]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大交通部已认证通用动力湾流公司的G700和G800公务机，政府文件显示，此前数周美国总统特朗普曾指责加拿大监管机构审批该机型耗时过长。【原文：Transport Canada has certified General Dynamics Gulfstream's G700 and G800 business jets, according to a government document, weeks after U.S. President Donald Trump called out the Canadian regulator for taking too long to approve the aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/transport-canada-certifies-gulfstream-g700-g800-jets-after-trump-spat-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BM266K2MRVOF3EDTY4KQFO34VQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国无人机制造商大疆提起诉讼，挑战美国对新款机型的进口禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国无人机制造商大疆周二表示，已提起诉讼，对美国联邦通信委员会禁止进口其所有新型号及关键组件的决定提出质疑，该禁令涉及中国大疆和奥图尔等企业。【原文：Chinese dronemaker DJI said Tuesday it has filed suit challenging the Federal Communications Commission decision to bar imports of all of its new models and critical components including from China's DJI and Autel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/chinese-dronemaker-dji-files-lawsuit-challenge-us-import-ban-new-models-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGV6CT2SSZKJLMIWPSEHRDIZYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:59:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，欧盟预计美国将在数周内降低钢铁和铝制品关税。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周二报道，欧盟官员预计美国将在数周内降低对含钢铝产品的关税，这可能缓解跨大西洋贸易关系中的主要摩擦点。该报道援引知情人士消息称。【原文：European Union officials expect the U.S. to lower tariffs on goods containing steel and aluminum within weeks, potentially easing a major source of friction in transatlantic trade ties, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-expects-us-scale-back-steel-aluminum-tariffs-within-weeks-bloomberg-news-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUMEI5IY6RM2JOHZPBSYC3IQDI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安普瑞克在法律插件引发市场暴跌数周后推出新型人工智能工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能实验室Anthropic近日公布了10种新方案，帮助企业客户将其技术融入关键业务领域。此前数周，该公司的其他产品发布曾引发传统软件公司股价的剧烈抛售。【原文：Artificial intelligence lab Anthropic unveiled 10 new ways for business customers to plug in its technology to key areas of their work, weeks after other releases sparked an aggressive selloff in traditional software company shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/anthropic-touts-new-ai-tools-weeks-after-legal-plug-in-spurred-market-rout-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XN2OJDNXNRIDXOD62SJMVF55AE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>