<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:16:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:16:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士央行行长称美联储独立性"对世界至关重要"]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行行长马丁·施莱格尔周三表示，央行独立性对控制通胀至关重要。当前美国联邦储备委员会主席正面临刑事调查，并遭受总统唐纳德·特朗普的猛烈抨击。【原文：Central bank independence is crucial to controlling inflation, Swiss National Bank Chairman Martin Schlegel said on Wednesday, as the U.S. Federal Reserve chair faces a criminal probe and an onslaught of attacks from President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/snb-chairman-says-fed-independence-important-world-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFQMC7RLH5IH3DQP6VMACY264Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储将维持利率至3月，甚至可能延续至鲍威尔任期结束——路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场预期美国经济将持续强劲增长，这使得美联储短期内难以降息，因为通胀率仍高于其2%的目标水平。【原文：Expectations the U.S. economy will continue growing strongly argue against near-term cuts as inflation still remains above the Fed's 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-hold-rates-through-march-possibly-through-powells-tenure-strong-growth-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24GHM6HLOVLGBNL66FBM3ACCBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险业风向标Travelers公司因承保业务强劲表现，盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[财产险与意外险巨头旅行者集团周三公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于承保业绩改善及投资回报率提升。【原文：Property and casualty insurance giant Travelers beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Wednesday, driven by stronger underwriting performance and higher investment returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/insurance-bellwether-travelers-beats-profit-estimates-stronger-underwriting-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJLRPNEBJBIVLBABJ7QXG7L6IM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，华尔街试图影响特朗普的可负担性理念]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，在中期选举前夕，华尔街主要银行正对特朗普总统降低美国生活成本的部分主张提出反对意见，同时建议其他方案以期影响政策走向。【原文：Major Wall Street banks are pushing back on some of President Donald Trump's ideas for lowering the U.S. cost of living ​ahead of mid-term elections, while suggesting others in an effort to shape policy, sources familiar with the discussions said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/wall-street-seeks-shape-trump-affordability-ideas-sources-say-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTXI56IMFBMJDE3DQKW75FQ7EE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:59:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈里伯顿第四季度盈利超预期，得益于稳定的国际需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈里伯顿周三公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，这得益于其服务和设备在国际市场上的需求保持稳定。【原文：Halliburton surpassed Wall Street expectations for fourth-quarter profit on Wednesday, on the back of steady demand for its services and equipment in international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/halliburton-beats-estimates-fourth-quarter-profit-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMF7254MYFPXBHOKGPREGDQHMI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:51:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达沃斯-城堡集团首席执行官格里芬称美国与欧洲盟友关系"日渐疏离"]]></title><description><![CDATA[城堡投资集团首席执行官肯·格里芬周三表示，美国与欧洲盟友的关系已"出现裂痕"，这位亿万富翁坦言对此"无法理解也难以认同"。【原文：Ken Griffin, the CEO of Citadel, said on Wednesday that the United States ​had "frayed its relationship" with its European allies in ‌a way that the billionaire said he did not "understand or appreciate".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/davos-citadel-ceo-griffin-says-us-has-frayed-relationship-with-european-allies-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2E6S7Z2ZNOJNIGZHTYQ5QQPRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:43:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普抵达，市场静观其变]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHZEATEXHFPD5CRJM2EO2DQGEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特Humain公司获12亿美元融资用于扩展人工智能基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯国家基础设施基金与该国人工智能公司Humain周三宣布达成最高12亿美元的融资协议，以支持该国人工智能和数字基础设施的扩展。【原文：Saudi Arabia's National Infrastructure Fund and Humain, the kingdom's artificial intelligence company, announced a financing agreement of up to $1.2 billion on Wednesday to support the expansion of AI and digital infrastructure in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudis-humain-secures-up-12-bln-expand-ai-infrastructure-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDV2RBTACBKZVPGHIMCZMJJVZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:23:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司预测2026年利润将超华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司周三公布的2026年销售额和利润预测超出华尔街预期，即便计入本月早些时候与特朗普政府达成的药品定价协议造成的"数亿美元"损失。【原文：Johnson & Johnson ​on Wednesday forecast 2026 sales and profit ahead of Wall Street estimates, even when including a hit of "hundreds of ‌millions of dollars" from the drug pricing deal it signed with the Trump administration earlier this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/johnson-johnson-forecasts-2026-profit-above-wall-street-estimates-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXLFRDYB4JIRFG4DZYK2OT4LB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:23:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰科电子预测第二季度盈利向好，因人工智能工具需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰科电子周三公布的第二季度利润超出华尔街预期，这家电子元件制造商正押注其人工智能相关工具和产品的需求激增。【原文：TE Connectivity projected second-quarter profit above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, as the electronic component maker banks on a surge in demand for its AI-related tools and products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/te-connectivity-forecasts-upbeat-second-quarter-profit-strong-ai-tools-demand-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NULV7L5O5NIHNKOUFIPJEGQ6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:09:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道明银行从摩根大通、高盛等竞争对手处挖角银行家，以扩大其债务与股权资本市场团队。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，TD银行高管透露，该行已从北美多家顶级银行挖角六名资深银行家至纽约，以推动其债务与股权资本市场业务发展。【原文：TD Bank has recruited half a dozen senior bankers in New York from top North American banks to boost its debt and equity capital market businesses, senior executives told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/td-hires-bankers-rivals-including-jpmorgan-goldman-expand-debt-equity-capital-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGT2QUQKZZL4TE7AHQ7JOMLTWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的攻击目标——美联储的库克，是位身经百战的斗士，身上的伤痕便是明证。]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普总统解雇美联储理事丽莎·库克的争议性决定，已成为其试图掌控美国央行及不断挑战总统权力边界行动的试金石。【原文：President Donald Trump's contested firing of Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook has become a test case in his ​bid to assert control over the U.S. central bank and his ongoing efforts to push the limits of presidential power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/targeted-by-trump-feds-cook-is-fighter-with-scars-prove-it-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YINDNCSPMFKE5JQA6DUB52SW2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院审议特朗普解雇美联储委员丽莎·库克的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院即将审理唐纳德·特朗普总统解雇美联储理事丽莎·库克的史无前例之举。此案将考验大法官们为维护央行独立性愿意走多远。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court is set to consider President Donald Trump's unprecedented attempt to fire Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook in a case that tests how far the justices may be willing to ​go to preserve the central bank's independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-considers-trumps-bid-fire-feds-lisa-cook-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COJ3D4KVJBLSTNTUVTLNGCCLZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称德意志银行首席执行官致电要求银行与分析师的格陵兰报告保持距离]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，德意志银行首席执行官致电告知，该行不再支持其分析师报告中关于欧洲投资者可能抛售美国资产的观点。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that Deutsche Bank's chief executive had called him to say the bank does not stand by one of its analyst reports suggesting European investors may dump U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/bessent-says-deutsche-bank-ceo-called-distance-bank-analysts-greenland-report-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZ2YYI3V4BLNXEDXUW5W7KHM3E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克对阵瑞安航空：奥利里驳斥收购威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空首席执行官迈克尔·奥利里周三表示，埃隆·马斯克无法收购瑞安航空，但任何投资都比他在X平台的收益更可观。这是双方最新一轮公开交锋，奥利里称这场争论正助推瑞安航空的预订量。【原文：Elon Musk can't buy Ryanair , but any investment would do better than his returns from X, the airline's boss Michael O'Leary said on Wednesday, in the latest round of a public spat that O'Leary said was helping Ryanair's bookings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ryanair-would-welcome-musk-investment-says-oleary-spat-continues-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BX5OS6RWYZNXVBSV5WC5ZDC5UY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度塔塔通信季度利润因强劲需求激增；任命候任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度塔塔通信公司周三公布，受云服务和连接解决方案需求强劲推动，该公司实现三个季度以来的首次利润增长。【原文：India's Tata Communications reported its first profit rise in three quarters on Wednesday, on strong demand for its cloud services and connectivity solutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/indias-tata-communications-quarterly-profit-jumps-robust-demand-names-ceo-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZCMTHUTM5IPDPZPZ27LMJJK5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:14:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奈飞为收购华纳兄弟计划辩护，股价因业绩疲软下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA["YouTube已不再只是用户生成内容和猫咪视频的聚集地，"网飞首席执行官泰德·萨兰多斯周二表示。【原文："YouTube is not just user-generated content and cat videos anymore," Netflix CEO Ted Sarandos said on ​Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-shares-drop-tepid-results-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRFBADKONNJJBKE7BHJTATPA3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子能源首席执行官将出席特朗普与商界领袖的会议，董事长表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子能源公司监事会主席乔·凯泽表示，该公司首席执行官克里斯蒂安·布鲁赫将出席定于周三晚些时候在瑞士达沃斯举行的企业领袖与美国总统唐纳德·特朗普的会晤。【原文：Siemens Energy CEO Christian Bruch will attend a meeting of business leaders with U.S. President Donald Trump scheduled later on Wednesday in Davos, Switzerland, the company's Supervisory Board Chairman Joe Kaeser said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/siemens-energy-ceo-attend-trump-meeting-with-business-leaders-chairman-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FP7TQIH46ZP7FKT52MWMTRWOWI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[无论华纳兄弟被谁收购，摩根大通和艾伦公司都将凭借1.8亿美元的并购佣金获利。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在奈飞与派拉蒙天空舞影业争夺华纳兄弟探索公司的竞购战中，摩根大通和艾伦公司正成为明显的赢家。【原文：Some clear winners are emerging in the bidding war between Netflix and Paramount Skydance for Warner Bros Discovery: JPMorgan and Allen & Company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/no-matter-who-buys-warner-bros-jpmorgan-allen-co-win-with-180-million-ma-fees-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTO3EOFFVJPQNBJKSWKUFLV5L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优必选与空客达成协议，将扩大机器人在航空制造领域的应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国机器人企业优必选周三宣布，已与全球最大飞机制造商空客签署协议，为其航空制造领域提供机器人设备。【原文：Chinese robotics firm UBTech said on Wednesday it had signed a deal with the world's largest planemaker, Airbus , to supply robots for use in aviation manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/ubtech-agrees-airbus-deal-expand-robot-use-aviation-manufacturing-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4GB6ANC4BIFFJCRMA2KNCCZ5E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:55:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉预计日本将把赤字控制在可控范围内，尽管实施了减税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉评级的日本主权分析师周三向路透社表示，该机构预计日本政府在下月众议院选举后将继续将财政赤字控制在可控范围内，因东京方面正面临债券市场对其减税政策的压力。【原文：Fitch Ratings expects Japan's government to continue to keep deficits within manageable levels after a lower house election next month as Tokyo faces pressure from the bond market over tax cuts, its sovereign analyst told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fitch-expects-japan-keep-deficits-within-manageable-levels-despite-tax-cut-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KLYOTZ27JPKHGUGWBSYB6PV4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：Meta新成立的人工智能团队本月已向内部交付首批关键模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms公司首席技术官周三表示，该公司新成立的人工智能实验室本月已向内部交付了首批备受瞩目的人工智能模型。【原文：Meta Platforms' new artificial intelligence lab has delivered its first high-profile AI models internally this month, the company's chief technology officer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/metas-new-ai-team-has-delivered-first-key-models-internally-this-month-cto-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVKV7DDC7FO4DPHUCLHISVFCXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟草案拟赋予欧洲电信运营商无限无线电频谱使用权]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周三公布的一项提案将为欧洲电信运营商提供重大助力，允许其无限期使用无线电频谱。但运营商要求科技巨头分担宽带部署成本的诉求未获采纳。【原文：Europe's telecoms operators will get a major boost under a European Commission proposal announced on Wednesday, allowing them to use radio spectrum for an unlimited duration, but their demand that Big Tech be required to help fund the cost of rolling out broadband went unheeded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/european-telcos-get-unlimited-radio-spectrum-under-eu-draft-law-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGW4HFRNZVKCDD2OBBFK7Y62AI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长贝森特对国债抛售潮不感到担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，他不担心因特朗普政府威胁对反对美国收购格陵兰岛的欧洲盟友加征关税而引发的美国国债抛售潮。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday he ​was not concerned about any sell-off in U.S. Treasuries related to the ‌Trump administration's threats to impose tariffs on European allies opposing U.S. efforts to acquire Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/us-treasury-secretary-bessent-not-concerned-about-any-treasuries-sell-off-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5HDRHBY5BKZNARSEDYMJ5C6OI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源署称，全球石油市场第一季度将面临显著过剩]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际能源署周三表示，2026年第一季度全球石油市场将出现严重过剩，因为迄今为止过剩的供应已抵消了地缘政治风险导致的供应中断。【原文：The global oil market will be in deep surplus in the first quarter of 2026, the International Energy Agency said on Wednesday, as so far excess supplies have offset the geopolitical risk of disruption.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/global-oil-demand-growth-rise-2026-iea-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5DOLTMIPNLI3ADZAY3WHQI5AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI致力于推动人工智能在全球日常生活中的广泛应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI正扩大其努力，旨在说服全球各国政府建设更多数据中心，并鼓励在教育、医疗和防灾等领域更广泛地应用人工智能。【原文：OpenAI is expanding its efforts to convince global governments to build more data centers and encourage greater usage of artificial intelligence in areas such as education, health and disaster preparedness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/openai-seeks-increase-global-ai-use-everyday-life-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCS6XVGODBLUTFBBLVGAK2T2O4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解读：特朗普对六个欧盟国家加征关税可能给美国海关带来麻烦]]></title><description><![CDATA[若美国总统特朗普兑现其对六个欧盟国家（而非整个欧盟）加征关税的威胁，鉴于欧盟成员国间货物流通的便利性，美国海关当局将面临真正的挑战。【原文：U.S. customs authorities will face a real challenge if President Donald Trump goes through with his threat to place tariffs on six EU countries - rather than the whole European Union - given the ease of movement of goods between EU members.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-six-eu-nations-could-create-us-customs-headache-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAGVHX7FWBMEZGAW43MFFVH73Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，福特因发动机缸体加热器存在起火风险召回逾11.9万辆美国本土车辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周三表示，福特汽车公司正在美国召回119,075辆汽车，原因是发动机缸体加热器可能出现裂纹并泄漏冷却液，当加热器插电时可能导致短路，从而增加起火风险。【原文：Ford Motor is recalling 119,075 vehicles in the U.S. as the engine block heater may crack and leak coolant, potentially causing a short circuit and increasing the risk of a fire when the heater is plugged in, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recalls-over-119000-vehicles-over-engine-block-heater-fire-risk-nhtsa-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2Q7I26R3FLSBMPBCDFMCMSXNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:20:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奈飞股价在欧洲暴跌7%，此前公布第四季度财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管Netflix第四季度营收和盈利超出预期，但该公司周三在法兰克福上市的股票早盘仍出现下跌，原因是其仍在与华纳兄弟探索公司展开激烈的收购竞标战。【原文：Netflix , shares listed in Frankfurt fell in early trade on Wednesday despite beating expectations for fourth quarter revenue and earnings, as the company remains locked in a fierce bidding war for Warner Bros Discovery .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-shares-drop-7-europe-after-q4-results-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5G3KHXOPN5LFTNYYPMOPC5SMIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalWafers董事长表示，该公司正为德克萨斯州工厂的第二阶段扩建做准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾硅晶圆制造商华晶科技董事长徐丽珍周三向记者透露，该公司正筹备其位于美国得克萨斯州工厂的二期扩建计划，具体实施将取决于客户订单承诺。【原文：Taiwanese silicon wafer manufacturer GlobalWafers is preparing for the phase two expansion of its plant in the U.S. state of Texas, subject to customer commitments, Chairperson Doris Hsu told reporters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/globalwafers-is-preparing-phase-two-expansion-texas-plant-chairperson-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFCTDORMYBOO5IWJVN3NSZCUIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>