<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:10:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:10:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[大科技公司将在人工智能泡沫阴影下公布财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国科技巨头纷纷公布财报，其中一个问题迫在眉睫：人工智能的蓬勃发展是否会导致估值膨胀，从而引发下一个大泡沫？【原文：As America's tech titans report earnings this week, one question looms large: is the artificial intelligence boom that has inflated valuations headed for the next big bubble?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/big-tech-report-earnings-under-specter-ai-bubble-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SFB7GHCWNIOVFJKBOKGCOXFHU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储减息倒计时：债券投资者减少购买较长期限的国债]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美联储准备在周三再次降息四分之一个百分点，债券投资者正在重新审视其持有的较长期限国债，一些投资者减少了头寸，另一些投资者甚至做空基准国债。【原文：Bond investors are re-examining their holdings of longer-dated Treasuries, with some reducing positions and others even going short relative to their benchmark, as the Federal Reserve prepares to cut interest rates by another quarter percentage point on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/countdown-fed-cut-bond-investors-scale-back-longer-dated-treasuries-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCHJSN5ICZN6NNAC4WJ6A5ONGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 LTIMindtree 公司首席执行官表示将大力发展新的人工智能部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[在印度 2830 亿美元的 IT 行业面临客户广泛削减非必要支出之际，LTIMindtree 公司的最高负责人表示，公司将加倍努力发展人工智能，投资于一个新推出的平台，帮助企业采用这项技术。【原文：LTIMindtree is doubling down on AI with investments in a newly-launched platform that helps companies adopt the technology, its top boss said, as India's $283-billion IT industry faces broader cuts in non-essential spending by clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-ltimindtree-betting-big-new-ai-unit-ceo-says-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4BE75UH3NKGPBGQ3GUYUYUYCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空首席执行官称美国政府关门影响 "不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司
 达美航空公司首席执行官周一表示，美国政府停摆造成的影响 "很小"，每天的损失不到 100 万美元，而机场安检人员的短缺才是更令人担忧的问题。【原文：Delta Air Lines 
 is seeing a "small" impact from the U.S. government shutdown, costing it less than $1 million a day, and the shortage of airport security staff is of greater concern, the carrier's CEO said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/delta-air-lines-seeing-small-impact-us-government-shutdown-ceo-says-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTXOW2PZUFNUDKX6DLIW5KFALY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:47:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美关系乐观，华尔街期货创历史新高；科技业绩受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货跃升至历史新高，原因是对中美达成贸易协议的预期在本周大科技公司财报和美联储可能降息的背景下刺激了风险偏好。【原文：U.S. stock index futures jumped to record highs on Monday as expectations of a trade deal between China and the United States fanned risk appetite in a week packed with Big Tech earnings and a potential interest-rate cut from the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/wall-st-futures-hit-record-highs-us-china-optimism-tech-results-focus-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NO7VAGZCVPYJBJZPDJOY6VXQ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊称尽管美国征收关税，但印度电子商务出口额仍突破 200 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周一表示，它已帮助印度卖家的出口总额突破 200 亿美元，其中包括今年的近 70 亿美元，因为小型经营者正在努力抵消 8 月份美国新征收的进口关税的影响。【原文：Amazon on Monday said it has helped Indian sellers surpass $20 billion in total exports, including nearly $7 billion this year, as small operators work to offset the impact of new U.S. import tariffs that were imposed in August.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-says-indias-e-commerce-exports-top-20-billion-despite-us-tariffs-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VIMTSH4ISJPQZAGPX7TK7MWVCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴林主权基金与 SandboxAQ 签署协议，利用人工智能加速药物发现]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国人工智能和量子技术公司 SandboxAQ 周一与巴林主权财富基金签署了一项协议，旨在加快药物开发并创造价值 10 亿美元的生物技术资产。【原文：SandboxAQ, a U.S.-based artificial intelligence and quantum technology firm, signed an agreement with Bahrain's sovereign wealth fund on Monday aimed at speeding up the development of drugs and creating biotech assets worth $1 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bahrains-sovereign-fund-sandboxaq-sign-deal-speed-up-drug-discovery-with-ai-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETWDWF4U3JPZFNS66TPCQ34VQE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特人工智能公司 Humain 公布 6 千兆瓦数据中心计划和新的人工智能操作系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特人工智能公司 Humain 首席执行官塔里克-阿明（Tareq Amin）周一在利雅得举行的《财富》会议上表示，该公司计划建设约 6 千兆瓦容量的数据中心，并将推出 Humain 1。【原文：Saudi AI firm Humain is planning to construct approximately 6 gigawatts of data centre capacity and is launching Humain 1, its CEO Tareq Amin said on Monday at the Fortune conference in Riyadh.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-ai-firm-humain-unveils-6-gigawatt-data-centre-plan-new-ai-operating-system-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CM5VERGPFBI4NNQJ2AKDEBAWM4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 07:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称年底或将决定美联储新主席人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，可能会在今年年底前决定下一任美联储主席的人选。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said a decision on the next Federal Reserve chair might be made by the end of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-new-fed-chair-decision-might-be-made-by-year-end-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVGKBRJDBRIMPALBHCT3ZVYQ5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中美将达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，美国和中国将 "达成 "一项贸易协议，预计本周晚些时候他将在亚洲之行中与中国国家主席习近平在韩国会面。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said the U.S. and China are set to "come away with" a trade deal, as he is expected to meet Chinese President Xi Jinping later this week in South Korea during his Asia tour.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-says-he-might-sign-final-tiktok-deal-thursday-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSMITGHREFMPRFGNM6Y3RLDT3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 FD 报道，亚马逊将向荷兰业务投资 16 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰金融日报《FD》周一援引亚马逊比利时和荷兰负责人的话报道，亚马逊计划未来三年在荷兰投资 14 亿欧元（16.3 亿美元）。【原文：Amazon plans to invest 1.4 billion euros ($1.63 billion) in the Netherlands in the next three years, Dutch financial daily FD reported on Monday, citing the company's head for Belgium and the Netherlands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-invest-16-billion-dutch-operations-fd-reports-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJ3KSJVWLJK4DJEODLIPHBLBMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰在线银行 Bunq 获得美国经纪商牌照]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰在线银行 Bunq 周一表示，该公司已获得在美国作为经纪交易商运营的许可，这也是该公司向欧洲以外地区扩张的举措之一。【原文：Dutch online bank Bunq said on Monday that it had received a licence to operate as a broker-dealer in the United States, part of a drive to expand outside of Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dutch-online-bank-bunq-gets-us-broker-dealer-licence-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DGWKJ2O3BLWXNH7HHZAQ4BABA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奢侈品牌在中国展现魅力]]></title><description><![CDATA[路威酩轩和爱马仕等公司越来越多地提供私密晚宴和大型表演，以及设有私人购物区和专用电梯的商店，他们打赌这些贵宾将有助于结束大流行后的销售低迷。【原文：Firms like LVMH and Hermes increasingly offer intimate dinners and large-scale shows, as well as stores with private shopping areas and exclusive elevator access for the VIPs they bet will help end a post-pandemic sales slump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/luxury-brands-turn-charm-china-kindle-nascent-spending-recovery-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KS47HVOGRBPPJBA6X4VH4I6ABY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 05:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普离开东盟峰会后，世界各国领导人期待建立经贸联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普总统离开东南亚国家峰会继续访问该地区之后，世界各国领导人周一将齐聚马来西亚，讨论如何在美国关税迫在眉睫的阴影下加强经贸联系。【原文：World leaders gathered in Malaysia on Monday will discuss ways to strengthen economic and trade ties in the shadow of looming U.S. tariffs after President Donald Trump left a summit of Southeast Asian nations to continue a tour of the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/world-leaders-look-build-economic-trade-ties-after-trump-departs-asean-summit-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBLDXIXHQROVBCFR2MXEPCGHWA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 05:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价贸易协议希望刺激风险反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNKYQ7MNCRJJNLBTHJXGVSEVSM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国需求强劲，丰田 9 月产量连续第四个月增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周一称，9月份全球产量增长超过10%，连续第四个月增长，原因是日本汽车制造商的第一大市场--美国的销量和产量均有所增长。【原文：Toyota Motor on Monday said its worldwide production increased by more than 10% in September and rose for a fourth straight month, as both sales and output increased in the U.S., the Japanese automaker's top market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-september-output-grows-fourth-stright-month-aided-by-strong-us-demand-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TODZ5IHJRFOQNLW45TRR5CI2NQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与习近平在韩国会谈的关键问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四将在韩国会见中国国家主席习近平，这是他第二个任期内面临的最严峻挑战之一，世界上最大的两个经济体将寻求避免贸易战升级。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump faces one of the toughest challenges of his second term when he meets Chinese President Xi Jinping in South Korea on Thursday, where the world's two largest economies will seek to avert an escalation of their trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/key-issues-stake-trump-xi-talks-south-korea-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMXQQMN3ZFPQXDUBUBN57VDLJM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西总统卢拉称特朗普 "保证 "与美国达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周一表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在两国领导人最近的会晤中 "保证 "两国将达成贸易协议。【原文：Brazil's President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Monday that U.S. President Donald Trump had "guaranteed" that the two countries would reach a deal on trade during a recent meeting between the two leaders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazilian-president-lula-says-trump-guaranteed-trade-deal-with-us-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GH64VSLDGVNLTB5ET4YXLITQBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 03:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在习近平峰会前赴东京举行贸易和安全会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一启程前往东京，他计划在那里会见日本天皇和新当选的首相佐那江隆一，这是旨在确保贸易协议、投资和增加国防开支的亚洲之行的一部分。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump departed for Tokyo on Monday, where he was scheduled to meet Japan's emperor and newly elected Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi as part of an Asia trip aimed at securing trade deals, investment and increased defence spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-heads-tokyo-trade-security-talks-before-xi-summit-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSYWXAL4MNOVNDCZNAPH7WCSJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 03:15:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机器狗和人工智能无人机群：中国如何将 DeepSeek 用于战争时代]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对数以百计的研究论文、专利和采购记录进行了审查，为中国政府利用人工智能获取军事优势的系统性努力提供了一个缩影。【原文：A Reuters review of hundreds of research papers, patents and procurement records gives a snapshot of the systematic effort by Beijing to harness AI for military advantage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/robot-dogs-ai-drone-swarms-how-china-could-use-deepseek-an-era-war-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEJMXTL74BPS3PFT4M4IVST5LI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 03:01:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储会议召开前，股市因贸易协议乐观情绪而飙升，美元则随波逐流]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，随着中美贸易紧张局势缓和的迹象提振了风险偏好，亚洲股市大涨，美元走势徘徊，为本周的央行会议和巨头财报开了个好头。【原文：Asian stocks surged and the dollar meandered on Monday as signs of easing trade tensions between China and the U.S. buoyed risk appetite, in a strong start to a week that will be headlined by central bank meetings and megacap earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37LYXPNQ25L3BNUC3SH2XJS2F4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 02:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球首个与日元挂钩的稳定币在日本首次亮相]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界上首个与日元挂钩的稳定币将于周一在日本推出，这在一个现金和信用卡等传统支付手段占据金融基础设施主导地位的国家是一个微小但意义重大的举措。【原文：The world's first stablecoin pegged to the yen will be launched in Japan on Monday, a small but significant move in a country where traditional payment means like cash and credit cards dominate financial infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/worlds-first-yen-pegged-stablecoin-debuts-japan-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ER2K2LP4JL4BFIL32T3V2GLZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易谈判和美联储会议迫在眉睫，美元兑日元创两周新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，在全球贸易谈判和央行会议密集的一周开始之际，美元兑日元汇率升至两周多来的新高。【原文：The U.S. dollar rose to a more than two-week high against the yen on Monday at the start of a packed week of global trade negotiations and central bank meetings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-hits-two-week-high-against-yen-trade-talks-fed-meeting-loom-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JP3XU5MRXJMC5GSQ2BCVGGGSDI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美达成贸易协议框架后油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中美两国经济官员勾勒出贸易协议框架后，油价在周一早盘上涨，缓解了人们对全球前两大石油消费国之间的关税和出口限制可能影响全球经济增长的担忧。【原文：Oil prices rose in early trade on Monday after U.S. and Chinese economic officials sketched out a trade-deal framework, easing fears that tariffs and export curbs between the world's top two oil consumers could dent global economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-after-us-china-reach-trade-deal-framework-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUVKQRFXVNPSRLUW37AAWW2OLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 9 月服务业通胀领先指标回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的数据显示，9月份日本服务业通胀的领先指标连续第二个月回升，支持了日本央行的观点，即劳动力成本上升将有助于把通胀率持续维持在2%的目标附近。【原文：A leading indicator of Japan's service-sector inflation perked up for the second straight month in September, data showed on Monday, backing up the central bank's view that rising labour costs will help keep inflation sustainably around its 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-leading-indicator-service-inflation-perks-up-september-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XD5C53LXPJLELMA7WX4X33FOTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢森堡法院就麦道夫案作出裁决后，汇丰银行将计提 11 亿美元拨备]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰控股周一表示，在卢森堡法院就与麦道夫投资欺诈案有关的长期诉讼作出裁决后，该公司将在第三季度业绩中确认 11 亿美元的拨备。【原文：HSBC Holdings said on Monday it will recognise a provision of $1.1 billion in its third-quarter results after a Luxembourg court ruling in a long-running lawsuit tied to the Bernard Madoff investment fraud.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-book-11-billion-provision-after-luxembourg-court-ruling-madoff-case-2025-10-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XZNY67FOBICDG5IYVJ4ZRNG6A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Larvotto 资源公司因估值问题拒绝 3.73 亿美元收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Larvotto 资源公司周一表示，该公司拒绝了上周从美国锑业公司（United States Antimony Corporation）收到的不具约束力的指示性报价，该报价对该矿商的估值约为 7.229 亿澳元（4.6974 亿美元）。【原文：Australia's Larvotto Resources said on Monday it had rejected a non-binding indicative offer received last week from United States Antimony Corporation, valuing the miner at about A$722.9 million ($469.74 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-larvotto-resources-rejects-373-million-takeover-offer-valuation-2025-10-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MV7HAGMEJPXBEYPMS2OJ5YI44</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 22:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚将微软告上法庭，称其误导了 270 万客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚竞争监督机构周一表示，已向联邦法院提起诉讼，指控微软澳大利亚公司及其母公司微软公司涉嫌误导约 270 万澳大利亚客户。【原文：Australia's competition watchdog said on Monday said it has filed proceedings in the Federal Court against Microsoft Australia and its parent company Microsoft Corp for allegedly misleading about 2.7 million Australian customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-takes-microsoft-court-says-it-misled-27-million-customers-2025-10-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YVT3AZILRNC5AKII7VQMRYTCQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 22:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国运输部长称出现空中交通管制员短缺问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）表示，美国机场周六报告了 20 多起空中交通管制员短缺事件，这是政府停摆影响的最新迹象。【原文：U.S. airports reported more than 20 incidents of air traffic controller shortages on Saturday, Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said, in the latest sign of the government shutdown's impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-traffic-controller-shortages-emerge-us-transportation-secretary-says-2025-10-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSCK2CGQYZOHLAEJQAKHRQ6OGE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华将以约 120 亿美元收购 Avidity 生物科学公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士制药商诺华（Novartis）周日表示，同意以约 120 亿美元的现金收购美国生物技术公司 Avidity Biosciences。【原文：Swiss drugmaker Novartis on Sunday said it agreed to acquire U.S. biotech firm Avidity Biosciences for about $12 billion in cash, as the company looks to bolster its portfolio of treatments for rare muscle disorders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-acquire-avidity-biosciences-12-billion-2025-10-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBQED76HIVJFLOAZR6ALFS5JTQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>