<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:04:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[因债务问题和收益率上升，美国股票基金每周面临资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至5月21日的一周里，美国股票基金资金大量流出，因为人们担心唐纳德-特朗普总统提出的减税法案一旦获得国会通过，会使美国债务增加数万亿美元，导致国债收益率飙升。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw huge outflows in the week ended May 21, as Treasury yields surged on fears President Donald Trump’s proposed tax-cut bill could add trillions to U.S. debt if passed by Congress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-face-weekly-outflows-debt-concerns-rising-yields-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDRYWG3RKBJ65AR4EDZKBGMQXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普助手称，必须继续对中国实施 EUV 光刻机限制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫人工智能和加密沙皇大卫-萨克斯（David Sacks）周五表示，限制向中国出售极紫外（EUV）光刻设备是美国在半导体领域 "最重要的一项出口管制措施"。【原文：Restricting the sale of extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography equipment to China is the "single most important export control" the United States has in the area of semiconductors, the White House's AI and crypto czar David Sacks said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/euv-lithography-restrictions-china-must-continue-trump-aide-says-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WIWSDDLOJKL7DFZ5JFVUYIL6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普紧张局势加剧，哈佛大学部分债券触及历史新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈佛大学的债券是这所常春藤盟校 82 亿美元债务的一部分，周五在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府日益激烈的对峙中陷入困境。【原文：Harvard University's bonds, which are part of the Ivy League school's $8.2 billion debt pile, struggled on Friday amid an increasingly fraught standoff with U.S. President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/some-harvard-bonds-hit-near-record-low-trump-tensions-mount-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFR3GGGEUNMUHJJ7AUBD3O4VGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:15:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯警告消费者数据泄露]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国运动服制造商阿迪达斯周五表示，一家未经授权的外部机构通过第三方客户服务提供商获取了某些消费者数据，但不包括密码或信用卡数据。【原文：German sportswear maker Adidas said on Friday an unauthorised external party had obtained certain consumer data through a third-party customer service provider albeit not passwords or credit card data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-warns-consumer-data-breach-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KY33BAFKJVODBOC3CL6HJRTETE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储库克四月市场波动将有助于完善金融稳定性评估]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）周五指出，上个月由特朗普政府宣布的出人意料的高关税所引发的金融市场波动并没有导致 COVID-19 大流行病所引发的那种美国市场功能失调，但她补充说，这次经历将有助于 "磨练我们对 "金融体系稳定性的 "持续评估"。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook on Friday noted financial market volatility last month driven by the Trump administration's announcement of unexpectedly high tariffs did not result in the kind of U.S. market dysfunction triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic, but added that the experience would help "hone our ongoing assessment" of the stability of the financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-cook-april-market-volatility-will-help-hone-financial-stability-assessment-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYPCPY22ZJJCNN7DYGWOZYR2SI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通扩充技术团队，四名资深银行家分别来自美国银行、高盛和拉扎德银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份给员工的备忘录，摩根大通正在扩大投资银行的技术团队，从高盛、美国银行和拉扎德公司招聘了四名西海岸员工。【原文：JPMorgan is expanding its technology team in the investment bank with four West Coast hires from Goldman Sachs, Bank of America and Lazard, according to a memo to staff seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-expands-tech-team-with-four-veteran-bankers-bofa-goldman-lazard-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q735JJA6FNNCNOULAD6Y2GVJ6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司和赫斯公司将就雪佛龙公司的油田财富交易展开对峙]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国顶级石油生产商埃克森美孚公司和赫斯公司将于周一在法庭听证会上面对面会谈，以决定雪佛龙公司以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司以及圭亚那多产油田宝贵股份的交易的命运。【原文：Top U.S. oil producer Exxon Mobil and Hess will meet face-to-face on Monday in a court hearing to determine the fate of Chevron's $53 billion deal to buy Hess and with it a prized stake in Guyana's prolific oilfields.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-hess-face-off-over-chevron-deal-oilfield-riches-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KCMMBTHLNLQXMQPVF3DM2FZIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:50:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特说特朗普的关税威胁可能会在欧盟贸易谈判中点燃一把火]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统并不认为欧盟向美国提出的贸易提议质量足够高，他希望 6 月 1 日的 50%关税威胁能在欧盟与华盛顿的谈判中 "点燃一把火"。【原文：Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Friday that President Donald Trump does not believe that the European Union's trade offers to the United States are of sufficient quality and that he hopes that a June 1 50% tariff threat will "light a fire under the EU" in negotiations with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bessent-says-trump-tariff-threat-may-light-fire-under-eu-trade-talks-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJI4XQCXUNMD3F7TJQ2CZSYNKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:12:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员敦促司法部不要让波音公司逃避刑事起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名美国参议员周五呼吁司法部在两起致命的 737 MAX 坠毁事故引发的刑事欺诈案中起诉波音公司，并拒绝接受允许该飞机制造商避免认罪的临时协议。【原文：Two U.S. senators called on the Justice Department on Friday to prosecute Boeing in a criminal fraud case stemming from two fatal 737 MAX crashes and reject a tentative deal to allow the planemaker to avoid pleading guilty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-senators-urge-doj-not-let-boeing-avoid-criminal-prosecution-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76LSXG5WJ5J63FXM42C7JSUB5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:09:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对特朗普威胁对欧盟商品征收 50%关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五再次威胁要加强贸易战，建议从6月1日起对欧盟商品征收50%的关税，并警告苹果公司，他可能会对在美国以外生产的任何iPhone手机征收25%的关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump threatened once again on Friday to ramp up his trade war, recommending a 50% tariff on European Union goods starting June 1 and warning Apple he may impose a 25% tariff on any iPhones manufactured outside the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/reaction-trumps-threat-50-tariffs-eu-goods-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVWZYVVYXJMKNHQR6ERKLCAXVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金创六周来最大单周流出量]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪（Moody）下调美国主权信用评级后，美国国债收益率上升，市场对美国债务负担和减税立法的担忧与日俱增，受此压力，全球股票基金六周来首次出现周度资金外流。【原文：Global equity funds have seen weekly outflows for the first time in six weeks, pressured by rising U.S. Treasury yields and mounting concerns over the U.S. debt burden and tax-cut legislation, following Moody’s downgrade of the U.S. sovereign credit rating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TQHXODN4JO27O5Y2BNXFQU6CU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月新屋销售意外增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于建筑商降低价格以吸引购房者，4 月份美国新建独户住宅的销量意外增长，但抵押贷款利率的上升和经济前景的不确定性仍然制约着房地产市场。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes unexpectedly increased in April as builders lowered prices to lure buyers, but rising mortgage rates and an uncertain economic outlook remain constraints for the housing market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-unexpectedly-rise-april-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PB2P7ZISLJJUJLUTJ5LHFY6GI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟等待特朗普50%关税威胁的澄清]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五建议从6月1日起对欧盟进口商品征收50%的关税后，欧盟委员会寻求美国的澄清。【原文：The European Commission sought clarity from the United States after U.S. President Donald Trump recommended on Friday putting a 50% tariff on EU imports from June 1, with Brussels' and Washington's trade chiefs due to talk later.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-awaits-clarity-trumps-50-tariff-threat-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZO2AJJ4I5NDBGIVDRFDBPS3FE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：维萨卡和万事达卡面临欧盟反垄断挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，欧盟反垄断机构正在审查支付处理巨头威士（Visa）和万事达（Mastercard）收取的费用。【原文：European Union antitrust authorities are scrutinizing fees charged by payments processing giants Visa and Mastercard , Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/visa-mastercard-face-eu-antitrust-heat-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TXBDIU3YJMANILBRSJSMY3JJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:04:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JBS 小股东批准在美国和巴西两地上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西肉类加工企业 JBS 周五在提交的一份证券文件中表示，该公司获得了股东的支持，将继续推进计划已久的股票在美国和巴西两地上市的计划。【原文：Brazilian meatpacker JBS on Friday secured shareholder support to move ahead with a long-planned dual listing of shares in both the United States and Brazil, it said in a securities filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/jbs-minority-shareholders-approve-dual-us-brazil-listing-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XODGLWZOX5MV7HLZJWK23RJIKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:36:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税冲击欧洲奢侈品行业，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，他建议从 6 月 1 日起对来自欧盟的商品直接征收 50%的关税，欧洲奢侈品股周五下跌。【原文：European luxury shares tanked on Friday as U.S. President Donald Trump said he is recommending a straight 50% tariff on goods from the European Union starting on June 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-tariffs-hit-european-luxury-industry-shares-tank-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHBPUSVRGZNOHDV4WVZL6F3MQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国维权组织阻止 Meta 将数据用于人工智能的申请失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一个德国消费者权益组织未能赢得法院禁令，阻止 Meta Platforms 利用 Facebook 和 Instagram 用户帖子训练其人工智能模型。【原文：A German consumer rights group on Friday failed to win a court injunction to stop Meta Platforms from training its artificial intelligence models with Facebook and Instagram user posts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/german-rights-group-fails-bid-stop-metas-data-use-ai-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDCUSO5IWFO3HFHFVGU3NZTV5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:09:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司首席执行官称客户必须为关税上涨买单]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司首席执行官哈坎-萨缪尔森（Hakan Samuelsson）周五告诉路透社记者，该公司的客户将不得不支付与关税相关的大部分成本增加。【原文：Volvo Cars CEO Hakan Samuelsson told Reuters on Friday that the company's customers would have to pay a large part of tariff-related cost increases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/volvo-cars-ceo-says-customers-must-pay-rising-tariffs-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKPI5WZKAZPRROAXE5W2FLP7DY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普建议对欧盟征收 50%关税后，欧洲股市下跌，债券反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示建议从6月1日起对来自欧盟的商品直接征收50%的关税后，欧洲股市暴跌，欧元回吐部分涨幅，欧元区政府债券收益率大幅下跌。【原文：European stocks tumbled, the euro gave back some gains, and euro zone government bond yields fell sharply on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he is recommending a straight 50% tariff on goods from the European Union starting on June 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/european-stocks-tumble-bonds-rally-after-trump-recommends-50-tariff-eu-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2DTLIE4DJMSNEA4G2YRMD37ZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:18:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[减肥药折扣不足，美国患者举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[多年来，礼来公司和诺和诺德公司高效减肥药的廉价复制品一直很容易买到，但一些美国患者表示，他们不愿意支付更多的费用，正在寻找替代品，以避开监管部门规定的复方药店停止生产这些药物的最后期限。【原文：After years of easily available, cheap copies of Eli Lilly's and Novo Nordisk's highly effective weight-loss drugs, some U.S. patients say they are unwilling to pay more and are pursuing alternatives to get around the regulatory deadline for compounding pharmacies to stop making them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/amid-compounding-crackdown-us-patients-struggle-weight-loss-drug-discounts-fall-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWIAZIIFNJOAJEDUGLPQ6WBNTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:18:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普建议从 6 月 1 日起对欧盟征收 50%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他建议从 6 月 1 日起对来自欧盟的商品直接征收 50%的关税，并称欧盟在贸易问题上一直很难打交道。【原文：President Donald Trump said that he is recommending a straight 50% tariff on goods from the European Union starting on June 1, saying the EU has been hard to deal with on trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-recommends-50-tariff-european-union-starting-june-1-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2X5LCCWENK2JOPR35HNA5K7GU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:57:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利有多少起银行收购案？]]></title><description><![CDATA[并购浪潮正在席卷意大利银行业，在一些主要参与者之间形成了一张复杂的交易网。【原文：A wave of M&amp;A activity is sweeping through Italy's banking industry, creating a complex web of deals between some of the major players.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/how-many-bank-takeover-bids-are-happening-italy-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X72E3B6IHVJM5NHAAXY6IBWECM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:39:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普警告苹果，如果 iPhone 不是美国制造，将征收 25% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五表示，如果在美国销售的手机不是在其境内生产的，苹果公司将不得不支付 25% 的关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday Apple will have to pay a 25% tariff if phones sold in the country are not made within its borders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-pay-25-tariff-if-phones-not-made-us-trump-says-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJJMRQHWIFMNXG7VXNIBX6WZ7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗马在意大利银行并购谈判桌上的席位让投资者猜不透]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗马决心在重塑意大利金融业的过程中拥有发言权，这让投资者越来越难以预料，因为他们多年来一直在等待意大利分散的银行业格局得到整合。【原文：Rome's determination to have a say in the reshaping of Italy's financial sector has made things increasingly unpredictable for investors who have waited years for consolidation of the country's fragmented banking landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/romes-seat-italian-bank-ma-table-keeps-investors-guessing-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADJ7NG4WQ5JOLHGQFUD6H2CV5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司任命新技术主管进行研究调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一份内部备忘录显示，空中客车公司在研究其最畅销的A320neo喷气式客机的后继机型时，对设计和工程部门进行了调整，任命其南亚地区的高级管理人员担任下一任技术主管。【原文：Airbus has appointed its top executive in South Asia to be its next head of technology in a shake-up of design and engineering as it studies options for a successor to its best-selling A320neo jetliner, an internal memo showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-appoints-remi-maillard-head-technology-sources-say-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHGOSSTVVJPETJCJMGO26U6LGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:11:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，塔塔咨询服务公司就 M&S 黑客事件展开内部调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，印度塔塔咨询服务公司正在进行内部调查，以确定自己是否是英国玛莎百货公司遭受网络攻击的网关，这次攻击泄露了客户数据并扰乱了该零售商的运营。【原文：India's Tata Consultancy Services is conducting an internal investigation to determine whether it was the gateway for a cyberattack on UK's Marks and Spencer that compromised customer data and disrupted the retailer’s operations, FT reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tata-consultancy-services-carries-out-internal-probe-into-ms-hack-ft-reports-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHYNPUV3K5PKJBLYJIERFTQ57Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美元持续下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融与市场》无任所编辑 Mike Dolan 为您解读当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：A look at what matters in U.S. and global markets today from Mike Dolan, Editor-At-Large, Finance and Markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E66TWVJ7LFNYPMYKYQ554TG53U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普推动能源扩张，美国输油管道公司面临买入/建造难题]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的支持能源政策旨在加快美国下一代能源基础设施的建设，但由于一系列阻碍大型项目的因素，许多石油和天然气管道运营商仍然宁愿购买也不愿建设，以实现扩张。【原文：President Donald Trump's pro-energy policies were meant to speed the construction of the United States' next generation of energy infrastructure, but many oil and gas pipeline operators would still rather buy than build their way to expansion due to a host of factors impeding large projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-pipeline-firms-wrestle-buybuild-conundrum-trump-pushes-energy-expansion-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MN2C2FQ555IVXK4JBQHI4DZXCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：马斯克的 DOGE 在美国政府中推广其 Grok 人工智能，引发冲突担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉此事的人士表示，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的DOGE团队正在扩大其人工智能聊天机器人Grok在美国联邦政府中的使用，以分析数据，这可能违反了利益冲突法，并危及数百万美国人的敏感信息。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk’s DOGE team is expanding use of his artificial intelligence chatbot Grok in the U.S. federal government to analyze data, said three people familiar with the matter, potentially violating conflict-of-interest laws and putting at risk sensitive information on millions of Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/musks-doge-expanding-his-grok-ai-us-government-raising-conflict-concerns-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHYHHROTE5PB5MAQQ7TRUXFXLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 英伟达财报受关注，美国收益率和债务上升扰动市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[半导体巨头、人工智能风向标英伟达（Nvidia）的财报将在下周成为华尔街的焦点，而股市则因联邦赤字导致国债收益率上升的担忧而遭遇减速。【原文：An earnings report from semiconductor giant and artificial intelligence bellwether Nvidia takes center stage for Wall Street in the coming week, as stocks hit a speed bump of worries over federal deficits driving up Treasury yields.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-nvidia-earnings-focus-rising-us-yields-debt-rattle-markets-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTNSUI7KPRKITBN3XQI63TVDDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>