<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 22:34:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 22:34:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[媒体报道称，苹果和谷歌首席执行官将与科技界领袖一起出席特朗普就职典礼]]></title><description><![CDATA[据外媒周三报道，苹果公司蒂姆-库克（Tim Cook）和谷歌首席执行官桑达尔-皮查伊（Sundar Pichai）等大科技公司领导人计划出席美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周一的就职典礼。【原文：Apple's Tim Cook and Google CEO Sundar Pichai are among the Big Tech leaders planning to attend U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's inauguration on Monday, according to media reports on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/apple-google-ceos-join-tech-leaders-trump-inauguration-media-reports-say-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6JYUSFG5ZORFK4JPECTGU7GFA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 22:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，冷库房地产投资信托基金 Lineage 裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周二援引公司声明报道，冷藏房地产投资信托公司 Lineage Inc 去年在美国首次发行股票大获成功后，正在裁员。【原文：Cold storage real estate investment trust Lineage Inc is cutting staff after a blockbuster initial stock offering in the U.S. last year, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing a company statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cold-storage-reit-lineage-trims-staff-wsj-reports-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5VUO3YZ5EFJB3JOZCETIFIAJ5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 22:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片需求强劲，台积电第四季度利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾中芯国际集成电路制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co , the main global producer of advanced chips used in artificial intelligence applications, is expected to report a 58% leap in fourth-quarter profit on Thursday because of surging demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-q4-profit-set-big-leap-strong-demand-ai-chips-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7QILLW5XFK2HMX3RPH3XQ6JIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 22:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间投标全球通胀缓解缓解债券收益率阴霾]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7W4C5BEA5P7DP7UXB5FUAU5U4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:51:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》报道：特朗普考虑暂停执行 TikTok 禁令 60 至 90 天]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》周三援引两位熟悉此事的人士的话报道称，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普正在考虑发布一项行政命令，在 60 至 90 天内暂停执行 TikTok 出售或禁令法律。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump is considering an executive order that would suspend the enforcement of the TikTok sale-or-ban law for 60 to 90 days, the Washington Post reported on Wednesday, citing two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-considers-suspending-tiktok-ban-enforcement-60-90-days-washington-post-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZ3AM5K4JJKEZELJKPUHCMWEGQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜邦表示不会分离水业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[工业材料制造商杜邦公司周三表示，不再打算分离其水业务。【原文：Industrial materials maker DuPont said on Wednesday it no longer intends to separate its water business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dupont-says-it-will-not-separate-its-water-business-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XWNIYOPENKERDVLSFM53FSP2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[州监管机构对违反反洗钱规定的 Block Inc 罚款 8000 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[布洛克公司同意向 48 个州的金融监管机构支付 8000 万美元的罚款，原因是其移动支付服务 "现金应用程序 "违反了反洗钱法。【原文：Block, Inc has agreed to pay a fine of $80 million to a group of 48 state financial regulators for violations of anti-money laundering laws through its mobile payment service, Cash App.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/state-regulators-fine-block-inc-80-million-anti-money-laundering-violations-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X332IL3BKZMB5JFF7XKBO6JH7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛杉矶商会设立基金帮助受火灾影响的小企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶地区商会（Los Angeles Area Chamber of Commerce）周三宣布设立一项救济基金，用于支持和重建受过去一周肆虐洛杉矶部分地区的野火影响的小型企业。【原文：The Los Angeles Area Chamber of Commerce on Wednesday announced the creation of a relief fund to support and rebuild small businesses affected by the wildfires that have ravaged parts of Los Angeles for the past week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/la-chamber-commerce-sets-up-fund-help-blaze-affected-small-businesses-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2H754VCM3BPGZEVO4RT2EXCBHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 20:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管 CPI 推动了市场反弹，但通胀复苏仍是市场风险所在]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国消费者物价涨幅相对温和，引发股市和债券大幅松动反弹，但交易员和投资者警告说，市场可能仍对通胀速度感到焦虑。【原文：A relatively benign U.S. reading on consumer price increases triggered a sharp relief rally in stocks and bonds on Wednesday, but traders and investors warn that markets are likely to remain anxious about the pace of inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/inflation-revival-persists-market-risk-despite-cpi-fueled-rally-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDS3BQWAQZN75KVMCA22TA53A4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 20:49:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司与美国政府就艾滋病预防药物专利案达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周三向特拉华州联邦法院提交的一份文件显示，吉利德科学公司与美国政府已就吉利德公司的艾滋病预防药物特鲁瓦达（Truvada）和德科威（Descovy）价值数十亿美元的专利纠纷达成和解。【原文：Gilead Sciences and the U.S. government have settled a billion-dollar patent dispute over Gilead's HIV prevention drugs Truvada and Descovy, according to a Wednesday filing in Delaware federal court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/gilead-sciences-us-government-settle-patent-case-over-hiv-prevention-drugs-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5M3POCCCBKIJIEZBSY3X4EKWQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 20:45:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员要求美国贸易部长戴维斯停止投资者保护问题的后期谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个由两党议员组成的美国参议员团体周三呼吁美国贸易代表凯瑟琳∙戴停止与墨西哥、加拿大和哥伦比亚的 "秘密谈判"，这些谈判将在拜登政府任期的最后几天削弱美国自由贸易协定中对投资者的保护。【原文：A bipartisan group of U.S. senators on Wednesday called on U.S. Trade Representative Katherine Tai to stop "secret negotiations" with Mexico, Canada and Colombia that would weaken investor protections in some U.S. free trade deals during the Biden administration's final days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/senators-demand-us-trade-chief-tai-halt-late-talks-investor-protections-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOPQMS356FM4PMGLN5KL63I36I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 20:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就航班长期延误起诉西南航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周三起诉西南航空公司，指控该公司非法运营多个长期延误的航班，扰乱了乘客的出行。【原文：The Biden administration on Wednesday sued Southwest Airlines , accusing the carrier of illegally operating multiple chronically delayed flights and disrupting passengers’ travel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-southwest-airlines-over-chronically-delayed-flights-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDIHQIL72FMTBEKECYZQG6IKCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 20:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德雷克因肯德瑞克-拉马尔（Kendrick Lamar）的《不像我们》起诉长期合作的唱片公司 UMG 诽谤]]></title><description><![CDATA[德雷克（Drake）周三起诉了他长期合作的唱片公司，指控环球音乐集团推广肯德里克-拉马尔（Kendrick Lamar）的《不像我们》（"Not Like Us"）构成诽谤，称这首歌诬陷这位加拿大说唱歌手有恋童癖，使他和家人处于危险之中。【原文：Drake sued his longtime label on Wednesday, accusing Universal Music Group of defamation for promoting Kendrick Lamar's "Not Like Us," saying the song's false accusation that the Canadian rapper is a pedophile has put him and his family in danger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/drake-sues-longtime-label-umg-defamation-over-kendrick-lamars-not-like-us-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KW3FFO3CLBIPJAJ4KRSALYRWSY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储调查显示，美国企业持乐观态度，但仍有担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三表示，美国经济活动在11月底和12月小幅至温和增长，就业率上升，物价温和上涨，但人们对当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的政策可能产生的影响感到担忧。【原文：U.S. economic activity increased slightly to moderately in late November and December, the Federal Reserve said on Wednesday, with employment ticking up and prices rising moderately amid concerns about the potential impact of policies under President-elect Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-businesses-optimistic-flag-concerns-fed-survey-shows-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VA3AWNY32JNDZFIPAAZMG75JNQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普将终止对部分液化天然气出口许可证的延期要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普计划取消一些液化天然气（LNG）生产商申请出口许可证延期的要求。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump plans to abolish the requirement for some producers of liquefied natural gas (LNG) to seek export permit renewals, according to two sources with knowledge of the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-end-need-some-lng-export-permit-renewals-sources-say-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PF6DAZLKFRPZPLMQHQVNFLVGHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国防承包商告诉马斯克小组，五角大楼的官僚主义是问题所在]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的国防承包商之一 L3Harris Technologies 公司的首席执行官周三在一封信中告诉美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府效率小组，五角大楼庞大的承包系统过于缓慢和官僚，无法应对中国和伊朗构成的威胁，需要进行改革。【原文：The CEO of one of the world's biggest defense contractors, L3Harris Technologies, told President-elect Donald Trump's government efficiency panel in a letter on Wednesday that the Pentagon's huge contracting system is too slow and bureaucratic to meet threats posed by China and Iran and needs to be reformed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-defense-contractor-tells-musk-panel-that-pentagon-bureaucracy-is-problem-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUQ7RHNUDRI2TJGZP4XAXKS4T4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:53:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[殖民地管道公司的美国汽油大动脉可能关闭至周五]]></title><description><![CDATA[Colonial 管道公司在周三的一份声明中表示，由于该公司继续在佐治亚州保定县寻找疑似泄漏源，其美国汽油主干道预计将关闭至周五。【原文：Colonial Pipeline's main U.S. gasoline artery is expected to be shut through Friday as the company continues to search for the source of a suspected leak in Paulding County, Georgia, the company said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/colonial-pipelines-main-us-gasoline-artery-likely-shut-until-friday-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRNW5FRDOFJV3E22KGJXW4E42A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名的美国交通部官员称将继续调查特斯拉安全问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的交通部负责人表示，他将允许政府继续对特斯拉的高级驾驶辅助系统进行调查。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's nominee to head the Transportation Department said he would allow an ongoing government probe into Tesla's advanced driver assistance system to continue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trump-usdot-nominee-says-tesla-safety-probe-will-continue-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DN3DDFMUCBPJPCPBHX2UBU3ML4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[注释 BOX 投资者对加沙停火协议的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位了解谈判情况的官员说，谈判代表周三达成了一项分阶段协议，以结束以色列和哈马斯之间的加沙战争，在此之前，15 个月的冲突已造成数万巴勒斯坦人死亡，并激化了中东局势。【原文：Negotiators reached a phased deal on Wednesday to end the war in Gaza between Israel and Hamas, an official briefed on the negotiations said, after 15 months of conflict that has killed tens of thousands of Palestinians and inflamed the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/quote-box-investor-reactions-gaza-ceasefire-deal-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEXIXQV6RFNKXMDBJW3VLN57EQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国经济持续疲软，奢侈品集团寄希望于美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于预计中国市场将更加疲软，全球奢侈品公司今年将使出浑身解数，说服美国购物者在钻石手镯、绗缝皮手袋和其他名牌时装上挥金如土。【原文：Global luxury goods companies are expected to pull out all the stops this year to persuade U.S. shoppers to splash out on diamond bracelets, quilted leather handbags and other designer fashions, given forecasts for more market weakness in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/luxury-groups-pin-hopes-us-china-weakness-persists-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7XF7BCTANI4RCLBTAWD4QJKDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:45:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州公用事业公司面临数十亿美元的火灾损失索赔，即使它没有做错任何事]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶野火可能是美国历史上损失最惨重的一场大火，这场大火的受害者正在利用加州独特的法律原则，如果电力公司的设备导致了大火，即使电力公司没有做错任何事，他们也可以向电力公司索赔。【原文：Victims of the Los Angeles wildfires, likely the costliest in U.S. history, are seizing upon a unique California legal doctrine that allows them to collect from their power utility if its equipment caused the blaze -- even if the company did nothing wrong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/california-utility-faces-billions-claims-fire-damage-even-if-it-did-nothing-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYB5L2AIJFMDNNRI6BXQXLATCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:23:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田旗下日野汽车公司被控柴油排放造假]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车旗下日野汽车公司周三在底特律美国地区法院被指控欺诈，罪名是在美国非法销售 10.5 万台不符合排放标准的重型柴油发动机。【原文：Toyota Motor unit Hino Motors on Wednesday was charged with fraud in U.S. District Court in Detroit for unlawfully selling 105,000 heavy-duty diesel engines in the United States that did not meet emissions standards.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/toyota-unit-hino-motors-charged-with-diesel-emissions-fraud-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KX5OY7ZG6RMCBKOKMN4RZNTVSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车首席财务官：削减成本协议之后，生产率必须提高]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三看到，大众汽车首席财务官在向投资者发表的评论中说，要使其德国工厂具有竞争力，下一步就是要提高生产率，增加每个工人生产的汽车数量。【原文：Volkswagen's chief financial officer said in comments to investors seen by Reuters on Wednesday that the next step to making its German plants competitive was to improve productivity, increasing the number of cars produced per worker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-cfo-after-cost-cutting-deal-productivity-must-go-up-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELPIFA65VFLZ5NNR7QZ5Y2DCPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英格兰银行泰勒称是时候降息了]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行最近任命的利率制定者艾伦-泰勒（Alan Taylor）周三表示，鉴于英国经济出现放缓迹象，英国央行应迅速采取行动降低利率。【原文：The Bank of England should move quickly to bring down interest rates given signs of a slowdown in Britain's economy, Alan Taylor, the BoE's most recently appointed interest rate setter, said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-englands-taylor-says-its-time-cut-interest-rates-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKTERES5IJOW5P5M3ORT266SEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易强劲，交易反弹，华尔街银行利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着交易量的回升以及股市走强对交易的提振，一些美国最大的贷款机构第四季度的利润出现增长，从而引发了周三银行股的反弹。【原文：Profits at some of the biggest U.S. lenders rose in the fourth quarter as dealmaking picked up and trading was boosted by strong equity markets, sparking a rally in banking stocks on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wrapup-profits-wall-street-banks-jump-with-trading-strength-dealmaking-rebound-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJM7O5DOAZKLFCCOIGEE2OEIWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官称欧洲两大战斗机项目可能合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官纪尧姆-福里（Guillaume Faury）说，他可以预见，这两个独立的欧洲新型战斗机和作战航空系统项目将来会合并，或至少在设计上可以协同工作。【原文：Airbus CEO Guillaume Faury said he could see the two separate European programmes working on new fighter jets and combat air systems being combined in future or at least designed to work together.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-ceo-says-europes-two-fighter-jet-programmes-could-combine-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AU4MPCBO3RK7FHKM3PNFF722EQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛首席执行官称苹果卡合作可能在 2030 年前结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团首席执行官大卫-所罗门（David Solomon）周三表示，高盛与苹果公司的信用卡合作关系可能会在 2030 年合同到期前终止。【原文：Goldman Sachs' credit-card partnership with Apple may end before its contract runs out in 2030, Goldman CEO David Solomon said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-ceo-says-apple-card-partnership-may-end-before-2030-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWVU3TGWBRIAHAWWIPNCGIJNKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储威廉姆斯称政策数据取决于非常不确定的环境]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周三表示，未来的货币政策行动将由经济数据驱动，因为该央行面临着很大程度上由政府潜在政策变化所导致的高度不确定性。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams said Wednesday that future monetary policy actions will be driven by economic data as the central bank confronts a high level of uncertainty in large part driven by potential government policy changes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-williams-says-policy-data-dependent-very-uncertain-environment-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWWUEDIXAVJVXAIXQYRE2ISSZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名人称电动汽车应付费使用道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的美国交通部部长人选周三表示，电动汽车使用道路应付费。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's nominee to head the U.S. Transportation Department said Wednesday electric vehicles should pay to use roads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-nominee-says-electric-vehicles-should-pay-use-roads-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKUKG7SF5RN4JLS5KTTHEWOTOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会就设备维修限制起诉迪尔公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周三起诉农用设备制造商迪尔（Deere），称其迫使农民依赖其授权经销商网络，从而非法抬高了维修成本。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Wednesday sued farm equipment maker Deere , alleging it illegally drives up repair costs by forcing farmers to rely on its authorized dealer network.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-ftc-sues-deere-over-equipment-repair-restrictions-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5RRRZRL4BJRTE4GBRUMW72MAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>