<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 07:26:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 07:26:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[软银旗下 Arm 计划在韩国建立芯片设计工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统政策顾问周五表示，韩国工业部和软银的芯片部门 Arm Holdings 已经签署了一项协议，以加强韩国的半导体和人工智能行业。【原文：South Korea's industry ministry and SoftBank's chip unit, Arm Holdings, have signed an agreement to strengthen the country's semiconductor and Artificial Intelligence sectors, a presidential policy adviser said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbanks-arm-plans-set-up-chip-design-facility-south-korea-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCVOQG6ZNBNG3LMEO5UFT3H2YA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 07:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾反对党称禁用中国红记应用程序是审查制度]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾反对党领导人周五谴责政府暂停中国社交媒体平台红笔记访问一年的计划是审查制度，而台湾总统府则支持这一计划。【原文：Taiwan's opposition leader decried as censorship on Friday a government plan to suspend access for a year to Chinese social media platform Rednote, while the island's presidential office backed the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/taiwan-opposition-says-ban-chinas-rednote-app-is-censorship-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MBUXKI36JNVVAVMKUNCJ6ZKGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 07:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，Visa 将把欧洲总部迁至伦敦金丝雀码头]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周五报道，Visa 正在将其欧洲总部迁往伦敦金丝雀码头。【原文：Visa is moving its European headquarters to London's Canary Wharf, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/visa-is-moving-its-european-headquarters-londons-canary-wharf-ft-says-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NROOAHK625NP7G22XBZ7VGUM6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宜家将在关税影响下加强美国生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[宜家家居计划从美国工厂采购更多产品，这家瑞典家具集团的供应链高管告诉路透社记者，因为唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税导致进口书柜、床垫和沙发的成本上升。【原文：IKEA plans to source more products from factories in the United States, the Swedish furniture group's top supply chain executive told Reuters, as President Donald Trump's tariffs drive up the cost of importing bookcases, mattresses and sofas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ikea-ramp-up-us-production-tariffs-bite-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRUH74UIPBKTFASOX7VBASO67Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:05:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：坚定的美联储减息押注提振股市，打压美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXYESCSDD5OGRJWU3ULSE3RGFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:33:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其 Paribu 公司收购巴林 CoinMENA 公司多数股权，估值高达 2.4 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其数字资产平台 Paribu 周五表示，它收购了总部位于巴林和迪拜的加密货币平台 CoinMENA 的多数股权，交易估值高达 2.4 亿美元。【原文：Turkish digital asset platform Paribu said on Friday it acquired a majority stake in the Bahrain and Dubai-based cryptocurrency platform CoinMENA in a transaction valuing the company at up to $240 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/turkeys-paribu-buys-majority-stake-bahrains-coinmena-valuing-it-at-up-to-240-mln-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67H3IQ2CUNNYZLDEAW6DJY2LK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥普拉-温弗瑞称赞澳大利亚的儿童社交媒体禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国脱口秀主持人奥普拉-温弗瑞（Oprah Winfrey）对澳大利亚从下周起禁止 16 岁以下青少年使用社交媒体的决定表示赞赏，称此举将有助于青少年加强社交。【原文：American talk show host Oprah Winfrey has praised Australia's decision to ban social media for under-16s from next week, saying the move would help young people socialise more.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/oprah-winfrey-praises-australias-social-media-ban-children-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCR25J3KAFNUDAGZBK7VDY3ZSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，估值近 30 亿美元的百度昆仑万维有意在香港上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，中国互联网搜索巨头百度旗下的人工智能芯片部门昆仑万维正计划在香港进行首次公开募股，该公司最近完成了一次融资，估值为210亿元人民币（约合29.7亿美元）。【原文：Kunlunxin, the AI chip unit of Chinese internet search giant Baidu , is planning an initial public offering in Hong Kong, having recently completed a fundraising that valued it at 21 billion yuan ($2.97 billion), three people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/baidus-kunlunxin-valued-close-3-billion-eyes-hong-kong-ipo-sources-say-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EW44XZ4SJNOW7C7XUZG6Z32SRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:42:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国11月出口有望因美国关税休战而反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于制造商急于转移库存，以利用与美国达成的新关税休战协议，中国的出口在 10 月份意外下滑后，很可能在 11 月份恢复增长。【原文：China's exports likely returned to growth in November after an unexpected dip in October, as manufacturers rushed to move inventory to take advantage of a fresh tariff truce with the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-november-exports-expected-have-rebounded-off-us-tariff-truce-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYFU27DHSBI3BDMOIWRLBLB234</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社记者称，Netflix 就收购华纳兄弟发现工作室和流媒体服务展开独家谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社的一名记者在 X 日的一篇文章中称，Netflix 已与华纳兄弟发现公司进行独家谈判，以收购其工作室和流媒体服务。【原文：Netflix has entered exclusive talks with Warner Bros Discovery to acquire its studio and streaming service, a Bloomberg News reporter said in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-enters-exclusive-talks-acquire-warner-bros-discovery-studio-streaming-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSG4GKQ5WJI45DGHJAO62BO6VA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 03:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Variety 报道，电影制片人游说国会反对 Netflix-Warner Bros Discovery 收购案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《综艺》杂志周四报道，一个由电影业领军人物组成的财团敦促美国国会进行干预，并警告说如果 Netflix 成功收购华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery），好莱坞将面临一场迫在眉睫的经济和体制危机。【原文：A consortium of leading film industry figures has urged the U.S. Congress to intervene, warning of a looming economic and institutional crisis in Hollywood if Netflix succeeds in acquiring Warner Bros Discovery , Variety reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/film-producers-lobby-congress-against-netflix-warner-bros-discovery-acquisition-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E47QNUFT6FNA7CKKKGLL4AR3QQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 03:05:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社调查：英国央行将于 12 月按兵不动，前景转向长期持有至 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，澳大利亚储备银行周二将把现金利率维持在 3.60% 的水平，并一直维持到 2026 年。【原文：The Reserve Bank of Australia will hold its cash rate at 3.60% on Tuesday and keep it there through 2026, according to a Reuters poll, a shift from last month when a majority of economists expected at least one rate cut next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rba-hold-december-outlook-shifts-long-hold-through-2026-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUWUDVHW6ZMH7KYB52IZIBET6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 02:33:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市低迷，日本股市日经指数下滑，加息押注增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日本股市日经指数（Nikkei）大幅下挫，抹去了本周的涨幅，而亚洲股市则表现低迷。此前，由于市场对日本央行将加息的押注增加，支出数据弱于预期，凸显了通胀的祸害。【原文：Japan's Nikkei skidded on Friday, wiping out this week's gains amid an otherwise subdued Asian session, after weaker-than-expected spending data underscored the scourge of inflation as bets grew that the Bank of Japan would hike interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCZ7C3VOY5PHNMV2Z6XICLBHZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 02:30:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LG Elec 称微软和 LG 附属公司正在寻求数据中心方面的合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国 LG 电子公司周五表示，微软和 LG 附属公司正在寻求有关数据中心的整体业务合作，但目前尚未签署具体协议。【原文：South Korea's LG Electronics Inc said on Friday that Microsoft and LG affiliates are pursuing overall business cooperation regarding data centres, but no specific deal has been signed at this time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/lg-elec-says-microsoft-lg-affiliates-pursuing-cooperation-data-centres-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWLHHO53MJKWFDSMVIRIKKQBIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 01:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储希望提振市场，委内瑞拉紧张局势迫在眉睫，油价有望实现 2% 的周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五早盘，受美联储降息预期、美国与委内瑞拉紧张局势升级以及莫斯科和谈停滞等因素的支撑，WTI油价周涨幅接近2%。【原文：WTI oil prices were heading for weekly gains of close to 2% in early trading on Friday, supported by an expected Federal Reserve interest rate cut, escalating U.S.-Venezuela tensions and stalled peace talks in Moscow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-head-2-weekly-gain-fed-hopes-boost-market-venezuela-tensions-loom-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5O3OEWTRM5MRBH2MSZPPSJ6F3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 01:25:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国类似于英伟达的摩尔语丝公司 11 亿美元首次公开募股后首日交易大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[被分析师称为 "中国的英伟达 "的摩尔芯线科技股份有限公司周五在上海上市时股价飙升，因为市场押注这家被美国列入黑名单的初创公司将受益于中国政府推动国内芯片制造的举措。【原文：Shares of Moore Threads Technology Co , dubbed by analysts as "China's Nvidia", soared on debut in Shanghai on Friday, on bets the U.S.-blacklisted startup will benefit from Beijing's drive to boost domestic chip manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-nvidia-like-moore-threads-set-trading-debut-after-11-billion-ipo-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QIMBT7Z45JTNKXFX2MW3BFHIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 01:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙运营的戈尔贡项目获得 20 亿美元投资点头同意]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油巨头雪佛龙公司（Chevron Corp）的澳大利亚分公司周五表示，Gorgon 合资企业的合作伙伴已就西澳大利亚西北海岸外的 Gorgon 第三阶段开发项目做出了最终投资决定，该项目耗资 30 亿澳元（19.8 亿美元）。【原文：The Australian unit of U.S. oil giant Chevron Corp said on Friday that the partners of the Gorgon Joint Venture have made a final investment decision on the A$3 billion ($1.98 billion) Gorgon Stage 3 development off Western Australia's northwest coast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-operated-gorgon-project-secures-2-billion-investment-nod-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BO2TLFJ4IVJVTOIDU5JLCCRPE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 01:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美联储降息押注影响，美元徘徊在五周低点附近]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于投资者对美联储下周降息做好了准备，美元兑主要同业货币在距离五周低点不远处徘徊。【原文：The U.S. dollar languished not far from a five-week low against its major peers on Friday as investors braced for a Federal Reserve rate cut next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-hovers-near-five-week-low-fed-rate-cut-bets-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWYZ6CA6RZN53IYN5ILMTQL2AY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司 Cohere 首席执行官称美国在人工智能竞赛中比中国更有优势]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大科技初创公司Cohere的首席执行官艾丹-戈麦斯（Aidan Gomez）周四表示，美国和加拿大在与全球采用人工智能的经济体合作方面拥有 "令人难以置信的地位"，这使两国在全球人工智能竞赛中领先于中国。【原文：Canadian tech startup Cohere's CEO Aidan Gomez said on Thursday the U.S. and Canada hold an "incredible position" to partner with economies adopting AI around the world, putting the countries in the lead against China in the global AI race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ai-startup-cohere-ceo-says-us-holds-edge-over-china-ai-race-2025-12-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6L7VGEEBVNJMDJO2XULKUKADXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 10 月家庭支出创近两年最快降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周五公布的数据显示，10月份日本家庭支出出人意料地出现了近两年来最快的下滑，这引发了人们对经济前景的担忧，因为日本央行正在为最早于本月加息做准备。【原文：Japanese household spending unexpectedly slumped at the fastest pace in nearly two years in October, government data showed Friday, raising concerns about the economic outlook as the Bank of Japan gears up for a rate hike as early as this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-october-household-spending-unexpectedly-falls-30-yearyear-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEE67S57Z5KOLO6JVBJQWSDSX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:47:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局选派佩拉顿监督空中交通管制改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周四表示，已选定 Veritas Capital 旗下的国家安全公司 Peraton 作为项目经理，负责耗资 125 亿美元对老化的美国空中交通管制系统进行大修。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said on Thursday it has picked Peraton, a national security company owned by Veritas Capital, as the project manager of a $12.5-billion effort to overhaul the aging U.S. air traffic control system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-faa-picks-peraton-oversee-air-traffic-control-reform-effort-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6NVNGYDLVNK3BXCQQYDMI7EZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:41:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司将重启花岗岩城高炉以满足客户需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）周四表示，在客户需求的推动下，该公司已开始重启花岗岩城工厂两座高炉中的一座。【原文：U.S. Steel said on Thursday it has begun the process to restart operations in one of two blast furnaces at Granite City Works, driven by customer demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-steel-restart-granite-citys-blast-furnace-support-customer-demand-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEFRW3C5LFILDAPGRMY2PQBBYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表格里尔：美国对华贸易规模可能需要缩小]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周四表示，美国与中国的贸易需要平衡，而且可能需要缩小规模，并补充说，他认为与中国的货物贸易额下降 25% 是朝着 "正确的方向 "前进。【原文：U.S. trade with China needs to be balanced and probably needs to be smaller, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Thursday, adding that he viewed a 25% drop in goods trade with China as heading in the "right direction."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-trade-with-china-probably-needs-be-smaller-ustrs-greer-says-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3AC6SR3SRIMFIGPU2WROH6P4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表表示：加拿大和墨西哥不应成为中国的出口中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周四表示，加拿大和墨西哥不应被用作中国、越南、印度尼西亚和其他国家的出口中心，并称墨西哥在某些情况下已经出现了这种情况。【原文：Canada and Mexico should not be used as export hubs for China, Vietnam, Indonesia and other countries, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Thursday, saying that this was already happening in some cases in Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-mexico-should-not-be-export-hubs-china-says-ustr-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TS7X6KILSBKSPO2XNVK2ODWPVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司在高管变动中任命 Meta 公司的纽斯特德为总法律顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四宣布，Meta Platforms 的首席法务官珍妮弗-纽斯特德（Jennifer Newstead）将加入公司，担任总法律顾问兼高级副总裁。【原文：Apple on Thursday announced that Meta Platforms' chief legal officer, Jennifer Newstead, will join the company as its general counsel and senior vice president.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-appoints-metas-newstead-general-counsel-amid-executive-changes-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUJCPO4LMNJR3BU6ELZRQQALOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:35:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国大豆转向美国之前，巴西 11 月大豆出口猛增 64]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西政府周四称，11月份巴西大豆出口量同比增长64%，达到420万吨。【原文：Brazil's soybean exports jumped 64% in November from a year ago to 4.2 million metric tons, the government said on Thursday, with good local supply allowing elevated shipments before the world's largest importer China shifts to United States' beans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/brazil-soy-exports-jump-64-november-ahead-chinese-shift-us-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3QGL5HBPZMQTHKFTW7Z5BCASI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:21:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[- 路透社 NEXT 会议上科技、人工智能领域发言人的精彩发言]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社将于本周三和周四在纽约举办为期两天的路透 NEXT 会议，700 多位国际商界领袖和政策制定者将齐聚一堂，共同探讨社会、商业和世界面临的最大问题。以下是会议技术和人工智能分会上发言人的一些精彩发言。【原文：Reuters is hosting a two-day Reuters NEXT conference in New York on Wednesday and Thursday, bringing together more than 700 international business leaders and policymakers to examine the biggest issues facing society, business and the world. The following are some notable quotes from speakers at the technology and AI sessions of the conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/notable-quotes-tech-ai-sector-speakers-reuters-next-conference-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DY7NRQJO5JMZXLT3XCK6XJAU74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和加拿大称与中国有联系的黑客利用后门进行潜在 "破坏活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和加拿大网络安全机构周四表示，与中国有关联的黑客利用复杂的恶意软件渗透并长期访问未具名的政府和信息技术实体。【原文：Chinese-linked hackers used sophisticated malware to penetrate and maintain long-term access to unnamed government and information technology entities, U.S. and Canadian cybersecurity agencies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-linked-hackers-use-back-door-potential-sabotage-us-canada-say-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAASVGLJTJL6JELDTUEATYWKLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 索偿令美联储前景扑朔迷离]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，华尔街三大股指变化不大，美元和国债收益率上涨，此前美国劳动力市场指标出人意料地强劲，令人质疑美联储明年的降息幅度。【原文：Wall Street's big three indices were little changed on Thursday, while the dollar and Treasury yields rose, after a surprisingly strong U.S. labor market indicator called into question how much lower the Fed will cut interest rates next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZDFTXHIWBJPNI7L4D26ZUZ25I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 因化妆品需求而上调年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 周四上调了年度销售额和利润预期，寄希望于节假日期间化妆品和护肤品的强劲需求。【原文：Ulta Beauty raised its annual sales and profit forecast on Thursday, betting on strong demand for its makeup and skincare products going into the holiday season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ulta-beauty-lifts-annual-forecasts-demand-cosmetics-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHDD5D5655N7VN7RNABWNTBM3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:57:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>