<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:09:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:09:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[参议院小组委员会将就Netflix与华纳兄弟拟议交易举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院司法委员会周二表示，其反垄断小组委员会将于下周就奈飞与华纳兄弟拟议的合并案举行听证会。【原文：The U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee said on Tuesday that its antitrust subcommittee will hold a hearing next week on a proposed tie-up between Netflix and Warner Brothers .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/senate-subcommittee-hold-hearing-proposed-netflix-warner-bros-deal-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JDW7VHJG5PB7LRT77OH7XAGJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:28:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关键预测市场押注黑石集团的里德尔成为下一任美联储主席的赔率颇高]]></title><description><![CDATA[预测市场Kalshi的数据显示，贝莱德首席债券投资经理里克·里德尔已成为接替现任美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的热门人选，后者任期即将届满。【原文：BlackRock's chief bond investment manager Rick Rieder is now the clear favorite to succeed current Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell when his term is up, according to prediction market Kalshi.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/key-prediction-market-putting-strong-odds-blackrocks-rieder-next-fed-chair-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWH4CL7CGZKILG67VRGFQLNLGQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:15:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭记录显示，壳牌公司与Venture Global的法律纠纷焦点在于与工程师的沟通记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[壳牌公司对液化天然气生产商Venture Global胜诉的仲裁结果提出质疑，其核心争议点在于美国企业与独立工程公司Lummus Consultants之间可能存在的沟通往来。路透社获得的法庭听证会记录草案显示了这一情况。【原文：Shell's challenge to its arbitration defeat to liquefied natural gas producer Venture Global centres on potential communications between the U.S. firm and independent engineer Lummus Consultants, a draft court hearing transcript seen by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/shells-legal-fight-against-venture-global-focuses-communication-with-engineer-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5AQMK5ZZVJ3HF33LMBTN6IMYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭文件指控Meta首席执行官扎克伯格阻挠了针对未成年人性话题聊天机器人的限制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据新墨西哥州法院案件中提交并于周一公开的Meta内部文件显示，该公司首席执行官马克·扎克伯格批准允许未成年人使用AI聊天机器人伴侣，尽管安全团队曾警告这些机器人具备进行性互动的能力。【原文：Meta Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg approved allowing minors to access AI chatbot companions that safety staffers warned were capable of sexual interactions, according to internal Meta documents filed in a New Mexico state court case and made public Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/meta-ceo-zuckerberg-blocked-curbs-sex-talking-chatbots-minors-court-filing-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTHRGFFDLZLBZJO4NB5SF2DWMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:59:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称雪佛龙要求伊拉克改善条款后再接管卢克石油油田]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名知情人士透露，美国石油巨头雪佛龙正敦促伊拉克提高西古尔纳2号油田的回报率，作为从俄罗斯卢克石油公司收购该项目的条件。【原文：U.S. oil major Chevron is pushing Iraq to improve returns on the giant West Qurna 2 oil field as a condition for buying the project from Russia's Lukoil , three sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-seeks-better-terms-iraq-before-taking-over-lukoil-oilfield-sources-say-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHFRN5MBABPFDK72RVSCKOCUCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场动态：华尔街押注下任美联储主席将挺身对抗特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普上周对任命下一任美联储主席一事表示遗憾：他说问题在于，这些人一旦上任就会改变立场。华尔街正指望这一点。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump bemoaned last week his issue with naming the next Federal Reserve chair: The problem, he said, is they change once they have the job. Wall Street is counting on it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/market-wall-streets-banking-next-fed-chair-stand-up-trump-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7LQT4O7HJLE5PPA4XSRCYF3LY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称美国将很快颁布通用许可证，解除对委内瑞拉石油行业部分制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名知情人士周二透露，美国官员正着手尽快颁布一项通用许可证，以解除对委内瑞拉能源领域的部分制裁。此举改变了此前为寻求在该国开展业务的企业提供个别制裁豁免的计划。【原文：U.S. officials are working to issue a general license soon that would lift some sanctions on Venezuela's energy sector, three sources familiar with the preparation said on Tuesday, a shift from a previous plan to grant individual exemptions to sanctions for companies seeking to do business in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-issue-general-license-soon-lifting-some-sanctions-venezuelan-oil-industry-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLS3OICDARMB7BOGC6FIH7HZN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟官员称Shein可能面临欧盟调查，但不会采取临时措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会一位高级官员周二表示，中国快时尚电商平台Shein可能因平台销售非法产品面临欧盟调查，但不太可能被勒令暂停运营。【原文：Chinese fast-fashion online retailer Shein could face an EU investigation on the sale of illegal products on its platform, but is unlikely to be hit with an order to suspend its website, a senior European Commission official said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/shein-could-face-eu-investigation-no-interim-measure-commission-official-says-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2C5CUZ6PZOKBFYXHWPHOOJXKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:41:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉原油回归或将削减美国燃料油进口]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着炼油商大量采购新到港的委内瑞拉重质原油，今年美国对进口燃料油的需求将出现下滑。这些原油可生产出更多国产燃料油，进而加工成汽油和柴油等高附加值产品。【原文：U.S. demand for imported fuel oil is set to fall this year as refiners snap up new flows of heavy Venezuelan crude, yielding more domestically produced fuel oil that can be processed into higher-value products such as gasoline and diesel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/return-venezuelan-crude-could-cut-us-fuel-oil-imports-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KD3BCR6FW5KGHKYKKQM7VIWG44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Revolut在墨西哥启动全面银行业务，实现首次欧洲以外扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融科技公司Revolut周二宣布，已在墨西哥正式开展全面银行业务，标志着该公司在欧洲以外地区设立的首家银行正式运营。随着Revolut加速向高增长市场扩张，其全球业务版图持续扩大。【原文：Britain's Revolut said on Tuesday that it has officially launched full banking operations in Mexico, marking its first bank established outside of Europe as the fintech accelerates its expansion into high-growth markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/revolut-launches-full-banking-operations-mexico-first-expansion-outside-europe-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKPMOZ7WERMFZC3CJWXJ2E5UBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[渣打银行警告称，到2028年，美国银行可能因稳定币损失5000亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周二预测，以美元为支撑的加密货币代币（即稳定币）可能在2028年底前从美国银行体系抽走约5000亿美元存款。这项新分析或将加剧银行与加密货币公司之间围绕数字资产行业监管立法的博弈。【原文：U.S. dollar-backed crypto tokens ​known as stablecoins could pull around $500 billion in deposits out of U.S. banks by ‌the end of 2028, Standard Chartered estimated on Tuesday - new analysis that could intensify a fight between banks and crypto companies over legislation to set rules for the digital asset sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-banks-may-lose-500-billion-stablecoins-by-2028-standard-chartered-warns-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36V3A6PBJJJPVLQ25PNBTS7MVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究人员称，2025年加密货币洗钱规模达820亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[区块链研究人员周二表示，去年洗钱者收到的加密货币至少达820亿美元，较2020年的100亿美元大幅增长，部分原因在于中文区块链群体的快速扩张。【原文：Money launderers received at least $82 billion in cryptocurrencies last year, up sharply from $10 billion in 2020, driven in part by fast ​growth among Chinese-speaking groups, blockchain researchers said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/crypto-money-laundering-hit-82-billion-2025-researchers-say-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKCPVGTXQZLOBB2WEHD6PJOAYI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团任命新领导层，侧重企业银行业务，备忘录显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周二宣布对其企业与投资银行业务部门进行一系列领导层调整，首席执行官简·弗雷泽正加大力度提升该行在华尔街竞争对手中的竞争力。【原文：Citigroup on Tuesday announced a series of leadership changes across its corporate and investment banking divisions as CEO Jane Fraser steps up efforts to sharpen the bank's competitiveness against Wall Street rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-names-new-leaders-with-corporate-banking-focus-memo-shows-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRL2QQ2YXFLD3EYDBO2VRBLCTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:57:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路威酩轩第四季度销售额超预期，得益于中国市场回暖]]></title><description><![CDATA[路易威登和蒂芙尼的母公司LVMH集团第四季度销售额超出分析师预期，提振了奢侈品行业复苏的希望。尽管贸易紧张局势、美元走弱和黄金价格高企对其利润率造成冲击。【原文：LVMH , the owner of Louis Vuitton and Tiffany, sold more goods than analysts expected in the fourth quarter, boosting hopes of a luxury sector rebound even as trade tensions, a weaker dollar and high gold prices hit its margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/lvmh-fourth-quarter-sales-beat-expectations-china-improves-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZ75Z75EYVK3DPSOOUL5YSW7S4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok在庭审前达成社交媒体成瘾诉讼和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[据原告律师透露，TikTok周二同意就一起社交媒体成瘾诉讼达成和解。【原文：Tiktok agreed to settle a social media addiction lawsuit on Tuesday, according to one of the plaintiff's lawyers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/tiktok-settles-social-media-addiction-lawsuit-ahead-trial-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YD5NTXAHTBI5HJXBFN2WB3PTO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联邦银行重组领导层以强化财富管理业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国历史最悠久的银行花旗集团周二宣布，已委派内部人士亚当·沃斯负责监督加强其财富管理和托管账户业务的举措。【原文：BNY has tasked insider Adam Vos to oversee the push to strengthen its wealth and managed accounts offerings, the oldest U.S. bank said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-rejigs-leadership-strengthen-wealth-management-push-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIF23SALZRNY7MUUFMEYR2VNWA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗珀公司预测2026年营收与利润将低于预期，因政府合同需求疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗珀科技公司周二公布的2026年营收和利润预测低于华尔街预期，称其政府承包部门德尔泰克的需求疲软，导致该公司股价下跌14.9%。【原文：Roper Technologies forecast 2026 revenue and profit below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, citing softer demand ​at its government contracting unit Deltek, sending ‌shares of the company down 14.9%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/roper-forecasts-2026-revenue-profit-below-estimates-soft-government-contract-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63BRQFIUOJIBFOVNQMWVCWCLF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanda Research称美国散户投资者购买白银ETF的速度快于科技股]]></title><description><![CDATA[范达研究公司表示，美国股市中散户对白银的投资热情未见减弱迹象，当前资金流入量已与热门科技股交易不相上下。【原文：Retail traders' appetite for silver shows no sign of slowing in the U.S. stock market, with flows now rivaling ​popular technology trades, Vanda Research said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/us-retail-traders-buy-silver-etfs-faster-than-tech-favorites-vanda-research-says-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RF3QTIRRJJOWTJSRAGWAV3QXQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者信心指数1月骤降，跌至2014年以来的最低水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项调查周二显示，美国消费者信心指数1月份意外恶化，跌至2014年以来最低水平，原因是人们对高物价和疲软劳动力市场的担忧日益加剧。【原文：U.S. consumer confidence unexpectedly deteriorated in January, slumping ​to its lowest level ‌since 2014, amid growing anxiety over high prices and a sluggish labor market, a survey ‌showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-confidence-slumps-january-level-last-seen-2014-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3M67S65SHBKKVKU3GJU5BWTONU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列风投公司称金融科技行业将在2026年持续复苏]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列科技投资集团Viola Ventures周二在一份报告中指出，全球金融科技行业将在2025年从三年低迷中强劲复苏后，于2026年继续走向成熟。【原文：The global financial technology sector will continue to mature in 2026 after recovering sharply in 2025 from a three-year downturn, Israeli technology investment group Viola Ventures said in a report on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/fintech-sector-continue-recovery-2026-israeli-venture-firm-says-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHRIJQHH4ZJXNHMCXANDWLN6W4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:10:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊将扩大当日达服务，并在全食超市扩张计划中关闭部分门店]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周二表示，今年将把当日达服务扩展至更多城市，同时关闭部分亚马逊Go和亚马逊生鲜实体店，将其改造为全食超市门店。【原文：Amazon said on Tuesday it would expand its same-day delivery service to more cities this year while closing some of its Amazon Go and Amazon Fresh physical locations to convert them into Whole Foods super market stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-expand-same-day-delivery-close-some-stores-whole-foods-expansion-push-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VLF6DWRJRJA7NMTGPFBMC4VFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WhatsApp推出高安全模式，成为最新一家为用户提供更强保护的技术公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta旗下的WhatsApp即时通讯服务正向用户提供高级安全模式，加入了越来越多允许用户选择更强保护以抵御黑客攻击的美国科技公司行列——尽管这会带来更受限制的使用体验。【原文：Meta's WhatsApp messaging service is offering users an advanced security mode, joining a growing number of U.S. tech firms that are letting users opt into stronger protections against hackers in exchange for a more restrictive experience.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/whatsapp-unveils-high-security-mode-latest-tech-firm-offer-users-stronger-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52PTD4ZLERIS7NPLZGS3DHWQSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦住房金融局称11月独栋住宅价格大幅上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国单户住宅价格在11月加速上涨，加之高企的抵押贷款利率，可能使潜在购房者继续观望，即便特朗普政府正采取措施解决住房可负担性问题。【原文：U.S. single-family house prices accelerated in November, which combined with high mortgage rates could keep potential homeowners on the sidelines even as the Trump administration takes steps to ​address the issue of housing affordability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-single-family-home-prices-jump-november-fhfa-says-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PRXOX5V3VMC7N6WV46OP4QIJQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloudflare股价飙升，病毒式传播的人工智能代理概念推高市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二盘前交易中，Cloudflare股价飙升约14%，因社交媒体上围绕"Clawdbot"人工智能代理的热议，重新点燃了投资者对该公司技术运营工具的热情。【原文：Cloudflare shares surged about 14% premarket on Tuesday as social media buzz around the "Clawdbot" AI agent rekindled investor ​enthusiasm for the company's tools that help run ‌the technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cloudflare-surges-viral-ai-agent-buzz-lifts-expectations-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPFXKWKCPRLPXOWJOEASXYBQFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《大空头》投资人巴里押注GameStop的五大启示]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克尔·伯里披露了其在电子游戏零售商GameStop的持仓，同时淡化了再次出现重大逼空行情的可能性，并将该公司首席执行官瑞安·科恩比作传奇投资者沃伦·巴菲特。【原文：Michael Burry has disclosed a position in videogame retailer GameStop , playing down the odds of another major short squeeze and likening its CEO, Ryan Cohen, to legendary investor Warren Buffett.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/five-takeaways-big-short-investor-burrys-gamestop-bet-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHCZ56SLMRM6XCX26F4KREXW3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[食品分销商赛斯高上调年度利润预期，因美国业务表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[食品分销商赛斯科周二上调了年度利润预期，其第二季度利润和销售额均超出市场预期。由于对牛排、鱼片和冷冻食品的强劲需求，该公司美国业务持续复苏。【原文：Food distributor Sysco lifted its annual profit forecast and beat estimates for both second-quarter profit and sales on Tuesday, as strong demand for its steaks, fillets and frozen-food products helped the company's U.S. business continue its recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/food-distributor-sysco-lifts-annual-profit-forecast-robust-us-business-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7JZ6DF36VO25EGHEYARCXRKRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UPS首席财务官称，2026年将裁减多达3万个运营岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合包裹服务公司首席财务官布莱恩·戴克斯在财报电话会议上表示，该公司计划在2026年前裁减多达3万个运营岗位。【原文：United Parcel Service plans to cut up to 30,000 operational roles in 2026, CFO Brian Dykes said on the company's post-earnings conference call.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ups-cut-up-30000-operational-jobs-2026-cfo-says-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLL7D43QDJLT7H7ZLUEJK3TSKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音与以色列理工学院携手开发可持续航空燃料，航空业正为实现2050年目标而努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司与以色列理工学院周二宣布，双方正着手开发可持续航空燃料（SAF），原料包括绿色氢气和二氧化碳，旨在推动航空业的长期发展。【原文：Boeing and Israel's Technion university said on Tuesday they were beginning to develop Sustainable Aviation Fuel (SAF) from feedstocks including green hydrogen and carbon dioxide to enable the aviation sector's long-term growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boeing-israels-technion-develop-sustainable-aviation-fuel-sector-grapples-with-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIMIZHKHTRIZLEBMCZLE7SHAFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CBS新闻主管将公布应对所谓偏见及收视下滑的对策方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[CBS新闻总编辑巴里·韦斯定于周二首次向CBS新闻编辑部揭晓其战略规划。这位前评论记者兼企业家正致力于扩大"蒂芙尼网络"的受众规模，并向全国证明该媒体已摆脱自由派偏见。【原文：CBS News Editor-In-Chief Bari Weiss is scheduled to unveil her strategy to the CBS newsroom for the first time on Tuesday, as the former opinion journalist and entrepreneur seeks to grow the Tiffany Network’s audience and convince the nation that it is free from liberal bias.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cbs-news-chief-unveil-blueprint-counter-perceived-bias-audience-slump-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3Q322X7QKFORLKLMB7JTMYAJFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:43:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称哈萨克斯坦腾吉兹油田产量预计在2月7日前恢复不足半数]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士向路透社透露，哈萨克斯坦最大的油田——腾吉斯油田——在经历火灾和停电后正缓慢恢复生产，预计到2月7日其产量恢复水平将不足正常水平的一半。【原文：Kazakhstan's biggest oilfield, Tengiz, is likely to have restored less than half of its normal production by February 7 as it slowly recovers from a fire and power outage, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/kazakhstans-tengiz-oilfield-seen-recovering-less-than-half-its-output-by-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5KBZP775FKZHK7RKUHVQOEK6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>