<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:04:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:04:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[iPhone 销量下滑，苹果投资者寻求关税和人工智能战略的明确性]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四发布业绩报告时，预计将面临一连串的质疑，包括推迟推出关键的人工智能功能，以及中美关税对峙对其业务的影响。【原文：Apple is expected to face a string of questions over the delayed roll-out of key AI features and the impact of the Sino-U.S. tariff standoff on its business, when it reports results on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-investors-seek-clarity-tariffs-ai-strategy-iphone-sales-decline-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KQF5SRXVVPJTF2OOZ6XY6HZNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可口可乐季度收入降幅低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，可口可乐公司公布第一季度收入降幅小于预期，主要得益于其苏打水、果汁和牛奶产品 Fairlife 的提价和强劲需求。【原文：Coca-Cola reported a smaller-than-expected drop in first-quarter revenue on Tuesday, benefiting from price hikes and strong demand for its sodas, juices and milk offering Fairlife.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coca-cola-posts-smaller-than-expected-drop-quarterly-revenue-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UELB4MALNVPAZIKJNUTRFC23YI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税给企业带来利润警告和不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战继续令企业界不寒而栗，通用汽车和沃尔沃汽车放弃了指导，阿迪达斯警告将提价，保时捷和伊莱克斯周二下调了全年展望。【原文：General Motors and Volvo Cars abandoned their guidance, Adidas warned of price hikes and Porsche and Electrolux cut their full-year outlooks on Tuesday as U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war continued to send shivers through the corporate world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/profit-warnings-uncertainty-trump-tariffs-send-chill-through-businesses-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQNYEUUPIZPZ3G4TGQT5VZIHAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻美国贸易担忧消退，加拿大卡尼回归]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-trade-fears-ebb-canadas-carney-returns-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3UWQAXBI5N6ZAK54H66CXC5VE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游轮需求强劲，皇家加勒比上调年度盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[皇家加勒比公司周二上调了年度盈利预期，主要得益于其高端私人岛屿旅游目的地以及前往阿拉斯加和日本等地区的高端航次预订火爆。【原文：Royal Caribbean raised its annual profit forecast on Tuesday, benefiting from strong bookings for its high-end private island destinations and premium sailings to regions such as Alaska and Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/royal-caribbean-raises-annual-profit-forecast-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGFC5UQ25VKVHGFP236LW2UQFE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:38:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电力需求增长、成本降低，公用事业公司 Entergy 盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受电力需求强劲和成本下降的影响，美国公用事业公司 Entergy 周二公布的第一季度利润超过了分析师的预期。【原文：U.S. utility Entergy surpassed analysts' estimate for first-quarter profit on Tuesday, helped by strong demand for power and lower costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/utility-entergy-beats-profit-estimate-growing-power-demand-lower-costs-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44VTMESHKZLLPGROHUKQRIJM7A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，通用汽车下调业绩预期，紧张的消费者抢购一空]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）下调了今年的业绩预期，反映了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全球贸易战对该行业的不确定影响，尽管该公司公布了强劲的季度业绩。【原文：General Motors has pulled its forecast for the year, reflecting the uncertain effects of U.S. President Donald Trump's global trade war on the industry, even as it reported strong quarterly results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-pulls-forecast-due-tariffs-nervous-consumers-rush-buy-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3V5UHCNWPRJUVPMC6VYZZMILNE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌干达领导人会见星链公司，商讨进入东非国家事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌干达总统约韦里-穆塞韦尼（Yoweri Museveni）周二表示，他与科技亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的星链公司（Starlink）代表进行了 "富有成效的会晤"。【原文：Ugandan President Yoweri Museveni said on Tuesday that he had a "productive meeting" with the representatives of tech billionaire Elon Musk's Starlink, which is looking to establish a presence in the East African country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/ugandan-leader-meets-starlink-discuss-entry-east-african-nation-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AL5GUZ3W7RKEZP4SJ55RYQUP2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受经济不确定性影响，希尔顿下调 2025 年收入增长预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收关税和由此引发的全球贸易战引发人们对经济衰退的担忧之际，酒店运营商希尔顿全球（Hilton Worldwide）下调了 2025 年客房收入增长预期。【原文：Hotel operator Hilton Worldwide cut forecast for 2025 room revenue growth at a time when U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs and resulting global trade war have sparked fears of an economic recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hilton-cuts-2025-revenue-growth-forecast-economic-uncertainty-weighs-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEKE4XSNDRNNLLOXXUOMZXKULA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:14:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UPS 公布第一季度收入因需求疲软而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合包裹服务公司（United Parcel Service）周二公布季度收入下降，原因是航运需求降温，显示出美国贸易政策的早期影响。【原文：United Parcel Service on Tuesday reported a drop in quarterly revenue, as cooling demand for shipping pointed to the early impact of U.S. trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ups-reports-fall-first-quarter-revenue-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPWBNY5OFNITNK3K2I6ITZI2RM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:13:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股期货因关税减免而上扬，财报和数据成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货小幅走高，原因是特朗普政府发出了放松汽车行业关税的信号，而投资者则在等待关键的盈利和经济数据以寻找更多方向。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were slightly higher on Tuesday as the Trump administration signaled easing tariffs on the auto sector and investors awaited key earnings and economic data for more direction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-edge-up-tariff-relief-with-earnings-data-focus-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33PDORCW2VLU3JOG4LYJRIQGMA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔第一季度利润因航空航天业务强劲而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔周二公布第一季度调整后利润增长，并上调了 2025 年业绩预期的下限，原因是新喷气式飞机的短缺刺激了对其航空航天零部件和飞机维修服务的需求。【原文：Honeywell posted a rise in first-quarter adjusted profit on Tuesday and raised the lower end of its 2025 forecast, as a shortage of new jets fueled demand for its aerospace parts and aircraft maintenance services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/honeywells-first-quarter-profit-rises-aerospace-strength-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7JK3YKJ3JOULLMOGKTEGRK5JI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院之争可能影响特朗普解雇美联储主席的能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[当美国最高法院就唐纳德-特朗普总统罢免两名联邦劳工委员会成员的努力做出裁决时，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔将关注有关其自身工作保障的线索。【原文：When the U.S. Supreme Court rules on President Donald Trump's effort to remove two federal labor board members, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell will be watching for clues about his own job security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-supreme-court-fight-may-shape-trumps-ability-fire-fed-chair-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDNXXR3LMNIBXMCMP7KGJEOUP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify 预测用户数和月度用户数均高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，Spotify 预测第二季度的月活跃用户数和高级订户数均高于市场预期，这表明其音频流媒体服务的需求强劲，因为该公司正依靠人工智能功能来推动增长。【原文：Spotify forecast monthly active users and premium subscribers for the second quarter above market estimates on Tuesday, signaling strong demand for its audio streaming services as it leans on AI features to drive growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/spotify-forecasts-subscribers-monthly-users-above-estimates-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3W5I4VARCBOLZG7VMTECPJQX6A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在需求放缓和成本上升的双重夹击下，小企业发出了前方有麻烦的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚气候温和，一年 365 天都是修剪树木的季节，这对克里斯托弗-奥特曼（Christopher Altman）来说，通常意味着要提前三周预约，这足以让他位于奥克兰的公司 Trees Company 的五名员工稳定地工作。【原文：Tree trimming season runs 365 days a year in California's temperate climate and that typically means appointments running three weeks in advance for Christopher Altman, enough to keep a staff of five at his Oakland-based business, Trees Company, steadily employed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/vise-slowing-demand-rising-costs-small-businesses-are-signaling-trouble-ahead-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NYKZVSIS5NEBKVMR6Y4KALLJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，默克将投资 10 亿美元在特拉华州新建工厂，以促进美国制造业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周二报道，美国制药商默克公司将投资 10 亿美元在特拉华州新建一家工厂，以扩大其国内生产，同时准备应对唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税。【原文：U.S. drugmaker Merck is investing $1 billion in a new Delaware plant to expand its domestic production as it prepares to deal with President Donald Trump's tariffs, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-invest-1-billion-new-delaware-plant-boost-us-manufacturing-wsj-reports-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LW6ZRBSVSFMRTCQRYQF7SLVIPM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:01:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国抓住美元回落的机会，加大人民币在全球的推广力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在中国国家主席习近平本月出访东南亚，为抵制美国提高关税而加强联系之际，中国人民银行正抓住全球贸易出现混乱和中断的时机，促进人民币的更广泛使用。【原文：As Chinese President Xi Jinping toured Southeast Asia this month to forge closer ties against higher U.S. tariffs, the People's Bank of China was seizing a moment of confusion and disruption in global trade to promote greater usage of the yuan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-ramps-up-global-yuan-push-seizing-retreating-dollar-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EN5ISCQDRFONNPK7XMZUFJVIVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:59:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[史密斯菲尔德食品公司（Smithfield Foods）因包装肉类和猪肉需求强劲而实现销售额和利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国猪肉加工商史密斯菲尔德食品公司（Smithfield Foods）周二公布，受包装肉类和猪肉业务需求强劲以及成本控制努力的帮助，该公司第一季度销售额和利润均有所增长。【原文：U.S. pork processor Smithfield Foods on Tuesday posted higher first-quarter sales and profit, helped by strong demand for its packaged meats and pork businesses and cost-control efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/smithfield-foods-posts-higher-sales-profit-strong-packaged-meats-pork-demand-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56MWG4PK2ZO4ROLAGHFDCN2V6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普关税动荡之际，英国银行业监管机构停止每日流动性监测]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国审慎监管局（Prudential Regulation Authority）首席执行官萨姆-伍兹（Sam Woods）周二在立法者听证会上表示，尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策引发了市场混乱，但英国银行业稳定监督机构还没有理由要求银行业报告每日流动性水平。【原文：Britain's banking stability watchdog has not yet seen reason to require the banking sector to report daily liquidity levels despite the market chaos unleashed by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, Prudential Regulation Authority CEO Sam Woods told a hearing of lawmakers on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/britains-banking-watchdog-stops-short-daily-liquidity-monitoring-amid-trump-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4BAOVHBVFIKJEUMJEQVRV3XW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法拉利首席执行官表示，法拉利不会从外部供应商购买战略部件]]></title><description><![CDATA[法拉利首席执行官贝内代托-维格纳（Benedetto Vigna）周二表示，这家意大利豪华跑车制造商绝不会从外部供应商那里购买汽车的关键零部件。【原文：Ferrari Chief Executive Benedetto Vigna said on Tuesday the Italian luxury sportscar maker would never buy key components for its vehicles from external suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ferrari-will-not-buy-strategic-components-external-suppliers-ceo-says-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSJPMZWMYNJYRAPXTL7ZSWWEX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果美国对制药业征收的关税与其他行业一致，阿斯利康将维持 2025 年的预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康公司（AstraZeneca）首席执行官周二表示，即使美国对欧盟生产的制药产品征收关税，只要关税与其他行业的税率一致，该制药公司仍将维持其2025年的销售指导。【原文：The chief executive of AstraZeneca said on Tuesday that the drugmaker will maintain its 2025 sales guidance even if the U.S. levies tariffs on pharma products made in the European Union, provided they are in line with rates for other sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-keep-2025-forecast-if-us-pharmaceutical-tariffs-line-with-other-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBNHWT7C5VLVHJIZ4P4AOJPQHU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:16:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易机构将墨西哥列入知识产权优先观察名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室周二将墨西哥列入其知识产权优先观察名单，理由是长期以来对商标假冒执法和药品相关知识产权保护的关切。【原文：The U.S. Trade Representative's office on Tuesday placed Mexico on its priority watch list on intellectual property rights citing longstanding concerns over enforcement against trademark counterfeiting and protection of pharmaceutical-related IP.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-trade-agency-adds-mexico-priority-watch-list-over-intellectual-property-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS456XV5D5KY7BYOL5XQHPKNGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国家主席习近平称赞人工智能进展，上海之行会见金砖四国银行代表]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家通讯社新华社报道，中国国家主席习近平自2023年11月以来首次访问上海，敦促上海加快建设具有全球影响力的科技创新中心。【原文：China's President Xi Jinping urged Shanghai to accelerate efforts to turn itself into a technological and innovation hub with global influence as he made his first visit to the city since November 2023, state news agency Xinhua reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-xi-lauds-ai-progress-meets-brics-bank-shanghai-visit-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJW24DZ7WJL25D2WPH7CGDSRMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度在对亚马逊和 Flipkart 的电子商务调查中询问苹果和小米]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，作为对亚马逊和沃尔玛旗下 Flipkart 调查的一部分，印度金融犯罪机构已私下要求苹果和小米等智能手机厂商提供销售数据和其他文件。【原文：India's financial crime agency has privately sought sales data and other documents from smartphone players including Apple and Xiaomi as part of an investigation into Amazon and Walmart-owned Flipkart, sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-queries-apple-xiaomi-e-commerce-probe-amazon-flipkart-sources-say-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTSWO7JQRFM7VJ475AO6YFKQ2E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金冒险重返市场购买银行股，高盛集团称]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）的一份报告显示，对冲基金在连续八周抛售银行股后，上周重返市场买入银行股。【原文：Hedge funds returned into markets last week to buy bank stocks having sold out of positions for eight straight weeks, a Goldman Sachs note shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-venture-back-markets-buy-bank-shares-says-goldman-sachs-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXPFDBXP6BNHVBG2O7LMTU6MAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管关税存在不确定性，但 Primark 老板表示仍将致力于美国扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国联合食品公司（Associated British Foods）老板周二表示，尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对关税的态度反复无常，但该公司旗下的普利马克（Primark）服装零售业务仍致力于在美国扩张。【原文：Associated British Foods' Primark clothing retail business is committed to expanding in the United States despite President Donald Trump's erratic approach to tariffs, its boss said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/primark-committed-us-expansion-despite-tariff-uncertainty-says-boss-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDMQSTSYFZL75L2TNCWC3TBAFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:18:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长西波罗内表示，贸易战可能会降低欧元区的经济增长和通货膨胀率]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行董事会成员皮耶罗-西波隆（Piero Cipollone）周二表示，全球贸易战可能会降低欧元区的经济增长和通胀率，并可能对相关国家产生 "明确的衰退效应"。【原文：A global trade war could lower both economic growth and inflation in the euro zone and it could have an "unambiguously recessionary effect" on the countries involved, ECB board member Piero Cipollone said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trade-war-may-lower-growth-inflation-euro-zone-ecbs-cipollone-says-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLNUTLJFRRNLBCR4AUA7VDW7BY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国大使馆称比亚迪柬埔寨汽车厂破土动工]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国驻柬埔寨大使馆称，中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪在柬埔寨的乘用车工厂于本周一破土动工。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle giant BYD broke ground on its Cambodia passenger vehicle factory on Monday, according to the Chinese embassy in Cambodia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/byd-breaks-ground-cambodian-car-factory-chinese-embassy-says-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IQXZUGRXZO7JCRNBCOACXHDDU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迫于埃利奥特的压力，英国石油公司战略主管奇尔基亚将于 6 月离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国石油公司（BP）周二表示，该公司战略与可持续发展主管朱莉娅-切尔奇亚（Giulia Chierchia）将于 6 月 1 日卸任，她是该公司进军可再生能源这一命运多舛的项目的主要设计师。【原文：BP's strategy and sustainability chief Giulia Chierchia, the key architect of the group's ill-fated foray into renewables, will step down on June 1, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bp-strategy-chief-chierchia-leave-june-after-elliott-pressure-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDH3G5B63NMDZKX4SM6TFISNAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国广州港开通秘鲁航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国中央电视台报道，中国南方最大的航运枢纽广州港周二开通了直达秘鲁尚凯港的航线，此举将降低物流成本，促进与拉美地区的贸易往来。【原文：China's Guangzhou Port, the largest shipping hub in the country's south, opened a direct route to Chancay port in Peru on Tuesday, state broadcaster CCTV reported, a move it said would reduce logistics costs and bolster trade with Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-guangzhou-port-starts-shipping-route-peru-2025-04-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIQRTG2UO5N2LFQ67V7B7A7ABM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>