<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:09:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:08:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[怡安商业风险解决方案部门业绩强劲，季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，保险经纪公司怡安公布第四季度利润增长，商业风险解决方案业务的强劲表现为其带来了帮助。【原文：Insurance brokerage firm Aon reported a higher fourth-quarter profit on Friday, helped by robust performance in its commercial risk solutions business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/aons-quarterly-profit-rises-commercial-risk-solutions-unit-strength-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VANCOBPVXBJMTJ7TYDC2TU43OQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司第四季度业绩超出预期，二叠纪和圭亚那产量增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚周五公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，原因是石油和天然气产量的增加抵消了油价下跌和炼油利润率下降的影响。【原文：Exxon Mobil on Friday beat Wall Street's estimate for fourth-quarter profit as higher oil and gas production offset lower oil prices and weaker refining margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-beats-q4-estimates-with-higher-permian-guyana-output-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX7QC6UO7JO3PIEYVOWT4YBHPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普京下令允许向亚美尼亚基金出售高盛俄罗斯分部]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的一项政府法令显示，弗拉基米尔-普京总统已授权投资公司 Balchug Capital 收购高盛在俄罗斯的部门。【原文：President Vladimir Putin has authorised the purchase of Goldman Sachs' unit in Russia by investment company Balchug Capital, a government decree published on Friday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/putin-decree-permits-sale-goldman-sachs-russian-unit-armenian-fund-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQOY4IMBKROBTKWQLYTOX7GLYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街准备应对加拿大和墨西哥可能征收关税的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球政策制定者和华尔街分析师一直在为特朗普新政府的大规模贸易壁垒做准备。但在执政的第一周，特朗普政府将更多精力放在了国内方面，全球贸易格局基本未变。【原文：Global policymakers and Wall Street analysts have been bracing for massive trade barriers from the new Trump administration. But it focused more on the domestic front in the first week in power, leaving the global trade landscape largely unchanged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-gears-up-fallout-likely-tariffs-canada-mexico-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQF3TNYXF5LRBLOQ6O3HE5GGRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 就业数据迫在眉睫，科技股抛售令投资者心惊肉跳]]></title><description><![CDATA[受本周科技股大幅抛售影响，美国投资者将密切关注即将公布的就业数据，以寻找经济持续复苏的迹象，这可能会加剧美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政策已经激起的通胀担忧。【原文：U.S. investors rattled by this week's sharp tech sell-off will closely watch upcoming jobs data for signs of continued economic resilience, which could fuel inflationary concerns already stoked by President Donald Trump's policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-tech-sell-off-jolts-investors-jobs-data-looms-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42QRSZXC4RJURH37GEUVSWG45E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:19:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电网电力提升项目将错过 7 月最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社对监管文件的审查，美国电网运营商正要求监管机构给予更多时间，以满足联邦命令的要求，即使用可将输电容量提高 40% 的设备升级现有输电线路。【原文：U.S. grid operators are asking regulators for more time to meet a federal order to upgrade existing transmission lines with equipment that can boost their capacity up to 40%, according to a Reuters review of regulatory documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/power-boosting-project-us-grid-miss-july-deadline-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MKJOSYNPJMGBD2X2HOCEJEEXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:17:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金四周来首次出现单周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 1 月 29 日的一周里，美国股票基金四周来首次吸引资金流入，这主要是受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发表讲话后降息希望的刺激，以及科技股在周一下跌后反弹。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted inflows for the first time in four weeks in the week through Jan. 29, spurred by hopes of interest rate cuts following comments from President Donald Trump, and a rebound in tech shares following Monday's losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-draw-first-weekly-inflow-four-weeks-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWMU37HZXZNJXIBODXWCMBGE7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:16:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税最后期限临近，外汇市场为加拿大和墨西哥波动做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对其两个最大贸易伙伴加征关税的最后期限一到，全球货币市场就做好了波动加剧的准备，外汇期权发出了信号，加元成为众矢之的。【原文：A deadline for U.S. tariff hikes on two of its top trading partners has global currency markets braced for increased volatility, FX options signal, with the Canadian dollar in the crosshairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/forex-markets-brace-canada-mexico-swings-us-tariff-deadline-looms-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6BK4NA42BMMDOB3ELLMCDBCVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道调查人员称，比亚迪巴西工厂的中国工人签订的合同存在滥用条款]]></title><description><![CDATA[从中国到巴西东北部为电动汽车制造商比亚迪建造新工厂的工人，每班工作 10 小时的收入约为 70 美元，是中国许多地区每小时最低工资的两倍多。对许多人来说，这让他们很容易就做出了加入的决定，但要退出就难上加难了。【原文：The workers who traveled from China to northeast Brazil to build a new factory for electric car maker BYD earned roughly $70 per 10-hour shift, over twice the Chinese hourly minimum wage in many regions. For many, that made signing up an easy decision - but getting out would be much harder.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-workers-byd-brazil-factory-signed-contracts-with-abusive-clauses-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BV4MV6L3JNC7OCBMQQPX4A2SE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:06:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面对特朗普对仔猪和农作物征收关税，加拿大农民修改销售计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大农民正在与美国买家重新谈判牲畜合同，并为他们之前计划销往边境以南的农作物寻找本地市场，以尽量减少美国潜在的新关税带来的经济打击。【原文：Canadian farmers are renegotiating livestock contracts with U.S. buyers and finding local markets for crops they previously planned to sell south of the border to minimize the economic hit from potential new U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/facing-trump-tariffs-piglets-crops-canadian-farmers-revise-sales-plans-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IUXW3W6ZNPEPK2ROHX3F2CEKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 美元因关税而走高，苹果大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX25XQNH3NN73A32BPMS5IW2E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝多芬还是鸟类？欧洲央行征集新钞票设计创意]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行正在为欧元钞票寻找新的设计，可能的主题包括伟大的文化人物，如德国作曲家路德维希-凡-贝多芬，或鸟类和河流。【原文：The European Central Bank is seeking a new design for euro banknotes, with possible subjects including great cultural figures like German composer Ludwig van Beethoven, or birds and rivers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/beethoven-or-birds-ecb-seeks-ideas-new-banknote-designs-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFLKBC4RIJL5DDYU7FHDLWXE4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 10:57:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 以扎根美国为由躲避印度法院，但律师称案件可以审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI面临着艰难的爬坡过程，因为它认为印度法院不能在该国审理有关其美国业务的诉讼，而Telegram在该国的类似抗辩已经失败，美国科技公司在合规性方面也面临着政府的压力。【原文：OpenAI faces an uphill climb as it argues that Indian courts cannot hear lawsuits about its U.S.-based business in the country, where Telegram has failed with similar defences and U.S. technology firms have faced government heat on compliance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-cites-us-roots-dodge-india-courts-lawyers-say-case-can-be-heard-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F422FHEBXNMTBIXPBR7DVQKABU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 10:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙盈利不及预期，炼油业务四年来首次出现亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司（Chevron Corp）周五公布的第四季度盈利低于华尔街预期，利润率疲软使其炼油业务自 2020 年以来首次出现亏损。【原文：Chevron Corp reported fourth-quarter earnings below Wall Street estimates on Friday as weak margins pushed its refining business into a loss for the first time since 2020.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-misses-earnings-estimate-refining-posts-first-loss-four-years-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBMDDGVGMJPWZJ6NEOZM54Y44E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 10:32:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀考验迫在眉睫，苹果提振美股指数期货]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货上涨，受苹果公司强劲的销售增长预期推动，投资者关注当天晚些时候将公布的可能影响美联储政策决定的关键通胀数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday, driven by gains in Apple following a strong sales growth forecast, as investors focused on key inflation data expected later in the day that could influence the Federal Reserve's policy decisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/apple-lifts-us-stock-index-futures-crucial-inflation-test-looms-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKL3I7IUPJKJ3KO35FSUYXWBKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 10:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金创五周来最大单周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月29日的一周内，受欧洲股市创纪录大涨、美国对华关税预期减弱以及主要央行进一步降息前景的推动，全球股票基金投资激增。【原文：Global equity funds witnessed a surge in investments in the week through Jan. 29, driven by a record rally in European shares, softened U.S. tariff expectations on China, and prospects of further rate cuts by major central banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-lows-graphic-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUQZ6DQDLZKIDFE7JEY7YSWZKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 10:22:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：斯堪尼亚试图为陷入困境的电动汽车电池制造商 Northvolt 注入活力]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡车制造商斯堪尼亚（Scania）已经介入，帮助 Northvolt 处理其位于瑞典北部的旗舰工厂的日常运营，这是在这家陷入困境的电动汽车电池制造商努力争取资金之际，为提高质量和产量所做的最后努力。【原文：Truckmaker Scania has stepped in to help Northvolt with the day-to-day running of its flagship plant in northern Sweden, a last-ditch effort to boost quality and output at the struggling electric vehicle battery maker as it scrambles to secure funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/scania-tries-breathe-life-into-troubled-ev-battery-maker-northvolt-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEFXALW6DNLUHBJHYYW4MAISNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 10:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士法院将对具有里程碑意义的特拉菲古拉腐败案做出裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士法官将于周五对一宗涉及大宗商品贸易商Trafigura和其他三名被告的贪污案作出判决，他们涉嫌向一名安哥拉石油官员行贿以换取石油交易。【原文：Swiss judges will issue a verdict on Friday in a corruption trial involving commodities trader Trafigura and three other defendants who allegedly paid bribes to an Angolan oil official in exchange for oil deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/swiss-court-rule-landmark-trafigura-corruption-case-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UCSQ7TULFNDDDD7LONNWUTDUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 08:59:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美国不参与气候问题，但 SAP 发现对可持续发展软件的需求不断增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国 SAP 公司首席财务官多米尼克-阿萨姆（Dominik Asam）在接受路透社采访时说，尽管美国的气候保护目标有减弱的趋势，但该公司认为全球对管理和记录公司可持续发展努力的软件的需求仍在增长。【原文：Germany's SAP sees a growing global demand for software to manage and document companies' sustainability efforts despite a trend of weakening climate protection targets in the United States, its chief financial officer, Dominik Asam, said in an interview with Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sap-sees-growing-demand-sustainability-software-despite-us-climate-disengagement-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U2JIBYP4NJZTB7NJLZ47AEUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 08:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[设计师金-琼斯（Kim Jones）离开 LVMH 旗下 Dior Homme 品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[时装设计师金-琼斯（Kim Jones）周五表示，将离开路威酩轩集团（LVMH）旗下的 Dior Homme 品牌。【原文：Fashion designer Kim Jones is leaving LVMH's Dior Homme brand, said the company on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/designer-kim-jones-leaving-lvmhs-dior-homme-brand-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBU3FFGL55PTRCLW5YXPTVD7WQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 08:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可再生能源集团 Orsted 更换首席执行官以遏制股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦可再生能源公司 Orsted 周五表示，该公司首席执行官 Mads Nipper 将卸任，由公司内部人士 Rasmus Errboe 接替，以避免股价自 2021 年最高点以来暴跌 83%。【原文：Orsted Chief Executive Mads Nipper will step down to be replaced by company insider Rasmus Errboe, the Danish renewable energy company said on Friday as it seeks to arrest an 83% slump in its share price since its 2021 peak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/orsted-ousts-ceo-appoints-company-insider-new-boss-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2KFQPL7GFKU5CZ7GN3ODXGRBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 07:45:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[销售前景乐观，苹果欧洲股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周五在法兰克福股价上涨 2.5%，原因是该公司预测本季度销售增长相对强劲，这表明该公司将从 iPhone 销量下滑中恢复过来。【原文：Shares in Apple rose 2.5% in Frankfurt on Friday after results the day before, as the company forecast relatively strong sales growth in the current quarter, a sign it will recover from a dip in iPhone sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-shares-rise-europe-after-upbeat-sales-outlook-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSOJ2VIPMZLVNELIYQOWXCM7JY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 07:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[叙利亚伊斯兰统治者通过解雇和国有企业私有化全面整顿经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[叙利亚新任伊斯兰教领导人正在对该国支离破碎的经济进行大刀阔斧的改革，包括计划解雇三分之一的公共部门员工，并将阿萨德家族半个世纪统治期间占主导地位的国营公司私有化。【原文：Syria's new Islamist leaders are undertaking a radical overhaul of the country's broken economy, including plans to fire a third of all public sector workers and privatising state-run companies dominant during half a century of Assad family rule.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/syrias-islamist-rulers-overhaul-economy-with-firings-privatization-state-firms-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDWHKVQDYZILXMPMXXVTEU7UFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 07:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国电动汽车产量将大幅增长，在伤痕累累的市场上引发价格战]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家表示，中国汽车制造商在当地的产量激增，泰国正准备应对由此引发的电动汽车价格战，此举很可能会进一步打击本已因销量下滑而举步维艰的国内汽车业。【原文：Thailand is bracing for an extended EV price war triggered by a surge in local production from Chinese car makers, a move likely to deal a further blow to a domestic auto industry already struggling with tumbling sales, industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/thai-ev-output-set-jump-sparking-price-war-bruised-market-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6T2AJJRGVZISHMDE5HDUCF2IBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepSeek 大跌中闪烁红色市场信号的五张图表]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，人工智能芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）遭遇了有史以来最大的单日价值损失，美联储也表示不急于再次降息。【原文：In a week when AI chipmaker Nvidia suffered the biggest one-day loss of value on record and the Federal Reserve said it was in no hurry to cut rates again, a few gauges underscore markets' vulnerability to big swings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-positioning-graphic-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EMO2ZE6FFMSFNTZFP25I2UJDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:17:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华第四季度盈利大幅超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺华周五公布的季度调整后净收入远高于分析师的预期，原因是心力衰竭治疗药物 Entresto 和多发性硬化症治疗药物 Kesimpta 的销售额超出预期。【原文：Novartis on Friday posted quarterly adjusted net income well above analyst estimates on forecast-beating sales of established heart failure drug Entresto and multiple sclerosis drug Kesimpta.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-beats-consensus-q4-earnings-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QASRS6PKKVMB5EQVTOVZQC47IQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:14:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[除了美联储，特朗普正从所有人那里获得他要求的更低利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）正如愿以偿地在全球范围内降低利率，但在美国国内却并非如此，强劲的经济和对其自身政策的不确定性为美联储与其他央行的分歧埋下了伏笔。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is getting his wish that interest rates drop across the world, just not at home where a strong economy and uncertainty over his own policies have set the stage for the Federal Reserve to diverge from its central bank peers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/trump-is-getting-lower-interest-rates-he-demanded-everyone-fed-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIWJTTR3BFM5VJ7AY2W3MYYF4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:13:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列初创企业在战争中发挥关键作用后制定全球计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，去年 10 月追踪哈马斯领导人叶海亚-辛瓦尔（Yahya Sinwar）并拍摄他奄奄一息画面的无人机是由以色列初创公司 Xtend 制造的。【原文：The drone that tracked Hamas leader Yahya Sinwar and filmed him as he lay dying in footage beamed around the world last October was made by Israeli startup Xtend, according to media reports, one of many such firms to get a boost from Israel's war needs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-startups-make-global-plans-after-key-role-war-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIDPKXIDXBPA3PELPXIPTMWA7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道日本权衡阿拉斯加液化天然气管道承诺以赢得特朗普青睐]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉内情的官员透露，日本正在考虑为阿拉斯加一条价值 440 亿美元的天然气管道提供支持，以讨好美国总统唐纳德-特朗普并防止潜在的贸易摩擦。【原文：Japan is considering offering support for a $44 billion gas pipeline in Alaska as it seeks to court U.S. President Donald Trump and forestall potential trade friction, according to three officials familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/japan-weighs-alaska-lng-pipeline-pledge-win-trumps-favour-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LZDU53GZJKWPLPEUBY5G4MOEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 05:28:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国隐私监管机构将询问 DeepSeek 个人信息使用情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国信息隐私监管机构的一位官员周五表示，该机构计划向 DeepSeek 询问如何管理用户的个人信息。【原文：South Korea's information privacy watchdog plans to ask DeepSeek about how the personal information of users is managed, an agency official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/south-korea-privacy-watchdog-ask-deepseek-about-personal-information-use-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74JAYK55SFO27E75AER6L5ZGN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 04:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>