<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:29:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:29:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛以新品牌和全球重点推动增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球化妆品生产商雅诗兰黛公司首席执行官周四在路透社 NEXT 会议上表示，该公司正致力于通过开发新品牌和关注全球年轻消费者，以及定制产品以满足不同文化消费者的需求，来扩大市场份额和增加销售额。【原文：Global cosmetics maker Estée Lauder Companies is focused on expanding market share and growing sales by developing new brands and focusing on younger consumers worldwide, and customizing products to meet consumers' needs across cultures, its CEO said at the Reuters NEXT conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/este-lauder-driving-growth-with-new-brands-global-focus-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CHVSYF75RMP3JEBZN6QR4MMIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将提高面向企业和政府的生产力套件价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司周四表示，将从2026年7月起在全球范围内提高其面向商业和政府客户的Microsoft 365生产力套件的价格。【原文：Microsoft will increase prices for its Microsoft 365 productivity suites globally starting July 2026 for commercial and government clients, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-lift-productivity-suite-prices-businesses-governments-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUDNP32JE5JNLH5KYMK3V47HTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员提出法案，阻止特朗普放松对华人工智能芯片销售限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括著名共和党对华鹰派人物汤姆-科顿（Tom Cotton）在内的美国两党参议员周四公布了一项法案，该法案将阻止特朗普政府在两年半时间内放松限制中国政府获得人工智能芯片的规定。【原文：A bipartisan group of U.S. senators, including prominent Republican China hawk Tom Cotton, on Thursday unveiled a bill that would block the Trump administration from loosening rules that restrict Beijing's access to artificial intelligence chips for 2.5 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senators-unveil-bill-keep-trump-easing-curbs-ai-chip-sales-china-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THKZ7DTSDZOORH7M7SOAZA2ONA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌高管认为人工智能搜索是网络的扩展]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，谷歌搜索公司的一位高管回击了人们对其人工智能搜索将损害网络出版商及其广告业务的担忧，称这项技术是互联网的 "扩张时刻"。【原文：A Google search executive on Thursday pushed back against fears that its AI-powered search will harm web publishers and its advertising business, calling the technology an “expansionary moment” for the internet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/google-executive-sees-ai-search-expansion-web-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXWJABFDCFNVFBYOFGKLBV3I4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:42:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CNBC 与 Kalshi 签订协议，明年起增加预测数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[CNBC与预测市场运营商Kalshi周四表示，双方已签署一项多年协议，从明年开始将实时概率数据引入CNBC的电视广播和数字平台。【原文：CNBC has signed a multi-year deal with prediction-market operator Kalshi, bringing real-time probability data into the network's TV broadcasts and digital platforms starting next year, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cnbc-signs-deal-with-kalshi-add-prediction-data-next-year-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SVWNTI23ZIH3IG4BUB274WXIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:32:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行扩大财富管理客户的加密货币访问权限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（Bank of America）周四表示，将从下个月开始允许其财富顾问在客户投资组合中建议配置加密货币，这对数字资产领域来说是一个具有里程碑意义的时刻。【原文：Bank of America will begin allowing its wealth advisers to recommend allocations to crypto in client portfolios from next month, the U.S. lending giant said on Thursday, in a landmark moment for the digital assets sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-expands-crypto-access-wealth-management-clients-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBR54P7M5FLBZMWS3KQYJMKIMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:15:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，激进投资者埃利奥特接近与百事公司达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，激进投资者埃利奥特管理公司（Elliott Management）即将与百事公司达成和解协议。【原文：Activist investor Elliott Management is close to striking a settlement agreement with PepsiCo , the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/activist-investor-elliott-nears-settlement-with-pepsico-wsj-reports-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UACALDWUY5JMVEX3RYZ47DNCYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:48:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官们认为年轻消费者将在关税和人工智能变革中推动增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[几位首席执行官周四表示，尽管关税和其他经济压力导致价格上涨，但年轻购物者正在帮助推动一些消费品的增长，如Honest Co尿布和Kate Spade手袋，而人工智能则提高了效率和利润率。【原文：Younger shoppers are helping to drive growth in some consumer products like Honest Co diapers and Kate Spade handbags despite higher prices from tariffs and other economic pressures, while artificial intelligence boosts efficiencies and margins, several CEOs said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ceos-see-younger-consumers-driving-growth-amid-tariffs-ai-changes-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HOF4AA535PBXOMJOHD6YIMZCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD 首席执行官称公司已准备好为运往中国的 AI 芯片支付 15%的税款]]></title><description><![CDATA[先进微设备公司首席执行官苏丽莎周四表示，该公司已获得向中国运输部分 MI 308 芯片的许可，如果向中国运输这些芯片，该公司准备向美国政府缴纳 15%的税款。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices CEO Lisa Su on Thursday said the company has licenses to ship some of its MI 308 chips to China and is prepared to pay a 15% tax to the U.S. government if it ships them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/amd-chief-says-company-ready-pay-15-tax-ai-chip-shipments-china-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WHXZ52OIBMYJFQIETPLDL2554</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:28:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国联邦贸易委员会正在调查 TP-Link 在中国分拆一事上是否误导了美国消费者]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士周四透露，美国联邦贸易委员会正在调查路由器制造商TP-Link Systems Inc.自去年重组以来是否涉嫌隐瞒与中国的关系，从而欺骗了消费者。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is examining whether router maker TP-Link Systems Inc. may have deceived consumers by allegedly concealing its connections to China since its restructuring last year, a source familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ftc-examines-whether-tp-link-misled-us-consumers-about-its-china-split-source-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCRLP7DCNBKAZDYRKPKNJUKZN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大黄集团终止与 Blackstone 的交易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国自助仓储公司 Big Yellow Group 周四表示，没有继续与 Blackstone 讨论潜在交易的基础。【原文：British self-storage company Big Yellow Group said on Thursday that there was no basis of continuing discussions with Blackstone on a potential deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/big-yellow-group-terminates-deal-talks-with-blackstone-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXN7C2Q4MJPXZD66GLZO4IIMOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利对加密货币风险进行 "深入 "审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利银行和其他金融监管机构周四表示，意大利经济部已下令对现有的加密货币风险保障措施进行深入审查，因为加密货币风险有可能上升。【原文：Italy's Economy Ministry has ordered an in-depth review of existing safeguards against cryptocurrency risks, which are seen potentially rising, the Bank of Italy and other financial regulators said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/italy-launches-in-depth-review-cryptocurrency-risks-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHLEVKUGMFKEDJVWCJOJCKGVYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国调查 Waymo 自动驾驶汽车在得克萨斯州非法超越校车 19 次的报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州官员称，Alphabet 旗下公司 Waymo 的自动驾驶汽车自开学以来非法超越校车 19 次，美国一家机构周四表示，已要求 Waymo 回答更多问题。【原文：A U.S. agency said on Thursday it has asked Waymo to answer more questions after Texas officials said the Alphabet unit's self-driving vehicles had illegally passed school buses 19 times since the start of the school year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-probes-reports-waymo-self-driving-cars-illegally-passed-school-buses-19-times-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCKLN23U7VIAVDARXTATA4Y6WQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会敦促美国法官阻止国务院裁员 1,300 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国国务院雇员的工会要求联邦法官阻止国务院周五裁员1300多人，这是唐纳德-特朗普总统政府大规模裁员的最新一场法律战。【原文：Unions representing U.S. State Department employees have asked a federal judge to block the agency from laying off more than 1,300 workers on Friday, the latest legal battle over mass job cuts by President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/unions-urge-us-judge-block-1300-state-department-layoffs-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHX5UFL35BMTLPH57C7J767JDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会批准 AT&T 10 亿美元收购美国蜂窝公司频谱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（Federal Communications Commission）周四表示，已批准 AT&amp;T 公司以 10.2 亿美元从美国蜂窝公司（U.S. Cellular）购买部分无线频谱许可证的交易，此前这家总部位于德克萨斯州的运营商已承诺终止 DEI 计划。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission said Thursday it has approved AT&amp;T's deal to buy some wireless spectrum licenses from U.S. Cellular in a $1.02 billion deal after the Texas-based carrier committed to end DEI programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/fcc-approves-att-1-billion-purchase-spectrum-us-cellular-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZG623CJVJ5JGRNMRXXHGK54GHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mercuria 从 LME 亚洲抢夺铜矿加剧了供应焦虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的消息人士称，大宗商品交易商摩科瑞（Mercuria）已发出通知，计划从伦敦金属交易所位于亚洲的仓库中提取大量铜。【原文：Commodity trader Mercuria has given notice of its plans to take significant amounts of copper from London Metal Exchange warehouses in Asia, four sources familiar with the matter said, as prices rise on expectations of short supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/mercurias-copper-grab-lme-asia-intensifies-supply-angst-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWQYH6SHG5PVPJUSQXEK3RLDLQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ferrovial 首席执行官表示，将在美国机场寻找更多机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙建筑巨头 Ferrovial 公司首席执行官 Ignacio Madridejos 周四表示，在对纽约肯尼迪机场航站楼进行大规模翻修后，该公司看到了投资美国各地机场的其他机会。【原文：Spanish construction giant Ferrovial sees other opportunities for investment in airports across the United States following its massive terminal overhaul at New York's John F. Kennedy Airport, Chief Executive Officer Ignacio Madridejos said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ferrovial-eyeing-more-opportunities-us-airports-ceo-says-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KBI76V2UYBMJJNFYN5D6RBXHLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现货加密产品将在 CFTC 注册交易所开始交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会（CFTC）周四表示，现货加密资产合约将首次在该机构注册的期货交易所开始交易。【原文：The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) said on Thursday that spot crypto asset contracts will begin trading for the first time on futures exchanges registered with the agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/spot-crypto-products-begin-trading-cftc-registered-exchanges-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHQFCISHI5LAXAQHMOSUPIZZAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，派拉蒙指责华纳兄弟 Discovery 公司出售过程不公平]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周四援引新合并的媒体公司发出的一封信报道，派拉蒙 Skydance 指责华纳兄弟发现公司的出售程序不公平，偏袒 Netflix 而不是其他竞标者。【原文：Paramount Skydance has accused Warner Bros Discovery of running an unfair sale process that favors Netflix over other bidders, CNBC reported on Thursday, citing a letter sent by the newly merged media company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-accuses-warner-bros-discovery-unfair-sale-process-cnbc-reports-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PX7H7KCGHNN57B5FX47NBGQLAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄新社报道，俄罗斯封杀 Snapchat]]></title><description><![CDATA[据国营新闻社 RIA 周四援引俄罗斯通信监管机构 Roskomnadzor 的消息报道，俄罗斯已阻止 Snapchat 的访问。【原文：Russia has blocked access to Snapchat, state-run news agency RIA reported on Thursday, citing the country's communications regulator, Roskomnadzor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russia-blocks-snapchat-ria-reports-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTJZD5NDNFOBXBDYCZ4RXGDWEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国矿产项目寻求华盛顿更多支持，以与中国竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位美国矿业和精炼业高管周四表示，华盛顿必须加快项目许可和融资，以抵消中国对全球用于制造电子产品、武器和一系列其他商品的矿产供应的广泛控制。【原文：Washington must speed up permitting and financing for projects to offset China's broad sway over the world's supply of the minerals used to build electronics, weapons and a range of other goods, three U.S. mining and refining executives said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-minerals-projects-seek-more-support-washington-compete-with-china-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMDQGMSRCVOVDM6MSUYC5RP64A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LVMH集团的接班人？阿尔诺的妻子说：我们不谈论这个问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据法国《解放报》周四刊登的奢侈品巨头路威酩轩集团首席执行官贝尔纳-阿尔诺（Bernard Arnault）的妻子的言论称，控制权在阿尔诺家族内部很少讨论接班计划。【原文：Succession plans at luxury giant LVMH are seldom discussed within the controlling Arnault family, according to remarks by CEO Bernard Arnault's wife published in France's Liberation newspaper on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/succession-lvmh-we-dont-talk-about-it-says-arnaults-wife-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USCG4SPR3ZLW5LSUXPPZ33AWJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊在美国航运市场的影响力与日俱增]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊对新履约中心和配送站的投资逐渐巩固了这家网络巨头在近 1930 亿美元的美国包裹业中的重要地位，该行业长期由 UPS、联邦快递（FedEx）和美国邮政服务（U.S. Postal Service）主导。【原文：Amazon's investments in new fulfillment centers and delivery stations have gradually cemented the online giant's position as a key player in the nearly $193 billion U.S. parcel industry, long dominated by UPS , FedEx , and the U.S. Postal Service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/amazons-growing-clout-us-shipping-market-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQLRXZV6QNN3FHX77FGHJHYIJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:27:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国长安汽车高管表示，将在两年内向欧洲推出 Avatr 和 Nevo 电动汽车品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国长安汽车公司全球设计总监周四表示，该公司将在未来两年内在欧洲推出电动汽车品牌 Avatr 和 Nevo，并考虑在欧洲大陆销售轻型商用车。【原文：China's Changan will launch vehicles from its electric Avatr and Nevo brands in Europe over the next two years and is considering selling light commercial vehicles on the continent as well, the automaker's global design chief said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-changan-bringing-avatr-nevo-ev-brands-europe-within-two-years-executive-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66PWAMN4RRPUHKD4X5YOCW5GEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员希望航空公司向长时间延误的乘客支付现金]]></title><description><![CDATA[由 15 位民主党参议员组成的小组周四提议立法，要求航空公司在航班严重延误时提供现金补偿。【原文：A group of 15 Democratic senators proposed legislation Thursday to require airlines to provide cash compensation if carriers cause significant delays.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senators-want-airlines-pay-passengers-cash-long-delays-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFAG4SC3TBOIZGXAIVMKQS5KZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 首席执行官称混合动力车是美国市场的重中之重]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 首席执行官安东尼奥-菲罗萨（Antonio Filosa）周四表示，该汽车制造商正专注于在美国市场生产混合动力车型，这与他的前任专注于全电动车型的做法有所不同。【原文：Stellantis CEO Antonio Filosa said on Thursday that the automaker is focusing on hybrid production in the U.S. market, a shift from his predecessor's focus on fully-electric models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stellantis-ceo-says-hybrids-are-top-priority-us-market-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIEHJYIZ7NICNAUM5TM7KTSTR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:07:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国允许与卢克石油公司在俄罗斯境外的加油站进行交易，直至 4 月下旬]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周四批准了与卢克石油公司（Lukoil）在俄罗斯境外的零售加油站的交易，对美国10月份因该公司的收入在支持莫斯科的乌克兰战争中所扮演的角色而实施的制裁作出了窄幅豁免。【原文：The Trump administration on Thursday authorized transactions with Lukoil retail gas stations outside of Russia, issuing a narrow waiver to sanctions the U.S. imposed in October for the role the company's revenues play in supporting Moscow's war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-allows-transactions-with-lukoil-gas-stations-outside-russia-through-late-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6NTFJZZ75K3JNMPR6L24HVC6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prada 旗下范思哲在短暂任职后与首席创意官达里奥-维塔利分道扬镳]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利时装公司范思哲创意总监达里奥-维塔莱（Dario Vitale）周四表示，他在范思哲任职仅几个月后将离开该品牌。【原文：Versace's creative director Dario Vitale is leaving the brand after only a few months in the role, the Italian fashion company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pradas-versace-parts-ways-with-chief-creative-officer-dario-vitale-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MTF3DS7EJPR3MHP5MS63IFEH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[铜业巨头自由港首席执行官不指望兼并实现增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[铜业巨头 Freeport-McMoRan 公司首席执行官周四表示，对于并购机会永远不会说 "不"，但该公司并不指望通过交易实现增长。【原文：Copper giant Freeport-McMoRan would never say never for merger and acquisition opportunities, but the company is not counting on deals for growth, its chief executive said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/copper-giant-freeports-ceo-wont-count-mergers-growth-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NG3TQPG3CJLYBGK3AFJXSBT54A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称燃油经济性新规可能导致旅行车回归]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府表示，其新的燃油经济性退坡提案可能会允许汽车制造商恢复生产旅行车，这是 20 世纪 70 年代和 80 年代家庭旅行的主力车型。【原文：The Trump administration says its new fuel economy rollback proposal could allow automakers to resume building station wagons, a staple of 1970s and '80s family travel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-says-new-fuel-economy-rule-could-lead-return-station-wagons-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWIHGH3RNFN2XI5YN6BH7LKPLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>