<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:41:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:41:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalWafers 已从 CHIPS 法案中获得 2 亿美元用于美国项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于台湾的中美硅品公司周五表示，其子公司 GlobalWafers 于 6 月份从美国 CHIPS 法案中获得了略高于 2 亿美元的资助，约为这家主要硅晶圆供应商去年所获资助的一半。【原文：Taiwan-based Sino-American Silicon Products said on Friday its subsidiary GlobalWafers received just over $200 million from the U.S. CHIPS Act in June, about half of a grant the major silicon wafer supplier secured last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/globalwafers-has-received-200-million-chips-act-us-projects-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMVWJH6QRFOFNIM7LZ5SIAASSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，软银收购富士康俄亥俄州工厂，启动星际之门人工智能计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，软银集团公司正在收购富士康科技集团位于俄亥俄州的电动汽车工厂，此举旨在启动该日本公司与 OpenAI 和甲骨文公司合作的价值 5000 亿美元的星际之门数据中心项目。【原文：SoftBank Group Corp is acquiring Foxconn Technology Group’s electric vehicle plant in Ohio, in a move to launch the Japanese company's $500 billion Stargate data center project with OpenAI and Oracle Corp , Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-buys-foxconns-ohio-plant-jumpstart-stargate-ai-push-bloomberg-news-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7D4IJAOEFM5ZIUVOZ2GZUGFOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注玻利维亚选民将向右转向]]></title><description><![CDATA[在竞争激烈的总统选举之前，玻利维亚的国际债券大涨，投资者希望政治上的转机有助于支撑该国脆弱的经济，并为国际货币基金组织（IMF）的项目铺平道路。【原文：Bolivia's international bonds have rallied ahead of a fiercely contested presidential election, fueled by investors' hopes that a political U-turn could help shore up the country's fragile economy and pave the way for an IMF program.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/investors-betting-voters-bolivia-will-make-turn-right-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRM2CMBJHRL5VIASXF6YSOTKVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预期乐观，美国旅游业反弹，Expedia股价飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五盘前交易中，Expedia 股价大涨逾 17%，此前这家在线旅行社上调了全年总预订量预期，并对美国旅游需求的复苏持乐观态度。【原文：Shares of Expedia surged more than 17% in premarket trading on Friday, after the online travel agent raised its full-year gross bookings forecast and struck an optimistic tone on the recovery in U.S. travel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/expedia-shares-soar-upbeat-forecast-us-travel-rebound-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y57Z26TL3VOKXH2FOSCNQNZ6LA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：中国要求经纪商停止为稳定币背书，以避免不稳定因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，中国监管机构已要求当地经纪商和其他机构停止发布研究报告和举办研讨会，为稳定币背书，以检查该资产类别，避免不稳定因素。【原文：Chinese regulators have asked local brokers and other bodies to stop research publication and seminars to endorse stablecoins in a bid to check the asset class and avoid instability, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/china-tells-brokers-stop-endorsing-stablecoins-bid-avoid-instability-bloomberg-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVCIX3SM35PQDM3PCROUZLX374</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:20:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国缩小与美国的差距，成为德国最大贸易伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国统计局的初步数据显示，2025 年上半年，中国接近超过美国成为德国最大的贸易伙伴，因为德国对美国的出口因关税提高而下降。【原文：China came close to overtaking the United States as Germany's largest trading partner in the first half of 2025, preliminary data from the German statistics office showed, as German exports to the U.S. declined amid higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-narrows-gap-with-us-germanys-biggest-trading-partner-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REOTZYWFDJMRPDHLQWY4JGIWEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:16:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储动荡刺激鸽派押注，期指走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货上涨，此前唐纳德-特朗普总统临时挑选的美联储理事人选助长了人们对央行董事会更加鸽派的预期。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday after President Donald Trump's temporary pick for a Federal Reserve governor fueled expectations of a more dovish central bank board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/futures-edge-up-fed-shake-up-stokes-dovish-bets-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSQCTFCPPROFDPKCBJFGNBMB5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:12:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官使波音走出低谷，但新的挑战即将来临]]></title><description><![CDATA[在波音遭遇数十年来最严重危机的一年后，首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）成功阻止了公司的自由落体。现在，他面临着新的挑战：提高喷气机产量，重振陷入困境的国防和太空部门，以及恢复这家历史悠久的飞机制造商的盈利能力。【原文：One year after taking the helm during Boeing’s deepest crisis in decades, CEO Kelly Ortberg has stopped the company's freefall. Now, he faces new challenges: ramping up jet production, reviving a struggling defense and space division, and restoring profitability at the storied planemaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ceo-pulled-boeing-out-nosedive-new-challenges-approach-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NA7XSI3F35O6BNSA5K5JJDO6QM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 通胀数据考验股市，部分投资者为涨势暂停做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[对通胀趋势的重新审视将在下周对美国股市的涨势构成考验，一些投资者表示，股市在飙升至创纪录水平后可能会出现回调。【原文：A fresh look at inflation trends will test the U.S. stock market's rally in the coming week, with some investors saying equities are primed for a potential pullback after rocketing to records.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-inflation-data-test-stocks-some-investors-brace-rally-pause-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDUKGPFSQVNYFMQ422QHVIFRIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼和苹果交易提振业绩前景，MP材料公司在亏损减少后大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国稀土矿商公布产量增加、季度亏损小于预期并预测产量将进一步增加之后，MP Materials 公司股价在周五的盘前交易中跳涨超过 10%。【原文：MP Materials shares jumped more than 10% in premarket trading on Friday, after the U.S. rare earths miner posted higher output, a smaller-than-expected quarterly loss and forecast further production gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mp-materials-surges-after-smaller-loss-pentagon-apple-deals-boost-outlook-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJZ3GEVPKNJNBEMFU46MXSVGBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构批准波音与 Spirit AeroSystems 合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构周五表示，已批准波音公司收购 Spirit AeroSystems 公司的计划，决定不对该交易是否反竞争进行深入调查。【原文：Britain's competition regulator said on Friday it had cleared Boeing's planned acquisition of Spirit AeroSystems after deciding against an in-depth investigation into whether the deal would be anti-competitive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uk-competition-regulator-clears-boeing-spirit-aerosystems-merger-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3VLX43YTFNBXIBA4FRTQN3UGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国政府推迟就谷歌地图数据出口请求作出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国交通部表示，在美国施压要求谷歌在最近的贸易谈判中解决被华盛顿视为非关税壁垒的问题后，韩国周五推迟了对谷歌出口地图数据申请的决定。【原文：South Korea on Friday delayed a decision on Google's request for permission to export map data following U.S. pressure to address what Washington regards as a non-tariff barrier during recent trade talks, its transport ministry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-delays-decision-googles-request-map-data-exports-ministry-says-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLYOSK2UYZME5MV2CNYLBRHQ5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:40:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车工业集团数据显示，7月份中国汽车销量增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的汽车销量增长在 7 月份有所放缓，因为这个全球最大的汽车市场面临着更严格的法规和激烈的价格战，主要汽车制造商的命运也不尽相同。【原文：China's car sales growth slowed in July, as the world's largest auto market navigates uneven fortunes of major automakers amid tougher regulations against a bruising price war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-car-sales-growth-slows-july-auto-industry-group-data-shows-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AEBOABL2WVP5VGDQ2VAKRNWFDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:16:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[粮农组织称 7 月份世界粮食价格上涨至两年来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国粮食及农业组织周五表示，受国际肉类和植物油价格上涨的推动，7月份世界粮食商品价格上涨至两年多来的最高点。【原文：World food commodity prices rose in July to their highest in more than two years, driven by rising international prices for meat and vegetable oils, the United Nations' Food and Agriculture Organization said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-food-prices-rise-two-year-high-july-fao-says-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4OCQ52KLZKRXKGOXPN6CUC4LQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7 月新兴市场国家央行继续宽松，主要同行仍在观望]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国贸易和关税政策的不确定性波及全球经济，新兴市场央行在 7 月份实施了多年来最大规模的降息举措，而发达市场央行则保持稳定。【原文：Emerging market central banks implemented their largest rate-cutting push in years in July, while their developed market counterparts held steady as uncertainty over U.S. trade and tariff policies reverberated across global economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/em-central-banks-plough-with-easing-july-major-peers-linger-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPO3JYQUAZKEVPLKKCVCGWPSQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度科技巨头 TCS 裁员预示着人工智能对价值 2830 亿美元的外包行业的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度外包巨头塔塔咨询服务公司（Tata Consultancy Services）决定裁减 12000 多个工作岗位，这标志着由人工智能推动的更广泛趋势的开始，专家表示，在未来两三年内，这个价值 2830 亿美元的行业可能会裁减约 50 万个工作岗位。【原文：Indian outsourcing giant Tata Consultancy Services' decision to cut over 12,000 jobs signals the start of a broader AI-fueled trend that could end up eliminating around half a million jobs over the next two to three years from the $283 billion sector, experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/india-tech-giant-tcs-layoffs-herald-ai-shakeup-283-billion-outsourcing-sector-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ4VCBV6HNL4PGJCNKQVSURSVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[渣打银行成立合资企业在香港发行稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周五表示，该公司已与战略合作伙伴成立了一家合资企业，以申请在香港发行稳定币的执照，这是在香港稳定币立法生效几天后。【原文：Standard Chartered said on Friday that it has formed a joint venture with strategic partners to apply for a license to issue stablecoins in Hong Kong, days after the city's stablecoin legislation came into effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/standard-chartered-forms-joint-venture-issue-stablecoins-hong-kong-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EGVFOP5T5MFBHA4DM2CWZ7OPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:14:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求辞职后，英特尔首席执行官称正与美国政府合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司首席执行官陈立武周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）当天早些时候要求他立即辞职后，该芯片制造商正在与美国政府接触，以澄清关切，并确保提供准确的信息。【原文：Intel Chief Executive Lip-Bu Tan on Thursday said the chipmaker is engaging with the U.S. administration to clarify concerns and ensure accurate information is provided after President Donald Trump demanded his immediate resignation earlier in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-ceo-says-he-is-working-with-us-administration-after-trump-demands-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZARSA2RVD5NAFO7EXRDXBRUSOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对俄罗斯石油买家征收关税带来经济和政治风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[从惩罚巴西到试图遏制芬太尼的进口，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将关税威胁作为一种万能的外交政策武器。【原文：From punishing Brazil to trying to curb imports of fentanyl, U.S. President Donald Trump has wielded the threat of tariffs as an all-purpose foreign policy weapon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-tariffs-russias-oil-buyers-bring-economic-political-risks-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WP2T33HARVLEBHZINMWGO5TEWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高管表示，美国零售商百思买将把印度技术中心的员工人数增加 40% 以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高级管理人员告诉路透社记者，随着越来越多的跨国公司在印度设立办事处，以利用印度不断增长的人才库，美国电子连锁企业百思买计划在未来几个月内将其印度技术中心的员工人数增加 40% 以上。【原文：U.S. electronics chain Best Buy plans to expand the headcount at its Indian tech centre by over 40% in the next few months, a senior executive told Reuters, as more global corporations set up offices in the country to tap its growing talent pool.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-retailer-best-buy-boost-india-tech-hub-staff-by-over-40-executive-says-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4J6IDXH3BMPHF33EDUX6RWHAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：Binance 与 BBVA 合作，让客户在交易所外保留资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，Binance 正在与西班牙银行 BBVA 合作，允许客户在加密货币交易所之外持有资产。【原文：Binance is working with Spanish bank BBVA to allow customers to hold their assets off the crypto exchange, Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/binance-teams-up-with-bbva-let-customers-keep-assets-off-exchange-ft-reports-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQIOLKCQHVPQDNU3VHKAVI6I7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通认为美联储将在未来四次会议上逐次降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（J.P.Morgan）周四在一份报告中称，由于劳动力市场和整体经济出现放缓迹象，该公司目前预计美国联邦储备委员会将在未来四次会议上每次降息25个基点，从而使政策利率降至3.5%。【原文：J.P.Morgan now expects the U.S. Federal Reserve to cut interest rates by 25 basis points at each of its next four meetings, bringing the policy rate to 3.5%, it said in a note on Thursday, as the labor market and broader economy show signs of slowing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jpmorgan-sees-fed-cutting-rates-each-its-next-four-meetings-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDFTWJ5AHVJ3TNUDX6TAERMUO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:38:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻特朗普采取行动扩大对美联储的控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7PS7KYGT5L45E432XWSYJFIJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中远集团寻求在价值 230 亿美元的巴拿马运河港口交易中获得至少 20% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，中国国有航运巨头中远集团（Cosco）的目标是在一项涉及巴拿马运河战略资产的价值 230 亿美元的港口交易中获得至少 20%-30%的股份，因为中国政府正在就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）此前曾称赞过的出售条款进行重新谈判。【原文：China's state-owned shipping giant Cosco aims to secure at least 20%-30% stake in a $23 billion ports deal involving strategic assets in the Panama Canal, as Beijing moves to renegotiate the terms of a sale previously praised by U.S. President Donald Trump, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/cosco-seeks-least-20-stake-23-billion-panama-canal-ports-deal-ft-reports-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IMH4IXMVVPTBLU2KIO3HNVKTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:19:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一家拥有 240 年历史的瑞士钟表制造商为赶在特朗普的关税最后期限之前而展开的竞赛]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着本周美国关税最后期限的临近，瑞士钟表制造商DuBois et fils急于向美国运送五款高端手表，每款价值数千美元。到本周三，该公司已封锁了其美国网站上的订单。现在，首席执行官托马斯-施泰因曼（Thomas Steinemann）正在计算他需要提高的价格。【原文：As a U.S. tariff deadline neared this week, Swiss watch manufacturer DuBois et fils rushed to ship five high-end watches worth thousands of dollars each to the United States. By Wednesday the firm had blocked orders on its U.S. website. Now CEO Thomas Steinemann is calculating the price hikes he'll need to make.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/240-year-old-swiss-watchmakers-race-beat-trumps-tariff-deadline-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXJ6JAKCDBJHRHD4XHFNGU3MU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[看好人工智能前景提振第一季度盈利，软银股价飙升至创纪录水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五上午，软银集团（SoftBank Group）股价跳涨逾 13%，创下历史新高，表明投资者支持这家日本科技投资者在第一季度利润超出预期后推动人工智能发展。【原文：Shares in SoftBank Group jumped more than 13% to a record high on Friday morning in a show of investor support for the Japanese technology investor's AI push after first quarter profit beat expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-shares-surge-record-after-optimism-ai-prospects-boosted-q1-earnings-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLMB2H3DUBM3VNVWHGRE5ZSIAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国中芯国际称特朗普关税并未导致预期的 "硬着陆]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国顶级代工企业中芯国际的联席首席执行官周五表示，美国的关税政策并未导致该公司最初担心的 "硬着陆"，强劲的国内需求将使其产能在10月份之前一直处于紧张状态。【原文：China's top foundry SMIC's co-CEO said on Friday that U.S. tariff policy had not resulted in the "hard landing" that the company was initially worried about and that strong domestic demand will keep its production capacity tight until October.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-smic-says-trump-tariffs-did-not-cause-expected-hard-landing-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GG4ZDYDRGRIV3EXUALLXARM53Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财报提振日本股指创历史新高，亚洲其他市场有所缓和]]></title><description><![CDATA[在积极的盈利报告和美国将取消对日本商品征收重叠关税的预期之后，日本股市周五大涨。【原文：Japanese shares surged on Friday after positive earnings reports and expectations the U.S. would remove overlapping tariffs on the country's goods, while shares were down in other Asian markets after a late retreat on Wall Street during the previous session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJSAG47OS5PDDLXJCF6NUFNN5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美联储人选、英国央行的 "鹰派 "降息令美元承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普临时选择的美联储代理理事人选激起了人们对在杰罗姆-鲍威尔任期结束后由一个鸽派人选接替其职务的预期，美元周五承压，并有望每周下跌。【原文：The dollar was under pressure on Friday and was on course for a weekly fall as U.S. President Donald Trump's temporary choice for a fill-in Federal Reserve Governor stoked expectations for a dovish pick to replace chair Jerome Powell when his term ends.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/trumps-fed-pick-bank-englands-hawkish-cut-weigh-dollar-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTFGPIIS3FI2FDRN5GSIGLUALI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Meta 选择 Pimco 和 Blue Owl 为其数据中心融资 290 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，Meta 已选择投资管理公司 Pimco 和另类资产管理公司 Blue Owl Capital 为其路易斯安那州农村地区的数据中心项目提供 290 亿美元的融资。【原文：Meta has selected investment management firm Pimco and alternative asset manager Blue Owl Capital for a $29 billion financing deal related to its data center projects in rural Louisiana, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-selects-pimco-blue-owl-29-billion-data-center-financing-bloomberg-news-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGS7ZS4WUJIJHHKQIBM27AU4ZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>