<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:38:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:38:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称需求增加导致美国原油和燃料库存下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（EIA）周三称，由于炼油活动和需求上升，上周美国原油和燃料库存下降。【原文：U.S. crude oil and fuel inventories fell last week as refining activity and demand rose, the Energy Information Administration (EIA) said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-fuel-inventories-fall-higher-demand-eia-says-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW2CW7M3ABOK3FPJ5MLYHRLW3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月新屋销售降幅超预期；库存增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于高抵押贷款利率抑制了需求，增加了市场上未售出房屋的供应量，5 月份美国新建独户住宅的销量降幅超过预期。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell more than expected in May as high mortgage rates sapped demand, boosting the supply of unsold houses on the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-more-than-expected-may-inventory-rises-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62XRCKMJ5VLAPDBLUJNX2OOB5E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡车司机协会主席敦促国会废除人工智能州法律禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际卡车司机兄弟会（International Brotherhood of Teamsters）主席周三敦促美国国会废除一项将在 10 年内有效禁止各州监管人工智能的提案，称其为 "社区和劳动人民的灾难"。【原文：The president of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters urged Congress on Wednesday to scrap a proposal that would effectively bar states from regulating artificial intelligence for 10 years, calling it "a disaster for communities and working people."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/teamsters-president-urges-congress-scrap-ai-state-law-ban-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGLR7GB4ZRKX5DEC3X6EJ62PXA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:53:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[无人机需求推动 AeroVironment 股价飙升，季度业绩超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受军用无人机需求持续增长的推动，AeroVironment 公司第四季度业绩超出华尔街预期，周三该公司股价飙升。【原文：AeroVironment's shares soared on Wednesday after the company beat Wall Street expectations for fourth-quarter results, driven by sustained demand for its military drones.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aerovironment-shares-soar-drone-demand-fuels-quarterly-results-beat-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3DOMMLHYFL4DJS26DNYI6MKPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[业主称关闭的三哩岛核电站可能于 2027 年重启]]></title><description><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州前三里岛核电站的所有者星座能源公司（Constellation Energy）的高管周三表示，该核电站可能会在 2027 年重新启动，比原计划提前一年左右。【原文：The former Three Mile Island nuclear power plant in Pennsylvania may restart in 2027, about a year ahead of schedule after being put on a fast track to connect to the regional grid, executives with the plant's owner Constellation Energy said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/shut-three-mile-island-nuclear-plant-may-restart-2027-owner-says-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZMCZCWL6BPFJAQYKVUF4GRACM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:35:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔警告不要终止美联储支付储备金利息的权力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周三表示，央行向银行存放在央行的现金支付利息的权力是美联储利率控制工具包的关键部分，很难解除。【原文：Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell said Wednesday that the central bank's power to pay interest on cash that banks park at the central bank is a key part of the Fed's interest rate control toolkit and would be difficult to unwind.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-powell-cautions-against-ending-fed-power-pay-interest-reserves-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADO6KMCZNFPC5FSCDWCATH26QQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，黑狮集团以 80 亿美元现金竞购 Citgo 母公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司 Black Lion Capital Advisors 的关联公司 Black Lion Citgo Group 在周三发布的一份法院文件中表示，该公司提交了一份 80 亿美元的全现金竞购委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司的报价，这是法院组织的股权拍卖的一部分。【原文：Black Lion Citgo Group, an affiliate of private equity firm Black Lion Capital Advisors, submitted a $8-billion all-cash bid for the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum as part of a court-organized auction of shares, the company said in a court filing released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/black-lion-submits-8-billion-cash-bid-citgos-parent-filing-says-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAEXRP3CRZML5ORNJOXUEITRNI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:28:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星在与中兴通讯的英国专利战中赢得临时许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子周三赢得了伦敦高等法院的一项裁决，三星试图获得使用中兴通讯专利的临时许可，这是两家公司关于手机专利的全球许可纠纷的英国部分。【原文：Samsung Electronics on Wednesday won a ruling from London's High Court in its attempt to get an interim licence to use ZTE's patents, in the English leg of the firms' global licensing dispute over mobile phone patents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/samsung-wins-interim-licence-uk-patent-fight-with-zte-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZOSG37NNZIK7BQQU62N2VMZ3E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通认为 2025 年美国将因关税引发 "滞胀 "经济放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）分析师周三表示，美国的贸易政策可能会减缓全球经济增长，并重新引发美国的通货膨胀，今年下半年美国经济衰退的可能性为 40%。【原文：U.S. trade policies will likely slow down global economic growth and rekindle inflation in the United States, where there is a 40% probability of a recession in the second half of this year, JPMorgan analysts said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jpmorgan-sees-tariff-induced-us-stagflationary-slowdown-2025-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VM346YDIBNPFDIPLT6D7WEKQPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国政治阻碍了针对谷歌的反垄断行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国的竞争监管机构终于提出了一项控制谷歌庞大搜索业务的计划，但政治风向的转变有利于大型科技公司及其投入的资金，这使得该计划与其说是 "咬"，不如说是 "吠"。【原文：Britain's competition regulator has finally come up with a plan to control Google's huge search business, but a shift in the political wind in favour of big tech and the money it invests makes it more of a bark than a bite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/uk-politics-blunts-antitrust-action-against-google-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIFMAJCLFZIUZLM3XX5NSKH63M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯称今年晚些时候可能降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周三表示，她预计央行将在今年晚些时候降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said Wednesday she is expecting the central bank to cut interest rates later this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-collins-says-rate-cuts-later-this-year-are-possible-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFLMRIC44VJMZPTJKZ67VXG57A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 首席财务官 Paula Oyibo 离职，内部人士被任命为临时财务总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 周三表示，其财务总监 Paula Oyibo 在任职一年多后离职，并任命内部人士 Chris Lialios 担任临时首席财务官。【原文：Ulta Beauty's finance chief Paula Oyibo has departed after a little over a year in the role, it said on Wednesday, and named insider Chris Lialios as its interim CFO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ulta-beauty-names-insider-chris-lialios-interim-cfo-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7OEIDGMOVL7NNZEX7A5NOQPT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:16:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称美国 6 月新车销量将增长 2.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[J.D.Power和GlobalData周三在一份联合报告中称，经调整后，6月份美国新车总销量预计将增长2.5%，达到125万辆。【原文：U.S. total new vehicle sales are expected to rise 2.5% to 1.25 million units on an adjusted basis for the month of June, J.D. Power and GlobalData said in a joint report on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-new-vehicle-sales-set-rise-25-june-report-says-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYQSALYOOROMFPXORXCA5MX2DE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 称，在中国政府推动全球人工智能发展的背景下，中国的智普人工智能公司（Zhipu AI）正逐渐站稳脚跟]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周三表示，其分析师发现，中国初创公司智璞人工智能（Zhipu AI）在获得多个地区的政府合同方面取得了显著进展，这表明中国在追求全球人工智能领导地位方面的势头日益强劲。【原文：OpenAI said on Wednesday its analysts have seen notable progress by Chinese start-up Zhipu AI in securing government contracts across several regions, signaling China's growing momentum in pursuing global AI leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/openai-says-chinas-zhipu-ai-gaining-ground-amid-beijings-global-ai-push-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFHTAE65ARMN3K36L2CN6HZMR4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[桑坦德银行将向社区银行出售宾夕法尼亚州七家分行]]></title><description><![CDATA[桑坦德银行（Santander）周三表示，已同意将宾夕法尼亚州阿伦敦地区的七家分行出售给总部位于美国的社区银行（Community Bank），这家西班牙银行正努力成为美国数字优先的银行。【原文：Santander said on Wednesday it had agreed to sell seven branches in the Allentown, Pennsylvania area to U.S.-based Community Bank as the Spanish lender pivots towards becoming a digital-first bank in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/santander-sell-seven-pennsylvania-branches-community-bank-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJBWRH6LPBK3FJUPBECO2SNIPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bumble 将在全球裁员 30]]></title><description><![CDATA[约会应用 Bumble 周三表示，它将裁员约 240 人，占全球员工总数的 30%。【原文：Dating application Bumble said on Wednesday it will lay off about 240 roles or 30% of its global staff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/bumble-lay-off-30-global-workforce-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3OHPZGTJFP6BEKF5COOTYNIDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔前往参议院小组第二天作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周三将在参议院银行委员会继续为期两天的国会作证，前一天他在众议院的一个小组会议上重点阐述了美联储对特朗普政府关税计划将提高通胀率的担忧。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell resumes two days of Congressional testimony on Wednesday when he appears before the Senate Banking committee after scrutiny before a House panel the day before that focused on the Fed's concerns the Trump administration's tariff plans will raise inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-powell-heads-senate-panel-second-day-testimony-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTU327R5WNMPDHS7VZ4F2JIBAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:28:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员提出法案，禁止中国人工智能进入美国政府机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个由两党议员组成的美国议员团体周三计划在国会参众两院提出一项法案，禁止美国行政机构使用中国开发的人工智能模型，包括来自 DeepSeek 的模型。【原文：A bipartisan group of U.S. lawmakers on Wednesday planned to introduce a bill in both houses of Congress that would bar U.S. executive agencies from using artificial intelligence models developed in China, including those from DeepSeek.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-lawmakers-introduce-bill-bar-chinese-ai-us-government-agencies-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYWWLPCJ6JIPZE5Y5KTSVMFKEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五月投资者重返美国长期债券基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份，美国长期债券基金吸引了大量资金流入，扭转了 4 月份的萎缩态势，表明投资者在权衡贸易关税、通胀和财政赤字等一系列不确定性因素后，寻求高收益债务的安全性。【原文：U.S. long-term bond funds drew massive inflows in May, reversing April's drawdown and indicating investors sought the safety of higher-yielding debt, as they weighed a host of uncertainties around trade tariffs, inflation and fiscal deficits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-returned-us-long-term-bond-funds-may-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2QKDVA3ZFOJ5IXJRHYYJX4KZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融时报》报道：布鲁塞尔将无视欧洲央行关于稳定币规则的警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，尽管欧洲中央银行（ECB）警告称，拟议的标准可能会在市场波动期间破坏该地区银行的稳定，但欧盟委员会仍将在未来几天内宣布针对快速增长的稳定币市场的新规则。【原文：The European Commission is set to announce new rules for the fast-growing stablecoin market in the coming days, despite warnings from the European Central Bank (ECB) that the proposed standards could destabilise the region's banks during periods of market volatility, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/brussels-set-disregard-ecb-warnings-over-stablecoin-rules-ft-reports-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQ5CTVWW65JYHP37B2UUZVKMOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用磨坊因宏观经济不确定性预测年度利润下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用磨坊公司（General Mills）周三预测年度利润低于预期，原因是在关税驱动、宏观经济不确定的背景下，美国市场对其冷藏烘焙食品和零食的需求疲软。【原文：General Mills forecast annual profit below expectations on Wednesday, as the Pillsbury-owner was weighed by weak demand for its refrigerated baked goods and snacks in the U.S. in a tariff-driven, uncertain macroeconomic background.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/general-mills-forecasts-downbeat-annual-profit-macroeconomic-uncertainty-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGUWQ4IDRBLIHK5AESDRGPW2VE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:11:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴基斯坦称与美国的贸易谈判将于下周结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴基斯坦财政部长穆罕默德-奥朗泽布（Muhammad Aurangzeb）和美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周三会晤后表示，巴基斯坦和美国决心在下周结束贸易谈判。【原文：Pakistan and the U.S. have resolved to conclude trade talks next week, the South Asian nation said on Wednesday after a meeting between its Finance Minister Muhammad Aurangzeb and U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/pakistan-says-trade-talks-with-us-conclude-next-week-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4S7M7XJP7ROKPL22VJGGKWKOLY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴宝莉股价上涨，经纪公司预测业绩将恢复性增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴宝莉（Burberry）股价周三上涨，原因是在 7 月 18 日发布第一季度交易报告之前，券商对这家英国奢侈品牌的看法相对乐观。【原文：Burberry shares rose on Wednesday as brokerages turned relatively upbeat on the British luxury brand before its first quarter trading statement on July 18.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/stocks/burberry-shares-rise-brokers-forecast-resilient-results-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66754JN2CZM3FMEP3QPNFOVCRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:49:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美联储加息押注飙升，石油市场趋于平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYDQMI4XNVOTFJUWZQ7ZEL2D5A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:48:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析人士称，特朗普的预算计划将财富从年轻人手中转移到老年人手中]]></title><description><![CDATA[无党派分析人士表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面减税法案将有效地把财富从年轻一代美国人手中转移到老一代人手中。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tax-cut legislation would effectively transfer wealth from younger Americans to older generations, nonpartisan analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/trumps-budget-plan-shifts-wealth-young-old-analysts-say-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PH7JSTQC35MPTPCC4M6EY25WL4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:27:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东紧张局势降温，美股期货低迷；鲍威尔成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于以色列和伊朗发出空战已经结束的信号，也由于投资者在等待美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔发表更多评论，纳斯达克 100 指数在前一天创下收盘纪录新高后，周三美股期货表现低迷。【原文：U.S. stock futures were subdued on Wednesday, after the Nasdaq 100 closed at a record high a day earlier on Israel and Iran signaling their air war had ended, and as investors awaited more comments from Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-subdued-middle-east-tensions-cool-powell-focus-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUMFTF4LBZMQJG2LPWVEWTD2TM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国交易所和证交会正在商谈放宽上市公司监管条例]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国交易所运营商正在与美国证券交易委员会（Securities and Exchanges Commission）商谈减轻上市公司监管负担的事宜，以鼓励更多估值丰厚的初创企业上市。【原文：U.S. exchange operators are in talks with the Securities and Exchanges Commission on easing regulatory burdens for public companies, as they seek to encourage more richly valued startups to list, according to four people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-exchanges-sec-talks-ease-public-company-regulations-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3RU4SPG4NIMLB2T2FWLNK33LU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）的 "野孩子 "阿根廷寻求外汇储备缺失豁免--很可能会如愿以偿]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷是国际货币基金组织（IMF）的长期问题儿童和最大的债务国，它再次需要寻求宽恕：这一次是因为没有达到与 200 亿美元新协议相关的外汇储备增加目标。【原文：Argentina, the International Monetary Fund's long-term problem child and biggest debtor, once again needs to seek forgiveness: this time for falling short on foreign currency reserve build-up targets linked to a new $20 billion deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/imf-wild-child-argentina-seeks-waiver-fx-reserves-misses-will-probably-get-it-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4FLKAT3E5M6XBSA7QHCHMOPAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:13:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帕兰提尔的突飞猛进将在罗素大洗牌中留下印记]]></title><description><![CDATA[帕兰提尔科技公司（Palantir Technologies）股价的暴涨很可能会在周五富时罗素指数（FTSE Russell）对其基准指数的最终重组中留下印记，届时投资者可望在收盘前看到巨大的交易量。【原文：A meteoric rally in shares of Palantir Technologies is likely to leave its imprint on the final reconstitution by FTSE Russell of its benchmark indexes on Friday, when investors can expect a crush of trading volume heading into the closing bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/palantirs-surge-leave-its-mark-russell-reshuffle-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L46TB57QMRK77FJVT5U57TLR5A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gartner 表示，到 2027 年将有超过 40% 的人工智能代理项目被取消]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 Gartner 的一份报告，到 2027 年底，将有超过 40% 的代理人工智能项目因成本上升和商业价值不明而被取消。【原文：More than 40% of agentic artificial intelligence projects will be canceled by the end of 2027 due to escalating costs and unclear business value, according to a report by Gartner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/over-40-agentic-ai-projects-will-be-scrapped-by-2027-gartner-says-2025-06-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3533DFLUVM6XCO5FGEAYH2YRE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>