<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:09:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:09:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部协助的海外合同额在2025年跃升至2440亿美元，得益于波音公司订单的增长。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部国际贸易管理局周五表示，2025年在该部门协助下，美国企业签署了价值2440亿美元的外国政府采购合同，较2024年增长近三倍。波音公司客机订单量大幅攀升是主要推动因素。【原文：U.S. companies signed foreign government procurement contracts worth $244 billion in 2025 with assistance from the U.S. Commerce Department, nearly triple the total in 2024 as Boeing logged a massive increase in jetliner orders, the agency's International Trade Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-commerce-assisted-foreign-contracts-jump-244-billion-2025-boeing-order-gains-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46JL23NCCBKOZHB42QA2PMRJ4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望：美联储决议与财报大周临近，全球紧张局势令市场前景蒙尘]]></title><description><![CDATA[年初以来被地缘政治动荡所困扰的投资者，下周可能将关注焦点转向人工智能相关盈利前景及利率走向，届时将迎来大批财报发布和美联储会议。【原文：Investors who have been consumed by geopolitical turmoil to start the year may switch focus in the coming week to prospects for artificial intelligence-related profits ​and the path for interest rates, with a huge crop of earnings reports and a Federal Reserve meeting on tap.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-fed-big-earnings-week-loom-markets-global-tensions-muddy-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AH5VYNZREZP7NMCVMSAOVRXRPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道明证券称，全球股票基金遭遇创纪录资金外流，因美国和中国撤资激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[道明证券策略师周五在分析EPFR数据的报告中指出，全球股票基金创下史上最大规模资金流出纪录，因美国和中国市场的巨额赎回抵消了其他地区相对强劲的表现。【原文：Global equity funds recorded their largest outflows on record, as heavy withdrawals from the U.S. and China outweighed a relatively strong showing in other regions, TD Securities strategists said in a Friday note analysing EPFR data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-flows-urgent-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBD6CCTC4VL33FCOBWV627ZBQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希思罗机场新式安检仪终结令人厌烦的液体和笔记本电脑翻查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在欧洲最繁忙的希思罗机场，乘客通过安检时将不再被迫翻找随身行李中的洗发水、水瓶和笔记本电脑，这得益于新型专用扫描仪的投入使用。【原文：Passengers will no longer be forced to dig around in their hand luggage to extract shampoos, water bottles and laptops when travelling through security at Heathrow, Europe's busiest airport, thanks to new specialist scanners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/heathrows-new-scanners-end-dreaded-rummage-liquids-laptops-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4J6EBGITRPHZBTVZRNAEODSSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯联邦储蓄银行入股Element公司，普京推动技术主权建设]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯最大银行转型的科技集团俄罗斯联邦储蓄银行（Sberbank）已收购领先电子产品制造商Element的大部分股权。此举正值莫斯科推动在乌克兰战争所需高科技组件生产领域实现自主权之际。【原文：Sberbank, Russia's biggest bank turned technology conglomerate, has taken a major stake in leading electronics producer Element, as Moscow pushes for sovereignty in the production of the high-tech components needed for the war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/russias-sberbank-takes-stake-element-putin-pushes-tech-sovereignty-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCS3GEYJB5JYBCG32CV57EHFRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递将在法国裁员最多500人；重组运营业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递周五表示，计划裁减多达500个岗位，并投入高达7800万欧元（约合9158万美元）资金，作为其在该国国内业务重大重组计划的一部分。【原文：FedEx said on Friday that it planned to cut up to 500 jobs and invest as much as 78 million euros ($91.58 million) as part of a major overhaul to its domestic operations in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/fedex-cut-up-500-jobs-france-restructures-operations-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFXWALNKDNKIFI67HCI5PXQAUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果和戴尔的供应商和硕集团预计其美国工厂将于三月底前完工。]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾电子代工巨头和硕集团总裁兼首席执行官郑光志周五表示，该集团在得克萨斯州的首家美国工厂预计将于3月底完工，试产工作将在3月底或4月启动。【原文：Taiwanese contract electronics manufacturer Pegatron's first U.S. factory, in Texas, is expected to be ​completed by the end of March, with trial ‌production to begin around then or April, President and CEO Kuang-Chih Cheng said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-us-plant-be-completed-by-end-march-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4TLEZWUYFJ53NF6FIHI3OQFMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾期待亚利桑那州增加芯片投资，总统表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾期待亚利桑那州对半导体产业投入更多投资，以加强与美国的联系。台湾总统赖清德周五向到访的该州参议员如是表示。【原文：Taiwan looks forward to even more semiconductor investment in Arizona to bolster ties with the United States, President Lai Ching-te ​told a visiting senator from the state on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-looks-forward-more-chip-investment-arizona-president-says-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULP3RYOB3VMSROCYFCG2EKPNP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:24:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Euro zone business activity expands more slowly than expected in January]]></title><description><![CDATA[Euro zone business activity expanded more slowly than expected this month as weaker growth in the dominant services industry offset milder factory contraction, according to a survey, while price pressures picked up.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/euro-zone-business-activity-expands-more-slowly-than-expected-january-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XL36OIBZ5VPBXPQ5S4ZKUXRBIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CK Hutchison explores split sale of global ports, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[CK Hutchison is exploring a restructured sale of dozens of ports to a global consortium by breaking the transaction into smaller parcels with differing ownership structures, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ck-hutchison-explores-split-sale-global-ports-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4JFIK5S2VI5BEYEVYLR2RLUKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ericsson to continue job cuts, CEO says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Swedish telecoms equipment maker Ericsson expects to continue shedding jobs, CEO Börje Ekholm said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/ericsson-continue-job-cuts-ceo-says-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7WFE4LEF5L65AXOZO6KRU7GAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyundai Motor to recall nearly 84,000 US vehicles over instrument panel display failure, NHTSA says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hyundai Motor is recalling 83,877 vehicles in the U.S. as the instrument panel display may fail to show critical safety information, such as the speedometer or fuel gauge, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-recall-nearly-84000-us-vehicles-over-instrument-panel-display-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGNISQC3HRJWTMQXW5HO2XEDSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称中国最快下月推出液化天然气期货]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，中国最快将于下月推出境内上市、以人民币计价的液化天然气期货合约，此举将降低进口商在对冲价格波动时对西方的依赖。【原文：China is set to offer domestic-listed, yuan-denominated liquefied natural gas (LNG) futures contracts as soon as next month, people with knowledge of the matter said, reducing importer reliance on the West when hedging against price moves.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/china-offer-lng-futures-soon-next-month-sources-say-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDMP6HASMNJEDDRLJBFXM4BKIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 07:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对越南改革表示欢迎，但杜林的增长目标似乎难以实现]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家和分析师表示，他提出的在被称为"市场列宁主义"的模式下实现两位数增长的目标，看起来并不现实。【原文：Economists and analysts say his goal of double-digit growth under a model that has been called "market Leninism" looks unrealistic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/investors-cheer-vietnam-reforms-lams-growth-target-looks-elusive-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDCVW2PQWVIDLK5JE7KNU56XPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 07:16:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔股价暴跌，供应链困境阻碍业务复苏]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔股价周五暴跌12%，因该公司受限于供应链问题，难以满足数据中心芯片在人工智能领域的强劲需求，令押注其业务转型的投资者大失所望。【原文：Intel's shares plunged 12% on Friday after the company struggled to meet strong AI demand for ​data-center chips due to supply constraints, disappointing investors betting on its turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-frankfurt-listed-shares-slide-forecast-drops-short-estimates-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7P2CJMJG5BPU7KVVAIJZWA65W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 07:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国零售销售意外增长，进一步显示经济复苏迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国上月零售额意外增长，得益于强劲的线上销售。周五公布的数据显示，财政大臣瑞秋·里夫斯公布预算案后，经济复苏迹象进一步显现。【原文：British retail sales rose unexpectedly last month, helped by strong online sales, according to data published on Friday which added to signs of a pickup in the economy after finance minister Rachel Reeves' budget.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-retail-sales-show-unexpected-increase-december-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZHNMPTNXVJVXFTZICGJKJL5E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 07:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱立信利润超出市场预期，计划回购17亿美元股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电信设备制造商爱立信周五表示，计划通过股票回购向股东返还150亿瑞典克朗（约合17亿美元），此前该公司公布的季度营业利润超出市场预期。【原文：Swedish telecoms gear maker Ericsson said it planned to return 15 billion Swedish crowns ($1.7 billion) to shareholders through share repurchases as it beat quarterly operating earnings expectations on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ericssons-profit-beats-market-view-plans-17-billion-buyback-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDUPPMTUUZIW7EQVKW3VBNTJYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治分析在投资者中日益受到重视，因风险不断累积]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着资产管理公司和企业投资者寻求如何将战争、领土挑衅和全球政治风险纳入定价的最佳方式，对地缘政治分析的需求正在上升。【原文：Demand for geopolitical analysis is rising, as asset managers and corporate investors seek guidance on the best way to price in risk from wars, territorial saber-rattling and global political risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/geopolitical-analysis-rise-investors-risks-multiply-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKKDC4EL3JN7BCKMKWZGWNLIRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对委内瑞拉石油的控制可能引发与中国债务重组的对峙]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对委内瑞拉石油出口的管控已将本用于偿还中国债务的石油卷入其中，这为两大超级大国之间可能爆发的又一场对峙埋下伏笔，或将使这个南美国家摆脱债务违约困境的道路更加复杂。【原文：U.S. control of Venezuela's oil exports has ensnared barrels that had been servicing debt to China, lining up another potential showdown between the two superpowers that could further complicate the South American country's path out of default.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-control-venezuela-oil-risks-debt-restructuring-showdown-with-china-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PNDBW5R5FNTZJHDFZMBO7MNWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早盘竞价：特朗普北极闹剧令美元寒意袭人]]></title><description><![CDATA[汤姆·韦斯特布鲁克带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6NOVETCFFMEZNGBB36PY4PUJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 05:32:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚解除对Grok AI的封禁，因X平台已实施安全措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚通信监管机构周五表示，在社交媒体平台X实施额外安全措施后，该国用户已恢复访问Grok功能。【原文：Malaysia has restored access to Grok for its users after social media platform X implemented additional safety measures, its communications regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/malaysia-lifts-block-grok-ai-after-x-implements-safety-measures-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XHDMFUVOBI7VF6M2POAKAFQCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 05:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《金融时报》报道，在与华纳的竞争加剧之际，奈飞称派拉蒙的报价"经不起推敲"]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周五报道，奈飞联合首席执行官格雷格·彼得斯表示，该公司收购华纳兄弟探索公司影视制作部门的827亿美元要约正按计划推进，有望获得股东支持。他同时指出派拉蒙的竞购方案"经不起推敲"。【原文：Netflix co-chief executive Greg Peters said the company is on track to win the backing of Warner Bros Discovery shareholders for its $82.7 billion offer for the company's film and television studios, adding that Paramount's rival bid "doesn't pass the sniff test", the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-says-paramount-bid-doesnt-pass-sniff-test-warner-battle-intensifies-ft-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NG4T56SKVFKDDKRGXZ6SEPJWPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 05:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道称，Revolut放弃收购美国贷款机构的计划，转而寻求独立牌照。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周五报道，知情人士透露，英国Revolut公司已放弃收购美国贷款机构的计划，转而申请美国银行牌照。【原文：Britain's Revolut has scrapped plans to buy a U.S. lender and will instead apply for an American banking licence, Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/revolut-scraps-plans-buy-us-lender-favour-push-standalone-licence-ft-reports-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DR6XW6ISBJJCBGRCLW2KTX7KGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 05:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普获赠新款凯迪拉克座驾，空军一号专机即将启程]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普正在获得新的交通工具——陆地和空中都有。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is getting new transportation - on the ground and in the sky.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-gets-new-cadillac-ride-ahead-air-force-one-plane-way-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57XPZGNRMROQBIQDAFWUD47C5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:54:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[建筑科技公司EquipmentShare.com在美国IPO中筹集约7.47亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[建筑科技公司EquipmentShare.com周四在美国首次公开募股定价区间内完成定价，筹集资金7.473亿美元，凸显了初创企业寻求公开市场融资的强劲需求。【原文：Construction tech firm EquipmentShare.com priced its U.S. initial public offering within its indicated range on Thursday, ​raising $747.3 million and underscoring strong demand for startups looking ‌to tap public markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/construction-tech-firm-equipmentsharecom-raises-about-747-million-us-ipo-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5R26AQHMFJNZAXNEHNQIOLHRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行如预期维持利率不变，上调经济增长与通胀预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五维持利率不变，同时上调了经济和通胀预期，表明其准备继续提高目前仍处于低位的借贷成本。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady on Friday and raised its economic and inflation forecasts, signalling its readiness to continue hiking still-low borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/view-boj-keeps-rates-steady-expected-ups-growth-inflation-forecasts-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCF277I455N2XAN2C2WAGFQBNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:26:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行维持利率不变，上调经济增长与通胀预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五维持利率不变，同时上调了经济和通胀预期，表明其准备继续提高目前仍处于低位的借贷成本。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady on Friday and raised its economic and inflation forecasts, signalling its readiness to continue hiking still-low borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-keeps-rates-steady-raises-growth-inflation-forecasts-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2XFJORNHFJGJB6U2C6VRFN5TU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 03:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价反弹，因特朗普关于"舰队"驶向伊朗的言论引发供应担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周五反弹，此前美国总统唐纳德·特朗普再度对中东主要产油国伊朗发出威胁，引发市场担忧军事行动可能导致供应中断。【原文：Oil prices rebounded on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump renewed threats against major Middle Eastern producer Iran, raising concerns of military action that could disrupt supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rebound-after-trump-comments-armada-moving-iran-spur-supply-worries-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WHB6UC5SBOKVKWPA7OUS6TQJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 02:51:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市小幅上涨，日本央行利率决议前夕]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲早盘股市小幅上涨，日本央行即将召开最新政策会议，市场普遍预期其将维持利率不变。【原文：Stocks made tepid gains in early Asian trading on Friday ahead of the Bank of Japan's latest policy meeting, at which it is widely expected to keep rates on hold.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDXBTKJ35RMP5CYZG5B5BWWHF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:28:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元料创一年来最差单周表现，日元在日银决议前承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普总统对格陵兰岛的威胁及其突然转变令投资者感到不安后，美元正准备创下一年来最大单周跌幅；而日元在周五稍晚日本央行政策决定公布前，在接近一周低点附近徘徊。【原文：The U.S. dollar was poised for its biggest weekly drop in a year after President Donald Trump's Greenland threats and abrupt reversal unnerved investors, while the yen wobbled near one-week lows ahead of the Bank of Japan policy decision later on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-set-worst-week-year-yen-pressured-ahead-boj-2026-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GNGBJDWNBPMHOIM34O35YKVI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>