<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:16:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:15:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[ServiceNow to buy cybersecurity startup Armis for $7.75 billion]]></title><description><![CDATA[ServiceNow has agreed to buy cybersecurity startup Armis for $7.75 billion in cash, the companies said on Tuesday, as the enterprise software maker looks to attract new customers amid growing risks of cyberattacks.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/servicenow-buy-cybersecurity-startup-armis-775-billion-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WF52BBU2QFLJRFRIUZ6Y52UG7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US core capital goods orders, shipments increase in October]]></title><description><![CDATA[New orders for key U.S.-manufactured capital goods increased in October and shipments of these goods rose solidly, suggesting business spending on equipment remained strong at the start of the fourth quarter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-core-capital-goods-orders-shipments-increase-october-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VTACYXXUZLUBO5AYYHACEBVRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:58:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China's commerce ministry urges US to drop drone supplier ban]]></title><description><![CDATA[China's commerce ministry urged the U.S. on Tuesday to stop the "wrong practice" of adding all foreign-made drone systems and key components to its new "Covered List", and it vowed measures to protect the rights and interests of Chinese firms.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-commerce-ministry-urges-us-drop-drone-supplier-ban-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WULHGAQQXZP5PN2Z4BAK3POTKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:45:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 LandSpace 完成上海上市前的 "辅导 "流程]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国领先的民营火箭公司陆地空间（LandSpace）周二向中国证券监管机构提交的一份文件显示，该公司已经完成了可能进行首次公开募股的所谓 "辅导 "程序，中国政府希望通过促进资本市场的准入来推动国内航天产业的发展。【原文：China's leading private rocket firm LandSpace has completed the so-called "tutoring" process for a potential initial public offering, a filing with the country's securities regulator showed on Tuesday, as Beijing looks to boost the domestic space industry by faciliating access to its capital markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/chinas-landspace-completes-tutoring-process-ahead-shanghai-ipo-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IL6UEJ35ZRJHNPQZAYRX42YGL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:49:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威士卡和万事达卡报告美国假日零售额增长 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[据威士（Visa）和万事达（Mastercard）周二公布的初步数据显示，由于美国人在预算紧缩与渴望升级小工具和更新衣柜之间取得平衡，美国零售商的销售额在本假日季迄今已增长了约 4%。【原文：Sales for U.S. retailers have increased by about 4% so far this holiday season as Americans balanced tighter budgets with a desire to upgrade gadgets and refresh wardrobes, according to preliminary figures released by Visa and Mastercard on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/visa-mastercard-report-4-growth-us-holiday-retail-sales-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XIH6R5K44BLWLMSIITVWUQTW6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货在 GDP 数据公布前走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街期货周二走高，投资者在等待今年最后一批关键经济数据，以寻找可能重塑明年潜在降息预期的线索。【原文：Wall Street futures ticked higher on Tuesday as investors awaited the year's final batch of key economic data for clues that could reshape expectations for potential interest rate cuts next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/wall-st-futures-tick-higher-ahead-gdp-data-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MZZS4UK2NJMNBESB26WZTSFYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[创纪录的一年之后，散户投资者将对华尔街有更大的影响力]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，随着个人投资者成为美股反弹的主力军，2025 年美股的散户资金流入量将创下历史新高。【原文：Retail inflows into U.S. stocks are set to hit a record in 2025, as individual investors become a major force behind a rally that is likely to extend into the next year on hopes of interest rate cuts, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-investors-have-more-sway-over-wall-street-after-record-year-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEJMTW3EPFJWRHDEJRHKG6WOIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主要投资者称派拉蒙对华纳兄弟的新报价不够充分]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙天舞公司收购华纳兄弟发现公司的最新报价对著名股东哈里斯-奥克马克（Harris Oakmark）来说仍然不够好，这位投资者告诉路透社。【原文：Paramount Skydance's latest offer to buy Warner Bros Discovery still is not good enough for prominent shareholder Harris Oakmark, the investor told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/paramounts-new-offer-warner-bros-is-not-sufficient-major-investor-says-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IWUZMDNIJNVTDBKTTCEXXHPBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:08:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业在市场上收取几分钱，以收回部分关税成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[最高法院对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统全面征收紧急关税一案作出判决，一些美国公司正通过向外部投资者出售其收取政府可能退还的税款的权利来对冲风险。【原文：Some U.S. companies are hedging their bets on the Supreme Court case against President Donald Trump's sweeping emergency tariffs by selling their rights to collect potential government refunds of the taxes to outside investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/companies-collecting-pennies-dollar-market-recoup-some-tariff-costs-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M76HV2AD4BOKJASYPYV52T6V5U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能数据中心迫使过时的 "调峰 "电厂重新投入使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[在芝加哥的皮尔森（Pilsen）工人区，德沃夏克公园（Dvorak Park）后面的工业用地上耸立着一座 60 年代的燃油发电厂，天气暖和的时候，公园里挤满了在五颜六色的游乐场上攀爬和从滑梯上滑下来的孩子。【原文：In Chicago’s working-class Pilsen neighborhood, a 60s-era oil-fired power plant rises up from an industrial lot behind Dvorak Park, which in warmer weather is packed with children climbing on its colorful playground and zooming down slides.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ai-data-centers-are-forcing-obsolete-peaker-power-plants-back-into-service-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4T6HXQKIDVKXNK66E7ET6LODQE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据报道，WhatsApp 在俄罗斯的运行速度放缓，抱怨受到限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[WhatsApp 周二抱怨其在俄罗斯的服务受到限制，指责当局试图在节假日前剥夺 1 亿多俄罗斯人的私人通信权利。【原文：WhatsApp complained about restrictions to its service in Russia on Tuesday, accusing the authorities of trying to deprive more than 100 million Russians of the right to private communications before the holiday season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/whatsapp-complains-about-restrictions-russia-after-reported-slowdown-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4YG55RZANN4HCPMIXLBHSGABY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:54:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者如何购买黄金以及市场的推动因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，黄金徘徊在每盎司4,500美元大关附近，受美国货币政策宽松预期和地缘政治紧张局势挥之不去的影响，黄金价格屡创新高。【原文：Gold hovered within striking distance of the $4,500-an-ounce mark on Tuesday, buoyed by expectations of looser U.S. monetary policy and lingering geopolitical tensions that have driven the prices to a run of record highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-investors-buy-gold-what-fuels-market-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBC26QM6VZO2LK3AXDBUN2MVPE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:27:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年主要央行将推出十多年来最大力度的宽松政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025 年，主要央行以金融危机以来最快的速度和最大的规模下调了利率，而发展中国家决策者的宽松政策也加快了步伐。【原文：Major central banks have delivered interest rate cuts in 2025 at the fastest clip and largest scale since the financial crisis, while easing among policymakers in developing nations also accelerated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/major-central-banks-deliver-biggest-easing-push-over-decade-2025-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6CAHKEQXFKT3LCUWHQ2LPEIE4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:24:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称万科或将采用中国熟悉的方式应对债务危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[信贷分析师说，有国家支持的中国万科很可能会效仿其他一些资金紧张的中国开发商的策略，在最终提出债务重组之前，寻求多次短期延期偿还债券。【原文：State-backed China Vanke will likely mirror the strategies of some other cash-strapped Chinese developers and seek multiple short-term extensions for its bond repayments before ultimately proposing a debt restructuring, credit analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/vanke-may-adopt-familiar-playbook-china-tackle-debt-crisis-say-analysts-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLTW6KOXEFO4PI7QEO5NOFKI44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌干达在选举前几周限制进口星链设备]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌干达政府在全国大选前几周限制了 Starlink 卫星互联网设备的进口，反对派担心政府会在大选中再次实施互联网封锁。【原文：Uganda's government has restricted imports of Starlink satellite internet equipment weeks before a national election at which the opposition fears the government will again impose an internet blackout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/uganda-restricts-imports-starlink-equipment-weeks-before-election-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CFC7ZXRBBLQPOOSI4ANSXBYUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，丰田将因逆变器连接松动召回超过 5.5 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周二表示，丰田将在美国召回55,405辆汽车，原因是逆变器内的螺栓可能没有正确拧紧，导致逆变器终端接触不完全。【原文：Toyota is recalling 55,405 vehicles in the U.S. as bolt inside the inverter may not have been tightened properly, causing incomplete contact at the inverter terminal, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-recall-over-55000-us-vehicles-over-loose-inverter-connection-nhtsa-says-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7R3AC4DNRPE5N2TQSATVP3DGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，亚马逊旗下 Zoox 公司将因软件错误召回 332 辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周二表示，亚马逊的自动驾驶部门Zoox因自动驾驶系统（ADS）软件错误在美国召回332辆汽车。【原文：Amazon's self-driving unit Zoox is recalling 332 vehicles in the U.S. over an automated driving systems (ADS) software error, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/amazons-zoox-recall-332-us-vehicles-over-software-error-nhtsa-says-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DD2CBKXE4JKMBFS3GKCCOLYCDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子旗下哈曼公司将以 15 亿欧元收购采埃孚集团的 ADAS 业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子（Samsung Electronics）周二表示，该公司旗下的哈曼国际（Harman International）已同意以 15 亿欧元（17.7 亿美元）的价格收购德国汽车供应商采埃孚（ZF Friedrichshafen）的高级驾驶辅助系统（ADAS）业务。【原文：Samsung Electronics said on Tuesday its unit Harman International has agreed to acquire German automotive supplier ZF Friedrichshafen's advanced driver assistance system (ADAS) business for 1.5 billion euros ($1.77 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-elec-unit-harman-acquire-zf-groups-adas-business-15-bln-euros-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUY5YJX4PROODKG2A6WX7GE4NQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街担忧泡沫，全球投资者转向中国人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着华尔街对人工智能行业投机泡沫的担忧与日俱增，全球投资者正在加大对中国人工智能公司的投注，押注下一个 DeepSeek，并寻求多元化发展。【原文：Global investors are increasing their wagers on Chinese artificial intelligence companies, betting on the next DeepSeek and seeking to diversify, with concerns growing about a speculative bubble in the sector on Wall Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-investors-turn-chinese-ai-wall-street-fears-bubble-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBABIR7AGRNB7DEWWCUTDLG5Z4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 07:28:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国批准减肥药后，诺和诺德在法兰克福上涨近 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国食品和药物管理局批准诺和诺德公司生产减肥药后，该公司在法兰克福上市的股票周二早盘高开近10%。【原文：Novo Nordisk's Frankfurt-listed shares opened nearly 10% higher in early trading on Tuesday after the U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved its weight-loss pill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-up-nearly-10-frankfurt-after-us-approves-weight-loss-pill-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUMP7S4PZFIL5PLBLTAVOKODUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 07:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德的 Wegovy 药片将测试消费者对现金的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）新近获批的减肥药Wegovy将成为快速增长的现金支付消费市场的一个试验案例，计划于1月初直接进入美国自费渠道。【原文：Novo Nordisk's newly approved weight-loss pill version of Wegovy will be a test case for the fast-growing cash-paying consumer market, with plans for the first highly effective oral treatment to go straight to U.S. self-pay channels in early January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novos-wegovy-pill-test-demand-consumers-with-cash-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMKUACFSEBOXJCH6PNEE52ZMPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 06:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年的市场：黄金、金发姑娘和美元熊]]></title><description><![CDATA[大多数投资者都知道，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普重新掌权，这个世界上最大的经济体今年会有所不同，但很少有人预测到今年的走势会有多疯狂，或者最终的结果会如何。【原文：Most investors knew this year would be different given U.S. President Donald Trump's return to power in the world's biggest economy, but few predicted how wild the ride would get, or the end results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-performance-pix-graphics-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNJT5VJ3IBJM3KFWAFRL7WARBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 06:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车助力欧洲新车销量连续第五个月增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲汽车游说组织ACEA周二发布的数据显示，受德国、意大利和西班牙等市场电动汽车注册量增加的推动，11月份欧洲新车销量连续第五个月同比增长。【原文：New car sales in Europe rose year-on-year in November for a fifth consecutive month, helped by an increase in EV registrations in markets including Germany, Italy and Spain, data from the European auto lobby ACEA showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/new-car-sales-europe-rise-fifth-month-helped-by-evs-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGCKZ6KRPJINVMY76B24EXT6YQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:08:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲建筑股在创下历史新高后面临现实考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲建筑股是 2025 年涨幅最突出的股票之一，原因是围绕德国基础设施刺激政策、乌克兰重建希望和人工智能相关热潮的主题交易受到热捧。【原文：European construction shares have been among 2025's standout gainers, lifted by enthusiasm for thematic trades around Germany's infrastructure stimulus, hopes of Ukraine's rebuild and the AI-related boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/european-construction-stocks-face-reality-check-after-record-run-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTB5464D2NOGTLQWQHI4YEWDPM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度经济增长可能保持强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[在稳健的消费支出和企业投资的推动下，美国经济在第三季度可能实现了快速增长，但在生活成本上升和政府近期停摆的影响下，增长势头似乎有所减弱。【原文：The U.S. economy likely grew at a brisk clip in the third quarter, driven by solid consumer spending and business investment, but momentum appears to have since faded amid the rising cost of living and recent government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-economic-growth-likely-remained-strong-third-quarter-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4CSIJHOCJK6ROJBDVQTQHFMZM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚退休基金将购买悉尼 Westfield 购物中心 5.76 亿澳元的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚退休信托基金（ART）周二表示，将以 8.64 亿澳元（5.7568 亿美元）的价格收购 Scentre 集团旗下悉尼标志性购物中心 Westfield 近 20% 的股份。【原文：The Australian Retirement Trust (ART) will acquire a near 20% stake in Scentre Group's iconic Westfield Sydney shopping mall for A$864 million ($575.68 million), the shopping centre owner said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australian-retirement-fund-buy-576-million-stake-westfield-sydney-mall-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMWONXVKTZN77E3LVI6ABVXUTQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 04:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前日本央行决策者称，日本财政困境可能导致更多日元下跌和收益率上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[前央行决策者足立诚司告诉路透社，由于市场对政府扩张性财政政策的担忧，日本可能面临日元进一步下跌和债券收益率持续上升的局面。【原文：Japan may face further yen declines and a relentless rise in bond yields driven by market concern over the government's expansionary fiscal policy, former central bank policymaker Seiji Adachi told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-fiscal-woes-may-cause-more-yen-falls-yield-rises-says-ex-boj-policymaker-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APJZMFJCMVJ5BKPXVXFXHAQHR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 04:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[直播网络攻击后，中国瓜子网股价跌至近五周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一晚间，中国短视频平台酷爱秀遭遇网络攻击，周二股价下跌多达 6%，至 62.70 港元（8.06 美元），为 11 月 21 日以来最低。【原文：Shares of Kuaishou dropped by as much as 6% on Tuesday to HK$62.70 ($8.06), their lowest since November 21, after the Chinese short video platform was hit by a cyberattack on Monday night.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-kuaishou-shares-fall-near-five-week-low-after-livestreaming-cyberattack-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6E4PZKVGQFLLNIFHLWOKK3YMEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:59:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受网络攻击报告影响，中国瓜子网跌至近五周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，中国短视频平台周一遭遇网络攻击，导致露骨内容突然激增，瓜子二手车股价周二下跌多达 6%，至 62.70 港元（8.06 美元），创 11 月 21 日以来新低。【原文：Shares of Kuaishou Technology dropped by as much as 6% on Tuesday to HK$62.70 ($8.06), their lowest since November 21, after media reported that the Chinese short video platform experienced a sudden surge of explicit content because of a cyberattack on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-kuaishou-falls-near-five-week-low-report-cyberattack-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWQNBP3GJM2TN46Q7W6RRG5GA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市、贵金属上涨；日元受到干预观察]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市与贵金属齐涨，原因是投资者在节日假期前延续了买盘势头，预计当天晚些时候将公布美国国内生产总值（GDP）的预估数据。【原文：Asia shares rose alongside precious metals on Tuesday as momentum buying from investors extended ahead of the festive holidays, with an advanced reading on U.S. GDP expected later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGWUTPU52VM27GIUZ4V5QWOBP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 02:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>