<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:39:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:39:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[西门子将以 51 亿美元收购 Dotmatics]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子公司周三表示，将以 51 亿美元的价格从 Insight Partners 手中收购总部位于美国的 Dotmatics 公司。【原文：Siemens AG said on Wednesday it will acquire U.S.-based Dotmatics for $5.1 billion from Insight Partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siemens-acquire-dotmatics-51-billion-deal-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNXCEQTK75JCHNC25DHDBYHHJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦公报显示，特朗普 25% 的汽车关税将于美国东部时间 4 月 3 日上午 12:01 生效]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据《联邦公报》（Federal Register）上的一则公告，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）25%的汽车关税将于美国东部时间周四上午12:01生效。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's 25% automobile tariffs are due to take effect at 12:01 a.m. ET on Thursday, according to a post in the Federal Register.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-25-automobile-tariffs-due-take-effect-1201-am-et-april-3-federal-register-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QH3LRJ34ROQTAXJ7EM6KAIWYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:26:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普考虑取消对中国廉价货物的关税豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉计划的消息人士称，作为周三关税声明的一部分，特朗普政府正在考虑取消对来自中国的低价值货物的关税豁免。【原文：The Trump administration is considering revoking tariff exemptions for low-value shipments from China as part of Wednesday's tariff announcement, a source familiar with the plans said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-considering-revoking-tariff-exemptions-cheap-shipments-china-source-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHWPQW42V5NEBOUQTF4R7GOHHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官表示，波音正与司法部合作修改 737 MAX 欺诈案的认罪协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）周三表示，波音公司正在与美国司法部商讨，以就该公司涉嫌就737 MAX飞机上的一个关键系统向监管机构作出虚假陈述而引发的刑事欺诈案达成修订认罪协议。【原文：Boeing is in discussions with the U.S. Department of Justice to reach a revised plea agreement in a criminal fraud case stemming from the planemaker's alleged misrepresentations to regulators about a key system on the 737 MAX, company CEO Kelly Ortberg said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-working-with-doj-revised-plea-deal-737-max-fraud-case-ceo-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNDQN5YIHBIB5C37AWAKS276DQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:22:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GE Vernova 将在 2026 年之前为宾夕法尼亚州规划中的天然气发电厂提供涡轮机]]></title><description><![CDATA[GE Vernova 将提供七台涡轮机，生产近 4.5 千兆瓦（GW）的电力，从而帮助宾夕法尼亚州的霍默市发电站（以前是一家煤电厂）转变为以天然气为动力的数据中心园区。【原文：GE Vernova will aid in turning Homer City Generating Station — previously a coal-power plant in Pennsylvania — into a natural gas-powered data center campus by providing seven turbines to produce nearly 4.5 gigawatts (GW) of power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ge-vernova-supply-turbines-by-2026-planned-natgas-power-plant-pennsylvania-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OT3CJNFAYNOINCJIHM5S6ZPQAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OnlyFans 创始人和加密基金会提交收购 TikTok 的后期竞标书]]></title><description><![CDATA[由成人内容社交网站 OnlyFans 创始人蒂姆-斯托克利（Tim Stokely）运营的一家初创公司与一家加密货币基金会合作，提交了一份后期计划，准备从中国公司字节跳动手中收购短视频应用 TikTok。【原文：A startup run by Tim Stokely, founder of adult content social media site OnlyFans, has partnered with a cryptocurrency foundation to submit a late-stage plan to acquire short video app TikTok from Chinese owner ByteDance, the two said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/onlyfans-founder-crypto-foundation-submit-late-stage-bid-buy-tiktok-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWU7746B6FPOPNTLZLFCBMFXVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:35:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌双子座高管萧泓将卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周三对其人工智能部门的员工表示，将撤换领导人工智能聊天机器人 "巴德"（Bard）（现名 "双子座"）开发工作的萧泓（Sissie Hsiao）。【原文：Alphabet's Google is replacing Sissie Hsiao, who led the development of the artificial intelligence chatbot Bard, now known as Gemini, the company told staff in its AI division on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/google-gemini-executive-sissie-hsiao-step-down-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFW5SZCULBL25LPWKPUVWUWWPA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:31:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊计划于 4 月 9 日发射首批 Kuiper 互联网卫星]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周三表示，它计划在本月为其 "柯伊伯计划"（Project Kuiper）互联网网络发射首批27颗卫星，这是一个崭露头角的星座期待已久的时刻，它将对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）庞大的 "星链"（Starlink）系统构成最大的挑战。【原文：Amazon on Wednesday said it plans to launch this month the first 27 satellites for its Project Kuiper internet network, a long-awaited moment for a budding constellation that will pose the biggest challenge yet to Elon Musk's massive Starlink system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-targets-april-9-launch-first-kuiper-internet-satellites-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNWOIEACEVLQLICH7RNGQFYXOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:21:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局增加华盛顿机场的人员编制，可能会减缓航班抵达速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周三表示，在 1 月 29 日一架直升机与美国航空公司一架支线飞机相撞造成 67 人死亡后，可能会放慢里根华盛顿国家机场的航班到达速度。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday it may slow flight arrivals at Reagan Washington National Airport after a January 29 collision between a helicopter and an American Airlines regional jet that killed 67 people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-boosting-staffing-washington-airport-may-slow-arrivals-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROFAARXAWJN6LJUPGVR4TW66KQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PIMCO 加强对新兴市场政府的私人贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[债券巨头 PIMCO 新兴市场投资组合管理负责人周三表示，仅今年一年，PIMCO 就向新兴市场借款人（主要是政府）提供了近 60 亿美元的私人贷款，确保了更高的回报和更好的贷款人保护。【原文：Bond giant PIMCO has privately lent nearly $6 billion to emerging market borrowers, mostly governments, this year alone, securing higher returns and better lender protections, its head of emerging markets portfolio management said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/pimco-steps-up-private-lending-emerging-market-governments-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDOKLJIDXNKQDKOQ6EXWFFDYPA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：加拿大跨山输油管道下调石油运输量预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大跨山石油管道运营商提交的文件显示，由于新扩建管道的使用量增长速度低于预期，该公司下调了对未来三年预计流经其系统的石油量的预测。【原文：Canada's Trans Mountain oil pipeline has downgraded forecasts for the amount of oil expected to flow through its system over the next three years, documents filed by the operator show, as use of the newly expanded pipeline increases more slowly than expected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/canadas-trans-mountain-pipeline-lowers-forecasts-amount-oil-it-ships-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APJGFT4AUNPKREAJGY6A33CFCA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据报道使用 Gmail 后，白宫称华尔兹没有发送机密材料]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的国家安全顾问从未使用个人电子邮件帐户发送机密材料，此前有报道称迈克-华尔兹和其他国家安全委员会成员使用 Gmail 进行政府工作。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's national security adviser has never used his personal email account to send classified material, the White House said, following a report that Mike Waltz and other National Security Council members used Gmail for government work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-national-security-adviser-used-personal-email-white-house-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3WMYMBDZVJOTMVIAI3TF6K5XE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:20:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长维勒鲁瓦：特朗普关税不会导致欧洲通胀率下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行（ECB）决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周三表示，美国政府的关税上调不应破坏欧洲通胀率的持续下降。【原文：The U.S. administration's tariff hikes should not derail an ongoing decline in inflation in Europe, ECB policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Wednesday, adding that the fall boosted the case for a fresh interest rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/trump-tariffs-wont-derail-fall-european-inflation-ecbs-villeroy-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLZ5ULJ55FM7LLN3QF5QDP75DY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，亚马逊竞购 TikTok 的最后期限即将到来]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约时报》周三援引熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道，亚马逊公司已在最后一刻提出收购短视频应用 TikTok。【原文：Amazon.com has put in a last-minute offer to buy short-form video app TikTok, the New York Times reported on Wednesday, citing sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/amazon-has-bid-buy-tiktok-new-york-times-reports-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLEN7TBEEZN5ZEJXYQF5MFJ4YU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税颠覆日本汽车制造商的墨西哥赌局--日产汽车雪上加霜]]></title><description><![CDATA[长期以来，日本汽车制造商一直依靠其经济型汽车 "可靠、实惠 "的吸引力来推动美国汽车销量，这在一定程度上要归功于墨西哥的低成本生产。现在，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正在颠覆这种商业模式。【原文：Japanese automakers have long relied on the "dependable and affordable" appeal of their economy cars to drive U.S. sales, thanks in part to low-cost production in Mexico. Now, U.S. President Donald Trump is turning that business model on its head.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-tariffs-upend-japanese-carmakers-mexico-gambit-add-nissans-woes-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A33UU5BZNBOSDDVKWYT6CJYD34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:58:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府将啤酒和易拉罐进口产品纳入 25% 的美国铝关税征收范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周三修订了唐纳德-特朗普总统对衍生铝产品征收的25%关税，将所有啤酒和空铝罐进口产品也包括在内。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department on Wednesday revised President Donald Trump's 25% tariffs on derivative aluminum products to include all beer and empty aluminum can imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-administration-adds-beer-can-imports-25-us-aluminum-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGQIWOURR5LHBIBBWPL2URAMLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构暂停殖民地管道公司修改燃料运输条款的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦能源管理委员会发布命令，暂停 Colonial 管道公司对燃料运输条款的拟议修改，为期七个月。【原文：The Federal Energy Regulatory Commission issued an order to suspend Colonial Pipeline's proposed changes to fuel shipping terms for seven months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-regulator-suspends-colonial-pipelines-proposed-changes-fuel-shipping-terms-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKJOSBS4WBMDBH3PDKJL353OXY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:48:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，飞行员工会中断了有关汉莎航空裁员计划的谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉谈判情况的消息人士周三告诉路透社，VC 飞行员工会正在中断与汉莎航空就该公司核心品牌裁员建议的谈判，因为该工会认为汉莎航空对就业水平的承诺不够充分。【原文：The VC pilots union is breaking off talks with Lufthansa on proposed cuts at the airline's core brand because it believes the airline's commitments on employment levels are insufficient, sources familiar with the negotiations told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/pilots-union-breaks-off-talks-over-lufthansas-cuts-plans-sources-say-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KKOJR74KQBMHLJP4RN5KXDLKUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，欧盟将批准赛峰集团价值 18 亿美元的柯林斯项目交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据直接知情人士周三透露，欧盟反垄断监管机构将批准法国发动机和飞机设备制造商赛峰集团以 18 亿美元收购柯林斯宇航公司的飞行控制业务。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are set to approve French engine and aircraft equipment maker Safran's $1.8 billion bid for Collins Aerospace's flight controls business, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/eu-set-clear-safrans-18-billion-collins-deal-sources-say-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NP4EBGU6FZKCLKCTEIPJHCPX4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:25:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥总统表示不会与美国针锋相对地征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆周三表示，在唐纳德-特朗普总统宣布征收新关税的计划之前，墨西哥不打算对美国征收报复性关税。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Wednesday that Mexico doesn't plan to impose retaliatory tariffs on the United States, ahead of President Donald Trump's announcement of plans to impose new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-will-not-enter-tariff-tit-for-tat-with-us-president-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BAL5DDVKZIULI6ORJMEENFUZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道民主党人要求美国证券交易委员会保存与特朗普加密货币业务相关的记录，调查冲突问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[一对民主党高层议员周三要求美国证券监管机构保存与唐纳德-特朗普总统的加密货币企业世界自由金融公司（World Liberty Financial）有关的记录，并就潜在的利益冲突提出了问题。【原文：A pair of top Democratic lawmakers asked the U.S. securities regulator on Wednesday to preserve records related to President Donald Trump’s crypto venture World Liberty Financial and posed questions about potential conflicts of interest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/democrats-ask-sec-preserve-records-related-trumps-crypto-business-probing-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXHFHVB2GVLRDMKSNPLOW5FTIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称美国证券交易委员会反贿赂部门高官将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国证券交易委员会外国腐败行为部门的两位最高领导即将离职，而此时特朗普政府正在为反腐执法踩刹车。【原文：The top two leaders of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's foreign corrupt practices unit are leaving the agency, according to two people familiar with the matter, at a time when the Trump administration has been hitting the brakes on anti-corruption enforcement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-officials-leave-us-secs-anti-bribery-unit-sources-say-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDYCFZEIVZJE7NOCI5532C24CM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新的人工智能基准测试人工智能应用程序的运行速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能组织 MLCommons 公布了两项新基准，称它们有助于确定顶级硬件和软件运行人工智能应用的速度。【原文：Artificial intelligence group MLCommons unveiled two new benchmarks that it said can help determine how quickly top-of-the-line hardware and software can run AI applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/new-ai-benchmarks-test-speed-running-ai-applications-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFQNIMYWQRLKTITMHZPZPXITRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车充电公司联手推出欧洲最大网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的四家电动汽车充电公司周三表示，他们将联手打造欧洲大陆最大的公共充电网络。【原文：Four of Europe's biggest electric vehicle charging firms said on Wednesday they were teaming up to create the largest public charging network on the continent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-charging-firms-team-up-launch-europes-largest-network-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4F5DGOVAGFJDTMRXSN67OFRWZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长霍尔茨曼称潜在贸易战可能需要非常规货币政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）决策者罗伯特-霍尔兹曼（Robert Holzmann）周三表示，一旦美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布一系列新的关税措施，潜在的贸易战可能需要各国央行采取非常规政策。【原文：A potential trade war once U.S. President Donald Trump announces an array of new tariffs may require unconventional policies from central banks, European Central Bank policymaker Robert Holzmann said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecbs-holzmann-says-potential-trade-war-may-require-unconventional-monetary-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGG6UQRFYFKDXGUDWWN4GKOQA4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[里夫斯称英国不会因仓促应对关税而危及美国贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国财政大臣雷切尔-里夫斯（Rachel Reeves）表示，英国政府不会匆忙采取行动来应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三晚些时候宣布的任何进口关税，因为英国政府不想冒破坏与华盛顿可能达成的贸易协议的风险。【原文：Britain's government will not rush into action to counter any import tariffs announced later on Wednesday by U.S. President Donald Trump because it does not want to risk undermining a possible trade deal with Washington, finance minister Rachel Reeves said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/uk-wont-jeopardise-us-trade-talks-with-rushed-tariff-response-reeves-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXP4H3VJBVLMPCHWTXKOXMWTV4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丹麦马士基公司收购巴拿马运河铁路公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大堪萨斯城太平洋铁路公司周三表示，该公司和美国兰科集团已将巴拿马运河铁路公司出售给丹麦马士基公司旗下的一个部门，马士基公司是全球最大的集装箱航运集团之一。【原文：Canadian Pacific Kansas City said on Wednesday it and U.S.-based Lanco Group have sold the Panama Canal Railway Company to a unit of Denmark's Maersk , one of the world's largest container shipping groups.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/denmarks-maersk-buys-panama-canal-railway-company-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XK5LY2GBZRPGZEYM4TP7GCFCXM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称美国原油和馏分油库存上升，汽油库存下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周三称，上周美国原油和馏分油库存上升，而汽油库存下降。【原文：U.S. crude oil and distillate inventories rose while gasoline inventories fell last week, the Energy Information Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-stocks-distillate-inventories-rise-gasoline-stocks-fall-eia-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUQKOSJSDFPFXJR72T6XWJT77U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月份工厂订单稳健增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国制成品的新订单在 2 月份稳健增长，这很可能是因为企业在关税之前提前下达了订单。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods increased solidly in February, likely as businesses front-loaded orders ahead of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-factory-orders-rise-solidly-february-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKQWJPEOJNP6DKNYLN4LQBOTAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:29:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回美国食品及药物管理局（FDA）否决香精产品的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周三驳回了一项司法裁决，该裁决认定美国食品和药物管理局拒绝两家电子烟公司销售监管机构认为会对青少年健康造成危害的调味电子烟产品的行为是非法的。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court threw out on Wednesday a judicial decision that found the U.S. Food and Drug Administration acted unlawfully in refusing to let two e-cigarette companies sell flavored vape products that regulators consider a health risk to youths.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-supreme-court-tosses-ruling-faulting-fda-denying-flavored-vape-products-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSLRLJO6MVOS7AIDNS5CFA2FVM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>