<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 07:04:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 07:04:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[台湾官员称芯片业无需一国控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）批评台湾岛内的芯片主导地位后，台湾最高科技官员周六表示，半导体行业非常复杂，需要分工合作，没有必要由一个国家来控制。【原文：There is no need for one country to control the semiconductor industry, which is complex and needs a division of labour, Taiwan's top technology official said on Saturday after U.S. President Donald Trump criticised the island's chip dominance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/no-need-one-country-control-chip-industry-taiwan-official-says-2025-02-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7PT46PNKBJU7A2KVK5AXMP4RA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 05:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国季度文件显示，基金经理增持比特币 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据最近的监管文件，从财富管理公司到对冲基金和养老基金等资产管理公司都在2024年第四季度提高了与比特币价格挂钩的美国交易所交易基金的配置，因为这种世界上最大的加密货币的价格飙升了47%。【原文：Asset managers, ranging from wealth management companies to hedge funds and pension funds, boosted allocations to U.S. exchange-traded funds tied to the price of bitcoin in the fourth quarter of 2024, as the price of the world's largest cryptocurrency soared 47%, according to recent regulatory filings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fund-managers-boost-exposure-bitcoin-etfs-quarterly-us-filings-show-2025-02-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7GTHSRUSBLNJFZSXRZMESCBFQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton 赢得股东对座椅支柱召回诉讼的撤诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Peloton Interactive 公司周五赢得了一项拟议的股东集体诉讼的撤诉，该诉讼指控这家健身器材制造商隐瞒了与安全有关的问题，导致 2023 年 5 月召回了 220 万辆自行车，因为有报告称这些自行车的座杆存在缺陷。【原文：Peloton Interactive on Friday won the dismissal of a proposed shareholder class action lawsuit accusing the fitness equipment maker of concealing safety-related problems that led to a May 2023 recall of 2.2 million bikes following reports of defective seat posts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/peloton-wins-dismissal-shareholder-lawsuit-over-seat-post-recall-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHJKLLG6WVIU3FMPWP3ADJMKSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿克曼的公司在第四季度增持耐克，减持 Chipotle]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的一份监管文件显示，亿万富翁投资者威廉-阿克曼（William Ackman）在第四季度增持了体育用品公司耐克（Nike）15%的股份，并减持了快餐连锁店墨西哥烤肉店（Chipotle Mexican Grill）14%的股份。【原文：Billionaire investor William Ackman increased his stake in sportswear company Nike by 15% and cut his investment in fast-casual food chain Chipotle Mexican Grill by 14%, during the fourth quarter, according to a regulatory filing made on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ackmans-firm-boosts-stake-nike-cuts-chipotle-during-q4-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GE2MVUWGS5OI7LZYFCZZIETYF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:56:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普和马斯克的裁员对美国机构的影响有多大？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）和他最亲密的顾问之一、亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）发起了一场大刀阔斧的运动，以削减 230 万联邦员工的规模，本周至少解雇了 9,500 名员工，这一史无前例的努力没有任何放缓的迹象。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump and billionaire Elon Musk, one of his closest advisers, have mounted a sweeping campaign to slash the size of the 2.3 million-strong federal workforce, firing at least 9,500 employees this week in an unprecedented effort that shows no sign of slowing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-hard-have-us-agencies-been-bit-by-trump-musks-layoffs-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPLLZC2V3RPRDN47HHU2QAWKQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车关闭在华工厂作为重组的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[据通用汽车公司一位消息人士透露，该公司将于本月关闭位于中国东北部城市沈阳的一家工厂，这也是该公司在华重组的一部分。【原文：General Motors is closing a plant this month in the northeastern Chinese city of Shenyang as part of the U.S. automaker's restructuring in China, according to a company source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-closing-plant-china-part-restructuring-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5Z55FNTINNCLP7YO7CJRN7SCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:45:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通预计其 DEI 政策将受到批评]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周五向监管机构提交的文件显示，摩根大通预计其一些业务实践将面临批评，其中包括多元化、公平和包容性（DEI）。【原文：JPMorgan Chase expects to face criticism on some of its business practices, including diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI), according to its regulatory filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-expects-criticism-over-its-dei-policy-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFDNE75LTRLJBMUCYONROFTMKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马修斯宣布治理变革，董事会斗争投票迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[马修斯国际公司（Matthews International）周五宣布了一系列公司治理改革措施，目的是在股东在激烈的董事会投票前不到一周的时间里，推高这家棺材制造商的股价。【原文：Matthews International on Friday announced a number of corporate governance changes aimed at pushing up the casket maker's stock price less than a week before shareholders cast votes in a bitter boardroom battle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/matthews-announces-governance-changes-vote-boardroom-fight-looms-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2B6PK4FXZRK55L2HGBUPMDBR2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普继续加征关税，下一个目标是汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五继续发出关税威胁，称最快将于 4 月 2 日对汽车征收关税。【原文：President Donald Trump on Friday kept alive his drumbeat of tariff threats, saying levies on automobiles would be coming as soon as April 2, the day after members of his cabinet are due to deliver reports to him outlining options for a range of import duties as he seeks to reshape global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-keeps-tariffs-drumbeat-going-with-autos-targeted-next-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2FMHHREUZJJXLGIMSXU6RGI65E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 董事会拒绝马斯克 974 亿美元的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周五拒绝了亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）领导的财团以 974 亿美元收购这家 ChatGPT 制造商的出价，称这家初创公司是非卖品。【原文：OpenAI on Friday rejected a $97.4 billion bid from a consortium led by billionaire Elon Musk for the ChatGPT maker, saying the startup is not for sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-board-rejects-musks-974-billion-offer-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RO7RLSPUIRLVBCCSFW6LLRGSKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔收购星座品牌，减持大型银行股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周五披露了对酒精饮料生产商星座品牌公司（Constellation Brands）的新投资，并表示已经减持了花旗集团和美国银行的股票。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway on Friday disclosed a new investment in alcoholic beverages producer Constellation Brands , and said it has reduced its holdings in Citigroup and Bank of America .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/berkshire-buys-constellation-brands-cuts-big-bank-holdings-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QTR7JUHN5OORJGP2DKT3THX3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官将于 4 月 2 日在美国参议院商务小组作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商业委员会主席、共和党参议员特德-克鲁兹（Ted Cruz）周五表示，波音公司首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）将于4月2日在该委员会作证。【原文：Boeing CEO Kelly Ortberg will testify on April 2 before the U.S. Senate Commerce Committee, the panel's chair, Republican Senator Ted Cruz, said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-ceo-testify-before-us-senate-commerce-panel-april-2-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBIFEK7O5JKVZNKVM3WO63AKVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根呼吁即使通胀降温也要谨慎对待降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周五重申了她的观点，即即使未来几个月通胀率接近美联储2%的目标，美国央行也不一定要降低短期借贷成本作为回应。
"洛根在南卫理公会大学（Southern Methodist University）于加利福尼亚州棕榈沙漠（Palm Desert）举办的银行业会议上说："我认为，目前货币政策的限制性程度确实存在问题。"因此，我认为我们需要谨慎行事。【原文：Dallas Federal Reserve Bank President Lorie Logan on Friday reiterated her view that even if inflation nears the Fed's 2% goal in coming months, the U.S. central bank should not necessarily reduce short-term borrowing costs in response.
"I think there's a real question about how restrictive monetary policy is right now," Logan said at a banking conference hosted by Southern Methodist University in Palm Desert, California. "And so I think we need to be cautious."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-logan-calls-caution-rate-cuts-even-if-inflation-cools-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXMZEQJTSVPPBBKBFKHXDBVWFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Axios 报道，TikTok 竞标者直接与白宫而非 ByteDance 交谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Axios 周五报道，有意收购短视频应用 TikTok 的竞标者正直接与白宫而非其中国所有者字节跳动进行谈判。【原文：Bidders interested in buying the short-video app TikTok are talking directly with the White House, and not with its Chinese owner ByteDance, Axios reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-bidders-talk-directly-with-white-house-not-bytedance-axios-reports-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63ANN6UFVBK3XJMRDEQQUBJYUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:14:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官延长埃隆-马斯克的 DOGE 进入财政部系统的期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一名美国法官延长了对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的政府成本削减团队（被称为 DOGE）的临时禁令，禁止其访问负责数万亿美元支付的财政部系统。【原文：A U.S. judge on Friday extended a temporary block on Elon Musk's government cost-cutting team, known as DOGE, from accessing Treasury Department systems responsible for trillions of dollars in payments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-extends-block-elon-musks-doge-accessing-treasury-systems-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGBDI4W7GJNTLFPSQY5MGRBSP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，对冲基金维京买入波音股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五提交的一份监管文件显示，总部位于美国的对冲基金维京全球（Viking Global）在第四季度对飞机制造商波音公司建立了价值 5.26 亿美元的新头寸，持有 290 万股。【原文：U.S.-based hedge fund Viking Global built a $526 million-worth new position in planemaker Boeing in the fourth quarter, with 2.9 million shares, a regulatory filing showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/hedge-fund-viking-buys-boeing-shares-filing-shows-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOMFY5J6QVKCJAVBFXAISPTFDA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:49:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对美国收益率的关注助长了对银行杠杆率规则审查的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府承诺控制美国长期国债收益率，这增强了债券市场的预期，即人们期待已久的银行杠杆率要求监管转变可能最终迫在眉睫。【原文：The Trump administration's pledge to contain long-term U.S. Treasury yields has strengthened bond market expectations that a long-desired regulatory shift on bank leverage requirements could be finally looming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-focus-us-yields-fuels-bets-bank-leverage-rule-review-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXNLRMM2G5IXXPEHWIIUCK7Q4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示不介意新日铁持有美国钢铁公司少数股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他不介意日本新日铁公司持有美国钢铁公司的少数股份。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday said he wouldn't mind if Japan's Nippon Steel took a minority stake in U.S. Steel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-says-he-wouldnt-mind-if-nippon-steel-took-minority-stake-us-steel-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FSR6YVGUVOJJLYHPVBZQOEIZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将于 4 月 2 日前后征收汽车关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他计划在 4 月 2 日前后对进口汽车征收关税。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday he plans to impose tariffs on imported cars around April 2.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-auto-tariffs-coming-around-april-2-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOKEATH6W5IKTEOWVL7PGHJZYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登停摆后，特朗普政府开始批准液化天然气出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周五表示，已批准路易斯安那州英联邦液化天然气公司（Commonwealth LNG）出口液化天然气，这是继去年年初前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）暂停出口液化天然气后，首次批准出口这种资源。【原文：The administration of President Donald Trump said on Friday it has granted a license to export liquefied natural gas for Commonwealth LNG in Louisiana, the first approval of exports of the resource after former President Joe Biden paused them early last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-administration-begins-approve-lng-exports-after-biden-pause-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKU7L6EXSBKNLEMZBFTXYE44M4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道：应特朗普团队要求，台积电考虑运营英特尔美国工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，应美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）官员的要求，台湾合约制造商台积电正在考虑控股芯片制造商英特尔（Intel）的工厂。【原文：Taiwanese contract manufacturer TSMC is considering taking a controlling stake in chipmaker Intel's factories at the request of U.S. President Donald Trump's officials, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-considering-running-intels-us-factories-after-trump-team-request-bloomberg-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NLQXFAOZFLZ7HNFKQT6Y73W2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，马斯克的 xAI 公司正在洽谈以 750 亿美元估值融资 100 亿美元的事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引一位熟悉内情的人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 xAI 公司正在讨论融资 100 亿美元，这将使这家人工智能初创公司的估值达到约 750 亿美元。【原文：Elon Musk's xAI is discussing to raise $10 billion that could value the artificial intelligence startup at about $75 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/musks-xai-talks-raise-10-billion-75-billion-valuation-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F26YSE2GQVJYFKB6J2AJ7GDNL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西淡水河谷公司确认 2030 年前将向卡拉哈斯综合体投资 120 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷周五证实，该公司将在 2030 年前对其位于巴西北部的 Carajas 综合企业投资 700 亿雷亚尔（合 122.6 亿美元）。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale confirmed on Friday that it will invest 70 billion reais ($12.26 billion) in its Carajas complex in northern Brazil through 2030.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazils-vale-confirms-12-billion-investment-carajas-complex-through-2030-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIKSTH6O6FLI7KE7KOBUM5C7H4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，美国银行聘请摩根大通前高管加强私人银行业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份内部备忘录显示，美国银行已聘请摩根大通资深人士迈克-马里诺（Mike Marino）担任其私人银行乔治亚州市场主管。【原文：Bank of America has hired JPMorgan Chase veteran Mike Marino as the Georgia market executive of its private bank, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-hires-former-jpmorgan-executive-strengthen-private-bank-memo-says-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4QEM7GD55NUVESSPGQ7WKP6J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:34:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：戴尔接近达成向 xAI 出售 50 亿美元人工智能服务器的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，戴尔科技公司即将达成一项价值超过 50 亿美元的交易，为埃隆-马斯克的 xAI 公司提供为人工智能工作优化的服务器。【原文：Dell Technologies is nearing a deal worth more than $5 billion to provide Elon Musk's xAI with servers optimized for artificial intelligence work, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/dell-nears-deal-sell-5-billion-ai-servers-xai-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UILIAKTA2JPO5NLAMOSOTBR5GA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:20:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钻井商连续第三周增加油气钻机 - 贝克休斯]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第三周增加石油和天然气钻机，这是自2023年12月以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week added oil and natural gas rigs for a third week in a row for the first time since December 2023, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-drillers-add-oil-gas-rigs-third-week-row-baker-hughes-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NBQYK5CK5NQZASVAJZB6O5Y7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[桥水增持特斯拉股份，减持 "华丽 7 号 "其他股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份监管文件显示，对冲基金巨头桥水联合公司（Bridgewater Associates）第四季度在其投资组合中增持了特斯拉股票，同时削减了对美国科技股和成长股 "华丽七雄 "中其他股票的投资。【原文：Hedge fund giant Bridgewater Associates added shares of Tesla to its portfolio in the fourth quarter, while it trimmed exposure to the rest of the "Magnificent Seven" group of U.S. tech and growth stocks, a regulatory filing showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bridgewater-adds-tesla-stake-reduces-rest-magnificent-7-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAZLSMPV75N5VJV2V3DCZIUXQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，Meta 计划投资人工智能驱动的仿人机器人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五浏览的一份公司内部备忘录显示，Meta Platforms 公司正在其现实实验室（Reality Labs）部门内成立一个新的部门，开发人工智能驱动的仿人机器人，以协助完成体力劳动。【原文：Meta Platforms is establishing a new division within its Reality Labs unit to develop AI-powered humanoid robots that can assist with physical tasks, according to an internal company memo viewed by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/meta-plans-investments-into-ai-driven-humanoid-robots-memo-shows-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDWYQKWNTROTNIM4HV3DD7S6SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：对冲基金 Citadel 看空葛兰素史克]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，亿万富翁肯-格里芬（Ken Griffin）的对冲基金 Citadel 已持有英国制药商葛兰素史克的空头头寸。【原文：Billionaire Ken Griffin's hedge fund Citadel has taken a short position in British drugmaker GSK , the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hedge-fund-citadel-takes-short-position-gsk-ft-reports-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R274L32SBRJEPBX7AEPQPK4C7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，欧盟将无条件批准诺基亚价值 23 亿美元的英飞朗交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周五透露，欧盟反垄断监管机构将无条件批准诺基亚以 23 亿美元收购美国光半导体和网络设备制造商英飞朗。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are set to clear without conditions Nokia's $2.3 billion acquisition of U.S. optical semiconductors and networking equipment maker Infinera , people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/eu-set-clear-nokias-23-bln-infinera-deal-without-conditions-sources-say-2025-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REJ2YXOJTZMDNENHQDZAMF2X44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>