<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:37:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:37:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州黑客将对 PowerSchool 数据泄露事件认罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州一名男子同意认罪，承认黑客入侵云教育软件提供商 PowerSchool 并窃取了数百万学生和教师的相关数据，黑客利用这些数据勒索该公司和学区支付赎金。【原文：A Massachusetts man has agreed to plead guilty to hacking cloud-based education software provider PowerSchool and stealing data pertaining to millions of students and teachers that hackers used to extort the company and school districts into paying ransoms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/massachusetts-hacker-plead-guilty-powerschool-data-breach-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3KIA77VLNLGDORH4DT2DFOO3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:11:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席博斯蒂克：美国经济可能正处于加息潮的边缘]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联储主席拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周二表示，美国企业可能已经用完了推迟改变价格或就业以应对进口税提高的策略，经济可能处于价格上涨浪潮的边缘。【原文：U.S. businesses may have run out of strategies to delay changing prices or employment in response to higher import taxes, with the economy possibly on the brink of a wave of price increases, Atlanta Federal Reserve President Raphael Bostic said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economy-may-be-brink-price-hike-wave-feds-bostic-says-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWJGEO7KQBN5PFHPMSLKA5VMGE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:35:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪下调评级波及债券市场，引发股市担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪下调美国债务评级引发了投资者的担忧，他们可能会重新评估对美国政府债券的偏好，而收益率的上升可能会给估值较高的股票带来压力。【原文：Moody's U.S. debt downgrade is raising concerns that investors could reevaluate their appetite for U.S. government bonds, with the potential for rising yields to put pressure on stocks that are trading at elevated valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/moodys-downgrade-ripples-through-bond-market-causes-worries-stocks-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKEX2W22AZN3LIMVLHHSEAJUEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险经纪公司 Acrisure 在贝恩资本领投的新一轮融资中估值 320 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Acrisure 首席执行官周二告诉路透社记者，该公司已从贝恩资本和其他投资者处筹集到 21 亿美元，公司估值达 320 亿美元，这使其能够为向核心保险经纪业务以外的产品扩张提供资金。【原文：Acrisure has raised $2.1 billion from Bain Capital and other investors, its CEO told Reuters on Tuesday, valuing the firm at $32 billion and allowing it to fund an expansion into products beyond its core insurance brokerage business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/insurance-broker-acrisure-valued-32-billion-funding-round-led-by-bain-capital-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CI7MCV63VJSPMILIHMG2E4PZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国芯片制造商英飞凌将与英伟达合作开发电源传输芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国芯片制造商英飞凌（Infineon）周二表示，将与英伟达（Nvidia）合作开发用于人工智能数据中心内新型电力传输系统的芯片。【原文：German chipmaker Infineon said on Tuesday it will work with Nvidia on developing chips for new power delivery systems inside artificial intelligence data centers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/german-chipmaker-infineon-work-with-nvidia-power-delivery-chips-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLJPXHAT4VLC7C3BQNB4U2VWJE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克说，特斯拉将于 6 月底在得克萨斯州奥斯汀市启动机器人出租车试验项目。]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周二表示，机器人轴测试将于 6 月底在德克萨斯州奥斯汀如期开始。【原文：Tesla Chief Executive Elon Musk on Tuesday said a test of robotaxis would begin on schedule in Austin, Texas by the end of June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-says-tesla-is-track-launch-robotaxi-trial-austin-texas-by-end-june-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIDU5IBESVOF3EABTA6XEKSR44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:25:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称美国将宣布削减纽瓦克航班以减少拥堵]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空公司官员周二表示，美国运输部将于周二宣布，在与美国主要航空公司举行会议以解决拥堵影响问题后，将继续临时削减纽瓦克机场的航班。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department will announce on Tuesday that it is moving forward with temporary cuts to flights at Newark after meetings with major U.S. airlines to address congestion impacts, airline officials said Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-set-announce-newark-flight-cuts-reduce-congestion-officials-say-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7YRZTIP6NJMRPDIEJKY7EIG7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:14:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoma Bravo 的 Nearmap 将以超过 13 亿美元的价格收购保险科技公司 itel]]></title><description><![CDATA[Thoma Bravo 支持的 Nearmap 公司周二表示，该公司已同意从私募股权公司 GTCR 手中收购保险技术提供商 itel，以扩大其在房地产投资组合方面的服务。【原文：Thoma Bravo-backed Nearmap has agreed to buy insurance technology provider itel from private equity firm GTCR, the companies said on Tuesday, as it looks to expand its offerings across property portfolios.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/thoma-bravos-nearmap-buy-insurance-tech-firm-itel-over-13-billion-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3E6CKHJBBNT7HX75JCG3LQAWI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨莱姆：政策不确定性对经济前景有 "重大 "影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周一表示，特朗普政府的贸易和其他政策的高度不确定性可能会导致经济大幅放缓，因为家庭和企业在等待更加明朗的前景时会暂缓支出和投资决策。【原文：High uncertainty over the Trump administration's trade and other policies could slow the economy significantly as households and businesses put spending and investment decisions on hold while they wait for more clarity, St. Louis Federal Reserve Bank president Alberto Musalem said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-musalem-policy-uncertainty-has-meaningful-impact-economic-outlook-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5OOTVA4RRPLRGCKLIX4ODMDFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司称美国法院批准重组计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司周二表示，其破产保护程序下的重组计划已获美国法院批准。【原文：Brazilian airline Gol said on Tuesday its restructuring plan under Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings has been approved by a U.S. court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazilian-airline-gol-says-us-court-approves-restructuring-plan-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIVJ44N7TNMBDPZANNZB3S5NVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨勒姆称，如果贸易紧张局势持久缓和，利率可能保持不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周二表示，即使在中美贸易缓和之后，劳动力市场看起来仍有可能走弱，物价也有可能走高，但只要公众继续预期通胀率将降至美国中央银行2%的目标，针对这一具有挑战性的组合采取平衡的货币政策对策仍然是 "可行的"。【原文：Even after the U.S. and China trade detente, the labor market looks likely to weaken and prices to head higher, but as long as the public continues to expect inflation to fall to the U.S. central bank's 2% goal, a balanced monetary policy response to that challenging mix remains "feasible," St. Louis Federal Reserve President Alberto Musalem said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-musalem-says-rates-could-stay-put-if-trade-tensions-are-durably-de-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DUWKNELUZLRXPYIBVBLF6XIWQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:29:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息称中国五矿要求刚果解除钴出口禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士告诉路透社，世界顶级钴矿公司中国五矿集团上周呼吁刚果民主共和国解除对电池金属的出口禁令，该禁令目前将于下月到期。【原文：China's CMOC Group , the world's top cobalt mining company, called on Democratic Republic of Congo last week to lift a ban on exports of the battery metal, which is currently due to expire next month, three sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-cmoc-calls-congo-lift-cobalt-export-ban-sources-say-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HO7WREC3H5K65JWLFMP222FT7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:18:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果将向开发者开放其人工智能模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道称，苹果公司正准备允许第三方开发人员使用其人工智能模型编写软件，以推动新应用的开发。【原文：Apple is preparing to allow third-party developers to write software using its artificial intelligence models, in a push to boost the creation of new applications, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-open-its-ai-models-developers-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXBVWGAUE5NOTM62ZDSMDHL6DM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁仍致力于全面收购美国钢铁公司 - 高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新日铁仍致力于收购美国钢铁公司的全部股份，一位高级管理人员表示，该公司正在寻求与美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）会面，以澄清唐纳德-特朗普总统对这一交易的立场。【原文：Japan's Nippon Steel remains committed to acquiring a full stake in U.S. Steel , a senior executive said, adding that it is seeking a meeting with U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent to clarify President Donald Trump's stance on the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nippon-steel-still-committed-full-us-steel-takeover-executive-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EUZYNRXKJORRKVFD2W3JMO2LU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）支持的工作室 Promise 与谷歌合作开发人工智能，并增加了投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[由风险投资公司安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）支持的生成式人工智能工作室 Promise 周二表示，它已与 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司合作，使用其人工智能技术。【原文：Generative AI studio Promise, backed by venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz, said on Tuesday that it had partnered with Alphabet's Google to use its AI technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/andreessen-horowitz-backed-studio-promise-partners-with-google-ai-adds-investors-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTOB6WXGRBOYZNESETQRY4VKAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易小组的投票为对许多太阳能进口产品征收严格关税铺平了道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国际贸易委员会（U.S. International Trade Commission）周二认定，来自东南亚四国的大量廉价进口商品对美国国内太阳能电池板制造商造成了实质性损害或威胁，从而使美国向对这些商品征收严厉关税的目标又迈近了一步。【原文：The U.S. International Trade Commission determined on Tuesday that domestic solar panel makers were materially harmed or threatened by a flood of cheap imports from four Southeast Asian nations, bringing the United States a step closer to imposing stiff duties on those goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-trade-panels-vote-paves-way-stiff-tariffs-many-solar-imports-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APBCMGQDV5O37NZDI75X6TGEOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将在其 GitHub 服务中添加 Anthropic 的人工智能编码代理]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软表示，将在其 GitHub 服务中添加谷歌支持的初创公司 Anthropic 的人工智能编码代理。【原文：Microsoft said it will add an artificial intelligence coding agent from Google-backed startup Anthropic to its GitHub service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-add-anthropics-ai-coding-agent-its-github-service-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WK47HKGSVRPVTKHYRWCHSVYJBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街监管机构为大幅裁员辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）新任主席保罗-阿特金斯（Paul Atkins）周二向国会表示，尽管该机构最近大幅削减了人员编制，但华尔街的最高监管机构仍有能力监管市场。【原文：Wall Street's top regulator remains capable of policing markets despite steep recent cuts to agency staffing, Paul Atkins, the newly installed chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, told Congress on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/wall-st-regulator-defends-steep-staff-cuts-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAWXBLJWJRKAJOQRPPWSJDKIBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管奢侈品市场波澜不惊，香奈儿仍将继续投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国奢侈品集团香奈儿（Chanel）周二表示，尽管中国和美国市场动荡不安，但香奈儿今年仍将利用其雄厚的资金继续大力投资，并计划在中国和美国开设新店。【原文：French luxury group Chanel will continue to invest heavily this year, drawing on its deep pockets as other sector players pull back, with plans for new stores in China and the United States, despite volatility in both markets, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chanel-keep-investing-despite-choppy-luxury-market-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4VN7VDGWBOUDGGYXEMYKQZVXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院将于本周就禁止加州 2035 年电动车计划的法案进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院多数党领袖约翰-图恩（John Thune）周二表示，美国参议院计划在本周进行投票，禁止加利福尼亚州到 2035 年停止销售纯汽油车的里程碑式计划，该计划已被其他 11 个州采纳。【原文：The U.S. Senate plans to vote this week to bar California's landmark plan to end the sale of gasoline-only vehicles by 2035 that has been adopted by 11 other states, Majority Leader John Thune said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-senate-vote-this-week-bill-bar-california-2035-ev-plan-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASAWXKXALBM23DLL4NM6TTTAXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:43:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员就《60 分钟》试图与特朗普和解一事质询派拉蒙公司的雷德斯通]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一群参议员致信派拉蒙全球董事长莎莉-雷德斯通，希望了解哥伦比亚广播公司新闻频道（CBS News）所有者为解决与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的诉讼所做的努力。【原文：A group of senators sent a letter to Paramount Global chair Shari Redstone on Monday, seeking information about the CBS News owner's efforts to settle a lawsuit with U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/senators-question-paramounts-redstone-over-60-minutes-settlement-attempts-with-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R73STBPD2NLZFG2QEQZXKBVAOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:41:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[天气将影响俄罗斯最大谷物产区的收成]]></title><description><![CDATA[当地谷物游说团体负责人在宣布农业紧急状态后表示，未来几个月的高温和缺雨天气预计将导致俄罗斯最大的谷物产区罗斯托夫的收成减少。【原文：High temperatures and a lack of rain over the coming months are expected to deplete the harvest in Russia's largest grain region Rostov, the head of the local grain lobby group said after a farming emergency was declared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/weather-set-hit-harvest-russias-largest-grain-region-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORZWQN7SWRI2TBIKAXDVIS6G6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚亿万富翁的公司增持股份后，维多利亚的秘密采取 "毒丸 "措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[在澳大利亚亿万富翁布雷特-布伦迪（Brett Blundy）的投资公司增持这家内衣制造商的股份后，维多利亚的秘密（Victoria's Secret）周二通过了一项股东权利计划。【原文：Victoria's Secret adopted a shareholder rights plan on Tuesday, after Australian billionaire Brett Blundy's investment firm increased its stake in the lingerie maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/victorias-secret-adopts-poison-pill-after-australian-billionaires-firm-raises-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWPELFZ55FJ43FSV4BKGXVTKLA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道哈萨克斯坦 5 月石油产量增长 2%，与欧佩克（OPEC+）分庭抗礼]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位业内人士周二表示，哈萨克斯坦 5 月份的石油产量增长了 2%，这一增长无视欧佩克+组织（OPEC+）要求中亚国家减产的压力。【原文：Kazakhstan's oil production has risen by 2% in May, an industry source said on Tuesday, an increase that defies pressure from OPEC+ on the Central Asian country to reduce its output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/kazakhstans-oil-output-rises-2-may-defiance-opec-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNOV4JCA7JOXPAXNJ47JPNKC7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克表示 5 年后仍将担任特斯拉首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周二在卡塔尔的一个经济论坛上表示，他仍致力于在五年内担任特斯拉公司首席执行官。【原文：Elon Musk said on Tuesday at an economic forum in Qatar that he was still committed to being Tesla CEO in five years' time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/elon-musk-says-he-is-still-committed-being-tesla-ceo-5-years-time-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K25SJATYMBIQJIOTWFNFAAE3DA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:41:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[员工奖励公司 Awardco 在最新一轮融资后估值达 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[员工奖励平台 Awardco 周二表示，该公司在由投资公司 Sixth Street Growth 和 Spectrum Equity 领投的一轮融资中筹集了 1.65 亿美元，使其估值超过 10 亿美元。【原文：Employee-rewards platform Awardco said on Tuesday it has raised $165 million in a funding round led by investment firms Sixth Street Growth and Spectrum Equity, pushing its valuation to more than $1 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/employee-rewards-company-awardco-secures-1-billion-valuation-after-latest-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRGHOLDNPBP2NH7SUBD6D6J4UM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面临搜索挑战，谷歌将在 I/O 大会上发布人工智能升级版]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司（Google）将召开年度开发者大会，发布一系列公告，展示其在人工智能领域的巨额投资，同时试图抵御外界对其业务未来的担忧。【原文：Alphabet's Google kicks off its annual developer conference on Tuesday with a flurry of announcements showcasing its huge investment in artificial intelligence, while seeking to fend off concerns over the future of its business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-unveil-ai-upgrades-io-conference-amid-search-challenges-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZOIOMPJLFLZFCKXRUR4F4OWKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺首席执行官表示，雷诺仍愿意向竞争对手提供技术，以降低汽车成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国汽车制造商雷诺公司首席执行官卢卡-德-梅奥（Luca De Meo）周二表示，雷诺愿意向其他汽车制造商提供技术，帮助提高汽车的总产量。【原文：French automaker Renault is willing to supply technology to other carmakers to help increase the total output of vehicles with shared features that make them cheaper to manufacture, CEO Luca De Meo said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-still-open-supply-technology-rivals-make-cars-cheaper-ceo-says-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGKNKWSCHRLPNBITA2EKKWSWOM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 将以 3.11 亿美元向 Authentic Brands 出售 Dockers，专注于核心品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 周二表示，将以 3.11 亿美元的价格把旗下的 Dockers 服装品牌出售给锐步和 Van Heusen 的所有者 Authentic Brands Group，以专注于其旗舰品牌 Levi's 和 Beyond Yoga 运动服装系列。【原文：Levi Strauss on Tuesday said it will sell its Dockers apparel brand to Reebok and Van Heusen owner Authentic Brands Group for $311 million to focus on its flagship Levi's brand and the Beyond Yoga activewear line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-sell-dockers-authentic-brands-311-million-focus-core-labels-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOEB7QJD45MOVCYZBDQEBTNNP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 4 月份年度通胀率降至 1.7%，但核心指标上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大统计局（Statistics Canada）周二称，由于联邦消费者碳税取消后整体能源价格骤降12.7%，加拿大4月份的年通胀率从3月份的2.3%降至1.7%。【原文：Canada's annual inflation rate in April fell to 1.7% from 2.3% in March as overall energy prices plunged 12.7% after the removal of a federal consumer carbon tax, Statistics Canada said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-annual-inflation-rate-april-drops-17-core-measures-rise-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAYX5H6OVRL4RJJJAL6YLUHOVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>