<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:23:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:23:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[英国将对Netflix等流媒体平台实施与广播公司相同的监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国周二表示，Netflix、亚马逊Prime视频、Disney+等流媒体平台将被要求遵循与英国广播公司（BBC）等传统广播机构相同的内容和无障碍规则。【原文：Britain said on Tuesday Netflix , Amazon Prime Video , Disney+ and other streamers would be required to follow the same rules on content and accessibility as traditional broadcasters like the BBC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/uk-regulate-netflix-other-streamers-line-with-broadcasters-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHOTWBUPJVKEXIAJFHAJUIT3XE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税政策转向或惠及巴西航空工业公司、美国航空公司及航空航天产业]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司、美国航空公司以及更广泛的商用航空航天领域，有望从特朗普政府周二实施的修订版关税制度中获益。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer , U.S. airlines and the broader commercial aerospace sector are poised to benefit from the Trump administration imposing a revised tariff regime on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trump-tariff-pivot-could-benefit-brazils-embraer-us-airlines-aerospace-industry-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4FDQRSMTNPJJC7TVNV4JBS47U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 10:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克里姆林宫称Telegram即时通讯应用多次违反法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[克里姆林宫周二表示，当局已记录到Telegram通讯应用存在大量违规行为，并正采取相应措施应对该应用所谓不愿与俄罗斯合作的状况。【原文：The Kremlin said on Tuesday that the authorities had recorded a large number of violations by the Telegram messenger app and were taking appropriate steps in response to what it cast as the app's unwillingness to cooperate with Russia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/kremlin-says-telegram-messaging-app-has-violated-law-many-times-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEQJA7XJ3JOVHLGV37PLGDRZYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:50:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东石油出口推高油轮成本至六年高位，美伊战争阴云笼罩]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业消息人士称，随着中东原油出口激增，加上交易商在美国与伊朗可能爆发军事冲突前加速租船，石油运输成本已飙升至六年最高水平。【原文：The cost of shipping oil has surged to the highest in six years, fuelled by a wave of crude exports from the Middle East as traders accelerate charters ahead of possible military conflict between the U.S. and Iran, industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/middle-east-oil-exports-push-tanker-costs-6-year-high-amid-threat-us-iran-war-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTTIVBMG65PL3FA2RNQLCM34XQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:40:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金在数周抛售后悄然重返科技股领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周二向客户发布的报告显示，对冲基金上周买入了最大型科技股以及那些被认为易受人工智能发展冲击的股票。【原文：Hedge funds last week bought the biggest tech stocks as well as those considered vulnerable to advances in artificial intelligence, said a note to clients from JPMorgan seen by Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hedge-funds-creep-back-into-tech-stocks-after-weeks-selling-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4AIRVXXBNOWTC2XT7Y7UB7DSA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称科威特石油公司吸引贝莱德、布鲁克菲尔德、EIG参与70亿美元管道项目谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位知情人士透露，科威特国家石油公司（KPC）已就出售其原油管道70亿美元股权事宜，与大批潜在投资者展开初步磋商。此前，海湾地区同行沙特阿拉伯和阿联酋也采取了类似举措。【原文：National oil company Kuwait Petroleum Corporation (KPC) has held early stage talks with a large group of potential investors over a $7 billion stake sale in its crude oil pipelines, three sources familiar with the matter said, following similar moves by Gulf peers Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/kuwaits-kpc-draws-blackrock-brookfield-eig-possible-7-billion-pipeline-deal-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPNDTITGJVK4BPMWBIAJIYVNTQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国新关税税率定为较低的10%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国海关与边境保护局表示，从周二起，美国对所有未获豁免的商品征收10%的新关税。该税率由总统唐纳德·特朗普于周五首次宣布，而非他次日承诺的15%。【原文：The United States imposed a new tariff from Tuesday of 10% on all goods not covered by exemptions, the U.S. Customs and Border Protection said, the rate first announced by President Donald Trump on Friday rather than the 15% he promised a day later.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/new-us-tariffs-come-lower-10-rate-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NI6GFH7LXNKCJLZQ3P4H53GVAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱将诺和诺德旗下CagriSema的销售预测下调逾80%]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱分析师周二大幅下调了诺和诺德新一代减肥药CagriSema的峰值销售预期，从120亿美元降至仅20亿美元。此前一天，该药物临床试验结果令人失望。【原文：Barclays analysts on Tuesday slashed their peak sales forecasts for Novo Nordisk's next-generation obesity drug CagriSema to just $2 billion from $12 billion following disappointing trial results for the drug a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-slashes-sales-forecasts-novos-cagrisema-by-more-than-80-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUSBXWNVD5JS3G7JNEBMZCQHCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国敦促美国取消新关税，愿举行新一轮贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周二发表声明称，中方敦促美国放弃"单边加征关税"，同时表示愿与世界最大经济体再举行一轮贸易磋商。【原文：China has urged the United States to abandon its "unilateral tariffs", indicating also that it is willing to hold another round of trade talks with the world's largest economy, the country's commerce ministry said in a statement on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-urges-us-drop-new-tariffs-willing-have-new-round-trade-talks-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7KGM6XTGBNYVDLSQMNGPCMT6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，福特将召回约41.3万辆SUV，因存在转向控制失效风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周二表示，福特汽车公司正在美国召回412,774辆探险者SUV，原因是后悬架外倾角连杆存在问题，可能发生断裂，导致转向控制失效。【原文：Ford is recalling 412,774 Explorer SUVs in the U.S., citing an issue with rear suspension toe links, which may fracture, leading to a loss of steering control, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-about-413000-us-vehicles-over-rear-suspension-toe-links-fractures-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFB627WDMFJ3FMZSW3UXV7Z5UQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿提哈德航空利润飙升近50%，机队规模与航线网络扩张有力支撑强劲需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿提哈德航空周二宣布，去年净利润跃升近50%至6.98亿美元。运力提升支撑了各市场的强劲需求，并推高了其客座率。【原文：Etihad Airways reported a near 50% jump in net profit to $698 million last year, the carrier said on Tuesday, as increased capacity supported strong demand across markets and lifted its load factor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/etihad-airways-profits-soars-nearly-50-fleet-network-expansion-support-strong-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHAKDOMGLRKGXAHP7XZD3VCRSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度科技行业预计在2026财年增长6%，规模将达3150亿美元，行业机构称]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度科技行业预计在本财年实现6.1%的增长，营收将达到3150亿美元，并在下个财年保持在该水平。行业机构周二表示，人工智能驱动的服务以及全球产能中心业务将成为增长引擎。【原文：India's technology sector is expected to grow 6.1% to $315 billion revenue in the ongoing fiscal year and remain around that level next fiscal, driven by artificial intelligence-led services as well as business at global capacity centres, an industry body said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-technology-sector-grow-61-fiscal-2026-industry-body-says-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGRCJ5HX4ZLGBDILJCVRKUKBY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 07:59:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国现代汽车警告称，尽管最高法院作出裁决，美国关税压力仍可能加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车总裁金成周二敦促韩国迅速通过3500亿美元美国投资计划的立法，并警告称尽管特朗普政府在法律上遭遇挫折，但仍可能对汽车等行业加剧关税压力。
金成在与反对党议员及工商团体官员的会议上发表上述言论，会议旨在讨论该投资计划——该计划是去年达成的美韩贸易协定组成部分，若实施将使美方关税从25%降至15%。【原文：Hyundai Motor President Sung Kim on Tuesday urged South Korea to swiftly pass legislation for a $350  billion U.S. investment package, cautioning the Trump administration may escalate tariff pressure on sectors such as autos despite its legal setback.
Kim made the comments at a meeting with opposition lawmakers and business association officials to discuss the investment package which forms part of a U.S. trade deal agreed last year, which would see Washington lowering tariffs from 25% to 15%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-koreas-hyundai-motor-warns-us-tariff-pressure-may-intensify-despite-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRROOG4BCVNNFA4U5O5WGDPUII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:20:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[动荡的一年为特朗普的国情咨文演讲奠定基调]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普将于周二在国情咨文演讲中，向美国选民推销其动荡且打破常规的第二个任期。选民将在11月决定共和党是否能继续掌控国会。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will use his State of the Union address on Tuesday to sell his turbulent, norm-breaking second term to American voters who will decide in November whether his Republican Party retains control of Congress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/year-upheaval-sets-stage-trumps-state-union-address-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3B2YB5INJVKARHLJTWJZSVM624</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:16:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普新关税政策将焦点转向国际收支平衡；经济学家认为不会引发危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普总统为替代被美国最高法院否决的关税而临时征收的15%关税，旨在解决许多经济学家认为并不存在的问题：美国的国际收支危机。这使得新关税可能面临新的法律挑战。【原文：President Donald Trump'stemporary 15% tariffs to replace those struck down by the U.S. Supreme Court are meant to resolve a problem that many economists say does not exist: a U.S. balance of payments crisis, making them potentially vulnerable to new legal challenges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trumps-new-tariffs-shift-focus-balance-payments-economists-see-no-crisis-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2SECHP4HNOSFFERGLMNNVWSYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯《俄罗斯报》报道，俄方正以刑事案件为由调查Telegram创始人杜罗夫]]></title><description><![CDATA[据俄罗斯官方报纸《俄罗斯报》援引联邦安全局消息报道，俄罗斯正以"协助恐怖活动"的刑事案件为由，对Telegram创始人帕维尔·杜罗夫展开调查。【原文：Russia is investigating Telegram founder Pavel Durov as part of a criminal case on the "facilitation of terrorist activities", state-run newspaper Rossiyskaya Gazeta reported, citing the Federal Security Service (FSB).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/russia-investigating-telegram-founder-durov-part-criminal-case-rossiyskaya-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIZBYLM4YJPWTM53OSWTIZP4OE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间要闻：特朗普对全球怒不可遏，其关税政策成效不彰]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔·斯图尔特·亨特带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KTMSLQ2ZJP5FF2KEXPMKNE32E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲汽车销量1月下滑，汽油车销量大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲汽车制造商协会（ACEA）周二公布的数据显示，受德国、法国、比利时和波兰等主要市场销量下滑拖累，欧洲1月新车销量同比下降，这是自6月以来首次出现下滑。【原文：New car sales in Europe fell year-on-year in January for the first time since June, weighed by declines in major markets including Germany, France, Belgium and Poland, data from the European auto lobby ACEA showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-car-sales-fall-january-petrol-cars-sharply-decline-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUGA5RZX75JJVJXRFI76QO2BVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:18:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华的失误凸显礼来在减肥药领域不断扩大的领先优势]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国死对头礼来公司凭借减肥处方药和估值一路领先之际，诺和诺德最不愿做的就是助其一臂之力。然而，这家丹麦公司新一代减肥药的最新试验数据却横空出世。【原文：With U.S. arch rival Eli Lilly streaking away on weight-loss prescriptions and valuation, the last thing Novo Nordisk needed was to give it a helping hand. Then came the latest trial data for the Danish company's next-generation obesity drug.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novos-stumbles-burnish-lillys-widening-lead-weight-loss-drugs-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6OMTYKTZ5NYVLTXDU6T3R4ZOM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，美国散户投资者推动杠杆ETF交易激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据Direxion（该类ETF的提供商）与两家分析公司Vanda Research和The Compound Insights联合发布的新研究，美国市场上近90%的杠杆单只股票ETF交易可追溯至个人投资者。【原文：Nearly 90% of all the trading in leveraged single-stock ETFs in the U.S. market can be traced to transactions by individual investors, according to a new study co-authored by Direxion, a provider of those ETFs, together with two analytical firms, Vanda Research and The Compound Insights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-retail-investors-fuel-surge-leveraged-etf-trading-study-shows-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GI54CUHA7VM3LEOAX4DCUXYYV4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:07:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，Meta高管曾警告称Facebook Messenger加密计划"极其不负责任"]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据提交至新墨西哥州法院的一份内部文件显示，尽管公司内部警告称加密措施将阻碍这家社交媒体巨头向执法部门举报儿童剥削案件的能力，Meta高管仍推进了为其Facebook和Instagram应用相关消息服务加密的计划。【原文：Meta executives proceeded with a plan to encrypt the messaging services connected to its Facebook and Instagram apps despite internal warnings that it would hinder the social media giant’s ability to flag child-exploitation cases to law enforcement, according to internal company documents filed in a New Mexico state court case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/meta-executive-warned-facebook-messenger-encryption-plan-was-so-irresponsible-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQ6XFEQBQROZJM4YQ37NY275DE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:49:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBM股价创2000年以来最大单日跌幅，此前Anthropic公司称其人工智能技术可实现COBOL语言现代化]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际商业机器公司（IBM）股价周一创下逾25年来最大单日跌幅，此前人工智能初创公司Anthropic表示其Claude Code工具可用于现代化IBM系统上运行的编程语言。【原文：Shares of International Business Machines recorded their steepest daily drop in more than 25 years on Monday, after AI startup Anthropic said its Claude Code tool could be used to modernize a programming language run on IBM systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ibm-posts-steepest-daily-drop-since-2000-after-anthropic-says-ai-can-modernize-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JV5WKXOTRJ2FIKWPLZFACVJJQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金价自三周高点回落，美元走强]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二金价从逾三周高位回落，因美元走强带来的压力盖过了美国关税不确定性和华盛顿与德黑兰紧张局势带来的支撑。【原文：Gold prices fell from a more than three-week high on Tuesday, as pressure from a stronger dollar outweighed support from U.S. tariff uncertainty and Washington-Tehran tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/gold-falls-three-week-high-dollar-firms-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSB4BTN3CNPEFNU7BEXKZPKAMU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，苹果公司将把部分Mac Mini的生产从亚洲转移至休斯顿。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周一报道，苹果公司将把部分Mac Mini台式电脑的生产从亚洲转移至美国，今年晚些时候将在休斯顿北部的富士康工厂启动新的制造计划。【原文：Apple will move some production of its Mac Mini desktop computer to the U.S. from Asia, with a new manufacturing effort set to begin later this year at a Foxconn facility in north Houston, The Wall Street Journal reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/apple-plans-manufacture-mac-mini-houston-wsj-reports-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63PLBP7MJBOCRLMZUGDVZRGQLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:14:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价徘徊于七个月高点下方，交易员关注美伊会谈及贸易政策动向]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二油价徘徊在近七个月高点下方，交易员们正评估中东局势紧张之际美伊核谈判的前景，同时权衡美国贸易政策的不确定性。【原文：Oil prices hovered below an almost seven-month high on Tuesday as traders gauged the outlook for U.S.-Iran nuclear talks amid heightened Middle East tensions, while also weighing uncertainty around U.S. trade policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-hovers-below-seven-month-high-traders-eye-usiran-talks-trade-policy-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7SJV4NXFFLJRBEPQ3INWWIQ2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:56:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元持续疲软，亚洲市场重启之际关税风波再起]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二美元持续疲软，亚洲市场正评估美国总统特朗普关税政策引发的新一轮动荡对全球贸易造成的冲击。【原文：The dollar languished on Tuesday as Asian markets weighed the fallout on global trade from renewed turbulence over U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff regime.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-languishes-asia-markets-reopen-renewed-tariff-turmoil-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AITCG3HWCBMULIUFMQ6VN775RM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市震荡，因华尔街抛售削弱市场信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周二早盘震荡，因隔夜华尔街抛售令投资者感到不安，特朗普关税政策的不确定性加剧以及地缘政治紧张局势升级，均打击了市场情绪。【原文：Asian stock markets stuttered in early trade on Tuesday as a selloff on Wall Street overnight rattled investors, with sentiment hurt by heightened uncertainty over U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff policy and rising geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1pix-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAXPOPSNBBKNRGSXJ42QNGEA4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:07:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，埃利奥特正游说股东支持收购丰田工业]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，埃利奥特管理公司已提出以接近市场价格收购丰田工业股份，对象是那些同意其要约收购的股东。这家美国激进投资机构认为，当前股价低估了这家叉车制造商的价值。【原文：Elliott Management has offered to pay around market price to buy Toyota Industries shares from holders who have agreed to a tender offer that the U.S. activist said undervalues the forklift truck maker, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/elliott-woos-shareholders-backing-toyota-industries-buyout-sources-say-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5QKJYZ2JVKK5JXZQLUQKOHXSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：中国DeepSeek在美禁令下仍用英伟达顶级芯片训练AI模型，官方证实]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府一位高级官员周一表示，中国人工智能初创企业DeepSeek即将于下周发布的最新人工智能模型，是在英伟达最先进的人工智能芯片Blackwell上训练完成的。此举可能违反美国出口管制规定。【原文：Chinese AI startup DeepSeek's latest AI model, set to be released as soon as next week, was trained on Nvidia's most advanced AI chip, the Blackwell, a senior Trump administration official said on Monday, in what could represent a violation of U.S. export controls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-deepseek-trained-ai-model-nvidias-best-chip-despite-us-ban-official-says-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7H3SSVC45O6PG5XONIDRHENYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通的戴蒙表示他将继续担任首席执行官数年]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米·戴蒙周一表示，他将继续掌舵这家美国最大银行"几年"。【原文：JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon said on Monday he will remain at the helm of the largest U.S. bank for a "few years."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgans-dimon-says-he-will-remain-ceo-few-years-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYQ4WP7WEBN7DDE7AMJAFBGLPI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:55:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>