<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:36:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:36:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波音任命耶稣-杰伊-马拉维为新任首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周一表示，已任命耶稣-杰伊-马拉维（Jesus 'Jay' Malave）为该公司新任首席财务官，自 8 月 15 日起生效。【原文：Boeing Co said on Monday it had appointed Jesus 'Jay' Malave as the planemaker's new CFO, effective Aug. 15.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-names-jesus-jay-malave-new-cfo-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67THNTC75JIINHWSCYTRZBLSDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道Circle 首次公开募股大获成功后申请美国信托银行执照]]></title><description><![CDATA[稳定币公司Circle正在申请在美国创建一家国家信托银行，这是该公司本月早些时候进行首次公开募股（IPO），估值近180亿美元之后的一项重大举措。【原文：Stablecoin firm Circle is applying to create a national trust bank in the U.S., a major move after its blockbuster IPO valued the company at nearly $18 billion earlier this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/circle-applies-us-trust-bank-license-after-bumper-ipo-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3GQPRIE4BJTPDLA4WLE2XAXTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:07:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Meta 通过 "超级智能 "实验室深化人工智能发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士周一透露，Meta 公司首席执行官马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）已经重组了公司的人工智能工作，将其归入一个名为 Meta 超级智能实验室（Meta Superintelligence Labs）的新部门。【原文：Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg has reorganized the company's artificial intelligence efforts under a new division called Meta Superintelligence Labs, according to a source on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-deepens-ai-push-with-superintelligence-lab-source-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXYRIDLIRZIOLMFMUEFJK7CRFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:47:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭文件称，派拉蒙与特朗普正在进行 "高级 "和解谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司和唐纳德-特朗普总统正在进行 "真诚、先进的和解谈判"，以解决特朗普 10 月份对哥伦比亚广播公司提起的诉讼，指控该公司对时任副总统卡马拉-哈里斯的 "60 分钟 "采访进行了欺骗性编辑。【原文：Paramount Global and President Donald Trump are engaged in "good faith, advanced, settlement negotiations" to resolve a lawsuit filed by Trump against CBS in October, alleging the network deceptively edited a "60 Minutes" interview with then-vice president Kamala Harris.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/paramount-trump-advanced-settlement-talks-court-filing-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCHQRWVHDVLF7H5VBK2OEMA2AU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经纪公司伯恩斯坦称，梅赛德斯-奔驰预计第二季度利润率将因关税问题受挫不到 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰（Mercedes-Benz）在季度业绩发布前的投资者例行电话会议后，经纪公司伯恩斯坦（Bernstein）在一份说明中写道，预计第二季度与关税有关的不利因素对其核心汽车部门利润率的影响将低于 3%。【原文：Mercedes-Benz expects tariff-related headwinds to the profit margin at its core cars division to be less than 3% in the second quarter, brokerage Bernstein wrote in a note, following a regular investor call ahead of quarterly results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-benz-expects-q2-margin-headwind-less-than-3-over-tariffs-brokerage-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDBOTZHQWBNPFF733FOGS3TRUQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉加德：欧元区通胀波动加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）周一表示，不确定性必将继续成为全球经济的一个主要特征，可能会使通胀更加不稳定，并要求欧洲央行采取更有力的行动，使物价保持在其目标附近。【原文：Uncertainty is bound to remain a key feature of the global economy, likely making inflation more volatile and requiring the ECB to act more forcefully to keep prices around its target, ECB President Christine Lagarde said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/euro-zone-facing-increased-inflation-volatility-lagarde-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCK55NJUPBJXPLXBW2PICZ5SJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果公司权衡使用 Anthropic 或 OpenAI 为 Siri 提供动力，这是一次重大逆转]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周一援引熟悉相关讨论的人士的话报道称，苹果公司正在权衡使用 Anthropic 或 OpenAI 的人工智能技术来支持新版 Siri，而不是自己的内部模型。【原文：Apple is weighing using artificial intelligence technology from Anthropic or OpenAI to power a new version of Siri, instead of its own in-house models, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-weighs-using-anthropic-or-openai-power-siri-major-reversal-bloomberg-news-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEVM6HZEQVLU3LWFVWUGQR3HWA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:01:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织将在审查后向乌克兰提供 5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）周一表示，该组织已经完成了作为乌克兰扩展基金机制一部分的扩展安排下的第八次审查，向该国支付了约 5 亿美元（3.7 亿特别提款权）。【原文：The International Monetary Fund said on Monday it has completed its eighth review under an extended arrangement as part of the Extended Fund Facility for Ukraine, providing the country with a disbursement of about $500 million (SDR 0.37 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/imf-provide-ukraine-with-500-million-after-review-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2K75M5Z5VJ43OMUF5KLPT2FVU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果驳回美国智能手机垄断案的申请败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司必须面对美国司法部指控其非法主导美国智能手机市场的诉讼。【原文：Apple must face the U.S. Department of Justice's lawsuit accusing the iPhone maker of unlawfully dominating the U.S. smartphone market, a judge ruled on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apple-loses-bid-dismiss-us-smartphone-monopoly-case-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3AM2KXBCFOAPDGPI3DHIRKU2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：欧盟将接受特朗普的普遍关税，但寻求关键豁免权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周一报道，欧盟对与美国达成一项对其许多出口产品普遍征收 10%关税的贸易协定持开放态度，但欧盟正在寻求美国承诺降低制药、酒精、半导体和商用飞机等关键行业的关税。【原文：The European Union is open to a trade agreement with the United States that would apply a universal 10% tariff on many of its exports, but the EU is seeking U.S. commitments to reduce tariffs in key sectors such as pharmaceuticals, alcohol, semiconductors, and commercial aircraft, Bloomberg news reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-accept-trumps-universal-tariff-seeks-key-exemptions-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJYKG547XBPGFB6HESFGNHV4YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:33:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在与宗教领袖通话时将技术问题归咎于 AT&T]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，他与美国宗教领袖举行的电话会议遇到了技术问题，他为此指责 AT&amp;T，同时敦促这家无线运营商的老板参与处理这一情况。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday a conference call he had with American faith leaders faced tech issues for which he blamed AT&amp;T while urging the wireless carrier's boss to get involved in handling the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-blames-att-tech-issues-call-with-faith-leaders-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WB5HL27PUZJDRBIH7MMXDNHZ7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[排除 ICE 指数可能减缓华纳兄弟 143 亿美元债券转入垃圾投资组合的速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美银全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）的一份报告称，媒体巨头华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）总额达 143 亿美元的债券在高收益债券投资组合中的新家迁移可能会因最近宣布被排除在一个主要指数之外而放缓。【原文：A total $14.3 billion of media giant Warner Bros Discovery's bonds' move to their new home in high-yield bond portfolios will likely be slowed by a recently announced exclusion from a major index, said a BofA Global Research report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ice-index-exclusion-likely-slow-warner-bros-143-billion-bonds-move-junk-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LWLSF6DERK3RAXEHEK4452JBM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:18:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比认为不会出现滞胀，但情况 "肯定 "会变得更糟]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周一表示，随着失业率接近4%，通胀率约为2.5%并在下降，他认为关税或其他供应方面的冲击不可能在短期内造成20世纪70年代式的实际滞胀，当时的失业率是现在的两倍，通胀率超过13%。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee on Monday said that with unemployment near 4% and inflation around 2.5% and falling, he sees no possibility that tariffs or another supply-side shock could in the near term cause actual 1970s-style stagflation, when the unemployment was double today's rate and inflation was above 13%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-sees-no-stagflation-definitely-things-could-get-worse-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42JTFBUUPVL57MJJY62WYSDP74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:09:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华伦天奴面临不确定性，首席执行官因利润下滑请病假]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品牌华伦天奴（Valentino）周一表示，其首席执行官雅各布-文图里尼（Jacopo Venturini）目前正在休病假，以回应媒体关于他即将离职的报道。【原文：Italian luxury brand Valentino said on Monday its Chief Executive Jacopo Venturini was currently on sick leave, responding to media reports of his imminent departure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/valentino-faces-uncertainty-ceo-takes-sick-leave-amid-profit-slowdown-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJFZBGJB3BPVNETLSF3ZB6WS7A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:59:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称特朗普致信鲍威尔敦促降低利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫新闻秘书卡罗琳-利维特（Karoline Leavitt）周一告诉记者，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普写信给美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔，敦促他降低利率。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump wrote Fed Chair Jerome Powell urging him to lower interest rates, White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt told reporters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/white-house-says-trump-wrote-powell-urge-lower-rates-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MB7PKOXKUNKTBBL33FZUKNYUHY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官命令面临 161 亿美元判决的阿根廷放弃 YPF 股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一名美国法官命令阿根廷放弃其在石油和天然气公司 YPF 51% 的股份，以部分履行 161 亿美元的法庭判决，使这个资金短缺的国家遭遇失败。【原文：A U.S. judge on Monday ordered Argentina to give up its 51% stake in oil and gas company YPF to partially satisfy a $16.1 billion court judgment, handing a defeat to the cash-strapped country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-judge-orders-argentina-transfer-ypf-shares-help-satisfy-161-billion-judgment-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBDEICNOENOC7ME33QG4AO4M5A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际商会称新网络安全事件已得到控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际刑事法院（ICC）周一表示，上周末发现了一起 "新的、复杂的和有针对性的 "网络安全事件，并补充说该事件现已得到控制。【原文：The International Criminal Court (ICC) said on Monday it had detected a "new, sophisticated and targeted" cybersecurity incident late last week, adding it has now been contained.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/icc-says-new-cybersecurity-incident-has-been-contained-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2WHUD2EENP4TASVIOD5OJ3IWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙 BBVA 银行将继续收购萨瓦德尔银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙对外银行（BBVA）周一表示，尽管政府在至少三年内有效阻止该公司与较小的竞争对手萨瓦德尔（Sabadell）完全合并，但该公司仍将继续对较小的竞争对手萨瓦德尔（Sabadell）进行恶意收购。【原文：Spain's BBVA said on Monday it would move ahead with its hostile takeover bid for smaller rival Sabadell despite the government effectively blocking it from fully merging with its smaller rival for at least three years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/spains-bbva-proceed-with-takeover-bid-sabadell-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMBMPTU62ZOXLJA32QSMEMWKNQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:46:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德：政府债务上升对美国市场地位构成最大风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德（BlackRock）周一表示，美国政府债务激增可能会削弱投资者对美国主要资产（如长期国债和美元）的偏好，从而支持投资者转向美国境外的投资机会。【原文：Surging U.S. government debt may sap investor appetite for key U.S. assets like long-dated Treasuries and the dollar, bolstering the case for turning to opportunities beyond U.S. borders, BlackRock said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/rising-government-debt-poses-greatest-risk-us-market-standing-says-blackrock-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHQEBQNXDVKFHLO7ST2MXTMMVU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席博斯蒂克仍希望今年降息一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周一重申，他仍认为央行今年将下调一次利率目标，同时表示，由于贸易关税将如何影响美国经济的通胀动态仍存在很多不确定性，因此并不急于采取行动。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic repeated on Monday that he still sees the central bank cutting its interest rate target once this year, while suggesting there's no urgency to act as a lot of uncertainty remains in terms of how trade tariffs will affect inflation dynamics in the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bostic-still-eyes-one-rate-cut-this-year-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCAELDTS2FKVRGKU4YV3RUELXA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：特朗普政府希望在 2026 年初填补美联储空缺，任命鲍威尔继任者]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一表示，特朗普政府正在考虑利用预计于2026年初出现的下一个美联储理事会空缺来任命央行主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）的继任者。【原文：The Trump administration is considering using the next expected Federal Reserve Board of Governors vacancy in early 2026 for appointing a successor to central bank Chair Jerome Powell, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-eyes-fed-vacancy-early-2026-appoint-powell-successor-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LDZPLHAEVIGDK3J5POYX6DMVU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:26:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院就是否通过修订后的州人工智能监管禁令展开辩论]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位重要的美国共和党参议员同意将联邦对各州人工智能监管的暂停期修订为五年，并允许各州通过有关儿童网络安全和保护艺术家形象或肖像的规定。【原文：Two key U.S. Republican senators agreed to a revised federal moratorium on state regulation of artificial intelligence to five years and allow states to adopt rules on child online safety and protecting artists' image or likeliness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-senate-debates-whether-adopt-revised-state-ai-regulation-ban-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROX2MIGDEVOSHJFILLGH56RAUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:22:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅签署协议收购护发品牌 Color Wow]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国化妆品巨头欧莱雅（L'Oreal）周一表示，该公司已签署协议收购位于美国和英国的护发品牌 Color Wow。【原文：French cosmetics giant L'Oreal said on Monday it had signed an agreement to acquire Color Wow, a haircare brand based in the U.S. and Britain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/loreal-signs-agreement-acquire-haircare-brand-color-wow-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MR4LYJMVJJKLO7LT4PR247YUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗预计第三季度金价将在 3100-3500 美元附近盘整]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行在周一的一份报告中表示，由于中东地缘政治局势缓和以及全球经济增长前景改善，黄金价格将在第三季度巩固在每盎司3100美元至3500美元左右。【原文：Citi expects the price of gold to consolidate around $3,100 to $3,500 per ounce in the third quarter, as prices moderate due to geopolitical de-escalation in the Middle East and an improved global growth outlook, the bank said in a note on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/citi-expects-gold-price-consolidate-around-3100-3500-third-quarter-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UMAP2KJQRIU5GS6EUTTIWZSQQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府警告：与伊朗有关的黑客可能会攻击美国公司和关键基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国政府官员周一发布的一份公告称，受伊朗庇护的黑客可能会将目标对准美国公司和关键基础设施运营商，特别是与以色列研究和国防公司有控股或合作关系的国防组织。【原文：Iranian-affilited hackers may target U.S. companies and critical infrastructure operators, particularly defense organizations with holdings or relationships with Israeli research and defense firms, according to an advisory from U.S. government officials Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/iran-linked-hackers-may-target-us-firms-critical-infrastructure-us-government-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHVPQKCDKZNG3ATRDZDVG4YNF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:39:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 数据显示，4 月份美国原油产量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署发布的《石油供应月报》系列数据显示，4 月份美国原油产量达到创纪录的 1,347 万桶/日，高于 3 月份的 1,345 万桶/日。【原文：U.S. crude oil production hit a record 13.47 million barrels-per-day in April, up from 13.45 million bpd in March, according to data released by the Energy Information Administration as part of its Petroleum Supply Monthly series.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-oil-output-hit-record-april-eia-data-shows-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFWOQUPKUFJXXHJAZULCZU2Q6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:30:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院法案削减清洁能源引起劳工和商界反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院在其版本的唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统税收和支出法案中提出的削减清洁能源补贴的建议自上周末公布以来，招致了商界和劳工团体的猛烈抨击，一些人认为此举将提高电价并扼杀就业机会。【原文：The U.S. Senate’s proposed cuts to clean energy subsidies in its version of President Donald Trump's tax and spending bill have drawn searing criticism from business and labor groups since they were unveiled over the weekend, with some arguing the moves will raise power prices and kill jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-senate-bills-clean-energy-cuts-draw-backlash-labor-business-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTW52QIYXJICTCP3576UP6L36Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:18:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood 推出代币，允许欧盟用户交易美股]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 周一表示，它已推出代币，允许欧盟客户交易 200 多只美国股票和交易所交易基金，包括英伟达、苹果和微软。【原文：Robinhood said on Monday it has launched tokens that will allow its customers in the European Union to trade more than 200 U.S. stocks and exchange-traded funds, including Nvidia , Apple and Microsoft .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/robinhood-launches-tokens-allowing-eu-users-trade-us-stocks-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JITJBP5T4FOVFJNQE4UIWEAUFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示美国将立即重启与加拿大的贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周一表示，在加拿大取消针对美国科技公司的数字服务税后，美国将立即重启与加拿大的贸易谈判。【原文：The United States will restart trade negotiations with Canada immediately after Canada scrapped its digital services tax targeting U.S. technology firms, White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-restart-trade-negotiations-with-canada-immediately-white-house-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RS6GYAONZFNNXEXCFGKJ7JHDMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:49:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长贝森特警告各国在 7 月 9 日最后期限后将面临更高的关税税率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一警告说，即使各国本着诚意进行谈判，它们仍有可能在7月9日面临大幅提高关税的局面，并补充说，任何可能的延期都将取决于唐纳德-特朗普总统。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said warned on Monday that countries could still face sharply higher tariffs on July 9 even if they are negotiating in good faith, adding that any potential extensions will be up to President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasurys-bessent-warns-countries-face-higher-tariff-rates-after-july-9-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXV2ZY5CBROHFOCPKBYG6XGSEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>