<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:39:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:39:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨莱姆倾向于支持 10 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆周五表示，他将支持央行在本月底降息，同时警告说，在通胀风险仍不稳定的情况下，美联储在放宽信贷成本方面不能走得太远。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis President Alberto Musalem suggested Friday he will support a central bank interest rate cut at the end of the month, while warning it's important for the Fed not to go too far with easing the cost of credit amid still unsettled inflation risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-musalem-leans-toward-supporting-october-interest-rate-cut-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5PF6LSZNZLQLFCB5YKFWSMQUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:25:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉薪酬计划面临反弹，ISS敦促投票反对马斯克的 1 万亿美元方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，代理咨询公司机构股东服务公司（Institutional Shareholder Services）敦促特斯拉股东投票反对首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）提议的 1 万亿美元业绩奖励，理由是担心薪酬过高和治理风险。【原文：Proxy advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services on Friday urged Tesla shareholders to vote against CEO Elon Musk's proposed $1 trillion performance award, citing concerns over excessive compensation and governance risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/proxy-advisory-firm-iss-recommends-voting-against-tesla-ceo-1-trillion-pay-plan-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7DHGZNPOVKXFIKQUOO35A6WIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士部长在美国与贝森特会谈，未透露关税问题取得进展的迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士经济部长居伊-帕梅林（Guy Parmelin）周五表示，他已就美国对瑞士征收39%的关税一事与美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）进行了简短的交谈，但他没有表示在减少征税方面取得了进展。【原文：Swiss Economy Minister Guy Parmelin said on Friday he had spoken briefly to U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent about the United States' 39% tariffs on Switzerland, but he gave no indication of progress on reducing the levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swiss-minister-speaks-bessent-us-gives-no-sign-progress-tariffs-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGHCSWH2FFO5FEMQ5ZO2C5WQSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与甲骨文有关的黑客攻击活动针对特使航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司最大的地区性航空公司 Envoy Air 周五证实，该公司最近几天遭到黑客攻击，这是黑客利用甲骨文电子商务套件应用程序进行勒索的一部分。【原文：Envoy Air, American Airlines' largest regional carrier, suffered a hack in recent days as part of the wave of extortion attempts from hackers exploiting Oracle E-Business Suite applications, the company confirmed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/envoy-air-targeted-oracle-linked-hacking-campaign-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OE477JYCE5KINBVEFBAIGDXTJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:47:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷期待 SUV 老板莱特斯回归，接过 "毒杯]]></title><description><![CDATA[保时捷邀请前迈凯轮老板迈克尔-莱特斯（Michael Leiters）重振这家德国豪华汽车制造商的举动受到了投资者的欢迎，尽管他们对新老板面临的挑战并不抱幻想。【原文：Porsche's moves to bring in ex-McLaren boss Michael Leiters to revive the luxury German carmaker were welcomed by investors, although they have no illusions about the challenge in store for the new boss.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-eyes-return-suv-boss-leiters-assume-poisoned-chalice-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7J53H7Q7J5KRXNOOLO3RTV3YPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:20:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，高盛对新成立的资本解决方案集团管理层进行了调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份内部备忘录称，高盛已对其负责大型交易融资和为企业客户提供贷款的部门进行了多项组织调整和任命。【原文：Goldman Sachs has made several organizational changes and appointments in its unit that focuses on financing large deals and providing loans to corporate clients, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-rejigs-management-recently-created-capital-solutions-group-memo-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQNP4IWIFJN3RMQWKT27FSZC5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:14:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A2A 首席执行官称，米兰数据中心的容量将在五年内激增十倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源集团 A2A 首席执行官周五表示，意大利金融之都米兰周边的数据中心预计将在未来五年内增加约两千兆瓦的发电能力，比目前的水平增加十倍。【原文：Data centres around Italy's financial capital Milan are expected to add around two gigawatts of capacity over the next five years, a tenfold increase from current levels, the Chief Executive of energy group A2A said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/milans-data-centre-capacity-set-surge-tenfold-five-years-a2a-ceo-says-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQLPOMY5FVM2TIUPJADGWHKVII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称美国再次购买比索，比索汇率下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五表示，美国财政部周四在 "蓝筹掉期 "和现货市场上买入了阿根廷比索，并将继续监控所有市场。【原文：The U.S. Treasury bought Argentine pesos in the "Blue Chip Swap" and spot markets on Thursday and it continues to monitor all markets, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bessent-says-us-bought-pesos-again-currency-dips-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIHB7OYPBZJY3ENR2DEACFMPZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德聘请美国制药业资深人士，应对特朗普施加的定价压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）已任命美国制药业高管格雷格-麦利（Greg Miley）为其新任企业事务主管，因为这家肥胖症制药商在药品定价方面面临着来自美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）越来越大的压力。【原文：Novo Nordisk has appointed U.S. pharmaceutical executive Greg Miley as its new head of corporate affairs, as the obesity drugmaker faces growing pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump on drug pricing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-hires-us-pharma-veteran-trump-pricing-pressure-mounts-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SI22NLWKFLSJINQ3FVOVY52MA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:51:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行的班加呼吁提高债务重组过程的透明度]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行行长阿贾伊-班加（Ajay Banga）周五强调，有必要提高债务重组过程的透明度，使有关各方更加清楚地了解情况，包括将债务人报告制度扩大到 20 国集团的所有主要经济体。【原文：World Bank President Ajay Banga on Friday stressed the need to increase transparency in debt restructuring processes to give greater clarity to all parties involved, including by expanding the debtor reporting system to all Group of 20 major economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/world-banks-banga-calls-more-transparency-debt-restructuring-process-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6UO2IRRXZL2PNGGAQ3BLU7YQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受人工智能提振，瑞银将全球股市观点上调至 "有吸引力 "评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银全球财富管理公司（UBS Global Wealth Management）将其对全球股市的评级上调至 "有吸引力"，理由是人工智能支出有望提高生产率，且政策背景具有支持性。
"结构性趋势依然稳固。领先的人工智能企业之间的战略合作浪潮增强了我们对持续的资本支出周期和更高收入能见度的信心"，瑞银在周四的一份说明中说。
最近几周，人工智能热潮引发了一波涉及大型科技公司和硅谷初创企业的备受瞩目的交易。
受美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）提前开始降息以避免经济衰退的乐观情绪推动，全球股市攀升至历史新高。【原文：UBS Global Wealth Management upgraded its stance on global equities to "attractive", citing expected productivity gains from AI spending and a supportive policy backdrop.
"Structural trends remain firmly in place. The wave of strategic partnerships among leading AI players reinforces our confidence in a sustained capex cycle and greater revenue visibility", UBS said in a note on Thursday.
The AI boom has spurred a wave of high-profile deals involving Big Tech and Silicon Valley startups in recent weeks.
Global equities have climbed to record highs, driven by optimism that the U.S. Federal Reserve began cutting interest rates early enough to avoid a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/ubs-lifts-global-equities-view-attractive-ai-boost-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDT524KLLFKFDGPU3ZIFHWYEWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特敦促国际货币基金组织和世界银行对中国采取更强硬立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五向国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）和世界银行（World Bank）下达了具体指令，要求它们对中国以国家为主导的经济行为采取更强硬的立场，这是他推动全球贷款机构重新专注于其核心使命的一部分。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Friday gave specific marching orders for the International Monetary Fund and World Bank to take tougher stances on China's state-driven economic practices as part of his push to get the global lenders to refocus on their core missions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bessent-urges-imf-world-bank-take-tougher-line-china-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5HKIU7HG2VIQXEN4YL6735ING4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，激进控股公司持有东方银行股份公司股份，并推动出售]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉此事的人士和路透社看到的文件称，激进投资者 HoldCo Asset Management 已在 Eastern Bankshares 建立了相当大的仓位，并希望这家波士顿著名金融机构将自己出售，而不是收购其他银行。【原文：Activist investor HoldCo Asset Management has built a sizable position in Eastern Bankshares and wants the storied Boston financial institution to put itself up for sale, instead of buying up other banks, according to people familiar with the matter and documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/activist-holdco-owns-eastern-bankshares-stake-pushes-sale-sources-say-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46GDELJBNRKO7FNKFF5Y24U6NE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受降息押注和乐观盈利影响，美国股票基金重获资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 15 日的一周内，由于美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）发出了进一步降息的信号，加上企业财报季稳健开局，缓解了人们对贸易关税和政府停摆的担忧，美国股票基金再次受到追捧。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw renewed demand in the week to October 15 as signals of further rate cuts from Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell and a solid start to the corporate earnings season eased concerns over trade tariffs and a government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-regain-inflows-rate-cut-bets-upbeat-earnings-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URXSYRFT5NJX7JJE3K4EJ4T2OI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司与 F1 赛事达成五年独家美国媒体版权协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[继布拉德-皮特（Brad Pitt）主演的《F1.Movie》获得成功之后，苹果公司又获得了一级方程式赛车在美国的转播权，这项为期五年的协议将帮助这家科技巨头通过美国发展最快的体育运动之一来加强其流媒体服务：The Movie》取得成功之后。【原文：Apple has landed U.S. broadcast rights to Formula 1 in a five-year deal that would help the tech giant bolster its streaming service with one of the country's fastest-growing sports, following the success of its Brad Pitt-starrer "F1: The Movie".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/apple-clinches-exclusive-us-media-rights-f1-races-under-five-year-deal-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6U4KOLSORFO4BBRB2STUFOCE5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道世贸组织负责人敦促中美两国缓和贸易战，否则全球经济增长将面临长期打击的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织负责人表示，她正在敦促美国和中国缓和贸易紧张局势，并警告说，世界两大经济体脱钩可能会使全球经济产出长期减少 7%。【原文：The head of the World Trade Organization said she is urging the U.S. and China to de-escalate trade tensions, warning that a decoupling by the world's two largest economies could reduce global economic output by 7% over the longer term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/wto-chief-urges-us-china-de-escalate-trade-war-or-risk-long-term-hit-global-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7NGFLQOKFNFHL7S3SMQYMQHDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息预期升温，全球股票基金迎来本周第四次资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至10月15日，全球股票基金连续第四周吸引资金流入，原因是美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）的鸽派言论增强了人们对央行将在本月晚些时候的会议上降息的预期。【原文：Global equity funds attracted inflows for a fourth straight week through October 15, as dovish comments from U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell reinforced expectations that the central bank will cut interest rates at its meeting later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJHM7MQIM5PE5NMFL5OJK7NCL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称对中国征收 100%关税不可持续，仍计划与习近平会晤]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，他提出的对来自中国的商品征收 100%关税的建议是不可持续的，但他将贸易谈判的最新僵局归咎于中国政府，而这一僵局的起因是中国政府加强了对稀土出口的控制。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said his proposed 100% tariff on goods from China would not be sustainable, but blamed Beijing for the latest impasse in trade talks that began with Chinese authorities tightening control over rare earth exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-100-tariffs-china-not-sustainable-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSD5DIKXHRKJ3DAOBEW5RLWDGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亨廷顿因利息和费用增加而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[亨廷顿银行（Huntington Bancshares）周五报告称，由于各部门利息收入和费用增加，这家美国地区性贷款机构第三季度利润有所增长。【原文：Huntington Bancshares reported a rise in its third-quarter profit on Friday, as the regional U.S. lender benefited from increased interest income and fees across all divisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/huntingtons-profit-jumps-higher-interest-fees-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQLSHGOOSNMQRFU77U7XHZIGFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫哈塞特谈信贷市场：乐观地认为我们能保持领先地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周五表示，银行拥有充足的储备，他对信贷市场能够保持领先表示乐观。【原文：White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said on Friday that banks have ample reserves and that he was optimistic that credit markets could stay ahead of the curve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/white-houses-hassett-credit-markets-optimistic-we-can-stay-ahead-curve-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7C62ZVSEFO6DI5GDRAZVG4PXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博尔特首席执行官表示，欧盟需要更加重视自动驾驶技术，以赶上竞争对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱沙尼亚打车和送餐公司 Bolt 首席执行官周五表示，欧洲要想在未来十年的关键技术中发挥作用，至少需要像关注电动汽车一样关注自动驾驶汽车。【原文：Europe needs to pay at least as much attention to self-driving cars as it does to electric vehicles if it wants to play a role in one of the key technologies of the next decade, the CEO of Estonian ride-hailing and food delivery company Bolt said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-needs-more-focus-self-driving-catch-up-with-rivals-says-bolt-ceo-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GHE6SOJLDVLL3L7MTOASSUE4PM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调情人工智能聊天机器人遭批评后，Meta 将赋予青少年父母更多控制权]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 公司周五表示，它将允许家长禁用青少年与人工智能角色的私密聊天，这是在其调情聊天机器人的行为受到激烈批评后，为确保未成年人安全而采取的又一社交媒体平台措施。【原文：Meta said on Friday it will let parents disable their teens' private chats with AI characters, adding another measure to make its social media platforms safe for minors after fierce criticism over the behavior of its flirty chatbots.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/meta-give-teen-parents-more-control-after-criticism-over-flirty-ai-chatbots-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEVYT23VPVNAZLRBPENAJNIT4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度工程公司塔塔科技利润因非核心业务增长而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度工程公司塔塔技术周五公布第二季度利润增长 5%，原因是其非汽车业务的增长缓解了其主要汽车业务部门的疲软。【原文：Indian engineering firm Tata Technologies reported a 5% rise in second-quarter profit on Friday, as growth in its non-automotive business cushioned weakness in its key auto-focused segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-engineering-firm-tata-techs-profit-rises-non-core-business-boost-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKVZH4TKDJLBDCMY3O5FCUG2FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得益于强劲的财富管理和利息收入，Truist 第三季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[受强劲的财富管理业务和利息收入增加的推动，Truist Financial 周五公布第三季度利润增长，股价在盘前交易中上涨 2%。【原文：Truist Financial reported a rise in third-quarter profit on Friday, driven by a strong wealth management segment and increased interest income, sending its shares up 2% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/truists-third-quarter-profit-rises-robust-wealth-management-interest-income-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KR5ZBFHUMVNJ5KPJUHALT6IPB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:33:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰银行预计黄金 "牛浪 "将于 2026 年达到 5,000 美元/盎司]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行周五预测，黄金的牛市涨势将推动金价在2026年达到每盎司5,000美元，风险升高和新进入市场者的影响将对金价形成支撑。【原文：HSBC on Friday forecast that gold's bull rally would drive prices as high as $5,000 an ounce in 2026, supported by elevated risks and the impact of new entrants into the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/hsbc-expects-golds-bull-wave-hit-5000oz-2026-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QDYT7Y3NZNBRPZ3QPL7QEXC7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:32:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 和 Pony.ai 将在欧洲开发自动驾驶汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 和中国自动驾驶公司 Pony.ai 周五表示，双方已签署协议，将在欧洲联合开发和测试自动驾驶汽车。【原文：Stellantis and Chinese autonomous driving firm Pony.ai said on Friday that they had signed an agreement to jointly develop and test self-driving vehicles in Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/stellantis-ponyai-develop-self-driving-vehicles-europe-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLRFK4YHY5PGJDZF5O5SNLM4O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:31:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第五第三银行利润因手续费收入而大幅增长，因 Tricolor 破产而亏损 1.78 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国地区性银行 Fifth Third Bancorp 周五报告称，由于手续费收入强劲，第三季度利润飙升 14%，但因汽车经销商 Tricolor 破产而出现 1.78 亿美元的亏损。【原文：U.S. regional bank Fifth Third Bancorp reported a 14% jump in third-quarter profit on Friday on the back of robust fee income, but booked a $178 million loss related to the bankruptcy of auto dealer Tricolor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fifth-third-profit-jumps-fee-income-records-178-million-loss-tricolor-bankruptcy-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7AFW6HU2TVIETHVVICHUJXNS3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:24:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Regions Financial 第三季度利润因交易复苏而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[受惠于资本市场走强和利息收入增加，Regions Financial 周五公布第三季度利润增长，股价在盘前交易中上涨约 1%。【原文：Regions Financial reported a rise in third-quarter profit on Friday, benefiting from stronger capital markets and higher income from interests, sending its shares up about 1% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/regions-financials-third-quarter-profit-rises-dealmaking-recovery-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7LGM7KHLRNMVHTAQT6B5E7O7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:23:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国航运机构因意见分歧推迟一年决定碳价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国的压力下，联合国航运机构的大多数国家未能就减排措施达成共识，因此周五投票决定将全球国际航运碳价格的决定推迟一年。【原文：A majority of countries at the U.N. shipping agency voted on Friday to postpone by a year a decision on a global carbon price on international shipping, after failing to reach consensus on the emissions reduction measure amid U.S. pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-singapore-call-un-delay-carbon-shipping-price-vote-amid-splits-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZLG72ZTMJJ2RDQUMFCUT5OLHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰政府就 Nexperia 出口管制问题与中国进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰正与中国就对中资芯片制造商耐克斯派瑞亚公司（Nexperia）实施出口管制一事进行谈判。【原文：The Netherlands is in talks with China over export controls imposed on the Chinese-owned chipmaker Nexperia, which has become tangled up in the trade frictions between the U.S. and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dutch-government-talks-with-china-over-nexperia-export-controls-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23RN3PTVAJKU3A2A46KP4KJIGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>