<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:04:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:04:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官命令 DOGE 和马斯克提供削减成本的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名法官命令埃隆-马斯克和他的政府效率部回答有关他们削减联邦开支的问题。【原文：A judge has ordered Elon Musk and his Department of Government Efficiency to answer questions describing their efforts to slash federal spending.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-orders-doge-musk-produce-cost-cutting-records-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MOJ5R7KLQVP73JWQV3CK2XY52U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:51:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党领导的各州起诉阻止特朗普解散美国教育部]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群民主党州检察长周四提起诉讼，寻求阻止共和党美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府解散美国教育部，并阻止其裁员近一半。【原文：A group of Democratic state attorneys general on Thursday filed a lawsuit seeking to block Republican U.S. President Donald Trump's administration from dismantling the U.S. Department of Education and halt it from laying off nearly half of its staff.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-led-states-sue-block-trump-dismantling-us-education-department-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZVS2SIHHFIQPMBW452ZAVROPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Axios 报道，白宫撤回特朗普的疾控中心人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Axios 周四报道，白宫正在撤换唐纳德-特朗普总统提名的美国疾病控制和预防中心领导人戴夫-韦尔登（Dave Weldon），就在提名人即将在美国参议院接受确认之际。【原文：The White House is pulling President Donald Trump's nominee to lead the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Dave Weldon, Axios reported on Thursday just as the nominee was set to appear before the U.S. Senate for confirmation.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/white-house-withdraws-trumps-pick-cdc-axios-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEMDNK4GNFJZLCGFOJHVLJSGDE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 12:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降，劳动力市场保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济的美国人数有所下降，但政府大幅削减开支和贸易战升级威胁着劳动力市场的稳定。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell last week, but sharp government spending cuts and an escalating trade war threaten labor market stability.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-amid-labor-market-stability-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AK2JAUIPNINNKALEENEG32POM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 12:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克裁员缩减了帮助实现特朗普能源主导议程所需的员工队伍]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社采访的州政府官员、立法者和机构代表称，特朗普政府大规模裁减联邦工作人员，导致政府许可一些新能源项目的能力放缓，唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "钻井，宝贝，钻井 "议程可能因此受挫。【原文：The Trump administration’s mass layoffs of federal workers have slowed the government’s ability to permit some new energy projects in a potential setback to President Donald Trump’s ‘drill, baby, drill’ agenda, according to state officials, lawmakers and agency representatives interviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/musks-layoffs-shrink-workforce-needed-help-realize-trumps-energy-dominance-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZDCRGZRCRJW3AXRAXQACVWP5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 10:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国各机构提交大规模裁员计划的截止日期为周四]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四是政府机构提交第二波大规模裁员和削减预算计划的截止日期，唐纳德-特朗普总统缩减美国联邦政府的潜在规模可能会变得更加清晰。【原文：The potential scale of President Donald Trump's efforts to shrink the U.S. federal government could become clearer on Thursday, the deadline for government agencies to submit plans for a second wave of mass layoffs and to slash their budgets.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-agencies-face-thursday-deadline-submit-mass-layoff-plans-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6JQRF42KJIC7KOWLV7HOBSRWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 10:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的疾控中心人选韦尔登将面临禽流感和麻疹威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[疫苗评论家戴夫-韦尔登（Dave Weldon）是唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统选中领导美国疾病控制和预防中心（U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention）的人选，他将在这个已经因裁员和公众对 COVID-19 大流行病的不信任而陷入动荡的机构面临麻疹病例上升和禽流感的威胁。【原文：Vaccine critic Dave Weldon, President Donald Trump's pick to lead the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, will face rising measles cases and bird flu threats at an agency already in turmoil from staff cuts and public distrust over the COVID-19 pandemic.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trumps-cdc-pick-weldon-face-bird-flu-measles-threats-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGP5GLZIVNKUTN42V7PF5HHCTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 10:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：美国服装生产为何不可能发生重大转变]]></title><description><![CDATA[几位高管本周告诉路透社，唐纳德-特朗普总统推动的 "美国制造 "正在促使一些美国服装零售商扩大从T恤衫到大衣和西装等各种产品的国内生产。【原文：President Donald Trump's Made in America push is prompting some U.S. clothing retailers to expand domestic production of everything from T-shirts to coats and suits, several executives told Reuters this week.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/why-major-shift-us-clothing-production-is-unlikely-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CAY4HBL3ZOYNOV534VGD56C2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 09:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[警方称美国最高法院法官巴雷特的妹妹成为炸弹威胁目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[当地警方周三表示，保守派美国最高法院大法官艾米-科尼-巴雷特（Amy Coney Barrett）的妹妹本月初在南卡罗来纳州查尔斯顿的家中遭到炸弹威胁。【原文：A sister of conservative U.S. Supreme Court Justice Amy Coney Barrett was the target of a bomb threat at her home in Charleston, South Carolina, earlier this month, local police said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/sister-us-supreme-courts-barrett-target-bomb-threat-police-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIUFZDTVBJLWTFEYB7ZZWWKW5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报道称美国司法部正在调查纽约移民酒店]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，美国司法部周三开始调查纽约市酒店作为移民庇护所的运营情况。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department on Wednesday opened an investigation into the operation of New York City hotels as migrant shelters, according to media reports.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-justice-department-investigating-new-york-migrant-hotels-reports-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JS37A3QHKFPWXJEHRATA3Z3LJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人权组织称特朗普在提到舒默时使用了 "巴勒斯坦人 "这一蔑称]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国穆斯林和犹太人权益组织周三批评唐纳德-特朗普总统将参议院民主党最高级别的参议员查克-舒默称为巴勒斯坦人，这些组织称总统使用该词是一种污蔑。【原文：U.S. Muslim and Jewish advocacy groups criticized President Donald Trump on Wednesday for referring to the top Senate Democrat, Senator Chuck Schumer, as a Palestinian, with the organizations saying the president used the term as a slur.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/rights-groups-say-trump-used-term-palestinian-slur-reference-schumer-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGYP2KQHOBNDRAYEUYSQJW6CAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道被捕哥伦比亚大学学生的妻子说，她天真地以为他是安全的]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国特工逮捕马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil）的前两天，这位哥伦比亚大学学生和巴勒斯坦活动家问他的妻子，如果移民局特工上门，她知道该怎么办吗？【原文：Two days before U.S. agents arrested Mahmoud Khalil, the Columbia University student and Palestinian activist asked his wife if she knew what to do if immigration agents came to their door.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/wife-arrested-columbia-student-says-she-was-naive-believe-he-was-secure-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BP3KHLF6WRPXPIPIUCNIVQQ3ZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:06:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙德克萨斯炼油厂脚手架倒塌致工人受伤--消息人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉工厂运作的人士说，雪佛龙公司位于得克萨斯州帕萨迪纳的炼油厂周三发生脚手架倒塌事故，造成三名工人受伤。【原文：A scaffolding collapse on Wednesday at Chevron Corp's Pasadena, Texas, refinery injured three workers, people familiar with plant operations said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/scaffolding-collapse-injures-workers-chevron-texas-refinery-sources-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4TLBZLFTZPCBPQWBQNGR3KLGY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）取消了原定回收被困宇航员的宇航员航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）周三取消了向国际空间站发射由四名宇航员组成的替代机组人员的计划，该计划将启动美国宇航员布奇-威尔莫尔（Butch Wilmore）和苏尼-威廉姆斯（Suni Williams）期待已久的回家之旅，他们已在国际空间站滞留了九个月。【原文：SpaceX on Wednesday scrubbed the expected launch of a replacement crew of four astronauts to the International Space Station that would have set in motion the long-awaited homecoming of U.S. astronauts Butch Wilmore and Suni Williams, who have been stranded on the station for nine months.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/space/spacex-nasa-set-astronaut-flight-that-will-retrieve-stuck-astronauts-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VHWCCK7FZLFNINA2HXRKPHHOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官称特朗普不能解雇联邦劳工委员会的民主党成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周三表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统无权解除负责审理政府机构与其雇员工会之间纠纷的联邦劳工关系局一名民主党成员的职务，并下令恢复苏珊-徐-格伦德曼（Susan Tsui Grundmann）的职务。【原文：A federal judge on Wednesday said President Donald Trump lacked the power to remove a Democratic member from the Federal Labor Relations Authority, which hears disputes between government agencies and their employees' unions, and ordered that Susan Tsui Grundmann be reinstated to her post.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-says-trump-cannot-fire-democratic-member-federal-labor-board-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THXNMLGHQFM3PFMM4PU22I4WVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特拉华州力争继续保持美国顶级企业法律之家的地位；得克萨斯州准备迎接挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[在埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）敦促美国公司放弃将特拉华州作为其法律归属地并跟随特斯拉迁往德克萨斯州一年后，这两个州的立法者于周三审议了相关法案，这是一场关于公司法的不寻常之战，批评者称这有利于势力强大的股东。【原文：A year after Elon Musk urged U.S. companies to abandon Delaware as their legal home and follow Tesla to Texas, legislators in the two states on Wednesday considered bills in an unusual battle over corporate law that critics say benefits powerful shareholders.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/delaware-aims-remain-top-us-corporate-legal-home-texas-marshals-challenge-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIVBIFMLYFPAFDQFMGWILIGFRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，共和航空首席执行官布莱恩-贝德福德（Bryan Bedford）是美国联邦航空局（FAA）局长的主要候选人]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，共和航空公司首席执行官布莱恩-贝德福德（Bryan Bedford）是唐纳德-特朗普总统提名的下一任联邦航空管理局局长的主要候选人。【原文：Republic Airways CEO Bryan Bedford is the leading candidate to be nominated by President Donald Trump to serve as the next head of the Federal Aviation Administration, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/republic-airways-ceo-bryan-bedford-is-leading-candidate-head-faa-sources-say-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XAWX6BPGHNNWFFGICNTEUKVGL4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官暂时阻止了特朗普针对律师事务所帕金斯-科伊（Perkins Coie）的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官同意暂时阻止执行唐纳德-特朗普总统的行政命令，即针对著名律师事务所珀金斯柯伊（Perkins Coie）促进劳动力多元化的政策以及为其 2016 年大选对手希拉里-克林顿（Hillary Clinton）所做的工作，取消其安全许可并采取其他行动。【原文：A U.S. judge has agreed to temporarily block implementation of President Donald Trump's executive order to strip security clearances and take other actions against prominent law firm Perkins Coie over its policies promoting workforce diversity and its work for his 2016 election rival Hillary Clinton.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-temporarily-blocks-trump-order-targeting-law-firm-perkins-coie-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36IOQPKSVZNPDEVQERFXFCFHYU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社/益普索民意调查显示，许多美国人认为特朗普的经济行动过于反复无常]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社/益普索（Reuters/Ipsos）周三结束的一项民意调查显示，约有57%的美国人认为唐纳德-特朗普总统在动摇美国经济的举措上过于反复无常，包括他对进口产品征税的激进策略令股市受到惊吓。【原文：Some 57% of Americans think President Donald Trump is being too erratic in his moves to shake up the U.S. economy, including his aggressive strategy to tax imports that has spooked the stock market, a Reuters/Ipsos poll that closed on Wednesday found.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/many-americans-see-trumps-actions-economy-too-erratic-reutersipsos-poll-finds-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R43IMQFI25PQTFEZKKOFPFIUBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:40:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫顾问预计美国第一季度国内生产总值至少增长 2% 至 2.5%]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周三告诉福克斯新闻（Fox News），他预计美国第一季度的国内生产总值增长率 "至少 "为 2% 至 2.5%。【原文：White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett told Fox News on Wednesday that he expected U.S. gross domestic product growth to be "at least" 2% to 2.5% in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-adviser-expects-us-gdp-growth-least-2-25-q1-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAVMC7NK2FITPLTFESQNWJTYAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 内政部长称美国可削减 20-30% 的监管措施以促进能源发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国内政部长道格-伯格姆（Doug Burgum）周三表示，美国可能会削减20%至30%的法规，以消除更多能源和采矿项目的障碍。【原文：Interior Secretary Doug Burgum said on Wednesday that the United States could cut 20% to 30% of its regulations as it seeks to remove obstacles to more energy and mining projects.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ceraweek-us-can-slash-20-30-regulation-boost-energy-interior-secretary-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIUUBNOL3FNE7C7QIXLRZYCUBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府开始努力推翻美国环保署的汽车法规]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护局（U.S. Environmental Protection Agency）周三表示，该局正着手推翻拜登政府的汽车尾气排放规定，该规定将迫使汽车制造商生产越来越多的电动汽车。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency said on Wednesday it is beginning the effort to reverse the Biden administration's vehicle emissions rules that would force automakers to build a rising number of electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-begins-effort-reverse-epa-vehicle-rules-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4D2PHNRCK5N3ZIAQFWMZM4FPQ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:24:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国陆军工程兵部队为 3% 的文职人员提供买断服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国陆军工程兵团发言人表示，该兵团周三开始通知 1068 名员工（约占其文职人员总数的 3%），他们有资格参加特朗普政府为联邦工作人员推出的买断计划。【原文：The U.S. Army Corps of Engineers on Wednesday began notifying 1,068 employees, representing about 3% of its civilian workforce, of their eligibility for the Trump administration's buyout program for federal workers, a spokesperson said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-army-corps-engineers-offers-buyouts-3-civilian-staff-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG5SHUIQJNMGJNZA3ZHWLU62RM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上任首月美国预算赤字达 3,070 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三表示，在唐纳德-特朗普总统上任后的第一个完整月里，美国预算赤字总额为 3070 亿美元，比一年前增长了 4%，即 110 亿美元，尽管收入的增长速度超过了支出的增长速度。【原文：The U.S. budget deficit totaled $307 billion for President Donald Trump's first full month in office, up 4%, or $11 billion, from a year ago, the Treasury Department said on Wednesday, even as growth in receipts outpaced that of spending.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-budget-deficit-trumps-first-full-month-office-reaches-307-billion-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIDLXGQXWRKZJLHHDHGJJ6UOJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国环保局将重新考虑拜登清洁电厂规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[环境保护局周三宣布，计划重新审议拜登政府的一项法规，该法规旨在减少发电厂的温室气体排放，这也是新政府在更大范围内解除电力行业法规的努力的一部分。【原文：The Environmental Protection Agency announced on Wednesday it plans to reconsider a Biden administration regulation that sought to reduce greenhouse gas emissions from power plants, part of the new administration's broader efforts to unwind regulations for the power sector.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-epa-reconsider-biden-clean-power-plant-rule-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UA4DWYLYYZOKLO7DPJ5VPTVFHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普政府计划让美国肮脏的煤电厂暂缓排放烟尘]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府打算推翻旨在减少美国燃煤电厂烟尘排放的污染规定，此举旨在帮助美国一些最脏的电厂继续运营。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration intends to overturn pollution rules aimed at reducing soot emissions from U.S. coal-fired power plants in a move intended to help keep some of the nation's dirtiest plants operational, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-plans-give-dirty-us-coal-plants-reprieve-soot-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I42DLTNJINO2DA4SJ6LVYWFT3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普的疾病预防控制中心人选表示将推荐儿童接种麻疹疫苗]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的疾病控制和预防中心负责人大卫-韦尔登将于周四告诉立法者，他计划推荐儿童接种麻疹疫苗。【原文：President Donald Trump's nominee to run the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, David Weldon, will tell lawmakers on Thursday he plans to recommend the measles vaccines for children, Bloomberg News reported.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trumps-cdc-pick-says-he-would-recommend-measles-vaccine-children-bloomberg-news-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLFQJ3S3XZP5HFOA4XDMYSQB5Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将把无人陪伴移民儿童从最大的收容所提供者那里带走]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部（U.S. Department of Health and Human Services）周三表示，联邦政府已停止将孤身移民儿童安置在西南关键项目（Southwest Key Programs）运营的避难所，并将那里的所有儿童转移到其他避难所。【原文：The federal government has stopped the placement of unaccompanied migrant children in shelters operated by the Southwest Key Programs and moved all children there to other shelters, the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services said Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-remove-unaccompanied-migrant-children-largest-shelter-provider-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGGHWZR4VRK4DC2XVSH6HDCSDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:11:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，美国社会保障机构考虑削减电话服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周三报道，美国社会保障局正在考虑大幅削减 7300 万退休和残疾美国人赖以申请和获取政府福利的电话服务。【原文：The U.S. Social Security Administration is considering dramatically curtailing the phone services that 73 million retired and disabled Americans rely on to apply for and access their earned government benefits, the Washington Post reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-social-security-weighs-phone-service-cuts-report-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARQO4B463RNE3BKO344K2ZYPMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，美国社会保障机构考虑削减电话服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周三报道，美国社会保障局正在考虑大幅削减 7300 万退休和残疾美国人赖以申请和获取政府福利的电话服务。【原文：The U.S. Social Security Administration is considering dramatically curtailing the phone services that 73 million retired and disabled Americans rely on to apply for and access their earned government benefits, the Washington Post reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-social-security-weighs-phone-service-cuts-report-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARQO4B463RNE3BKO344K2ZYPMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>