<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:07:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:07:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通推出 1.5 万亿美元计划，促进对美国战略产业的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周一推出了一项 1.5 万亿美元的计划，旨在促进、资助和投资被认为对美国国家安全和经济恢复能力至关重要的行业，包括国防、能源和先进制造业。【原文：JPMorgan Chase launched a $1.5 trillion plan on Monday to facilitate, finance and invest in industries deemed critical to the U.S. national security and economic resilience, including defense, energy and advanced manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-unveils-15-trillion-plan-boost-investments-us-strategic-industries-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJB5GKMIIBJ6VIWTI237HTIXLA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际航空运输协会称，2025 年航空公司供应链将面临 110 亿美元的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家领先的行业组织周一表示，全球航空公司今年将因供应链中断而面临超过 110 亿美元的额外成本，这份报告很可能会再次引发人们对价值 2,500 亿美元的航空业竞争问题的讨论。【原文：Global airlines face more than $11 billion in extra costs from supply chain disruption this year, a leading industry group said on Monday, in a report likely to rekindle debate over competition in the $250-billion aerospace industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airlines-face-11-billion-supply-chain-hit-2025-iata-says-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFXWHCWANVKORJUDNQH4RHOVCE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普淡化贸易强硬言论，华尔街期货攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货在上周五回落后于周一上涨，原因是唐纳德-特朗普总统缓和的语气缓解了市场对中美贸易紧张局势重燃的担忧，投资者重返风险资产。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Monday following Friday's pullback, as investors returned to risk assets after President Donald Trump's softer tone eased concerns over renewed U.S.-China trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/wall-street-futures-climb-after-trump-tones-down-tough-talk-trade-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHXA5OC44ZJDBFL6V66JQ43ZEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:57:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称印度和美国将于本周在华盛顿举行贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位官员说，印度和美国将于本周举行贸易谈判，新德里承诺进口美国能源和天然气，以消除华盛顿对其购买俄罗斯石油的担忧。【原文：India and the United States are set to hold trade talks this week, with New Delhi pledging to import U.S. energy and gas as it aims to address Washington's concerns over its Russian oil purchases, an official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-us-hold-trade-talks-this-week-washington-source-says-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZQ3FIBFENLH7OS3BKG5KOB6FE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:49:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国首次对美国网站 4chan 罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国周一表示，已对美国互联网论坛网站 4chan 处以 20,000 英镑（26,644 美元）的罚款，原因是该网站未能提供有关其服务中非法内容风险的信息，这是新的网络安全制度下的首次处罚。【原文：Britain said on Monday it had issued U.S. internet forum site 4chan with a 20,000 pound ($26,644) fine for failing to provide information about the risk of illegal content on its service, marking the first penalty under the new online safety regime.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/britain-issues-first-online-safety-fine-us-website-4chan-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y624IGDSGRJUJJU4DG7XOFH3ZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:42:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金屡创新高，蒂芙尼所有者路威酩轩集团（LVMH）警惕利润被侵蚀]]></title><description><![CDATA[金价在两年内翻了一番，加上美国关税和美元走软，使得蒂芙尼的所有者路威酩轩集团（LVMH）和其他高端商品行业的公司更难维护毛利率。【原文：The doubling of gold prices in two years, along with U.S. tariffs and a weaker dollar, have made it harder to defend gross margins for Tiffany owner LVMH and others in the high-end goods industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/soaring-gold-prices-bring-new-headache-tiffany-owner-lvmh-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIOL5NU22FPDXGPY5HWRCCQZTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:12:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能支出激增，台积电第三季度利润预计飙升 28]]></title><description><![CDATA[台积电是全球最大的先进人工智能芯片制造商，由于对人工智能基础设施的无限需求，预计其第三季度利润将大增 28%，创下历史新高，不过美国关税可能会影响其前景。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest manufacturer of advanced artificial intelligence chips, is expected to post a 28% jump in third-quarter profit to a record due to the insatiable demand for AI infrastructure, though U.S. tariffs could impact its outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsmc-q3-profit-expected-soar-28-ai-spending-boom-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NJLM55IPBKVXN5F4F2PFA3MTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 推迟新任首席执行官的 2026 年战略发布会]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 公司已将其最新战略计划的发布时间推迟到 2026 年第二季度，以便新任首席执行官 Antonio Filosa 有比原先预期更长的时间为资本市场日做准备。【原文：Stellantis has postponed the launch of its latest strategic plan until the second quarter of 2026 to give new CEO Antonio Filosa longer than originally expected to prepare for its capital markets day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/stellantis-pushes-back-timing-new-ceos-strategic-plan-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SOFWRQNDORLDLNXBMHIV2CL7FI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:40:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚在阿尔巴内斯-特朗普会晤前就关键矿产储备进行磋商]]></title><description><![CDATA[在澳大利亚和美国领导人准备于下周举行会晤之际，业内人士透露，澳大利亚正在为其关键矿产储备制定一项计划，该计划将侧重于未来产量的销售，从而限制实物储备的需求。【原文：Australia is formulating a plan for its critical minerals reserve that will focus on sales of future production, limiting the need for a physical stockpile, industry sources said, as Australian and U.S. leaders prepare to meet next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/australia-consults-critical-minerals-stockpile-ahead-albanese-trump-meeting-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXC4G2VYT5LTZAAZGI53XDMWJM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:14:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[G20 风险监督机构警告金融市场可能崩溃]]></title><description><![CDATA[二十国集团（G20）风险监督机构周一表示，鉴于当前不确定的经济和地缘政治背景，全球股价和其他资产最近的飙升使市场很容易出现暴跌。【原文：The latest surge in global share prices and other assets has left markets susceptible to a crash given the current uncertain economic and geopolitical backdrop, the G20's risk watchdog said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/g20-risk-watchdog-warns-potential-financial-market-crash-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NTNZUZH4FJS5E34QBBYOWPX24</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Tritax Big Box 将以 14 亿美元收购 Blackstone 的物流资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国房地产投资信托公司 Tritax Big Box 周一同意以 10.4 亿英镑（13.9 亿美元）的价格从美国私募股权投资集团 Blackstone 收购物流资产。【原文：British real estate investment trust Tritax Big Box on Monday agreed to buy logistics assets from U.S. private equity group Blackstone for 1.04 billion pounds ($1.39 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/uks-tritax-big-box-buy-blackstones-logistics-assets-14-billion-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKA6EHIKIZLZRIGZYXFAILA5AA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:18:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长称韩国正与美国就建立外汇互换的各种方式进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部长周一表示，作为贸易协议的一部分，韩国正在与美国讨论建立双边外汇互换额度的各种方式，以控制美国拟议投资对国内货币市场的影响。【原文：South Korea is discussing with the U.S. various ways to set up a bilateral foreign exchange swap line as part of a trade deal to contain the impact of proposed U.S. investments on the domestic currency market, the country's finance minister said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-talks-with-us-various-ways-set-up-fx-swap-minister-says-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMTPPC36KBJMTK634ZXEB5UC74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管有美国支持，阿根廷投资者的看涨押注仍面临中期选举风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者表示，阿根廷即将举行的大选是市场看涨押注的主要风险，因为美国对哈维尔-米莱伊总统自由主义经济政策的财政支持浪潮并不能保证选民会支持他的少数党。【原文：Argentina's looming elections are the main risk to bullish market bets as a wave of U.S. financial support for President Javier Milei's libertarian economic policies does not guarantee that voters will back his minority party, investors say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentinas-bullish-investor-bets-face-midterm-election-risk-despite-us-backing-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCRNWIG45ZPGHIRXXJPS5IMS3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度监察机构要求印度航空公司检查部分 787 喷气式飞机的应急电源系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度航空监管机构周一表示，已要求印度航空公司检查其部分 787 喷气式飞机上的紧急供电系统，即拉姆空气涡轮（RAT）。【原文：India's aviation regulator said on Monday it has asked Air India to inspect the emergency power system, known as the Ram Air Turbine (RAT), on some of its 787 jets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/india-watchdog-asks-air-india-inspect-emergency-power-system-some-787-jets-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLXYKBZ2SJMTFOOQ7SN7D6SOZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普重燃对华贸易战为国际货币基金组织和世界银行会议蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周聚集在华盛顿的各国财政部长们准备讨论全球经济在唐纳德-特朗普的关税攻击面前令人惊讶的韧性--直到中美贸易战再次爆发，美国总统威胁要对中国进口商品征收 100%的关税，令市场陷入低迷。【原文：Finance chiefs gathering in Washington this week were ready to discuss the global economy's surprising resilience in the face of Donald Trump's tariff assaults - until the U.S.-China trade war erupted again with the U.S. president threatening 100% duties on Chinese imports and sending markets into a tailspin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-reignited-trade-war-with-china-clouds-imf-world-bank-meetings-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3KC5ZH5XFLXNPTX3DJ3DI4WHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国如何承受特朗普的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[早期迹象显示，美国公司和消费者在美国新的进口关税中首当其冲，这与唐纳德-特朗普总统的说法相矛盾，也使美联储对抗通胀的斗争变得更加复杂。【原文：U.S. companies and consumers are bearing the brunt of the country's new import tariffs, early indications show, contradicting assertions by President Donald Trump and complicating the Federal Reserve's fight against inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-united-states-is-eating-trumps-tariffs-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3A4UH7XXRM4NMFG2CPMWY3VSM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济学家认为美国经济增长强劲，但就业增长乏力，通胀更加严峻]]></title><description><![CDATA[全美商业经济协会的一项调查显示，尽管就业增长缓慢、失业率上升和通胀加剧将影响经济前景，但预计商业投资的激增将抵消消费和全球贸易增长的疲软，并使美国经济保持接近趋势的增长。【原文：Surging business investment is expected to offset weaker growth in consumption and global trade and keep the U.S. economy growing near trend, according to a National Association for Business Economics survey, though slow job growth, higher unemployment and stickier inflation will mar the outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/economists-see-stronger-us-growth-weak-job-gains-stickier-inflation-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6JIS7FDF5NGPIJKNB3BR5ZC7U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:06:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[招聘公司称，金融科技和人工智能推动第三季度伦敦金融业职位空缺增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[摹根麦肯立（Morgan McKinley）周一发布的《伦敦就业监测》（London Employment Monitor）报告显示，金融科技公司的蓬勃发展以及对人工智能的需求不断增长，提升了伦敦金融业第三季度的职位空缺数量。【原文：A boom at financial technology firms and growing demand to get to grips with artificial intelligence lifted financial sector job vacancy numbers in London in the third-quarter, Morgan McKinley's London Employment Monitor showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/fintech-ai-drive-london-finance-job-vacancy-growth-q3-recruiter-says-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXSLXONGOBNNNIJZ45YIDGG7XA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:06:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华平投资集团将以超过 7 亿欧元的价格收购德国 PSI 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司华平投资（Warburg Pincus）周一表示，计划以超过 7 亿欧元（8.1326 亿美元）的价格收购德国软件公司 PSI Software。【原文：Private equity firm Warburg Pincus plans to buy German software firm PSI Software for more than 700 million euros ($813.26 million), the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/warburg-pincus-buy-germanys-psi-over-700-million-euros-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z36DH5LYHNKFVMAEQF4N5VM23I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:45:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 9 月进出口超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税协议仍遥遥无期，而投资者又在努力应对双方贸易战中的最新炮火，制造商们在美国以外的市场找到了买家，这推动了中国 9 月份的出口增长。【原文：China's export growth picked up pace in September, buoyed by manufacturers finding buyers in markets beyond the U.S. as a tariff deal with President Donald Trump remained elusive while investors grappled with the latest salvoes in their trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-september-exports-imports-surpass-expectations-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GA57GVODNN4NDDQ7WAUDXVO7E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌称澳大利亚关于青少年使用社交媒体的法律 "极难 "执行]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌（Google）周一表示，澳大利亚要执行禁止 16 岁以下青少年使用社交媒体的法律 "极其困难"，并警告说政府的举措不会使儿童上网更安全。【原文：Alphabet-owned Google on Monday said it would be "extremely difficult" for Australia to enforce a law prohibiting people younger than 16 from using social media, warning that the government's initiative would not make children safer online.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/google-says-australian-law-teen-social-media-use-extremely-difficult-enforce-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLIBD4KSRZJQPA523UJZY5AUSQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:11:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁后，联合石化将超级油轮调离山东港口]]></title><description><![CDATA[LSEG的数据显示，美国周五对中国山东日照港的一个进口码头实施制裁后，一艘向该港运送石油的超级油轮在周末改变了目的地。【原文：A supertanker carrying oil to the Chinese port of Rizhao in Shandong province changed its destination from there over the weekend after the U.S. imposed sanctions on an import terminal at the port on Friday, LSEG data shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/unipec-diverts-supertanker-shandong-port-after-us-sanctions-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKNDEBK3HZO3BMCTW6RSMQJBWE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 02:25:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰富瑞认为 First Brands 破产影响有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰富瑞金融集团（Jefferies Financial Group）周日表示，该公司对破产汽车零部件制造商 First Brands Group 的风险敞口有限，任何潜在损失都 "可随时吸收"。【原文：Jefferies Financial Group said on Sunday its exposure to bankrupt auto parts maker First Brands Group is limited and any potential losses will be "readily absorbable".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jefferies-sees-limited-impact-first-brands-bankruptcy-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQ6HKINTCRMGFIAV3HP2FPQEKU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 02:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国汽车销量在 "金九月 "加速增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[9 月份是中国汽车市场的传统旺季，由于经销商和消费者在更多地方政府暂停汽车以旧换新补贴政策之前利用了这一政策，中国的汽车销量加速增长。【原文：China's car sales accelerated in September, the traditional peak season for the auto market, as dealers and consumers took advantage of trade-in subsidies before more local governments suspended the incentives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-car-sales-quicken-september-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BRCTNUHIZKPPC2NPR6PBVJW34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 02:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场关注中美贸易紧张局势和政治，美元保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元从周一早盘的大跌中回升，原因是投资者希望华盛顿能缓和其与中国政府贸易战的最新升级，而法国和日本的政治事态发展则削弱了欧元和日元的走势。【原文：The U.S. dollar recovered from a selloff in early trade on Monday as investors hoped Washington may temper its latest escalation of the trade war with Beijing, while political developments in France and Japan undermined the euro and the yen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dollar-steadies-markets-focus-us-china-trade-tensions-politics-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAZ4VQQUKJIEXK4AWSXLL4TSUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美紧张局势导致油价大幅下跌后反弹 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在上一交易日触及五个月低点后，周一回吐了一些涨幅，因为投资者希望中美两国总统可能举行的会谈能够缓解世界上最大的两个经济体和石油消费国之间的贸易紧张局势。【原文：Oil prices clawed back some gains on Monday after hitting five-month lows in the previous session as investors hoped potential talks between the presidents of the U.S. and China could ease trade tensions between the world's two largest economies and oil consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rebounds-1-after-sharp-losses-us-china-tensions-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6U6UY63OJISVHH6KXCQQDYB54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:50:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易战再起将使中国股市从高位回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国股市周一将承压，因为华盛顿和中国政府之间重启的贸易战打击了风险偏好，并刺激获利回吐，股市徘徊在十年来的最高水平附近。【原文：China stocks are set to come under pressure on Monday as the renewed trade war between Washington and Beijing hits risk appetite and spurs profit-taking in a share market hovering near its highest level in a decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/revived-us-trade-war-set-knock-chinas-stocks-lofty-peaks-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WR6PRFBB25J4BN7QLCLS5NJYCM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LG 能源解决方案公司称第三季度营业利润可能增长 34]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉（Tesla）和通用汽车（General Motors）的电动汽车电池供应商 LG Energy Solution 周一表示，其第三季度营业利润可能同比增长 34%，达到 6010 亿韩元（约合 4.2 亿美元）。【原文：LG Energy Solution , an electric car battery supplier for Tesla and General Motors , said on Monday its third-quarter operating profit likely rose 34% to 601 billion won ($420 million) from a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lg-energy-solution-says-q3-operating-profit-likely-up-34-2025-10-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFCDBGE3IRPT5K6G2AFSPPZ73Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[风险情绪稳定，华尔街期货反弹，亚洲仍不稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管有迹象表明风险情绪已经稳定，华尔街期货反弹，但在中美贸易战的新一轮冲击下，亚洲股市周一的开局注定坎坷。【原文：Asian stocks were set for a rocky start on Monday after fresh broadsides in the U.S. China trade war spooked markets with already stretched valuations, though there were signs risk sentiment had steadied with Wall St futures bouncing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CANKFGA6AJMFXPB3NY7ELMUYRM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国餐饮企业蜂拥新加坡，迈出扩张第一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[过去一年里，创纪录数量的中餐馆和咖啡馆涌入新加坡，它们将新加坡作为全球扩张的试验田，以躲避国内疲软的消费需求、激烈的价格竞争和超低的利润率。【原文：A record number of Chinese restaurants and cafes have flooded Singapore over the past year, using the island as a test bed for global expansion as they escape pallid consumer demand, extreme price competition and super-squeezed profit margins back home.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-food-beverage-firms-flock-singapore-first-step-expansion-drive-2025-10-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMSN3MFATRK6JF7O4EFZRW45OA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:11:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>