<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:10:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:10:04 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[罗马尼亚预计美国新贸易协定将对经济增长造成小幅冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗马尼亚周一表示，美国对欧洲商品征收15%的进口关税将意味着中欧第二大经济体受到的打击不大，而依赖出口的斯洛伐克则称赞美国的贸易协议是一个 "好结果"。【原文：Romania said on Monday a 15% U.S. import tariff on European goods would mean a small hit to central Europe's second-largest economy, while export-reliant Slovakia hailed the U.S. trade deal as a "good result".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/romania-expects-small-growth-hit-new-us-trade-deal-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFVI4VE6NZOONIWPKG73BGD5NQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:07:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员希望马斯克阻止东南亚金融诈骗集团使用 "星链 "系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位民主党参议员周一敦促 SpaceX 公司首席执行官埃隆-马斯克阻止东南亚的跨国犯罪集团利用 Starlink 卫星互联网服务对美国人实施诈骗。【原文：A Democratic senator on Monday urged SpaceX CEO Elon Musk to block transnational criminal groups in Southeast Asia from using Starlink satellite internet service to commit fraud against Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-senator-wants-musk-block-use-starlink-by-financial-fraud-groups-southeast-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLV6MTMKNJKJBJ4MMIV47Z4L3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国太空竞赛白热化，Firefly Aerospace 首次公开募股寻求 55 亿美元估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[太空技术初创公司 Firefly Aerospace 在美国首次公开募股的目标估值约为 55 亿美元，因为投资者对高增长行业的偏好显示出持续反弹的迹象。【原文：Space technology startup Firefly Aerospace is targeting a valuation of about $5.5 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, as investor appetite for high-growth sectors shows signs of a sustained rebound.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/firefly-aerospace-seeks-55-billion-valuation-ipo-us-space-race-heats-up-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6LHOEQUGBO4LKTPQDONSAD67U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Auterion 称将向乌克兰提供 33,000 套人工智能无人机制导套件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国防务公司 Auterion 周一表示，该公司将为乌克兰无人机提供 33,000 套人工智能制导工具，五角大楼为此提供了 5,000 万美元的合同资金。【原文：U.S. defence company Auterion will provide 33,000 artificial intelligence guidance kits for Ukrainian drones, funded by a $50 million Pentagon contract, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/auterion-says-it-will-provide-ukraine-with-33000-ai-drone-guidance-kits-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QY7JQUFK7JL7LOZPBCPH3IZNEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:26:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受欧盟制裁的印度炼油厂纳亚拉公司就断电问题将微软告上法庭]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯支持的印度炼油厂纳亚拉能源公司（Nayara Energy）周一表示，在总部位于美国的软件巨头突然单方面中止关键服务后，该公司已开始对微软提起法律诉讼。【原文：Russia-backed Indian refiner Nayara Energy Monday said it has started legal proceedings against Microsoft following the abrupt and unilateral suspension of critical services by the U.S.-headquartered software giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eu-sanctioned-indian-refiner-nayara-takes-microsoft-court-over-outage-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3COXY3YVCRJ3BK5ARDA7I54QKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:18:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大道明银行任命新行长领导监督工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[道明银行已任命独立董事约翰-麦金太尔（John MacIntyre）为新任董事会主席，这家加拿大贷款机构将启用新的后卫来加强监管并让投资者放心。【原文：TD Bank has named independent director John MacIntyre as the new chair of its board, as the Canadian lender turns to a new guard to bolster oversight and reassure investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/canadas-td-bank-names-new-chair-steer-oversight-push-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4I4VKTN5JRJHFICUZTHSPP5ADM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:17:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟称特木公司违反了防止销售非法产品的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周一称，中国在线市场特姆优在防止通过其平台销售非法产品方面做得不够，因而违反了欧盟规则。【原文：The European Commission on Monday said Chinese online marketplace Temu was breaking EU rules by not doing enough to prevent the sale of illegal products through its platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/eu-says-temu-breach-rules-prevent-sale-illegal-products-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAICRRQTO5IWHEGPR5HTLAISBY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:55:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BTG Pactual 将以 1.75 亿美元收购汇丰银行在乌拉圭的业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西银行 BTG Pactual 周一表示，将以 1.75 亿美元的价格收购汇丰银行在乌拉圭的业务，这是该银行首次进军这个西班牙语国家，并将扩大其在拉丁美洲的业务。【原文：Brazilian bank BTG Pactual on Monday said it will snap up HSBC's operations in Uruguay for $175 million, marking its first foray into the Spanish-speaking country and expanding its presence in Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/btg-pactual-buy-hsbcs-uruguay-operation-175-million-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6E3K53BZYJI47MPMYSTNJOW25Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻美欧协议提振市场和美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36HLJAJ4DNKMDLGGJLID5GTHRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯就俄航网络攻击立案调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯总检察长办公室周一称，俄罗斯检察官对未经授权访问俄航计算机系统的行为展开刑事调查，此前该航空公司将数十个航班被取消归咎于信息技术故障。【原文：Russian prosecutors on Monday opened a criminal investigation into unauthorised access to computer systems at Aeroflot , the Prosecutor General's office said, after the airline blamed an IT failure for the cancellation of dozens of flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-opens-criminal-case-over-aeroflot-cyberattack-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MPVJ5OIKVK4PAZLHBHSVZGL2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:28:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟同意每年购买 2,500 亿美元液化天然气，美国液化天然气生产商大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国液化天然气开发商的股票在周一盘前交易中大涨，此前欧盟承诺在未来三年内购买价值 7500 亿美元的超冷燃料，作为一项全面贸易协议的一部分。【原文：Shares of U.S. liquefied natural gas developers surged in premarket trading on Monday, after the European Union pledged to purchase $750 billion worth of the super-cooled fuel over the next three years as part of a sweeping trade pact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-lng-producers-soar-eu-agrees-250-billion-annual-purchases-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEVOYTY6OFORPKUN3AWM2QW7FM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interactive Brokers 考虑为客户推出新的稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国放宽对加密货币行业的监管，许多大型金融公司都在大力押注数字代币热潮，互动经纪集团（Interactive Brokers Group）正在考虑为客户推出稳定币。【原文：Interactive Brokers Group is considering launching a stablecoin for customers, joining a number of large financial firms that are betting big on the digital token boom as the U.S. eases regulations around the crypto industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/interactive-brokers-considers-launching-new-stablecoin-customers-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3JCS57X6VKGRBJ4TF6VV4DXQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[这家由贝索斯支持的电动汽车初创公司打赌，你会为你的小型皮卡中的立体声音响支付额外费用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年春天，当威尔-哈瑟尔廷在网上看到初创公司 Slate Auto 推出的小型箱式电动皮卡的图片时，他立刻就加入了候选名单。稀疏的内饰和曲柄车窗
 
 让他想起了他在田纳西州孟菲斯长大时身边的那些简朴的皮卡车
 
 - 但最让他着迷的还是低于 20,000 美元的价格。【原文：When Will Haseltine saw images online of a small, boxy electric pickup from startup Slate Auto this past spring, he got on the waitlist right away. The sparse interior and crank windows
 
 reminded him of the no-frills pickups he grew up around in Memphis, Tennessee
 
 – but he was most enamored with the sub-$20,000 price tag.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/this-bezos-backed-ev-startup-is-betting-youll-pay-extra-stereo-your-petite-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7WDWND6RBMMVAZQANRD6WCTGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:21:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在行动密集的一周到来之前，华尔街期货受美欧贸易协议提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，华尔街期货攀升，原因是美国和欧盟之间达成的贸易协议在本周伊始提振了市场情绪，本周将迎来巨头财报、美联储会议和美国关税最后期限。【原文：Wall Street futures climbed on Monday as a trade agreement between the U.S. and the European Union boosted sentiment at the start of a week packed with megacap earnings, a Federal Reserve meeting and a U.S. tariff deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/wall-street-futures-boosted-by-us-eu-trade-deal-ahead-action-packed-week-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQNDRK3SDFNPJBDCFGSCRE4FMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行博客认为：美元稳定币威胁欧洲货币自主权]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行周一发表博文称，美元在稳定币中的早期主导地位给美国带来了优势，最终可能推高欧洲的借贷成本，削弱欧洲央行的自主性，并增加对美国的地缘政治依赖。【原文：The dollar's early dominance of stablecoins gives the U.S. an advantage that could ultimately push up borrowing costs for Europe, reduce the ECB's autonomy and increase geopolitical dependency on the U.S., an ECB blog post argued on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-stablecoins-threaten-europes-monetary-autonomy-ecb-blog-argues-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6WNIDFUSVORTFEI32LOMHEAMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储在筛选喜忧参半的经济数据时预计将维持利率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[令唐纳德-特朗普总统懊恼不已的是，美国央行很可能在本周的政策会议上维持利率不变，但这并不是说不会有激烈的辩论，如果不是两位美联储理事，也可能会有一位理事罕见地提出异议，支持降低借贷成本。【原文：The U.S. central bank, to President Donald Trump's chagrin, will likely leave interest rates unchanged at a policy meeting this week, but that's not to say there won't be a vigorous debate, with one if not two Federal Reserve governors possibly casting a rare dissent in support of lower borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-expected-keep-rates-unchanged-it-sifts-through-mixed-economic-data-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6AM6A54EZIOXIOVW5RUITED2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲对美国贸易协议的反应既欣慰又担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲各国政府和企业都承认这是一项不平衡的协议，但它避免了更深层次的贸易战。【原文：European governments and companies acknowledged what was seen as an unbalanced deal but one that avoided a deeper trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/europe-reacts-with-mix-relief-concern-us-trade-deal-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAHXXRMWZVMPHMRUAJDOR2BBNQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德面临 "向我展示 "的时刻，在美国山寨产品禁令后促进 Wegovy 增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者和分析师表示，美国对诺和诺德公司Wegovy仿制药的禁令已开始提升这种减肥药的使用率，但该公司需要在未来几个月内显示出更强劲的增长势头，以增强市场信心。【原文：A U.S. ban on copycat versions of Novo Nordisk's Wegovy has begun to lift use of the weight loss drug, but the company will need to show more robust growth in the months ahead to bolster market confidence, investors and analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-faces-show-me-moment-boost-wegovy-growth-after-us-copycat-ban-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJ5Q6YKJQZK5PCEDHVAPADRC5Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普推动贸易之际，美国民主党和共和党计划通过法案向中国施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国两大党的参议员计划在本周提出针对中国对待少数民族、持不同政见者和台湾问题的法案，在唐纳德-特朗普总统关注与北京的贸易之际强调安全和人权。【原文：U.S. senators from both major parties plan to introduce bills this week targeting China over its treatment of minority groups, dissidents and Taiwan, emphasizing security and human rights as President Donald Trump focuses on trade with Beijing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-democrats-republicans-plan-bills-pressure-china-trump-pushes-trade-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQJZINSX45L6RJVHDBQWA5VSKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行卡齐米尔称 9 月降息需要经济出现意外大转变]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯洛伐克决策者彼得-卡齐米尔（Peter Kazimir）周一表示，欧洲中央银行并不急于再次降低借贷成本，需要出现意想不到的重大经济转变，才有理由在9月份采取行动。【原文：The European Central Bank is not in any hurry to lower borrowing costs again and it would take a major unexpected economic shift to make a case for action in September, Slovak policymaker Peter Kazimir said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ecbs-kazimir-says-big-unexpected-economic-shift-needed-september-rate-cut-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPF4ZFL5RVM2LLGI2NISW433LU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 09:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛集团称，对冲基金放弃科技，购买生活必需品]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份给高盛（Goldman Sachs）客户的说明称，最近一周，对冲基金以 12 个月来最快的速度逃离科技股，而此时，标准普尔 500 指数（S&amp;P 500）刚刚创下历史新高。【原文：Hedge funds fled technology stocks at the fastest pace in 12 months in the latest week, just as the S&amp;P 500 reached all-time highs, a note to Goldman Sachs clients and seen by Reuters said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-ditch-tech-buy-essentials-goldman-sachs-says-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWRDAQKCGRJCZIIB2EPB2EJURQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 09:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲领导人对美欧贸易协定作出反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周日与欧盟达成了一项框架贸易协议，对欧盟大部分商品征收 15%的进口关税，避免了这两个占全球贸易近三分之一的盟国之间爆发更大规模的贸易战。【原文：The U.S. struck a framework trade agreement with the European Union on Sunday, imposing a 15% import tariff on most EU goods and averting a bigger trade war between the two allies that account for almost a third of global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/european-leaders-react-us-eu-trade-deal-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">547C3KYIZNPKBC5OUAUVHIPCBM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 09:12:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲公司躲过特朗普贸易战 "飓风"，但感叹关税提高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，欧洲企业不知道是该为来之不易的美国贸易协议欢呼，还是该为与唐纳德-特朗普总统第二任期前相比仍在大幅飙升的关税哀叹。【原文：European companies were left wondering on Monday whether to cheer a hard-won U.S. trade deal or lament a still sharp jump in tariffs versus those in place before President Donald Trump's second term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/europe-inc-swerves-trump-trade-war-hurricane-laments-higher-tariffs-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KSK65MPHBMAHNG3PUFVN6YHSE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动车销量增长，大众斯柯达上半年利润增长 12]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车旗下斯柯达汽车公司（Skoda Auto）周一表示，今年上半年，该公司增加了电动汽车在销售组合中的份额，营业利润增长近 12%，达到 13 亿欧元（15.2 亿美元）。【原文：Skoda Auto, a Volkswagen unit, increased the share of electric vehicles in its sales mix in the first half of the year and posted a nearly 12% rise in operating profit to 1.3 billion euros ($1.52 billion), it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vws-skoda-posts-12-profit-rise-h1-electric-sales-grow-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODWQ6IPAJZIX5NECCQD5AU3ZOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:24:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：五张图表解读大型酒类产品为何需要美国关税减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟与美国周末达成的贸易协议被一些欧洲官员认为是不平衡的，而欧盟葡萄酒和烈酒生产商可能成为该协议中为数不多的赢家。【原文：European Union wine and spirits producers could emerge among the few winners of a EU-U.S. trade deal agreed at the weekend that some European officials consider unbalanced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/why-big-alcohol-needs-us-tariff-relief-five-charts-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLQKZVOQQFP3FEDJNEATW6XNIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国消费者投诉显示汽车销售数据普遍被篡改]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社（Reuters）对消费者投诉进行分析后发现，近年来，中国汽车制造商和经销商为应对全球最大汽车市场上激烈的价格战而采取的哄抬汽车销量的手段越来越普遍。【原文：A tactic used by Chinese automakers and dealers to inflate car sales has grown increasingly common in recent years in response to a bruising price war in the world's largest auto market, a Reuters analysis of consumer complaints has found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-consumer-complaints-show-widespread-padding-car-sales-figures-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UH4K6IHD4JKSTCQU2EAAB7IEZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众奥迪以关税和重组为由下调全年业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车旗下高端品牌奥迪周一下调了全年业绩指导，理由是受到美国提高进口关税和重组费用的影响。【原文：Volkswagen's premium brand Audi on Monday cut its its full-year guidance, citing the impact of higher U.S. import tariffs and restructuring expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vws-audi-cuts-full-year-outlook-citing-tariffs-restructuring-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZHE5BU6GJJQJBZCP5EURXASXA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称多位美国高管将于本周访华]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士周一告诉路透社，一个由美国高管组成的高级代表团将于本周前往中国，在美中贸易全国委员会（USCBC）的组织下会见中国高级官员。【原文：A high-level delegation of American executives will travel to China this week to meet senior Chinese officials in a trip organised by the U.S.-China Business Council (USCBC), two sources with knowledge of the visit told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/several-us-executives-visit-china-this-week-sources-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAEHKSW6DVKXFE7GIRPLLC6TYI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》：特朗普暂停出口管制以支持中国贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周一称，美国已暂停限制对华技术出口，以避免干扰与中国政府的贸易谈判，并支持唐纳德-特朗普总统为确保今年与习近平主席会晤所做的努力。【原文：The U.S. has paused curbs on tech exports to China to avoid disrupting trade talks with Beijing and support President Donald Trump's efforts to secure a meeting with President Xi Jinping this year, the Financial Times said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-pauses-export-controls-bolster-china-trade-deal-ft-says-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFV5JF2K4NOINF5NZOJFLJJGFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[啤酒制造商喜力上半年利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰啤酒制造商喜力周一公布，尽管其在欧洲的销售受到拖累，关税风险增加，但其半年有机营业利润仍增长了 7.4%，超过了分析师的预期。【原文：Dutch brewer Heineken on Monday reported a 7.4% rise in half-year organic operating profit, ahead of analyst expectations, even as its sales in Europe dragged and tariff risks increased.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/brewer-heinekens-first-half-profits-beat-forecasts-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFF6PY6KVJNJ5EZYCI2SQLA27Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>