<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 03:33:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 03:33:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社称，波音公司警告客户 737 Max 将进一步推迟生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，波音公司最近几周已通知一些737 Max客户，定于2025年和2026年交付的飞机可能会面临3至6个月的额外延期。【原文：Boeing has notified some 737 Max customers in recent weeks that aircraft due for delivery in 2025 and 2026 might face additional delays of three to six months, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-warns-customers-further-delays-737-max-bloomberg-news-says-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AW5346NO5LEJGPZU6EAZXZWMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[干预神经紧张，日元走势波澜不惊；亚洲股市瞩目本周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元在震荡交易中涨跌互现，反映出投资者在美国通胀报告低于预期后认为东京已采取干预措施支撑日元后的恐慌情绪。【原文：The yen swung between losses and gains on Friday in volatile trade, reflecting investors' skittishness after Tokyo was thought to have intervened to prop up the Japanese currency in the wake of a cooler-than-expected U.S. inflation report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZG7R72CP6FJ3NB7JBRLQ3QSLLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国无情的电商价格战让卖家入不敷出]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着销售增长放缓、价格压力增大，以及购物平台为吸引越来越注重成本的客户而采取越来越激进的政策，中国的电子商务供应商正在为生存而挣扎。【原文：Chinese e-commerce vendors are struggling for survival as sales growth slows, price pressure rises and shopping platforms compete with ever-more aggressive policies to attract increasingly cost-conscious customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-relentless-e-commerce-price-war-leaves-sellers-struggling-make-ends-meet-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFL5CM2IRZIPHP3TNDAHBGLQ2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:31:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩亚货运采购后仁川航空考虑订购宽体货机]]></title><description><![CDATA[仁川航空首席执行官表示，一旦收购韩亚航空货运部门的交易敲定，仁川航空将成为韩国第二大货运航空公司，该公司将考虑采用波音和空客货机来更新宽体机机队。【原文：Air Incheon, set to become South Korea's second-biggest freight carrier once a deal to buy Asiana Airlines' cargo unit is finalised, will consider both Boeing and Airbus freighters to refresh the widebody fleet, its CEO said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-incheon-consider-widebody-freighter-orders-after-asiana-cargo-purchase-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6ZBZDN6RJL4TKMXO4JQO236RY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出生率下降，日本纸尿裤制造商寻求成人市场创收]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本一家工厂里的大型金属臂将一簇簇蓬松的白色长方形布料从旋转台上扫下，放入一组布料中，然后用塑料包装起来，准备装运。【原文：A large metal arm in a Japanese factory swept a cluster of fluffy white fabric rectangles off a carousel into a group to be wrapped in plastic before packaging for shipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-diaper-makers-look-adult-market-revenue-births-fall-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4WXQULKAJOTBMKHIVQEIAEOUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀降温，夏季需求强劲，石油上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲交易时段早盘，油价上涨，因为有迹象表明夏季需求强劲，全球最大的石油市场美国的通胀压力有所缓解，这增强了投资者的信心。【原文：Oil prices rose in early Asian trading hours on Friday as signs of strong summer demand and easing inflationary pressures in the world's biggest oil market, the United States, bolstered investor confidence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-cooling-us-inflation-strong-summer-demand-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7AF46ZQGN5IS5A6XRSZKKJRCJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元波动令汇市紧张不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国 6 月份消费者物价意外下降，日元在前一交易日大幅飙升，引发了市场对东京采取干预措施使日元脱离 38 年低点的猜测，周五日元汇率波动剧烈。【原文：The yen was volatile on Friday after a sharp surge in the previous session in the wake of U.S. consumer prices unexpectedly dropping in June, stoking speculation that Tokyo had intervened to lift the currency away from 38-year lows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/volatile-yen-keeps-currency-market-edge-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXADV7DZJBM3LHUQQDZIMNJREM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:43:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本最高外汇外交官称当局将根据需要对日元采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最高货币外交官神田雅人（Masato Kanda）周五表示，在日元隔夜飙升引发市场对货币干预的猜测之后，日本当局将在外汇市场采取必要的行动。【原文：Japan's top currency diplomat, Masato Kanda, said on Friday authorities will take action as needed in the foreign exchange market, after the yen's spike overnight raised market speculation about currency intervention.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-top-fx-diplomat-says-authorities-take-action-needed-yen-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2Q2DSUZ75M7LJ44J3A2ZVB7NM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:28:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北约峰会强调 RTX、波音等公司的防务交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[在华盛顿举行的北约峰会为美国顶级防务公司和其他公司展示了一系列重大交易，包括 RTX 公司、洛克希德-马丁公司、波音公司、挪威康斯伯格防务公司和瑞典萨博公司。【原文：The NATO summit in Washington showcased a series of significant deals for top U.S. defense companies and others, including RTX , Lockheed Martin , Boeing , Norway's Kongsberg Defense and Sweden's SAAB .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/nato-summit-highlights-defense-deals-rtx-boeing-others-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IB3OCIPJYJJADLWOKL35FX2SIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:27:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rho Motion称，6月份全球电动汽车销量增长13%，欧洲下降7]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场研究公司 Rho Motion 称，受中国增长的推动，6 月份全电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车的全球销量与 2023 年同期相比增长了 13%，而欧洲的销量则有所下降。【原文：Global sales of fully electric and plug-in hybrid vehicles rose by 13% in June versus the same month in 2023 driven by growth in China, while they dropped in Europe, market research firm Rho Motion said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-ev-sales-up-13-june-down-7-europe-rho-motion-says-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5YRBAMGAJPR3DFQBSLOW7S3QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，UAW 因担心特朗普可能击败拜登而考虑下一步行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的消息人士称，美国汽车工人联合会主席肖恩-费恩（Shawn Fain）周四晚些时候会见了工会执行董事会，讨论了他对乔-拜登（Joe Biden）总统能否在 11 月大选中击败唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的深切担忧。【原文：United Auto Workers President Shawn Fain met with the union's executive board late on Thursday to discuss his deep concerns with President Joe Biden's ability to defeat Donald Trump in the November election, three sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/uaws-fain-tells-board-hes-worried-trump-could-beat-biden-sources-say-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BCXIU6M7GZLJZFXEAK7GS3S5UM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛称首席财务官特拉维斯将在 12 年后离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛（Estee Lauder）周四表示，特蕾西-特拉维斯（Tracey Travis）将于 2025 年 6 月 30 日卸任，从她担任了 12 年的 MAC 口红生产商财务总监的岗位上退休。【原文：Estee Lauder said on Thursday that Tracey Travis would be stepping down and retiring from her 12 years role as the MAC lipstick maker's finance chief, effective June 30, 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/estee-lauder-says-cfo-travis-depart-after-12-years-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSBLO6L52VOGNPX57H46RWGASE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲日元反弹：CPI利空还是干预？]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIUCM4EAMFKZVHI4X364KU6H7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国因 "未审查 "海上石油退役延迟造成的 "危害 "而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个环保组织周四起诉美国政府，指控其审查老化的海上石油和天然气基础设施所造成危害的方法，称延迟退役会给人类和环境带来风险。【原文：An environmental group on Thursday sued the U.S. government over its approach to examining the harm caused by ageing offshore oil and gas infrastructure, citing the risks delayed decommissioning poses to people and the environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sued-over-failure-examine-harms-delayed-offshore-oil-decommissioning-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3ITDP7EDZPZROGFTEZYHBZ3C4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储古尔斯比通往 2% 通胀率的道路是这样的]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯汀-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周四表示，美国经济在今年早些时候经历了一次上扬之后，似乎又回到了通胀率达到 2% 的轨道上。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee said on Thursday the U.S. economy looks like it is back on track to 2% inflation after a bump up earlier this year, a view that suggests he is gaining confidence that the time will soon be ripe to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-this-is-what-path-2-inflation-looks-like-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4XRQ2QTI5PLDNFM4DAYC4PFRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:56:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国和解协议中，Dollar General 将支付 1200 万美元罚款，并改善安全状况]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周四在一份声明中表示，折扣店运营商 Dollar General 因涉嫌违反安全规定导致出口和灭火器堵塞以及储藏不安全而同意支付 1200 万美元的罚款，要求该公司在与联邦劳工部达成的和解协议中改善全美商店的工作场所安全。【原文：Discount store operator Dollar General has agreed to pay $12 million in penalty for alleged safety violations that led to blocked exits and fire extinguishers and unsafe storage, requiring the company to improve workplace safety in stores across the U.S. in a settlement with the federal Labor Department, the government said in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dollar-general-pay-12-million-penalty-improve-safety-us-settlement-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFVQRRYACZJRXJZKPLJQQAOZOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:14:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公司推出基于掉期交易的比特币 ETF 期权]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，刚刚推出的通过衍生品掉期跟踪比特币现货价格的杠杆产品期权开始交易，这在加密货币交易所交易基金（ETF）领域尚属首次。【原文：Options on just-launched leveraged products that track the spot price of bitcoin via derivative swaps began trading on Thursday, a first for the cryptocurrency exchange-traded fund (ETF) universe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/firms-launch-options-swap-based-bitcoin-etf-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLXX6DSXSBK7LLHN5L5LJ26L5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:12:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，波音即将达成向大韩航空出售 777X 喷气式飞机的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内消息人士称，波音公司即将向大韩航空出售约二十多架 777X 喷气式飞机，交易金额约为 40 亿至 60 亿美元，最早可能在 7 月份的范堡罗航展上敲定。【原文：Boeing is nearing a potential sale of some two dozen 777X jets to Korean Air in a roughly $4 billion to $6 billion deal that could be finalised as early as July's Farnborough Airshow, industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-nearing-deal-sell-777x-jets-korean-air-sources-say-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KC2IEGKJ7BMPXPJF3XQ2RYTC3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 19:35:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利锂业将有资格享受美国税收优惠]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利政府周四表示，使用智利开采的电动汽车电池用锂制造的产品将有资格享受美国的税收优惠。【原文：Products made with Chilean-mined lithium - used for electric-vehicle batteries - will be eligible for U.S. tax benefits, the Andean country's government said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chilean-lithium-be-eligible-us-tax-break-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PQHYZPE7JISVE4B4HPPBBCVNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 19:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日历变动后，美国 6 月预算赤字缩减至 660 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四表示，美国政府 6 月份录得 660 亿美元的预算赤字，但由于将福利金支付转入 5 月份，导致该月赤字激增至 3,470 亿美元，从而大幅减少了预算赤字。【原文：The U.S. government recorded a $66 billion budget deficit for June that was reduced sharply by a shift of benefit payments into May that ballooned that month's deficit to $347 billion, the Treasury Department said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-june-budget-deficit-shrinks-66-billion-after-calendar-shifts-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7WTGLXCW5KRVAXM7GMNCHBNZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 18:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨勒姆称CPI数据降温 "令人鼓舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周四表示，当天早些时候公布的消费者物价数据正朝着正确的方向发展。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis President Alberto Musalem said on Thursday that consumer price data released earlier in the day is moving in the right direction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-musalem-says-cooler-cpi-data-is-encouraging-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTAV47PP3FMTBCHNBXIVT6TUQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:31:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求复苏乏力，Conagra Brands 预计全年销售额和利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[康奈格拉品牌公司（Conagra Brands）周四预测的年度收入和利润低于分析师的预期，原因是资金紧张的消费者转而选择价格更低廉的家庭主食。【原文：Conagra Brands forecast annual revenue and profit below analysts' estimates on Thursday, as cash-strapped consumers turned to cheaper pantry staples for their at-home meals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/conagra-brands-projects-lower-annual-sales-profit-tepid-demand-recovery-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEHZU74KJZNVRN3CGAO6A2F7UI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:25:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员希望波音公司首席执行官在准备新的 FAA 立法时出庭作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商务委员会主席玛丽亚-坎特韦尔（Maria Cantwell）周四表示，她希望波音公司首席执行官戴夫-卡尔霍恩（Dave Calhoun）在她准备立法加强联邦航空管理局对飞机制造商的监督时出席她的委员会。【原文：U.S. Senate Commerce Committee chair Maria Cantwell said Thursday she wants Boeing CEO Dave Calhoun to appear before her committee as she prepares legislation that would boost Federal Aviation Administration oversight of planemakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/senator-wants-boeing-ceo-testify-she-prepares-new-faa-legislation-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIGPMO6QUJPANGIQ3UKDC2CW7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:47:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织认为美国联邦储备委员会有望在今年晚些时候降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五表示，该组织仍然认为美联储可能会在今年晚些时候开始降息，并应保持谨慎，即使美国6月份消费者价格的下跌提高了提前降息的预期。【原文：The International Monetary Fund said on Friday it continues to believe that the Federal Reserve could start cutting interest rates later this year and should stay cautious, even as a fall in U.S. June consumer prices raises expectations for an earlier rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/imf-sees-us-fed-position-cut-interest-rates-later-this-year-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAD4W55ASBKNJCZZGSUS77OMYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，美国联邦贸易委员会将在埃克森仲裁期间推迟对雪佛龙-赫斯交易做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，美国联邦贸易委员会计划推迟决定是否阻止雪佛龙公司以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司，直到与埃克森美孚公司的仲裁案得到解决。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission plans to delay its decision whether to block Chevron's $53 billion takeover of Hess until after an arbitration case with Exxon Mobil is settled, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-ftc-delay-decision-chevron-hess-deal-during-exxon-arbitration-bloomberg-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZ3WG53ZFVNMNL7LHLMGM363GA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利称 "很可能 "需要调整政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周四表示，近期较低的通胀读数让人 "松了一口气"，她预计物价压力和劳动力市场将进一步放缓，从而有理由降息。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly on Thursday said that recent cooler inflation readings are a "relief" and she expects further easing in both price pressures and the labor market to warrant interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-daly-says-policy-adjustments-likely-warranted-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJWW5ZN46ZPLFGXRFJX56OMPJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:21:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪：私人信贷增长的新时代引发担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪评级公司（Moody's Ratings）的最新报告指出，由于缺乏监督和透明度，私人信贷借贷的快速增长超出了其传统市场，给美国经济带来了潜在的未来风险。【原文：The rapid growth of private credit lending beyond its traditional market presents potential future risks to the U.S. economy due to lack of oversight and transparency, according to a new Moody's Ratings report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/new-era-private-credit-growth-raises-concerns-moodys-says-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAYM3AKA5FMCDHLUFWB2PSBWZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:09:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约欺诈案庭审结束，律师称 Ozy Media 的卡洛斯-沃森被撒谎的联合创始人出卖了]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在前新闻主播欺诈案的结案陈词中，一名辩护律师说，Ozy Media 的联合创始人卡洛斯-沃森（Carlos Watson）遭到了一名高级副手的背叛，这名副手向投资者撒谎并伪造文件，以掩盖这家初创公司糟糕的财务状况。【原文：Ozy Media co-founder Carlos Watson was betrayed by a top deputy who lied to investors and forged documents to hide the startup’s dire finances, a defense lawyer said on Thursday during closing arguments in the former news anchor’s fraud trial.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ozy-medias-carlos-watson-was-betrayed-by-lying-co-founder-lawyer-says-new-york-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UD4AOUNK4ZLCFFOSXBEK3OVPIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特斯拉将机器人出租车的推出时间从 8 月推迟到 10 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引熟悉这一决定的人士的话报道，特斯拉正将其Robotaxi的推出时间从8月推迟到10月。【原文：Tesla is delaying the launch of its Robotaxi to October from August, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-delays-robotaxi-launch-october-august-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3C7C2RUZRNRVADGETHQ74NYRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:58:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[低收入消费者的经济压力蔓延，百事公司倍感压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事公司首席执行官拉蒙-拉瓜尔塔（Ramon Laguarta）周四表示，美国各收入群体而不仅仅是低收入消费者对价格的敏感度 "要高得多"，这凸显了百事公司对消费者需求广泛变化的敏感性。【原文：PepsiCo CEO Ramon Laguarta said Thursday there is "much more price sensitivity" across U.S. income groups and not just low-income consumers, highlighting its sensitivity to broad shifts in consumer demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pepsico-feels-squeeze-financial-pressure-spreads-low-income-consumers-2024-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOWFW34XU5LUZB6DPIJ6LXQPU4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:55:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>