<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:04:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:04:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通调查显示美元疲软和美国滞胀已成共识]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周五公布的一项调查结果显示，明年美国经济出现滞胀的风险远高于衰退，而最有望在2025年跑赢大盘的资产类别是现金。【原文：There is a much higher risk of stagflation than recession in the U.S. economy over the next year, while the asset class most expected to outperform in 2025 is cash, according to the results of a JPMorgan survey published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-survey-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R75OXJD7WZP4TGOYMCMI7WV77E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道巴里克黄金公司在马里的承包商因政府纠纷而裁员--文件、消息来源]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的文件和熟悉内情的人士透露，巴里克黄金公司在马里的矿场至少有四家分包商正在裁员，这些分包商雇用了数百名员工，而这家加拿大矿商与马里政府之间的纠纷已经持续了两年。【原文：At least four subcontractors employing several hundred people at Barrick Gold's complex in Mali are laying off staff following a two-year dispute between the Canadian miner and the state, according to documents seen by Reuters and people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/barrick-gold-contractors-mali-lay-off-staff-amid-government-dispute-documents-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S24ZZOAKCFJNNE7V4XLC52QQHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前美联储理事沃什称美国央行应改弦更张]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，前美联储理事凯文-沃什（Kevin Warsh）曾与唐纳德-特朗普总统讨论过解雇美国央行行长杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）并让他取而代之的问题。【原文：Former Federal Reserve Governor Kevin Warsh, with whom President Donald Trump is reported to have discussed firing U.S. central bank chief Jerome Powell and installing him in his place, on Friday unleashed a barrage of criticism of the Fed and argued for fundamental changes to how it operates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/former-fed-governor-warsh-says-us-central-bank-should-change-its-ways-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34OLQSI3ARODNOYNMCBANTWRYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储调查发现全球贸易战、政策不确定性是金融稳定的首要风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周五公布的一项最新调查显示，全球贸易风险上升、总体政策不确定性以及美国债务的可持续性在美国金融体系面临的潜在风险中名列前茅。【原文：Rising risks around global trade, general policy uncertainty, and the sustainability of U.S. debt topped the list of potential risks to the U.S. financial system in a new Federal Reserve survey released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-survey-finds-global-trade-fight-policy-uncertainty-top-financial-stability-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6D54HO32JLELHPGF6VLZZMM5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:06:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国批评美国 "近期滥用 "关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行行长周五批评美国 "最近滥用 "关税威胁全球金融稳定，此前双方最近都采取了被视为缓和贸易战的举措。【原文：China's central bank governor on Friday criticized the U.S. for threatening global financial stability with its "recent abuse" of tariffs, in the wake of recent moves seen by both sides as efforts to de-escalate their trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-criticizes-us-recent-abuse-tariffs-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIVFS277GFPN3D7GXV3OMFDDKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:23:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，TikTok 所有者正在权衡巴西的数据中心项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[其中一位消息人士说，初步谈判的重点是一个 300 兆瓦的数据中心，但该项目最终可能在第二阶段扩大到 900 兆瓦。【原文：One of the sources said initial talks are focused on a 300-megawatt data center, but the project could eventually expand to 900 megawatt in a second phase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/tiktok-owner-weighs-data-center-project-brazil-sources-say-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3WFFPTYQJMYXOAMTI4SCP3OWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:18:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官定于 5 月 2 日举行听证会，讨论谷歌数字广告诉讼案的补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官已定于 5 月 2 日举行听证会，讨论美国司法部和一些州可能要求法院对谷歌采取的补救措施，因为法院裁定 Alphabet 旗下公司非法主导了两个在线广告技术市场。【原文：A U.S. judge has set a May 2 hearing to discuss remedies the U.S. Justice Department and a group of states might ask the court to impose on Google after it ruled the Alphabet unit illegally dominates two markets for online advertising technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-judge-sets-may-2-hearing-discuss-remedies-google-digital-ads-lawsuit-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJN53SSLBZKZFCDP7E4F6YRN54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 科技巨头财报、美国就业数据凸显本周市场繁忙景象]]></title><description><![CDATA[即将到来的一周市场将考验美股的反弹，投资者将关注由苹果和微软领衔的企业业绩浪潮，而全球贸易发展的前景随时都有可能引发波动。【原文：A packed upcoming week for markets will test a U.S. stocks rebound, with investors focused on a wave of corporate results led by Apple and Microsoft, while the prospect of global trade developments threatens to cause volatility at any time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-big-tech-earnings-us-jobs-data-highlight-busy-week-markets-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YMDTMPGAZKZXOVMTIVJDPHI7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州建议允许自动驾驶重型卡车测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州机动车辆管理局周五表示，拟允许在州公共道路上对重型卡车和其他大型车辆进行测试。【原文：The California Department of Motor Vehicles said Friday it is proposing to allow testing of heavy-duty trucks and other large vehicles on state public roads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/california-proposes-allow-self-driving-heavy-duty-truck-testing-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">US5HCCSL55PLLHFLEZAFOHK5ME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:46:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼日利亚法庭维持对 Meta 公司罚款 2.2 亿美元的判决，因其违反消费者和数据法]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼日利亚竞争与消费者保护法庭周五表示，尼日利亚竞争监督机构对 Meta Platforms 公司违反当地消费者、数据保护和隐私法的 2.2 亿美元罚款在上诉未果后维持原判。【原文：A $220 million fine against Meta Platforms by Nigeria's competition watchdog for violating local consumer, data protection and privacy laws has been upheld following an unsuccessful appeal, Nigeria's Competition and Consumer Protection Tribunal said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nigerian-tribunal-upholds-220-million-fine-against-meta-violating-consumer-data-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPG63E2U6NJKBLPNRHBE2SHDS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:19:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[非同寻常的利益冲突沃伦要求美国证券交易委员会提供特朗普传媒投资产品的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）周五要求美国证券监管机构分享其对由总统唐纳德-特朗普创建并拥有多数股权的公司即将推出的交易所交易基金的监管计划。【原文：Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren asked the U.S. Securities regulator on Friday to share its plans for regulating exchange-traded funds due to be launched by a company founded and majority-owned by President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/extraordinary-conflict-interest-warren-asks-sec-records-trump-medias-investment-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHMAYILTRJL27CYBXXRIF3LU6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受外汇影响，智利矿业公司 Codelco 税前利润大幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利矿业公司 Codelco 是世界上最大的铜生产商，该公司周五报告称，第一季度产量略有增长，但这一增长不足以抵消汇率的影响，汇率影响导致其利润下滑。【原文：Chilean miner Codelco, the world's largest copper producer, on Friday reported a slight bump in production in the first quarter, though the boost was not enough to offset exchange-rate effects, which caused its profits to tumble.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chilean-miner-codelcos-pre-tax-profit-tumbles-fx-effects-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5GCDU5EINI4HBFGUPVBW2MN6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:41:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deliveroo 收到 DoorDash 提出的每股 180 便士的收购方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国送餐公司 Deliveroo 周五证实，它于 4 月 5 日收到了来自 DoorDash 以每股 180 便士的价格收购其全部股份的提议。【原文：British meal delivery company Deliveroo confirmed on Friday that it received a proposal from DoorDash on April 5 to buy all of its shares for 180 pence each.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/deliveroo-receives-buyout-proposal-doordash-180-pence-per-share-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ENVVMWONFJPFA22OG3IB34IQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元、日本央行利率政策可能仍是日美贸易谈判的焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本在周四的双边财政会谈中可能避免了美国要求日元走强的压力，但仔细研究一下官员们对会议的描述，就会发现货币和日本央行的利率政策可能仍然是更广泛贸易谈判中的关键因素。【原文：Japan may have averted U.S. pressure for a stronger yen in bilateral finance talks on Thursday, but a closer look at officials' descriptions of the meeting suggests currencies and the Bank of Japan's interest rate policy may remain key factors in broader trade negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/yen-bojs-rate-policy-may-remain-focus-japan-us-trade-talks-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X63IGKQE3BKZ3ATRFDEQXQ5OSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会新任主席称加密货币行业应受到明确监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）新任负责人周五表示，该机构在过去几年中助长了 "监管的不确定性"，从而扼杀了加密货币行业的创新。【原文：The new head of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday said that the agency has stifled innovation for the cryptocurrency sector by fostering "regulatory uncertainty" in prior years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/new-us-sec-chair-says-crypto-sector-deserves-clear-regulations-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O46TT27G75PBTP3WR753X54SAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安进公司将扩建俄亥俄州生物技术生产厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[安进公司周五宣布斥资9亿美元扩建其在俄亥俄州的生物技术生产设施，成为在特朗普政府威胁可能征收进口关税之际承诺提高美国产能的一系列制药商中的最新一家。【原文：Amgen on Friday announced a $900 million expansion of its Ohio biotech manufacturing facility, becoming the latest in a string of drugmakers pledging to increase U.S. capacity amid Trump administration threats of potential import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/amgen-expand-ohio-biotech-manufacturing-plant-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7274IFYD3VOC3GB3WAJU4U32VQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前 CISA 老大称特朗普的行动有可能 "危险地降低 "美国的网络防御能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国网络安全和基础设施安全局（CISA）前局长周五在一篇文章中说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对高级网络官员的清洗和明显的报复行为使国家的数字防御面临风险。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's purges and apparent acts of retribution aimed at top cyber officials put the nation's digital defenses at risk, the former head of the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) said in a post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ex-cisa-boss-says-trump-actions-risk-dangerously-degrading-us-cyber-defenses-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFMJLOJ65FK6DAEN5MZPYZQBJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股东批准家乐福将巴西业务私有化的申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的一份证券文件显示，家乐福巴西分公司 Atacadao SA 的股东在法国零售商提出私有化要求后，投票决定将其私有化。【原文：Shareholders in Carrefour's Brazil unit, Atacadao SA , voted to take it private after a bid by the French retailer to do so, according to a securities filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shareholders-approve-carrefour-bid-take-brazil-unit-private-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7YZMW4V6JPHXHY4OUPGQTZSWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰多诺霍表示，欧盟将 "不遗余力 "地减少与贸易有关的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰财政部长帕夏尔-多诺霍（Paschal Donohoe）周五表示，欧盟将尽其所能与美国就贸易问题进行接触，减少拖累全球经济的巨大不确定性，这凸显了欧盟成员国之间的团结。【原文：The European Union will do all it can to engage with the U.S. on trade and reduce the massive uncertainty that is weighing down the global economy, Irish Finance Minister Paschal Donohoe said on Friday, underscoring unity among the bloc's members.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-will-leave-no-stone-unturned-reduce-trade-related-uncertainty-irelands-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GUY5EWRVRJOTC7PJYMMTHMHL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:15:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西淡水河谷公司认为贸易战迄今未造成实质性影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿商淡水河谷周五表示，迄今为止尚未看到正在进行的全球贸易战对其运营和销售产生实质性影响，但誓言在不确定的市场条件下继续密切关注。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale said on Friday that it has so far not seen a material impact from the ongoing global trade war on its operations and sales, but vowed to keep monitoring it closely amid uncertain market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/brazils-vale-sees-no-material-impacts-trade-war-so-far-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QKZ2FS3UVOO5FI7S5ZVEHYSYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:50:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税担忧影响，美国 4 月消费者信心依然疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心关税对经济的影响，4 月份美国消费者情绪连续第四个月下滑。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment ebbed for a fourth straight month in April amid concerns about the economic impact of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-remains-weak-april-tariffs-concerns-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UOYAOBARMVLYVGBLIVDRY5NYEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:46:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国放弃对部分美国商品征收关税，但否认特朗普关于谈判正在进行中的说法]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，中国免除了部分美国进口商品的高额关税，这表明两国之间的贸易战可能会有所缓和，但中国很快驳斥了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于正在进行谈判的说法。【原文：China exempted some U.S. imports from its steep tariffs in a sign on Friday that the trade war between the two countries could be easing, though China quickly knocked down U.S. President Donald Trump's assertion that negotiations were underway.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-waives-tariffs-some-us-goods-denies-trumps-claim-that-talks-are-underway-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIJJODH4TFPQDMRC6EI3NX7CJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:18:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[散户投资者热捧比特币，Cantor Equity 股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[空头支票公司 Cantor Equity Partners 的股票周五大涨 29%，延续了上一交易日的炙热涨势，因为希望利用人们对比特币日益增长的兴趣的散户投资者蜂拥而至。【原文：Shares of blank-check firm Cantor Equity Partners surged 29% on Friday, extending a scorching rally from their previous session, as retail investors hoping to capitalize on the growing interest in bitcoin flocked to the stock.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cantor-equity-shares-rally-amid-retail-investor-fervor-bitcoin-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3W5PKUFF5PITPPXVOKYOTXZF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:57:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥矿业集团因金属价格上涨而利润大增 17]]></title><description><![CDATA[受金属价格上涨的推动，矿业和运输集团墨西哥集团（Grupo Mexico）周五报告称，2025 年第一季度净利润猛增 17%。【原文：Mining and transport conglomerate Grupo Mexico on Friday reported a 17% jump in its net profit during the first quarter of 2025, driven by higher metal prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/miner-grupo-mexico-posts-17-profit-jump-higher-metals-prices-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IB3M6S3PBI6HOQ2ZVNM76K4W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道报告称美国对制药业征收关税将使美国药品成本每年增加 510 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对一份由美国制药业贸易组织委托撰写的报告进行了审查，报告显示，如果美国对药品进口征收 25% 的关税，每年将使美国药品成本增加近 510 亿美元，如果转嫁出去，美国药品价格将上涨高达 12.9%。【原文：A 25% U.S. tariff on pharmaceutical imports would increase U.S. drug costs by nearly $51 billion annually, boosting U.S. prices by as much as 12.9% if passed on, a report commissioned by the industry's U.S. trade group and reviewed by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-pharma-tariffs-would-raise-us-drug-costs-by-51-bln-annually-report-finds-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSGZJRV2X5ICNATCVNCS3NVZWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车承运商寻求减免广泛的美国港口费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士告诉路透社，美国贸易代表突然计划对所有外国建造的汽车运输船征收港口费，其中包括 20 艘在战争或国家紧急状态下为美国军队提供运输保障的船舶，大型汽车运输船的运营商正在寻求救济。【原文：Operators of hulking car carriers are seeking relief from the U.S. Trade Representative's surprise plan to levy port fees on all foreign-built ships in that segment, including 20 vessels that guarantee transport for the U.S. military during a war or national emergency, three sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vehicle-carriers-seek-relief-broad-us-port-fees-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AXZFCRHTVP5DGLFKBI5PZQNE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:49:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国发展部长称世界银行不是美国银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国经济合作与发展部长斯文嘉-舒尔茨告诉路透社记者，特朗普政府不能决定世界银行的使命，因为这个全球贷款机构的目标是基于许多国家达成的协议。【原文：The Trump administration cannot determine the mission of the World Bank because the global lender's goals are based on agreement by many countries, Svenja Schulze, Germany's minister for economic cooperation and development, told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/world-bank-is-not-an-american-bank-german-development-minister-says-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUREGXGYGFLRNE7NLVMSYZ4BAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络攻击后，英国 M&S 停止接受网上订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周早些时候，玛莎百货公司报告了一起网络攻击事件，随后于周五停止了在英国和爱尔兰的在线订单，这一消息导致其股价下跌了 5%。【原文：Marks & Spencer stopped taking online orders in the UK and Ireland on Friday following a cyber attack which it reported earlier in the week, an announcement which sent its shares down by 5%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-ms-pauses-some-online-orders-after-cyber-incident-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCQAQBI24RNPZKOZKKHFQ4OOVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）非洲部负责人：撒哈拉以南非洲地区必须提高收入以渡过全球动荡期]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织非洲局局长阿贝贝-艾姆罗-塞拉西（Abebe Aemro Selassie）说，撒哈拉以南非洲经济体应努力增加国内税收，以避免在 "动荡的全球形势 "下不得不举债。【原文：Sub-Saharan African economies should work to increase their domestic revenue collection to avoid having to take on debt amid "turbulent global conditions", International Monetary Fund Africa Director Abebe Aemro Selassie said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/sub-saharan-africa-must-lift-revenue-ride-out-global-turbulence-imf-africa-head-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TN6E4RD7YJPD5EZYYH3Y5U3MRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美关税紧张局势缓解，全球股票基金第二周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至4月23日，全球股票基金连续第二周吸引资金流入，原因是有迹象表明中美之间的关税战可能降级，这刺激了对高风险资产的需求。【原文：Global equity funds attracted inflows for a second straight week through April 23, supported by signs of a potential de-escalation in the tariff war between the U.S. and China, which boosted demand for riskier assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BFQKT5YGJLRVID2LPD2TB7RTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>