<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:35:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:35:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[《华盛顿邮报》出版人威尔·刘易斯宣布离职，此前该公司进行了大规模裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[《华盛顿邮报》周六宣布，在经历本周大规模裁员后，其出版人兼首席执行官威尔·刘易斯将离职。【原文：Washington Post publisher and CEO Will Lewis is leaving the newspaper, it announced on Saturday after carrying out widespread layoffs this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/washington-post-publisher-will-lewis-announces-departure-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73UWBQDWOFPCBP7VICEO464DPI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 23:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道，道尔西旗下Block公司将裁员多达10%]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻周六援引知情人士报道，杰克·多尔西旗下的金融科技公司Block正考虑在年度绩效考核期间裁减多达10%的员工。【原文：Jack Dorsey's fintech Block is considering cutting up to 10% of its workforce during annual performance reviews, Bloomberg News reported on Saturday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dorseys-block-cutting-up-10-staff-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOOUYXCAS5P6JHRH7FWU347EUE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:19:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空首席执行官同意就飞行员关切问题与飞行员工会会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司首席执行官罗伯特·艾索姆周六表示，他将尽快与该航空公司的飞行员工会会面，因为飞行员们对该公司处理近期风暴事件及公司财务状况的方式日益担忧。【原文：American Airlines CEO Robert Isom said on Saturday he would meet with the carrier's pilots union as soon as possible, as concerns by aviators grow over its handling of a recent storm and company financials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/american-airlines-ceo-agrees-meet-pilots-union-over-concerns-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQR3OMU7DRPCVMVTWPA2GQGMQQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hims公司宣布停止提供GLP-1口服药，此前美国食品药品监督管理局警告将严厉打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[此前美国食品药品监督管理局表示，将对这家远程医疗服务商采取行动，因其销售售价49美元的减肥药。【原文：This comes after the FDA said it would take action against the telehealth provider for its $49 weight-loss pill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/hims-hers-stop-offering-compounded-semaglutide-pill-after-fda-crackdown-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKGRUUAHFFPXHGHASZBZYTH6VQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普支持Nexstar与Tegna合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普写道："我们需要更多力量对抗敌人——那些散布假新闻的国家电视台。""把这笔交易搞定！"【原文："We need more competition against THE ENEMY, the Fake News National TV Networks," Trump wrote. "GET THAT DEAL DONE!"】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-backs-merger-between-nexstar-tegna-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INVSJLE3PRJKDFD7F4HRJD2AN4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印美贸易协定为哈雷摩托车提供零关税准入，特斯拉未获豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度官员表示，根据一项临时贸易协定，印度将把美国高端汽车的关税从高达110%削减至30%，并取消哈雷戴维森摩托车的关税。但印度不会对电动汽车作出让步，这一举措明确将特斯拉排除在外。【原文：India will slash tariffs on high-end American cars to 30% from as high as 110% and eliminate duties on Harley-Davidson bikes under an interim trade pact, an official said, but will not make concessions for electric vehicles, a move that pointedly leaves Tesla out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/india-us-trade-deal-gives-tariff-free-access-harley-bikes-no-reprieve-tesla-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMBADCPEOJP6RHWXHYORJSHSLE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:57:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[匈牙利反对党蒂萨党在选举纲领中承诺开征财富税并推行欧元化]]></title><description><![CDATA[匈牙利反对党蒂萨党周六公布的240页选举纲领显示，该党计划对富人征收财富税，采用欧元货币，并将匈牙利牢牢锚定在欧盟和北约之中。【原文：Hungary's opposition Tisza party plans to introduce a wealth tax for the rich, adopt the euro currency and firmly anchor Hungary in the European Union and NATO, its 240-page election programme published on Saturday said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hungarys-opposition-tisza-promises-wealth-tax-euro-adoption-election-programme-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLJBWMHETJLSJE55FDOWKPCMEE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其副总统表示将维持紧缩的货币政策和财政纪律]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其副总统切夫德特·伊尔马兹周六表示，土耳其将维持紧缩的货币政策并保持财政纪律，以进一步降低通胀率。【原文：Turkey will maintain its tight monetary policy and keep fiscal discipline in order to further lower inflation, Vice President Cevdet Yilmaz said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/turkey-maintain-tight-monetary-policy-fiscal-discipline-vice-president-says-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZP2JFZTQHRI6BCPR5SUIYUSYUQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[减肥药将在超级碗广告中登上最大舞台]]></title><description><![CDATA[计划直接向消费者销售减肥药的公司——包括诺和诺德的Wegovy——将在周日的超级碗赛事期间斥资数百万美元投放明星云集的广告，该赛事承诺将吸引全球年度最大规模的观众群体。【原文：Companies looking to sell weight-loss drugs directly to consumers, including Novo Nordisk's Wegovy, will shell out millions of dollars for celebrity-filled ads during Sunday's Super Bowl with its promise of one of the year's largest global audiences.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/weight-loss-drugs-compete-biggest-stage-with-super-bowl-ads-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JW4JESAU45N4NIJDPNXK35VZ24</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币回吐特朗普时期涨幅，加密货币市场波动预示不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币可能进一步下跌，此前其已抹去自美国总统特朗普当选以来的所有涨幅，因预计近期流动性将持续低迷。【原文：Bitcoin could drop further after wiping out all of its price gains since the election of U.S. President Donald Trump as liquidity is expected to remain thin for the near future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-loses-trump-era-gains-crypto-market-volatility-signals-uncertainty-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGRG5O2UY5J6RII5W5452BQDSQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic购买超级碗广告位，借机抨击OpenAI在ChatGPT中投放广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[Anthropic公司斥资数百万美元，在周日晚的美国国家橄榄球联盟冠军赛期间投放广告，猛烈抨击竞争对手OpenAI计划在其ChatGPT聊天机器人上投放广告的行为。这是人工智能巨头之间爆发的一场最大规模的公开争执。【原文：Anthropic is spending millions of dollars to air commercials during Sunday night's National Football League championship game to slam rival OpenAI for its plan to sell ads on its ChatGPT chatbot, in one of the biggest public spats between the big artificial-intelligence companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/anthropic-buys-super-bowl-ads-slap-openai-selling-ads-chatgpt-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LN55LYBPS5KN5NML74FJS34VMU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从特朗普到爱泼斯坦案，布拉德·卡普如何失去对保罗·韦斯律所的掌控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国顶级律所保瑞律师事务所主席布拉德·卡普于2024年11月在华盛顿举行的选举之夜聚会上，与其他知名民主党筹款人共同出席，期待卡玛拉·哈里斯击败共和党对手唐纳德·特朗普赢得大选。【原文：Brad Karp, the chairman of high-powered U.S. law firm Paul Weiss, joined other prominent Democratic fundraisers at election night gatherings in Washington in November 2024 hoping for a Kamala Harris victory over Republican rival Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-epstein-how-brad-karp-lost-his-grip-law-firm-paul-weiss-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDH6Y3OEYVLUPPB2F6JLEVV4X4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在经济演讲中，特朗普近20次宣称战胜通胀，尽管物价持续上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普在选举年将自己塑造成共和党关于生活成本问题的首席代言人，但路透社对其演讲的梳理显示，这位总统屡屡宣称已战胜通胀，却鲜少承认许多美国人表示仍在承受的压力。【原文：Donald Trump has cast himself as Republicans’ chief messenger on the cost of living in an election year, but a Reuters review of his speeches shows a president repeatedly declaring inflation beaten while rarely acknowledging the strain many Americans say they still feel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/economic-speeches-trump-claims-inflation-victory-nearly-20-times-even-prices-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3T5JBAV3ZJEDFJ224I2KY6XXE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称，由Stellantis支持的ACC公司取消了在意大利和德国建设超级工厂的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利金属工人联合会UILM周六发表声明称，由Stellantis集团支持的汽车电池公司（ACC）已告知工会，其在意大利和德国建设超级工厂的计划已被搁置。【原文：The Stellantis-backed Automotive Cells Company (ACC) told unions it had shelved plans to build gigafactories in both Italy and Germany, the Italian metalworkers' union UILM said in a statement on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stellantis-backed-acc-drops-plans-italian-german-gigafactories-union-says-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VM3T4O2FFLV3MX67RWPKH5TYY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:48:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，英国国民西敏寺银行即将完成对财富管理公司伊芙琳的34亿美元收购。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻周六援引消息人士报道，英国银行NatWest集团即将以25亿英镑（约合34亿美元）收购英国最大财富管理公司之一伊芙琳合伙公司。【原文：British bank NatWest Group is closing in on a 2.5 billion pound ($3.4 billion) takeover of one of Britain's largest wealth managers, Evelyn Partners, Sky News reported on Saturday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/natwest-closes-34-billion-takeover-wealth-manager-evelyn-sky-news-reports-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JY4MGXFUMBKWVGB25CIEYHI6AI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:47:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马北美因发动机启动器过热问题召回逾8.7万辆美国车辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周六表示，宝马北美公司正在美国召回87,394辆汽车，因发动机启动器可能过热，存在起火风险。【原文：BMW North America is recalling 87,394 vehicles in the U.S. as the engine starter may overheat, causing a fire risk, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-north-america-recall-over-87000-us-vehicles-over-engine-starter-overheating-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QT6U5FMPN5OO5NSY4ZM6EKW63M</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司误将价值440亿美元的比特币转给用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国加密货币交易所Bithumb周六表示，其误将价值逾400亿美元的比特币作为促销奖励发放给客户，导致该交易所出现大幅抛售。【原文：South Korean cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb said on Saturday it had accidentally given away more than $40 billion worth of bitcoins to customers as promotional rewards, triggering a sharp selloff on the exchange.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/crypto-firm-accidentally-sends-44-billion-bitcoins-users-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3Q2HINJMJJAPCBDOYM6HZK66A</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 03:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic’s more than $20 billion funding to close as soon as next week, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[AI startup Anthropic is ironing out the final details on a funding round likely to raise more than $20 billion and slated to close as soon as next week, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing sources.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/anthropics-more-than-20-billion-funding-close-soon-next-week-bloomberg-news-2026-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLFBIHTA3FIDVP7INEU4NNWS3Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Toyota changes CEO despite its strength through industry turmoil]]></title><description><![CDATA[Toyota Motor's surprise CEO switch comes as global automakers confront a tumultuous industry landscape - one that the Japanese automaker has been navigating more adeptly than most.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/toyota-changes-ceo-despite-its-strength-through-industry-turmoil-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TYFCMZEUJKK7J5CF5QWBBBMBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SpaceX delays Mars plans to focus on 2027 moon landing, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elon Musk's SpaceX told investors it will prioritize going to the moon first and attempt a trip to Mars at a later time, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing sources.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/spacex-delays-mars-plans-focus-moon-wsj-reports-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REDYQZLIQ5LN3BKOUKT6I2443Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump orders prioritizing countries with higher defense spending as customers for US weapons]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump signed an executive order that would re-prioritize the customer list for U.S. weapons in favor of countries with higher defense spending and strategic importance in their region, the White House said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-orders-prioritizing-countries-with-higher-defense-spending-customers-us-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TI2WZSW2LZLIJAXDFC2443XVMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TrumpRx has limited reach at launch beyond weight-loss drugs, experts say]]></title><description><![CDATA[President Donald Trump's new prescription drug website, TrumpRx.gov, is focused largely on the significant discounts the administration has negotiated for users of the popular GLP-1 weight-loss drugs, limiting its savings for all consumers, experts said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trumprx-has-limited-reach-launch-beyond-weight-loss-drugs-experts-say-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XN4UMPPICJOXDLME5J46BB44J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palmer Luckey-backed Erebor receives US national banking charter, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Crypto-focused Erebor Bank became the first bank to receive a national bank charter during the second term of the Trump administration, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/palmer-luckey-backed-erebor-receives-us-national-banking-charter-wsj-reports-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUYV6UIAXZND7FNI6ZNH3IRODI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Judge bans Kalshi from offering sports-events contracts in Massachusetts in 30 days]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Massachusetts judge on Friday rejected a request by prediction-markets operator Kalshi to allow it to keep offering sports-events contracts in the state while it appeals an injunction that will lead to it being banned from operating there without a state gaming license in 30 days.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/judge-bans-kalshi-offering-sports-events-contracts-massachusetts-30-days-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VPFCAHGDNKM7INNAJRRAZK43M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US, India release framework for an interim trade deal]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United States and India on Friday released a framework for an interim trade agreement that the countries said affirms their commitment to negotiations towards a broader bilateral trade deal.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-india-release-framework-an-interim-trade-deal-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HGLYBWMRFJEVDVJFBKT4WBYRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFL to talk with partners outside of core media for live games, CNBC reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[The National Football League plans to hold discussions with non-traditional media outlets about the possible sale of rights to a live game, its media chief Hans Schroeder told CNBC Sport on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nfl-talk-with-partners-outside-core-media-live-games-cnbc-reports-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKWDIMQFNZO7FBV5KVZT3QWZ5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA to restrict GLP-1 ingredients used in non‑approved compounded drugs]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Friday it plans to restrict GLP-1 ingredients used in non-approved compounded drugs that companies such as Hims & Hers and other compounding pharmacies have been marketing as alternatives to authorized treatments, citing concerns over quality, safety and potential violations of federal law.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/fda-restrict-glp1-ingredients-used-nonapproved-compounded-drugs-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OCNJQ4EZBLO3KLNZX37SMQPWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:59:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senator Warren presses Trump over DOJ probe of Fed Chair Powell]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren on Friday challenged President Donald Trump's denial of involvement in a Justice Department investigation of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell that has heightened concerns about the Fed's independence and complicated the president's plan to install a rate-cut friendly Fed chair.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/senator-warren-presses-trump-over-doj-probe-fed-chair-powell-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYHDK6Y27FLALALL6EEKH7ZNCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla executives say hiring is ramping up to support Musk’s expanded solar strategy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tesla is hiring to support founder Elon Musk's recently announced plan to become what would be the biggest U.S. manufacturer of solar energy components, according to online posts by senior executives at the company.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/tesla-executives-say-hiring-is-ramping-up-support-musks-expanded-solar-strategy-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TU4AZ2AUKBLZTEPBSJWDEO5ISE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump signs proclamation on increasing certain types of beef imports, White House says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday signed a proclamation on increasing certain types of beef imports, the White House said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-signs-proclamation-increasing-certain-types-beef-imports-white-house-says-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLSZNOR5RVJZTAAFP3SSKZMNPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>