<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 23:47:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 23:47:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰称美国司法部已结束对柴油车排放丑闻的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰公司周六表示，美国司法部已经结束了对梅赛德斯-奔驰柴油排放丑闻的调查，该汽车制造商不再面临指控。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice has closed its probe into the Mercedes-Benz diesel emissions scandal and the car manufacturer is no longer facing charges, the company said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-benz-says-us-doj-ended-investigation-into-diesel-emissions-scandal-2024-04-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7ZZYFAELZP7JLD7CO4H77AIMQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:26:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，出价被拒后，必和必拓考虑改进对英美资源集团的收购方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，必和必拓集团正在考虑对英美资源集团（Anglo American）提出一个更好的收购方案，在此之前，必和必拓集团提出的 390 亿美元的初步收购方案遭到了这家在伦敦上市的矿业公司的拒绝。【原文：BHP Group is considering making an improved proposal for Anglo American after its $39 billion initial offer was rejected by the London-listed miner, a source familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bhp-consider-improved-anglo-proposal-after-bid-was-rejected-bloomberg-news-2024-04-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEUKGVURKZLPRFVJKZDJEWXVVI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 15:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟批评俄罗斯控制德国和意大利企业单位]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟周六批评俄罗斯将一家意大利公司和一家德国公司的子公司置于俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司实体的 "临时外部管理 "之下，称此举凸显了莫斯科对国际规范的漠视。【原文：The European Union criticised Russia on Saturday for putting subsidiaries of one Italian and one German company under the "temporary external management" of a Gazprom entity, saying the move underscored Moscow's disregard for international norms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/italys-ariston-says-it-wasnt-notified-transfer-russian-assets-2024-04-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7IL6CVMGNKG5CKILHXNAJE4XE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国第一季度工业利润增速放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六的官方数据显示，与前两个月相比，中国第一季度的工业利润增幅较小，这进一步证明这个世界第二大经济体的复苏并不均衡。【原文：China's industrial profits posted smaller gains for the first quarter compared to the first two months, official data showed on Saturday, adding to evidence of an uneven recovery for the world's second-biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-first-quarter-industrial-profits-rise-slower-pace-2024-04-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXXMDNRFQRJ4BAZ6LLKPMYWUSY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 02:40:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦肯锡前合伙人起诉公司，称自己成了阿片类药物的 "替罪羊]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦肯锡公司（McKinsey &amp; Co）的一名前合伙人周五起诉了这家全球咨询公司，指控该公司诽谤他，让他成为 "替罪羊"，以转移人们对其为奥施康定（OxyContin）生产商普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）和其他阿片类止痛药生产商提供咨询服务的注意力。【原文：A former McKinsey &amp; Co partner sued the global consulting firm on Friday and accused it of defaming him and making him a "scapegoat" to distract attention from its work advising OxyContin maker Purdue Pharma and other manufacturers of opioid pain medications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/ex-mckinsey-partner-sues-firm-claims-he-was-made-opioids-scapegoat-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6QCKPLU6NITLHMLP7W34CFY7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布林肯称美国芯片禁令无意阻碍中国经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务卿安东尼-布林肯周五在接受美国国家公共电台采访时表示，美国对向中国出口先进计算芯片实施出口管制并不是为了阻碍中国的经济或技术发展。【原文：U.S. export controls on sending advanced computing chips to China are not meant to hold back China's economy or technological development, Secretary of State Antony Blinken said during an interview with National Public Radio on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-chip-bans-not-meant-hobble-chinas-growth-blinken-says-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KBYZN3SEVLKDNZTL4NFXSMIBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:40:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果公司与 OpenAI 就 iPhone 生成式人工智能功能重启谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，苹果公司已与 OpenAI 就使用该公司的生成式人工智能技术为今年晚些时候推出的 iPhone 提供一些新功能重新展开讨论。【原文：Apple Inc has renewed discussions with OpenAI about using the startup's generative AI technology to power some new features being introduced in the iPhone later this year, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-renews-talks-with-openai-iphone-generative-ai-features-bloomberg-news-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HM5MSOKTTNNFDG4HDHFR65M5KA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 22:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司首席执行官称供应链不断改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）首席执行官周五表示，影响飞机制造商的供应链问题正在得到改善，但仍存在一些挑战。【原文：The chief executive of Brazil's Embraer said on Friday that supply chain issues impacting planemakers have been improving but some challenges remain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/planemaker-embraer-ceo-says-supply-chain-has-been-improving-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GEWYIDVPC5OI5DX7MYC5ORQSBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 22:37:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，美国监管机构将查封 Republic First Bancorp]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美国监管机构将查封 Republic First Bancorp，并接近达成将其出售给另一家贷款机构的协议。【原文：U.S. regulators are set to seize Republic First Bancorp and are nearing a deal to sell it to another lender, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regulators-set-seize-republic-first-bancorp-wsj-reports-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNM7OU6CCZOZJP6OMYLLEZ2QKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:56:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌计划在印第安纳州和弗吉尼亚州投资 30 亿美元建设数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下公司谷歌周五表示，将投资 30 亿美元在印第安纳州建立一个数据中心园区，并扩大在弗吉尼亚州的站点。【原文：Alphabet unit Google said on Friday it would invest $3 billion to set up a data center campus in Indiana and expand sites in Virginia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-plans-3-bln-data-center-investment-indiana-virginia-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KG2QNWR7RNPW7O6SZKPRJJAVUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:48:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国空军将末日飞机合同授予内华达山脉公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国空军周五表示，已将一份合同授予内华达山脉公司（Sierra Nevada Corp），由其开发 E-4B 的后继机型，该机型因能在核战争中生存而被称为 "末日机"。【原文：The U.S. Air Force said on Friday that it has awarded a contract to Sierra Nevada Corp to develop a successor to the E-4B, known as the Doomsday plane, due to its ability to survive a nuclear war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-air-force-awards-doomsday-plane-contract-sierra-nevada-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVATF33MKJLZXMLW7C5OQ56X3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[L3Harris 为节约成本裁员 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防承包商 L3Harris 公司首席执行官克里斯-库巴西克（Chris Kubasik）在周五的财报后电话会议上表示，该公司本月初裁员 5%，以精简业务和节约成本。【原文：U.S. defense contractor L3Harris cut 5% of its workforce earlier this month in a bid to streamline its business and save costs, CEO Chris Kubasik said in a post-earnings conference call on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/l3harris-cuts-5-workforce-cost-saving-measure-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFISYM22M5KYLNRXZLDO4B2KRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:28:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行将为邮政储蓄银行诉讼案提取准备金，这将影响第二季度利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行（Deutsche Bank AG）表示，法院对其收购邮政银行（Postbank）长达数年之久的诉讼做出裁决，要求其计提法律准备金，这将影响其第二季度和全年的盈利能力。【原文：Deutsche Bank AG said a court ruling in a years-long litigation over its takeover of Postbank will require it to make a legal provision that will impact its second quarter and full-year profitability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-make-provision-postbank-suit-that-will-hit-q2-profit-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKTG4SB6TNPBJJCJBPCHKE7HB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司因波音 787 交付延迟而调整航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司周五表示，将在2024年下半年和2025年第一季度对某些航线进行调整，理由是波音787飞机的交付仍在延期。【原文：American Airlines will be making adjustments to certain routes in the second half of 2024 and the first quarter of 2025, the carrier said on Friday, citing ongoing Boeing 787 delivery delays.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-adjust-routes-amid-boeing-787-delivery-delays-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZT2TQWAAVZIUHN6V6U235GYAXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:41:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美国股市高歌猛进，让投资者对财报失望感到失望]]></title><description><![CDATA[美股估值高企，让投资者对失望的容忍度越来越低，在本周又有两家科技和成长型巨头将公布财报之前，风险加大。【原文：Richly valued U.S. stocks are leaving investors with little tolerance for disappointment, raising the stakes ahead of a week in which two more technology and growth giants are set to report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-lofty-us-stocks-leave-investors-punishing-earnings-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4UR5NR3AZM67PVVFWZQ2YOQHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:36:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将在内华达州裁员 693 人--政府通知]]></title><description><![CDATA[这家电动汽车制造商在本周早些时候发布的 "工人调整和再培训通知"（WARN）中表示，特斯拉计划在其位于内华达州斯帕克斯的工厂裁员 693 人。【原文：Tesla plans to lay off 693 employees at its facilities in Sparks, Nevada, the electric-vehicle maker said in its Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification (WARN) notice earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-lay-off-693-employees-nevada-government-notice-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7GSJPM6HBMDVBYDVL2K54SLO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行将受到与收购邮政银行有关的法律条款的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行周五表示，科隆高等地方法院可能会认定某些前邮政银行股东对该银行的收购索赔有效，预计该银行将在 2024 年第二季度受到法律条款的影响。【原文：Deutsche Bank on Friday said it expected to be impacted by a legal provision in the second quarter of 2024 after the Higher Regional Court of Cologne indicated it may find claims of certain former Postbank shareholders linked to the unit's takeover valid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-be-hit-by-139-bln-legal-provision-related-postbank-takeover-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUPRKHKATROFXI22TWJ5E5HDOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:21:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔 500 指数第一季度盈利预估增长有所改善；本周股市上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国第一季度预估盈利增长在报告期将近过半时显得更为强劲，企业业绩在近期疲软之后本周给股市带来了提振。【原文：U.S. first-quarter estimated earnings growth is looking stronger at nearly the halfway mark of the reporting period, with corporate results giving a boost to stocks this week after recent weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sp-500-q1-earnings-estimated-growth-improves-stocks-up-week-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULVVRPCILFLPXI4RNFC5WCMC7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:52:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国土安全部任命人工智能安全和安保顾问委员会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国土安全部（DHS）周五宣布成立一个蓝带委员会，成员包括 OpenAI、微软、谷歌母公司 Alphabet 和 Nvidia 的首席执行官，该委员会将就人工智能在关键基础设施中的作用向政府提供建议。【原文：The U.S. Homeland Security Department (DHS) on Friday announced a blue-ribbon board that includes the CEOs of OpenAI, Microsoft, Google parent Alphabet and Nvidia that will advise the government on the role of artificial intelligence on critical infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-homeland-security-names-ai-safety-security-advisory-board-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSV3G6X7ERJ7PAKMCPDTNS2TVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌就美国广告技术案提出简易判决动议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet Inc.旗下的谷歌公司周五要求弗吉尼亚州一家联邦法院驳回美国政府指控这家广告和搜索公司在网络广告市场上采取反竞争做法的诉讼。【原文：Alphabet Inc's Google on Friday asked a federal court in Virginia to reject a U.S. government lawsuit accusing the advertising and search company of anticompetitive practices in the online advertising marketplace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/google-files-motion-summary-judgment-us-ad-tech-case-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMY2MNAEPVOU3BU2REBOVAGRQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:14:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉下调波音评级至 "负面"，原因是生产和现金流面临挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉评级公司周五将波音公司的评级展望从 "稳定 "下调至 "负面"，因为安全危机的余波影响到了这家美国飞机制造商的生产和现金流。【原文：Fitch Ratings downgraded outlook on Boeing to "negative" from "stable" on Friday, amid a fallout from safety crisis impacting the U.S. planemaker's production and cashflow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-downgrades-boeings-outlook-negative-production-cashflow-challenges-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2DQHW5B2JRJTZKQZ6I7FUHY5UQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：特朗普如何影响美联储的构成]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，如果唐纳德-特朗普被推定为共和党总统候选人，他的盟友们正在起草削弱美联储独立性的提案，其中一个关键因素就是在中央银行安插忠实拥护者。【原文：Donald Trump's allies are reported to be drafting proposals to erode the Federal Reserve's independence if the presumptive Republican presidential nominee regains the White House, with installing loyalists at the central bank as a key element.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-trump-could-influence-makeup-fed-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHHNWC6I5RNUPMIU2EPW26FPBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉斯维加斯 CVS Omnicare 员工投票加入新工会]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉斯维加斯 CVS Health 旗下 Omnicare 公司的员工投票决定加入药房公会，成为全国连锁药房加入工会的第一家。【原文：Staff at CVS Health's unit Omnicare in Las Vegas voted to join the Pharmacy Guild, becoming the first location at the national pharmacy chain to join the union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-omnicare-staff-las-vegas-vote-join-new-union-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZVW7RANYRIWLO7KHOUWDFV4JQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:36:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司与吉凯恩航空航天公司就圣路易斯厂址达成交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周五表示，该公司已经与航空供应商吉凯恩宇航公司及其母公司梅尔罗斯工业公司（Melrose Industries）就在圣路易斯建立工厂达成了协议。【原文：Boeing said on Friday that it has closed a deal with aero supplier GKN Aerospace and its parent company Melrose Industries for a plant in St. Louis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-gkn-aerospace-close-deal-st-louis-site-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHMPUAIUKJNXZJSHZX3QN6ZXPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工部更正 2019 年至 2023 年生产率数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工部周五更正了2019年至2023年的生产率数据，因为上个月公布的生产率和成本数据所依据的非在岗工时比率出现计算错误，导致工时水平偏低。【原文：The U.S. Labor Department on Friday corrected productivity data from 2019 through 2023 after a computation error in off-the-clock hours worked ratios biased downward the labor hours levels underlying the productivity and costs data published last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-labor-department-corrects-productivity-data-2019-through-2023-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PNBR56SGZOYDCPH6CZD2H2G7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:31:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称通用磨坊正在探索出售价值 20 多亿美元的北美酸奶业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，可可泡芙和Cheerios早餐谷物食品的制造商通用磨坊公司正在探讨出售其北美酸奶业务，包括广受欢迎的Yoplait品牌，交易价值可能超过20亿美元。【原文：General Mills , the maker of Cocoa Puffs and Cheerios breakfast cereals, is exploring a sale of its North America yogurt business including its popular Yoplait brand in a deal that could be worth more than $2 billion, people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/general-mills-explores-sale-2-billion-plus-yogurt-business-north-america-sources-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSYL43HYZBK5XIJ4VAHV6QEP2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:22:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国债退款将缓解供应上升的压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计美国财政部将在下周详细说明下一季度的退款计划时为市场提供一些宽慰，在经过三个季度的增加后，将保持大部分拍卖规模的稳定。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department is expected to offer markets some relief next week when it details refunding plans for the coming quarter, by keeping the size of most of its auctions steady after three quarters of increases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-treasury-refunding-set-offer-relief-supply-rises-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJNU4KSRMJJVJLFX5BXKXA247E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[两名参议员希望美国命令特斯拉限制自动驾驶汽车的使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位美国参议员周五敦促监管机构禁止特斯拉允许在非预定道路上使用驾驶辅助系统 Autopilot。【原文：Two U.S. senators on Friday urged regulators to bar Tesla from allowing the use of driver assistance system Autopilot on roads where it is not intended.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/two-senators-want-us-order-tesla-restrict-autopilot-use-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIFARPGAWJNATPWTKNP2IHUAXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:43:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克（OPEC）秘书长在《能源与环境》（MEES）发表文章称 "石油末日尚未到来]]></title><description><![CDATA[石油输出国组织（OPEC）的最高官员说，石油的末日还没有到来，因为能源需求的增长速度意味着替代品无法以所需的规模取代石油，重点应该放在减少排放上，而不是石油的使用上。【原文：The end of oil is not in sight, OPEC's top official said, as the pace of energy demand growth means that alternatives cannot replace it at the needed scale, and the focus should be on cutting emissions not oil use.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/end-oil-not-sight-opec-secretary-general-says-mees-article-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVTIXUQU2NLUPOOOMXWN5H42OY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[天然气价格暴跌，大石油公司盈利下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于天然气价格与一年前相比大幅下跌，美国和欧洲石油公司周五公布的第一季度业绩疲软。【原文：U.S. and European oil companies reported weaker first quarter results on Friday due to a sharp drop in natural gas prices compared with a year ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/earnings-big-oil-backpaddle-natgas-prices-tumble-2024-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSARL76CBVN3NK57E4JQA5OM6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>