<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:04:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:04:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[在美国征收对等关税之前，特朗普 4 月 1 日的贸易报告有哪些内容？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将于周三宣布对等关税，这一备受瞩目的消息将部分基于他的贸易、商务和财政部门主管周二提交的综合报告，以全面审查美国的贸易政策。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's hotly anticipated reciprocal tariff announcement on Wednesday will be based in part on consolidated reports due on Tuesday from his trade, Commerce and Treasury chiefs to thoroughly review U.S. trade policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/whats-trumps-april-1-trade-reports-ahead-us-reciprocal-tariffs-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVS2JHNW55OANJHBHWBLWVOJIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦存款保险公司（FDIC）表示，银行可以在未经事先批准的情况下从事加密货币活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦存款保险公司（Federal Deposit Insurance Corp）周五表示，受该机构监管的机构在开展允许的加密货币相关活动时无需事先获得批准。【原文：The Federal Deposit Insurance Corp said on Friday that institutions supervised by the agency do not need to get prior approval for permissible crypto-related activities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fdic-says-banks-can-engage-crypto-activities-without-prior-approval-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEUEU5C6P5KMLAYS4WBBAEMFZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[支出疲软、物价高企、通胀预期升温对美联储不利]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着消费者对支出的谨慎态度开始与新的通胀风险和通胀预期的再次飙升相吻合，美国联邦储备局似乎已经锁定的软着陆之路可能会变得更加复杂。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve's seemingly locked-in path to a soft landing, already roiled by the arrival of the Trump administration, may be growing even more complicated as evidence of consumer caution about spending starts to align with new inflation risks and another jump in inflation expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/weak-spending-sticky-prices-rising-inflation-expectations-bad-mix-fed-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q45O3NPCFRP6FKJMQCI5BCGM2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:53:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织确认与阿根廷就 200 亿美元计划进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五证实，正如阿根廷政府周四宣布的那样，该组织正在与阿根廷商讨的计划被要求提供 200 亿美元，而且该计划将是一项扩展基金机制（EFF）。【原文：The International Monetary Fund confirmed on Friday that the program it is discussing with Argentina was requested to be for $20 billion, as announced Thursday by the Argentine government, and that it will be an Extended Fund Facility (EFF).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/imf-confirms-20-billion-program-talks-with-argentina-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRZA3CTPRVLCNL5P6KKBSW4MEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海湾注入现金后，库什纳的 Affinity 公司资产跃升至 48 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份监管文件，贾里德-库什纳（Jared Kushner）的投资公司 Affinity Partners 在获得包括卡塔尔主权财富基金在内的中东投资者的现金注资后，去年管理的资产猛增 60%，达到 48 亿美元。【原文：Jared Kushner's investment company Affinity Partners saw assets under management jump 60% last year to $4.8 billion, according to a regulatory filing, after it received a cash injection from Middle East investors including Qatar's sovereign wealth fund.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/kushners-affinitys-assets-jump-48-billion-after-gulf-cash-injection-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4UHBE726ZN2FHMO2TT3OFND4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普关税逼近，汽车制造商权衡涨价风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内消息人士称，欧洲汽车制造商正试图制定价格上涨的幅度，以应对迫在眉睫的美国进口关税，他们担心任何先行者都有可能遭到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的反击。【原文：European carmakers are trying to work out how much their prices might have to rise in response to looming U.S. import tariffs, industry sources said, fearing any first-movers could risk a backlash from U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carmakers-weigh-risk-price-hikes-trump-tariffs-loom-sources-say-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7DB4KRHQRPKVLL6UUN4ASM6UM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司在艾滋病药物营销案中被判赔偿 16.4 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一起举报人诉讼案中，陪审团认定强生公司非法推广艾滋病药物 Prezista 和 Intelence，联邦法官周五下令强生公司的一个部门向美国政府支付 16.4 亿美元。【原文：A federal judge ordered a Johnson & Johnson unit on Friday to pay the U.S. government $1.64 billion after a jury found it liable in a whistleblower lawsuit for illegally promoting the HIV drugs Prezista and Intelence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/johnson-johnson-unit-ordered-pay-164-billion-hiv-drug-marketing-case-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7C36QKQUIVNQPKMRT4HJNGKMFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银与华尔街公司一道将标普 500 指数的年度目标下调至 6500 点以下]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国关税对经济的影响，瑞银全球财富管理公司（UBS Global Wealth Management）将S&amp;P 500指数2025年的目标值下调至6500点以下，这与巴克莱（Barclays）和高盛（Goldman Sachs）等其他华尔街公司的行动如出一辙。【原文：UBS Global Wealth Management cut the S&amp;P 500's 2025 target to below the 6,500 mark, widely mirroring actions from other Wall Street firms including Barclays and Goldman Sachs, due to the economic impact of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-joins-wall-street-firms-cutting-sp-500s-annual-target-below-6500-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOKVPNKJ3BIBVHKN2CPHP5BSQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟立法者提出在贸易紧张局势下可能收取新费用，PayPal 股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名欧盟立法者的言论引发了人们对支付公司可能被卷入不断升级的美欧贸易紧张局势和潜在关税的担忧，PayPal 的股价周五下跌了 4%。【原文：PayPal shares fell 4% on Friday after comments from a European Union lawmaker raised concerns that payments firms could get swept up in escalating U.S.-Europe trade tensions and potential tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/paypal-shares-slide-eu-lawmaker-raises-prospect-new-fees-amid-trade-tensions-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKC6KGRDIVM75LTJUXVNAKTLYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:03:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[缅甸发生地震后锡价跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[锡价周五在伦敦创下两周新高，原因是投机者押注主要生产国缅甸发生的地震可能会推迟其主要矿区的生产重启。【原文：Tin prices hit two-week highs in London on Friday as speculators bet that an earthquake that rocked major producer Myanmar could delay a restart of production in its main mining region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/tin-prices-jump-after-earthquake-hits-myanmar-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQEW6BFXKVJ6RLQLHM5UBP5CIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称与加拿大总理卡尼的通话富有成效]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，他周五与加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）进行了富有成效的通话，两国领导人将在加拿大大选后举行会晤。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said he had a productive call on Friday with Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney and that the two leaders would meet after Canada's election, which is scheduled for next month amid increased tensions between the neighboring allies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-says-he-had-productive-call-with-canadian-pm-carney-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLXV46EKCRLORKJ2TYCANCIFKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行业监管机构将在银行诉讼后废除最新的公平借贷规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行监管机构周五宣布，他们打算取消 2023 年更新的银行公平借贷规则，并恢复之前的要求，理由是银行业对新框架提出了法律挑战。【原文：U.S. bank regulators announced Friday they intended to rescind a 2023 update to fair lending rules for banks and reinstate the prior requirements, citing a legal challenge from the banking industry over the new framework.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-regulators-rescind-updated-fair-lending-rules-following-bank-litigation-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GAOQCZKQ4BNJHCA6MTP2YA43PI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[武契奇总统说美国将塞尔维亚石油公司NIS的制裁豁免延长30天]]></title><description><![CDATA[塞尔维亚总统亚历山大-武契奇（Aleksandar Vucic）周五表示，美国财政部已批准将塞尔维亚石油公司（NIS）的制裁豁免延长30天。【原文：The United States Treasury has granted a 30-day extension to the Serbian oil company NIS's sanctions waiver, Serbian President Aleksandar Vucic said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-extends-serbian-oil-firm-niss-sanctions-waiver-30-days-president-vucic-says-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6VSUVHVBRL4LEHB7AIWN3JUD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:33:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被制裁的俄罗斯油轮公司 Sovcomflot 2024 年运输量下降 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯国际文传电讯社（Interfax）周五援引俄罗斯领先的油轮集团 Sovcomflot 首席执行官伊戈尔-通科维多夫（Igor Tonkovidov）的话报道称，与 2023 年相比，该集团去年的运输量下降了约 16%，降至 6300 万吨。【原文：Russia's leading tanker group Sovcomflot's saw transportation volumes drop around 16% to 63 million metric tons last year compared to 2023, Russian news agency Interfax reported on Friday, citing the group's CEO Igor Tonkovidov as saying.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/sanctioned-russian-tanker-firm-sovcomflots-transportation-volumes-fell-16-2024-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MRRE6FROVMI5NFGB47UHI43QM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:23:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商 Wolfspeed 股价暴跌逾 45%，创 27 年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wolfspeed 的股价周五暴跌约 48%，创下自 1998 年以来的最低点，一天前这家芯片制造商在努力改善财务状况的同时任命了新的首席执行官。【原文：Wolfspeed's shares slumped about 48% on Friday, hitting their lowest since 1998, a day after the chipmaker appointed a new CEO amid its struggles to improve its financial position.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmaker-wolfspeeds-shares-plunge-over-45-27-year-low-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75X2GKKJ3BL3LBC2ZR3OS3O3R4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:01:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储主席戴利称今年降息两次 "合理"，企业将适应关税调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）仍然认为，今年降息两次是 "合理的 "预测，但在劳动力市场稳固、经济仍在增长、通胀趋于下降的情况下，决策者可以等待降息，直到他们评估企业将如何调整关税成本。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly still sees two interest-rate cuts this year as a "reasonable" projection, but with the labor market solid, the economy still growing and inflation edging down, policymakers can wait to reduce rates until they assess how businesses will adjust to tariff costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-daly-says-two-rate-cuts-this-year-reasonable-firms-adjust-tariffs-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2Q7VIA7F5JMZGRLNPSTJZMJ34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达支持的 CoreWeave 公司股价可能比首次公开募股价格高出最多 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[CoreWeave 公司周五在纳斯达克首次上市时，股价最高将比发行价高出 25%。【原文：CoreWeave's shares were set to open up to 25% above their offer price in the company's debut on the Nasdaq on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nvidia-backed-coreweaves-shares-likely-open-up-25-above-ipo-price-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTKZ5CSXJFOW5BTBBJA7RMB4VA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五家航空公司同意解决英国对跨大西洋航线的反垄断担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构周五表示，包括英国航空公司（British Airways）和美国航空公司（American Airlines）在内的五家航空公司已作出承诺，以解决人们对其英美客运航线合作协议的担忧。【原文：Britain's competition regulator said on Friday five airlines, including British Airways and American Airlines , have offered commitments to resolve concerns over their agreement to cooperate on passenger routes between the UK and the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/uk-antitrust-regulator-says-five-airlines-address-uk-us-route-deal-concerns-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PETLXYZRPZKXJN5JE6J5ROAI2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利铜矿商 Codelco 将于 2024 年实现盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利 Codelco 公司（COBRE.UL）是世界上最大的铜生产商，该公司周五公布的 2024 年财报显示，其税前利润为 7.9 亿美元，而上一年则亏损 7.57 亿美元。【原文：Chile's Codelco (COBRE.UL), the world's largest copper producer, on Friday reported a swing into the black for its 2024 earnings, posting a pre-tax profit of $790 million compared to a loss of $757 million the previous year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chiles-codelco-swings-profit-2024-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RFIWAVU2JLX3MBKC5ZCCIADDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金创 11 月以来最大单周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 3 月 26 日的一周内，美国股票基金需求旺盛，因为特朗普政府发出了更加谨慎的关税政策信号，帮助投资者将注意力重新转移到企业盈利增长的前景上。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed robust demand in the week through March 26 as signals of a more measured tariff approach from the Trump administration helped shift investor focus back to prospects of growth in corporate earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-biggest-weekly-inflows-since-november-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLGUNFHZIRJBBECCF35ZYVDJUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:46:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 董事在代理权争夺战中批评激进投资者埃利奥特]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 的独立董事鲍勃-皮斯（Bob Pease）周五为公司业绩辩护，并批评了埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management），这家美国炼油企业与激进投资者之间的董事会之争愈演愈烈。【原文：Phillips 66's independent director, Bob Pease, defended the company's performance and criticized Elliott Investment Management on Friday, as a boardroom battle between the U.S. refiner and the activist investor intensified.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/phillips-66-director-criticizes-activist-investor-elliott-amid-proxy-battle-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TALRZAV55M2ZLXIVPM6M4SE7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌将支付 1 亿美元解决广告商集体诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌已同意支付 1 亿美元现金，以了结一项长期诉讼，该诉讼称谷歌未能提供承诺的折扣，并对广告客户目标地理区域以外的广告点击收费，从而向广告客户多收费用。【原文：Google has agreed to pay $100 million in cash to settle a long-running lawsuit claiming it overcharged advertisers by failing to provide promised discounts and charged for clicks on ads outside the geographic areas the advertisers targeted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/google-pay-100-million-settle-advertisers-class-action-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LG6HW2OV7BMC5N7GZA4R4JDRIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:41:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[创纪录的液化天然气流量抵消了创纪录的产量，美国天然气价格保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国天然气期货周五持稳，原因是液化天然气（LNG）出口厂创纪录的流量抵消了日产量的下降，以及本周和下周需求低于此前预期的预测。【原文：U.S. natural gas futures held steady on Friday as record flows to liquefied natural gas (LNG) export plants offset a decline in daily output and forecasts for lower demand than previously expected this week and next.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-natgas-prices-steady-record-lng-flows-offset-record-output-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FC74CBL53ZM6TB2YKISUWDBEUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，力拓正在与刚果商谈开发锂矿床事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，力拓已与刚果民主共和国就开发世界上最大的硬岩锂矿之一进行了会谈。【原文：Rio Tinto has held talks with the Democratic Republic of Congo about developing one of the world's biggest hard rock lithium deposits, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/rio-tinto-talks-with-congo-develop-lithium-deposit-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWXVQUTH6RLJXCTZ5C53LYQSFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金因早期乐观情绪而强劲流入，但贸易担忧重现]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 3 月 26 日的一周内，全球股票基金吸引了大量资金流入，股市最初因对唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府将更有选择性地征收关税而非实施广泛贸易限制的乐观情绪而反弹。【原文：Global equity funds attracted large inflows in the week through March 26 when equity markets initially rebounded on optimism that President Donald Trump's administration would apply tariffs more selectively rather than impose broad trade restrictions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJ37OWDQ4FPQZCNR2QJL4OULFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:28:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门表示将审查长江和记的巴拿马港口交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周五发表声明称，将依法审查香港企业集团长江和记将其在巴拿马运河附近的两个港口业务出售给贝莱德领导的集团的交易，以保护公平竞争，维护公众利益。【原文：China's market regulator said in a statement on Friday it will review Hong Kong conglomerate CK Hutchison's deal to sell its two port operations near the Panama Canal to a BlackRock-led group in accordance with law to protect fair competition and safeguard public interests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chinas-market-regulator-says-review-ck-hutchisons-panama-port-deal-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7NGEBAID5N2PLMCWHMG2T7YS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:25:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 2 月 PCE 物价指数显示通胀形势依然严峻]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五公布，2月份个人消费支出（PCE）价格指数增长0.3%，而1月份为增长0.3%，未作修正。经济学家此前预计 PCE 物价指数将增长 0.3%。【原文：The Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) price index increased 0.3% in February after advancing by an unrevised 0.3% in January, the U.S. Commerce Department said on Friday. Economists had forecast the PCE price index gaining 0.3%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-us-feb-pce-prices-index-shows-inflation-picture-still-conundrum-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXIS5EIU3VLIPG7AV4YJFP6FDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国媒称中国将坚决应对美国对等关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家广播公司中央电视台下属的一个社交媒体账户周五称，如果美国即将对中国征收互惠关税，损害中国利益，中国将采取坚决反制措施。【原文：China will take resolute countermeasures if the United States harm the country's interests with its upcoming reciprocal tariffs, a social media account affiliated with Chinese state broadcaster CCTV said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-will-resolutely-respond-us-reciprocal-tariffs-state-media-says-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4FUQYUY6NOL7CED57D3XJU2KQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:04:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发布行政令后，詹纳-布洛克公司起诉美国政府]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）发布行政命令，暂停了詹纳-布洛克（Jenner & Block）律师事务所律师的安全许可，并限制他们进入政府大楼、接触官员和参与联邦合同工作，该律师事务所于周五起诉了美国政府。【原文：The law firm Jenner & Block sued the U.S. government on Friday, after President Donald Trump issued an executive order suspending security clearances for its lawyers and restricting access to government buildings, officials and federal contracting work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/jenner-block-sues-us-government-following-trump-executive-order-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTFEEIX6G5M67IWVOV64ND5PBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博鳌亚洲论坛称，由于Wegovy和Ozempic销售滞后，诺和诺德第一季度业绩可能不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（Bank of America）分析师周五表示，诺和诺德公司第一季度业绩可能会低于预期，因为其畅销药品Wegovy和Ozempic的销售滞后，这可能会促使这家丹麦制药商下调2025年的季度业绩指导。【原文：Bank of America analysts on Friday said Novo Nordisk may miss first-quarter expectations, as sales of its blockbuster Wegovy and Ozempic drugs lag, which could prompt the Danish drugmaker to cut its 2025 guidance in its quarterly results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bofa-says-novo-nordisk-may-miss-q1-expectations-wegovy-ozempic-sales-lag-2025-03-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNQ2LHSP3RJZPF2S5ZD6FSGSXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>