<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 13:10:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 13:10:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼亚取消与阿达尼集团的拟议交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯尼亚总统威廉-鲁托（William Ruto）周四表示，他已下令取消扩建肯尼亚主要机场的采购程序，政府正在考虑印度阿达尼集团（Adani Group）的提案。【原文：Kenyan President William Ruto said on Thursday he had ordered the cancellation of procurement process to expand the country's main airport, in which the government was considering a proposal by India's Adani Group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kenya-cancels-proposed-deals-with-adani-group-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYR76JEBVBK4ZLXPZ7YNUMRW3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 13:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《德国商报》报道，梅赛德斯计划每年削减成本数十亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《德国商报》周四援引德国汽车制造商发言人的话报道，梅赛德斯-奔驰计划在未来几年内每年削减数十亿欧元的成本。【原文：Mercedes-Benz plans to cut costs by several billion euros per year in the coming years, the Handelsblatt newspaper reported on Thursday, citing a spokesperson for the German carmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-plans-cut-costs-by-several-billion-euros-per-year-reports-handelsblatt-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z55QFSWFJZNI3EBQKTQ5BKARNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 12:47:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，中国信达为持有麦当劳中国股份的公司融资 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，Trustar Capital 已为一个延续基金筹集了 10 亿美元，该基金将持有中国私募股权公司在麦当劳公司中国大陆和香港业务中的控股权。【原文：Trustar Capital has raised $1 billion for a continuation fund that will hold the Chinese private equity firm's controlling stake in McDonald Corp's operations in mainland China and Hong Kong, two sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chinas-trustar-raises-1-bln-vehicle-that-holds-mcdonalds-china-stake-sources-say-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47HF3Y7WWRPFVLFVLVTHWMQVNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:52:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国对高塔姆-阿达尼受贿指控的调查结果是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）已被美国检方起诉，罪名是与一家曾在纽约上市的公司的高管合谋，策划了一项价值 2.65 亿美元的贿赂印度官员的计划，以促进其太阳能业务的发展。【原文：Indian billionaire Gautam Adani has been indicted by U.S. prosecutors for conspiring with executives of a formerly New York listed company to devise a $265 million scheme to bribe Indian officials to boost their solar energy business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/what-are-us-findings-related-gautam-adanis-bribery-charges-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELDDNJRQ3BIFNIWJCVQIZFV2FM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:28:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标英伟达实现三位数增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSSTR7UFSNOWDNZ2PWB363OP2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:26:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国天然气钻探商将提高 2025 年产量，扭转一年来的减产趋势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国天然气生产商在今年进行了一系列减产后，将在 2025 年提高产量，因为液化天然气出口工厂的需求增长有望提高已跌至数十年低点的价格。【原文：U.S. natural gas producers will boost output in 2025 following a series of production cuts this year, as rising demand from liquefied natural gas export plants is expected to increase prices that had fallen to multi-decade lows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-natural-gas-drillers-lift-2025-output-reversing-year-cuts-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLWFP4DJONJRLMQBE25BUMXRUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[农业设备需求下滑，迪尔预计年度利润低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪尔公司（Deere &amp; Co）周四预测 2025 年的利润将低于街调机构的预期，因为农业收入骤降和通胀压力削弱了对该公司拖拉机和其他农用设备的需求。【原文：Deere &amp; Co forecast 2025 profit below Street expectations on Thursday, as plummeting farm incomes and inflationary pressures dent demand for the company's tractors and other farm equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/deere-forecasts-annual-profit-below-estimates-farm-equipment-demand-slumps-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNBBRNZRTJJHDN6J73VZV3G72E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街等待安进减肥药数据有望推动股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[安进公司实验性减肥药MariTide的中期研究数据即将公布，这将揭示MariTide与礼来公司和诺和诺德公司销售的流行GLP-1药物相比有多大优势。【原文：Upcoming data from a mid-stage study of Amgen's experimental weight-loss drug MariTide will shed light on how well it might measure up against the popular GLP-1 drugs sold by Eli Lilly and Novo Nordisk .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/wall-street-awaits-amgen-weight-loss-drug-data-expected-move-shares-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AT74LVRZZBPTNOH6KPUZJGBPXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:14:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司机组人员对工会寻求更丰厚合同充满信心和愤怒]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司的空姐丽贝卡-欧文斯每天工作 10 小时，却只能拿到一半的工资--这是美国航空公司的一项通行政策，即只有在飞机运行时才向乘务员支付工资。欧文斯和成千上万像她一样的乘务员希望改变这种状况。【原文：Alaska Airlines flight attendant Rebecca Owens works 10 hours a day but only gets paid for half that time - a legacy of a common U.S. airline policy to pay cabin crew members only when planes are in motion. Owens, and thousands of cabin crew like her, wants that to change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airline-flight-crews-confident-angry-unions-seek-richer-contracts-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICMH3EY57BLZ7IKOSXXW2A5J4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[X 公司前高级政策主管与埃隆-马斯克的竞争对手山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）共事]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼克-皮克斯（Nick Pickles）是埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体平台 X 的前全球事务主管，他将与马斯克的竞争对手之一、OpenAI 的联合创始人萨姆-阿尔特曼（Sam Altman）携手合作。【原文：Nick Pickles, the former head of global affairs at Elon Musk's social media platform X, is joining forces with one of Musk's rivals, his fellow OpenAI co-founder Sam Altman.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/xs-former-top-policy-chief-takes-job-with-elon-musk-rival-sam-altman-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6YRXSOWL5ME3I62Z3DF34WRFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 11:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉高塔姆-阿达尼涉嫌贿赂案的主要事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因涉嫌参与印度一项价值 2.65 亿美元的贿赂计划而被美国检察官起诉，这使他的企业集团在两年内第二次深陷危机。【原文：Indian billionaire Gautam Adani has been indicted by U.S. prosecutors for his alleged role in a $265 million bribery scheme in India, plunging his conglomerate deep into crisis for the second time in two years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/key-events-gautam-adanis-us-indictment-over-alleged-bribery-scheme-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G34GFFNDVZJCPKA7NAHSSFDRAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:36:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达预测令人失望，纳斯达克期货领跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克期货周四领跌美国股指期货，英伟达（Nvidia）股价在盘前交易中下跌，此前投资者对这家人工智能领军企业的营收预期不以为然。【原文：Nasdaq futures led declines among U.S. stock index futures on Thursday, with Nvidia's shares falling in premarket trading after investors were unimpressed by the AI leader's revenue forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-futures-lead-declines-after-nvidias-forecast-disappoints-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCMIJH64DZPCDCMEWUQ45QYNFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:28:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在对特朗普关税的担忧中，中国宣布促进贸易的政策措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周四宣布了一系列旨在促进中国对外贸易的政策措施，包括承诺加强对企业的融资支持和扩大农产品出口。【原文：China's commerce ministry on Thursday announced a series of policy measures aimed at boosting the country's foreign trade, including pledging to strengthen financing support to firms and expand exports of agricultural products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-announces-policy-measures-boost-trade-amid-worries-over-trump-tariffs-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BQHXKU33ROLRPZRTUMN2YZT44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:18:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：美联储主席巴尔金称美国易受通胀冲击影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联邦储备银行行长汤姆-巴金（Tom Barkin）周三在接受《金融时报》采访时表示，美国比过去更容易受到通胀冲击的影响。【原文：The U.S. is more vulnerable to inflationary shocks than in the past, Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond President Tom Barkin said in an interview with the Financial Times published on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-barkin-says-us-is-vulnerable-inflation-shocks-ft-reports-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHVM3QXR5FIVVD2Y2GVN77F5CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴将电子商务平台整合为单一业务部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴集团周四在提交给证券交易所的文件中表示，将把旗下所有电子商务平台整合为一个单一的业务部门，命名为阿里巴巴电子商务事业群。【原文：Alibaba Group will integrate all of its e-commerce platforms into a single business unit to be called the Alibaba E-commerce Business Group, it said in a stock exchange filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/alibaba-integrate-e-commerce-platforms-into-one-business-group-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4NL2OJIPZPI5BZWSJNUBVQPGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产称约 1,000 名美国员工接受提前退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车公司发言人周四表示，该公司约有 6% 的美国员工接受了提前退休方案，这是这家陷入困境的日本汽车制造商在全球裁员 9000 人计划的一部分。【原文：About 6% of Nissan Motor staff in the United States have accepted early retirement packages, a company spokesperson said on Thursday, as part of the struggling Japanese carmaker's plan to cut 9,000 jobs worldwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-says-about-1000-us-staff-accept-early-retirement-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUGRTUHQYNJ5ZKKAJFZNDMSAGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构发布监管大科技支付和数字钱包的最终规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）表示，每年通过数字钱包和支付应用程序处理超过 130 亿笔金融交易的硅谷科技巨头和其他公司将接受政府监管。【原文：Silicon Valley tech giants and others who together process more than 13 billion financial transactions annually through digital wallets and payment apps will be subject to government supervision, the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-watchdog-issues-final-rule-supervise-big-tech-payments-digital-wallets-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HA4WMWR44ZJMXKNXVBPAQ4M2VM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国对高塔姆-阿达尼的起诉书中被指控的被告是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国检察官指控印度亿万富翁、以其名字命名的企业集团创始人高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）和其他七人涉嫌与印度一个可再生能源项目有关的贿赂和欺诈计划。【原文：U.S. prosecutors have charged Indian billionaire Gautam Adani, founder of a conglomerate named after him, and seven others in an alleged bribery and fraud scheme related to a renewable energy project in India.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/who-are-defendants-charged-us-indictment-gautam-adani-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPDX77TBBBLURGWMJUHB5APBFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 10:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度反对党呼吁调查阿达尼，莫迪领导的印度人民党质疑美国起诉的时机]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度反对党周四要求对阿达尼集团的不法行为指控进行调查，并表示将在该集团主席高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因涉嫌贿赂计划在美国受到指控后在议会提出这一问题。【原文：Indian opposition parties demanded a probe on Thursday into allegations of wrongdoing by the Adani Group and said they would raise the issue in parliament after its chair Gautam Adani was charged in the U.S. over an alleged bribery scheme.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-opposition-calls-adani-probe-modis-bjp-questions-timing-us-indictment-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INCINUFAKFLRJEEGGYZFGWD2MY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 09:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行任命新首席财务官，裕信银行与之接洽]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行（Commerzbank）周四任命卡斯滕-施密特（Carsten Schmitt）为新任首席财务官，这是这家德国第二大银行的关键职位，因为该银行正努力抵御意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）提出的并购要求。【原文：Commerzbank on Thursday named Carsten Schmitt as its new chief financial officer, a crucial role at Germany's No. 2 lender as it seeks to fend off an approach by Italy's UniCredit for a tie-up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commerzbank-names-new-cfo-amid-unicredit-approach-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23UR7KADLVJT7MDBYUIYJH3PSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 09:26:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国百度第三季度营收下降 3%，符合市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最大的互联网搜索服务提供商百度周四公布的第三季度财报显示，百度第三季度营收下降 3%，符合市场预期。【原文：Baidu reported a 3% fall in third-quarter revenue on Thursday, meeting market estimates, as China's biggest internet search provider grappled with weak spending on its advertising services in a sluggish economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-baidu-posts-3-fall-third-quarter-revenue-beats-market-estimates-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2TTYANYAZK6VBVTVZB2ZHY7HA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 09:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国检察官要求谷歌剥离 Chrome 浏览器以结束搜索垄断]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国检察官周三向法官提出，谷歌必须出售其 Chrome 浏览器，与竞争对手共享数据和搜索结果，并采取一系列其他措施结束其在网络搜索领域的垄断地位。【原文：U.S. prosecutors on Wednesday argued to a judge that Google must sell its Chrome browser, share data, and search results with rivals, and take a range of other measures to end its monopoly on online search.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-prosecutors-demand-google-divest-chrome-end-search-monopoly-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5IDDCPWUBKUPOO46BDIDABMYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 08:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[为应对特朗普关税，中国国家主席习近平在全球峰会上推动外交努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）再次当选美国总统后的首次全球会晤中，中国国家主席习近平展开了外交攻势，对冲预期的新关税，并准备利用华盛顿与其盟友之间未来可能出现的裂痕。【原文：In his first global meetings since Donald Trump was reelected to lead the U.S., Chinese President Xi Jinping went on a diplomatic offensive, hedging against expected new tariffs and preparing to exploit potential future rifts between Washington and its allies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bracing-trump-tariffs-chinas-xi-makes-diplomatic-push-global-summits-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJNN3KNOOZIV5BFHVTELUZBFPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 07:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国被起诉的高塔姆-阿达尼是备受争议的印度第一代富豪]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因 2.65 亿美元的贿赂计划在纽约被起诉，他是第一代富豪，在其惊人崛起的同时，也在国内外引发了一系列破坏性争议。【原文：Indian billionaire Gautam Adani, indicted in New York over a $265 million bribery scheme, is a first-generation tycoon whose phenomenal rise has been accompanied by a series of damaging controversies at home and abroad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/gautam-adani-indicted-us-is-controversial-first-generation-indian-tycoon-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVPHHRVNNRNX7JCGTLJMNLQ7SM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 06:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴伦周刊》报道：美联储威廉姆斯认为通胀降温，利率进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周四接受《巴伦周刊》（Barron's）采访时表示，他认为通胀会降温，利率会进一步下降。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams sees inflation cooling and interest rates falling further, he told Barron's in an interview published on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-williams-sees-inflation-cooling-interest-rates-falling-further-barrons-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">65TF5XYCNJP6FMXWKBDSUHY7AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 06:21:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，尽管受到美国的限制，华为仍计划在 2025 年初量产最新人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟知内情的人士表示，中国华为计划在 2025 年第一季度开始量产其最先进的人工智能芯片，尽管由于美国的限制，华为还在努力生产足够的芯片。【原文：China's Huawei plans to start mass-producing its most advanced artificial intelligence chip in the first quarter of 2025, even as it struggles to make enough chips due to U.S. restrictions, said two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/huawei-aims-mass-produce-newest-ai-chip-early-2025-despite-us-curbs-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIHEN442TJI7NJGWSLUVBKX62Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 06:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HEDGEFLOW 高盛：美国对冲基金扎堆中国剑网和 GDS]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的一份高盛（Goldman Sachs）报告显示，美国对冲基金在第三季度增加了对在美国上市的中国企业的投资，其中电子商务零售商京东商城（JD.com）和数据中心运营商GDS控股公司（GDS Holdings）的投资额居前。【原文：U.S. hedge funds raised their investments in U.S.-listed Chinese firms in the third quarter, with e-commerce retailer JD.com and data centre operator GDS Holdings leading the purchases, a Goldman Sachs note reviewed by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hedgeflow-us-hedge-funds-pile-into-chinas-jdcom-gds-goldman-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IU355RN7E5JW3NRX3NIWXDXJUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 06:08:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车进入第三轮工资谈判，罢工行动迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车管理层和工人代表将于本周四开始第三轮工资谈判，在工会威胁要通过在德国各工厂举行罢工将斗争升级之前，双方只剩下十天时间来寻找解决方案。【原文：Volkswagen management and worker representatives begin a third round of wage negotiations on Thursday, with just ten days left to find a solution before unions have threatened to escalate the fight with strikes across German sites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-enters-third-round-wage-talks-strike-action-looms-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQGQVWC4K5JXVFDBZAONLHKOJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 06:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家橄榄球联盟（NFL）的巨大收视率经受住了选举季的考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[在刚刚过去的选举季中，NFL 的电视收视率依然强劲。【原文：The NFL's television ratings remained strong in the wake of the recent election season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/nfls-massive-ratings-weather-election-season-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWGDUME2G5JVFPHGRSFI272T3E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 06:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小麦种植者收紧库存，面粉加工厂面临供应紧张问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些出口国的小麦种植者不愿意出售他们的作物，贸易商、农民和磨坊主说，由于价格接近四年来的最低点，面粉生产商的供应越来越少，很容易受到任何潜在价格上涨的影响。【原文：Wheat growers in several exporting countries are reluctant to sell their crops with prices near four-year lows, traders, farmers and millers say, leaving flour makers with dwindling supplies and vulnerable to any potential upswing in prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/flour-millers-face-supply-crunch-wheat-farmers-tighten-grip-stocks-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IVNYWQLSNROLLMSTZ3QI6DWHBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 05:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>