<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:41:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:41:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在与宗教领袖通话时将技术问题归咎于 AT&T]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，他与美国宗教领袖举行的电话会议遇到了技术问题，他为此指责 AT&amp;T，同时敦促这家无线运营商的老板参与处理这一情况。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday a conference call he had with American faith leaders faced tech issues for which he blamed AT&amp;T while urging the wireless carrier's boss to get involved in handling the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-blames-att-tech-issues-call-with-faith-leaders-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WB5HL27PUZJDRBIH7MMXDNHZ7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[排除 ICE 指数可能减缓华纳兄弟 143 亿美元债券转入垃圾投资组合的速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美银全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）的一份报告称，媒体巨头华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）总额达 143 亿美元的债券在高收益债券投资组合中的新家迁移可能会因最近宣布被排除在一个主要指数之外而放缓。【原文：A total $14.3 billion of media giant Warner Bros Discovery's bonds' move to their new home in high-yield bond portfolios will likely be slowed by a recently announced exclusion from a major index, said a BofA Global Research report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ice-index-exclusion-likely-slow-warner-bros-143-billion-bonds-move-junk-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LWLSF6DERK3RAXEHEK4452JBM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:18:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比认为不会出现滞胀，但情况 "肯定 "会变得更糟]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周一表示，随着失业率接近4%，通胀率约为2.5%并在下降，他认为关税或其他供应方面的冲击不可能在短期内造成20世纪70年代式的实际滞胀，当时的失业率是现在的两倍，通胀率超过13%。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee on Monday said that with unemployment near 4% and inflation around 2.5% and falling, he sees no possibility that tariffs or another supply-side shock could in the near term cause actual 1970s-style stagflation, when the unemployment was double today's rate and inflation was above 13%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-sees-no-stagflation-definitely-things-could-get-worse-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42JTFBUUPVL57MJJY62WYSDP74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:09:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华伦天奴面临不确定性，首席执行官因利润下滑请病假]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品牌华伦天奴（Valentino）周一表示，其首席执行官雅各布-文图里尼（Jacopo Venturini）目前正在休病假，以回应媒体关于他即将离职的报道。【原文：Italian luxury brand Valentino said on Monday its Chief Executive Jacopo Venturini was currently on sick leave, responding to media reports of his imminent departure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/valentino-faces-uncertainty-ceo-takes-sick-leave-amid-profit-slowdown-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJFZBGJB3BPVNETLSF3ZB6WS7A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:59:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称特朗普致信鲍威尔敦促降低利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫新闻秘书卡罗琳-利维特（Karoline Leavitt）周一告诉记者，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普写信给美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔，敦促他降低利率。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump wrote Fed Chair Jerome Powell urging him to lower interest rates, White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt told reporters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/white-house-says-trump-wrote-powell-urge-lower-rates-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MB7PKOXKUNKTBBL33FZUKNYUHY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际商会称新网络安全事件已得到控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际刑事法院（ICC）周一表示，上周末发现了一起 "新的、复杂的和有针对性的 "网络安全事件，并补充说该事件现已得到控制。【原文：The International Criminal Court (ICC) said on Monday it had detected a "new, sophisticated and targeted" cybersecurity incident late last week, adding it has now been contained.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/icc-says-new-cybersecurity-incident-has-been-contained-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2WHUD2EENP4TASVIOD5OJ3IWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙 BBVA 银行将继续收购萨瓦德尔银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙对外银行（BBVA）周一表示，尽管政府在至少三年内有效阻止该公司与较小的竞争对手萨瓦德尔（Sabadell）完全合并，但该公司仍将继续对较小的竞争对手萨瓦德尔（Sabadell）进行恶意收购。【原文：Spain's BBVA said on Monday it would move ahead with its hostile takeover bid for smaller rival Sabadell despite the government effectively blocking it from fully merging with its smaller rival for at least three years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/spains-bbva-proceed-with-takeover-bid-sabadell-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMBMPTU62ZOXLJA32QSMEMWKNQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:46:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德：政府债务上升对美国市场地位构成最大风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德（BlackRock）周一表示，美国政府债务激增可能会削弱投资者对美国主要资产（如长期国债和美元）的偏好，从而支持投资者转向美国境外的投资机会。【原文：Surging U.S. government debt may sap investor appetite for key U.S. assets like long-dated Treasuries and the dollar, bolstering the case for turning to opportunities beyond U.S. borders, BlackRock said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/rising-government-debt-poses-greatest-risk-us-market-standing-says-blackrock-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHQEBQNXDVKFHLO7ST2MXTMMVU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席博斯蒂克仍希望今年降息一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周一重申，他仍认为央行今年将下调一次利率目标，同时表示，由于贸易关税将如何影响美国经济的通胀动态仍存在很多不确定性，因此并不急于采取行动。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic repeated on Monday that he still sees the central bank cutting its interest rate target once this year, while suggesting there's no urgency to act as a lot of uncertainty remains in terms of how trade tariffs will affect inflation dynamics in the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bostic-still-eyes-one-rate-cut-this-year-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCAELDTS2FKVRGKU4YV3RUELXA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：特朗普政府希望在 2026 年初填补美联储空缺，任命鲍威尔继任者]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一表示，特朗普政府正在考虑利用预计于2026年初出现的下一个美联储理事会空缺来任命央行主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）的继任者。【原文：The Trump administration is considering using the next expected Federal Reserve Board of Governors vacancy in early 2026 for appointing a successor to central bank Chair Jerome Powell, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-eyes-fed-vacancy-early-2026-appoint-powell-successor-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LDZPLHAEVIGDK3J5POYX6DMVU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:26:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院就是否通过修订后的州人工智能监管禁令展开辩论]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位重要的美国共和党参议员同意将联邦对各州人工智能监管的暂停期修订为五年，并允许各州通过有关儿童网络安全和保护艺术家形象或肖像的规定。【原文：Two key U.S. Republican senators agreed to a revised federal moratorium on state regulation of artificial intelligence to five years and allow states to adopt rules on child online safety and protecting artists' image or likeliness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-senate-debates-whether-adopt-revised-state-ai-regulation-ban-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROX2MIGDEVOSHJFILLGH56RAUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:22:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅签署协议收购护发品牌 Color Wow]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国化妆品巨头欧莱雅（L'Oreal）周一表示，该公司已签署协议收购位于美国和英国的护发品牌 Color Wow。【原文：French cosmetics giant L'Oreal said on Monday it had signed an agreement to acquire Color Wow, a haircare brand based in the U.S. and Britain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/loreal-signs-agreement-acquire-haircare-brand-color-wow-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MR4LYJMVJJKLO7LT4PR247YUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗预计第三季度金价将在 3100-3500 美元附近盘整]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行在周一的一份报告中表示，由于中东地缘政治局势缓和以及全球经济增长前景改善，黄金价格将在第三季度巩固在每盎司3100美元至3500美元左右。【原文：Citi expects the price of gold to consolidate around $3,100 to $3,500 per ounce in the third quarter, as prices moderate due to geopolitical de-escalation in the Middle East and an improved global growth outlook, the bank said in a note on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/citi-expects-gold-price-consolidate-around-3100-3500-third-quarter-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UMAP2KJQRIU5GS6EUTTIWZSQQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府警告：与伊朗有关的黑客可能会攻击美国公司和关键基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国政府官员周一发布的一份公告称，受伊朗庇护的黑客可能会将目标对准美国公司和关键基础设施运营商，特别是与以色列研究和国防公司有控股或合作关系的国防组织。【原文：Iranian-affilited hackers may target U.S. companies and critical infrastructure operators, particularly defense organizations with holdings or relationships with Israeli research and defense firms, according to an advisory from U.S. government officials Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/iran-linked-hackers-may-target-us-firms-critical-infrastructure-us-government-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHVPQKCDKZNG3ATRDZDVG4YNF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:39:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 数据显示，4 月份美国原油产量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署发布的《石油供应月报》系列数据显示，4 月份美国原油产量达到创纪录的 1,347 万桶/日，高于 3 月份的 1,345 万桶/日。【原文：U.S. crude oil production hit a record 13.47 million barrels-per-day in April, up from 13.45 million bpd in March, according to data released by the Energy Information Administration as part of its Petroleum Supply Monthly series.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-oil-output-hit-record-april-eia-data-shows-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFWOQUPKUFJXXHJAZULCZU2Q6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:30:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院法案削减清洁能源引起劳工和商界反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院在其版本的唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统税收和支出法案中提出的削减清洁能源补贴的建议自上周末公布以来，招致了商界和劳工团体的猛烈抨击，一些人认为此举将提高电价并扼杀就业机会。【原文：The U.S. Senate’s proposed cuts to clean energy subsidies in its version of President Donald Trump's tax and spending bill have drawn searing criticism from business and labor groups since they were unveiled over the weekend, with some arguing the moves will raise power prices and kill jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-senate-bills-clean-energy-cuts-draw-backlash-labor-business-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTW52QIYXJICTCP3576UP6L36Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:18:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood 推出代币，允许欧盟用户交易美股]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 周一表示，它已推出代币，允许欧盟客户交易 200 多只美国股票和交易所交易基金，包括英伟达、苹果和微软。【原文：Robinhood said on Monday it has launched tokens that will allow its customers in the European Union to trade more than 200 U.S. stocks and exchange-traded funds, including Nvidia , Apple and Microsoft .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/robinhood-launches-tokens-allowing-eu-users-trade-us-stocks-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JITJBP5T4FOVFJNQE4UIWEAUFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示美国将立即重启与加拿大的贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周一表示，在加拿大取消针对美国科技公司的数字服务税后，美国将立即重启与加拿大的贸易谈判。【原文：The United States will restart trade negotiations with Canada immediately after Canada scrapped its digital services tax targeting U.S. technology firms, White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-restart-trade-negotiations-with-canada-immediately-white-house-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RS6GYAONZFNNXEXCFGKJ7JHDMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:49:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长贝森特警告各国在 7 月 9 日最后期限后将面临更高的关税税率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一警告说，即使各国本着诚意进行谈判，它们仍有可能在7月9日面临大幅提高关税的局面，并补充说，任何可能的延期都将取决于唐纳德-特朗普总统。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said warned on Monday that countries could still face sharply higher tariffs on July 9 even if they are negotiating in good faith, adding that any potential extensions will be up to President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasurys-bessent-warns-countries-face-higher-tariff-rates-after-july-9-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXV2ZY5CBROHFOCPKBYG6XGSEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约市少年在 "地铁冲浪 "时遇害，其母可起诉 Meta、TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州法官裁定，Meta Platforms 和 TikTok 的所有者 ByteDance 必须面对曼哈顿一名 15 岁男孩的母亲提起的过失致死诉讼，这名男孩是在行驶的列车上 "地铁冲浪 "时死亡的。【原文：Meta Platforms and TikTok owner ByteDance must face a wrongful death lawsuit by the mother of a 15-year-old Manhattan boy who died while "subway surfing" on a moving train, a New York state judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/meta-tiktok-can-be-sued-by-mother-nyc-teen-killed-while-subway-surfing-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNIQ6X3MLBNVJEHNDVZW6Y4COE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉将波音公司的前景展望调整为稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构惠誉（Fitch）周一将飞机制造商波音公司的评级展望从 "负面 "调整为 "稳定"，理由是其财务灵活性和生产状况有所改善。【原文：Global ratings agency Fitch on Monday revised its outlook on planemaker Boeing to 'stable' from 'negative', citing improved financial flexibility and production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-revises-boeing-outlook-stable-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMI3K6WOYVNQNKUOVOEJUW5TLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟技术主管称，欧洲推动的人工智能千兆工厂吸引了 76 项投标]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟技术主管周一表示，已有76家公司竞标开发欧洲人工智能千亿国际娱乐，这对该集团为在这一关键技术上赶超美国和中国而做出的努力来说，是一个超出预期的回应。【原文：Seventy-six companies have bid to develop Europe's artificial intelligence gigafactories, the EU's tech chief said on Monday, hailing a bigger than expected response to the bloc's push to catch up with the U.S. and China in this key technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/europes-ai-gigafactory-push-attracts-76-bids-eu-tech-chief-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2GTEOV525PIZDM7ZZBQUOLD5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院在特朗普法案中保留部分税收抵免，可再生能源股涨跌不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国参议院推进总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全面税收和支出法案之后，美国可再生能源公司的股票在周一早盘交易中表现不一。【原文：Shares of U.S. renewable energy firms saw a mixed performance in early Monday trading after the U.S. Senate advanced President Donald Trump's sweeping tax-and-spending bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/renewable-energy-shares-mixed-us-senate-preserves-some-tax-credits-trump-bill-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWAMR6Z4VNO6FJCNUSV6IU3QRQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回美国航空公司对禁止捷蓝航空联盟裁决的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一驳回了美国航空公司要求推翻一项司法判决的请求，该判决认定该公司与捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）现已破裂的美国东北部地区合作关系违反了联邦反垄断法。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court rejected on Monday a request by American Airlines to overturn a judicial decision that found that the company's now-scrapped U.S. Northeast partnership with JetBlue Airways violated federal antitrust law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-rejects-american-airlines-appeal-ruling-barring-jetblue-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCJ4EVCF5BOWNFTMVSEXLCVFDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:56:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回埃克森公司对 1425 万美元空气污染罚款的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一驳回了埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil Corp）的诉讼请求，该公司要求推翻法官在德克萨斯州贝敦（Baytown）原油精炼厂空气污染的长期诉讼中判处的 1425 万美元民事罚款。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court turned away on Monday Exxon Mobil Corp's bid to overturn a $14.25 million civil penalty that a judge imposed in a long-running lawsuit over air pollution at its Baytown, Texas, crude oil refinery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-rejects-exxons-appeal-1425-million-air-pollution-penalty-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAGTWWMTCZPLLHQL6GIBOFZKMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:56:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将复审考克斯通信公司价值数十亿美元的版权案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一同意就考克斯通信公司 [RIC:RIC:COXC.UL] 与一些音乐唱片公司之间的版权纠纷做出裁决，此前的司法判决驳回了陪审团针对考克斯用户涉嫌盗版音乐而对这家互联网服务提供商做出的价值 10 亿美元的判决。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court agreed on Monday to decide a copyright dispute between Cox Communications [RIC:RIC:COXC.UL] and a group of music labels following a judicial decision that threw out a $1 billion jury verdict against the internet service provider over alleged piracy of music by Cox customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-review-billion-dollar-cox-communications-copyright-case-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAXJ5BMHSRJ7DK6BJ5MJZPDE3M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子从亚马逊招聘人工智能专家]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国技术公司西门子周一表示，已聘请亚马逊高管瓦西-菲洛明（Vasi Philomin）担任新的数据和人工智能主管一职。【原文：Siemens has recruited Amazon executive Vasi Philomin to its new position of head of data and artificial intelligence, the German technology company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/siemens-recruits-artificial-intelligence-expert-amazon-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSPB5QSUGNMUHDNEGTIIJRAPAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治紧张局势推高石油前景，但需求担忧依然存在：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周一的一项民意调查显示，中东紧张局势爆发后，分析师小幅上调了油价预期，但欧佩克+供应增加和需求前景缓和继续对原油构成压力。【原文：Analysts have marginally lifted their oil price forecasts after the flare-up of tensions in the Middle East, but rising OPEC+ supply and a tempered demand outlook continue to weigh on crude, a Reuters poll showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/geopolitical-tensions-nudge-oil-outlook-higher-demand-concerns-persist-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E74ANWXFUBNTLLATCQNHAXK4YM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年上半年或 2025 年的市场：美元下行，枪支上行]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普做出激进的竞选承诺后，投资者知道，随着他重返领导世界最大经济体的岗位，今年的市场将变得崎岖不平。但迄今为止，几乎没有人预测到结果，尤其是美元的大幅下跌。【原文：After U.S. President Donald Trump's radical campaign pledges, investors knew markets would get bumpy this year as he returned to lead the world's biggest economy. But almost nobody predicted the outcome so far, especially the dollar's dramatic fall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-h1-analysis-pix-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOQBRHJL3FOZJAFUWMN2ASI3UY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:10:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与麻省理工学院分拆出来的 Commonwealth 公司达成购买核聚变动力的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周一表示，它已达成一项协议，将从弗吉尼亚州的一个以核聚变为燃料的项目中购买电力。【原文：Alphabet's Google said on Monday it has struck a deal to buy power from a project in Virginia fueled by fusion, the reaction that powers the sun and the stars but is not yet commercial on Earth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/google-strikes-deal-buy-fusion-power-mit-spinoff-commonwealth-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HZZRQK6IBO5TFN65A5W5ZS5RU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>