<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:06:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:06:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 分析师：雪佛龙在赫斯交易仲裁中胜过埃克森]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司将继续以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司，在此之前，雪佛龙在一场具有里程碑意义的法律战中战胜了更大的竞争对手埃克森美孚，获得了圭亚那海岸数十年来最大的石油发现。【原文：Chevron will proceed with its $53 billion acquisition of Hess after it prevailed in a landmark legal battle against larger rival Exxon Mobil to gain access to the largest oil discovery in decades off the coast of Guyana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/view-analysts-chevron-winning-arbitration-over-exxon-hess-deal-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7IGJ4AJKQ5I5ZDQTFUFO2WPM4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，美国医疗保险公司寻求实现自 2018 年以来奥巴马医改保费的最大跃升]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据健康研究公司 KFF 的分析，受保费税收抵免即将到期和医疗商品可能被征收关税的影响，美国保险公司要求对奥巴马医保计划的保费进行自 2018 年以来最大的一次上调。【原文：U.S. insurers are requesting the biggest premium increases for Obamacare plans since 2018, according to an analysis by health-research firm KFF, prompted by the looming expiry of premium tax credits and potential tariffs on medical goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-health-insurers-seek-largest-jump-obamacare-premiums-since-2018-study-shows-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGHEK2YBANLALKYCI7WVJFMOJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:16:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉信理财因交易繁荣和资产增长而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经纪公司嘉信理财（Charles Schwab）周五表示，受强劲的交易活动和资产管理费增加的推动，该公司第二季度利润增长了近 60%。【原文：U.S. brokerage firm Charles Schwab said on Friday its profit rose nearly 60% in the second quarter, driven by robust trading activity and increased asset management fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/charles-schwab-profit-surges-trading-boom-asset-growth-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEHGBM6XXFP3PLJ7SU2XU2DYWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月独户住宅开工量和许可量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于高抵押贷款利率和经济不确定性阻碍了购房，6 月份美国单户住宅建设和未来建设许可大幅下降，这表明住宅投资在第二季度再次萎缩。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding and permits for future construction fell sharply in June as high mortgage rates and economic uncertainty hampered home purchases, suggesting residential investment contracted again in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-single-family-housing-starts-permits-decline-june-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KNEUAVVFZKBRJI7LL247M6Q7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税忧虑和通胀压力导致美国股票基金每周资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至7月16日的一周内，美国股票基金再次面临抛售压力，原因是人们担心唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税言论和通胀压力的增加，可能会使美联储对过早降息保持谨慎。【原文：U.S. equity funds again came under selling pressure through the week to July 16, dampened by worries over President Donald Trump's tariff rhetoric and the buildup in inflationary pressure, potentially keeping the Federal Reserve cautious about a premature rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-weekly-outflows-tariff-worries-inflation-pressure-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSRZWVGGCZPHFMO3XJGS6RJAWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威兹航空公司将恢复波兰莫德林机场的航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[运营官罗兰-蒂施纳（Roland Tischner）周五表示，在伦敦上市的低成本航空公司威兹航空（Wizz Air）将在停飞 13 年后恢复波兰中部华沙莫德林机场的航班，并计划从 12 月起在该机场部署两架飞机。【原文：London-listed low-cost carrier Wizz Air will resume flights from Warsaw Modlin Airport in central Poland after a 13-year hiatus, with plans to deploy two aircraft there from December, operations officer Roland Tischner said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/wizz-air-resume-flights-polands-modlin-airport-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLCCCEN7N5OBTOSTMEL2QE2JCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:16:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《卫报》报道，英国 JLR 公司推迟推出路虎揽胜和捷豹电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《卫报》周五援引两位知情人士的话报道称，英国豪华汽车制造商捷豹路虎已推迟推出电动路虎揽胜和捷豹车型，以便有时间进行更多测试，并等待需求回升。【原文：British luxury carmaker Jaguar Land Rover has delayed the launch of its electric Range Rover and Jaguar models to allow time for more testing and for demand to pick up, The Guardian reported on Friday citing two people with knowledge of the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/britains-jlr-delays-launch-range-rover-jaguar-evs-guardian-reports-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIJQ66DDJZIIVBY2I6E75KFUJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国财长告诉七国集团伙伴，关税战必须尽快结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国财政部长拉尔斯-克林拜尔周五在与来自七大经济体集团的同行会晤时明确表示，必须尽快结束全球贸易冲突。【原文：German Finance Minister Lars Klingbeil made clear in a meeting with his counterparts from the Group of Seven major economies on Friday that the global trade conflict must be ended quickly, he told reporters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tariff-war-must-end-quickly-german-finance-minister-tells-g7-partners-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2EKK2BULROGLAN3ZDHGAQ3N2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行在华业务，高管面临离职禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士称，在一名银行家被禁止离开中国后，富国银行已暂停了所有前往中国的旅行，这使这家美国银行在世界第二大经济体的业务成为焦点。【原文：Wells Fargo has suspended all travel to China after a banker was blocked from leaving the country, a source said, bringing the U.S. bank's operations in the world's second-largest economy into focus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargos-business-china-where-senior-executive-faces-an-exit-ban-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUFEES4DANLEHDUAYN3D6BMLBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街券商撤回 9 月英国央行降息呼声，因通胀形势胶着]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街主要券商已经撤销了对英国央行 9 月份降息的预期，因为通胀依然坚挺，劳动力市场具有活力。【原文：Major Wall Street brokerages have withdrawn their expectations for a September interest rate cut by the Bank of England, as inflation remains sticky and the labour market resilient.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-brokerages-pull-september-boe-rate-cut-calls-inflation-proves-sticky-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KQRQJP3P5IJ7M3YIAFGAUNAPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税担忧导致全球股票基金资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至7月16日的一周内，全球投资者纷纷从股票基金中撤资，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税威胁和一份显示美国消费者价格上涨的通胀报告抑制了风险情绪。【原文：Global investors pulled money out of equity funds in the week through July 16 as U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats and an inflation report indicating an increase in U.S. consumer prices, dampened risk sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFOLIZLSLNLTDLL2EZFI5KK5BE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[具有系统性风险的人工智能模型就如何遵守欧盟人工智能规则给出了指导意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五制定了指导方针，以帮助其认定存在系统性风险并面临更严格义务以减轻潜在威胁的人工智能模型遵守欧盟人工智能法规（AI Act）。【原文：The European Commission set out guidelines on Friday to help AI models it has determined have systemic risks and face tougher obligations to mitigate potential threats comply with European Union artificial intelligence regulation (AI Act).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ai-models-with-systemic-risks-given-pointers-how-comply-with-eu-ai-rules-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJ7KLDVLDNIKROVVABTUSAFESA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费强劲，美国运通利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运通周五公布的第二季度利润超过预期，这主要得益于其富裕持卡人的弹性消费。【原文：American Express surpassed estimates for second-quarter profit on Friday, fueled by resilient spending from its affluent cardholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/american-express-exceeds-profit-expectations-robust-spending-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYY2AIWPFVM2VN2AMD6QFH52RU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税威胁到香槟在美国市场的重要地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个法国行业组织的主席说，在唐纳德-特朗普总统威胁对欧盟出口产品征收 30% 的关税后，法国东北部的香槟生产商需要寻找新的市场，他建议巴西、东南亚和南非作为选择。【原文：Champagne producers in northeastern France need to find new markets after President Donald Trump threatened 30% tariffs on EU exports, the chairman of a French industry group said, suggesting Brazil, Southeast Asia and South Africa as options.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-tariffs-threaten-take-fizz-out-champagnes-crucial-us-market-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHSBW5YTYROTDAO4QN3DZTW7PY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价正面惊喜和股票新纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZG2SZSUMZL3TH3RWE525DCCEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币创 6 个月新高，以太币相关股票大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币相关股票在周五的盘前交易中上涨，其中与以太坊相关的股票在以太坊创下六个月新高后领涨。【原文：Cryptocurrency-related stocks rose in premarket trading on Friday, with shares linked to ether leading the charge after the No. 2 crypto hit a six-month high.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ether-linked-stocks-jump-crypto-coin-hits-6-month-high-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFZWX67KV5K7FMDTQWMTGX45D4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3M 因削减成本和扩大利润率而上调 2025 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[3M 公司周五上调了全年利润预期，因为其削减成本的措施和专注于高利润产品的努力开始见效，这使得这家工业巨头的股价在盘前交易中上涨了 2.5%。【原文：3M on Friday raised its full-year profit forecast, as its cost-cutting measures and efforts to focus on high-margin products begin to pay off, sending shares of the industrial giant up 2.5% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/3m-lifts-2025-profit-forecast-cost-cutting-margin-expansion-efforts-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6KWXOV5XNMTRBRUVNVSOVCUJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:38:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国联科机器人启动上市程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国初创企业 Unitree Robotics 周五向证券监管机构提交的一份文件显示，该公司已开始为潜在的首次公开募股进行所谓的 "辅导"。【原文：Chinese startup Unitree Robotics has begun the so-called "tutoring" process for a potential initial public offering, a filing with the securities regulator showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-unitree-robotics-starts-ipo-process-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYHTPV2QUFOYZF2KABKGI6FJXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 随着盈利增加，工业板块涨势将面临考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[在华尔街跌宕起伏的一年中，工业板块一直引领着美国股市的走势，但随着财报季的升温，该板块的实力将受到考验。【原文：The industrial sector has led the way for U.S. equities during a topsy-turvy year on Wall Street, but its strength will be tested as earnings season heats up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/wall-st-week-ahead-industrial-sectors-gains-be-tested-earnings-ramp-up-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZLQ2CAXNFPVXPLZGHCKKH4SJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对经济的乐观情绪抵消了 Netflix 的跌幅，华尔街期货走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国经济复苏迹象的提振，美国股指期货周五走高，尽管 Netflix 的季度利润跑赢大市，但仍未能令投资者眼前一亮。【原文：U.S. stock index futures inched higher on Friday, buoyed by signs of a resilient U.S. economy, even as Netflix's market-beating quarterly profit failed to dazzle investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-edge-up-optimism-over-economy-offsets-netflixs-fall-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UYQ3WZMBBOLDCTXD7563T2FDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:14:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司赢得埃克森公司圭亚那油田争夺战]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司将继续以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司（Hess），在此之前，雪佛龙在一场具有里程碑意义的法律战中战胜了更大的竞争对手埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil），获得了几十年来最大的石油发现。【原文：Chevron will proceed with its $53 billion acquisition of Hess , after it prevailed in a landmark legal battle against larger rival Exxon Mobil to gain access to the largest oil discovery in decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-wins-exxon-battle-over-guyana-oilfield-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3C7D7HOOFMVRIDDVO7PYB7VXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:13:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在需求低迷的情况下从高端旅行战略中获得回报]]></title><description><![CDATA[大流行病发生后，美国航空公司加倍努力发展高端旅游，以提高利润，减少受经济波动影响的可能性。【原文：U.S. airlines doubled down on high-end travel after the pandemic to drive up profits and reduce their vulnerability to economic swings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-airlines-reap-rewards-premium-travel-strategy-amid-demand-slump-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVI7NY344FPQNLGTYRWFRIYZUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀担忧压倒特朗普压力，美联储推迟降息立场不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储官员即将于本月晚些时候召开政策会议之际，美国降息的理由仍悬而未决，数据显示出通胀走高的新迹象，而唐纳德-特朗普总统也在加紧要求降低借贷成本。【原文：The case for a U.S. interest rate cut remains unresolved as Federal Reserve officials head into their policy meeting later this month, with data showing fresh signs of higher inflation and President Donald Trump intensifying his demands for lower borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-rate-cut-delay-intact-inflation-fears-override-trump-pressure-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NX7W3SJCXFNKNLNJJTXH2GTLDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本为库什塔德的零售梦想提供了现实检验]]></title><description><![CDATA[当 Alimentation Couche-Tard 放弃以 460 亿美元竞购 Seven & i 时，其打造全球便利店巨头的企图受挫。【原文：Alimentation Couche-Tard's attempt to create a global convenience store behemoth was set back when it pulled its $46 billion bid for Seven & i , whose consumers in Japan have emotional ties to their purveyor of rice balls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-provides-reality-check-couche-tards-grand-retail-dream-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4KD3KKVEBKN7FOFY4WOBGWCYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称中国悄然发布 2025 年稀土配额]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士本周表示，中国已悄然发布了 2025 年的首个稀土开采和冶炼配额，而没有典型的公开声明，这是中国政府加强对这一关键行业控制的又一迹象。【原文：China has quietly issued its first 2025 rare earth mining and smelting quotas without the typical public statement, sources with knowledge of the matter said this week, another sign of Beijing tightening its control over the crucial sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-quietly-issues-2025-rare-earth-quotas-sources-say-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7NYQVBWZVJK5K7DR6DWAFUVLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂表示，美国财政部部长贝森特相信有可能达成良好的关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五在东京的办公室会见日本首相石破茂（Shigeru Ishiba）后表示，两国可以就关税问题达成 "良好的协议"。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba that their countries can reach a "good agreement" on tariffs, Ishiba said on Friday after meeting Bessent at his office in Tokyo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasurys-bessent-believes-good-tariff-deal-is-possible-japan-pm-ishiba-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSPPJ4JRMBKXNNXP4Z5KHTQZBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国敦促加拿大放弃钢铁进口限制并威胁采取反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部呼吁加拿大纠正限制钢铁进口的 "错误做法"，并在周五的一份声明中表示，将采取必要措施维护中国企业的合法权益。【原文：China's commerce ministry called on Canada to correct the "wrong practice" of restrictions on steel imports and said in a statement on Friday it would take necessary measures to safeguard the legitimate rights and interests of Chinese firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-urges-canada-drop-steel-import-curbs-threatens-countermeasures-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUXGIPRWQRLRXLR7MEJJEGS47A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美国关税关系紧张，G20 财长仍在南非达成共识]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策给他们的会议蒙上了一层阴影，但二十国集团（G20）各国财政部长周五仍对就贸易和其他全球挑战的共同立场达成一致表示乐观。【原文：Finance chiefs of G20 countries expressed optimism for an agreement on a common position on trade and other global challenges on Friday despite U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs which have overshadowed their meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/g20-finance-chiefs-approach-consensus-south-africa-despite-us-tariff-tensions-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DX4WQK4URNLATDO5ESMXYGCDWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:35:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，日本央行可能在报告中减少对美国关税打击的悲观看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉日本央行想法的消息人士称，日本央行将在本月发布的季度报告中警告美国关税影响的不确定性，但对日本经济近期受到的冲击可能会给出一个没有三个月前那么悲观的看法。【原文：The Bank of Japan will warn of uncertainty over the impact of U.S. tariffs in a quarterly report due this month, but may offer a less gloomy view on the near-term hit to Japan's economy than three months ago, said three sources familiar with its thinking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bank-japan-may-offer-less-gloomy-view-us-tariff-hit-report-sources-say-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52RNTXNIJ5JCRMGSLXNEIYN54U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果美联储鲍威尔提前离职，对冲基金青睐短期可转换债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金表示，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔明年任期届满前解雇他，他们已经做好了准备。【原文：Hedge funds say they are prepared if U.S. President Donald Trump fires Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell before his term expires next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hedge-funds-favour-short-dated-convertible-bonds-if-feds-powell-leaves-early-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOI7QLF2ORIZ7OYQ3R7AEUMMTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:12:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>