<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:04:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:04:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储报告 2024 年全面净亏损 775 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周五表示，与 2023 年相比，美联储去年在运营方面面临的损失有所减少。【原文：The Federal Reserve said on Friday the loss it faced last year on its operations declined relative to 2023.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-reports-comprehensive-2024-net-loss-775-billion-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62DQX6I6ZRMOXLH4U5ACZEBUT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 17:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅虎达成向投资公司出售 TechCrunch 的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[雅虎与媒体投资公司 Regent 周五表示，雅虎已签署协议，将向 Regent 出售其拥有 20 年历史的科技新闻网站 TechCrunch。【原文：Yahoo has signed a deal to sell its 20-year-old technology news website, TechCrunch, to media investment firm Regent, the companies said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/yahoo-strikes-deal-sell-techcrunch-investment-firm-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPLJSYR5DROC3K7YCSWCWRJL3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:52:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与习近平会谈在即，美国贸易代表将会见中国贸易代表]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他的最高贸易主管贾米森-格里尔计划下周与中国贸易部长通话，并重申他计划利用关税来帮助缩小美国与其主要经济对手之间的贸易逆差。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday his top trade chief, Jamieson Greer, plans to speak with his Chinese counterpart next week and reiterated his plan to use tariffs to help narrow the U.S. trade deficit with its main economic rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-trade-chief-meet-with-chinese-counterpart-trump-xi-talks-loom-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GH6PBQUAWZJHBHFV7RYULL2YOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:46:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会调查中国科技和电信公司是否试图逃避美国限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会周五表示，正在对华为、中兴、杭州海康威视、中国移动、中国电信等中国公司进行调查，以确定它们是否在设法规避美国的限制。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission said Friday it is investigating Chinese companies including Huawei Technology, ZTE , Hangzhou Hikvision , China Mobile , China Telecom and others to determine if they are seeking to evade U.S. restrictions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fcc-probing-if-chinese-tech-telecom-firms-seeking-evade-us-restrictions-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4K6OZOCYRPBXO56T6EI2NBPJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希思罗机场恢复航班，预计周六提供全面服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦希思罗机场周五表示，在一个变电站发生火灾导致电力中断后，该机场正在恢复航班，预计周六将全面运营。【原文：London's Heathrow Airport said on Friday it was resuming flights after a fire at a substation knocked out its power, and it expected to run a full operation on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/heathrow-resuming-flights-expects-full-service-saturday-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRBXUBRZYJPG5HEJ3Y4Q7BI37A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国取消对被控为朝鲜洗钱的加密货币 "搅拌机 "龙卷风现金公司的制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五解除了对龙卷风现金公司（Tornado Cash）的经济制裁，这是一家使加密货币交易更难追踪的公司，拜登政府曾指责该公司帮助朝鲜和其他网络黑客洗钱 70 多亿美元。【原文：The U.S. Treasury on Friday lifted economic sanctions against Tornado Cash, a firm that makes cryptocurrency transactions harder to track, which the Biden administration had accused of helping launder more than $7 billion for North Korean and other cyber hackers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-scraps-sanctions-tornado-cash-crypto-mixer-accused-laundering-north-korea-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYZB3FUI45NBHKLPXP2SC2P4VA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:15:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北达科他州石油监管机构预计今年油价将在特朗普关税不确定性的影响下走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[北达科他州石油监管机构负责人预测，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对邻国加拿大和墨西哥征收关税的不确定性影响下，今年的石油价格可能会下滑。【原文：Oil prices will likely slip this year, the director of North Dakota's state oil regulator predicted, amid uncertainty surrounding U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on neighboring Canada and Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/north-dakota-oil-regulator-expects-lower-oil-prices-this-year-amid-trump-tariff-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVHQD4UUKRKQDD7DUZDKRVN63E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 为部分工厂工人启动新一轮买断计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉普车制造商斯泰兰特正在为其工厂的部分工人提供新一轮的买断服务，因为该汽车制造商希望在 2024 年的困难时期之后削减成本。【原文：Jeep-maker Stellantis is offering a new round of buyouts for some of its factory workers as the automaker looks to cut costs following a difficult 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-initiates-new-round-buyouts-some-factory-workers-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24FBC5QPQFPN5FOASKZ44LOROA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:04:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SMBC 与更多保险公司就俄罗斯战机搁浅诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[SMBC Aviation Capital 公司发言人周五表示，该公司已就 2022 年西方制裁后滞留在俄罗斯的喷气式飞机对更多保险公司提起的爱尔兰诉讼达成和解。【原文：Aircraft lessor SMBC Aviation Capital has settled Irish lawsuits against more insurers over jets stranded in Russia following Western sanctions in 2022, a company spokesperson said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/smbc-settles-with-more-insurers-lawsuit-over-stranded-russian-jets-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCNKK3ZMRBIGDOUJP7JTTFRTG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:34:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普向波音公司授予了一份急需的战斗机合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五授予波音公司建造美国空军最先进战斗机（被称为 "下一代空中霸主"）的合同。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday awarded Boeing the contract to build the U.S. Air Force's most sophisticated fighter jet, known as Next Generation Air Dominance, two sources familiar with the situation said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trump-awards-boeing-much-needed-win-with-fighter-jet-contract-sources-say-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIOFMUDPSFJADFXM55QZ4BKQQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:11:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席沃勒尔称目前无需放慢资产负债表缩减速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）周五表示，他反对美国央行本周决定放慢减持证券的步伐，因为银行系统的储备水平依然充裕。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Christopher Waller on Friday said he opposed the U.S. central bank's decision this week to slow the pace of reduction of its securities holdings because the level of reserves in the banking system remains abundant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-waller-says-no-need-slow-balance-sheet-drawdown-this-time-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">523I7UFSCNOZ7FQESBLK2R4ULM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民调显示，大多数美国人支持特朗普推动重建美国造船业，以更好地与中国竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）推动重建美国造船业的努力得到了美国两党罕见的支持，周五公布的一项民意调查显示，72%的美国人认为美国不能继续依赖中国和其他外国生产商造船。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's push to rebuild U.S. shipbuilding is finding rare bipartisan support from Americans, with 72% saying the U.S. cannot remain dependent on China and other foreign producers to build ships, a poll released Friday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/most-americans-back-trump-push-rebuild-us-shipbuilding-better-compete-with-china-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">726ITFD5YVL2NOPXDAAQF6DODI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:49:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商美光股价暴跌，不温不火的利润率预期令人工智能前景黯然失色]]></title><description><![CDATA[美光公司的股价周五下跌了 8%，原因是其低迷的利润率预期使其强劲的季度收入前景黯然失色，而强劲的季度收入前景则是受其用于人工智能任务的半导体需求的推动。【原文：Micron's shares fell 8% on Friday, as its dour margin forecast took the shine off a robust quarterly revenue outlook driven by demand for its semiconductors used in artificial intelligence tasks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmaker-microns-shares-slump-tepid-margin-forecast-eclipses-ai-prospects-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STHIMOJDQZJ47EGJWFKTOQVXDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大韩航空即将敲定波音飞机订单，凸显美韩关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国工业部在访问美国以加强双边关系期间表示，大韩航空将很快敲定一项价值 327 亿美元的交易，购买波音新飞机和通用电气航空发动机。【原文：Korean Air will soon finalise a $32.7 billion deal for new Boeing aircraft and GE Aerospace engines, South Korea's industry ministry said during a visit to the United States to strengthen bilateral relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/korean-air-finalise-boeing-plane-order-soon-highlighting-us-skorea-ties-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UH5M4TE5KJJ5TPVTWIBHBUU2N4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:33:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BuildOps 在本轮融资中估值 10 亿美元，计划在强劲需求下扩大运营规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[BuildOps 周五表示，它已在一轮后期融资中筹集了 1.27 亿美元，估值达 10 亿美元，因为它希望扩大运营规模，满足承包商对其人工智能软件平台日益增长的需求。【原文：BuildOps said on Friday it has raised $127 million in a late-stage funding round at a valuation of $1 billion, as it looks to scale operations and meet growing demand from contractors for its AI-enabled software platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/buildops-valued-1-billion-funding-round-plans-scale-operations-amid-strong-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWCVKHC2AVOQXGIS7NHPCMKELQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:06:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官称，Tether 正与 "四大 "事务所商谈储备审计事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大稳定币的创造者 Tether 正在 "与一家四大会计师事务所接洽"，以推动对其储备进行期待已久的审计，该公司首席执行官保罗-阿尔多诺（Paolo Ardoino）表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的领导下，这项工作将变得更加容易。【原文：Tether, the creator of the world's largest stablecoin, is "engaging with a Big Four accounting firm" as it pushes for a long-awaited audit of its reserves, an effort CEO Paolo Ardoino said will be easier under U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tether-is-talks-with-big-four-firm-about-reserve-audit-ceo-says-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVW7LGL3MFLLTNWZ4VWP3DNMJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特勤局就下一代装甲 SUV 与通用汽车高管会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国特勤局周五表示，美国特勤局负责人本周在密歇根州与通用汽车公司高管会面，讨论下一代装甲 SUV，因为该汽车制造商正在开发即将推出的总统豪华轿车版本。【原文：The head of the U.S. Secret Service met with General Motors executives this week in Michigan to discuss next-generation armored SUVs as the automaker works on the upcoming version of the presidential limousine, the agency said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/secret-service-meets-with-gm-execs-next-generation-armored-suvs-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASFQIZDSMFJSJGTIYKBNRUZCC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:59:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国天然气价格上涨 1%，原因是液化天然气出口量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于液化天然气（LNG）出口厂的天然气流量创下新高，美国天然气期货周五微涨约1%。【原文：U.S. natural gas futures edged up about 1% on Friday on record flows to liquefied natural gas (LNG) export plants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-natgas-prices-edge-up-1-record-flows-lng-export-plants-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2O3ZJSNBQ5KSHH5MNXVN3N4M4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美团加入中国人工智能支出竞赛，称将投资 "数十亿 "芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最大的餐饮外卖公司美团首席执行官王兴周五在财报后的电话会议上表示，公司正在向用于训练人工智能模型的芯片投入 "数十亿美元"，并计划在今年进行更多投资。【原文：Wang Xing, CEO of China's largest food delivery firm Meituan , said on Friday in a post-earnings call that the company is pouring "billions" into chips used to train AI models, with more investment planned this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/meituan-joins-chinas-ai-spending-race-says-investing-billions-chips-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK3DOD6BPZJPZPYLV4P4DICKOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫官员称，特朗普会晤后，阿联酋承诺在美国实施为期 10 年、价值 1.4 万亿美元的投资框架]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员周五表示，在阿联酋高级官员本周与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普会面后，阿联酋已承诺在美国建立一个为期 10 年、总值 1.4 万亿美元的投资框架。【原文：The United Arab Emirates has committed to a 10-year, $1.4 trillion investment framework in the United States after top UAE officials met President Donald Trump this week, a White House official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/after-trump-meeting-uae-commits-10-year-14-trillion-investment-framework-us-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTM5P5I2IFJ4PI2MRYEOO5JLRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:49:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邮轮需求强劲，嘉年华上调年度盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，邮轮运营商嘉年华公司（Carnival Corp）上调了年度利润预期，主要受益于较高的票价、有弹性的提前预订以及强劲的船上消费。【原文：Cruise operator Carnival Corp raised its annual profit forecast on Friday, benefiting from higher ticket prices, resilient advance bookings and strong on-board customer spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carnival-corp-raises-annual-profit-forecast-strong-demand-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCVOP373KFI7VM4K2FGVPMY4XY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，受美国支出困境影响，2026 财年印度 IT 盈利可能出现停滞]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃森哲公司（Accenture）在其季度报告中指出，印度信息技术公司是今年表现最差的行业之一，在 2026 财年可能不会出现复苏。【原文：India's information technology companies, among the worst-performing sectors this year, may not see a recovery in fiscal 2026, analysts said, after Accenture flagged weak discretionary spending and demand in its quarterly report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indian-it-earnings-likely-stutter-fiscal-2026-us-spending-woes-analysts-say-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCMG2EI3SNPH5DAUBZKDOKDQKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:12:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储威廉姆斯称货币政策在显著的不确定性中处于正确位置]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，鉴于经济在前景相当不确定的环境中的表现，美国央行的货币政策目前正处于正确的位置。【原文：New York Federal Reserve President John Williams said on Friday the U.S. central bank's monetary policy is in the right place at this time, given how the economy is performing in an environment where the outlook is quite uncertain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-williams-says-monetary-policy-right-place-amid-notable-uncertainty-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZGIC6WQR5J2PKYGLCLS3MBKFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：摩根大通资产管理部门退出行业气候联盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通公司（JPMorgan Chase & Co）表示，其资产管理部门已经退出了一项旗舰行业气候行动，这对该集团来说是一个打击，该集团曾在 1 月份暂停运营，以阻止叛逃。【原文：JPMorgan Chase & Co said its asset management unit has left a flagship industry climate effort, a blow to the group that had paused operations in January in an effort to halt defections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/jpmorgan-asset-management-unit-quits-industry-climate-coalition-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTHMLPVVSVI5LKWUSD4WEUH7WM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:56:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Stellantis 和 Leapmotor 均倾向于在西班牙生产 B10 电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位直接了解此事的人士说，Stellantis 及其中国合作伙伴 Leapmotor 认为，西班牙是从 2026 年起为欧洲市场生产 B10 电动跨界车的最佳候选国。【原文：Stellantis and its Chinese partner Leapmotor consider Spain the top candidate to produce the B10 electric crossover for the European market from 2026, a person with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-leapmotor-favour-spain-production-b10-ev-source-says-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS44B2H6SJOVVI3XSP5YNUCBEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:46:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金流动 高盛称对华尔街的悲观情绪创 5 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据高盛周四发给客户的一份说明，对冲基金在 3 月份增加的看跌头寸多于看涨头寸，超过了 2020 年以来的任何时候，加倍押注美股还将进一步下跌。【原文：Hedge funds added more bearish positions than bullish ones in March than at any time since 2020, doubling down on bets that U.S. stocks have further to fall, according to a Goldman Sachs note sent to clients on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/hedge-flow-hedge-fund-pessimism-over-wall-street-hits-5-year-high-goldman-says-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULBGDRCIGBI4RKBN6NAGGEOJ2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税担忧影响，美国股票基金周流出量飙升至三个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至3月19日的一周内，美国股票基金出现了三个月来最大的净流出，原因是担心美国关税政策的影响，以及在美联储作出货币政策决定之前持谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw the largest net outflows in three months in the week through March 19 on worries about the impact of U.S. tariff policies and caution ahead of a monetary policy decision from the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-weekly-outflows-surge-three-month-high-tariff-concerns-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEBC6VXVE5LIXCH7SE7GRK3IXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《Ary News》报道，马斯克的 "星链 "公司获得了在巴基斯坦发射服务的许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地广播公司 Ary News 周五援引消息人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 "星链"（Starlink）公司已获得在巴基斯坦发射服务的无异议证书。【原文：Elon Musk's Starlink has obtained a no-objection certificate to launch services in Pakistan, local broadcaster Ary News reported on Friday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/musks-starlink-gets-noc-launch-services-pakistan-ary-news-reports-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRMSH2AOVRKUND4WHIFJHYWSUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通对其多元化项目进行改革，备忘录称]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，摩根大通首席运营官 Jenn Piepszak 表示，该行正在对其 "多元化、公平和包容 "计划以及描述这些计划的语言进行一些调整，以跟上市场和法规的变化。【原文：JPMorgan Chase Chief Operating Officer Jenn Piepszak said the bank was making some changes to its Diversity, Equity and Inclusion programs and the language it uses to describe them in an effort to keep up with the market and changes in regulations, according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-makes-changes-its-diversity-programs-memo-says-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKBHD7PLMVPNBDSOCPH5DXMNZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟国家集团寻求加快芯片产业发展步伐]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟联盟的一位领导人周五表示，九个欧盟国家正在努力加快推动该集团计算机芯片产业发展的计划，并计划在今年夏天之前提出他们的建议。【原文：Nine European Union countries are working to speed up plans to boost the bloc's computer chip industry and aim to present their proposals by the summer, one of the coalition's leaders said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/group-eu-states-seeks-faster-progress-chips-industry-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RQYM54QLPZOU3ETOZBUN3Y45TY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 11:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>