<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:19:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:19:54 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[How AI boom is pressuring videogame console industry in race for memory chips]]></title><description><![CDATA[Videogame console sales were already under pressure owing to tariff turmoil and weak consumer spending. Now a surge in the prices of memory chips is threatening to make the devices costlier in what could be another blow to the industry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-ai-boom-is-pressuring-videogame-console-industry-race-memory-chips-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HO2O5TBNGNONHLY5J7SKAW5ITU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mexico antitrust commission to revise Volaris-Viva Aerobus tie-up]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexico's antitrust commission will revise a planned tie-up between low-cost airlines Viva Aerobus and Volaris , the country's President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Monday, adding she considered the deal good news for Mexico's airline sector.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mexico-antitrust-commission-revise-volaris-viva-aerobus-tie-up-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KBPBYZD3XZJO3BWJYGI5WHRQWE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:04:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daiwa to raise M&A revenue target to 100 billion yen by 2031, CEO says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's Daiwa Securities is aiming to generate 100 billion yen ($635.61 million) in M&amp;A-related revenue by the financial year ended March 2031, its CEO said, as Japan undergoes a dealmaking boom that neared record levels in 2025.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/daiwa-raise-ma-revenue-target-100-billion-yen-by-2031-ceo-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHD4BNJFLJMFXCNX4ENTZPHCIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Union Pacific, Norfolk Southern merger faces pushback from signalmen's union]]></title><description><![CDATA[A rail workers' union on Monday opposed Union Pacific's proposed $85 billion acquisition of Norfolk Southern , warning that the deal could undermine safety and impact the workforce.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/union-pacific-norfolk-southern-merger-faces-pushback-signalmens-union-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AWBGZZ7HBNCLFYHSADP3DL2EM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China confirms talks between Wingtech, Nexperia BV, urges further negotiations]]></title><description><![CDATA[China on Monday confirmed that Wingtech and Nexperia B.V. had held the first round of talks last week, with both sides agreeing to maintain communications, according to a statement released by China's commerce ministry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-confirms-talks-between-wingtech-nexperia-bv-urges-further-negotiations-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRQCVJQWYRLA7MGNIL3NJYPWYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instacart ends AI-driven price experiments after criticism]]></title><description><![CDATA[Instacart is ending price tests that resulted in different shoppers being shown different prices for groceries, the online retail platform said on Monday after criticism of its artificial intelligence-driven pricing tool.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/instacart-ends-ai-driven-price-experiments-after-criticism-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5SDBGDM5FPC7MTMRFHFDSUKWA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trian, General Catalyst to buy Janus Henderson for $7.4 billion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nelson Peltz's Trian and VC firm General Catalyst have agreed to buy asset manager Janus Henderson for $7.4 billion, the companies said on Monday, bringing to close a more than five-year activist campaign by the billionaire's hedge fund.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/trian-general-catalyst-buy-janus-henderson-74-billion-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LKROVXG6RLPDOW5N2PATAP4TE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed's Miran says he'll likely stay after term ends until his seat is filled - Bloomberg]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran on Monday said he is likely to remain on the central bank's Board of Governors beyond the expiration of his term until whoever President Donald Trump nominates as the next Fed chair is confirmed by the Senate.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-miran-says-hell-likely-stay-after-term-ends-until-his-seat-is-filled-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGIP2N76YJK2NOF45XLFM5IEPU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:11:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JPMorgan exploring crypto trading for institutional clients, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase is considering offering cryptocurrency trading to its institutional clients, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing a person familiar with the plans.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-exploring-crypto-trading-institutional-clients-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45SHY6YIT5NWLDWC6VJF72UKCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[European investment banks fail to capitalise on Trump Tariff turmoil]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wall Street banks strengthened their lead in European investment banking in 2025, as clients stayed loyal despite global market turmoil and President Donald Trump's trade tariffs.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/european-investment-banks-fail-capitalise-trump-tariff-turmoil-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4MRPZK2TFKXPAKAUDF3KLP7VA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:41:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CACI 公司斥资 26 亿美元收购 ARKA 公司，扩大航天和国防领域的业务范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防承包商 CACI International 将以 26 亿美元的价格从 Blackstone Tactical Opportunities 管理的基金手中收购空间技术提供商 ARKA Group，从而扩大其在国家安全和天基情报领域的业务范围。【原文：U.S. defense contractor CACI International will acquire space technology provider ARKA Group from funds managed by Blackstone Tactical Opportunities for $2.6 billion, expanding its footprint in national security and space-based intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/caci-expands-space-defense-footprint-with-26-billion-arka-buy-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIJUVFUPDJNMJIN32KVXGG3DYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:16:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉里-埃里森为派拉蒙竞购华纳兄弟提供 404 亿美元担保]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一份文件显示，甲骨文公司联合创始人拉里-埃里森（Larry Ellison）已同意为派拉蒙天舞公司收购华纳兄弟发现公司的股权融资提供 404 亿美元的个人担保。【原文：Oracle co-founder Larry Ellison has agreed to provide a personal guarantee of $40.4 billion of the equity financing for Paramount Skydance's offer to acquire Warner Bros Discovery , a filing showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/larry-ellison-gives-404-billion-guarantee-paramount-bid-warner-bros-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCDJNTCIENMIHKYGHCMERAPS4A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道英伟达计划二月中旬开始向中国出货 H200 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，英伟达（Nvidia）已经告诉中国客户，它的目标是在二月中旬农历新年假期前开始向中国运送其功能第二强大的人工智能芯片。【原文：Nvidia has told Chinese clients it aims to start shipping its second-most powerful AI chips to China before the Lunar New Year holiday in mid-February, three people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-aims-begin-h200-chip-shipments-china-by-mid-february-sources-say-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTGFCQ263BJGTNBSC47CTCN6WA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:21:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）储备数据显示第三季度趋于稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）的数据显示，2025 年第三季度，美元在向该组织报告的全球货币储备中所占的份额走低至 56.92%，而以欧元计价的储备所占的份额则悄然上升。【原文：The U.S. dollar's share of global currency reserves reported to the International Monetary Fund edged lower to 56.92% in the third quarter of 2025, while the share of euro-denominated reserves crept higher, International Monetary Fund data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/imf-reserve-data-shows-stabilisation-third-quarter-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCGDZUWMVNPIHDK6QLVU3AUGJQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔预计将从 Flexjet 和解协议中支出 4.7 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔周一表示，预计第四季度将因与 Flexjet 有关的诉讼可能达成和解而一次性支出约 4.7 亿美元，导致其股价在盘前交易中下跌 1.3%。【原文：Honeywell on Monday said it expects to record a one-time charge of about $470 million in the fourth quarter related to a potential settlement of Flexjet-linked litigation, sending its shares down 1.3% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/honeywell-expects-470-million-charge-flexjet-settlement-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKPFN66EIVKADOWQ2DNFIFN5GE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:55:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 为与华纳兄弟 Discovery 交易相关的 590 亿美元过桥贷款进行部分再融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周一提交的一份监管文件显示，Netflix 已对 590 亿美元过桥贷款中的一部分进行了再融资，该贷款是为支持其可能收购华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）而安排的。【原文：Netflix has refinanced part of a $59 billion bridge loan arranged to support its potential acquisition of Warner Bros Discovery , according to a regulatory filing on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/netflix-refinances-part-59-billion-bridge-loan-tied-warner-bros-discovery-deal-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EV4AYC7CFNLTPXPHPYTSJYLZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货在交易周缩短前上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货以积极的态势拉开了假期缩短周的序幕，科技股因人们对人工智能的热情再度高涨而进一步上扬，而投资者则在等待本周晚些时候的关键经济数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures kicked off the holiday-shortened week on a positive note, as technology stocks rose further on renewed enthusiasm over artificial intelligence, while investors awaited key economic data later this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-rise-ahead-shortened-trading-week-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWOKDWIWE5KPFAV44AFB43A3WM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coty新任临时首席执行官是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[科蒂公司周一任命宝洁公司资深人士马库斯-斯特罗贝尔（Markus Strobel）为临时首席执行官，接替苏-纳比（Sue Nabi），CoverGirl 的母公司成为今年一连串零售商和消费品公司更新 C-suites 的最新案例。【原文：Coty on Monday named Procter & Gamble veteran Markus Strobel interim CEO, replacing Sue Nabi, as the CoverGirl parent became the latest in a string of retailers and consumer goods companies refreshing their C-suites this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/who-is-cotys-new-interim-ceo-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHSIHZBCRJMMBIR2AIDQN6DFOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:22:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金做空医疗服务提供商，补贴争论愈演愈烈]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）周五在一份报告中称，由于补贴即将到期，立法者们急于抑制成本，对冲基金上周卖出的美国医疗保健类股票数量14周以来首次超过了买入的数量。【原文：Hedge funds last week sold more U.S. healthcare stocks than they bought for the first time in 14 weeks, Goldman Sachs said in a note on Friday, as expiring subsidies leave lawmakers scrambling to curb costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-short-healthcare-providers-subsidies-debate-intensifies-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4N55F4F6FPMDJVC2R3GV6PXE4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026 年是美元的悲惨一年，隧道尽头的曙光渺茫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元惨淡的一年即将结束，出现了企稳迹象，但许多投资者认为，随着全球经济增长回升和美联储进一步放宽政策，美元明年将重现跌势。【原文：A dismal year for the U.S. dollar is ending with signs of stabilization, but many investors believe the currency's decline will resume next year as global growth picks up and the Fed eases further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dire-year-dollar-has-little-light-end-tunnel-2026-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JC3AU6QHWJN5TNACD7GAAVJYDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:03:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步和 Lyft 明年起在英国测试百度机器人出租车]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步科技公司（Uber Technologies）和Lyft将与中国科技巨头百度合作，明年在英国试运行无人驾驶出租车，这标志着全球机器人出租车商业化竞赛迈出了重要一步。【原文：Uber Technologies and Lyft are teaming up with Chinese tech giant Baidu to try out driverless taxis in the UK next year, marking a major step in the global race to commercialize robotaxis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-lyft-test-baidu-robotaxis-uk-next-year-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6J5GMDPKNJC3GRWV4BJRFATNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宏达电押注开放式人工智能战略以推动智能眼镜销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾宏达电（HTC）公司的高管表示，该公司新推出的人工智能眼镜可以让佩戴者选择他们想要使用的人工智能模型，因此该公司打赌其开放平台战略将使其能够在快速增长的智能眼镜行业建立市场份额。【原文：Taiwan’s HTC is betting its open platform strategy will allow it to build market share in the fast-growing smartglasses industry, as its newly launched AI-powered eyewear lets wearers choose which AI model they want to use, its executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/htc-bets-its-open-ai-strategy-drive-smartglasses-sales-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZSGP4XC6NMFHJHVY4DAVEHMWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 08:35:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前央行政策制定者：上田领导下的日本央行将把利率上调至 1.5%]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行前董事会成员樱井诚（Makoto Sakurai）周一告诉路透社，日本央行可能会在行长上田一夫至2028年初的剩余任期内再加息三次至1.5%。【原文：The Bank of Japan will likely raise interest rates three more times to 1.5% during Governor Kazuo Ueda's remaining term through early 2028, former central bank board member Makoto Sakurai told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-raise-interest-rates-15-under-ueda-ex-cbank-policymaker-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VWTKDY3GFLKXLTTOM3PWHUDPU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 08:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利反垄断机构因苹果公司涉嫌滥用 App Store 市场支配地位对其处以罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利竞争管理机构周一表示，已对美国科技巨头苹果公司及其两家子公司处以 9860 万欧元（1.1553 亿美元）的罚款，原因是它们涉嫌滥用在 iOS 用户移动应用程序分销方面的支配地位。【原文：Italy's competition authority said on Monday it had fined U.S tech giant Apple and two of its units 98.6 million euros ($115.53 million) over alleged abuse of dominant position for the distribution of mobile applications for iOS users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/italys-antitrust-fines-apple-alleged-abuse-dominant-position-with-app-store-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75NNZ5DL4JNA7JU66T2IGLREOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 07:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coty任命Markus Strobel自1月起担任临时首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国化妆品制造商科蒂公司（Coty）周一表示，已任命马库斯-施特罗贝尔（Markus Strobel）为临时首席执行官，自 1 月 1 日起生效。【原文：U.S. cosmetics maker Coty appointed Markus Strobel as its interim chief executive officer effective January 1, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/coty-appoints-markus-strobel-interim-ceo-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPCVHI2ZTVKKVDZCKYH2VJV36A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 07:23:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国商务部副部长周五会见苹果公司首席运营官]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周一发表声明称，中国商务部副部长李成钢和苹果公司首席运营官萨比汗在周五的一次会议上讨论了美国公司在中国的业务运营问题。【原文：China's Vice Commerce Minister Li Chenggang and Apple's Chief Operating Officer Sabih Khan discussed the U.S. firm's business operations in China in a meeting on Friday, a commerce ministry statement said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-vice-commerce-minister-met-apple-coo-friday-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EL3KSSFQUZMZTMFIYHO5LOGLUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 06:48:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，德国汽车出口受特朗普关税影响严重]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周一看到的一份研究报告显示，2025 年前三季度，德国对美国的汽车出口下滑了近 14%，成为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普贸易战中受冲击最严重的德国工业部门。【原文：German car exports to the United States slumped by almost 14% in the first three quarters of 2025, making it the hardest-hit branch of German industry in U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war, according to a study seen by Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/german-auto-exports-hit-hard-by-trump-tariffs-study-shows-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NSG26IYRVJQLHZPWCO2PGU7XM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 06:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在炮火中送达：新星邮政如何成为乌克兰战时的成功典范]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯入侵近四年来，新星邮政学会了如何在停电、导弹袭击和交通中断的情况下开展业务。现在，它每天投递的包裹超过 150 万个，巩固了其作为战时罕见的成功企业的地位。【原文：Nearly four years into Russia's invasion, Nova Post has learned to operate through blackouts, missile strikes and broken transport links. It now delivers more than 1.5 million parcels a day, cementing its status as a rare wartime corporate success.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/delivering-under-fire-how-nova-post-became-ukraines-wartime-success-story-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUSH5XXDPFIY5OF577RFHGMLJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 06:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普震撼了今年的全球贸易；2026 年可能仍存在一些不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025 年，唐纳德-特朗普总统重返白宫，拉开了全球贸易狂热之年的序幕，对美国贸易伙伴征收关税的浪潮将进口税提高到了大萧条以来的最高水平，震荡了金融市场，并引发了一轮又一轮的贸易和投资协议谈判。【原文：President Donald Trump's return to the White House in 2025 kicked off a frenetic year for global trade, with waves of tariffs on U.S. trading partners that lifted import taxes to their highest since the Great Depression, roiled financial markets and sparked rounds of negotiations over trade and investment deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-shook-up-global-trade-this-year-some-uncertainty-may-persist-2026-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGFPSIES3RM4BIRI6C5XSHEWFY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 06:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本关注 7 万亿美元家庭储蓄带来的新债券需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本希望利用该国 7 万亿美元的家庭储蓄来支持债券需求，计划推出新产品和激励措施，在近期零售销售火爆的基础上再接再厉，填补央行购买减少留下的空白。【原文：Japan is looking to the country's $7 trillion household savings hoard to support bond demand with plans to launch new products and incentives, building on hot recent retail sales and filling a void left by diminished central bank buying.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japan-eyes-7-trillion-household-savings-pile-fresh-bond-demand-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2W6CN5KGJRLNVNWTJYJIEMH3PE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>