<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:07:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:07:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[行业数据显示，特斯拉第二季度在加州的电动汽车注册量下降了 21]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业数据显示，特斯拉第二季度在加利福尼亚州的电动汽车注册量下降了 21.1%，这表明埃隆-马斯克领导的汽车制造商在美国这一重要市场面临的挑战日益严峻。【原文：Tesla's electric vehicle registrations in California fell 21.1% in the second quarter, according to industry data, indicating growing challenges for the Elon Musk-led automaker in the crucial U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-second-quarter-ev-registrations-california-fell-21-industry-data-shows-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNGWQ3DULZJUHCSNLV47LA3DCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称菲律宾将支付 19% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，在与美国达成贸易协议后，菲律宾将支付 19% 的关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that the Philippines will pay a 19% tariff rate following the conclusion of a trade deal with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/philippines-pay-19-tariff-trump-says-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7IMNDCQ2JLRXGFLURSYK4HVTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国考虑取消房屋销售资本利得税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，他的政府正在考虑取消房屋销售资本利得税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday his administration is considering removing taxes on capital gains on home sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-considering-removing-tax-capital-gains-home-sales-trump-says-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSL6S5O3DZPH7N2YZU47KBHXDI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:35:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司 CPS Energy 和 Modern Hydrogen 同意合作开展清洁发电项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于得克萨斯州的公用事业公司 CPS Energy 周二表示，该公司与能源公司 Modern Hydrogen 就一个新项目达成了协议，以探索提高电网弹性和利用天然气进行清洁发电的潜力。【原文：Texas-based utility firm CPS Energy on Tuesday said it entered into an agreement with energy company Modern Hydrogen on a new project to explore the potential for increasing electricity grid resiliency and enabling cleaner power generation from natural gas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-companies-cps-energy-modern-hydrogen-agree-work-clean-power-generation-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTJXFTRBERJ2NPR2PNTHTK2ETU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公共电台（NPR）高级编辑伊迪丝-查平（Edith Chapin）将卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公共广播电台（NPR）新闻机构周二表示，伊迪丝-查平（Edith Chapin）将于今年晚些时候辞去总编辑和代理首席内容官的职务。【原文：National Public Radio's (NPR) Edith Chapin will step down from her role as editor in chief and acting chief content officer later this year, the news outlet said on Tuesday, at a time when the broadcaster faces funding pressure after the Trump administration slashed public media subsidies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nprs-top-editor-edith-chapin-step-down-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5EWSUMUQJJK5NMEIARFFEYUPE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Soitec 第一季度销售额符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国半导体材料供应商索泰克（Soitec）报告称，由于客户库存高企和汽车市场疲软，按固定汇率计算，其第一季度销售额下降了 16%。【原文：French semiconductor materials supplier Soitec reported a 16% drop at constant exchange rates in its first-quarter sales, due to high customer inventory and a weak automotive market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/soitec-posts-q1-sales-line-with-expectations-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPE6QTHQDRKL5N5JLHXEFRYYSQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:11:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，马斯克的 xAI 正在努力筹集高达 120 亿美元的资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周二援引熟悉情况的人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克的人工智能初创公司xAI正在与一家金融公司合作，为其扩张计划再融资120亿美元。【原文：Elon Musk's artificial intelligence startup xAI is working with a financier to secure up to $12 billion more for its expansion plans, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-xai-working-raise-up-12-billion-wsj-reports-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJ3EEXVDCFKMHH36QVEEZ6AENE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:25:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称埃克森公司正与特立尼达谈判七个深水区块]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位接近谈判的消息人士告诉路透社，埃克森美孚公司已开始与特立尼达和多巴哥政府谈判，在这个加勒比海国家东海岸的最多七个深水区块勘探石油和天然气。【原文：Exxon Mobil has begun negotiations with the Trinidad and Tobago government to explore for oil and gas in up to seven deepwater blocks off the East Coast of the Caribbean country, which the top U.S. oil producer left more than two decades ago, two sources close to the talks told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-talks-with-trinidad-seven-deepwater-blocks-sources-say-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CII6YMGFJJPRJK3SXARWZANEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[好时、雀巢和其他可可公司驳回奴役儿童诉讼上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，联邦上诉法院驳回了八名马里公民提出的集体诉讼，他们要求好时、雀巢和其他五家公司为象牙海岸可可农场的童工问题承担责任。【原文：A federal appeals court on Tuesday rejected a proposed class action by eight Malian citizens who sought to hold Hershey , Nestle and five other companies liable for child labor on Ivory Coast cocoa farms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hershey-nestle-other-cocoa-companies-defeat-appeal-child-slavery-lawsuit-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSRDHHGYQZJP3ISO364CCMNMCU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美墨航空争端有望在未来几天内解决]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥航空公司沃拉瑞斯（Volaris）首席执行官周二表示，该公司相信美国和墨西哥之间的航空争端可能在未来几天内得到解决。【原文：Mexican airline Volaris believes a resolution to a dispute between the U.S. and Mexico on aviation could arrive in the coming days, the carrier's CEO said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/solution-us-mexico-aviation-dispute-seen-coming-days-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLL3NW4KORNDFGZTKWQKTALV2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[育碧推出 "创意屋 "模式，第一季度预订额不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国领先的电子游戏生产商育碧公司周二宣布对其内部结构进行全面重组，转而成立针对特定游戏类型的自主 "创意中心"，该公司公布的第一季度净预订额低于预期。【原文：France's lead videogame maker Ubisoft announced on Tuesday a sweeping reorganisation of its internal structure, shifting to autonomous "Creative Houses" tailored to specific gaming genres, as it reported first-quarter net bookings that fell short of expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubisoft-unveils-creative-houses-model-first-quarter-bookings-miss-expectations-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z2WVR6NISNNXJG3WYPBF2BM4EI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:07:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[去风险情绪增加了对美国企业债券的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国股指接近历史新高，投资者开始降低股票投资组合的风险，购买更多的投资级公司债券，进而推动企业借贷成本在八个月内第二次达到 1998 年以来最紧张的水平。【原文：Investors have begun to de-risk their equity portfolios and buy more investment-grade corporate bonds as U.S. stock indices near new record highs, in turn pushing corporate borrowing costs to their tightest levels since 1998 for the second time in eight months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/de-risking-mood-adds-more-demand-us-corporate-bonds-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNOBHPXDU5PWHIX4OWIB7CGCAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储鲍威尔将很快下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在周二的新闻发布会上表示，美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔将利率维持在过高水平，并将在八个月后卸任。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell kept rates too high and will be out in eight months, President Donald Trump said at a news conference on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-feds-powell-will-be-out-soon-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ESTZ3CPJZFNSLN2ZPD7IUCTDUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耗资 75 亿美元的美国基础设施项目建成的电动汽车充电桩不足 400 个]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府问责局（Government Accountability Office）周二表示，截至 4 月份，美国各州在 75 亿美元的联邦基础设施项目下建造的电动汽车充电桩还不到 400 个。【原文：U.S. states have built less than 400 electric vehicle charging ports through April under $7.5 billion federal infrastructure programs, the Government Accountability Office said Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/less-than-400-ev-charging-ports-built-under-75-billion-us-infrastructure-program-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGDNW5KEJNM47EUW5JCSX4NWW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《西雅图时报》报道，波音公司开始生产 777-8 型货机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《西雅图时报》周二报道，波音公司已开始生产其最新型货运飞机 777-8。【原文：Boeing has kicked off production of its newest freight carrier, the 777-8, the Seattle Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-kicks-off-production-777-8-freighter-seattle-times-reports-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVMDVMTXVFOG5PSQJSBRBUHVNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，苹果将避免每日罚款，欧盟将接受应用程序商店的变更]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的人士称，苹果公司对其应用程序商店规则和收费的修改很可能会获得欧盟反垄断监管机构的绿灯，此举将避免这家 iPhone 制造商可能面临的每日巨额罚款。【原文：Apple's changes to its App Store rules and fees will likely secure the green light from EU antitrust regulators, people with direct knowledge of the matter said, a move that would stave off potentially hefty daily fines for the iPhone maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apple-set-stave-off-daily-fines-eu-accept-app-store-changes-sources-say-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJOSBTOOXJKG5FQFWWZMQDZSAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:39:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈里伯顿称墨西哥石油产出下降率将给业务重启带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国油田服务供应商哈里伯顿公司周二表示，墨西哥原油产量的下降给重新启动业务带来了压力，因为国营的墨西哥石油公司（Pemex）长期拖延向其供应商付款。【原文：U.S. oilfield service provider Halliburton on Tuesday said Mexico's crude production decline rates are creating pressure for a reactivation of business amid long delays from state-run Pemex to pay its suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/halliburton-says-mexico-oil-output-decline-rates-will-pressure-reactivation-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VHODUBXYFLOBGVOHMDZJUEJTE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称，PCAOB的长期官员将领导审计监督机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）已任命一位长期任职于上市公司会计监督委员会（Public Company Accounting Oversight Board）的官员领导该审计监督机构，此前该机构的负责人已于上周赶走了其民主党负责人。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has tapped a longtime official of the Public Company Accounting Oversight Board to lead the audit watchdog, after the agency's head pushed out its Democratic chief last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/longtime-pcaob-official-lead-audit-watchdog-us-sec-says-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMH6FZAFOJOADHKS7EQKTU7LJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:09:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国汽车零部件制造商博世将裁员1,100人]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车零部件制造商博世公司一位高级官员周二表示，由于汽车市场急剧恶化导致销售下滑，博世将在2029年前裁员1100人，并重组其罗伊特林根工厂。【原文：German car parts maker Bosch will cut up to 1,100 jobs by 2029 and restructure its Reutlingen plant as a rapidly worsening auto market drives down sales, a senior company official said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/german-car-parts-maker-bosch-cut-up-1100-jobs-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQAHCHEJVVJLDKRKYGYMKOFTWU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，白宫将公布将美国人工智能推向海外的计划，打击美国的人工智能规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份文件显示，白宫周三打算公布一项计划，要求向国外出口美国的人工智能技术，并打击被认为对美国人工智能发展限制过多的州法律。【原文：The White House on Wednesday intends to publish a plan that calls for the export of American AI technology abroad and a crackdown on state laws deemed too restrictive to let American AI flourish, a document seen by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/white-house-unveil-plan-push-us-ai-abroad-crackdown-us-ai-rules-document-shows-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQ3UCAMSFBP4ZAMVR5TD5YJ7P4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软知道 SharePoint 服务器存在漏洞，但未能有效修补]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软上个月发布的一个安全补丁未能完全修复美国科技巨头 SharePoint 服务器软件中的一个关键漏洞，而该漏洞早在 5 月份就已被发现，这为一场席卷全球的网络间谍行动打开了方便之门。【原文：A security patch released by Microsoft last month failed to fully fix a critical flaw in U.S. tech giant's SharePoint server software that had been identified in May, opening the door to a sweeping global cyber espionage operation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-knew-sharepoint-server-exploit-failed-effectively-patch-it-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F56C3J5L4ZJ4BIMLUKNMVHNWYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:20:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟监管机构警告称，环球公司 7.75 亿美元的市中心交易可能会阻碍竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构周二警告说，环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）旗下维珍音乐集团（Virgin Music Group）斥资 7.75 亿美元收购下城音乐公司（Downtown Music）可能会阻碍竞争，并使一个重要的竞争对手消失。【原文：Universal Music Group unit Virgin Music Group's $775 million acquisition of Downtown Music may hinder competition and remove an important competitor, EU antitrust regulators warned on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/universals-775-million-downtown-deal-may-hinder-competition-eu-regulators-warn-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPQDIQOLLBIFTIRV4HJPWHT75A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[散户投资者扎堆，科尔股价翻番]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国连锁百货公司科尔（Kohl's）的股价大涨超过 100%，成为零售交易平台上交易量最大的股票之一。【原文：Shares of U.S. department store chain Kohl's jumped more than 100% on Tuesday, making it one of the most traded stocks on retail trading platforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kohls-shares-double-retail-investors-pile-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2J7TIM3UWVNF7D57SYLJFYTZBM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广告公司 Interpublic 季度业绩超出预期，原因是客户支出恢复性增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，广告集团 Interpublic 的第二季度收入和利润超过了分析师的预期，这主要得益于客户营销支出的恢复性增长，使其股价在收盘前上涨了 3%。【原文：Ad group Interpublic surpassed analysts' estimates for second-quarter revenue and profit on Tuesday, thanks to resilient marketing spend from clients, sending its shares up 3% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ad-firm-interpublic-beats-quarterly-estimates-resilient-client-spending-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3HT5EMVEZLFPNM6MJRY3DC2AY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:22:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国负责人敦促科技界利用可再生能源为数据中心供电]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国秘书长安东尼奥-古特雷斯（António Guterres）周二呼吁科技公司到2030年在数据中心的建设中100%使用可再生能源，即使该行业转向天然气和燃煤电厂以满足激增的需求。【原文：U.N. Secretary General António Guterres on Tuesday called on tech companies to power the build out of data centers with 100% renewable energy by 2030, even as the industry turns to gas and coal-fired power plants to meet surging demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/un-chief-urges-tech-sector-power-data-centers-with-renewables-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG4GY4HKHJIRRH6PANS55IF3DU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织警告关税不是解决全球失衡的办法]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周二表示，全球经常账户余额在2024年急剧扩大，扭转了自2008-2009年全球金融危机以来的收窄趋势，并警告说关税不是解决问题的办法。【原文：Global current account balances widened sharply in 2024, reversing a narrowing under way since the global financial crisis of 2008-2009, the International Monetary Fund said on Tuesday, warning that tariffs were not the answer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imf-warns-tariffs-arent-answer-global-imbalances-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDEO2GAOIJIUHE6XPAOBUCOI44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲第二季度企业利润预计下降 0.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，最新的盈利预测显示，尽管全球贸易仍存在不确定性，欧盟也在准备对美国的任何重大关税采取反制措施，但欧洲企业的健康前景略有改善。【原文：The outlook for European corporate health has slightly improved, the latest earnings forecasts showed on Tuesday, despite continued uncertainty over global trade and the European Union preparing for counter-measures against any major U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-second-quarter-corporate-profits-expected-fall-03-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K3KVWEIPPBIDNMN3Y5J5AXQZ3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 将于今年在南非首次推出 Leapmotor 电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 公司周二表示，计划从 9 月份开始在南非销售由其合作伙伴 Leapmotor 开发的中国品牌电动汽车 C10。【原文：Stellantis plans to sell Chinese-branded electric vehicles developed by its partner Leapmotor in South Africa starting with the C10 from September, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-debut-leapmotors-evs-south-africa-this-year-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOYO2SONVBOSHMZVYWLTA33PPQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普-莫里斯公司因卷烟销量下降而收入不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于香烟销量下滑，生产万宝路香烟的菲利普莫里斯国际公司（PMI）周二公布的第二季度营收低于分析师预期。【原文：Philip Morris International (PMI) , which makes Marlboro cigarettes, reported second-quarter revenue on Tuesday that fell short of analysts' estimates as cigarette sales volumes slipped.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/philip-morriss-revenue-misses-estimates-cigarette-volumes-drop-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQE4I42CPBPYDFZBMUTFQF6ZTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于需求疲软，油漆制造商 Sherwin-Williams 下调 2025 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受涂料产品需求疲软的影响，谢尔温-威廉姆斯（Sherwin-Williams）周二下调了全年调整后利润预期，第二季度盈利未达预期，导致该公司股价在盘前交易中下跌超过 4%。【原文：Sherwin-Williams cut full-year adjusted profit forecast and missed second-quarter earnings estimate on Tuesday, hit by soft demand for paint products, sending the company's shares down more than 4% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/paintmaker-sherwin-williams-cuts-2025-profit-forecast-soft-demand-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HAVUG6AQFNOHLK7SQPIJ6BSH5E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>