<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:37:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:37:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[市场关注美国政府重开，油价变化不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，油价在前一交易日上涨后变化不大，因为市场预期美国政府结束有史以来最长的停摆可能会提振世界最大原油消费国的需求。【原文：Oil prices were little changed on Wednesday after rising in the previous session amid expectations that an end to the longest-ever U.S. government shutdown could boost demand in the world's biggest crude consuming nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-little-changed-markets-eye-us-government-reopening-2025-11-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZTPP3JAKFOWPMXUIY4WMKS3JM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管机构称，爱尔兰企业税收可避免关税打击，但风险上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰财政监督机构表示，迄今为止，爱尔兰大多数企业纳税大户都没有受到美国关税的直接影响，但美国的贸易政策使这一重要的政府收入来源的前景变得越来越不确定。【原文：Most of Ireland's big corporate taxpayers have so far escaped the direct impact of U.S. tariffs, but American trade policies have made the outlook for this critical source of government revenue increasingly uncertain, Ireland's fiscal watchdog said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/irish-corporate-taxes-avoid-tariff-hit-risks-rise-watchdog-says-2025-11-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PD6WVL556RKCZHCMMWVQCXDEYE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就业市场疲软，交易员关注美联储 12 月减息，美元走软]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国私营部门的就业数据激起了投资者对劳动力市场健康状况的担忧，美元汇率有所回落，投资者还在为即将到来的美国政府重开做准备，预计重开后将发布一系列积压的经济数据。【原文：The dollar eased on Wednesday after private-sector U.S. jobs data stoked worries about the health of the labour market, with investors also bracing for an imminent U.S. government reopening that is expected to unleash a backlog of economic releases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-eases-traders-eye-december-fed-cut-weakening-us-jobs-market-2025-11-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQSZKKC3ZVJW5JBJQEFZ6KPGIQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国停摆即将结束，亚洲市场温和上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三亚市盘初，由于美国国会有望结束联邦停摆，交易商在缺乏政府数据服务线索的情况下寻找方向，股市蹑手蹑脚地向前走。【原文：Stocks tiptoed forward at the start of Asian trading on Wednesday as the U.S. Congress looked set to end the federal shutdown and traders looked for direction in the absence of clues from government data services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-11-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4UGVL2MVBOGZJ47DXFMWNV6EQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普周三将在白宫与华尔街首席执行官共进晚餐]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位政府官员告诉路透社记者，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普预计将于周三在白宫与几位商界高管举行私人晚宴，其中包括纳斯达克（Nasdaq）和摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）的首席执行官。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is expected to host a private dinner at the White House on Wednesday with several top business executives, including the chief executives of Nasdaq and JPMorgan Chase, an administration official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-expected-dine-with-wall-street-ceos-white-house-wednesday-2025-11-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HR2OJ2VRGRJ4NNRGQ23RYS3QKE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:40:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究公司称，10 月份全球电动汽车销量增长 23]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场研究公司 Rho Motion 周三表示，受主要市场强劲需求的推动，10 月份全球全电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车的销量增长了 23%，达到 190 万辆。【原文：Global sales of fully electric and plug-in hybrid vehicles rose 23% in October to 1.9 million units, driven by strong demand across major markets, market research firm Rho Motion said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-ev-sales-growth-hits-23-october-research-firm-says-2025-11-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSBA3IDAWRLYZNFYZIZ5OUZHXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国计划制定更严厉的法律保护公共服务免受网络攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国计划加强公共服务部门对网络攻击的防御能力，要求向国民健康服务等私营和公共部门机构提供服务的公司达到严格的安全标准。【原文：Britain plans to strengthen its public services' defences against cyberattacks, requiring companies that provide services to private and public sector organisations such as the National Health Service to meet strict security standards.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-plans-tougher-laws-protect-public-services-cyberattacks-2025-11-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWBC376D5VPFPKCHZP35TB245M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，沙特阿拉伯将在本-萨勒曼访问华盛顿期间举办投资峰会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉计划的消息人士透露，沙特阿拉伯预计将于 11 月 19 日在王储穆罕默德-本-萨勒曼访问华盛顿期间主办一次美国-沙特投资峰会。【原文：Saudi Arabia is expected to host a U.S.-Saudi investment summit in Washington on November 19 during a visit by Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, according to a source familiar with the planning.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-arabia-host-investment-summit-during-bin-salmans-washington-visit-source-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7JHMBNT6BZPG3M4SL7256B2DXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国银行业监管机构着手敲定与国债挂钩的资本计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道称，美国监管机构已就放宽一系列资本要求的条款达成一致，这些要求可能允许银行持有更多的国债。【原文：U.S. regulators have agreed on the terms to ease a set of capital requirements that could potentially allow banks to hold more Treasuries, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-bank-regulators-move-finalize-treasuries-linked-capital-plan-bloomberg-news-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AJK2Z4IXZIBPPW3JLIWWIQ4VM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:41:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥对食糖进口征收 156% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据墨西哥《官方公报》报道，由于国际糖价下跌和国内市场供应过剩的风险，墨西哥于本周二对食糖进口实施了新的关税。【原文：Mexico on Tuesday implemented a new tariff for sugar imports due to falling international prices and a risk of oversupply in the domestic market, according to the country's Official Gazette.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-imposes-156-tariff-sugar-imports-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSP4ZY53LVP5RI4MT7OAPOLLYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 MinRes 公司将以 7.65 亿美元向浦项制铁出售 30% 锂合资公司股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚矿产资源公司（Mineral Resources）周三表示，该公司将以 7.65 亿美元的价格向韩国浦项制铁控股公司（POSCO Holdings）出售其锂业务运营公司 30% 的股份，此前该公司已将该业务置于一家新的合资企业之下。【原文：Australia's Mineral Resources will sell a 30% stake in its operational lithium business to South Korea's POSCO Holdings for $765 million after placing it under a new joint venture, the miner said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-minres-sell-30-lithium-jv-stake-posco-765-mln-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36GAHYT2GZK5RO4AYYX4VWM444</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:24:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 晴朗华尔街上的孤云--科技]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国政府关门预期结束，令道指创下收盘纪录新高，其他股指也纷纷创下新高。【原文：U.S. tech was the major outlier in an otherwise buoyant day for global stocks on Tuesday, as relief around the expected end of the U.S. government shutdown lifted the Dow to a record closing high and other indices to new peaks too.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DC3A3SGTYRIA7GLEVXRSYWCYUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西为价值十亿美元的餐券市场设定收费上限并缩短支付期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周二签署了一项法令，旨在降低该国数十亿雷亚尔餐券市场的中介成本，该法令将规定银行卡处理商费用的上限，并缩短结算时间。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva signed on Tuesday a decree seeking to lower intermediation costs in the country's multi-billion-real meal voucher market, which will cap card processor fees and shorten settlement periods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-caps-fees-shortens-payment-terms-billion-dollar-meal-voucher-market-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KU6472JSNLFFOFZU3TLT4BWAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 21:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国消费者监督机构将缩小民权时代贷款法的范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，随着共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府全面改革其认为给企业造成负担的保护措施和规则，美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）计划在未来几天内提议缩小民权时代公平借贷法规的一个关键部分。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau plans to propose in the coming days narrowing a key part of civil-rights era fair-lending regulations as Republican President Donald Trump's administration overhauls protections and rules it says burden companies, according to two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/us-consumer-watchdog-narrow-civil-rights-era-lending-law-sources-say-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQRZ3NR7IJOARCIK2Q4TWB5LKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:47:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[感恩节临近，美国航空公司正努力应对停运带来的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几天，联邦政府停摆时间最长，数以万计的航班因此中断，美国航空公司对本季度假期的乐观预期也随之破灭。现在，在政府有望于本周末重新开放的情况下，他们正在纠结如何最大限度地减少对旅客和底线的连锁反应。【原文：The longest federal government shutdown disrupted tens of thousands of flights in recent days, and with it, U.S. carriers' optimistic expectations for the holiday quarter. Now, they are wrangling with how to minimize the ripple effects on travelers and their bottom line as the government looks set to reopen by the end of the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-airlines-grapple-with-shutdown-fallout-thanksgiving-nears-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHRKS6WB5FKSRE4XMSRMQGFDRA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最新私营部门数据显示，美国截至 10 月下旬的就业岗位减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国薪资处理机构ADP周二在其对就业市场趋势的最新实时估计中称，截至10月下旬，美国企业每周减少超过1.1万个工作岗位。【原文：U.S. firms were shedding more than 11,000 jobs a week through late October, payroll processor ADP said on Tuesday in its latest real-time estimate of job market trends.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-lost-jobs-through-late-october-new-private-sector-data-shows-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPSG6TTAKVLNFIITSC6HNGLYMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福克斯新闻称，美国银行首席执行官寻求与当选市长马姆达尼会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行首席执行官布莱恩-莫伊尼汉（Brian Moynihan）周二告诉福克斯新闻（Fox News），他将要求与纽约当选市长佐赫兰-马姆达尼（Zohran Mamdani）会面，讨论如何与他合作，并将提出一些想法。【原文：Bank of America CEO Brian Moynihan will ask for a meeting with New York Mayor-elect Zohran Mamdani to discuss how he can work with him and will also offer some ideas, he told Fox News on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-ceo-seeks-meet-mayor-elect-mamdani-fox-news-says-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZE4KEL4IVJKIXNVT3ST3BOH4AA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府继续关门，美国航空公司周二取消 1200 个航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，航空公司取消了近1200个航班，这是自政府为解决安全问题强制减少航班以来连续第五天取消航班超过1000个。【原文：Airlines canceled nearly 1,200 flights on Tuesday, the fifth consecutive day they have topped 1,000 since the government imposed mandatory flight reductions to address safety concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-airlines-cancel-1200-flights-tuesday-government-shutdown-continues-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKCVJ5R7PVP7PGQIGPU2JREAL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司 10 月份保持强劲交付速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二表示，该公司在 10 月份交付了 53 架喷气式飞机，使今年的总交付量达到 493 架，并在上个月收到了 15 份新订单。【原文：Boeing said on Tuesday that it delivered 53 jets in October, bringing its total for the year to 493, and received 15 new orders last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-keeps-up-strong-delivery-pace-in-october-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ONNW3UJNNMY7ANYPVFGJ3XMY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 50 年抵押贷款不是什么 "大问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对提供 50 年期抵押贷款的努力轻描淡写，认为这是让人们比一般的 30 年期贷款更能负担得起住房的一种方式，尽管房主将支付更多的利息，需要更长的时间来积累资产。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump downplayed efforts to offer a 50-year mortgage as a way to make owning a house more affordable than with typical 30-year loans, even as homeowners would pay far more in interest and take longer to build equity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-50-year-mortgages-would-be-no-big-deal-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ERODLN54FP7LCR5YLVPCIAVTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:03:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitwise 推出 Solana ETF，引发行业争相追捧]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内高管表示，加密货币公司比特慧资产管理公司（Bitwise Asset Management）在美国证券交易委员会（Securities and Exchange Commission）关闭期间成功推动推出美国首只现货索拉纳 ETF，颠覆了监管玩法，迫使竞争对手重新思考自己的产品计划。【原文：Crypto firm Bitwise Asset Management's successful push to launch the first U.S. spot Solana ETF while the Securities and Exchange Commission was shut down has upended the regulatory playbook and forced competitors to rethink their product plans, said industry executives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bitwise-sparks-industry-scramble-with-solana-etf-launch-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXZH4JYOMZKOXFSKSBCRBU36ZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，摩根士丹利与竞争对手一起推出私人公司研究报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部备忘录，摩根士丹利周二推出了一个专门的私人公司研究页面，因为投资者对高增长初创企业的兴趣正在上升。【原文：Morgan Stanley launched a dedicated private company research page on Tuesday, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters, as investors' interest in high-growth startups rises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-joins-rivals-rolling-out-private-company-research-memo-shows-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CM6TWVMISRNYXNAH4P3VUCXIGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行布里登称进一步淡化稳定币规则可能会破坏金融体系]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行副行长萨拉-布里登（Sarah Breeden）周二警告说，进一步淡化稳定币规则有可能危及金融稳定并导致信贷紧缩，并表示英国需要采取与美国不同的方法。【原文：Bank of England Deputy Governor Sarah Breeden on Tuesday warned that further diluting rules for stablecoins risked endangering financial stability and causing a credit crunch, and said that the UK needed a different approach to the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bank-englands-breeden-says-diluting-stablecoin-rules-further-could-damage-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMNLMFEEXNM7REVWZDFPS7NWJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长贝森特：美国从阿根廷货币互换交易中获利]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，美国政府在上月南美国家中期选举前向阿根廷央行提供支持 "赚了钱"。【原文：The U.S. government "made money" by giving support to the Argentine central bank ahead of last month's midterm election in the South American country, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-profited-argentina-currency-swap-deal-treasury-chief-bessent-says-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKWRUPZR4JKYNGBVQXKEGGVLIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌表示将在德国投资约 64 亿美元建设云基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周二表示，未来几年将在德国投资 55 亿欧元（64.1 亿美元），以扩大其在欧洲最大经济体的基础设施和数据中心容量。【原文：Alphabet's Google said on Tuesday that it will invest 5.5 billion euros ($6.41 billion) in Germany in the coming years in a push to expand its infrastructure and data centre capacity in Europe's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-says-it-will-invest-around-64-billion-cloud-infrastructure-germany-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HUMPXHCJ5LUXISLIYHVXJZEGQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:08:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际金融协会（IIF）称，10 月份外资为新兴市场投资组合增资 270 亿美元，股票大放异彩]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家银行贸易集团的数据显示，10 月份，非居民投资者在新兴市场的股票和债务投资组合中增加了 269 亿美元，从而带动了股票资金的回流。【原文：A pick-up in flows into stocks led the way as non-resident investors added $26.9 billion to their emerging markets' equities and debt portfolios in October, data from a banking trade group showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/stocks-shine-foreigners-add-27-bln-em-portfolios-october-says-iif-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HWJNUIFGXJJJLLZUO276NKOYMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通在德国的数字零售银行雇佣了 120 名员工，并将逐步增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通已将其即将成立的数字零售银行的 120 名员工迁入柏林市中心的新总部，并预计在未来几年内将在一栋可容纳 400 人的大楼内雇佣更多员工。【原文：JPMorgan has moved 120 employees for its upcoming digital retail bank into its new central Berlin headquarters and expects to hire more people in the years to come in a building with space for 400.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-employs-120-digital-retail-bank-germany-grow-over-time-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QWBQTWZ45OE3HUJZY2DLIRMBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院返回华盛顿投票结束政府停摆]]></title><description><![CDATA[众议院议员周二返回华盛顿，冒着全国机场拥堵的危险进行投票，这可能为美国政府史上最长的停摆画上句号。【原文：Members of the House of Representatives returned to Washington on Tuesday, braving the nation's tangled airports for a vote that could bring the longest U.S. government shutdown in history to a close.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-returns-washington-vote-end-government-shutdown-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECOWFDT67BNHBGTQJDPXICQD4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:58:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国航空旅行混乱之际，公共汽车和火车再度兴起]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年的感恩节，越来越多的美国人开始预订前往目的地的巴士和火车，而一些人则直接取消了他们的计划，因为航空旅行受到了自政府停摆以来最严重的干扰。【原文：Americans are increasingly booking buses and trains to their Thanksgiving destinations this year while some have outright canceled their plans following the worst disruptions to air travel since the start of the government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/buses-trains-see-resurgence-amid-us-air-travel-chaos-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6X2RE5EMYJNQLHW7TC7SKKUPDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:52:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪恩设定新目标，超越欧洲竞争对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[因为 eBay 和 Spotify 处理支付业务而闻名的荷兰公司 Adyen 周二制定了新的财务目标，旨在实现更强的盈利能力和稳定的收入增长。【原文：Adyen , the Dutch company known for handling payment processing for eBay and Spotify, set new financial targets on Tuesday, aiming for stronger profitability and steady revenue growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/adyen-sets-new-targets-outpacing-european-rivals-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6Z6YKFJVZOOLBADXYHIINPVSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>