<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:33:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:33:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院阻止特朗普加征关税，油价攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国法院阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税措施生效后，油价周四上涨，同时市场还在关注美国可能采取新的制裁措施遏制俄罗斯原油流动，以及欧佩克+组织（OPEC+）7月份决定提高产量。【原文：Oil prices rose on Thursday after a U.S. court blocked President Donald Trump's tariffs from taking effect, while the market was watching out for potential new U.S. sanctions curbing Russian crude flows and an OPEC+ decision on hiking output in July.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-climb-us-court-blocks-trump-tariffs-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CGKTY7PFXBOJXIL3DP37ED6QCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税抵消强劲芯片需求，韩国 5 月出口预计下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税的影响抵消了对半导体的强劲需求，韩国5月份的出口预计将出现四个月来的首次下降。【原文：South Korea's exports are expected to have fallen in May for the first time in four months, as the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs offset strong demand for semiconductors, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-korea-may-exports-expected-fall-us-tariffs-offset-robust-chip-demand-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J754QJOY2FJ3JEBCNBFSST2D64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:07:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》报道：美国暂停向中国飞机制造商中国商飞出售部分美国技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周三报道，美国已暂停向中国出售美国的一些关键技术，包括向中国国有航空航天制造商中国商飞公司出售与喷气发动机有关的技术。【原文：The United States has suspended some sales to China of critical U.S. technologies, including those related to jet engines to Chinese state-owned aerospace manufacturer COMAC, the New York Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-suspends-sales-some-us-technologies-chinas-airplane-maker-comac-new-york-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKOL3RCNXBIIRGD4ESTQEJLZQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:50:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰乳品公司恒天然上调年度利润预期，股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰恒天然集团（Fonterra）周四上调了其年度盈利预期的下限，此前该公司公布的第三季度利润有所增长，这主要得益于乳业巨头配料渠道和消费者运营业务的强劲表现。【原文：New Zealand's Fonterra raised the lower end of its annual earnings forecast on Thursday, after reporting higher third-quarter profit, helped by strength in the dairy giant's ingredients channel and consumer operations business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nzs-dairy-firm-fonterra-raises-annual-profit-forecast-shares-rise-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3RDQAZMIVLILFAT6IN64ALLN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官告诉《航空周刊》，波音的目标是在年底前认证 737 MAX 变体]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）周三在接受行业刊物《航空周刊》（Aviation Week）采访时表示，波音公司预计将在今年年底前完成其最畅销的737 MAX系列飞机的认证工作。【原文：Boeing expects to finish certification of its best-selling 737 MAX family by the end of the year, CEO Kelly Ortberg said in an interview with trade publication Aviation Week published on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-aims-certify-737-max-variants-by-year-end-ceo-tells-aviation-week-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWJRK76TUBKFVPNMMFHJ5GNJP4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:39:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院阻止特朗普征收关税后美元反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[在法院阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统征收所谓的 "解放日 "进口关税后，美元周四大幅反弹，尤其是对欧元、日元和瑞士法郎的汇率飙升。【原文：The U.S. dollar rallied sharply on Thursday after a court blocked President Donald Trump from imposing his so-called Liberation Day import tariffs, with the currency surging against the euro, yen and Swiss franc in particular.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-rallies-after-us-court-blocks-trumps-tariffs-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDOZKXVC7NMPXEK324P7WWOJ2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:38:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 市场欢呼法院裁决阻止特朗普加征关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国联邦法院阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "解放日 "关税生效后，美国股指期货跳涨，美元兑日元和瑞郎等避险货币上涨。【原文：U.S. stock futures jumped and the dollar gained against safe-haven peers including the yen and Swiss franc on Thursday, after a U.S. federal court blocked President Donald Trump's "Liberation Day" tariffs from going into effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-markets-cheer-court-ruling-block-trump-tariffs-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6HZEA5AT7BKQ7IJNLOWGONVWME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税遭遇法庭障碍，亚洲股市反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国联邦法院阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "解放日 "关税生效后，周四亚洲股市和华尔街期货攀升，美元在避险货币的推动下上涨。【原文：Asian shares and Wall Street futures climbed in Asia on Thursday after a U.S. federal court blocked President Donald Trump's "Liberation Day" tariffs from going into effect, sending the dollar up on safe haven currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EH6GFLPSUJII3LYZPZULMLVD6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙将在得克萨斯州裁员近 800 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙周三向德克萨斯州劳动力委员会（Texas Workforce Commission）发出通知，称将在德克萨斯州裁员近 800 人，这也是这家美国石油生产商计划在 2026 年底前裁减全球 20% 员工的一部分。【原文：Chevron will lay off nearly 800 employees in Texas, according to a notice on Wednesday to the Texas Workforce Commission, part of the U.S. oil producer's plan to cut up to 20% of its global workforce by the end of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/chevron-cut-nearly-800-jobs-texas-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BF2EKDQQFOMXF6VZHRPBIER5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院阻止特朗普征收 "解放日 "关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家联邦法院周三阻止了唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "解放日 "关税生效，裁定总统越权对来自向美国销售多于购买的国家的进口商品征收全面关税。【原文：A U.S. federal court on Wednesday blocked President Donald Trump's "Liberation Day" tariffs from going into effect, ruling that the president overstepped his authority by imposing across-the-board duties on imports from nations that sell more to the United States than they buy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-court-blocks-trumps-liberation-day-tariffs-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBDTXDVX4ZLBTCHVJUUBDOMHLE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，派拉蒙出价 1500 万美元和解哥伦比亚广播公司诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，派拉蒙全球公司与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普就解决他对哥伦比亚广播公司新闻（CBS News）的诉讼进行了一个月的谈判，但双方在条件上仍有很大分歧。【原文：A month into negotiations between Paramount Global and U.S. President Donald Trump to settle his lawsuit against CBS News, the parties remain far apart on terms, The Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/paramount-has-offered-15-million-settle-cbs-lawsuit-wsj-reports-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VM4JO3WEW5OCPCW34R7PJUARL4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kaiser Permanente 表示其网络正面临间歇性中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[医疗保健集团凯撒医疗集团（Kaiser Permanente）周三表示，该公司正面临间歇性网络中断，影响到其多个系统，包括电子健康记录和病人服务。【原文：Healthcare conglomerate Kaiser Permanente said on Wednesday it is facing intermittent network disruptions affecting several of its systems, including electronic health records and patient services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kaiser-permanente-says-it-is-facing-intermittent-network-disruptions-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXN4DHKVLFLN7HOCH6BL3XO5OA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国机器人出租车制造商进军热情洋溢的海湾地区，海外雄心日益壮大]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你是一家中国的机器人出租车公司，海湾地区已经成为你的首选之地，因为这里的监管环境正在接受这种技术，而且对乘车服务的需求也很旺盛。【原文：If you're a Chinese robotaxi company, the Gulf has become the place to be, attractive for a regulatory environment that is embracing the technology and robust demand for ride-hailing services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/chinese-robotaxi-makers-head-welcoming-gulf-overseas-ambitions-grow-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXPW4F4ZZNN23PQCHUXHVDNRG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会将要求 Synopsys 和 Ansys 剥离部分资产以解决合并问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周三表示，将要求两家软件公司（Synopsys 和 Ansys）剥离某些资产，以解决围绕其 350 亿美元合并案的反垄断问题。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Wednesday it will require two software companies —Synopsys and Ansys — to divest certain assets to resolve antitrust concerns surrounding their $35 billion merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-ftc-will-require-synopsys-ansys-divest-certain-assets-resolve-merger-concerns-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAW3R6WLGFPO7KVB6GF5QFXLMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[维多利亚的秘密因安全事件关闭网站]]></title><description><![CDATA[服装和内衣零售商维多利亚的秘密周三在其网站上发布声明称，为 "处理一起安全事件"，公司暂停了网站的大部分功能和部分店内服务。【原文：Clothing and lingerie retailer Victoria’s Secret suspended most of the functionality of its website and some in-store services to “address a security incident,” according to a statement posted to the company’s website on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/victorias-secret-pulls-down-website-amid-security-incident-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5OU2V7HQVN3JAQLWYDI7ZVCQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:16:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国取消对 Moderna 禽流感疫苗超过 7 亿美元的资助]]></title><description><![CDATA[该制药商周三宣布，特朗普政府已取消了授予 Moderna 公司用于人类禽流感疫苗后期开发的合同以及购买疫苗的权利。【原文：The Trump administration has canceled a contract awarded to Moderna for the late-stage development of its bird flu vaccine for humans, as well as the right to purchase shots, the drugmaker announced on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-cancels-more-700-million-funding-moderna-bird-flu-vaccine-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTY2M7LXKVNCXOU3Y4GIRC3AHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[象征日产崛起的工厂可能成为日产衰落的牺牲品]]></title><description><![CDATA[1961 年，日产汽车的 Oppama 工厂开业，它是日本最早的大型汽车工厂之一，也是该公司全球雄心的象征。64 年过去了，数以百万计的汽车从这里驶出，但随着日产汽车陷入更深的危机，这家充满传奇色彩的工厂现在面临着关闭的可能。【原文：When Nissan's Oppama plant opened in 1961, it was one of Japan's first large-scale auto factories and a symbol of the company's global ambitions. Sixty-four years and millions of cars later, the storied plant now faces possible closure as Nissan sinks deeper into crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/factory-that-symbolised-nissans-rise-may-become-victim-its-decline-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLZ2VMAO5ZNWLNEMTEHPWW6FCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[REX Financial 在财报发布前数小时推出备兑英伟达 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三上午，在 Nvidia 财报发布前几个小时，REX Financial 推出了与 Nvidia 相关的单一股票交易所交易基金，Nvidia 是一家强大的芯片制造商，在过去两年中主导了股市回报率。【原文：REX Financial launched a single-stock exchange-traded fund tied to Nvidia , the powerhouse chipmaker that has dominated stock market returns over the last two years, on Wednesday morning, hours ahead of the release of Nvidia's earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rex-financial-launches-covered-call-nvidia-etf-hours-before-earnings-release-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QKI5CGQXFMZRJYYXZOL2GMJG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：特朗普政府取消新诺华能源公司 30 亿美元贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周三援引住宅太阳能电池板安装商 Sunnova Energy 的消息报道称，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府已经取消了向该公司提供的高达 30 亿美元的贷款担保。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration has canceled an up to $3 billion loan guarantee that was awarded to residential solar panel installer Sunnova Energy, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-administration-cancels-sunnova-energy-3-billion-loan-bloomberg-news-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Z5IHT53DVNPHMHRW4HXBYLHAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:41:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党人沃伦对美国关税协议将有利于大科技公司而不利于工人表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）周三对特朗普政府的关税谈判将有利于大型科技公司而牺牲消费者和工人利益表示担忧。【原文：Democratic U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren on Wednesday expressed concern the Trump administration's tariff negotiations would favor big technology firms at the expense of consumers and workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/democrat-warren-raises-concerns-that-us-tariff-deals-will-favor-big-tech-over-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5XCJYTOIVVPG3HLF3Q7HEIY7UI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:23:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：投资者摆脱对英伟达的谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NCJA5S4LJKOHDFP5Y2BSAWKSU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[生命科学公司安捷伦因仪器需求超出季度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[安捷伦科技公司（Agilent Technologies）周三公布的第二季度利润和收入超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于市场对药物开发工具和设备的强劲需求，该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨了 5.1%。【原文：Agilent Technologies beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit and revenue on Wednesday, helped by strong demand for its tools and equipment used in drug development, sending its shares up 5.1% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/life-sciences-firm-agilent-beats-quarterly-estimates-instrument-demand-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PB7LWNWBU5K6VEP7W557QVMF34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特斯拉计划于 6 月 12 日在奥斯汀推出机器人出租车服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引一位知情人士的话报道，特斯拉准备于 6 月 12 日在奥斯汀开始提供期待已久的机器人出租车服务。【原文：Tesla is poised to begin its long-awaited robotaxi service in Austin on June 12, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-targets-june-12-launch-robotaxi-service-austin-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKC7PS4MFZNXJMLS32RP4FLWOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SentinelOne 下调年度收入预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[SentinelOne 周三下调了年度营收预期，表明企业在经济不确定的情况下支出谨慎，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌近 14%。【原文：SentinelOne trimmed its annual revenue forecast on Wednesday, signaling cautious spending by businesses amid economic uncertainty, sending its shares down nearly 14% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sentinelone-cuts-annual-revenue-forecast-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z73IMRBNK5MEVFHJV4TN5B3EFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达预测第二季度营收低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周三预测第二季度营收低于市场预期，预计美国收紧对主要半导体市场中国的人工智能芯片出口限制将对销售造成重大打击。【原文：Nvidia forecast second-quarter revenue below market estimates on Wednesday, expecting a major hit to sales from tighter U.S. curbs on exports of its AI chips to key semiconductor market China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-forecasts-second-quarter-revenue-below-estimates-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7F4GTFKL5JRHLGYLH5RCAHVXY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:24:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠普下调年度利润预期，因关税拖累需求，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠普公司周三下调了年度利润预期，原因是该公司预计在全球经济环境持续动荡的情况下，个人电脑市场的增长速度将有所放缓，从而导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌了 14%。【原文：HP Inc cut its annual profit forecast on Wednesday as it expects a moderation in PC market growth at a time when the global economic environment remains volatile, sending its shares down 14% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hp-cuts-annual-profit-forecast-tariffs-weigh-demand-shares-fall-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2SV27TCLVI6NKBNVWDQMWUZIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:21:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Synopsys 预测季度收入大幅高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[新思科技（Synopsys）周三预测，随着企业加大对人工智能芯片的投入，对其半导体设计软件的需求强劲，第三季度营收将大幅高于华尔街预期。【原文：Synopsys forecast third-quarter revenue largely above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, driven by strong demand for its semiconductor design software, as companies ramp up spending on AI chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/synopsys-forecasts-quarterly-revenue-largely-above-estimates-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKNZ3V7Z7BKYNOWD3FNOZNDP5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海莉-比伯（Hailey Bieber）以 10 亿美元的价格将彩妆品牌 Rhode 出售给 Elf Beauty]]></title><description><![CDATA[名模海莉-比伯（Hailey Bieber）的彩妆和护肤品牌 Rhode 将以约 10 亿美元的价格被 Elf Beauty 收购，从而使这家经济型化妆品零售商获得在 Z 世代和千禧一代中大受欢迎的明星代言产品系列。【原文：Model Hailey Bieber's makeup and skincare brand, Rhode, is being snapped up by Elf Beauty for about $1 billion, giving the budget cosmetic retailer access to a celebrity-endorsed product line that has become hugely popular among Gen Z and millennials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hailey-bieber-sells-makeup-brand-rhode-elf-beauty-1-billion-deal-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFIQ4WQF7ZPVVECL2MRDS5GM4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[云计算支出强劲，Salesforce上调年度业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Salesforce 周三上调了 2026 财年的营收和调整后利润预期，原因是这家企业软件供应商受益于强劲的云计算支出，同时加大了人工智能代理的货币化力度。【原文：Salesforce raised its revenue and adjusted profit forecast for fiscal 2026 on Wednesday, as the enterprise software provider benefits from strong cloud spending while ramping up monetization of its artificial intelligence agents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/salesforce-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRISSKKK2FOFNDWPAUX6XFZA7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:08:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，网络安全提供商 Netskope 选择摩根士丹利进行美国 IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，网络安全公司 Netskope 已聘请摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）牵头筹备在美国的首次公开募股，募集资金可能超过 5 亿美元。【原文：Cybersecurity firm Netskope has hired Morgan Stanley to lead preparations for a U.S. initial public offering that could raise more than $500 million, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cybersecurity-provider-netskope-taps-morgan-stanley-us-ipo-sources-say-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUWATU2JBVPATDEF4N5XRN5JKA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:06:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>