<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:35:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:35:12 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[因房东拒绝将房屋出租给带孩子的母亲，美国起诉 Airbnb]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Airbnb 因一名房东拒绝将公寓租给一位有三个学龄儿童的母亲而被美国政府起诉。【原文：Airbnb was sued by the U.S. government on Friday over a host's refusal to rent an apartment to a mother with three school-age children.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-airbnb-after-host-rejected-rental-mother-with-children-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6LF5RCGYVIXTLUS54AI4C5YGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:17:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Blackstone 正酝酿以 40 多亿美元出售 Liftoff]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉此事的人士周五表示，收购公司 Blackstone 正在权衡 Liftoff 的战略选择，包括出售，该移动应用程序营销提供商的估值可能超过 40 亿美元（包括债务）。【原文：Buyout firm Blackstone is weighing strategic options, including a sale, for Liftoff that could value the mobile app marketing provider at more than $4 billion, including debt, two people familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/blackstone-mulls-4-billion-plus-sale-liftoff-sources-say-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74FYIQFONNMZVKSGNDLM6X2EKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Semafor 报道，好时公司将宣布首席执行官米歇尔-巴克离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Semafor 周五援引知情人士的话报道，巧克力生产商好时公司计划宣布首席执行官米歇尔-巴克（Michele Buck）离职。【原文：Chocolate maker Hershey plans to announce the departure of CEO Michele Buck, Semafor reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hershey-set-announce-ceo-michele-buck-step-down-semafor-reports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RNFL4WYGNN7HNNHBRWTSGSBE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉阻止企业旅游公司合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国已起诉阻止美国运通全球商务旅行集团与 CWT Holdings 之间的拟议合并，称这笔价值 5.7 亿美元的交易将消除最大和第三大商务旅行管理服务提供商之间的竞争。【原文：The U.S. has sued to block a proposed merger between American Express Global Business Travel Group and CWT Holdings, saying the $570 million deal would eliminate competition between the largest and third largest providers of business travel management services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-block-corporate-travel-company-merger-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBDYJWSVQNJWBFYGG3W7LTWSXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将在特朗普就职典礼前终止多元化计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周五在公司内部论坛上发布了一份致员工的备忘录，称将终止其多元化、公平与包容（DEI）计划，包括招聘、培训和挑选供应商的计划。【原文：Meta Platforms is ending its diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) programs, including those for hiring, training and picking suppliers, it said in a memo to employees posted on an internal company forum on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/meta-end-diversity-programs-ahead-trump-inauguration-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RV3HXX7EFRI37CUVWVK6NZ5G3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西给 Meta 公司 72 小时解释对事实核查计划的修改]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西副检察长豪尔赫-梅西亚斯（Jorge Messias）周五表示，巴西政府将要求梅塔公司在周一之前对该计划做出解释。【原文：Brazil's government will give Meta until Monday to explain the program, Solicitor General Jorge Messias said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-gives-meta-72-hours-explain-changes-fact-checking-program-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHZATBMRFJN6VIDOIDVCDK6NVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税担忧影响，1 月份美国消费者通胀预期飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者预计未来 12 个月及以后的通胀率将上升，这可能反映出人们担心当选总统唐纳德-特朗普即将上任的政府承诺对进口商品征收的广泛关税可能会提高家庭的物价。【原文：U.S. consumers expect inflation to increase over the next 12 months and beyond, likely reflecting concerns that broad tariffs on imports pledged by President-elect Donald Trump's incoming administration could raise prices for households.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-inflation-expectations-soar-january-tariff-fears-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVK53OQ62JOXZMCVJWDSDQ6GWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国负责人对 Blackrock 退出气候组织表示不满，敦促其他人留下]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国秘书长安东尼奥-古特雷斯（Antonio Guterres）的发言人周五表示，他对全球最大的资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock BLK.N）退出应对气候变化的全球倡议感到失望，并敦促其他公司 "坚持到底"。【原文：U.N. Secretary-General Antonio Guterres is disappointed that the world's biggest asset manager, BlackRock BLK.N, has left a global initiative to combat climate change, his spokesperson said on Friday, urging other companies to "stay the course."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/un-chief-upset-blackrock-quit-climate-group-urges-others-stay-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEUUUVPHGZITTGFLQA7MT57FCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，特朗普将脱离家族企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引特朗普公司的道德计划报道称，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普上任后将不会参与特朗普组织的日常管理。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump won't be involved in the day-to-day management of the Trump Organization once he takes office, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing an ethics plan from the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-will-separate-himself-family-business-wsj-reports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXJ2ZFF3U5PQ7DX5GUY2SAXFEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官裁定，美国航空公司在 401（k）计划中关注环境、社会和公司治理（ESG）不合法]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州的一名联邦法官周五称，美国航空公司以环境、社会和其他非财务因素为依据为其员工退休计划做出投资决策，违反了联邦法律。【原文：A federal judge in Texas on Friday said American Airlines violated federal law by basing investment decisions for its employee retirement plan on environmental, social, and other non-financial factors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-focus-esg-401k-plan-is-illegal-us-judge-rules-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIK3ZGV3KVJL5ITHSVVMNULFKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liquidnet支付500万美元罚款，以了结美国证券交易委员会对其控制和保密性的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[Liquidnet 同意支付 500 万美元的民事罚款，以解决美国证券交易委员会对该经纪自营商在市场准入方面缺乏必要控制以及未能保护机密用户交易信息的指控。【原文：Liquidnet agreed to pay a $5 million civil fine to resolve U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charges that the broker-dealer lacked necessary controls regarding market access, and failed to protect confidential subscriber trading information.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/liquidnet-pays-5-million-fine-settle-us-sec-charges-over-controls-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUUQSBPXTRI75AFEILRUDMCLXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:29:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市下挫，华尔街 "恐惧指数 "创三周新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，华尔街最受关注的投资者焦虑指数升至三周高点，因为一份乐观的就业报告推低了市场对美联储进一步降息的预期，股指遭到抛售。【原文：Wall Street's most watched gauge of investor anxiety rose to a three-week high on Friday as stock indexes sold off following a an upbeat jobs report that pushed back market expectations for further Federal Reserve interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-fear-gauge-3-week-high-stocks-sink-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BKJK4XWTTBPFBBRKSHYCSRNUJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:18:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院裁定，辉瑞必须面对有关多元化奖学金计划的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周五恢复了一个反对医药多元化倡议的保守团体提起的诉讼，该团体对辉瑞公司旨在促进黑人、拉丁裔和美国原住民担任该制药公司领导职位的奖学金计划提出了质疑。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Friday revived a lawsuit by a conservative group opposed to diversity initiatives in medicine that challenged a Pfizer fellowship program designed to boost the pipeline of Black, Latino and Native American people in leadership positions at the drugmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/pfizer-must-face-lawsuit-over-diversity-fellowship-program-us-court-rules-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NS67QLETRLPJFNAI5CIK6MECI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:15:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟有条件批准 Synopsys 350 亿美元的 Ansys 交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五表示，已经有条件地批准了芯片设计软件制造商 Synopsys 对软件公司 Ansys 的收购，这是去年 1 月宣布的一项价值 350 亿美元的现金加股票交易。【原文：The European Commission on Friday said it had approved under conditions the takeover by chip design software maker Synopsys of software company Ansys , a $35 billion cash-and-stock deal announced in January last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/eu-approves-synopsys-35-billion-ansys-deal-under-conditions-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWOABTUYQ5MSFH4U6DPZURQWCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国今年有充足的财政空间促进经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国财政部副部长廖岷周五表示，中国有充足的财政政策空间和工具来支持今年的经济增长，并将加大支出以刺激投资。【原文：China has ample fiscal policy space and tools to support economic growth this year and it will step up spending to spur investment, Vice Finance Minister Liao Min said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-has-ample-fiscal-space-bolster-growth-this-year-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2JWON46IFME3P36K2FRDVPBEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:43:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，KKR 探讨出售英国 Viridor 公司的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，美国私募股权基金 KKR 正在探索出售 Viridor Ltd 的可能性，包括债务在内，这家英国废物管理公司的估值可能高达 70 亿英镑（85.5 亿美元）。【原文：U.S. private equity fund KKR is exploring a potential sale of Viridor Ltd, which could value the UK waste management firm at as much as 7 billion pounds ($8.55 billion) including debt, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-explores-potential-sale-uks-viridor-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEPPQPWQJZN2NLYBPJWBUBCN4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国资深立法者向伦敦政治经济学院和监管机构表达对 Shein 的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国议会委员会主席周四致信英国金融行为监管局（Financial Conduct Authortiy）和伦敦证券交易所（London Stock Exchange）负责人，称申银万国在本周举行的委员会听证会上对立法者就其供应链提出的问题缺乏回应。【原文：The chair of a British parliamentary committee wrote on Thursday to the chiefs of the Financial Conduct Authortiy and the London Stock Exchange about Shein's lack of response to lawmakers' questions about its supply chain at a committee hearing this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/senior-uk-lawmaker-flags-concerns-about-shein-lse-regulator-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2KPJYQSJBMGZDABOS3DGCLIUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:31:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业报告发布后，美银美林押注美联储可能加息，华尔街顶级经纪商修改预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街顶级券商在周五的美国就业报告公布后修改了对美联储降息的预测，博雅全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）预测央行可能会加息。【原文：Top Wall-Street brokerages revised their Fed rate cut forecasts, after a blow-out U.S. jobs report on Friday, with BofA Global Research forecasting a potential rate hike from the central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bofa-bets-potential-fed-rate-hike-after-jobs-report-top-wall-st-brokers-revise-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OW52MFIBGFN6RFD5N5CIQZYID4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦肯锡前合伙人承认销毁有关阿片类药物推广工作的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦肯锡公司（McKinsey &amp; Co）的一名前合伙人周五承认犯有妨碍司法罪，因为他销毁了与他和该咨询公司向普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）提供的关于如何 "加速 "其阿片类止痛药奥施康定（OxyContin）销售的建议有关的记录。【原文：A former partner at McKinsey &amp; Co pleaded guilty on Friday to obstructing justice by destroying records related to advice he and the consulting firm provided to Purdue Pharma on how to "turbocharge" sales of its opioid painkiller OxyContin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ex-mckinsey-partner-pleads-guilty-destroying-records-about-work-promoting-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N44RGXOIXJJY7OD3AVE3BBZZME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:13:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 实现将美国库存减少 10 万台的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯特兰蒂斯汽车公司北美区负责人周五在底特律车展上表示，该公司已于去年年底实现了将美国库存汽车削减10万辆以上的目标。【原文：Automaker Stellantis achieved its goal of cutting U.S. inventories by over 100,000 vehicles late last year, its North American chief said at the Detroit Auto Show Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-reaches-goal-cutting-us-inventories-by-100000-units-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QR64BM3AYVPIVKOPN3NN7NDBWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 16:46:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[曼哈顿顶级联邦检察官威廉姆斯加盟 Paul Weiss 律师事务所]]></title><description><![CDATA[Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton &amp; Garrison 律师事务所周五表示，曼哈顿前最高联邦检察官达米安-威廉姆斯（Damian Williams）将重返该事务所，担任纽约合伙人。【原文：Damian Williams, the former top federal prosecutor in Manhattan, will return to law firm Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton &amp; Garrison as a partner in New York, the firm said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/manhattans-top-federal-prosecutor-williams-joins-law-firm-paul-weiss-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5GGJMPCPROMFNN2PLPZXLDHTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 16:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对俄罗斯能源利益集团实施新制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五宣布对俄罗斯能源行业（包括石油巨头俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司（Gazprom Neft）和苏尔古特石油公司（Surgutneftegaz））实施全面的新制裁，试图阻止莫斯科与乌克兰的战争。【原文：The U.S. Treasury on Friday announced sweeping new sanctions against the Russian energy sector, including oil majors Gazprom Neft and Surgutneftegaz , to try to hinder Moscow in its war with Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-us-sanctions-against-russian-energy-interests-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADBZDNNUT5PUPC5QI4DSWT3FP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:49:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国世茂集团收到清算申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国世茂集团周五称，CPYM Link Investment Limited 已就该房地产开发商提供的 2.58 亿元人民币（3519 万美元）跨境贷款担保向香港高等法院提交了针对该公司的清算申请。【原文：China's Shimao Group said on Friday CPYM Link Investment Limited had filed a liquidation petition against the company in the Hong Kong high court regarding a 258 million yuan ($35.19 million) cross-border loan guarantee provided by the property developer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-shimao-group-receives-liquidation-petition-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NN5YTJ4IXZOVZL25U2AZDGMK5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:45:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普领导银行监管机构的潜在人选预示着规则制定将更加宽松]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行业监管机构的下一任潜在负责人周五提出了一项全面计划，将在从资本到加密货币等问题上对银行业采取更宽松的政策。【原文：The potential next head of a U.S. banking regulator laid out a sweeping plan on Friday to adopt a lighter touch on the banking industry on matters ranging from capital to cryptocurrency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/potential-trump-pick-lead-bank-regulator-signals-lighter-rulewriting-touch-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEXLBR3FENM4XNL3RU5VENGF7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国金边债券大跌引发养老金现金调用，这是 2022 年危机以来的首次重大考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近借贷成本飙升后，一些英国养老基金被资产管理公司告知要拿出更多现金来支持他们的对冲头寸，但养老金顾问本周告诉路透社，市场的表现是有序的。【原文：Some British pension funds are being told by asset managers to come up with more cash to support their hedging positions after a recent jump in borrowing costs, but pensions advisers told Reuters this week the market was behaving in an orderly way.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/uk-gilt-selloff-triggers-pension-cash-calls-first-big-test-since-2022-crisis-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTBBOOMQO5IB5JMFJMYAOQ6SGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:17:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，摩根大通要求员工在三月份恢复每周五天的办公时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份内部备忘录显示，华尔街巨头摩根大通要求实行混合工作制的员工从 3 月份开始每周五天返回办公室。【原文：Wall Street giant JPMorgan Chase asked its employees who are on hybrid work schedules to return to the office five days a week starting in March, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-asks-staff-return-office-five-days-week-march-memo-shows-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZHLOUPRM5PC5JBPG7SV3WEZEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:10:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险业面临洛杉矶野火可能造成的破纪录损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师们正在评估烧毁洛杉矶县山坡、房屋和街道的野火造成的经济影响，初步估计保险损失总额可能高达 200 亿美元。【原文：Analysts are evaluating the financial impact of the wildfires that have charred hillsides, homes, and streets in Los Angeles County, with initial estimates suggesting total insured losses could reach as high as $20 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/insurance-industry-stares-potential-record-breaking-losses-los-angeles-wildfires-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDX5IVKDHRJINNXABUAA3RTQ2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:40:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就业数据强劲，美元跳涨，股票期货暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元反弹，而美国股票期货大幅下跌，因为数据显示美国经济在 12 月份创造的就业岗位远超预期，这让投资者更加相信美国利率今年可能不会大幅下降。【原文：The dollar rallied, while U.S. stock futures fell sharply on Friday after data showed the U.S. economy created far more jobs in December than expected, reinforcing the belief among investors that U.S. interest rates may not fall much this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEB7IJ22Q5OSTCUZINHVNORLW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[激进分子巴林顿敦促制造商 TriMas 考虑出售公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[激进投资者巴林顿资本集团（Barington Capital Group）希望 TriMas 对各种方案进行战略审查，包括可能出售整个公司，并在信中称，聘请财务顾问比寻找新首席执行官更重要。【原文：Activist investor Barington Capital Group wants TriMas to launch a strategic review of options, including the possible sale of the entire company, arguing in a letter that hiring a financial adviser is a higher priority than finding a new CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/activist-barington-urges-manufacturer-trimas-consider-sale-company-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUZ7OZYXYBO4HDMO5L3OJE5QLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫：经济强劲、安全资产需求推动美国在资本流动中占据主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周五表示，COVID 事件后美国经济的强劲复苏以及对避险投资的追求帮助提升了美国在全球资金流动中的主导地位，而制造业激励措施则导致了外国直接投资的激增。【原文：The strength of the U.S. economic recovery post-COVID and a quest for safe-haven investments helped boost U.S. dominance of global financial flows, while manufacturing incentives led to a surge in foreign direct investment, the White House said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/strong-economy-safe-asset-demand-boosted-us-dominance-capital-flows-white-house-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQU6I5U6FFKTHDVFLIGMVLITCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>