<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:26:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:23:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Match Group forecasts upbeat revenue as turnaround gains traction]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tinder parent Match Group forecast first-quarter revenue above estimates, signaling early gains from its turnaround push.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/match-group-forecasts-upbeat-revenue-turnaround-gains-traction-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4H3QKRR6JL27MO6JJYKE5QM6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take-Two raises annual bookings forecast]]></title><description><![CDATA[Take-Two Interactive raised its annual bookings forecast on Tuesday, betting on strong sales of its premium sports, action and mobile titles as it gears up to launch the highly-awaited "Grand Theft Auto VI" this year.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/take-two-raises-annual-bookings-forecast-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FPZYSIFLVNM5C2Y3WSUBU7TYI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Instruments in advanced talks to buy chip designer Silicon Laboratories, FT reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Texas Instruments is in advanced talks to buy chip designer Silicon Laboratories for about $7 billion, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/texas-instruments-advanced-talks-buy-chip-designer-silicon-laboratories-ft-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CYNQWMHYRO2TPDDRQOYCSEECQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amgen quarterly results beat Street estimates on higher sales, lower tax rate]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amgen on Tuesday reported fourth-quarter financial results that came in ahead of Wall Street expectations, driven by a 7% increase in drug sales and a lower tax rate.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/amgen-quarterly-results-beat-street-estimates-higher-sales-lower-tax-rate-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKNUDR2GDJIRVE5ZWJPACY3UNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lumen forecasts upbeat free cash flow, sees rising adoption of its digital products]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lumen Technologies forecast annual free cash flow exceeding Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, after posting a surprise adjusted profit in the fourth quarter, driven by strong demand for its connectivity solutions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/lumen-forecasts-upbeat-free-cash-flow-sees-rising-adoption-its-digital-products-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQBZL5LGJFIYNLS737W6G57OLA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US files appeal in Google search case, court filing shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. government and a majority of U.S. states on Tuesday said they will appeal the outcome of a landmark antitrust case against Alphabet's Google, according to court papers.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-states-file-appeal-google-search-case-court-filing-shows-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GS6WC37XM5IMBD4VJF6QESMBJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:59:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: KKR prepares OPI owner Wella Company for US IPO, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Investment firm KKR is preparing OPI nail polish owner Wella Company for an initial public offering in the U.S. as soon as this year that could value the global beauty company at meaningfully more than the $4.3 billion KKR paid for it, according to sources familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/kkr-prepares-opi-owner-wella-company-us-ipo-sources-say-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWXVG4PBKZLCPO6NUCYBZ6UKVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:54:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Musk loses bid to dismiss SEC lawsuit over Twitter stake]]></title><description><![CDATA[A federal judge on Tuesday rejected Elon Musk's bid to dismiss a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission lawsuit claiming he waited too long to disclose his purchases of Twitter shares in 2022.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/musk-loses-bid-dismiss-sec-lawsuit-over-twitter-stake-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBBPCUDJPBKB5BTPSTPUF4SVBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:52:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ChatGPT down for thousands of users in US, Downdetector shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[ChatGPT was down for thousands of users in the U.S. on Tuesday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chatgpt-down-thousands-users-us-downdetector-shows-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FX4NVS3QMFLAHP6RM2YJCYS4OU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:49:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia-backed UK AI firm Nscale hires banks for IPO, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia -backed British artificial intelligence group Nscale Global Holdings has hired Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan to prepare for an initial public offering, people familiar with the matter said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-backed-uk-ai-firm-nscale-hires-banks-ipo-sources-say-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QER3JNAKUZIP3NIATXJIYU5HBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kaiser readies for pharmacy, lab worker strike as nurse walkout continues]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kaiser Permanente urged members on Tuesday to get laboratory tests done this week after unions representing pharmacy and lab workers filed to begin striking in Southern California on Monday and an ongoing strike by thousands of nurses and other health workers continued into a second week.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/kaiser-readies-pharmacy-lab-worker-strike-nurse-walkout-continues-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCBNOY4T5JMUNJFTM36WDH5IG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:38:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Zealand's Synlait Milk expects first-half loss on high costs, operational woes]]></title><description><![CDATA[New Zealand's Synlait Milk said on Wednesday it expects to post a loss for the first half of fiscal 2026 as higher costs, operational impacts and lower relative returns from its commodities portfolio hit earnings.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-synlait-milk-expects-first-half-loss-high-costs-operational-woes-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5FGRNURY5MBZHKB54SZJ7HIFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia will consider investing in OpenAI IPO, CEO Huang tells CNBC]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia would consider investing in OpenAI's next fundraising round and also in the startup's eventual IPO, CEO Jensen Huang told CNBC in an interview on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-will-consider-investing-openai-ipo-ceo-huang-tells-cnbc-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2T63ZXXQYZOZLCD7GZLBTDFUOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:11:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some 30 countries want to join critical minerals club, US Interior Secretary Burgum says]]></title><description><![CDATA[About 30 countries want to join a club of allies and partners on trading critical minerals to reduce reliance on China, U.S. Interior Secretary Doug Burgum told a conference on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/some-30-countries-want-join-critical-minerals-club-us-interior-secretary-burgum-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFOCXBMBKNIK3PSREZERR7YICE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Altman dismisses Moltbook as likely fad, backs the tech behind it]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman on Tuesday played down the viral AI social network Moltbook as a likely fad, but he said the technology that let bots act on their own offered a glimpse of the future.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-ceo-altman-dismisses-moltbook-likely-fad-backs-tech-behind-it-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOQNBF2AE5PF7CMDN7VALTVO7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senator says AT&T, Verizon blocking release of Salt Typhoon security assessment reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Democratic Senator Maria Cantwell on Tuesday said Verizon and AT&amp;T are blocking release of key documents about an alleged massive Chinese spying operation that infiltrated U.S. telecommunications networks known as Salt Typhoon and wants their CEOs to appear before Congress to answer questions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/senator-says-att-verizon-blocking-release-salt-typhoon-security-assessment-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKFSTGYWDNLPZIF5VLRRBZQUHI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Griffin says US dollar has lost some shine]]></title><description><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Ken Griffin said on Tuesday that he believed the U.S. dollar had lost some of its luster with investors in the last 12 months.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/billionaire-investor-griffin-says-us-dollar-has-lost-some-shine-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXMW573CRNPBVIEO6ZWSNZEE2M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:57:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investors ramp up bets on steeper yield curve under Warsh-led Fed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Investors are ramping up bets on higher long‑dated Treasury yields and a steeper yield curve as incoming Federal Reserve Chair Kevin Warsh is expected to press for interest rate cuts while shrinking the U.S. central bank's balance sheet.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-ramp-up-bets-steeper-yield-curve-under-warsh-led-fed-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEVUVRV6NRI25JPN4HLDBP43W4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:38:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aviation automation firm Skyryse hits over $1 billion valuation in latest funding round]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. aviation technology company Skyryse said on Tuesday it raised $300 million in a funding round that valued it at $1.15 billion.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/aviation-automation-firm-skyryse-hits-over-1-billion-valuation-latest-funding-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4KM6NPKDZJ2DEYWN3VJE3CZQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Obesity stocks slump on Novo's underwhelming 2026 sales forecast]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shares of obesity drugmakers and developers slid on Tuesday after Novo Nordisk forecast a sharper-than-expected sales decline for 2026, underscoring intensifying competition in the blockbuster weight-loss market.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/obesity-stocks-slump-novos-underwhelming-2026-sales-forecast-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUTV5LOMVNJT3JR3CVJTNDL7CI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:27:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔首席执行官表示公司将生产GPU，并已聘请首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔首席执行官陈立武周二表示，该公司计划生产图形处理器（GPU），该类芯片由英伟达公司推广普及。【原文：Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan on Tuesday said the company plans to build graphics processing units (GPUs), the category of chip popularized by Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-ceo-says-company-will-make-gpus-has-hired-lead-executive-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7IOCRPBD5JYDDS7AHL6JVG2IE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US soon to issue general license for oil production in Venezuela, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. government is working to issue as early as this week a general license allowing companies to produce oil and gas in Venezuela, as Washington seeks to encourage expanded output in the OPEC nation since capturing its leader, three sources close to the matter told Reuters.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-soon-license-expanded-oil-production-venezuela-sources-say-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBL3MAC7JROEFIENAXRQKDORC4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:16:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，随着美国收紧签证政策，谷歌母公司Alphabet计划在印度进行大规模扩张。]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周二报道称，谷歌母公司Alphabet计划大幅扩大在印度的业务规模，可能在印度科技中心班加罗尔租用数百万平方英尺的新办公空间。【原文：Google-parent Alphabet is planning to dramatically expand its presence in India, with the possibility of taking millions of square feet in new office space in Bengaluru, India's tech hub, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/alphabet-plans-major-india-expansion-us-tightens-visa-rules-bloomberg-news-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMRCK7MIL5MN3LXIUISZRCXP3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waymo将捍卫自动驾驶安全记录，并警示中国竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动驾驶公司Waymo将于周三在美国参议院商务委员会听证会上为其安全记录辩护。此前联邦机构已就多起事故展开调查，包括一辆自动驾驶汽车在小学附近撞伤儿童，以及自动驾驶出租车在停靠的校车上下车时驶过现场的事件。【原文：Self-driving company Waymo on Wednesday will defend its safety record before the U.S. Senate Commerce Committee after federal agencies opened investigations into a vehicle striking a child near an elementary school and incidents involving robotaxis driving past were loading or unloading parked school buses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/waymo-defend-self-driving-safety-record-warn-china-competition-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGEV53KWONPALPIGTLSB5I5DXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:45:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油厂努力消化委内瑞拉原油进口的突然激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[据交易员和航运数据显示，自上月委内瑞拉与美国达成20亿美元的旗舰供应协议以来，美国墨西哥湾沿岸的炼油商正努力消化委内瑞拉原油运量的激增，这给油价带来压力，并导致部分原油滞销。【原文：Oil refiners on the U.S. Gulf Coast are struggling to absorb a rapid surge in Venezuelan crude shipments since last month's flagship $2 billion supply deal between Caracas and Washington, pressuring prices and leaving some volumes unsold, according to traders and shipping data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refiners-struggle-absorb-sudden-surge-venezuelan-oil-imports-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMUJ2NSJ7ZPJRIL7XUTMSYN4GY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德警告称，特朗普政府对药品价格的严厉打击将对其利润和销售额造成冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德周二警告称，今年其减肥药Wegovy的利润和销售额可能下滑多达13%，这将是该药数年来的首次下滑。作为减肥药领域的先驱，该公司正努力从竞争对手礼来手中夺回市场份额，此次预警对其构成新的打击。【原文：Wegovy maker Novo Nordisk warned on Tuesday that profits and sales could drop as much as 13% this year, the first declines in years, in a new setback for the obesity drug pioneer as it struggles to claw back market share from rival Eli Lilly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/novo-nordisk-warns-2026-sales-decline-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7B5JBFJTQBPFVJBIHHGFADICCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:59:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁激进投资者佩尔茨对更多收购持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者纳尔逊·佩尔茨周二表示，他正寻求回归其创立的Trian基金管理公司的初衷，未来可能直接收购更多公司。【原文：Nelson Peltz is looking to go back to his roots with Trian Fund Management and could buy more companies outright in the future, the billionaire investor said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/billionaire-activist-investor-peltz-open-more-buyouts-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPNIC5LQ35IEZP47SQZOBLW5B4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员称欧洲必须掌控关键技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟金融服务专员周二表示，欧洲必须掌控支撑该地区经济的关键技术，此言呼应了日益高涨的呼声——要求欧盟减少对美国科技巨头的依赖。【原文：Europe must keep control over key technologies that underpin the region's economies, the European Union's Financial Services Commissioner said on Tuesday, adding to growing calls for the bloc to be less reliant on U.S.-based technology giants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/europe-must-keep-control-key-technologies-says-eu-commissioner-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQ6NCMBF5VKIPHYJNECE3SSONU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑石集团的格雷表示，人工智能带来的颠覆性风险是我们最优先考虑的事项。]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大另类资产管理公司黑石集团总裁兼首席运营官乔恩·格雷周二表示，人工智能发展对企业的颠覆性影响是该集团"首要关注事项"。【原文：Disruption to businesses from artificial intelligence development is "top of the page" for Blackstone , the world's largest alternative asset manager, its president and chief operating officer Jon Gray said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackstones-gray-says-ai-disruption-risk-is-top-page-us-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AS4AR7WKCNLHVFUNCCWQLYIGOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帕兰蒂尔股价反弹，此前美国国防开支推动其创纪录季度业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘交易中，Palantir Technologies股价飙升6.9%，投资者押注该公司军用级人工智能工具与服务。此前该公司报告季度销售额激增，得益于美国国防开支的增长。【原文：Shares of Palantir Technologies jumped 6.9% in early trading on Tuesday as investors bet on the company's military-grade AI tools and services after it reported a surge in quarterly sales, boosted by rising U.S. defense spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/palantir-rallies-after-bumper-quarter-fueled-by-us-defense-spending-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7BVST33N5N2RDTVPHM4NCKIY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>