<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:05:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:05:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Pemex 计划令等待数十亿美元逾期付款的供应商失望]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥一家代表全球油田服务公司的协会负责人周四表示，尽管官方承诺加快付款速度，但墨西哥国家石油公司（Pemex）的新业务计划缺乏解决其与供应商之间巨额债务的具体措施。
AMESPAC协会主席拉斐尔-埃斯皮诺（Rafael Espino）告诉路透社记者，在周二与财政部、能源部和Pemex公司官员举行的会议上，没有提到该公司将如何偿还2024年和2025年上半年已完成工作的债务。
埃斯皮诺说，截至 6 月底，AMESPAC 成员被拖欠了约 650 亿比索（约合 34.9 亿美元）的工程款，而这些工程款甚至尚未开具发票。
"埃斯皮诺在接受采访时说："这令人失望，因为没有具体提及 2024 年的债务。"如果我们不得不等待用未来的现金流来偿还......这笔债务将继续得不到偿还，直接影响的将是生产"。
不过，埃斯皮诺补充说，与会官员表示，墨西哥石油公司将加快付款速度，不会让发票账龄超过两个月，并预计手头将有更多现金。这些现金将来自较低的税负、最近发行的 120 亿美元债务以及新设立的用于 2025 年项目的 130 亿美元特别基金。
Pemex 欠下了约 230 亿美元的供应商债务和近 1000 亿美元的金融债务，尽管近年来政府为其履行债务提供了数十亿美元的支持。
虽然支付了一些款项并经常做出承诺，但债务仍在不断累积，给服务供应商造成了前所未有的支付危机。
埃斯皮诺说，AMESPAC 对该计划表示欢迎，但正在寻求与当局建立一个正式的工作组，以了解新的 2025 年投资工具及其相关服务付款的规则、时间表和资格。
该协会认为，偿还未偿债务对于重新启用闲置设备和帮助实现墨西哥原油日产量 180 万桶的目标是必要的，而这一目标在很大程度上依赖于墨西哥石油公司。
AMESPAC 的成员包括全球最大的四家能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）、哈里伯顿（Halliburton）、威德福（Weatherford）和 SLB，以及采矿和运输集团墨西哥集团（Grupo Mexico）。
最近，大亨卡洛斯-斯利姆（Carlos Slim）控制的卡索集团（Grupo Carso）报告称，Pemex 欠其各种服务费超过 7 亿美元，其中一些债务可追溯到两年前。
Grupo Mexico 的一家子公司报告称，由于拖欠款项，它已暂时停止了四个平台的开采，而哈里伯顿公司也表示，它与 Pemex 的付款问题仍未解决。
(1 美元 = 18.6360 墨西哥比索）【原文：The head of an association representing global oilfield service firms in Mexico said on Thursday that a new business plan for state oil company Pemex lacks concrete measures to address its massive debt with suppliers, despite official promises to speed up payments.
Rafael Espino, president of the AMESPAC association, told Reuters that in a Tuesday meeting with officials from the finance and energy ministries and Pemex, there was no mention of how the company would pay down debts for work already performed in 2024 and the first half of 2025.
As of the end of June, Espino said, AMESPAC members were owed about 65 billion pesos ($3.49 billion) for work that has not yet even been invoiced.
"It was a disappointment because there was no specific reference to the 2024 debts," Espino said in an interview. "If we have to wait for it to be paid with future cash flow... this debt will continue to go unpaid and the immediate effect will be on production."
However, Espino added that officials at the meeting said Pemex would speed up payments, not let invoices age beyond two months, and that it expects to have more cash on hand. This would come from a lower tax burden, a recent $12 billion debt issuance, and a new $13 billion special fund for 2025 projects.
Pemex is saddled with supplier debts of around $23 billion and financial debt of nearly $100 billion, despite receiving billions in government support in recent years to meet its obligations.
While making some payments and frequent promises, the debts have continued to accumulate, creating an unprecedented payment crisis for service providers.
Espino said AMESPAC welcomes the plan but is seeking to establish a formal working group with authorities to understand the rules, timeline and eligibility for the new 2025 investment vehicle and its associated service payments.
The association argues that paying off outstanding debts is necessary to reactivate idled equipment and help meet Mexico's national crude production target of 1.8 million barrels per day (bpd), a goal heavily reliant on Pemex.
AMESPAC members include four of the world's largest energy services firms Baker Hughes , Halliburton , Weatherford , and SLB , and mining and transportation conglomerate Grupo Mexico .
Recently, Grupo Carso - controlled by tycoon Carlos Slim - reported that Pemex owes it more than $700 million for various services, with some debts dating back two years.
A subsidiary of Grupo Mexico reported it had temporarily halted four platforms due to non-payment, and Halliburton has stated its payment issues with Pemex remain unresolved.
($1 = 18.6360 Mexican pesos)】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pemex-plan-disappoints-suppliers-awaiting-billions-overdue-payments-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMKRL72N3NOEHMKMRFTKCLM56I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GoDaddy 季度收入略超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受互联网托管服务需求稳定的影响，GoDaddy 周四公布的第二季度营收略高于华尔街预期。【原文：GoDaddy marginally beat Wall Street expectations for second quarter revenue on Thursday, aided by steady demand for its internet hosting services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/godaddy-marginally-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIQV6MUTCVOELPB67O4WD2ZDNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微芯科技第一季度净销售额和利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商微芯科技（Microchip Technology）周四公布的第一季度净销售额和利润超出分析师预期，主要得益于客户清理了过剩库存。【原文：Chipmaker Microchip Technology beat analysts' estimates for first-quarter net sales and profit on Thursday, helped by customers clearing excess inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microchip-tech-beats-q1-net-sales-profit-estimates-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEUNQA4URNNABGUFHR5WQOTOWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府将终止 70 亿美元的太阳能补助计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护署署长李-泽尔丁（Lee Zeldin）周四在 X 上发表文章称，美国环境保护署将终止拜登时代的一项耗资 70 亿美元的拨款计划，该计划旨在将太阳能推广到低收入社区。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency will end a $7 billion Biden-era grant program to expand solar energy to low-income communities, Administrator Lee Zeldin said in a post on X on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trump-administration-will-end-7-billion-solar-energy-grant-program-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OVVKLGGVTNJJNOBOENJZ6BTCYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:52:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Atlassian 预测季度收入下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于企业客户在严峻的经济形势下削减了云软件服务支出，Atlassian 周四预计第一季度营收低于预期。【原文：Atlassian projected first-quarter revenue below estimates on Thursday, as enterprise customers cut spending on cloud software services in a tough economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/atlassian-forecasts-downbeat-quarterly-revenue-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AS2FGHE7WFNCVN3KC7ZTXDJZKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:42:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MSCI 宣布调整股票指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利资本国际公司（MSCI）周四表示，将从其广受关注的 ACWI 股票指数中增加 42 种证券，删除 56 种证券。【原文：MSCI said on Thursday it will add 42 securities and delete 56 from its widely followed ACWI equity index .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/msci-announces-changes-equity-indexes-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NP4VQFNS2BJ7FLVZHKHWCRLIOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:33:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼解决与《曼达洛人》女演员吉娜-卡拉诺的法律纠纷]]></title><description><![CDATA[卢卡斯影业公司（Lucasfilm）发言人周四表示，迪士尼公司已经解决了与演员吉娜-卡拉诺（Gina Carano）之间关于她被 "星球大战 "流媒体电视剧《曼达洛人》（The Mandalorian）解雇的法律纠纷。【原文：Walt Disney has resolved a legal dispute with actor Gina Carano over her firing from the "Star Wars" streaming TV series "The Mandalorian," a spokesperson for Lucasfilm said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/disney-resolves-legal-dispute-with-mandalorian-actress-gina-carano-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORFTJQBQ3ZNIXGHXWLXMDDO4C4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:33:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诉讼指控苹果公司窃取商业机密创建 Apple Pay]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司被一家德克萨斯州公司起诉，该公司指控这家 iPhone 制造商窃取了其技术，用来创建利润丰厚的移动钱包 Apple Pay。【原文：Apple has been sued by a Texas company that accused the iPhone maker of stealing its technology to create its lucrative mobile wallet Apple Pay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/lawsuit-accuses-apple-stealing-trade-secrets-create-apple-pay-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YX52B6FOI5KO3CPEQMM2AC7LAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拟任美联储理事米兰建议加强对他将加入的中央银行的政治控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济顾问委员会主席斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）曾抨击行政部门与美国联邦储备局之间的 "旋转门"，在唐纳德-特朗普总统提名他进入米兰希望彻底改革的机构--美国联邦储备局理事会之后，他现在可能就要走进这扇 "旋转门 "了。【原文：Having railed against the "revolving door" between the executive branch and the U.S. Federal Reserve, Council of Economic Advisers chair Stephen Miran may now be walking through it after President Donald Trump nominated him to the Board of Governors of an institution Miran would like to radically overhaul.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/proposed-fed-governor-miran-recommended-tighter-political-control-central-bank-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T66PWIKV5BLJBCRIBFWVM3SN5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：关税、美联储担忧与科技乐观情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量。【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCUWL3QJFRKQFAT2MYSNZIYADI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:04:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因网络安全需求，Gen Digital 上调年度收入和利润展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[受益于网络安全工具的强劲需求，杀毒软件供应商 Gen Digital 周四上调了年度营收和利润目标。【原文：Antivirus software provider Gen Digital raised its annual revenue and profit targets on Thursday, benefiting from strong demand for its cybersecurity tools.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gen-digital-raises-annual-revenue-profit-outlook-cybersecurity-demand-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBCHBYHBC5M7BJCIFKULTJ3XBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chime 在美国上市后首次盈利，收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受数字银行和金融服务强劲需求的推动，Chime 周四公布了在美国上市后的首份财报，第二季度营收超出华尔街预期。【原文：Chime beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue on Thursday, driven by strong demand for its digital banking and financial services, in its first results following a blockbuster U.S. listing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/chime-beats-revenue-estimates-first-earnings-since-blowout-us-ipo-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LO7KCJ7MUVP7PHDLT37JUW6GMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solventum 上调年度利润预期，原因是手术设备业务增长强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[受伤口护理和手术消毒产品销售强劲以及支出减少的影响，医疗设备制造商索万特公司周四上调了全年调整后利润预期。【原文：Medical device maker Solventum raised full-year adjusted profit forecast on Thursday, driven by strong sales of its wound care and surgical sterilization products alongside lower expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/solventum-raises-annual-profit-forecast-strength-surgical-equipment-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TT2FN3WFCVKHLEB5IJSA737QUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点特朗普挑选斯蒂芬-米兰填补美联储董事会空缺职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，他将提名经济顾问委员会主席斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）担任美联储理事。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday said he will nominate Council of Economic Advisers Chairman Stephen Miran to serve as a Federal Reserve governor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-trump-picks-stephen-miran-fill-open-spot-fed-board-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNAW2BPXLJKSPKMO3C5HBTQ6N4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:51:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：美国对一公斤重的金条征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引海关边境保护局的一封信报道称，美国已对进口一公斤重的金条征收关税。【原文：The United States has imposed tariffs on imports of one-kilo gold bars, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing a letter from Customs Border Protection.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/us-imposes-tariffs-one-kilo-gold-bars-ft-reports-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2HR4SGYEJLU5O75RNLTZVZPWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[稀土产量增加，MP 材料公司季度亏损低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[MP Materials 公司周四公布的第二季度亏损额小于预期，原因是美国稀土矿商受益于需求上升带来的产量增加。【原文：MP Materials posted a smaller-than-expected second-quarter loss Thursday, as the U.S. rare earths miner benefited from higher production amid rising demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mp-materials-quarterly-loss-smaller-than-expected-higher-rare-earths-production-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSXTFBE2JJK5JM2OTQZFQDVJNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能工具推动广告支出，Pinterest 营收超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，Pinterest 的第二季度营收超过了分析师的预期，原因是人工智能广告工具推动了该平台营销支出的增长。【原文：Pinterest beat analysts' estimates for second-quarter revenue on Thursday, as increased marketing spend on the platform was fueled by its artificial intelligence-powered advertising tools.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pinterest-beats-revenue-estimates-ai-tools-drive-ad-spend-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKIAWQ3BIFJ27KLMPWORNIKDXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:28:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德公司季度利润持平，上调全年业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司（Gilead Sciences）周四公布的季度财报显示，该公司季度盈利持平，收入略有增长，但上调了全年财务展望，主要原因是艾滋病药物的销售好于预期。【原文：Gilead Sciences on Thursday reported flat quarterly earnings on slightly higher revenue and raised its full-year financial outlook due largely to better-than-expected sales of HIV drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/gilead-posts-flat-quarterly-profit-raises-full-year-outlook-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIF6PPWLONIVXBWLQ4YIAFR4SQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赌徒连胜结束，FanDuel 所有者上调盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[FanDuel 的所有者 Flutter 周四上调了全年利润增长预期，此前美国赌客长达六个月的连胜势头在好于预期的第二季度急转直下，转而有利于博彩公司。【原文：FanDuel-owner Flutter raised its forecast for full-year profit growth on Thursday after a six-month-long winning streak for U.S. gamblers swung sharply back in the favour of bookmakers during a better-than-expected second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fanduel-owner-raises-profit-forecast-gamblers-winning-streak-ends-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UO425UNJZ5IM3CBDQFLXN2KXAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:22:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国石油生产商 EOG 第二季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源生产商 EOG Resources 周四公布的第二季度利润超出预期，原因是产量的增长帮助该公司抵消了原油价格的下跌。【原文：EOG Resources beat estimates for second-quarter profit on Thursday, as a rise in output helped the U.S. energy producer offset a drop in crude oil prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-producer-eog-beats-second-quarter-profit-estimates-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67RDQIKWOVK55IWCC47BG4SYEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:21:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[演唱会需求火爆，Live Nation 收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受演唱会需求强劲的推动，Ticketmaster 母公司 Live Nation Entertainment 周四公布的第二季度营收超出华尔街预期。【原文：Ticketmaster-parent Live Nation Entertainment beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue on Thursday, driven by strong demand for concerts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/live-nation-beats-revenue-estimates-red-hot-concert-demand-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LA3AF5WRD5MQVI4NBRE2AKINLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国旅游需求复苏，Expedia 季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Expedia 周四报告称，受美国需求复苏的帮助，该公司第二季度利润增长，使得这家在线旅游公司的股价在盘后交易中上涨了 12%。【原文：Expedia reported a rise in its second-quarter profit on Thursday, helped by a recovery of demand in the United States, sending the online travel company's shares up 12% in extended trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/expedias-quarterly-profit-rises-us-travel-demand-recovers-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4J7VO6GEFVJSDJX3CMLDFWDJ2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:14:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者支出回暖，百佳超市上调年度盈利预期，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，布洛克公司报告第二季度收入增长，并上调了对全年毛利润的预期，这家支付公司受到了消费者支出恢复性增长的帮助，股价在延时交易中上涨了 12%。【原文：Block reported a rise in second-quarter income and raised its expectations for annual gross profit on Thursday, as the payments firm was helped by resilient consumer spending, lifting its shares 12% higher in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/block-raises-annual-profit-forecast-resilient-consumer-spending-shares-jump-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDICRKUNLRKUPBSVHPIY4GVKS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署针对银行歧视申诉的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四签署了一项行政命令，针对银行的歧视性做法。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Thursday that targeted banks over what his administration says are discriminatory practices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-signs-order-targeting-banks-over-claims-discrimination-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4II5SGYRNPI3DED2TSW5BSJMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:03:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因网络安全需求，Akamai上调年度业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Akamai Technologies周四上调了年度收入和利润预期，这主要得益于对其云基础设施服务和内容分发网络产品的稳定需求。【原文：Akamai Technologies raised its annual revenue and profit forecast on Thursday, helped by steady demand for its cloud infrastructure services and content delivery network offerings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/akamai-raises-annual-results-forecast-cybersecurity-demand-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTEPIYOGLRP6JIA3F5TWXDEJSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《美国汽车新闻》报道，福特将电动皮卡和厢式货车的生产推迟到 2028 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国《汽车新闻》周四援引知情人士的话报道称，福特汽车正在推迟推出两款下一代电动汽车，因为该公司正将重点转向更小、更经济实惠的车型。【原文：Ford Motor is delaying the launch of two next-generation electric vehicles as it shifts focus to smaller and more affordable models, Automotive News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-delays-electric-pickup-van-2028-automotive-news-reports-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLCQXY5X6BLHXL4I7LWGGSSZ3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:54:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名米兰临时担任美联储理事]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普表示，米兰的任期将持续到 2026 年 1 月 31 日，同时他将继续寻找永久继任者。【原文：Trump said Miran will serve in the role until January 31, 2026, while he continues a search for a permanent replacement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-nominates-miran-temporarily-serve-fed-board-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORIYYXOMGRNEVFJTNQNZCPAEJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:53:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于国内供应量低迷，美国 7 月原油出口量创四年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于国内供应量低，以及亚洲和欧洲买家找到了更便宜的替代品，美国原油出口在7月份降至近四年来的最低水平，这削弱了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普推动更多外国购买美国能源供应的努力。【原文：U.S. crude oil exports eased in July to the lowest levels in nearly four years on low domestic supplies and as Asian and European buyers found cheaper alternatives, undermining U.S. President Donald Trump's push for more foreign countries to purchase U.S. energy supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-exports-hit-four-year-low-july-low-domestic-supplies-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GBQSBP33VLUVO66RXENYDCFKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:47:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，白宫准备提名斯蒂芬-米兰为美联储理事]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四援引知情人士的话报道，白宫正准备让美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名经济顾问委员会主席斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）担任美联储理事。【原文：The White House is preparing for U.S. President Donald Trump to nominate Council of Economic Advisers Chairman Stephen Miran to serve as a Federal Reserve governor, Bloomberg reported on Thursday, citing a person familiar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-prepares-stephen-miran-be-nominated-fed-board-bloomberg-reports-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVGVKADSM5OUJFGDHIDGLHEQ44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:40:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者博弈市场对美联储主席更换人选的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着特朗普总统缩小下一任美联储主席的候选名单，投资者和策略师正在密切分析市场对每一位准备在鲍威尔任期结束后接替他的潜在提名人可能作出的一系列反应。【原文：As President Trump narrows his shortlist for the next Federal Reserve chair, investors and strategists are closely analyzing the range of possible market reactions to each potential nominee poised to replace Jerome Powell when his term is over.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-game-out-market-reaction-fed-chair-replacement-favorites-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZJ22ZDUTBPMND2CE3TF6MNQGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>