<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:37:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:37:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓和隆丁将申请阿根廷激励措施，但其他矿商担心错过机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[必和必拓（BHP）和伦丁集团（Lundin）的高管们在本周举行的一次矿业会议上表示，必和必拓和伦丁计划很快为其维库纳铜矿项目申请阿根廷新的投资激励计划，但其他矿商担心，在该计划一年后的截止日期之前，他们可能会被排除在外。【原文：BHP and Lundin plan to soon apply for a new Argentine investment incentives scheme for their Vicuna copper project, but other miners fear they may get left out before the program's cut-off date a year from now, executives said at a mining conference this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bhp-lundin-will-request-argentina-incentives-other-miners-fear-missing-out-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGCDJTVOYVIL5HRHFSCW4EHRRI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大将向木材行业提供高达 12 亿加元的援助以应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周二表示，加拿大将提供高达12亿加元（8.7亿美元）的资金，帮助软木木材生产商应对美国的反补贴和反倾销税。【原文：Canada will provide up to C$1.2 billion ($870 million) to help softwood lumber producers deal with U.S. countervailing and anti-dumping duties, Prime Minister Mark Carney said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-give-lumber-industry-up-c12-billion-aid-cope-with-us-duties-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNOE2ILXI5ONTBCMBWD4U66RRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡尼表示，加拿大将帮助木材行业应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社渥太华8月5日电）加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周二表示，加拿大将提供高达12亿加元的资金，帮助软木木材生产商应对美国的反补贴和反倾销税。【原文：OTTAWA, Aug 5 (Reuters) - Canada will provide up to C$1.2 billion to help softwood lumber producers deal with U.S. countervailing and anti-dumping duties, Prime Minister Mark Carney said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/canada-help-lumber-industry-cope-with-us-tariffs-says-carney-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUM2LZWPPZMY3BNDGSTLIT7ZAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国石油公司在巴西发现大量油气资源，为 Equinor 公司的拍卖前景增添砝码]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国石油公司周一宣布在巴西近海桑托斯盆地发现了 25 年来全球最大的石油和天然气，这预示着 Equinor 在附近的利益以及对 10 月份该地区石油区块拍卖的强烈兴趣。【原文：BP's announcement on Monday of its largest global oil and gas discovery in 25 years in Brazil's offshore Santos basin bodes well for Equinor's nearby interests and strong appetite for an October auction of oil blocks in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bps-big-brazil-oil-gas-find-boosts-prospects-equinor-auction-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4P43D6K5HJMEDN4EB27ENBMFSQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Orange 将使用 OpenAI 的最新模型处理非洲语言]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国移动运营商 Orange 周二表示，它计划将 OpenAI 的最新人工智能模型用于非洲语言。【原文：French mobile operator Orange said on Tuesday it plans to use OpenAI's latest AI models with African languages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/orange-use-openais-latest-models-work-with-african-languages-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABT42CBUFJOMHAAZRGCWHQSUFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 发布专为在笔记本电脑上运行而优化的开放式推理模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周二表示，它已发布了两个开放重量级语言模型，这两个模型在高级推理方面表现出色，并经过优化，可在笔记本电脑上运行，其性能水平与其较小的专有推理模型类似。【原文：OpenAI said on Tuesday it has released two open-weight language models that excel in advanced reasoning and are optimized to run on laptops with performance levels similar to its smaller proprietary reasoning models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/openai-releases-open-weight-reasoning-models-optimized-running-laptops-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q24CT5QZ7BNGFH7V6P4PS4TGNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在线零售商 Zalando 在收购 About You 之后上调了 2025 年指导价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国在线时尚市场 Zalando 周二上调了 2025 年业绩预期，将新收购的 About You 纳入其中。【原文：German online fashion marketplace Zalando raised its 2025 guidance on Tuesday after adjusting its projections to include newly acquired About You .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/online-retailer-zalando-raises-2025-guidance-after-about-you-acquisition-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ2MMRDDC5JL7PJ7ZRLK3DTDAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国批评使用人工智能个性化机票价格，将展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）周二表示，交通部对使用人工智能制定个性化机票价格表示担忧，如果有人这样做，交通部将进行调查。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said Tuesday the department has concerns about the use of AI to set personalized airline ticket prices and will investigate if anyone does so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-criticizes-use-ai-personalize-airline-ticket-prices-would-investigate-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4QNOQQFMVJNDJPSCZ7ADW62GE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国高等级企业以更多股权和现金、更少债务为新并购融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家和投资者表示，今年以来，评级最高的美国公司主要通过股权和现金而不是债务为其收购融资，即使并购活动和降息希望升温，这些公司也可能继续这样做。【原文：Top-rated U.S. companies have financed their acquisitions mostly with equity and cash instead of debt this year, and could continue doing so even as M&amp;A activity and hopes of interest rate cuts rise, bankers and investors said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/high-grade-us-firms-finance-new-ma-with-more-equity-cash-less-debt-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74VLHAWEGRIPLFW3VW7JEHNZ3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:32:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从原料成本到需求下滑，关税进一步抑制企业盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）发动的关税战给各企业带来了更多的痛苦，卡特彼勒（Caterpillar）、万豪（Marriott）等行业领军企业周二指出，需求疲软，价格上涨。【原文：Companies across the corporate spectrum revealed more pain from the cost of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff war, with bellwethers Caterpillar, Marriott and others on Tuesday noting weaker demand and higher prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wrapup-ingredient-costs-sagging-demand-tariffs-further-pinch-company-earnings-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWZ6HCMFQFNP5LEV5FC4TEFWKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shein和Temu在南非时装市场上超越全球零售巨头]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一份报告显示，中国创办的电子商务零售商Shein和Temu已占据南非零售、服装、纺织品、鞋类和皮革（CTFL）市场3.6%的份额，2024年的销售额将达到73亿兰特（约合4.05亿美元）。【原文：China-founded e-commerce retailers Shein and Temu have captured a combined 3.6% share of South Africa's retail, clothing, textile, footwear and leather (CTFL) market, accounting for 7.3 billion rand ($405 million) in sales in 2024, a report showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/shein-temu-outpace-global-retail-giants-south-africas-fashion-market-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSTDBRIGXFPX5DZ7IBOX33JBXU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:22:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥公布解决墨西哥石油公司（Pemex）债务问题、促进投资的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥政府周二宣布了一项计划，旨在使负债累累的国营石油公司墨西哥石油公司（Pemex）实现财政自给自足，并建立一个新的投资工具，努力稳定石油生产。【原文：Mexico's government on Tuesday announced a plan aimed at moving its highly indebted state oil company Pemex toward financial self-sufficiency, and the establishment of a new investment vehicle and efforts to stabilize oil production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-reveals-plans-address-pemex-debt-boost-investment-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLDSO7NJXFJK5O7QLRITVMMNYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员要求美国调查 DeepSeek 的数据安全问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[由七位美国共和党参议员组成的小组周二要求商务部评估 DeepSeek 等中国开源人工智能模型带来的潜在数据安全漏洞。【原文：A group of seven Republican U.S. senators on Tuesday asked the Commerce Department to evaluate potential data security vulnerabilities posed by Chinese open-source AI models like DeepSeek.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senators-ask-us-probe-data-security-issues-with-deepseek-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKZUTWSBKFM2RDG57O6EL53B7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国提出新的无人机规则，可能导致星巴克和亚马逊送货上门]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部正在提议制定新的规则，以加快无人机在操作员视线范围之外的部署速度，这是推进包裹递送等商业用途所需的关键变革。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department is proposing new rules to speed deployment of drones beyond the visual line of sight of operators, a key change needed to advance commercial uses like package deliveries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-proposes-new-drone-rules-that-could-lead-starbucks-amazon-deliveries-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3R74FCFJZOLPEBQYH45F765G4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 BRF 股东批准与 Marfrig 合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份证券文件显示，巴西家禽和猪肉加工商 BRF 的股东周三投票通过了与牛肉加工商 Marfrig 合并的提议。【原文：Shareholders in Brazilian poultry and pork processor BRF voted on Wednesday to approve a proposed merger with beefpacker Marfrig , according to a securities filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-brf-shareholders-approve-merger-with-marfrig-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2OR7N67BBN3JHCMV3RFXCFEM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储第二季度学生贷款问题增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于越来越多的学生贷款者和一些新购房者面临信贷挑战，第二季度家庭总债务水平有所上升。【原文：Total household debt levels rose during the second quarter as a growing number of student loan borrowers and some newer home borrowers faced rising credit challenges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/ny-fed-flags-rise-student-loan-borrowing-troubles-second-quarter-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDCZOLFOWROMROKDY443QXBS7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西经济已做好应对特朗普50%关税的准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西从美国进口的商品很快将成为唐纳德-特朗普总统征收的最高关税之一，但由于有大量豁免以及与中国更紧密的贸易关系，这不可能使拉美最大的经济体脱轨。【原文：Brazilian goods imported by the United States will soon carry one of the highest tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump, but that will not likely derail Latin America's largest economy, due to ample exemptions and stronger trade ties with China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-economy-ready-ride-out-trumps-50-tariff-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKIJ4OMOBZKN7GZYAMD6IGOQVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对美国经济数据的信任岌岌可危：易失难复]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）解雇美国劳工统计局局长的举动使人们对美国数据报告机制的信任岌岌可危，而人们对世界最大经济体健康状况的可靠诊断的需求却比以往任何时候都大。【原文：Donald Trump's move to fire the head of the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics has put trust in U.S. data reporting mechanisms on the line just as demand for reliable diagnoses of the health of the world's largest economy is bigger than ever.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/easy-lose-hard-restore-us-data-trust-line-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COSMBS7PQZMAFFE2BSCZFYE65Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[二叠纪石油前景黯淡，Diamondback 称应成为二叠纪的 "首选整合者]]></title><description><![CDATA[页岩钻探公司 Diamondback Energy 周二表示，随着页岩开采活动的放缓，该公司在以 260 亿美元与 Endeavor Energy 合并后将专注于股东回报，因此它仍将是二叠纪盆地的 "首选整合者"。【原文：Shale driller Diamondback Energy said on Tuesday it should remain the Permian Basin's "consolidator of choice" as shale activity slows and the company focuses on shareholder returns following its $26 billion merger with Endeavor Energy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/diamondback-says-it-should-be-permians-consolidator-choice-oil-outlook-dims-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWCZENZL6FNDNJIZBPIN7F3KXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:27:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国最初将对进口药品征收 "小额关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，美国将首先对药品进口征收 "小额关税"，然后在18个月内将关税提高到150%，最终提高到250%，以促进国内生产。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that the United States would initially place a "small tariff" on pharmaceutical imports before hiking it to 150% within 18 months and eventually to 250% in an effort to boost domestic production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-initially-impose-small-tariff-pharma-imports-trump-says-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7GD446IFNPTTK3ACL7N3FHMOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:26:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示，如果达成贸易协议，他将会见中国国家主席习近平]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，美国即将与中国达成贸易协议，如果协议达成，他将在年底前与中国外长习近平会面。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Tuesday the U.S. was close to a trade deal with China and that he would meet his Chinese counterpart Xi Jinping before the end of the year if an agreement is struck.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-he-will-meet-chinas-xi-if-trade-deal-is-struck-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZLI355D6NLSHEOS6XVFBM42SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISM数据显示，7月份美国服务业活动持平]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份，美国服务业活动出乎意料地表现平平，订单变化不大，就业进一步减弱，即使投入成本攀升至近三年来的最高点，这凸显了特朗普政府关税政策的不确定性对企业的持续拖累。【原文：U.S. services sector activity unexpectedly flatlined in July with little change in orders and a further weakening in employment even as input costs climbed by the most in nearly three years, underscoring the ongoing drag of uncertainty over the Trump administration's tariff policy on businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-services-activity-flatlined-july-ism-data-shows-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LA6AMFSTRMETFJ4BLSPN7XB7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构称，YouTube 和其他网站对虐待儿童材料 "视而不见]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚互联网监管机构称，全球最大的社交媒体公司仍对其平台上的在线儿童性虐待材料 "视而不见"，并称YouTube尤其对其询问反应迟钝。【原文：Australia’s internet watchdog has said the world’s biggest social media firms are still “turning a blind eye” to online child sex abuse material on their platforms, and said YouTube in particular had been unresponsive to its enquiries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-regulator-says-youtube-others-turning-blind-eye-child-abuse-material-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M644BI5HANJJTOQHTWKBOZKNO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[发电需求激增，康明斯季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卡车发动机制造商康明斯公司（Cummins Inc）周二公布的第二季度财报显示，由于发电系统需求强劲，该公司第二季度营收高于华尔街预期，使其股价在早盘交易中上涨了 4%。【原文：U.S. truck engine maker Cummins Inc on Tuesday reported second-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on strong demand for its power generation systems, sending its shares up 4% in early trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cummins-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-surging-power-generation-demand-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWEJGLYH6FPMBCFC3AEBNGEHNE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:49:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构批准 OpenAI、谷歌和 Anthropic 列入联邦人工智能供应商名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，美国政府的中央采购部门将 OpenAI 的 ChatGPT、谷歌的 Gemini 和 Anthropic 的 Claude 列入了批准的人工智能供应商名单，以加快政府机构的使用。【原文：The U.S. government's central purchasing arm on Tuesday added OpenAI's ChatGPT, Google's Gemini and Anthropic's Claude to a list of approved artificial intelligence vendors to speed use by government agencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-agency-approves-openai-google-anthropic-federal-ai-vendor-list-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XA3HU6SWC5MK7HRJSMV3HZDWLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:49:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行将美国小型股股票评级下调至 "不利 "评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行投资研究所周二将美国小盘股的评级从 "中性 "下调至 "不利"，指出其面临严重的关税风险和盈利疲软。【原文：Wells Fargo Investment Institute on Tuesday downgraded U.S. small-cap equities to "unfavorable" from "neutral", pointing to its heavy tariff exposure and weak earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wells-fargo-downgrades-us-small-cap-equities-unfavourable-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LDAS6DIDVKP3AMDLDZRNAS5JY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:44:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普抨击美联储，数据完整性影响美元预测：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二对外汇分析师进行的一项调查显示，由于对美联储独立性、官方统计数据可信度、财政债务膨胀和降息押注上升的担忧日益加剧，美元在未来几个月将持续走软。【原文：The U.S. dollar will weaken steadily over the coming months on mounting concerns over the Federal Reserve's independence, the credibility of official statistics, ballooning fiscal debt and rising bets on interest rate cuts, a Reuters survey of foreign exchange analysts showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-attacks-fed-data-integrity-weigh-us-dollar-forecasts-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FENACZV5RVJDXPGGPIKSZIV4PI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福克斯公司季度业绩超出预期，回购金额增加 50 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[福克斯公司周二公布的季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于广告业务、联盟费激增以及免费广告流媒体服务 Tubi 的持续增长。【原文：Fox Corp topped Wall Street estimates for quarterly revenue and profit on Tuesday, driven by a surge in advertising, affiliate fee and continued growth at its free ad-supported streaming service, Tubi.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fox-beats-quarterly-estimates-boosts-buyback-by-5-billion-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BP4FHOM7RN5PHLYDPPKQCD6DI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于货运量和海关费用增加，Expeditors 公布了乐观的业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，全球货运代理公司 Expeditors International of Washington 公布的第二季度利润和收入均高于华尔街预期，主要得益于空运和海运集装箱量的增加以及更高的海关费用。【原文：Global freight forwarder Expeditors International of Washington reported second-quarter profit and revenue above Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, helped by higher airfreight and ocean container volumes and bigger custom fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/expeditors-posts-upbeat-results-higher-freight-volumes-customs-fees-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7E3JELFQVL23JWFEOEAIV3JCA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数字医疗公司 eMed 聘用前 X 公司老板琳达-雅卡里诺担任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字医疗平台 eMed Population Health 周二表示，已任命社交媒体网站 X 的前首席执行官琳达-雅卡里诺（Linda Yaccarino）为首席执行官。【原文：Digital health platform eMed Population Health said on Tuesday it has appointed Linda Yaccarino, the former CEO of social media site X, as its chief executive officer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/digital-health-company-emed-taps-former-x-boss-linda-yaccarino-ceo-2025-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKWXCL5JNRIGRHJSN3ZPWPOTTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:06:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>