<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:09:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:09:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波兰电力系统去年12月遭遇大规模网络攻击未遂，部长称]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰能源部长周二表示，该国电力系统在去年12月最后一周遭遇了近年来最大规模的网络攻击，且此次攻击模式与以往不同。【原文：Poland's power system faced its largest cyberattack in years in the last week of December that also followed a different pattern, the country's energy minister said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/massive-cyberattack-polish-power-system-december-failed-minister-says-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFGM4QBLGRPAVDLQWDRY5TI3CE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼将向L3Harris火箭发动机业务投资10亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府将向L3Harris Technologies公司的火箭发动机业务投资10亿美元，以确保为"战斧"巡航导弹和"爱国者"拦截导弹等各类导弹提供急需的发动机稳定供应。【原文：The U.S. government will invest $1 billion in L3Harris Technologies' rocket motor business, guaranteeing a steady supply of the much-needed motors used in a wide range of missiles such as Tomahawks and Patriot interceptors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/pentagon-invest-1-billion-l3harris-rocket-motor-business-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YKV2B3ANJIF3MTMZBFK2UEMHU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普最新针对美联储的举措可能触发了导火索，鲍威尔背后正形成一股支持浪潮。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在多年抨击美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔后，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普对这位72岁的前投资银行家发起刑事调查，此举可能已触发危险信号。共和党议员和前高级政策制定者纷纷站队鲍威尔，而市场也发出警示：若总统动摇全球最重要中央银行的独立性，恐将引发强烈反弹。【原文：After years of berating Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, President Donald Trump may have hit a tripwire in launching a criminal probe of the 72-year-old former investment banker, with Republican lawmakers and former top policymakers rallying ​to Powell's side and markets hinting at potential blowback if the president undermines the independence of the world's most important central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/latest-trump-move-fed-may-have-hit-tripwire-with-rally-behind-powell-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USKPIG343ZJ23JJPAVCS7YV7LA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下跌，摩根大通财报与通胀数据即将公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周二小幅下挫，投资者正等待关键通胀数据以获取利率路径的线索，同时摩根大通即将公布的第四季度财报将拉开财报季序幕。【原文：U.S. stock index futures dipped on Tuesday, as investors awaited ‌crucial inflation data for clues on the interest rate trajectory, and fourth-quarter results from JPMorgan Chase that would mark the start of the earnings season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-dip-ahead-jpmorgan-earnings-inflation-data-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLDMDY2KINNIXICDBFZQ55DQTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对伊朗加征关税的威胁可能重启中美裂痕]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普威胁对与伊朗有贸易往来的国家征收25%的关税。【原文：Donald Trump threatened to slap a 25% tariff on countries that trade with Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-iran-tariff-threat-risks-reopening-china-rift-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FP2OVJ2VVBM7ZGGRC4A5DPFRNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:41:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本投资者在12月抛售海外资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本投资者12月成为外国债务的净卖方，因美国国债收益率上升；同时抛售外国股票，因高企的股价估值引发获利了结。【原文：Japanese investors were net sellers of foreign debt in December with U.S. Treasury yields rising, and also sold foreign equities as elevated stock valuations prompted profit-taking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japanese-investors-sell-foreign-assets-december-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4TU7DUAZZIQJJ4VHPR7T64VCU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球央行行长力挺美联储主席鲍威尔，此前特朗普曾对其发出威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA["我们完全支持美联储及其主席杰罗姆·H·鲍威尔，"欧洲央行、英国央行及其他九家机构的负责人表示。【原文："We stand in full solidarity with the Federal ‍Reserve System and its Chair Jerome H. Powell," the heads of the ⁠European Central Bank, the ‍Bank of England and nine other institutions ‌said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-central-bankers-defend-feds-powell-after-trump-threat-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDO77K73LZKOTEAEWMAZK44BPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:23:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德最新裁员计划将削减约250个岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大资产管理公司贝莱德将裁减数百个岗位，作为定期裁员计划的一部分以提升效率，该公司发言人向路透社透露。【原文：BlackRock , the world's largest asset manager, will cut hundreds of jobs as part of a regular round of layoffs to improve efficiency, a spokesperson for the company told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/blackrock-cut-around-250-jobs-latest-layoffs-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAQI24FODBOM5EOX73K4NEU7XY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:13:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺将于3月起在韩国销售基于吉利平台的Filante SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷诺周二宣布，其新款Filante车型将于3月起在韩国上市销售，并计划于2027年初前在拉丁美洲及海湾国家推出。【原文：Renault will sell its new Filante car in South Korea from March before launching sales in Latin American and Gulf countries by early 2027, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-sell-geely-based-filante-suv-south-korea-march-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3W2GVWLQENJK3CH2MMNXWNGMMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球央行行长计划发表声明支持美联储主席鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名消息人士称，全球央行官员正计划发表一份协调声明，以支持美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔。此前特朗普政府曾威胁要对他提起刑事指控。【原文：Global central bank officials are planning to release a coordinated statement of support for U.S. ​Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell after ‌the Trump administration threatened him with a criminal indictment, two sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-central-bank-chiefs-plan-statement-support-feds-powell-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2YLEGPZ6RNSPJKHO3YG7J2A6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:17:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经亚洲报道：谷歌将在越南开发、制造高端智能手机]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经亚洲周二援引知情人士消息报道，谷歌将于今年在越南启动高端智能手机的研发与制造业务。【原文：Google will start developing and manufacturing high-end smartphones in Vietnam this year, Nikkei Asia reported on Tuesday, citing sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/google-develop-manufacture-smartphones-vietnam-nikkei-asia-says-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDF43LE2KNIW7ATNI6SGWHIRNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:12:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global central banks work on statement in solidarity with Fed's Powell, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Global central bank officials are working on a statement to express support for Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell after the Trump administration opened a criminal investigation into him, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-central-banks-work-statement-solidarity-with-feds-powell-bloomberg-news-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">747M5GUNGJOMTNAWBUF52TAJEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:09:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indian cloud firm Amagi bets on tech shift in media industry for growth]]></title><description><![CDATA[General Atlantic-backed Indian cloud software player Amagi Media Labs is banking on media customers moving to the cloud to boost revenue, the company's chief executive said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/indian-cloud-firm-amagi-bets-tech-shift-media-industry-growth-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZLS47ACAZOT3OYTS2R3CVTHTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Malaysia to take legal action against X over Grok AI concerns]]></title><description><![CDATA[Malaysia's communications regulator said on Tuesday it will take legal action against social media platform X due to concerns over user safety in relation to artificial intelligence feature Grok.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/malaysia-take-legal-action-against-x-over-grok-ai-concerns-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHCGJHQTRBKP3MTK34CCV3HAJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥斯特德股价飙升，因美国法院撤销特朗普对海上风电项目的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦海上风电开发商奥斯特德公司股价周二飙升5.1%，此前美国法院批准该公司重启其近乎完工的"革命风电"项目，缓解了市场对其可能遭受巨额财务损失的担忧。【原文：Shares of Danish offshore wind developer ​Orsted jumped 5.1% on ‌Tuesday after a U.S. court cleared the company to resume work on its ‌nearly completed Revolution Wind project, ​easing fears of massive financial losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/orsted-shares-jump-us-court-reverses-trumps-block-offshore-wind-project-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWLGRTJTQVNZZOM3NPI5TTTEGQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德称投资者在2026年人工智能押注中更青睐能源供应商而非科技巨头]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大资产管理公司贝莱德周二表示，尽管仍看好未来一年人工智能领域的投资前景，但将把重点转向更广泛的机遇。【原文：BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, still believes in the investment case for artificial intelligence in the year ahead but will be focusing on broader opportunities, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-back-energy-providers-over-big-tech-2026-ai-bets-says-blackrock-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNYBJ2JVJJMA5CKLOH577TE2I4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名的越南特使将目光投向贸易逆差，因河内对美顺差已超越中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府计划任命一位致力于解决"不平衡"贸易关系的候选人接替美国驻越南大使。在与华盛顿陷入未决关税谈判期间，近几个季度越南对美商品贸易顺差已超越中国。【原文：The Trump administration plans to replace the U.S. ambassador to Vietnam with a nominee set on addressing "imbalanced" trade relations, as Hanoi's goods trade surplus with Washington surpassed China's in recent quarters while it was locked in unresolved tariff negotiations with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-pick-vietnam-envoy-sets-sights-trade-gap-hanois-surplus-with-us-tops-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XB6RQR3N6BMHNPNNWKDUDZVNPE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国Trustpilot公司预计年收入将增长20%，得益于预订量提升。]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球在线评论平台Trustpilot周二预测，2025年营收和利润将实现超预期增长，增幅达20%，这得益于其所有市场订单量均实现两位数增长。【原文：Global online review platform Trustpilot forecast 20% growth in revenue and profit ahead of expectations for 2025 on Tuesday, helped by double-digit growth in bookings in all its markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/uks-trustpilot-expects-20-annual-revenue-jump-higher-bookings-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">677YGPMI6ZJP3MSCOQSU3XV6XQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lindt的年度销售额略高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士巧克力制造商连德（Lindt & Sprüngli）周二表示，2025年其销售额实现12.4%的有机增长，这得益于其将上涨的可可豆价格转嫁给消费者，该业绩略高于市场预期。【原文：Swiss chocolate maker Lindt & Spruengli said on Tuesday its sales grew 12.4% organically in 2025, driven by higher cocoa prices that it passed through to customers, and slightly beat market expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lindts-yearly-sales-slightly-beat-expectations-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZFTCKQ435LQLLQTRBAMKRV35E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:10:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面临美国25%关税的伊朗贸易伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周一表示，任何与伊朗有贸易往来的国家都将面临25%的关税，而德黑兰正面临多年来最严重的反政府抗议活动。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said any country that does business with Iran will face a 25% tariff on trade with the U.S., as Tehran grapples with its most substantial anti-government protests in years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/irans-trading-partners-that-face-25-us-tariffs-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBL7AXNTZBIUJOTMYESF5ZHUEU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:35:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早盘竞价：日元贬值助推日经指数创纪录新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩·科尔为您解析欧洲及全球市场今日展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUPUDYRVMZMTTMIF46XTCSA2I4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:33:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《金融时报》报道，瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥·埃尔莫蒂计划于2027年4月卸任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周二报道，瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥·埃尔莫蒂计划于2027年4月卸任。【原文：UBS Group CEO Sergio Ermotti is planning to step down in April 2027, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-ceo-sergio-ermotti-plans-step-down-april-2027-ft-reports-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EETKJNAFBBOLRNVBL2J4LS5AAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者价格指数在政府停摆造成的扭曲影响下有所回落，但近期可能已出现反弹。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国12月消费者价格涨幅可能扩大，因部分与政府停摆相关的扭曲因素已消除——这些因素曾人为压低11月通胀水平。这将强化市场预期，即美联储本月将维持利率不变。【原文：U.S. consumer prices likely accelerated in December as some of the distortions related to the government shutdown that had artificially lowered inflation in November unwound, which would ​cement expectations of the Federal Reserve leaving interest rates unchanged this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-prices-likely-snapped-back-after-being-restrained-by-government-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">362MZEHY4VJXTJ3YNVKWSO77Z4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾称已与美国就关税谈判达成"广泛共识"]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾与美国在关税谈判中已达成"广泛共识"，双方正商讨举行最终会议的时间表。台北当局周二表示，知情人士称相关公告可能在本月底前发布。【原文：Taiwan and the U.S. have reached a "broad consensus" on their tariff talks and are discussing a timetable for holding a concluding meeting, Taipei said on Tuesday, as a source familiar with the matter said an announcement could come by the end of the month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-says-it-has-reached-broad-consensus-with-us-tariff-talks-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FBHTXGRTNOTDLUUA757PGX4XQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:56:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际足联携手Stats Perform获取博彩数据及世界杯直播权]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际足联宣布，已选定体育人工智能公司Stats Perform作为其首个官方博彩数据及博彩流媒体版权分销商，该合作涵盖2026年世界杯所有赛事的直播流媒体服务。【原文：FIFA has selected sports AI firm Stats Perform as their first official betting data and betting streaming rights distributor, which includes live streams for all matches at the 2026 World Cup, world soccer's governing body said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/fifa-taps-stats-perform-betting-data-live-streaming-rights-ahead-world-cup-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLEB727BYJMQLEDUTO5WJU4DFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:25:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管遭到特朗普斥责，埃克森美孚仍有意访问委内瑞拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉埃克森美孚公司战略的消息人士周一告诉路透社，该公司仍有意访问委内瑞拉，并准备派遣评估团队前往该国。此前一天，美国总统特朗普表示可能禁止这家石油公司进入委内瑞拉。【原文：Exxon Mobil remains interested in visiting Venezuela and is prepared to send an assessment team there, a source familiar with the company's strategy told Reuters on Monday, a day after U.S. President Donald Trump said he might keep the oil company out of the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-mobil-still-interested-venezuela-visit-despite-trump-rebuke-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5ZDPQQXZBID7MDTAAGCIMMVLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达表示其H200芯片无需预付费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达发言人周二向路透社发表声明称，该公司不要求客户预付H200芯片的货款。【原文：Nvidia does not require upfront payment for H200 chips, a spokesperson for the U.S. chipmaker said in a statement to Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-says-no-upfront-payment-needed-its-h200-chips-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PF7F7WJC4NJKXACQEFS7TASE4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市攀升 日经指数创历史新高 企业财报季临近]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，日本股市强劲上涨带动亚洲股市走高，投资者对人工智能相关板块普遍持乐观态度。与此同时，美联储独立性面临的不确定性阴云虽令美元承压，却利好黄金走势。【原文：A surge in Japanese shares led Asia higher on Tuesday amid investor bullishness over all things AI, while the cloud of uncertainty over Federal Reserve independence favoured gold even as it weighed on the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-global-markets-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI574EQHFRK4NFIGZ44KCZKBA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因伊朗供应中断担忧而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二油价小幅走高，因市场对伊朗局势及潜在供应中断的担忧加剧，抵消了委内瑞拉原油供应可能增加的预期。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Tuesday, as heightened concerns surrounding Iran and potential supply disruptions outweighed the prospect of increased crude supply from Venezuela.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-gain-iran-supply-disruption-concerns-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGKT3ABHLFJPTODEIJC2H2AIGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元汇率波动，因市场担忧美联储独立性面临威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二美元延续跌势，此前特朗普政府对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔启动刑事调查，此举威胁到美联储的独立性及市场对美国资产的信心。【原文：The dollar held to its losses on Tuesday after the Trump administration opened a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, a move that threatens the central bank's independence and faith in U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-wobbles-markets-fret-about-threat-fed-independence-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCHXFKEPL5JK7CZED6YWSFJJTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>