<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:05:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:05:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 计划在未来几个月内发布开放重量级语言模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 首席执行官山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）周一表示，OpenAI 计划在未来几个月内发布自 GPT-2 以来首个具有推理能力的开放重量级语言模型。【原文：OpenAI is planning to release its first open-weight language model with reasoning capabilities since GPT‑2 in the coming months, CEO Sam Altman said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-plans-release-open-weight-language-model-coming-months-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YVAIVZENNNTFNZPFFVF2JVVXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称瑞银任命全球投资管理新主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周一看到的一份内部备忘录显示，瑞银已任命其美洲首席投资官 Solita Marcelli 接替 Bruno Marxer 担任全球投资管理主管。【原文：UBS has appointed its Americas chief investment officer, Solita Marcelli, to succeed Bruno Marxer as head of global investment management, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-names-new-head-global-investment-management-memo-says-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BMNU4PTZJIUXEJUMIU6JCRIZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西财政部长称欧盟应将南方共同市场协议视为政治协议而不仅仅是经济协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西财政部长费尔南多-哈达德（Fernando Haddad）周一表示，欧盟应从政治意义而不仅仅是经济影响的角度来看待与南方共同市场达成的贸易协议。【原文：Brazilian Finance Minister Fernando Haddad said on Monday the European Union should view its trade deal with Mercosur for its political significance, not just its economic impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-finance-minister-says-eu-should-see-mercosur-deal-political-not-just-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PY3KUHFHRBKGBKHOP6GTRWOU7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[透视：特朗普家族如何在一家加密货币公司融资数亿美元时接管该公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着 World Liberty Financial 筹集到超过 5 亿美元的资金，唐纳德-特朗普总统的家族控制了这家加密企业，并在业内专家认为有利于内部人员的管理条款的帮助下，攫取了这些资金的大部分份额。【原文：As World Liberty Financial raised more than half a billion dollars, President Donald Trump’s family took control of the crypto venture and grabbed the lion’s share of those funds, aided by governance terms that industry experts say favor insiders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/how-trump-family-took-over-crypto-firm-it-raised-hundreds-millions-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTEC6DKFGBK3FJXKG2KIWM2UAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司获得 49.4 亿美元的美国陆军导弹合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司（Lockheed Martin）周一表示，美国陆军已授予该公司一份价值高达 49.4 亿美元的合同，生产精确打击导弹（PrSM）。【原文：Lockheed Martin on Monday said the U.S. Army had awarded it a contract worth up to $4.94 billion to produce Precision Strike Missiles (PrSM).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-martin-clinches-494-billion-us-army-missile-contract-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMKT3BQSGNJ5BA2LAX5AOGZKOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:08:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦航空局调查后，蓝色起源公司将下一次发射 "新格伦 "的时间定在春末]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰夫-贝索斯（Jeff Bezos）的蓝色起源公司（Blue Origin）周一表示，将在 "春末 "进行其巨型火箭 "新格伦"（New Glenn）的第二次发射，因为美国联邦航空局（FAA）已经结束了对火箭着陆失败的调查。【原文：Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin said on Monday it is targeting "late spring" for the second launch of its giant New Glenn rocket, as the U.S. FAA closed an investigation into the rocket's landing failure that followed an otherwise successful debut mission in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/blue-origin-targets-late-spring-next-new-glenn-launch-after-faa-probe-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDSGRO53DRLBHLJAJOZHSXCK6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:21:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国驻外使馆要求全球供应商遵守特朗普多元化政策禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府已警告美国大使馆和领事馆的当地供应商以及美国在全球的拨款接受者，他们必须遵守其关于 "多元化、公平与包容"（DEI）计划的禁令，否则将面临失去拨款的风险。【原文：The Trump administration has warned local suppliers to U.S. embassies and consulates as well as recipients of U.S. grants worldwide that they must comply with its ban on Diversity, Equity and Inclusion (DEI) programmes or risk losing payments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-embassies-globally-tell-suppliers-comply-with-trump-ban-diversity-policies-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NO5LPVC4YRNGJLBVTXBBUBQCRM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:13:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件称，美国证交会与马斯克就亿万富翁回应诉讼的时间表达成一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一提交的一份联合动议，美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）和埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）已经提出了这位亿万富翁回应监管机构今年 1 月对其提起的诉讼的日期。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission and Elon Musk have proposed a date for which the billionaire will respond to the lawsuit the regulator filed against him in January, according to a joint motion filed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-musk-agree-timeline-billionaire-respond-lawsuit-filing-says-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEXFETCCYJMAHMKPV4JCU6OD2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[秘鲁原住民团体抗议嘉能可公司的安塔帕卡伊矿山]]></title><description><![CDATA[当地一位社区领袖周一表示，原住民社区成员封锁了嘉能可公司位于秘鲁库斯科地区的安塔帕卡伊铜矿的通道，以抗议该矿区的扩建计划。【原文：Members of Indigenous communities blocked access to Glencore's Antapaccay copper mine in Peru's Cusco region to protest an expansion plan at the site, a local community leader said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/indigenous-groups-peru-protest-glencores-antapaccay-mine-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPVR76QYXVPHLOHUUGH5G5SJEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称白宫正在权衡快速推进深海采矿的行政命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位直接了解审议情况的消息人士称，白宫正在权衡一项行政命令，该命令将快速审批国际水域的深海采矿，并允许采矿公司绕过联合国支持的审查程序。【原文：The White House is weighing an executive order that would fast-track permitting for deep-sea mining in international waters and let mining companies bypass a United Nations-backed review process, according to two sources with direct knowledge of the deliberations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/white-house-weighs-executive-order-fast-track-deep-sea-mining-sources-say-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZWDGSXVEBNIPGNQ2MIQ2VELOA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局关闭 SpaceX 两艘星际飞船探测器中的一艘]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周一表示，它已经结束了对太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）1月份爆炸性 "星际飞船"（Starship）试飞的审查，但表示对该火箭随后在3月份测试中爆炸的另一次审查仍未结束。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration on Monday said it closed out a review into SpaceX's explosive Starship test flight in January, but said another review into the rocket's subsequent testing explosion in March remains open.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/faa-closes-one-two-spacex-starship-probes-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IYLJHV3ERIDNG3W3Q5JJ4SM44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[未来几天，Comex 仓库中的黄金库存有望创下新纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和交易商表示，由于进口关税风险导致其他国家运往美国的货物减少，未来几天Comex交易所仓库中的黄金库存有望创下新纪录。【原文：Gold stocks in Comex warehouses are on track to hit new records over the coming days due to the risk of import tariffs curtailing shipments to the United States from other countries, analysts and traders say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-stocks-comex-warehouses-track-hit-new-records-over-coming-days-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27YRUHYEJVOXHNP3S7LS4ODTPI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国赛峰集团称国防投资取决于订单情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[赛峰集团负责人周一表示，只要欧洲对提高防务能力的需求不断增加，从而带来实际订单，法国航空航天与防务集团就愿意投资增加防务设备的生产。【原文：The head of Safran said on Monday the French aerospace and defence group was ready to invest in increased production of defence equipment as long as the mounting appetite for increased European defence capacity led to tangible orders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/frances-safran-says-defence-investment-depends-orders-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NN3VE2SZJIRPIQEPU7V7HFAFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利卫星星座计划进入第二阶段]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位接近此事的消息人士周一告诉路透社，意大利正在加紧实施建立自己的低轨道卫星星座的计划。【原文：Italy is pressing ahead with a plan to set up its own low-orbit satellite constellation, a source close to the matter told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/italy-moves-phase-2-satellite-constellation-plan-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYZU3VBZJZLE7OBTXIPRQSVXGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:50:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃出人意料地更换首席执行官，回归汽车行业的基本原理]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和投资者表示，沃尔沃汽车公司突然决定聘请哈坎-塞缪尔森（Hakan Samuelsson）担任首席执行官，这使这位汽车行业的资深人士重新掌管沃尔沃汽车公司，带领该公司渡过美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税动荡和向电动汽车转型的艰难时期。【原文：Volvo Car's abrupt decision to tap Hakan Samuelsson as its CEO puts the car industry veteran back in charge of steering the automaker through U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff turbulence and a wobbly transition to electric cars, analysts and investors said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-goes-back-car-industry-basics-with-surprise-ceo-switch-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXP6IOKCHVKIDEVIXWWJCWF63Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会关注 23andMe 破产案中的隐私保护问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会主席周一表示，该机构对最近申请破产的 23andMe 祖先测试公司可能出售或转让美国人个人信息的行为表示担忧。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is concerned about the potential sale or transfer of Americans' personal information by 23andMe ancestry testing company that recently filed for bankruptcy, the agency's chairman said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/ftc-concerned-about-privacy-protections-23andme-bankruptcy-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMHZKQ6HVZO2TMQS2JHAEBPGWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会起诉阻止特朗普终止许多联邦工作人员的集体谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表 15 万名美国政府雇员的工会周一提起诉讼，寻求阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统剥夺数十万联邦工作人员通过工会与政府机构进行集体谈判的能力。【原文：A union that represents 150,000 U.S. government employees filed a lawsuit on Monday seeking to block President Donald Trump from stripping hundreds of thousands of federal workers of the ability to collectively bargain with government agencies through their unions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/union-sues-block-trump-ending-collective-bargaining-many-federal-workers-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJEL4FIPMZNFJLH3GWEAUEDK4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国喷气燃料油轮运营商因碰撞事故在英国提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[上个月，一艘美国军方承包的油轮在英格兰东北海岸附近被一艘货轮撞击，该油轮的管理者周一就撞击事件向伦敦高等法院提起诉讼。【原文：The manager of a U.S. military-contracted tanker that was struck by a cargo ship off England's northeast coast last month filed a lawsuit at London's High Court on Monday over the collision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/operator-us-jet-fuel-tanker-brings-uk-lawsuit-over-collision-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SLIEIVPTJOKNOGPEAO5HHJGWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即使经济前景有所改善，受贫困影响的阿根廷人仍在寻找食物]]></title><description><![CDATA[在自由主义总统哈维尔-米莱伊的领导下，阿根廷实施了严厉的财政紧缩政策，一些阿根廷人正在四处觅食，从事更多非正式的低薪工作，尽管随着通胀降温，最痛苦的时期可能已经过去的希望正在升温。【原文：Some Argentines, hit by tough austerity under libertarian President Javier Milei, are rummaging for food and taking on more informal low-salary jobs, even as hope rises that the most painful period may be over as inflation cools.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/poverty-hit-argentines-rummage-food-even-economic-outlook-improves-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I35XEZB6ZFKHTABFTKFRYQGBLE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:33:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国营媒体称中日韩将联合应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家广播公司中央电视台下属的一个社交媒体账户周一称，中国、日本和韩国同意共同应对美国的关税。【原文：China, Japan and South Korea agreed to jointly respond to U.S. tariffs, a social media account affiliated with Chinese state broadcaster CCTV said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-japan-south-korea-will-jointly-respond-us-tariffs-chinese-state-media-says-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXNA6MSPORO37LLN2OHXJ2QEZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，GlobalFoundries 和台湾芯片制造商联电正在酝酿潜在合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》（Nikkei）周一援引该报看到的一份评估计划报道，台湾主要芯片制造商联华电子（United Microelectronics）和美国环球晶圆厂（GlobalFoundries）正在探讨合并的可能性。【原文：Taiwan's major chipmaker United Microelectronics and U.S.-based GlobalFoundries are exploring the possibility of a merger, the Nikkei reported on Monday, citing an assessment plan seen by the newspaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/globalfoundries-taiwanese-chipmaker-umc-mull-potential-merger-nikkei-reports-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNCI447WORIDLHANKAIMLJM2JU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本银行业游说团主席：受关税影响的企业可能需要业务转型融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本银行业游说团团长表示，日本银行可能需要为受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府征收关税打击的企业提供业务周转支持。【原文：Japanese banks may need to offer business turnaround support to companies hit by tariffs imposed by the administration of U.S. President Donald Trump, the head of the country's banking lobby said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tariff-hit-firms-may-need-business-turnaround-financing-japans-bank-lobby-chair-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SR5HKJF7CZIO5PGTEWJDIBJUSM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:03:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在中国为新款 Model Y 提供 3 年免息贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周一在其社交媒体账户上发布公告称，该公司将于 4 月 30 日前在中国为改款 Model Y 提供为期三年的无息贷款。【原文：Tesla said on Monday the company will offer three-year interest-free loans for the refreshed Model Y before April 30 in China, a notice on its social media account showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-offers-3-year-interest-free-loans-refreshed-model-y-china-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ET4N7R6F3BPQLBV5FU6TC35ZEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党参议员敦促特朗普改革对华贸易关系，修改自由贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位民主党参议员周一敦促美国总统唐纳德-特朗普 "大幅修改 "美国与中国的贸易关系以及14项自由贸易协定，为他推动美国贸易政策改革提供了助力。【原文：Three Democratic senators on Monday urged U.S. President Donald Trump to "dramatically revise" the United States' trade relationship with China along with 14 free trade agreements, providing a boost to his push to revamp U.S. trade policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-senators-urge-trump-revamp-china-trade-ties-revise-free-trade-deals-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONMAXODNKZI3DMJKX7IEEKODC4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:39:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税临近，黄金突破 3100 美元，进入未知领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[金价飙升至每盎司 3100 美元以上的创纪录水平，这是该贵金属历史上最重要的涨势之一，心理价位被各种因素一扫而空，其中包括对美国即将征收关税的担忧。【原文：Gold prices soared to record levels above $3,100 per ounce in a rally marking one of the most significant upswings in the precious metal's history, with psychological levels swept aside by a cocktail of factors - including worry about fallout from impending U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-sails-above-3100-uncharted-territory-us-tariffs-approach-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRYMHO6CJNL4RNRP6HWNJBOFS4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:37:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 数据显示，1 月份美国石油产量降至 11 个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周一公布的数据显示，1月份美国原油产量减少30.5万桶/日，降至1315万桶/日，为2024年2月以来最低。【原文：U.S. crude oil production fell by 305,000-barrels-per-day (bpd) to 13.15 million bpd in January, the lowest since February 2024, data from the U.S. Energy Information Administration showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-production-fell-an-11-month-low-january-eia-data-shows-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJOWHUQJ45IZDGGNXRW25TBR2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，Brookfield 接近以 90 多亿美元收购 Colonial 管道公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周一表示，布鲁克菲尔德资产管理公司（Brookfield Asset Management）正在为收购美国最大的燃料运输系统殖民管道公司（Colonial Pipeline）的交易做最后的润色，包括债务在内的收购价格将超过 90 亿美元。【原文：Brookfield Asset Management is putting the final touches on a deal to acquire Colonial Pipeline, the largest U.S. fuel transportation system, for more than $9 billion including debt, people familiar with the matter said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/brookfield-nears-9-billion-plus-deal-colonial-pipeline-sources-say-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIT25A4ERZOZZLHBV2VJPUDM7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:22:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲防务挑战在黑客马拉松上为青年技术人员注入活力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周末在阿姆斯特丹举行的旨在为乌克兰寻找快速廉价战场解决方案的黑客马拉松吸引了 100 多名年轻程序员和工程师参加，其中许多人表示，欧洲的重整军备计划促使他们考虑从事国防事业。【原文：A weekend hackathon in Amsterdam aimed at finding fast-and-cheap battlefield solutions for Ukraine drew more than 100 young programmers and engineers, with many saying Europe's rearmament plans were prompting them to consider careers in defence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/europes-defence-challenge-energises-young-techies-hackathon-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B634GGRF6NPE7ONBTGUSUEHLJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:14:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片初创公司 Retym 融资 7500 万美元，打造人工智能连接数据中心的芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片初创公司 Retym 周一表示，该公司今年已融资 7500 万美元，这是公司 1.8 亿美元融资总额的一部分，用于在数据中心开发人工智能计算所需的网络芯片。【原文：Chip startup Retym has raised $75 million this year as part of $180 million in total funding the company is using to pursue networking chips for artificial intelligence computing in data centers, the company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chip-startup-retym-raises-75-million-build-chip-that-will-ai-connect-data-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2YUTB77KRKT5JRCZQ2HFRIKZM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行建议克尔斯蒂-罗斯和克劳斯-穆斯迈尔加入监事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行（Deutsche Bank）周一表示，在即将于 5 月 22 日召开的年度股东大会上，Kirsty Roth 和 Klaus Moosmayer 已被提议加入德意志银行监事会。【原文：Deutsche Bank said on Monday that Kirsty Roth and Klaus Moosmayer have been proposed to join the German bank's supervisory board in a vote at the upcoming annual shareholder meeting on May 22.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-kirsty-roth-klaus-moosmayer-proposed-join-supervisory-board-2025-03-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMOJ3QMTLZOM5LHJROFQTEVYLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>