<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:46:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:46:52 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[预测显示移动游戏反弹，Take-Two 公司业绩大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Take-Two 互动软件公司股价上涨 5.6%，原因是 Zynga 所有者的强劲预测预示着移动游戏行业在经历了长达数年的大流行后的低迷后将出现反弹。【原文：Take-Two Interactive Software shares rose 5.6% on Friday as the Zynga owner's strong forecast signaled a rebound in the mobile gaming industry following a years-long post-pandemic slump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/take-two-soars-after-forecast-signals-mobile-gaming-rebound-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZPKJE55QBLMPL2VB3UK5GAMOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金因关税谨慎和经济担忧而大幅流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至8月6日的一周内，受唐纳德-特朗普总统新贸易关税和令人沮丧的经济数据的影响，美国投资者撤出了风险较高的股票基金，大量投资于安全的货币市场基金。【原文：U.S. investors divested riskier equity funds and significantly invested in the safety of money market funds in the week through August 6, spooked by President Donald Trump's new trade tariffs and discouraging economic readings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-sharp-outflows-tariff-caution-economic-concerns-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6U6F5CHORJJHNBWMQK2QHXE2IQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:24:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行皮尔认为存在可能放缓降息步伐的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[英格兰银行首席经济学家休-皮尔（Huw Pill）周五表示，通胀压力可能继续减弱，但未来降息有可能因经济中长期价格和工资设定行为的变化而推迟。【原文：Bank of England Chief Economist Huw Pill said on Friday that inflation pressures were likely to continue weakening, but there was a risk that future rate cuts could be delayed by shifts in longer-term price- and wage-setting behaviour in the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/bank-englands-pill-sees-risks-that-could-slow-pace-rate-cuts-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIWE6DHOP5NALABWMYC5QFOQ3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Firefly Aerospace 在纳斯达克闪亮登场一天后陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[Firefly Aerospace 的股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌了 9%，这被认为是一次正常的市场波动，但这家太空技术公司的强劲表现凸显了投资者对高增长上市企业的重新追捧。【原文：Firefly Aerospace shares fell 9% in premarket trading on Friday, in what was perceived as a normal market swing, but the space tech firm's robust debut highlighted renewed investor appetite for high-growth listings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/firefly-aerospace-sputters-day-after-stellar-nasdaq-debut-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IC3UCTHXRBMQ7K5ZB56KQR7VRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:38:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易台首席执行官警告关税对大型品牌广告商的影响后暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五盘前交易中，云广告技术公司 Trade Desk 的股价下跌了三分之一，因为首席执行官杰夫-格林（Jeff Green）警告说，持续的关税不确定性给一些全球最大的广告商带来了压力。【原文：Shares of cloud-based ad tech firm Trade Desk fell by a third during premarket trading on Friday, after CEO Jeff Green warned about ongoing tariff uncertainty pressuring some of the world's largest advertisers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trade-desk-tumbles-after-ceo-warns-tariff-impact-large-brand-advertisers-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52FNBASQAVK6RF4G2FYQAOVT2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求英特尔首席执行官谭群钊下台，可能会阻碍芯片制造商实现扭亏为盈]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司首席执行官陈立武在扭转这家濒临倒闭的芯片制造商的困境方面已经面临着一场艰苦的战斗。两位投资者和一位前高级雇员说，现在，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普要求陈立武因与中国公司的关系而辞职，这只会分散他的注意力。【原文：Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan is already facing an uphill battle in turning around the ailing chipmaker. Now, U.S. President Donald Trump's demand that Tan resign over his ties to Chinese firms will only distract him from that task, two investors and a former senior employee said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-call-oust-intel-ceo-tan-could-sidetrack-chipmakers-turnaround-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24GLW5ACDRKJNIWBO3W75TDJVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:23:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷的铜矿梦需要基础设施，但谁来建设？]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷北部沿智利边境的山区蕴藏着丰富的铜矿，但与矿业强国邻国不同的是，阿根廷尚未建设必和必拓和力拓等矿商支持的新项目所需的输电线路和道路。【原文：Argentina holds rich copper deposits in the mountainous north along the Chilean border, but, unlike its mining powerhouse neighbor, has not built power lines and roads needed for new projects backed by miners such as BHP and Rio Tinto.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/argentinas-copper-dreams-need-infrastructure-who-will-build-it-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUXT7H7KC5IIND4AGFH335MPUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Under Armour 预测第二季度销售额下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Under Armour 预测第二季度营收低于预期，因为这家运动服制造商正努力应对北美地区因通胀依然高企和关税不确定性而导致的需求低迷。【原文：Under Armour forecast second-quarter revenue below estimates on Friday as the sportswear maker grapples with muted demand in North America due to still-high inflation and tariff uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/under-armour-forecasts-downbeat-second-quarter-sales-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKQB3GCGIBKGPJM5KWMGHOYVBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百度机器人出租车在中国掉入建筑基坑，引发安全担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，在中国西南部，一辆由百度Apollo Go机器人出租车服务运营的自动驾驶汽车在载客时掉入一个深坑。【原文：An autonomous vehicle operated by Baidu's Apollo Go robotaxi service fell into a deep construction pit while carrying a passenger in southwestern China, according to local media reports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/baidu-robotaxi-falls-into-construction-pit-china-raising-safety-concerns-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2VISE667JLDLM5R6TQTDPA7VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:50:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：特朗普组建美联储，科技股创下新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4COMU6W3ERPPDDEKNV6PMG5S6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:41:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NHTSA 对起亚美国公司超过 13.7 万辆汽车展开审计调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，已开始对起亚美国公司的 137,256 辆汽车进行审计，以评估该汽车制造商对部分 Seltos 和 Soul 车型活塞油环缺陷的补救措施是否有效。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said it had opened an audit into 137,256 Kia America vehicles on Friday to assess the effectiveness of the automaker's remedy for defective piston oil rings in some Seltos and Soul models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/nhtsa-opens-audit-query-into-more-than-137000-kia-america-vehicles-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WUUIXMMMBOQ5FQHVXBCTTOJ6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalWafers 已从 CHIPS 法案中获得 2 亿美元用于美国项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于台湾的中美硅品公司周五表示，其子公司 GlobalWafers 于 6 月份从美国 CHIPS 法案中获得了略高于 2 亿美元的资助，约为这家主要硅晶圆供应商去年所获资助的一半。【原文：Taiwan-based Sino-American Silicon Products said on Friday its subsidiary GlobalWafers received just over $200 million from the U.S. CHIPS Act in June, about half of a grant the major silicon wafer supplier secured last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/globalwafers-has-received-200-million-chips-act-us-projects-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMVWJH6QRFOFNIM7LZ5SIAASSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，软银收购富士康俄亥俄州工厂，启动星际之门人工智能计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，软银集团公司正在收购富士康科技集团位于俄亥俄州的电动汽车工厂，此举旨在启动该日本公司与 OpenAI 和甲骨文公司合作的价值 5000 亿美元的星际之门数据中心项目。【原文：SoftBank Group Corp is acquiring Foxconn Technology Group’s electric vehicle plant in Ohio, in a move to launch the Japanese company's $500 billion Stargate data center project with OpenAI and Oracle Corp , Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-buys-foxconns-ohio-plant-jumpstart-stargate-ai-push-bloomberg-news-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7D4IJAOEFM5ZIUVOZ2GZUGFOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注玻利维亚选民将向右转向]]></title><description><![CDATA[在竞争激烈的总统选举之前，玻利维亚的国际债券大涨，投资者希望政治上的转机有助于支撑该国脆弱的经济，并为国际货币基金组织（IMF）的项目铺平道路。【原文：Bolivia's international bonds have rallied ahead of a fiercely contested presidential election, fueled by investors' hopes that a political U-turn could help shore up the country's fragile economy and pave the way for an IMF program.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/investors-betting-voters-bolivia-will-make-turn-right-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRM2CMBJHRL5VIASXF6YSOTKVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预期乐观，美国旅游业反弹，Expedia股价飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五盘前交易中，Expedia 股价大涨逾 17%，此前这家在线旅行社上调了全年总预订量预期，并对美国旅游需求的复苏持乐观态度。【原文：Shares of Expedia surged more than 17% in premarket trading on Friday, after the online travel agent raised its full-year gross bookings forecast and struck an optimistic tone on the recovery in U.S. travel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/expedia-shares-soar-upbeat-forecast-us-travel-rebound-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y57Z26TL3VOKXH2FOSCNQNZ6LA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：中国要求经纪商停止为稳定币背书，以避免不稳定因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，中国监管机构已要求当地经纪商和其他机构停止发布研究报告和举办研讨会，为稳定币背书，以检查该资产类别，避免不稳定因素。【原文：Chinese regulators have asked local brokers and other bodies to stop research publication and seminars to endorse stablecoins in a bid to check the asset class and avoid instability, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/china-tells-brokers-stop-endorsing-stablecoins-bid-avoid-instability-bloomberg-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVCIX3SM35PQDM3PCROUZLX374</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:20:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国缩小与美国的差距，成为德国最大贸易伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国统计局的初步数据显示，2025 年上半年，中国接近超过美国成为德国最大的贸易伙伴，因为德国对美国的出口因关税提高而下降。【原文：China came close to overtaking the United States as Germany's largest trading partner in the first half of 2025, preliminary data from the German statistics office showed, as German exports to the U.S. declined amid higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-narrows-gap-with-us-germanys-biggest-trading-partner-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REOTZYWFDJMRPDHLQWY4JGIWEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:16:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储动荡刺激鸽派押注，期指走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货上涨，此前唐纳德-特朗普总统临时挑选的美联储理事人选助长了人们对央行董事会更加鸽派的预期。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday after President Donald Trump's temporary pick for a Federal Reserve governor fueled expectations of a more dovish central bank board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/futures-edge-up-fed-shake-up-stokes-dovish-bets-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSQCTFCPPROFDPKCBJFGNBMB5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:12:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官使波音走出低谷，但新的挑战即将来临]]></title><description><![CDATA[在波音遭遇数十年来最严重危机的一年后，首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）成功阻止了公司的自由落体。现在，他面临着新的挑战：提高喷气机产量，重振陷入困境的国防和太空部门，以及恢复这家历史悠久的飞机制造商的盈利能力。【原文：One year after taking the helm during Boeing’s deepest crisis in decades, CEO Kelly Ortberg has stopped the company's freefall. Now, he faces new challenges: ramping up jet production, reviving a struggling defense and space division, and restoring profitability at the storied planemaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ceo-pulled-boeing-out-nosedive-new-challenges-approach-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NA7XSI3F35O6BNSA5K5JJDO6QM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 通胀数据考验股市，部分投资者为涨势暂停做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[对通胀趋势的重新审视将在下周对美国股市的涨势构成考验，一些投资者表示，股市在飙升至创纪录水平后可能会出现回调。【原文：A fresh look at inflation trends will test the U.S. stock market's rally in the coming week, with some investors saying equities are primed for a potential pullback after rocketing to records.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-inflation-data-test-stocks-some-investors-brace-rally-pause-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDUKGPFSQVNYFMQ422QHVIFRIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼和苹果交易提振业绩前景，MP材料公司在亏损减少后大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国稀土矿商公布产量增加、季度亏损小于预期并预测产量将进一步增加之后，MP Materials 公司股价在周五的盘前交易中跳涨超过 10%。【原文：MP Materials shares jumped more than 10% in premarket trading on Friday, after the U.S. rare earths miner posted higher output, a smaller-than-expected quarterly loss and forecast further production gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mp-materials-surges-after-smaller-loss-pentagon-apple-deals-boost-outlook-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJZ3GEVPKNJNBEMFU46MXSVGBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构批准波音与 Spirit AeroSystems 合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构周五表示，已批准波音公司收购 Spirit AeroSystems 公司的计划，决定不对该交易是否反竞争进行深入调查。【原文：Britain's competition regulator said on Friday it had cleared Boeing's planned acquisition of Spirit AeroSystems after deciding against an in-depth investigation into whether the deal would be anti-competitive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uk-competition-regulator-clears-boeing-spirit-aerosystems-merger-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3VLX43YTFNBXIBA4FRTQN3UGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国政府推迟就谷歌地图数据出口请求作出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国交通部表示，在美国施压要求谷歌在最近的贸易谈判中解决被华盛顿视为非关税壁垒的问题后，韩国周五推迟了对谷歌出口地图数据申请的决定。【原文：South Korea on Friday delayed a decision on Google's request for permission to export map data following U.S. pressure to address what Washington regards as a non-tariff barrier during recent trade talks, its transport ministry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-delays-decision-googles-request-map-data-exports-ministry-says-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLYOSK2UYZME5MV2CNYLBRHQ5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:40:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车工业集团数据显示，7月份中国汽车销量增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的汽车销量增长在 7 月份有所放缓，因为这个全球最大的汽车市场面临着更严格的法规和激烈的价格战，主要汽车制造商的命运也不尽相同。【原文：China's car sales growth slowed in July, as the world's largest auto market navigates uneven fortunes of major automakers amid tougher regulations against a bruising price war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-car-sales-growth-slows-july-auto-industry-group-data-shows-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AEBOABL2WVP5VGDQ2VAKRNWFDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:16:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[粮农组织称 7 月份世界粮食价格上涨至两年来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国粮食及农业组织周五表示，受国际肉类和植物油价格上涨的推动，7月份世界粮食商品价格上涨至两年多来的最高点。【原文：World food commodity prices rose in July to their highest in more than two years, driven by rising international prices for meat and vegetable oils, the United Nations' Food and Agriculture Organization said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-food-prices-rise-two-year-high-july-fao-says-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4OCQ52KLZKRXKGOXPN6CUC4LQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7 月新兴市场国家央行继续宽松，主要同行仍在观望]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国贸易和关税政策的不确定性波及全球经济，新兴市场央行在 7 月份实施了多年来最大规模的降息举措，而发达市场央行则保持稳定。【原文：Emerging market central banks implemented their largest rate-cutting push in years in July, while their developed market counterparts held steady as uncertainty over U.S. trade and tariff policies reverberated across global economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/em-central-banks-plough-with-easing-july-major-peers-linger-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPO3JYQUAZKEVPLKKCVCGWPSQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度科技巨头 TCS 裁员预示着人工智能对价值 2830 亿美元的外包行业的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度外包巨头塔塔咨询服务公司（Tata Consultancy Services）决定裁减 12000 多个工作岗位，这标志着由人工智能推动的更广泛趋势的开始，专家表示，在未来两三年内，这个价值 2830 亿美元的行业可能会裁减约 50 万个工作岗位。【原文：Indian outsourcing giant Tata Consultancy Services' decision to cut over 12,000 jobs signals the start of a broader AI-fueled trend that could end up eliminating around half a million jobs over the next two to three years from the $283 billion sector, experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/india-tech-giant-tcs-layoffs-herald-ai-shakeup-283-billion-outsourcing-sector-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ4VCBV6HNL4PGJCNKQVSURSVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[渣打银行成立合资企业在香港发行稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周五表示，该公司已与战略合作伙伴成立了一家合资企业，以申请在香港发行稳定币的执照，这是在香港稳定币立法生效几天后。【原文：Standard Chartered said on Friday that it has formed a joint venture with strategic partners to apply for a license to issue stablecoins in Hong Kong, days after the city's stablecoin legislation came into effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/standard-chartered-forms-joint-venture-issue-stablecoins-hong-kong-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EGVFOP5T5MFBHA4DM2CWZ7OPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:14:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求辞职后，英特尔首席执行官称正与美国政府合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司首席执行官陈立武周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）当天早些时候要求他立即辞职后，该芯片制造商正在与美国政府接触，以澄清关切，并确保提供准确的信息。【原文：Intel Chief Executive Lip-Bu Tan on Thursday said the chipmaker is engaging with the U.S. administration to clarify concerns and ensure accurate information is provided after President Donald Trump demanded his immediate resignation earlier in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-ceo-says-he-is-working-with-us-administration-after-trump-demands-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZARSA2RVD5NAFO7EXRDXBRUSOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对俄罗斯石油买家征收关税带来经济和政治风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[从惩罚巴西到试图遏制芬太尼的进口，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将关税威胁作为一种万能的外交政策武器。【原文：From punishing Brazil to trying to curb imports of fentanyl, U.S. President Donald Trump has wielded the threat of tariffs as an all-purpose foreign policy weapon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-tariffs-russias-oil-buyers-bring-economic-political-risks-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WP2T33HARVLEBHZINMWGO5TEWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>