<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:06:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:06:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊 AWS 首席执行官斥责员工产品推出缓慢]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的一份会议记录显示，亚马逊网络服务公司（Amazon Web Services）高层周四对员工进行了告诫，称他们在 12 月举行的首届 "重塑"（Reinvent）客户活动中，云计算服务提供商推出产品的速度太慢。【原文：Amazon Web Services' top executive admonished staff on Thursday for what he called slow product rollouts by the cloud computing provider at its premier Reinvent customer event in December, according to a transcript of a meeting reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/amazons-aws-ceo-chides-staff-slow-product-rollouts-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UI25YKWDSJNJ5CLQKFR7K5PMYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 推出新的人工智能视频节目 Vibes]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体巨头 Meta Platforms 推出了名为 Vibes 的新人工智能视频源，以加快人工智能技术的发展。【原文：Meta Platforms launched a new feed of AI videos, called Vibes, as the social media giant looks to fast-track work on artificial intelligence technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-unveils-new-ai-video-feed-vibes-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YY4QKG7DBRLC5PRC76SWM6OAUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利："随着时间的推移 "可能需要 "更多一点点 "的降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周四重申，美国央行可能需要进一步降息，但在平衡充分就业和物价稳定这两大目标的风险时，需要缓慢行动。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly repeated on Thursday that the U.S. central bank likely needs to cut interest rates further, but it needs to move slowly as it balances risks to its twin goals of full employment and price stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-a-little-bit-more-rate-cutting-likely-needed-over-time-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNH3JLZVFVL65FPHXC2GRSCWPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:56:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，英特尔与台积电洽谈投资或合作事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，芯片制造商英特尔已就投资制造或合作事宜与台湾半导体制造公司进行了接触。【原文：Chipmaker Intel has approached Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company about investments in manufacturing or partnerships, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/intel-approaches-tsmc-investments-or-partnership-wsj-reports-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPMVW352NNPR5POBLFFGOVYGYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库克敦促美国最高法院驳回特朗普解雇她的要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）周四敦促美国最高法院驳回唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）解雇她的企图，并告诉大法官们共和党总统这一史无前例的举动将破坏中央银行的独立性并扰乱金融市场。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook urged the U.S. Supreme Court on Thursday to reject Donald Trump's attempt to fire her, telling the justices the Republican president's unprecedented move would destroy the central bank's independence and disrupt financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/feds-cook-urges-us-supreme-court-reject-trumps-attempt-fire-her-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPRREGROVJPSPCDP3O7QTGAPSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:34:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼称美国批准向德国出售价值 12.3 亿美元的导弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[五角大楼在周四的一份声明中说，美国国务院已批准可能向德国出售 AIM-120D-3 先进中程空对空导弹，售价约为 12.3 亿美元。【原文：The U.S. State Department has approved the potential sale of AIM-120D-3 advanced medium range air-to-air missiles to Germany for an estimated $1.23 billion, the Pentagon said in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-approves-potential-123-billion-missile-sale-germany-pentagon-says-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5LWW3HIRZPXTJLBJSF3GGRM4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[思科推出旨在连接量子计算云的软件]]></title><description><![CDATA[思科公司周四发布了一款新的软件工具，旨在将不同制造商的量子计算机整合到一个单一的云中，从而更容易开发有用的应用。【原文：Cisco on Thursday announced a new software tool aimed at weaving together quantum computers from various makers into a single cloud, making it easier to develop useful applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cisco-rolls-out-software-aimed-connecting-quantum-computing-cloud-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YESZ7NQA3NNWXM5W5REHPFNSZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛总裁称行业整合推动并购增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛总裁约翰-沃尔德伦（John Waldron）周四表示，受各行业整合以及私募股权支持交易可能加速的推动，高盛对并购的前景变得更加乐观。【原文：Goldman Sachs' outlook for mergers and acquisitions has become more optimistic, fueled by consolidation in various industry sectors and likely acceleration in private equity-backed deals, its President John Waldron said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-sees-ma-growth-driven-by-industry-consolidation-its-president-says-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDL2L6GIU5KEZF2JTJ4CXLHW7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:01:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席米兰力挺快速降息，但其他政策制定者表示反对]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储最新政策制定者斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周四继续敦促美国大幅降息，以防止劳动力市场崩溃。【原文：The Federal Reserve's newest policymaker, Stephen Miran, continued on Thursday to press for sharp U.S. interest-rate cuts to prevent labor market collapse, saying his fellow central bankers are more scared than they should be that tariffs will drive inflation up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-mirans-presses-case-fast-rate-cuts-other-policymakers-push-back-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOKZOVACWFKOFNNSIG7NVWS6SY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:44:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将限制纽瓦克机场航班的命令延长至 2026 年 10 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周四表示，将把限制纽瓦克自由国际机场运营的命令延长至 2026 年 10 月 24 日。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration on Thursday said it was extending an order limiting operations at Newark Liberty International Airport through October 24, 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/faa-extends-order-limiting-newark-airport-flights-through-october-2026-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6A3MQBP7UZKYNAD6GLQEXD7BNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:26:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citadel 首席执行官格里芬在接受 CNBC 采访时表示，预计美联储今年还会降息一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citadel 首席执行官肯-格里芬（Ken Griffin）周四在接受 CNBC 采访时表示，他预计美国联邦储备委员会今年还会降息一次。【原文：Citadel CEO Ken Griffin expects the U.S. Federal Reserve to cut interest rates one more time this year, he said on Thursday in a CNBC interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citadel-ceo-griffin-expects-fed-cut-rates-once-more-this-year-says-cnbc-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OU2FJ3RR7VJ3LCUJVOLHXWDKOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:08:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究小组称，美国资金短缺将导致空中交通管制员培训中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个行业组织周四表示，美国政府下周的部分停摆将导致空中交通管制员的招聘和培训停摆，并使美国旅游业每周损失 10 亿美元。【原文：A partial U.S. government shutdown next week would halt air traffic controller hiring and training and cost the U.S. travel sector $1 billion per week, an industry group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-funding-lapse-would-halt-air-traffic-controller-training-group-says-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHZ4OZ6QC5PY5CPKSKW7V4ESJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:59:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，甲骨文、银湖、MGX 将成为 TikTok 美国公司的主要投资者，持股比例为 45]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周四援引消息人士的话报道，甲骨文、私募股权公司银湖和 MGX 将成为 TikTok 美国公司的主要投资者，合计持股 45%。【原文：Oracle , private equity firm Silver Lake and MGX are set to be the main investors in TikTok U.S. with a combined 45% ownership, CNBC reported on Thursday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/oracle-silver-lake-mgx-be-main-investors-tiktok-us-with-45-ownership-cnbc-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XY3RVYIKHFOTVAD2HIMTNYZDWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:54:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国东风目标明年欧洲汽车销量跃升至 80,000 辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商东风汽车公司（Dongfeng Motor）周四表示，该公司的目标是通过混合使用内燃机、混合动力、增程器和全电动汽车，使明年在欧洲的销量增加两倍，达到 80,000 辆。【原文：Chinese automaker Dongfeng Motor said on Thursday it aims to triple sales in Europe to 80,000 units next year through a mix of internal combustion engine, hybrid, range extender and fully-electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-dongfeng-targets-jump-european-vehicle-sales-80000-next-year-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSL374ZW6FK7HP7RCJ22RE4WEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根呼吁全面改革央行利率控制工具包]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周四表示，中央银行为实现货币政策目标而对货币市场状况进行现代化管理的时机已经到来。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan said Thursday the time has come for the central bank to modernize how it manages money market conditions to achieve its monetary policy objectives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-calls-overhaul-central-bank-rate-control-toolkit-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6RTW3YJLRJHDMWVO7Q2UOSEGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:43:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用动力公司获得战略司令部 15 亿美元 IT 合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用动力公司（General Dynamics）周四表示，其信息技术部门已获得一份价值 15 亿美元的企业现代化合同，以帮助支持美国战略司令部（STRATCOM）。【原文：General Dynamics said on Thursday its information technology unit has secured an enterprise modernization contract worth $1.5 billion, to help support the U.S. Strategic Command, or STRATCOM.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/general-dynamics-secures-15-billion-it-contract-stratcom-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDUCZ5FVFZIJ7NGAG2AHUAASII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉敦促特朗普不要废除汽车排放规定和气候调查结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商特斯拉敦促特朗普政府不要废除汽车尾气排放标准，也不要废除美国关于温室气体排放危及人类健康的长期认定。【原文：Electric vehicle manufacturer Tesla urged the Trump administration not to repeal vehicle emissions standards or the long-standing U.S. finding that greenhouse gas emissions endanger human health.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/tesla-urges-trump-not-repeal-vehicle-emissions-rules-climate-finding-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XOQK7LWTVMNNLZMWTZWXZL44Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源部长表示，随着人工智能需求激增，美国敦促公用事业公司保持燃煤电厂运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）周四告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府正在敦促全国各地的公用事业公司延长燃煤发电厂的运行时间，部分原因是为了帮助提供人工智能所需的大量电力。【原文：The administration of U.S. President Donald Trump is urging utilities across the country to keep coal-fired power plants running longer, in part to help deliver the vast amount of electricity needed to fuel artificial intelligence, Energy Secretary Chris Wright told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-urges-utilities-keep-coal-fired-plants-running-ai-demand-booms-energy-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UFQTGG7WJIFLENQBI25D2RCBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:26:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度提议调整出口外商投资规则，亚马逊可能胜出]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份文件显示，印度政府已经起草了一份放宽外商投资规定的提案，允许亚马逊等电子商务公司直接从印度卖家那里购买产品，然后销售给海外客户。【原文：India's government has drafted a proposal to ease foreign investment rules to allow e-commerce companies like Amazon to buy products directly from Indian sellers and then sell them to overseas customers, a document showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/india-proposes-tweaks-foreign-investment-rules-exports-possible-win-amazon-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFX6WATCIBMY3PCFTFVEM3PBPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:15:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cantor Fitzgerald 聘请 Segouin 和 Goel 推动科技交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份内部备忘录，精品投资银行 Cantor Fitzgerald 已聘请 Stephan Segouin 和 Abhinav Goel 担任董事总经理，以加强其在技术交易领域的影响力。【原文：Boutique investment bank Cantor Fitzgerald has hired Stephan Segouin and Abhinav Goel as managing directors to bolster its presence in the technology dealmaking space, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cantor-fitzgerald-hires-segouin-goel-tech-dealmaking-push-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RFDWBYMNH5LYDB7VCS54IIPAYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌和 Flo Health 在生理期跟踪应用程序隐私案中支付 5600 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌和应用程序开发商 Flo Health 将支付 5600 万美元，以解决一起集体诉讼，该集体诉讼称，谷歌和 Flo Health 收集了数百万 Flo 应用程序用户的月经健康周期信息，并将这些信息用于定向广告，侵犯了他们的隐私。【原文：Google and app developer Flo Health will pay $56 million to settle a class action claiming they violated the privacy of millions of Flo app users by collecting information about their menstrual health cycles, and using it for targeted advertising.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-flo-health-pay-56-million-period-tracking-app-privacy-case-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HR4HRJRYKNJX3IQL3MDEFLDYLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:44:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[农业部长表示，美国农业部重建牛群计划将不包括生产者补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部部长布鲁克-罗林斯（Brooke Rollins）周四表示，美国农业部正在制定一项计划，以重振濒临灭绝的美国牛群，但不会向生产者提供补贴。【原文：The U.S. Department of Agriculture is developing a plan to revitalize the decimated U.S. beef herd, but will not offer payments to producers, Agriculture Secretary Brooke Rollins said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-plan-rebuild-beef-herd-will-not-include-producer-payments-says-farm-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLHGNUYEAJOEBHLWCCBLSQQIXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美达公司将因未能对非法职位进行监管而面临欧盟指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，Meta Platforms 因未能充分监管非法内容而将面临欧盟的指控，有可能因违反欧盟的内容审核规则而被罚款。【原文：Meta Platforms is set to face a charge sheet from the European Union for failing to adequately police illegal content, risking fines for violating the bloc's content moderation rulebook, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-face-eu-charge-failing-police-illegal-posts-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JE5WTKAWDBJOTP34UR77WMUIVY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部长表示，司法部将审查农业投入成本上涨问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部长布鲁克-罗林斯（Brooke Rollins）表示，根据周四签署的一份谅解备忘录，美国司法部反垄断部门将与农业部合作，密切关注化肥和种子等农业投入成本上升的问题。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice antitrust division will work with the Department of Agriculture to look closely at the rising cost of agricultural inputs like fertilizer and seeds under a memorandum of understanding signed on Thursday, said Agriculture Secretary Brooke Rollins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-justice-department-examine-rising-cost-farm-inputs-says-farm-secretary-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDZJYMNUJJKAHG2C64VNXPZLQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软在审查后禁用对以色列国防部门的服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周四表示，在内部审查发现初步证据支持加沙和约旦河西岸监控系统的媒体报道后，微软禁用了以色列国防部（IMOD）下属单位使用的一套云计算和人工智能服务。【原文：Microsoft on Thursday said it disabled a set of cloud and AI services used by a unit within the Israel Ministry of Defense (IMOD) after an internal review found preliminary evidence supporting media reports of a surveillance system in Gaza and West Bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/microsoft-disables-services-israel-defense-unit-after-review-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFX6WPNB45IADLBE2HFH4ULCDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯预计汽车报废费收入将增加，尽管销量有所下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的一份文件显示，尽管汽车销量急剧下降，但俄罗斯政府预计今明两年来自汽车报废费的预算收入将大幅增加。【原文：The Russian government expects budget revenues from car scrappage fees to rise sharply this year and next, even though vehicle sales are in steep decline, a document reviewed by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/land-use-biodiversity/russia-expects-vehicle-scrappage-fee-revenues-rise-despite-drop-sales-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZ4JN2CRZJOBDPXQURSVW72MZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼表示，监管机构将在 2026 年初公布巴塞尔资本协议重修规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储最高监管官员周四表示，银行机构准备在 2025 年底或 2026 年初公布更有利于行业的有争议资本规则版本，即 "巴塞尔协议 III 终局"。【原文：The Federal Reserve's top regulatory official said Thursday that bank agencies are poised to unveil a more industry-friendly version of contentious capital rules known as "Basel III Endgame" by the end of 2025 or early 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-bowman-says-regulators-unveil-basel-capital-rule-redo-by-early-2026-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T66I3CHD4RNL3KNBY77Y4MBAIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:39:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊将支付 25 亿美元和解 Prime 欺骗指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（FTC）周四表示，亚马逊公司将向 Prime 用户支付 25 亿美元的罚款和赔偿金，以了结该委员会指控亚马逊这一零售巨头在未征得用户同意的情况下为其注册并使其难以取消的案件。【原文：Amazon.com will pay $2.5 billion in fines and redress to Prime subscribers to settle the U.S. Federal Trade Commission's case alleging the retail juggernaut signed users up for the subscription without their consent and made it difficult to cancel, the FTC said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/amazon-pay-25-billion-settle-prime-deception-allegations-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFDXQCYDTBPUHPRCSR55QIRKT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:25:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，谷歌很可能被处以第二张欧盟反垄断罚单]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位直接了解此事的人士说，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌很可能在未来几个月内被处以具有里程碑意义的欧盟科技规则规定的第二张罚单，欧盟委员会目前正在起草相关决定。【原文：Alphabet's Google is likely to be hit with its second fine under landmark EU tech rules in the coming months, and the European Commission is now drafting its decision, three people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/google-likely-be-hit-with-second-eu-antitrust-fine-sources-say-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDDONPQT3FOKHNTDJRX44TF6CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府启动进口调查，美国医疗科技股下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部对进口医疗器械展开调查后，美国医疗科技股周四下跌，此举最终可能导致关税。【原文：U.S. medtech stocks fell on Thursday after the U.S. Commerce Department opened a probe into imports of medical devices, a move that could ultimately lead to tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-medtech-stocks-fall-trump-administration-opens-import-probe-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFHXWWR2JVIPBDTPWBSBTIMKIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:17:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>