<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:11:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:11:34 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，黑石旗下规模最大的对冲基金业务在2025年实现了12%的回报率。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周三透露，黑石旗下规模最大的对冲基金平台——绝对回报组合基金（AR）去年收益率接近12%，超越基准HFRX全球对冲基金指数7.1%的涨幅。【原文：Blackstone's biggest hedge fund platform, Absolute Return Composite (AR), returned nearly 12% last ​year, beating the benchmark HFRX Global Hedge Fund Index's 7.1% gain, two ‌people familiar with the numbers said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackstones-biggest-hedge-fund-business-returned-12-2025-sources-say-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDBR7UAH3BIA3KVXSNYRUOA62A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得宝将在其亚特兰大门店支持中心裁减800个企业岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[家得宝周三宣布，将裁减其亚特兰大门店支持中心800个岗位，并要求公司员工每周五天返回办公室工作。【原文：Home Depot said on Wednesday it is cutting 800 jobs associated with its Atlanta store support center, and is calling on its corporate employees to return to the office five days a week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/home-depot-cut-800-corporate-jobs-its-atlanta-store-support-center-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEGF6NHRWJJ5JHL5NZ7U4MXQCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空2026年盈利预期超出市场预期，因业务重组成效渐显]]></title><description><![CDATA[西南航空周三预测2026年盈利将超出预期，并表示尽管上周末席卷美国的冬季风暴造成运营中断，但今年开局稳健，其业务重组已初见成效。【原文：Southwest Airlines on Wednesday forecast a stronger-than-expected profit in 2026 and signaled a solid start to the year despite disruptions from the winter storm that swept the U.S. last weekend, saying its overhaul is beginning to gain traction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/southwest-forecasts-2026-profit-above-estimates-overhaul-gains-traction-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5HRIBZGC7RKC7ER6SKZXATJ74U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威主权财富基金持有的美国国债在2025年下半年有所增加。]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威2.2万亿美元主权财富基金持有的美国国债价值在2025年下半年持续增长，延续了长期趋势，该基金周三公布的数据显示。【原文：The value of U.S. Treasuries held by Norway's $2.2 trillion sovereign wealth fund increased during the second half of 2025, continuing a long-term trend, fund data showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/norway-wealth-funds-us-treasuries-holding-rose-second-half-2025-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRSMS53OIRJVHLRO7UG4HVAJTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:24:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[李维斯季度业绩超预期，得益于强劲的牛仔需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[李维斯周三公布的第四季度销售额和利润超出华尔街预期，尽管面临美国提高进口关税的压力以及国内消费支出疲软，但其牛仔裤的强劲需求仍支撑了业绩。【原文：Levi Strauss beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter sales and profit on Wednesday, buoyed by ​strong demand for its denim jeans despite pressure from higher U.S. import ‌tariffs and dampened consumer spending in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-beats-quarterly-results-estimates-strong-denim-demand-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZKZT63IT5MURJXKBJMKJOOJRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，自2019年与委内瑞拉母公司断绝关系以来，雪佛龙旗下Citgo公司首次购入委内瑞拉原油货运]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周三向路透社透露，美国炼油商雪佛龙石油公司（Citgo Petroleum）自2019年初与母公司委内瑞拉国家石油公司（Petroleos de Venezuela SA）断绝关系以来，首次购入委内瑞拉原油。【原文：U.S. refiner Citgo Petroleum has bought Venezuelan crude oil for the first time since it severed ties with its parent, state-run oil firm Petroleos de Venezuela SA, in early 2019, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/citgo-buys-first-venezuelan-oil-cargo-since-ending-ties-with-venezuelan-parent-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3AZGOE6MZIBZOIXGUO7FUDOMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:18:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ServiceNow年度订阅收入超预期，彰显人工智能实力]]></title><description><![CDATA[-【原文：-】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/servicenow-projects-annual-subscription-revenue-above-estimates-signals-ai-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7B7X2ULYFNIHFB4ILY763HJDPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBM第四季度营收超预期，人工智能推动软件需求增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[IBM周三公布的第四季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，人工智能的快速普及推动了对该公司软件服务的需求，这些服务涵盖从海量数据管理到IT流程自动化等多个领域。【原文：IBM beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter revenue and profit on Wednesday, as the rapid adoption of artificial intelligence boosts demand for its software services, ranging from managing swaths of data to automating IT processes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ibm-beats-fourth-quarter-revenue-estimates-ai-boosts-software-demand-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JLBQACUDJN6HGXHNZMGHU5NJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:13:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉营收超预期，尽管汽车交付量疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周三公布的第四季度营收超出华尔街预期，尽管这家由埃隆·马斯克领导的汽车制造商在假日季度交付的车辆数量低于预期。【原文：Tesla beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter revenue on Wednesday despite the Elon Musk-led automaker delivering fewer-than-expected vehicles in the holiday quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-revenue-beats-estimates-despite-weaker-vehicle-deliveries-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G742GPI6ENO6NIZ5G3WN2HX7L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta预计年度资本支出将因超级智能计划而增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta周三预测其年度资本支出将大幅增加，这家社交媒体巨头正致力于构建人工智能基础设施，以追求超级智能。【原文：Meta on Wednesday forecast its annual capital expenditure to increase sharply, as the social media giant builds artificial intelligence infrastructure in the pursuit of superintelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-expects-annual-capital-expenditures-rise-superintelligence-push-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ESRVSR6A5IFXCDXZ6TVOWXKQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软云业务增长超预期，引发对人工智能回报的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周三公布的季度营收略超市场预期，但其关键的云计算业务表现平平，这加剧了投资者对其巨额人工智能投资回报的疑虑，同时也凸显出该行业日益激烈的竞争态势。【原文：Microsoft delivered a marginal beat on quarterly revenue expectations for its crucial cloud-computing business on Wednesday, amplifying investor doubts about the payoff ​from its hefty artificial intelligence spending and highlighting growing competition in ‌the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/microsoft-edges-past-cloud-growth-expectations-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DINL275P2ZMDVI4GKPKYDICFKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[若特朗普限制信用卡利率，航空公司忠诚度计划或面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普提出的限制信用卡利率的提案若得以实施，可能对美国航空公司利润丰厚的忠诚度计划产生重大影响，行业顾问周三表示。【原文：A proposal by U.S. President Donald Trump to cap credit-card interest rates, if implemented, could have a big impact on the profitable loyalty programmes of the country's airlines, industry advisers said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/airline-loyalty-programs-seen-risk-if-trump-caps-credit-card-interest-rates-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUDKYC445BL2TNYTSVOOTHYDSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:51:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[真相社交基金计划收购上帝保佑美国ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[约克维尔美国股票有限责任公司（Yorkville America Equities, LLC）——这家管理着五只新推出的"真相社交"品牌ETF的投资顾问公司，其投资主题聚焦于"美国优先"理念——周三宣布已同意收购"上帝保佑美国"ETF。【原文：Yorkville America ​Equities, LLC, the investment adviser that manages the five just-launched Truth Social-branded ETFs focusing ‌on "America first" investment themes, said on Wednesday it has agreed to acquire the God Bless America ETF .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/truth-social-funds-plans-acquisition-god-bless-america-etf-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MHUGBI2EJM5BPC6S6PAGSTMX4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊、香奈儿获任代表萨克斯百货债权人处理破产事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[电商巨头亚马逊与奢侈品集团LVMH、香奈儿已被任命加入萨克斯全球公司新组建的债权人委员会，这将使它们在该奢侈品零售商的破产重组过程中拥有更大话语权。【原文：Ecommerce giant Amazon and high-end brands LVMH and Chanel have been appointed to Saks Global's newly formed creditors committee, which will give them a stronger voice in the luxury ​retailer's bankruptcy restructuring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/amazon-chanel-appointed-represent-saks-creditors-bankruptcy-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNGEDXF7WFN4FP673JVM55TA6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国自动驾驶出租车公司Waymo计划于2026年第四季度进军伦敦市场。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国无人驾驶出租车公司Waymo周三表示，计划于2026年第四季度在伦敦推出其全自动无人驾驶网约车服务。【原文：U.S. robotaxi company Waymo said on Wednesday it was aiming to launch its fully driverless ride-hailing service in London by the fourth quarter of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/us-robotaxi-group-waymo-aims-launch-london-by-fourth-quarter-2026-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MF5C2OOY5LXRFHJCHN2MC7WF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法警局调查政府数字资产遭黑客攻击事件，彭博社报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法警局表示正在调查一起可能针对美国政府数字资产账户的黑客攻击事件，彭博新闻周三援引该机构的一封电子邮件报道称。【原文：The U.S. Marshals Service said it is investigating a possible hack of ​U.S. government digital-asset accounts, Bloomberg News ‌reported on Wednesday, citing an email from the agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-marshals-probe-possible-government-digital-asset-hack-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MBYNKHGSBKYBFAVX23PUYASBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储按预期维持利率不变，但认为通胀水平居高不下]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三如市场普遍预期般维持利率不变，称通胀水平依然居高不下，同时经济增长势头强劲。在最新政策声明中，美联储几乎未透露何时可能再次降息。【原文：The Federal Reserve held interest rates steady on Wednesday, as was widely expected, citing still-elevated inflation alongside solid economic growth, and giving little indication in its latest policy statement of when borrowing costs might fall again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-fed-holds-rates-steady-expected-sees-elevated-inflation-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3MAPWNUYFN2BBBGAFNT3ZH4LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储维持利率不变后，美元兑欧元和日元汇率保持涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元兑欧元和日元汇率维持升势。此前美国联邦储备委员会维持利率不变，称通胀率仍居高不下，经济增长稳健，且在最新政策声明中未透露何时可能再次降息。【原文：The U.S. dollar held gains against the euro and the yen on Wednesday after the U.S. Federal Reserve kept interest rates steady, citing still-elevated inflation alongside solid economic growth, and gave little indication in its latest policy statement of when borrowing costs might fall again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-holds-gains-against-euro-yen-after-fed-stands-pat-rates-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4MQ426RRFOZLF25H5CWFQFGWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：白宫将与银行及加密货币企业就立法分歧举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位知情人士透露，白宫将于周一与银行业和加密货币行业高管举行会晤，商讨具有里程碑意义的加密货币立法的推进路径。该立法因两大强势行业之间的冲突而陷入停滞。【原文：The White House on Monday will meet with ​executives from the banking and ‌cryptocurrency industries to discuss a path forward for landmark crypto legislation which has stalled due a clash between ‌the two powerful sectors, said ​three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/white-house-set-meet-with-banks-crypto-companies-legislation-clash-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQZOENPOCBLIZC6AGDPDLCA6OQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航运集团达飞海运将与石峰资本成立港口合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国航运集团达飞海运与美国投资公司石峰资本周三宣布，双方已达成协议，将成立一家估值近100亿美元的合资企业，共同运营并投资港口码头业务，包括在美国市场的相关投资。【原文：French shipping group CMA CGM and U.S. investment firm Stonepeak have agreed to create a joint ​venture valued at nearly $10 billion to operate and invest in port terminals, ‌including in the United States, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/shipping-group-cma-cgm-form-port-joint-venture-with-stonepeak-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74FJX2X2YNLQRHBSL4EVUIHLBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会提起诉讼，阻止联邦应急管理局裁减数千名雇员]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国政府雇员的工会组织已向联邦法官提出申请，要求阻止唐纳德·特朗普政府在联邦紧急事务管理局裁减逾1万个职位。【原文：Unions representing U.S. government workers have asked a federal judge to block President Donald Trump's administration from cutting more than 10,000 jobs at the Federal Emergency Management Agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/unions-sue-block-thousands-staffing-cuts-fema-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQDL5C4UBNOVZDODGHYHKTFFAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长称与特朗普就美联储主席人选进行了长时间交谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，他已就美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔继任人选的提名问题与唐纳德·特朗普总统进行了长时间的讨论，并称目前仍有四位"优秀"候选人参与角逐。【原文：Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Wednesday said he had spoken at length with President Donald Trump about the nomination of a successor for Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, saying there were still four "great" candidates in the running.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasury-chief-says-spoke-length-with-trump-about-fed-chair-candidates-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXEZKSMTBBPI7GJL7TU6JCCZPU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油商第四季度利润有望攀升，委内瑞拉成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源分析师表示，随着俄乌冲突持续推高产品利润率，美国主要炼油企业预计将公布更强劲的第四季度利润。【原文：Top U.S. oil refiners are expected to post stronger fourth-quarter profits as product margins spurred by the ongoing Russia-Ukraine war boosted earnings, energy analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refiners-poised-higher-q4-profit-venezuela-focus-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGIMVF5HUJKBPKNSHMIVCZJD2Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递计划在5月31日前恢复MD-11货运飞机运营，此前联合包裹服务公司发生事故]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递周三表示，正与波音公司及美国航空安全监管机构合作，计划在5月31日前恢复其停飞的MD-11货运飞机的运营。此前，联合包裹服务公司运营的一架该型号飞机于去年11月发生致命坠毁事故。【原文：FedEx said on Wednesday it is working with Boeing and U.S. aircraft safety regulators to return to service by May 31 the MD-11 cargo planes it grounded after the deadly crash of one of those jets operated by United Parcel Service in November.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fedex-plans-md-11-cargo-plane-return-by-may-31-following-ups-accident-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47TOWEMBCJJMHHMZ2WQN4RU2SQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克旗下Neuralink公司表示，已有21名参与者加入其试验项目。]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克旗下脑机接口公司Neuralink周三表示，自正式启动人体试验两周年之际，目前全球共有21名参与者加入试验。【原文：Elon Musk's brain implant company Neuralink said on Wednesday it now has 21 total participants enrolled in trials worldwide, as it completes two years since it officially began testing on humans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/elon-musks-neuralink-says-it-has-21-participants-enrolled-trials-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYEF2VPTRJNKFIHE7M6XQMFURA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司与印度炼油商续签价值逾31亿美元的石油协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国有石油公司巴西石油公司周三表示，已与印度国有炼油企业扩大并续签了石油销售合同。【原文：Brazil's state-run oil firm Petrobras said on Wednesday it has expanded and renewed oil sales contracts with Indian state-owned oil refiners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/petrobras-renews-oil-deals-with-indian-refiners-worth-more-than-31-bln-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4HGLC3XSRMFVGDGRYSDAGETVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:26:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员审视福特计划采用宁德时代技术生产电池]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院某委员会的共和党主席正密切审查福特汽车的计划。该计划拟将现有美国电池制造工厂改造为生产磷酸铁锂电池及电网级储能系统的基地，所用技术将从中国宁德时代（CATL）获得授权。【原文：The Republican chair of a U.S. House committee is scrutinizing Ford's plan to repurpose its existing U.S. battery manufacturing facilities to produce lithium iron phosphate cells and grid-scale energy storage systems using technology licensed from China's CATL .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-lawmaker-scrutinizes-ford-plan-produce-batteries-with-technology-catl-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTPXPSERBFJADHGTXY3KZDUFUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：风暴考验美国航空，滞留机组人员面临酒店短缺、救援漫长等待]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周席卷美国的冬季风暴不仅导致美国航空数千架次航班停飞，更使该航空公司的恢复系统不堪重负——从为机组人员寻找酒店房间到在连续数日航班取消后重建航班时刻表，各项工作都面临严峻考验。【原文：The winter storm that swept the U.S. last weekend did more than ground thousands of American Airlines flights. It strained the carrier's recovery system — from finding crews hotel rooms to rebuilding schedules after days of cancellations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/storm-tests-american-airlines-stranded-crews-face-hotel-shortages-long-waits-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I73FPA2RWVMWPNV5TZ5AHSQ7HI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:14:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与墨西哥同意就《美墨加协定》改革启动谈判，美国贸易代表办公室称]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔与墨西哥经济部长马塞洛·埃布拉德周三会晤时达成共识，将就《美墨加贸易协定》的潜在改革启动正式磋商，格里尔办公室表示。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer and ​Mexican Secretary of Economy ‌Marcelo Ebrard agreed during a meeting on Wednesday to ‌begin formal discussions on ​possible reforms to the United States-Mexico-Canada ‍trade agreement, Greer's office said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-mexico-agree-begin-talks-usmca-reforms-ustrs-office-says-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQQCENRQN5PU3HWSD7OJNE6MEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行行长称，对美联储独立性的威胁加剧了经济不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大央行行长蒂夫·麦克勒姆周三表示，美联储独立性面临的威胁正加剧全球经济不确定性。这是他迄今对美联储前景最严厉的表态。【原文：The threat to the independence of the U.S. Federal Reserve is boosting economic uncertainty around the world, Bank ​of Canada Governor Tiff Macklem said on Wednesday in his strongest ‌comments to date on the outlook for the Fed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/threat-feds-independence-boosts-economic-uncertainty-says-bank-canada-head-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVY7XMR43JLLXK3HD2KJRJGRLE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:42:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>