<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:18:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:18:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国商务部长在北京会见 AMD 首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周五发表声明称，中国商务部长王文涛周四在北京会见了美国计算机处理器制造商Advanced Micro Devices公司首席执行官苏丽莎。【原文：Chinese Commerce Minister Wang Wentao met with U.S. computer processor manufacturer Advanced Micro Devices' CEO Lisa Su in Beijing on Thursday, according to a statement released by Wang's ministry on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-commerce-minister-meets-with-amd-ceo-beijing-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNL2KXRXEFPO5NEV26IUVIQ7ZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大型央行发出降息周期即将结束的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着日本央行周五将利率上调至 30 年来的最高点，大型经济体的中央银行正在发出改变立场的信号。【原文：Central banks in big economies are signalling a change of stance as the Bank of Japan raised interest rates to a 30-year high on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-cenbank-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WLRTSTS3FMAPHPFMEKGE3YZWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司的夏娃号 "飞行汽车 "原型首飞成功]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）旗下的电动飞机部门伊夫公司（Eve）周五表示，其全尺寸 "飞行汽车 "原型机已完成首次飞行，这是获得认证的一个重要里程碑。【原文：Eve , the electric aircraft unit of Embraer , said on Friday its full-scale "flying car" prototype has completed its first flight, marking a key milestone toward certification.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/embraers-eve-makes-maiden-flight-flying-car-prototype-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54OFAYNRDFPFRK4JK77SBND7OY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，谷歌云与 Palo Alto Networks 的交易 "接近 100 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 的云计算部门和网络安全公司 Palo Alto Networks 周五宣布扩大合作，一位消息人士告诉路透社，这是迄今为止谷歌云最大的安全服务交易。【原文：Alphabet's cloud computing unit and cybersecurity company Palo Alto Networks on Friday announced an expanded partnership that one source told Reuters was by far Google Cloud's largest security services deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-cloud-lands-deal-with-palo-alto-networks-approaching-10-billion-per-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAMSHLIK5BMT7FKUCCXNW7G2JI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合太平洋公司和诺福克公司就 850 亿美元的合并提交监管审查文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合太平洋公司（Union Pacific）和诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern）周五向美国运输监管机构提交了一份申请，要求对其价值 850 亿美元的合并提议进行审查，该合并将创建美国第一条海岸至海岸货运铁路。【原文：Union Pacific and Norfolk Southern on Friday filed an application with the U.S. transport regulator to review their $85 billion proposed merger, which would create the nation's first coast-to-coast freight railroad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/union-pacific-norfolk-submit-papers-regulatory-review-85-billion-merger-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGLAV4QODZLRXOWQCP4W67OOAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Conagra 保持年度预测不变，第二季度支出 9.68 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Conagra Brands 周五维持了年度销售额和利润预期，原因是消费者支出压力和激烈的竞争影响了对 Slim Jim 肉类零食和 Act II 爆米花等主食的需求。【原文：Conagra Brands maintained its annual sales and profit forecasts on Friday, as pressured consumer spending and stiff competition weigh on demand for its pantry staples such as Slim Jim meat snacks and Act II popcorn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/conagra-maintains-annual-forecasts-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5SYD7A5LFMNJOPLDAMTTBQQ6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:43:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行不出意外将令日元熊市更加大胆]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田一夫周五含糊其辞的展望给了投资者胆量增加对日元的押注，这可能很快使日本货币回到令人不舒服的低水平，而日本政府担心日元可能已经太便宜了。【原文：A vague outlook from Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda on Friday has given investors the nerve to add to their bets against the yen, which could soon put Japan's currency back at uncomfortably low levels for a government concerned it may already be too cheap.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-bears-emboldened-by-no-surprises-boj-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7I4DILDPJFJMRAWK2CZCB6F6TA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:36:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康承诺在外部审计后进行运营改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康周五表示，外部咨询公司对其医疗服务和药房福利部门的审计将导致运营变革，包括提高内部流程的自动化和标准化程度。【原文：UnitedHealth said on Friday that audits by outside consulting firms of its health services and pharmacy benefit units would result in operational changes including more automation and increased standardization of internal processes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-pledges-operational-changes-after-external-audits-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6NMVKLNINIAZHYYKY7MKLGDY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国参议员就与贩毒集团有关的海上燃料走私问题向油轮巨头施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的信件副本，美国参议员罗恩-怀登（Ron Wyden）联系了七家海运公司，作为调查美国和墨西哥之间与卡特尔有关联的燃料走私活动的一部分，要求这些公司解释其确保油轮不被用于运输非法碳氢化合物的审查程序。【原文：U.S. Senator Ron Wyden has contacted seven maritime shipping companies as part of an inquiry into cartel-linked fuel smuggling between the United States and Mexico, asking the firms to explain their vetting procedures for ensuring their tankers aren't used to transport illicit hydrocarbons, according to copies of the letters seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-senator-presses-tanker-giants-over-cartel-linked-fuel-smuggling-sea-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLT4FU5CHFLF3MZQLECEZPQXQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:29:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国对雀巢公司的 Perrier 生产设定新条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国南部加尔省周五表示，已批准雀巢公司继续使用为其 Perrier 矿泉水供应的两口水井，但增加了新的生产条件。【原文：France's southern Gard department has authorised Nestle to continue using two of the wells that supply its Perrier mineral water but added new conditions for production, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/france-sets-new-conditions-nestles-perrier-production-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZ3WEVXCMFIDVDJ2GEIAPGM7YI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:36:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期货因科技股反弹而走高，耐克因中国市场的痛苦而下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货走高，科技股从本周早些时候的大跌中延续反弹，而耐克则因中国销售疲软拖累其季度业绩而下跌。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Friday, as technology shares extended their rebound from a selloff earlier this week, while Nike tumbled after weak China sales weighed on its quarterly results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/futures-edge-higher-tech-rebound-nike-slumps-china-pain-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXWZEMTVZBM5TEO2M4MT44QSU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国工业界对欧盟-南方共同市场协议延迟表示不满]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大经济体德国的商业协会对欧盟将与南美集团南方共同市场（Mercosur）的自由贸易协定推迟到一月份签署表示失望和沮丧。【原文：Business associations in Germany, Europe's largest economy, voiced disappointment and frustration over the European Union's postponed signing of a free trade deal with South American bloc Mercosur until January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/german-industry-voices-frustration-over-eu-mercosur-deal-delay-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SQS53MLGFNKLHCM3N5XUMFYOAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:17:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 圣诞节反弹？投资者希望年底收益为强劲的 2025 年划上句号]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者希望美国股市能在传统节日里欢呼雀跃，但却遭遇了动荡，这可能会让市场在年底时仍处于紧张状态。【原文：Investors hoping for traditional holiday cheer for the U.S. stock market are encountering turbulence that could keep markets on edge into year-end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-santa-rally-investors-hope-year-end-gains-cap-strong-2025-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5O3X3KCDDBNITHFOOFOUR2OBVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:10:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多家顶级制药商将降低部分药品在美国的价格--消息人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉情况的消息人士透露，艾伯维、百时美施贵宝、吉利德、默克和其他制药商预计将于周五下午宣布与美国政府达成降低某些处方药价格的协议。【原文：AbbVie, Bristol Myers Squibb, Gilead, Merck and other drugmakers are expected on Friday afternoon to announce agreements with the U.S. government to lower certain prescription drug prices, according to sources familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/several-top-drugmakers-lower-us-prices-some-drugs-sources-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCR5PE5YDFKAPCJX7US5D33NPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑客利用人工智能和其他手段攻击俄罗斯国防企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位网络安全分析师称，最近几周，一个网络间谍组织利用人工智能生成的诱饵文件，将从事防空、敏感电子产品和其他国防应用的俄罗斯技术公司作为攻击目标。【原文：Russian technology companies working on air defense, sensitive electronics and other defense applications were targeted in recent weeks by a cyber espionage group using AI-generated decoy documents, according to a cybersecurity analyst.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russian-defense-firms-targeted-by-hackers-using-ai-other-tactics-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPP3NXTSWRN4FC4HFGCZM6EBQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:06:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：EEOC 主席称，美国公司将在 2026 年面临 DEI 的清算]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国平等就业机会委员会（Equal Employment Opportunity Commission）负责人周四告诉路透社，联邦正在对企业多元化计划进行调查，这标志着唐纳德-特朗普总统领导的政府在民权执法方面发生了重大转变。【原文：Federal inquiries into corporate diversity programs are underway, signaling a major shift in civil rights enforcement under President Donald Trump's administration, the head of the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission told Reuters Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/corporate-america-faces-dei-reckoning-2026-eeoc-chair-says-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSSMXPYUJ5KFFNLNHHRPQUIGGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 我的圣诞愿望就是获得准确的经济数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克-多兰（Mike Dolan）和投资回报率团队周末兴奋地阅读、观看和收听的所有内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHWLACUHKBPXLNUP7XZIL5OQZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 JERA 为美国进口合成氨争取到政府补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大的发电企业 JERA 已获得为期 15 年的政府补贴，以弥补氨水和煤炭价格之间的差价，因为该公司计划于 2029 年开始从计划中的美国工厂进口氨水。【原文：Japan's biggest power generator JERA has secured a government subsidy for 15 years to cover the difference between ammonia and coal prices, as it aims to start importing ammonia from its planned U.S. plant in 2029.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/japans-jera-secures-government-subsidy-us-ammonia-imports-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIBO4B3XCZO2VJTVIGXTUKFMFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 10:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道Nexperia中国公司转向本地公司供应晶圆--文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份文件显示，荷兰 Nexperia 公司因公司纠纷停止供应原材料后，该公司在中国的分支机构已锁定了当地公司的硅晶圆供应，以满足其 2026 年一种关键产品的全部生产需求。【原文：The Chinese unit of Netherlands-based Nexperia has locked in supplies of silicon wafers from local firms to cover its entire 2026 production of a key product, a document showed, after the Dutch firm stopped supplying the raw material in a corporate dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nexperias-china-unit-switches-local-firms-wafer-supplies-document-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIHN5YRUONIGLMFMI3U3BIV6UY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 10:05:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基完成近两年来首次红海航行]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦船运公司马士基周五宣布，该公司的一艘船近两年来首次在红海和曼德海峡成功航行，不过目前该公司还没有计划全面重开这条航线。【原文：Danish shipping company Maersk announced on Friday that one of its vessels successfully navigated the Red Sea and Bab el-Mandeb Strait for the first time in nearly two years, though it currently has no plans to fully reopen the route.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/maersk-completes-first-red-sea-voyage-nearly-two-years-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6VWD2FILZO5PN52XFDNCRXNPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:35:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称宝马将在美国召回36,922辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周五表示，宝马将在美国召回36922辆汽车，原因是车辆静止时方向盘意外移动。【原文：BMW will recall 36,922 vehicles in the United States as over unintended steering wheel movement while the vehicle is stationary, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-recall-36922-vehicles-us-nhtsa-says-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2Q3UIC6QJIYFDBO2BF3NEA4JM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特因驻车功能丧失召回逾 27.2 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ford is recalling 272,645 vehicles in the U.S. due to a loss of park function, causing the vehicle to roll away and increasing the risk of a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-over-272000-us-vehicles-due-loss-park-function-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4UQZPGMKBMLNGEYTYDDKKCRL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债务繁荣预示着人民币将成为融资货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者正在抢购人民币信贷，人民币贷款激增，有望超过中国银行的海外美元贷款，因为有吸引力的定价有助于推动中国政府持续推动人民币走向全球舞台。【原文：Investors are snapping up yuan credits and surging yuan lending is poised to overtake overseas dollar loans at Chinese banks as attractive pricing helps drive a sustained push by Beijing to put the yuan on the global stage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/debt-boom-signals-yuans-arrival-funding-currency-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEI6PMUZRFJXRFNAOPPARECYEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:13:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japan holds economic view steady in monthly report]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Japanese government revised down its view on public investment but largely kept its overall outlook on the economy intact in a monthly report published on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-holds-economic-view-steady-monthly-report-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WC4O4VWFEBOC3LGNYATTPWFHA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China set to keep rates steady for seventh month despite slowing economy]]></title><description><![CDATA[China is expected to leave benchmark lending rates unchanged for a seventh consecutive month in December, a Reuters survey showed, despite a depressed economy and deepening woes in the property sector.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-set-keep-rates-steady-seventh-month-despite-slowing-economy-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFLIGURQKNK6HBTDNXFG2FJUJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK government was hacked in October, minister confirms]]></title><description><![CDATA[British trade minister Chris Bryant said the government had been hacked in October, partly confirming a report in the Sun newspaper, which said a Chinese group had breached systems to access foreign office data.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-government-was-hacked-october-minister-confirms-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6RIF7S24ZNH7IRUMBXILY35V4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PUBG maker Krafton leads South Korean trio in $666 million India tech bet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gaming giant Krafton will lead a new $666 million investment fund in Asia, partnering with South Korean peers Naver and Mirae Asset to diversify beyond gaming into a wider pool of tech startups, primarily in India.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/pubg-maker-krafton-leads-south-korean-trio-666-million-india-tech-bet-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTRTUJPE3VNP5CWAVNIDL54EAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Coty 将向 KKR 出售 Wella 剩余的 25.8% 股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，Coty 将以 7.5 亿美元的价格向 KKR 出售其在 Wella 的剩余股份，并有权分享该护发品牌未来出售或首次公开募股的收益。【原文：Coty is selling its remaining stake in Wella to KKR for $750 million and the right to a share of future proceeds from a sale or initial public offering of the hair care brand, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coty-sell-remaining-258-stake-wella-kkr-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCDJ4OSFV5ODFIREJF25PRIA4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田在新闻发布会上的讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五将利率上调至三十年来从未见过的水平，并表示准备进一步加息，在结束数十年的巨额货币支持和近乎零的借贷成本方面又迈出了具有里程碑意义的一步。【原文：The Bank of Japan raised its interest rates on Friday to levels unseen in three decades and signalled its readiness for further hikes, taking another landmark step in ending decades of huge monetary support and near-zero borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/boj-governor-uedas-comments-news-conference-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFWS6Y6UDJODLJ73GNJGF4QY7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:51:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道富山县计划建设日本最大的数据中心枢纽 - 文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份文件显示，日本西部的一个城市计划启动该国第三个也是最大的数据中心集群，总发电能力达 3.1 千兆瓦，因为这个亚洲国家正在努力满足人工智能相关服务的激增需求。【原文：A city in western Japan plans to launch the country's third and largest data centre cluster with total power capacity of 3.1 gigawatts, a document showed, as the Asian nation races to meet surging demand for artificial intelligence-related services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/japans-biggest-data-centre-hub-planned-toyama-prefecture-document-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GG4LP3QGVKJVKQYLY26DGRW6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:22:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>