<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:10:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:10:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国住宅建筑商信心指数1月回落，购房负担能力受限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国住房建筑商信心指数1月份恶化，一项周五公布的调查显示，购房负担能力担忧使潜在买家望而却步，而成本上升则阻碍了建筑活动。【原文：U.S. homebuilder sentiment deteriorated in January as affordability worries sidelined potential buyers and rising costs hampered construction activity, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-home-builder-sentiment-eases-january-amid-affordability-constraints-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACXILOEKYBMABAIAHGIUI6TUOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISS建议股东批准金佰利·克拉克公司拟议的肯维尤交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[机构股东服务公司周五建议股东批准金佰利·克拉克公司收购泰诺制造商健威公司的计划，称此次合并有望改善财务指标。【原文：Institutional Shareholder Services on ​Friday recommended that ‌shareholders approve plans by Kleenex maker Kimberly-Clark ‌to buy Tylenol maker ​Kenvue, saying a tie-up ‍could improve financial metrics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/iss-recommends-shareholders-approve-kimberly-clarks-planned-kenvue-deal-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNSSAQMFTVNSRK5MPOHZG67RLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期权到期或为美股波动率上升扫清道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[期权市场专家指出，周五的月度期权到期日可能使美国股市在未来几天面临更大涨跌幅，或将推动市场波动率从历史低位回升。【原文：Friday's monthly options expiration is likely to exposeU.S. stocks to greater swings in either direction in coming days, potentially boosting market volatility from historically low levels, according to options market experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/options-expiration-could-clear-path-us-stock-market-volatility-rise-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CKXQIODMUFL7TPA76Y5QH7ACMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛任命内部人士大卫·古吉纳为美国首席执行官，领导层迎来人事变动]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛周五任命资深高管大卫·古吉纳执掌美国业务部门，接替约翰·弗纳的职位。弗纳将出任这家零售巨头的首席执行官。【原文：Walmart on Friday named long-time executive ​David Guggina to head its U.S. division, succeeding ‌John Furner, who would take over as the chief executive officer of the retail behemoth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/walmart-names-insider-david-guggina-us-ceo-amid-leadership-shuffle-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZWRHQE6PZIWNIRDS3QDYXCYWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易撮合者预计2026年零售业并购与IPO将增多，因关税因素去年抑制了并购活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易撮合者预测，今年零售商和消费品公司的并购及首次公开募股活动将有所回升。此前，美国对进口商品征收的惩罚性关税导致该行业在2025年上半年陷入停滞。【原文：Dealmakers predict an uptick in mergers and IPOs for retailers and consumer goods companies this year after punishing tariffs on imports to the U.S. had sidelined activity in the industry for the first half of 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/dealmakers-see-more-retail-mergers-ipos-2026-after-tariffs-sidelined-ma-last-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQQFWZWIQZKCBP2SNK472AM2PY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫顾问哈塞特淡化对美联储主席鲍威尔的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫顾问凯文·哈塞特周五淡化了针对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的联邦刑事调查，称他预计"此事不会有任何结果"。【原文：White House adviser Kevin Hassett played down the federal criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday, saying he expected there would be "nothing to see here".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-adviser-hassett-plays-down-probe-fed-chair-powell-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRDSWOVBTFJGRBDUCYOGZZ7GIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:50:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通组建新顾问团队，借势私募市场繁荣期]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周五宣布组建新的顾问团队，协助企业及发起人从私募市场筹集资金。作为美国最大贷款机构，该行正寻求在炙手可热的另类资产领域深化布局。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has formed a new advisory team to help companies and sponsors raise money from private markets, it said on Friday, as the largest U.S. lender looks to deepen its presence in the red-hot alternative asset class.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-forms-new-advisory-group-tap-boom-private-markets-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UBJHC37ENLNLDSE6D6OCENZSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:46:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在美国全自动驾驶交通违规调查中获准延期五周]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构已批准特斯拉延长五周时间，以回应针对其车辆在开启马斯克领导的公司全自动驾驶系统时是否违反交通法规的调查。【原文：U.S. auto safety regulators have granted Tesla a five-week extension to respond to an investigation into whether its vehicles violated traffic laws while the Elon Musk-led company's Full Self-Driving system was engaged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/tesla-gets-5-week-extension-us-probe-full-self-driving-traffic-violations-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LK57TV2DEJLFFMAAANGXRR2QYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:25:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国汽车业称重返苏伊士运河前仍有疑问]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车工业协会VDA周五表示，德国汽车行业在恢复经苏伊士运河运输前仍面临诸多悬而未决的问题，尤其是保险问题。【原文：The German automotive industry is still seeing open questions, particularly insurance issues, before resuming transports through the Suez Canal, its business association VDA said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/still-questions-before-return-suez-canal-german-car-industry-says-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHJM2PSYEZLK5JGSXWTPHV2NIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:11:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国主导的跨境数字货币平台用户激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[最新报告显示，中国主导的新型数字货币平台交易额已飙升至550亿美元以上，这再次表明，建立替代美元主导的全球支付体系的努力正在取得进展。【原文：Transactions on a new China-led digital currency platform have surged to over $55 billion, a new report shows, the latest sign that efforts to build alternatives to dollar-dependent global payment systems are ​gaining traction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-led-cross-border-digital-currency-platform-sees-surge-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJFYD3AETNLFDCWAIMYDNFYXAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺沃制药的Wegovy药丸上市首日即追踪到3,071份处方]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德的减肥药Wegovy上市后前四天在美国开出3071张处方，IQVIA数据周五披露的数据显示。投资者正密切关注该公司能否在竞争激烈的减肥药市场中，凭借先发优势压制竞争对手礼来公司。【原文：Novo Nordisk's Wegovy pill hit 3,071 U.S. prescriptions in the first four days after its launch, IQVIA data shared by analysts on Friday showed, as investors closely watch to see if the firm can ram home its first-mover advantage against rival Eli Lilly in a competitive weight-loss market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novos-wegovy-pill-tracks-3071-prescriptions-first-days-launch-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KERHUPQKO5P4BDJLLG5WJJCCZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:43:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称戴安娜航运计划发起Genco代理权争夺战，拟提名6名董事]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，全球航运公司戴安娜航运计划发起代理权争夺战，以取代竞争对手Genco航运贸易公司现有的六名董事。此前该公司董事会刚于数日前否决了戴安娜的收购要约。【原文：Global shipping company Diana Shipping plans to launch a proxy fight to replace rival Genco Shipping & Trading's six current directors, making its decision just days after the board rejected Diana's takeover offer, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/diana-shipping-plans-proxy-fight-genco-ready-nominate-6-directors-sources-say-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAYNIZFGE5L7VGPQAPLOFPONVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:32:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢克石油的国际资产与潜在买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部已将受制裁的俄罗斯石油公司卢克石油就出售其大部分国际资产进行谈判的截止日期延长至2月28日。【原文：The U.S. Treasury has extended the deadline for sanctioned Russian oil firm Lukoil to negotiate the sale of the bulk of its international assets until February 28.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/lukoils-international-assets-potential-buyers-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3YBE7P5JRKXFKADFL7QEGU3AY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:28:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马赛克公司警告称北美化肥需求将在第四季度下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[马赛克公司周五警告称，北美化肥需求在第四季度出现异常急剧下滑，已对其销售额和现金流造成压力，导致该公司股价在盘前交易中下跌逾6%。【原文：Mosaic warned on Friday that an unusually steep drop in ​North American fertilizer demand during the fourth quarter ‌has weighed on its sales and cash flow, sending the company's shares declining more than 6% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mosaic-flags-steep-fall-north-america-fertilizer-demand-phosphate-shipments-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52ZTY5GH6JKJJBY2D6YVAODOWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:19:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星链竞争对手欧卫通信与欧洲MaiaSpace公司达成协议，将共同发射卫星]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲卫星运营商欧卫通信周五宣布，已与法国太空初创企业MaiaSpace签署协议，未来将由后者负责其低地球轨道（LEO）卫星的发射任务。此举对欧洲而言具有重大战略意义，助力其追赶美国竞争对手SpaceX。【原文：European satellite operator Eutelsat said on Friday it had signed a deal with French space startup MaiaSpace for the future launches of its low Earth orbit (LEO) satellites, in a major strategic boost for Europe as it seeks to catch up with U.S. rival SpaceX.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/starlink-rival-eutelsat-signs-deal-with-europes-maiaspace-launch-satellites-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27NXJS6RSFOOTKD3JJDPQHB3SY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:11:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix财报料将因华纳兄弟交易问题而退居次席]]></title><description><![CDATA[网飞计划通过收购华纳兄弟加速营收增长，这一战略将在周二该公司公布第四季度财报时成为焦点。这家流媒体先驱正与派拉蒙争夺好莱坞最受追捧的制片厂之一。【原文：Netflix's plans to accelerate revenue growth by buying Warner Bros will be in focus on Tuesday when it reports fourth-quarter results, as the streaming pioneer battles Paramount for one of the most prized studios in Hollywood.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-results-likely-take-backseat-warner-bros-deal-questions-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XXOIYRVIBLA5DO5Z5AVDVJC3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟与南共市贸易协定风波后续将如何发展？]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟高层官员将于周六前往巴拉圭，与南美国家联盟南方共同市场签署自由贸易协定。历经25年谈判，这项协定将为欧盟缔结史上最大规模贸易协定铺平道路。【原文：Top EU officials will travel to Paraguay on Saturday to sign a free trade agreement with South American bloc Mercosur, paving the way for the European Union's largest ever trade accord after 25 years of negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/what-happens-next-eu-mercosur-trade-deal-saga-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETGGJSMWXVPDDA6UAX3SJOUEFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:47:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度塔塔科技季度利润暴跌96%，因一次性劳动法合规费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[工程研发公司塔塔科技周四公布，其第三季度利润暴跌96%，主要受印度新劳动法规相关的一次性费用拖累，创下该公司2023年上市以来最大跌幅。【原文：Engineering research and development (ER&amp;D) firm Tata Technologies reported a 96% drop in third-quarter profit on Thursday, hurt primarily by a one-time charge tied to India's new labour codes, their largest such drop since the company's 2023 market debut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-tata-tech-has-quarterly-profit-plummet-96-one-time-labour-code-charge-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4AFRWCM45OFPAJLLQK5GP6F5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲茨沃尔特资本将对英国拍卖技术公司的收购要约提高至6.58亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司菲茨沃尔特资本于周五将对拍卖技术集团的潜在现金收购报价提高至每股400便士。此前，这家英国在线拍卖运营商的董事会以低估企业价值为由拒绝了之前的收购提案。【原文：Investment firm FitzWalter Capital raised its possible cash offer for Auction Technology Group to 400 pence per share on Friday, after the British online auction operator's board rejected previous proposals as undervaluing the business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/fitzwalter-capital-raises-buyout-bid-uks-auction-technology-658-million-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTL627HZLRLSPFKS2WST2UN3D4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:44:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：淹没区域]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克·多兰和ROI团队本周末最期待阅读、观看和收听的内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBVNCDHPMFMBVG4J4D6U7Z7IIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:39:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PNC金融服务集团利润激增，得益于并购交易带来的意外之财和利息收入的提升]]></title><description><![CDATA[PNC金融服务集团第四季度利润飙升25%，这家美国银行从利息支付中获得更多收益，并从并购交易的复苏中获利。【原文：PNC Financial's profit jumped 25% in the fourth quarter, as the U.S. bank earned more from interest payments and cashed in on a dealmaking rebound.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/pnc-financial-profit-jumps-dealmaking-windfall-interest-income-boost-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JUIWNKKLFPKDEHDO6UDAR7BG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街银行第四季度财报：五张图表解读]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街大型银行以强劲表现结束2025年，高管们对新一年持乐观态度，尽管美国总统唐纳德·特朗普提出的信用卡利率上限提案令整个行业保持警惕。【原文：Wall Street's largest banks ended 2025 on a strong note and executives struck an upbeat tone for the year ahead, even as U.S. President Donald Trump's proposed cap on credit card interest rates ​kept the industry on edge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-banks-fourth-quarter-earnings-five-charts-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAVIMDMBYNMTXKYPFTGT4UWYZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:27:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货上涨，芯片制造商在震荡一周后收高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五上涨，因半导体股延续了人工智能驱动的涨势，结束了震荡交投的一周，同时拉开了第四季度财报季的序幕。【原文：U.S. stock index ​futures rose on Friday as semiconductor shares extended their AI‑fueled rally at the end ‌of a choppy trading week that ushered in the fourth‑quarter earnings season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-rise-chipmakers-advance-end-choppy-week-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6M4GLUDGVK3RPBGFG4XIT4HNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:23:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金创下三个半月来最大单周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月14日当周，美国股票基金资金大幅涌入，投资者对即将到来的第四季度财报季持乐观预期，同时对地缘政治风险及美联储独立性的担忧被暂时抛诸脑后。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed sharp inflows in the week to January 14 on upbeat earnings expectations ahead of the ​fourth quarter earnings season, with investors brushing off concerns around geopolitics ‌and the Federal Reserve's independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-largest-weekly-inflow-3-12-months-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSVL2X2WV5JBHGASJL47JVYBBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[M&T银行第四季度利润因利息收入增长而提升]]></title><description><![CDATA[M&amp;T银行周五公布的第四季度利润实现增长，主要得益于利息收入增加和抵押贷款业务表现强劲。【原文：M&amp;T Bank posted a rise in fourth-quarter profit on Friday, driven by higher interest income and stronger mortgage banking results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mt-banks-fourth-quarter-profit-lifted-by-interest-income-growth-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXV7GEHL2VNFTPBORKIPQTUXFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯小型企业因移民执法行动遭受重创，而大企业却保持沉默]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心遭到报复或面临抵制威胁，企业在特朗普总统第二任期内对其政策的态度明显收敛了许多。【原文：Businesses have been much less outspoken about President Donald Trump's policies in his second term, due to fear of retaliation or threats of boycotts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/small-minneapolis-businesses-hit-hard-by-ice-crackdown-while-corporations-stay-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AS4NGPMPYRKL3ENZSUWMZ544QE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：部分制药商对FDA快速审查计划的法律风险暗自忧虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[六位行业消息人士向路透社透露，尽管有六家以上大型制药商参与了特朗普政府的新药加速审批计划，但其他领先制药企业仍因潜在法律风险而犹豫不决。【原文：More than half a dozen major drugmakers are participating in the Trump administration's speedier review program for new medicines, yet other leading pharmaceutical companies are hesitating over what they see as potential legal risks, six industry sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/some-drugmakers-quietly-concerned-about-legal-risk-with-speedy-fda-review-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYV2SJ3AOFPKZJAZV5WYJAOW44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在移民与海关执法局突袭行动之际，部分家得宝投资者希望了解执法部门如何使用其监控数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群家得宝投资者要求该公司重新评估与监控公司Flock Safety的合作关系，并说明其数据如何被使用及与执法部门共享。此前有独立媒体报道称，该供应商的数据已被用于移民与海关执法局的调查。【原文：A group of Home Depot investors is asking the company to review its partnership with surveillance firm Flock Safety and state how its data is used and shared with law enforcement, following reports by an independent media outlet that the vendor's data has been used in Immigration and Customs Enforcement investigations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/amid-ice-raids-some-home-depot-investors-want-know-how-law-enforcement-uses-its-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3I7NO7XS5PNPDWUV74JWY2D2U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[扑克脸鲍威尔或藏有王牌以阻挠特朗普对美联储的改组]]></title><description><![CDATA[现年72岁的美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔，如今可以陪伴孙辈玩耍，重拾高尔夫球技，还能在吉他上练上几首曲子。【原文：At 72, U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell has grandkids to play with, a golf game to get back to and a tune or two to master on the guitar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/poker-faced-powell-may-have-ace-up-sleeve-stymie-trumps-fed-shakeup-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUU6N5JUWJIY3MMLXVKTLUZEWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：美联航与美国航空争夺芝加哥奥黑尔机场主导权]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥奥黑尔国际机场作为美国航空交通的枢纽，如今已成为美联航与美航之间日益激烈的竞争前线。【原文：Chicago O'Hare International Airport, long a crossroads of U.S. air travel, has become the front line in an intensifying contest between United Airlines and American Airlines .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/united-american-compete-dominate-chicagos-ohare-airport-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JI5QS3C2SJMFHPG37TRNRL5JA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>