<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:49:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:49:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据报道，Seven & i 的创始家族计划在本年度完成收购，之后股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，日本零售商 Seven &amp; i Holdings 的创始家族计划在本财年（截至 3 月）内将其私有化，该公司股价在周三的东京早盘交易中跳涨逾 9%。【原文：Shares in Seven &amp; i Holdings jumped more than 9% in early Tokyo trading on Wednesday following a media report that the founding family behind the Japanese retailer was aiming to take it private within this financial year ending in March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/seven-i-shares-soar-after-report-founding-family-aims-complete-buyout-this-fy-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INPFEOEX6ZJPBGXWNWTYF4BIQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:42:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼谈判消息传出后，角川股价大涨 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社报道索尼正在洽谈收购这家集出版、动漫和游戏于一身的公司一天之后，角川的股价在周三的东京早盘交易中大涨 16%。【原文：Kadokawa's shares jumped 16% in early Tokyo trading on Wednesday, a day after Reuters reported Sony was in talks to acquire the publishing, anime and gaming powerhouse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/kadokawa-shares-jump-16-after-news-sony-talks-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUHFHUM2I5JHDPEP5FSEZPWHVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:38:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官称精神航空会谈进展顺利，但面临工业挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲飞机制造商空中客车公司（Airbus）负责人表示，最终完成收购陷入困境的美国航空结构供应商 Spirit Aerosystems 公司部分股权的谈判进展顺利，但将其纳入空中客车公司 "并非轻而易举"。【原文：The head of European planemaker Airbus said talks to finalise the takeover of part of troubled U.S. aerostructures supplier Spirit Aerosystems were going smoothly but that bringing it into Airbus would "not be a walk in the park".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-ceo-says-spirit-aero-talks-going-well-industrial-challenges-lie-ahead-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3TVX3FZYRMCXBA3AXCX7AZCUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 23:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 T-Mobile 表示不打算停止合作后，诺基亚美股股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在美国上市的诺基亚公司股价在延时交易中跳涨约 5%，此前 T-Mobile 公司表示，它没有计划停止与这家芬兰公司的合作，以回应分析师报告中声称的这种可能性。【原文：U.S.-listed shares of Nokia jumped around 5% in extended trading on Tuesday after T-Mobile said it has no plans to stop working with the Finnish company in a response to an analyst report claiming such a possibility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nokias-us-shares-rise-after-t-mobile-says-no-plans-stop-partnership-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4H32LX46UBI77MZQAFHNYGJOEI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 22:58:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞公司要求从证交会和解协议中收回 7500 万美元的申请败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二驳回了辉瑞公司的请求，即收回美国证券交易委员会与亿万富翁史蒂文-科恩（Steven A. Cohen）的对冲基金 SAC Capital 在一起内幕交易案中达成和解后剩余的约 7,520 万美元。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday rejected Pfizer's bid to recoup about $75.2 million left over from a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission settlement with billionaire Steven A. Cohen's hedge fund SAC Capital in an insider trading case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pfizer-loses-bid-recoup-75-million-left-over-sec-settlement-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAXI55PBVFOJHJTO6FC6XP7SEQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 22:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞购美俄恐慌消退，英伟达守夜即将结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPY3A633OZJALDRWQRGH76IAZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司预计五年内汽车和 PC 芯片收入将达 120 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[高通公司周二在纽约举行的投资者活动上表示，预计到 2029 财年，汽车芯片收入将达到 80 亿美元，个人电脑芯片销售额将达到 40 亿美元。【原文：Qualcomm expects $8 billion in automotive chip revenue and $4 billion in PC chip sales by fiscal 2029, it said at an investor event held in New York on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qualcomm-expects-12-bln-revenue-autos-pc-chips-five-years-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4DLAQ4UGJO5TMAHK7FJ6Q3SPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:36:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部称戴尔和 Iron Bow 公司就多收军队费用的指控达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周二表示，戴尔科技公司（Dell Technologies）和铁弓科技公司（Iron Bow Technologies）已同意各支付 200 多万美元，以解决美国政府对它们在一份计算合同中向陆军多收费用的指控。【原文：Dell Technologies and Iron Bow Technologies have agreed to pay more than $2 million each to resolve allegations by the U.S. government they overcharged the Army on a computing contract, the Justice Department said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/dell-iron-bow-settle-charges-they-overcharged-army-doj-says-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFMYEFBC4JNYRLFC7IYCB65JHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国海军上将：乌克兰和中东冲突蚕食美国防空储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国驻亚太地区美军最高将领周二表示，乌克兰和中东的冲突正在蚕食美国的防空系统储备。【原文：Conflicts in Ukraine and the Middle East are eating into U.S. stockpiles of air defenses, the top U.S. admiral overseeing American forces in the Asia-Pacific region said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ukraine-middle-east-conflicts-eating-into-us-air-defense-stocks-us-admiral-says-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y42QN6A36BLEVKCBEGD26BOJUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）在 "大流行病 "后的趋势中举步维艰，最终陷入破产境地]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）本有望成为大流行病后旅游业的大赢家之一。但是，在变化了的商业和经营环境中，这家免票价的先驱者始终没有找到自己的翅膀。【原文：Spirit Airlines was expected to be one of the big travel industry winners after the pandemic. But the no-frills pioneer never found its wings in a changed business and operating landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-struggle-navigate-post-pandemic-trends-lands-it-bankruptcy-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWDF4ANGJ5KAFNNPK6LTXJSFBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 20:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员称特朗普不能无视要求字节跳动在明年之前剥离 TikTok 的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院司法小组委员会主席周二表示，当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）不能无视一项法律，该法律要求总部位于中国的 TikTok 在明年初之前剥离 1.7 亿美国人使用的短视频应用。【原文：The chair of a U.S. Senate Judiciary subcommittee said on Tuesday that President-elect Donald Trump cannot ignore a law requiring Chinese-based TikTok to divest the short video app used by 170 million Americans by early next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senator-says-trump-cannot-ignore-law-requiring-bytedance-divest-tiktok-by-next-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMSBZOYRRRP4FLTVOZTNMD6Y6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 19:49:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）支持的工作室 Promise 将开始利用人工智能制作电影和连续剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[Promise 公司由前新闻集团总裁彼得-切宁（Peter Chernin）和风险投资公司安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）支持，将使用生成式人工智能工具制作电影和连续剧。【原文：Promise, backed by former News Corp President Peter Chernin and venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz, will produce films and series using generative AI tools, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/andreessen-horowitz-backed-studio-promise-start-producing-movies-series-using-ai-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STV4VPJBEJKTRODFURK3MLQXVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 18:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 推出支持灵活电动汽车和混合动力汽车生产的技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 正准备利用新的汽车系统来应对动荡的电动汽车转型，该系统将支持汽油、混合动力和电动车型的组装，在唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫后，该系统的灵活性将变得尤为重要。【原文：Stellantis is preparing to navigate the turbulent electric-vehicle transition with a new vehicle system that will support assembly of gasoline, hybrid and electric models, providing flexibility that will be especially important with Donald Trump returning to the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-unveils-technology-support-flexible-ev-hybrid-auto-production-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5EQ2CVFSJMKBJLA7SWRME74F4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 18:19:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德称利率还不确定能下降多少]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储主席杰弗里-施密德（Jeffrey Schmid）周二表示，尽管美国央行的首次降息是对通胀率正在回归2%目标的信心投票，但利率能下降到什么程度仍不确定。【原文：It remains uncertain how far interest rates can fall, though the initial reductions made by the U.S. central bank are a vote of confidence that inflation is returning to its 2% target, Kansas City Fed President Jeffrey Schmid said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-schmid-says-it-is-uncertain-how-far-interest-rates-can-fall-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNSZ6Q377BOYVM22ZHDEYGZXTE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 18:14:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官称CFM发动机供应量可实现，但供应紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，空中客车公司首席执行官对关键的发动机供应表示谨慎乐观，他告诉路透社记者，CFM国际公司应该能够提供足够的机组来支持该飞机制造商的年底计划，但供应将 "非常紧张"。【原文：The CEO of Airbus signalled cautious optimism on crucial engine supplies on Tuesday, telling Reuters that CFM International should be able to supply enough units to support the planemaker's end-year plans but it would be "very tight".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-ceo-says-cfm-engine-supplies-achievable-tight-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CABP7NMEFNKBJP4ESSJXAS6V7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛等美国公司对特朗普提议的关税表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普誓言在 1 月上任后对进口商品征收高额关税，企业高管们对此持观望态度，但许多人对这种征税将对通胀产生的影响表示担忧。【原文：Corporate executives were taking a wait-and-see approach to President-elect Donald Trump's vow to impose heavy tariffs on imports when he takes office in January, but many have raised concerns about the effect such levies will have on inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/walmart-other-us-companies-raise-concerns-over-proposed-trump-tariffs-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDZ4PTBL3RNCRKMXCWETNMDCCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:20:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SpaceX 将从得克萨斯州发射第六次星际飞船测试，特朗普将出席]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索公司（SpaceX）将于本周二从得克萨斯州发射其巨型 "星际飞船"（Starship）火箭的第六次试验，希望改进其高超音速重返地球大气层的技术，并采用新颖的助推器着陆技术，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将亲自观看。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX is set on Tuesday to launch the sixth test of its giant Starship rocket from Texas, eyeing improvements in its hypersonic reentry into Earth's atmosphere and a novel technique for landing its booster, as U.S. President-elect Donald Trump watches in person.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spacex-launch-sixth-starship-test-texas-with-trump-attending-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7U6MOA7VBNOHEYVLQMNKQXPQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行业监管机构格伦伯格将在特朗普就任总统前于一月退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦存款保险公司（Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation）主席马丁-格伦伯格（Martin Gruenberg）周二告诉同事们，他将从 1 月 19 日起从该机构退休，为当选总统唐纳德-特朗普任命该机构的新领导层扫清道路。【原文：U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation Chairman Martin Gruenberg told colleagues Tuesday he would retire from the agency effective January 19, clearing the way for President-elect Donald Trump to name new leadership to the agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-bank-regulator-gruenberg-retire-january-ahead-trump-presidency-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUZF6JMD7JLQPCLL27Y5CCC4XY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西开发银行与巴拉圭签署 1 亿美元协议，为巴西航空工业公司喷气机出口提供资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西开发银行（BNDES）周一与巴拉圭政府签署了一项协议，将为巴拉圭出口六架巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）的超级巨嘴鸟（Super Tucano）战斗机提供 6 亿雷亚尔（1.039 亿美元）的资金。【原文：Brazilian development bank BNDES signed a deal with Paraguay's government on Monday to provide 600 million reais ($103.9 million) in financing for the export of six Embraer's Super Tucano fighter planes to the South American nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/brazil-development-bank-signs-100-million-deal-with-paraguay-fund-export-embraer-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H253F4KWXVORDLMBSXRLBDSJW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:59:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保罗-泰森门创下非拉斯维加斯门票收入 1810 万美元的纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰克-保罗（Jake Paul）和迈克-泰森（Mike Tyson）周六在 AT&amp;T 体育馆创下了破纪录的门票收入，共有 72300 名球迷到场观看，总收入达 18117072 美元，创下了在拉斯维加斯以外举行的拳击和综合格斗赛事的最高纪录。【原文：Jake Paul and Mike Tyson punched up a record-breaking gate at AT&amp;T Stadium on Saturday with 72,300 fans in attendance leading to $18,117,072 in total revenue, a record for boxing and mixed martial events held outside of Las Vegas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/paul-tyson-gate-fetches-non-vegas-record-181m-revenue-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNTXVDXZHNI2VCJF3HYD6MYRNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[内布拉斯加州就重型卡车制造商推动电动汽车发展提起反垄断诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[内布拉斯加州总检察长迈克尔-希尔杰斯（Michael Hilgers）周二对几家最大的重型卡车制造商提起反垄断诉讼，指控他们在向电动卡车转型的过程中限制柴油动力半挂卡车的供应。【原文：Nebraska Attorney General Michael Hilgers on Tuesday filed an antitrust lawsuit against some of the largest heavy-duty truck manufacturers accusing them of limiting the availability of diesel-powered semi-trucks in a shift to electric trucks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/nebraska-files-antitrust-lawsuit-against-heavy-duty-truck-manufacturers-over-ev-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQM754357ZNELFJ75TC667VX5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众任命前 Rivian 高管为美国业务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车周二任命前 Rivian 公司高管谢尔-格鲁纳（Kjell Gruner）为其美国业务主管，因为该汽车制造商正面临着波折不断的电动化转型以及与美国汽车工人联合会（United Auto Workers union）在该地区持续进行的谈判。【原文：Volkswagen appointed former Rivian executive Kjell Gruner as head of its American business Tuesday, as the automaker faces a choppy electric transition and ongoing negotiations with the United Auto Workers union in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-appoints-former-rivian-executive-head-american-business-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUI7ENERCVN5NAMFZBSFEMYVMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:16:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wipro 主席称特朗普的亲商政策将使印度 IT 行业受益]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，Wipro 执行主席里沙德-普雷姆吉（Rishad Premji）在印度南部城市班加罗尔（Bengaluru）举行的一次活动上表示，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）担任美国总统将 "有利于商业和增长"，对科技服务业有利。【原文：Donald Trump's presidency in the United States is going to be "pro-business and pro-growth" and good for the tech services industry, Wipro Executive Chairman Rishad Premji said at an event in the southern Indian city of Bengaluru on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/trumps-pro-business-policies-benefit-indias-it-sector-wipro-chair-says-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHQ4XVPUAVNHLJYJE52YKKTU5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司罢工、海伦火山爆发导致华盛顿州和佛罗里达州的薪资下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿州和佛罗里达州 10 月份的就业人数有所减少，这表明波音公司工厂工人罢工和海伦飓风是上个月美国就业增长突然放缓的部分原因。【原文：Employment decreased in Washington State and Florida in October, suggesting that a strike by factory workers at Boeing and Hurricane Helene accounted for part of the abrupt slowdown in U.S. job growth last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/boeing-strike-helene-depress-payrolls-washington-state-florida-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">326BN6QSXFLETHA3HTRFJL63H4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府委员会推动曼哈顿计划式的人工智能计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与中国就先进技术的竞争日益加剧之际，美国国会一个委员会周二提出了一项曼哈顿计划式的倡议，资助开发与人类一样聪明或比人类更聪明的人工智能系统。【原文：A U.S. congressional commission on Tuesday proposed a Manhattan Project-style initiative to fund the development of AI systems that will be as smart or smarter than humans, amid intensifying competition with China over advanced technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/us-government-commission-pushes-manhattan-project-style-ai-initiative-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMNRUSMB3FJ77OSMSZZK2OFEFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着休闲旅游需求的增长，希尔顿计划扩大在印度的业务范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[希尔顿全球亚太区首席执行官表示，希尔顿全球预计在未来五年内将把其在印度的酒店客房数量翻两番，因为在国内旅游市场蓬勃发展的背景下，该酒店运营商正努力缩小与竞争对手的差距。【原文：Hilton Worldwide expects to quadruple the number of hotel rooms in its India pipeline in the next five years, the company's APAC chief said, as the hotel operator seeks to close the gap with rivals amid a booming domestic travel market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/hilton-plans-expand-footprint-india-amid-boom-leisure-travel-demand-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V43RMNCAYFLORPNFJFOQ6JI2RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:28:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[COP29 气候谈判：哪些新税种有助于筹集资金应对气候变化？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在阿塞拜疆举行的 COP29 气候谈判旨在达成一项每年 1 万亿美元或更多的年度融资目标，以帮助较贫穷的国家应对全球变暖。一些人认为，征收新税是实现这一目标的途径之一。【原文：The COP29 climate talks in Azerbaijan aim to agree an annual finance target of $1 trillion or more a year to help poorer countries respond to global warming. Some see new taxes as one way to get there.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/what-new-taxes-could-help-raise-money-fight-climate-change-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FFDZW5L2FPRTJNNFXKQB4ZYVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:21:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典副首相表示，瑞典没有入股 Northvolt 的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典能源、商业和工业大臣兼副首相 Ebba Busch 周二告诉路透社，瑞典政府不打算入股电池制造商 Northvolt。【原文：The Swedish government does not plan to take a stake in battery maker Northvolt, Sweden's Minister for Energy, Business and Industry and Deputy Prime Minister Ebba Busch told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sweden-has-no-plan-take-stake-northvolt-deputy-pm-says-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THQ6ROV7JNJPPNJKARDMYZE7EQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 14:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达Run:ai交易将于12月20日前获得欧盟反垄断裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据欧盟委员会的一份文件，欧盟反垄断监管机构将在12月20日前就美国芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）收购以色列人工智能初创公司Run:ai的提议做出决定。【原文：EU antitrust regulators will make a decision on U.S. chipmaker Nvidia's proposed acquisition of Israeli AI startup Run:ai by Dec. 20, according to a European Commission filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/nvidias-runai-deal-get-eu-antitrust-decision-by-dec-20-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6Q2QP5HHFKDFE4BESASA23DRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 14:27:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗保健行业高管预计 2025 年将有更多首次公开募股和企业交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰富瑞（Jefferies）周二发布的年度医疗报告显示，医疗行业高管和投资者预计2025年首次公开募股和企业交易将有所上升，地缘政治紧张局势将取代资金挑战，成为该行业面临的最大风险。【原文：Healthcare executives and investors expect an uptick in initial public offerings and corporate dealmaking in 2025, with geopolitical tensions overtaking funding challenges as the biggest risk to the sector, Jefferies' annual healthcare report showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/healthcare-executives-expect-more-ipos-corporate-dealmaking-2025-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBIBNI6I6RLI3PMYQCXPAKMQHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 14:17:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>