<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 17:07:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 17:07:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴西几乎没有退出特朗普关税的途径，但感受到的痛苦较少]]></title><description><![CDATA[当美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将对巴西征收 50%的关税与其盟友--巴西前极右翼领导人--的审判联系起来时，华盛顿让这个拉丁美洲最大的经济体几乎没有缓和局势的选择，但却可能高估了巴西在征税面前的脆弱性。【原文：When U.S. President Donald Trump linked 50% tariffs on Brazil to the trial against his ally, the country's former far-right leader, Washington left Latin America's largest economy with few options to deescalate but may have overestimated the country's vulnerability to the levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-has-few-exit-routes-trump-tariff-feels-less-pain-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRBIUBINW5KL3GC6LLGKU6KDUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 17:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师警告特朗普关税影响，巴西航空工业公司股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将对来自南美国家的所有进口商品征收50%的关税后，巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司的股票周四大幅下跌。【原文：Shares of Brazilian planemaker Embraer fell sharply on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would impose a 50% tariff on all imports from the South American country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/shares-brazils-embraer-slide-analysts-warn-impact-trump-tariffs-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONH4LFKFKFJLTJ3BP73N3XDBBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 16:39:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：华为在中东和东南亚寻求人工智能芯片交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，华为技术公司正试图向中东和东南亚出口少量人工智能芯片，以期在美国芯片设计公司英伟达（Nvidia）主导的市场站稳脚跟。【原文：Huawei Technologies is attempting to export small amounts of AI chips to the Middle East and Southeast Asia, as it looks to establish itself in markets dominated by U.S. chip designer Nvidia , Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/huawei-seeks-ai-chip-deals-middle-east-southeast-asia-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJCQCFZHYVIJDPR7RX57EIYJEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品集团 Cucinelli 上半年收入增长 10.7]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品集团布鲁内罗-库奇内利（Brunello Cucinelli）周四表示，按固定汇率计算，该集团今年上半年的收入增长了 10.7%，略高于分析师的预测。【原文：Revenues at Brunello Cucinelli rose 10.7% at constant exchange rates in the first half of the year, the Italian luxury group said on Thursday, slightly beating analysts forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italian-luxury-group-cucinelli-posts-107-increase-first-half-revenues-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7QOMLXOGZOFVGVL6SWSQIEJIA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官戴蒙称市场对美国利率上升的风险定价过低]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米-戴蒙（Jamie Dimon）周四表示，他认为市场低估了美国利率攀升的可能性，他认为这种可能性 "令人担忧"。【原文：JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon said on Thursday he thought the market was underestimating the possibility of U.S. interest rates climbing higher, a possibility he described as a "cause for concern".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-ceo-dimon-says-markets-under-pricing-risk-higher-us-interest-rates-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKHVJ4HZ5NIBTM3JGXE32KK7QM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构称，沃尔玛在接到三起受伤报告后召回 Ozark Trail 瓶装饮料]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费品安全委员会周四表示，在接到三起受伤报告后，沃尔玛召回了约 85 万个 Ozark Trail 水瓶。【原文：Walmart has recalled about 850,000 of its Ozark Trail water bottles after reports of three injuries, the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-recalls-ozark-trail-bottles-after-three-reported-injuries-us-agency-says-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCAQ4XJQTJLSBFFTV6KORTRFKY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[胡塞武装船只发动致命袭击后，红海保险费飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士周四表示，也门胡塞武装袭击并击沉了两艘船只，造成至少四名海员死亡，经过数月的平静之后，通过红海运输货物的保险费用在最近几天增加了一倍多。【原文：The insurance cost of shipping goods through the Red Sea has more than doubled in recent days after Yemen's Houthis attacked and sank two ships, killing at least four seafarers after months of calm, industry sources said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/red-sea-insurance-soars-after-deadly-houthi-ship-attacks-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6PRT45EIJNHLFXSMO4FIF3GFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:10:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果特朗普坚持对巴西征收关税，美国咖啡和橙汁价格可能飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商和专家周四表示，如果特朗普政府坚持对从巴西进口的所有商品征收50%关税的计划，美国消费者将面临咖啡和橙汁等主食价格大幅上涨的问题。【原文：U.S. consumers face sharp price rises on food staples like coffee and orange juice if the Trump administration sticks to its plan to slap 50% tariffs on all imports from Brazil, traders and experts said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-coffee-orange-juice-prices-could-surge-if-trumps-brazil-tariffs-stick-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXAMOTUUZJJT3OPOI62DKLMXB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西争相应对特朗普征收 50%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对巴西出口商品征收50%的关税，巴西慌忙应对，总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦周四召开紧急内阁会议，官员们努力缓和危机。【原文：Brazil scrambled to respond to U.S. President Donald Trump’s announcement of 50% tariffs on Brazilian exports, with President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva convening an urgent cabinet meeting on Thursday as officials worked to de-escalate the crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-scrambles-respond-trumps-50-tariffs-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IA7DO4TD4JIVLGZBNFC523AF4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[东京面临新关税，日本首相石破敦促减少对美国的依赖]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂（Shigeru Ishiba）周四表示，日本需要在安全、食品和能源等关键领域摆脱对美国的依赖。【原文：Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba said on Thursday his country needed to wean itself from U.S. dependence in such key areas as security, food and energy, as Tokyo faces the prospect of new U.S. tariffs in three weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-pm-ishiba-urges-less-us-dependence-tokyo-faces-new-tariffs-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7KZHIDYTFKSBG5UNRIN5YBVFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[收盘前积极的财报电话会议后，宝马股价上涨 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这家德国汽车制造商召开了广受好评的收盘前财报电话会议后，宝马股价周四攀升。【原文：Shares in BMW climbed on Thursday after the German automaker held a well-received pre-close earnings call.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-shares-rise-4-after-positive-pre-close-earnings-call-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76TAZIHSV5KKTMORIHOW3VCQNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:29:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究发现，人工智能拖慢了一些经验丰富的软件开发人员的速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项新的研究发现，与人们普遍认为的相反，当经验丰富的软件开发人员在他们熟悉的代码库中工作时，使用尖端的人工智能工具会降低他们的工作速度，而不是提高他们的工作效率。【原文：Contrary to popular belief, using cutting-edge artificial intelligence tools slowed down experienced software developers when they were working in codebases familiar to them, rather than supercharging their work, a new study found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-slows-down-some-experienced-software-developers-study-finds-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBMQWPAOHNN3JJM7ZN5NMSRZBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安托法加斯塔首席执行官称特朗普铜关税的背景可能有助于美国项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[铜矿商安托法加斯塔公司首席执行官伊万-阿里亚加达（Ivan Arriagada）在周四的一次活动上表示，在特朗普政府对金属征收50%关税的背景下，安托法加斯塔公司计划在美国开展的铜矿项目看到了机遇。【原文：Copper miner Antofagasta sees opportunity for its planned copper project in the United States in the context of 50% tariffs on the metal imposed by the Trump administration, CEO Ivan Arriagada said at an event on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/antofagasta-ceo-says-context-trump-copper-tariffs-could-help-us-project-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEQ6VC5B5RJYHKAWEC7SO54OKY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:49:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[淡马锡去年在欧洲投资 78 亿美元，看到了更多机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡国家投资者淡马锡周四告诉路透社，随着贸易紧张局势对经济环境的影响使一些公司的估值更具吸引力，淡马锡在欧洲看到了越来越多的投资机会。【原文：Singapore's state investor Temasek sees growing investment opportunities in Europe as the impact of trade tensions on the economic climate makes some companies more attractive in terms of valuations, a senior executive told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/temasek-sees-more-opportunities-europe-after-investing-78-bln-region-last-year-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZ5AK7VTO5N4TARLQEQUDLAQVY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:40:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗马尼亚在针对英国税务局的网络钓鱼欺诈案中逮捕 13 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国税务局（HMRC）周四表示，在针对英国税务局的网络钓鱼攻击后，罗马尼亚已有 13 人被捕，当局怀疑在这些攻击中，有人利用窃取的数据骗取了数百万英镑的税款。【原文：Thirteen people have been arrested in Romania after phishing attacks against Britain's tax office HMRC, in which authorities suspect stolen data was used to fraudulently obtain millions of pounds of tax payments, HMRC said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/romania-arrests-13-phishing-scam-targeting-british-tax-office-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34M4NUXFPBJKPFNZNC6OZ4AIDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:33:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最近一周每周申请失业救济人数意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，新申请失业救济金的美国人数量意外下降，这表明尽管有其他迹象表明劳动力市场正在降温，但雇主可能仍在留住工人。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for jobless benefits unexpectedly fell last week, suggesting employers may be holding on to workers despite other indications of a cooling labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-unexpectedly-latest-week-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLKUPCJQYZL6LN7W3UG2BYLQXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[仿人机器人初创公司 Diligent 聘请克鲁斯公司高管，将目光投向医疗保健以外的领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[仿人机器人制造商 Diligent Robotics 公司周四表示，该公司已从机器人出租车公司 Cruise 增聘了两名高管，准备将业务扩展到医院物流以外的领域。【原文：Diligent Robotics has added two top executives from robotaxi firm Cruise as it prepares to scale beyond hospital logistics, the humanoid robot maker said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/humanoid-robot-startup-diligent-taps-cruise-executives-it-looks-beyond-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHYEJJ537NJN5LG75XNAAO4M6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WK Kellogg 同意意大利费列罗公司 31 亿美元的收购交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[WK Kellogg 周四同意被 Ferrero Rocher 的所有者收购，交易价值约为 31 亿美元。【原文：WK Kellogg on Thursday agreed to be bought by the owner of Ferrero Rocher in a deal worth around $3.1 billion, as the cereal maker has been struggling with weakening consumer demand due to persistently high inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/wk-kellogg-agrees-31-billion-buyout-deal-by-italys-ferrero-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27XMCWQLSRM3HFLLE33DB4IFYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[恩智浦前员工因共享公司机密被判入狱三年]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰一家法院周四判处半导体公司 ASML 和恩智浦（NXP）的一名前雇员三年监禁，原因是他与俄罗斯的一名联系人分享了公司的敏感技术，违反了欧盟的制裁规定。
鹿特丹地方法院认定这名 43 岁的男子 German Aksenov 犯有入侵计算机和非法向俄罗斯提供技术援助的罪行。【原文：A Dutch court on Thursday sentenced a former employee of semiconductor firms ASML and NXP to three years in prison for sharing sensitive company technology with a contact in Russia, in violation of European Union sanctions.
The District Court of Rotterdam found the 43-year-old man, German Aksenov, guilty of computer intrusion and illegally providing technical assistance to Russia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ex-asml-nxp-employee-sentenced-three-year-jail-term-sharing-corporate-secrets-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RKMH4BZGZNANN7RRSW55VD2GU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德勤预测：经济困境缩减预算，返校开支将下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[德勤公司周四发布的一项预测显示，由于关税导致的价格上涨和经济不确定性迫使美国人紧缩家庭预算，预计今年返校开支将有所下降。【原文：Back-to-school spending is expected to dip this year, as tariff-driven price hikes and economic uncertainty force Americans to tighten household budgets, according to a Deloitte forecast released Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/back-to-school-spending-set-dip-economic-woes-shrink-budgets-deloitte-forecasts-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CAGQW5QWBOSNLQYHSO4KI35YQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Varda Space 公司融资 1.87 亿美元，加速太空药物开发]]></title><description><![CDATA[瓦尔达太空工业公司（Varda Space Industries）周四表示，该公司已在由风险投资公司自然资本（Natural Capital）和Shrug Capital领投的一轮融资中筹集到1.87亿美元，用于推动太空机器人药物制造技术的发展。【原文：Varda Space Industries said on Thursday it has raised $187 million in a funding round led by venture capital firms Natural Capital and Shrug Capital, to boost the technology for robotic drug manufacturing in space.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/varda-space-raises-187-million-accelerate-development-drugs-space-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUTZTOS6T5MF7ICFZWYWWJVQNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:45:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[后特朗普关税时代，铜贸易商寄望中国买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球铜贸易商正在向中国买家提供货物，因为他们希望在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收 50%铜关税的最后期限之前卸下无法运抵美国的金属。【原文：Global copper traders are offering cargoes to Chinese buyers as they look to offload metal no longer able to reach the U.S. before President Donald Trump's 50% copper tariff deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/copper-traders-look-chinese-buyers-post-trump-tariff-world-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDQFZOWXMBOBTJFK4RAP4BMA54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:23:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国再次因螺旋虫害停止从墨西哥进口牛只]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于破坏性牲畜害虫新世界螺虫在墨西哥蔓延，美国农业部再次停止向美国进口墨西哥牛。【原文：The U.S. Department of Agriculture has again halted imports of Mexican cattle into the United States due to the spread of the damaging livestock pest New World Screwworm in Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-again-halts-cattle-imports-mexico-over-screwworm-pest-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2BSW3FIPNNPVFKNBXZFS7CFEE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其竞争委员会对谷歌处以 890 万美元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其竞争管理局周四表示，已决定对谷歌处以约3.55亿里拉（约合887万美元）的行政罚款，原因是谷歌未能履行监管义务。【原文：The Turkish Competition Authority said on Thursday it had decided to impose an administrative fine of around 355 million lira ($8.87 million) on Google for failing to comply with regulatory obligations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/turkeys-competition-board-imposes-89-million-fine-google-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCMETYYWNRJBXLM4BYJWIHYUVM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，Conagra 预计全年利润下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[瘦肉精零食生产商康奈格拉品牌公司（Conagra Brands）周四预测年度利润低于预期，原因是预计美国关税将导致原料成本上升。【原文：Slim Jim snack maker Conagra Brands forecast annual profit below expectations on Thursday, anticipating higher costs of ingredients due to U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/conagra-forecasts-annual-profit-below-expectations-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVS5BAT2BJOI5CMYNHKPO5QIR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:37:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私募市场金融科技公司 iCapital 在最新融资中估值超过 75 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[另类投资金融科技公司iCapital周四表示，在最新一轮外部融资中，该公司估值超过75亿美元，融资额超过8.2亿美元，凸显出投资者对扩大私人市场战略渠道的平台的兴趣与日俱增。【原文：Alternative investments fintech iCapital was valued at more than $7.5 billion in its latest external funding round, where it raised more than $820 million, the company said on Thursday, highlighting increasing investor interest in platforms that expand access to private-market strategies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/private-market-fintech-icapital-valued-over-75-billion-latest-fundraise-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YYXOMVGN5M4FLRY4EHKREXTMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰数据监管机构就存储在中国的数据对 TikTok 展开新调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰强大的数据保护委员会周四表示，已对 TikTok 在中国服务器上存储欧洲用户数据一事展开新的调查。【原文：Ireland's powerful Data Protection Commission has opened a new inquiry into TikTok over the storage of European users' data on servers in China, the regulator said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/irish-data-regulator-opens-new-inquiry-into-tiktok-over-data-stored-china-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3AJ4U2K75JAHLQT62SFOWHRTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:25:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司任命拉尔斯-瓦格纳自 2026 年起担任其商用飞机业务首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司周四表示，拉尔斯-瓦格纳将从 2026 年 1 月 1 日起担任其商用飞机业务首席执行官。【原文：Airbus said on Thursday that Lars Wagner would become the CEO of its commercial aircraft business from January 1, 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-taps-lars-wagner-ceo-its-commercial-aircraft-business-2026-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TEKFFKJPFIGPNQVVFBKXQJW6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:23:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国警方逮捕四名与 M&S、Co-op 和 Harrods 网络攻击事件有关的人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国国家打击犯罪局称，警方对扰乱零售商玛莎百货、Co-op 和哈罗德百货运营的网络攻击进行了调查，并逮捕了四人。【原文：Four people have been arrested as part of a police investigation into cyberattacks that disrupted the operations of retailers Marks & Spencer , the Co-op and Harrods, Britain's National Crime Agency said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uk-police-arrest-four-connection-with-ms-co-op-cyberattacks-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOXIT7DFZZKCDONOP2A73Z2PFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞购：4 万亿美元的英伟达掩盖了新关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRPVSYBBZVP45CMSBEWF3BNIV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>