<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 12:47:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 12:47:36 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[冯德莱恩表示，欧盟将提出针对初创企业的统一规则，以帮助它们成长]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟行政首长周五表示，欧盟计划明年提出一套针对初创企业的单一规则，以帮助集团内的创新企业在整个地区发展和运营，并更容易留住人才。【原文：The European Union plans to propose a single set of rules for startups next year to help the bloc's innovative companies grow and operate across the region and find it easier to retain talent, the head of EU's executive said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-propose-uniform-rules-startups-help-them-grow-von-der-leyen-says-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IV2XBYQ2FIHBL3A26L4AGT6AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:45:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受降息预期影响，美国股票基金每周资金大幅流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 1 日的一周，美国股票基金因再次押注降息而出现强劲流入，因为一份通胀报告缓解了人们对物价上涨将促使美联储推迟对疲软的劳动力市场提供政策支持的担忧。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw robust inflows in the week to October 1 on renewed bets of rate cuts, as an inflation report eased worries that a buildup in prices would push the Federal Reserve to delay policy support for a weakening labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-sharp-weekly-inflows-rate-cut-hopes-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEURJWT2X5NUFLLSNUEXGDFH4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:33:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年迄今发生的美国炼油厂火灾事故]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，雪佛龙公司在洛杉矶附近日产量 28.5 万桶的埃尔塞贡多炼油厂的喷气燃料装置发生火灾，火焰和浓烟弥漫在空中。【原文：A fire broke out in a jet fuel unit at Chevron's 285,000 barrel-per-day El Segundo refinery near Los Angeles on Thursday, sending flames and smoke into the air.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refinery-fire-incidents-so-far-2025-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ4WGM25CJNDVBEIIHLPDYRYGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:26:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔里萨公司计划斥资5.47亿美元建设地下铂矿项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非 Tharisa Plc 公司周五宣布，计划在未来十年内斥资 5.47 亿美元建设一个地下铂族金属开采项目，希望这些金属能成为全球向清洁能源技术转变过程中不可或缺的一部分。【原文：South Africa's Tharisa Plc announced plans on Friday to spend $547 million on an underground platinum group metals mining project over the next decade, betting on the metals being integral to the global shift to cleaner energy technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/tharisa-plans-spend-547-million-underground-platinum-mine-project-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5KKU345ANMDDHY5EJHGJSWNQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:13:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据库初创公司 Supabase 在本轮融资中估值达 50 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[开源数据库初创公司 Supabase 周五表示，它已在一轮融资中筹集到 1 亿美元，估值达 50 亿美元。【原文：Open-source database startup Supabase said on Friday it has raised $100 million in a funding round, which valued it at $5 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/database-startup-supabase-notches-5-billion-valuation-funding-round-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4JELGSQZNK6BLUBQEAAJ5OFVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因押注美联储降息，全球股票基金流入量创 11 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 1 日的一周内，全球股票基金需求旺盛，原因是美国通胀报告与预期持平，而民间就业数据弱于预期，重新燃起了人们对美联储降息的希望。【原文：Global equity funds witnessed robust demand in the week through October 1 as an inline U.S. inflation report and weaker-than-expected private payrolls data renewed hopes of Federal Reserve rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJUAWTAHUVM7LH4TBNKQCJ5R4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟冯德莱恩敦促欧洲推动人工智能汽车发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）周五呼吁在整个欧洲范围内推动自动驾驶汽车的发展，称人工智能有助于重振该地区陷入困境的汽车行业并改善道路安全。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen called on Friday for a continent-wide push to develop self-driving cars, saying artificial intelligence could help revive the region's struggling automotive sector and improve road safety.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/eus-von-der-leyen-urges-european-push-ai-driven-cars-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H56ADMRJ3VOHHC7XN2H2I6L5NM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:46:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早安保持冷静，继续前进]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZQAWFBRNBPK5H2AZHCQ4ASHGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:45:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社报道后，数十部宝莱坞人工智能视频从 YouTube 上消失]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，谷歌的 YouTube 上已删除了数百部人工智能生成的宝莱坞视频，这些视频的浏览量高达 1600 万次。【原文：Hundreds of AI-generated Bollywood videos with 16 million views have been deleted from Google's YouTube after Reuters reported they were similar to those at the centre of a legal challenge filed by a celebrity couple to protect their rights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/scores-bollywood-ai-videos-vanish-youtube-after-reuters-story-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDWUJCRVWVLR3J3NEM4EZEIJ7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯称央行必须做好应对意外的准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，不可预测的变化是不可避免的，中央银行需要意识到这一点，并制定在这些环境中运作的策略。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams said Friday that unpredictable change is inevitable and central banks need to be aware of that and have strategies to operate in those environments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-williams-says-central-banks-must-prepare-unexpected-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I7H2F5ZFBLMNLLQIKQ7Z7XXTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[冰封的薪资数据给华尔街带来了新的自由时间，但解读经济却存在很大问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国就业数据的发布通常会让交易员和投资者在早上 8:30 就守在屏幕前，等待这些至关重要的数据。然而，本周五的数据却让一些人突然有了更多的空闲时间，同时还面临着试图从其他来源拼凑经济拼图的问题。【原文：The release of U.S. jobs data typically has traders and investors glued to their screens at 8:30 am waiting for the all-important numbers. This Friday, however, is giving some a sudden surplus of free time along with the problem of trying to piece together the economic jigsaw puzzle from other sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/payroll-data-ice-gives-wall-street-newfound-free-time-big-problem-reading-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAV3V52AVZIOXHGTNABINQH6NQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[陆军备忘录称，Anduril 和 Palantir 战场通信系统存在严重缺陷]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份最新的陆军内部备忘录，Anduril、Palantir 和其他公司正在对美国陆军亟需的战场通信网络进行现代化改造，但这一改造充斥着 "基本安全 "问题和漏洞，应被视为 "极高风险"。【原文：The much-needed modernization of the U.S. Army's battlefield communications network being undertaken by Anduril, Palantir and others is rife with "fundamental security" problems and vulnerabilities, and should be treated as a "very high risk," according to a recent internal Army memo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/anduril-palantir-battlefield-communication-system-has-deep-flaws-army-memo-says-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GS7X54C43RIQBBV276CHWC3SLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 华尔街关注华盛顿对峙，股市接近历史纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[在市场进入季节性强劲的第四季度之际，美国政府停摆成为投资者下周的首要议题，接近历史高点的股市正准备迎接本月晚些时候财报季的考验。【原文：The U.S. government shutdown tops investors' agenda next week as markets head into the seasonally strong fourth quarter, with equities near record highs bracing for an earnings-season test later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-wall-st-eyes-washington-standoff-with-stocks-near-records-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72QZBMW3VNMHPHEIYSOXZRQJII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被大买家中国抛弃的美国豆农争相寻找其他进口商]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼日利亚贸易代表团。与越南签署谅解备忘录。从孟加拉国的采购激增。【原文：A trade mission to Nigeria. A memorandum of understanding with Vietnam. A surge of purchases from Bangladesh.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-soybean-farmers-deserted-by-big-buyer-china-scramble-other-importers-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQJT7PVWKJLQDO53SYF3CZ74GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货在动荡一周的最后一个交易日攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周动荡不安的最后一个交易日，美国股指期货周五上涨，因为降息的希望支撑了市场情绪。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday as hopes of an interest rate cut underpinned sentiment in the final trading session of a volatile week, marked by a government shutdown that has dragged into its third day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/wall-street-futures-climb-final-session-volatile-week-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGERSU4BU5JWXNC7WJ3X3LTP3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 09:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国稀土股价大涨，此前有报道称矿商正在与白宫进行密切谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，美国稀土矿业公司首席执行官芭芭拉-汉普顿（Barbara Humpton）表示，该公司正在与白宫进行密切讨论，随后该公司股价在周五的盘前交易中大涨 10%。【原文：USA Rare Earth shares jumped 10% in premarket trading on Friday, after a report that the mining company's CEO Barbara Humpton said it was in close discussions with the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/usa-rare-earth-shares-surge-after-report-miner-close-talks-with-white-house-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H23EE6QQRVO3ZIWSGSAG6JED7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 09:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Five：前方能见度低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府已经关门，但这并不妨碍股市再创新高，因为人们完全相信，看涨的降息政策将使股市保持良好势头。唯一的障碍是，人们对当前经济的实际情况完全不了解。【原文：The U.S. government has shut down, but that hasn't prevented stocks from hitting more record highs, fully confident that bullish rate cuts will keep momentum going. The one hitch is a complete lack of visibility when it comes to what is actually happening in the economy right now.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/take-five/global-markets-themes-graphic-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TK2EBSJ62NJORMCV7XQY5S5G7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 09:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[糖和乳制品价格下跌抵消了肉类价格的新高，世界食品价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国粮食及农业组织周五表示，由于糖和乳制品价格的下跌抵消了肉类价格的新高，9月份全球食品商品价格出现下滑。【原文：Global food commodity prices dipped in September as declines in sugar and dairy offset a new peak for meat prices, the United Nations' Food and Agriculture Organization said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-food-prices-dip-falls-sugar-dairy-offset-new-high-meat-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7AJW7OMD5MX5EH6ZWT7H5NHAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 08:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉公司称开始在卡塔尔销售 Cybertrucks]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电动汽车制造商特斯拉周五在 X 上发帖称，继今年早些时候在沙特阿拉伯开展业务后，特斯拉现已开始在卡塔尔销售 Cybertruck。【原文：Tesla has now begun selling its Cybertruck in Qatar, the U.S. electric vehicle maker said in a post on X on Friday, following the launch of its operations in Saudi Arabia earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-begins-selling-cybertrucks-qatar-company-says-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5LBPZPMKFNEDEXYKFMMCSXSME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 08:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关系紧张，印度部长力推谷歌和微软应用程序的国内替代方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪（Narendra Modi）的三位内阁同事正在推广使用谷歌地图、WhatsApp 和微软的国内竞争对手的应用程序，这是在与美国贸易关系紧张的情况下对 "印度制造 "产品的最有力支持。【原文：Three cabinet colleagues of Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi are promoting use of apps by domestic rivals to Google Maps, WhatsApp and Microsoft, in the strongest backing yet for "Made in India" products amid trade tension with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-ministers-push-domestic-alternatives-google-microsoft-apps-amid-strained-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BW6TWDXAEJPL7P3TIS32CN3LTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 08:38:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，雅吉欧成功以 7.4 亿美元要约收购芝浦电子公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾雅吉欧公司在周五提交的一份文件中说，由于大多数股东同意其每股7130日元（48.32美元）的出价，该公司已成功地以7.4亿美元主动竞购日本芝浦电子公司。【原文：Taiwan's Yageo has succeeded in its $740 million unsolicited bid to buy Japan's Shibaura Electronics as a majority of shareholders tendered to its bid of 7,130 yen ($48.32) per share, it said in a filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yageo-succeeds-740-million-tender-offer-shibaura-electronics-filing-shows-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3XXWERVNNIRRMLSLZ3YEUMQ3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 07:49:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[融资激增，人工智能初创企业估值引发泡沫担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创企业正在吸引创纪录的风险投资，但一些全球最大的投资者周五警告说，早期阶段的估值开始显得泡沫化。【原文：Artificial intelligence startups are attracting record sums of venture capital, but some of the world's largest investors warned that early-stage valuations are starting to look frothy, senior investment executives said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/ai-startup-valuations-raise-bubble-fears-funding-surges-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HV3WEW2AFN7LDUVTOY44BK64E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 07:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[喝完了：网络攻击停摆，日本朝日啤酒即将枯竭]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本餐厅、酒吧和商店的啤酒和行业领先企业朝日集团（Asahi Group）的其他饮料供应不足，因为网络攻击造成的影响周五已进入第五天，目前仍未看到任何解决方案。【原文：Japanese restaurants, bars and stores are running low on beer and other beverages from industry leader Asahi Group as the impact from a cyberattack entered a fifth day on Friday, with no resolution in sight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tapped-out-asahi-beers-running-dry-japan-cyberattack-shutdown-lingers-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DYWR4FVGNKHTD7Y7YKVIRIJHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 07:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产汽车将召回 1.9 万多辆美国汽车，理由是快速充电存在起火风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，日产汽车将在美国召回19,077辆电动汽车，原因是这些汽车在快速充电过程中可能因过热而起火。【原文：Nissan is recalling 19,077 electric vehicles in the United States due to a potential fire risk linked to overheating during quick charging, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-recall-over-19000-us-vehicles-citing-quick-charging-fire-risk-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KMOKENY5FKBPO35KS6O2Z6BV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 07:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼部委称 TikTok 因数据共享失败而暂停注册]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼表示，由于 TikTok 未能交出与使用其直播流功能有关的所有数据，印尼已暂停其作为电子系统供应商的注册资格，尽管周五用户仍可访问该社交媒体应用程序。【原文：Indonesia said it has suspended TikTok's registration status as an electronic system provider after it failed to hand over all data relating to the use of its live stream feature, though the social media app was still accessible to users on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/indonesia-suspends-tiktok-registration-over-data-sharing-failures-ministry-says-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCEMADOLYBKRBAHHV435EZOUEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 06:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科蒂（Coty）的消费者美容产品线看起来很难卖出去]]></title><description><![CDATA[品牌老化和销售额下降可能会使科蒂的化妆品业务难以出售，从而引发零散交易或收益低于预期的前景，这可能会使该集团削减债务和投资增长的计划复杂化。【原文：Ageing brands and declining sales could make Coty's makeup business a hard sell, raising the prospect of piecemeal deals or lower than expected proceeds that might complicate the group's plans to cut debt and invest in growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cotys-consumer-beauty-line-looks-like-hard-sell-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAJZD2JM7BLTNG5RPXZEGBGAIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 06:03:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗氏董事Suessmuth Dyckerhoff将退出董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗氏公司周五表示，Claudia Suessmuth Dyckerhoff 将不再竞选连任制药公司董事会成员。【原文：Roche said on Friday Claudia Suessmuth Dyckerhoff would not stand for re-election as a member of the pharma company's board of directors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/roche-director-suessmuth-dyckerhoff-stand-down-board-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCG5H3EQMBM7LL3LW57LAAFCFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛杉矶雪佛龙埃尔塞贡多炼油厂发生火灾]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州州长加文-纽森（Gavin Newsom）的新闻办公室周四表示，雪佛龙公司的埃尔塞贡多炼油厂发生火灾，这是美国西海岸最大的炼油厂之一。【原文：A fire broke out at Chevron's El Segundo refinery, one of the largest on the U.S. west coast, California Governor Gavin Newsom's press office said on Thursday, with a county official adding that the flames had been confined to one area.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fire-breaks-out-chevrons-refinery-el-segundo-la-times-says-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57ACGZQNXNI3HHWAQ4D56H4GCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:13:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储重启宽松政策，外国投资者可利用更便宜的美元对冲工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[期待已久的美联储降息周期的重启，很可能会降低外国投资者对美元风险敞口的对冲成本，并提高他们保护更多美国资产以防货币进一步走软的积极性。【原文：The long-awaited resumption of the Federal Reserve's rate-cutting cycle is likely to cheapen hedging of dollar exposure for foreign investors and increase their motivation to guard more of their U.S. assets against further currency weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/foreign-investors-can-exploit-cheaper-dollar-hedges-fed-easing-resumes-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRYJBWMMBJJMTJ4XMH3ZS7SMZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 美国政治无法关闭动物精神]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天：【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHJUAECPT5JLXMCCJUONM7GSCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 04:33:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>