<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 21:33:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 21:33:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[苹果任命内部人士凯文-帕瑞克（Kevan Parekh）为财务总监，取代梅斯特里]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周一任命内部人士凯文-帕瑞克（Kevan Parekh）为首席财务官，接替将于 2025 年 1 月 1 日卸任的卢卡-梅斯特里（Luca Maestri）。【原文：Apple on Monday named insider Kevan Parekh as its chief financial officer, replacing Luca Maestri who will transition from the role on Jan. 1, 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-finance-chief-luca-maestri-step-down-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCMEBOYJWZNU7OP6DQ4GE4BPRY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 20:38:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织任命牙买加财政部长担任副职]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）周一任命牙买加财政部长奈杰尔-克拉克（Nigel Clarke）担任该机构的高级职务，在此之前，这位官员曾率先在这个加勒比国家进行财政改革。【原文：The International Monetary Fund on Monday named Jamaican Finance Minister Nigel Clarke to a top post at the agency, after the official spearheaded fiscal reforms in the Caribbean nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/imf-taps-jamaica-finance-minister-deputy-role-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2AUAO6FDRI7TJJ2QGMIW7IARE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 20:22:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行业输掉对 CFPB 小企业贷款规则的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）通过了一项规定，要求贷款机构收集小企业借款人的人口统计数据，一名联邦法官周一驳回了银行业支持的对该规定的质疑。【原文：A federal judge on Monday rejected a banking industry-backed challenge to a rule adopted by the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau that requires lenders to gather demographic data on small business borrowers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/banking-industry-loses-challenge-cfpb-small-business-loan-rule-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QB3OKBHKXFOKPFHECCXM372PK4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 19:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会称，纽约梅隆银行将就掉期报告和监管失误支付 500 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会（Commodity Futures Trading Commission）指控纽约梅隆银行（Bank of New York Mellon）多次未能正确报告数百万笔掉期交易，违反了之前的一项命令，该监管机构在周一的一份声明中表示，同意支付 500 万美元和解。【原文：The Bank of New York Mellon has agreed to pay $5 million to settle U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission charges for repeatedly failing to correctly report millions of swap transactions, violating a previous order, the regulator said in a statement on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-new-york-mellon-pay-5-mln-over-swap-reporting-supervision-failures-cftc-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDDPMN5CXZJKJMO5N6V4I2QPJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 19:44:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴利称美联储下月最有可能降息四分之一个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联储主席玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周一表示，降息的 "时机已到"，可能首先将借贷成本降低四分之一个百分点。
当被问及是否有什么事情会破坏美国央行在9月17-18日政策会议上的降息行动时，戴利告诉彭博电视台，"目前很难想象"。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve President Mary Daly on Monday said "the time is upon us" to cut interest rates, likely starting with a quarter-percentage point reduction in borrowing costs.
Asked if there is anything that could derail a rate cut at the U.S. central bank's Sept. 17-18 policy meeting, Daly told Bloomberg TV that it "would be hard to imagine at this point."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-most-likely-cut-rates-by-quarter-percentage-point-next-month-daly-says-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGSN3MIOAVKMXKW7MYZWRLBA7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 19:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大停工结束后，美国铁路取消禁运]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国诺福克南方铁路公司（Norfolk Southern）和 BNSF 铁路公司周一表示，与加拿大可能发生的停工有关的所有禁运均已取消，受影响的铁路运输已经恢复，从而结束了前所未有的跨境货物运输服务中断。【原文：U.S. railroads Norfolk Southern and BNSF Railway on Monday said all embargoes associated with the potential Canadian work stoppage stand canceled and affected rail traffic has resumed, putting an end to an unprecedented service disruption in the movement of goods across the border.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-rails-cancel-embargoes-after-canada-work-stoppage-ends-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56FIP3YIWROVHOJFAWZFBWKOVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:29:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通因低利率扫码取现遭起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通在一项新的诉讼中被指控将客户的闲置现金转入利率 "不合理 "的低账户。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has been accused in a new lawsuit of sweeping customers' idle cash into accounts with "unreasonably" low interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/jpmorgan-chase-is-sued-over-low-rates-cash-sweeps-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCJXZLYQAVK3PMXWNC4QNQ7UIE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:24:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 与 Sage Geosystems 达成地热能源协议，为数据中心供电]]></title><description><![CDATA[Facebook 的所有者 Meta Platforms 周一在一份声明中表示，该公司向 Sage Geosystems 公司购买多达 150 兆瓦的地热能，用于为其数据中心供电，因为该公司正在努力建设基础设施，以支持其大量耗能的人工智能投资。【原文：Facebook owner Meta Platforms struck a deal to buy up to 150 MW of geothermal power from Sage Geosystems to supply its data centers, as it races to build out the infrastructure to support its massive energy-hungry artificial intelligence investments, it said in a statement on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/meta-strikes-geothermal-energy-deal-with-sage-geosystems-power-data-centers-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNXOGZOGLNMJ5G3I3EEI5DRWLU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 17:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航空监管机构敦促全球努力解决气流问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[在蒙特利尔举行的一次监管机构会议上，最近发生的一些备受瞩目的事件促使人们呼吁改进跨境预测。【原文：Recent high-profile incidents are prompting calls to improve forecasting across borders at a Montreal gathering of regulators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aviation-regulators-press-global-efforts-tackle-turbulence-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33XYIX4USNM4NKGZGR2XPAGJVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 17:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[壳牌计划关闭 Zydeco 输油管道的不同部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[壳牌石油公司周一表示，计划从 9 月 24 日起关闭其 Zydeco 输油管道系统的不同部分，为期三至四天。【原文：Oil major Shell on Monday said it plans to shut-in different portions of its Zydeco pipeline system for three to four days starting Sept 24.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-plans-shut-in-different-portions-zydeco-pipeline-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDS6IDUBZNJRTJ2R2NDJBZTOI4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 16:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Care.com 就会员续费问题与美国联邦贸易委员会达成 850 万美元的和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Care.com 是一个为儿童、老年人和宠物提供居家护理服务的平台，该公司同意支付 850 万美元，以了结美国联邦贸易委员会对其严重夸大可用工作数量并使客户难以取消会员资格的指控。【原文：Care.com, a platform for providing in-home care services to children, older adults and pets, agreed to pay $8.5 million to settle U.S. Federal Trade Commission charges it grossly inflated the number of available jobs and made it difficult for customers to cancel memberships.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/carecom-reaches-85-million-settlement-with-us-ftc-over-membership-renewals-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFJSD6I63JOJTJF3Z7BW2SLPX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 16:45:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工机构称，Chipotle 拒绝为工会工人加薪]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会检察官认定，一家工会声称 Chipotle Mexican Grill 公司非法拒绝为密歇根州一家餐厅的工人加薪，因为这些工人是该快餐连锁店第一批也是唯一一批加入工会的员工。【原文：U.S. labor board prosecutors have determined that a union's claims that Chipotle Mexican Grill illegally refused to give raises to workers at a Michigan restaurant after they became the first and only employees of the fast-casual chain to unionize have merit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chipotle-denied-raises-unionized-workers-us-labor-agency-says-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUWDDWODZNPIPPUAXFSH7KADT4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 16:31:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司将于 9 月 9 日举行秋季发布会，预计将推出新款 iPhone]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周一表示，将于 9 月 9 日在加利福尼亚州库比蒂诺举行秋季新品发布会，预计届时将推出新款 iPhone 系列。【原文：Apple said on Monday it will hold its fall event on Sept. 9 in Cupertino, California, during which it is expected to launch its new iPhone series.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-hold-its-fall-event-sept-9-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCMLSSAN4RLZ7BMBIQXPCPYZG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 16:20:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[红龙虾在破产退出计划中聘请前 P.F. Chang's 负责人担任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资管理公司 Fortress 周一表示，在法庭批准 Red Lobster 连锁餐厅的破产计划后，P.F. Chang's 前首席执行官 Damola Adamolekun 将执掌 Red Lobster。【原文：Damola Adamolekun, former CEO of P.F. Chang's, will take the helm at Red Lobster after a court approval of the restaurant chain's bankruptcy plan, investment management firm Fortress said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/red-lobster-taps-former-pf-changs-head-ceo-bankruptcy-exit-plan-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPQOXCXFHJKFHATQFNYIHO7LQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊坎企业将出售价值最多 4 亿美元的股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者卡尔-伊坎（Carl Icahn）的公司伊坎企业（Icahn Enterprises）在周一提交的一份监管文件中表示，该公司已申请通过 "场内 "发行计划出售最多 4 亿美元的存托单位，这导致其股价下跌近 3%。【原文：Billionaire investor Carl Icahn's firm Icahn Enterprises has filed to sell up to $400 million depository units through an "at-the-market" offering program, the company said in a regulatory filing on Monday, sending its shares down nearly 3%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/icahn-enterprises-sell-up-400-mln-worth-shares-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSODRFGK65KIPPFOEGQI7AWQXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 14:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛、巴斯夫和其他公司达成 2,000 万美元的铂金和钯金价格操纵和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）、德国工业公司巴斯夫（BASF）和另外两家银行同意支付 2000 万美元，以了结一项长达近十年的反垄断诉讼，该诉讼指控高盛、巴斯夫和另外两家银行合谋压低铂金和钯金价格。【原文：Goldman Sachs , German industrial company BASF and two other banks agreed to pay $20 million to settle a nearly decade-old antitrust lawsuit accusing them of conspiring to suppress platinum and palladium prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/goldman-basf-others-20-million-platinum-palladium-price-fixing-settlement-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T46O5U4MMVMDRI74D6GRVBULYU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 14:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员巴尔金告诉 BBG，美国公司的 "低解雇 "做法可能会导致更多裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）在最新发表的评论中表示，美国企业目前采取的 "低招聘、低解雇 "的就业决策方式不太可能持久，他提到了如果经济疲软，企业可能采取裁员措施的风险。【原文：The "low-hiring, low-firing" approach that U.S. businesses currently take to their employment decisions is unlikely to last, Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said in newly released comments, citing the risk that firms could resort to layoffs if the economy weakens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-firms-low-firing-approach-may-turn-more-layoffs-feds-barkin-tells-bbg-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TIDW6Y3OBNDVND7OKOX6BXEEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 14:12:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Trintech 的所有者正在探讨以 20 亿美元出售金融软件制造商的事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，私募股权公司 Summit Partners 和 Vista Equity Partners 正在探讨出售 Trintech 的可能性，包括债务在内，这家金融软件供应商的估值可能在 20 亿美元左右。【原文：Private equity firms Summit Partners and Vista Equity Partners are exploring a potential sale of Trintech that could value the financial software provider at about $2 billion, including debt, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trintechs-owners-explore-2-billion-sale-financial-software-maker-sources-say-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AURSZRIPRRNBJHLZG4ZHVIL2WI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 13:35:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 支持要求对合成内容进行 "水印 "处理的加州人工智能法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[ChatGPT 开发商 OpenAI 支持加利福尼亚州的一项法案，该法案将要求科技公司对人工智能生成的内容进行标注，这些内容既包括无害的备忘录，也包括旨在传播政治候选人错误信息的深度伪造内容。【原文：ChatGPT developer OpenAI is supporting a California bill that would require tech companies to label AI-generated content, which can range from harmless memes to deepfakes aimed at spreading misinformation about political candidates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-supports-california-ai-bill-requiring-watermarking-synthetic-content-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOTWYSIHAVNUDK665YLXP2GT3Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 13:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特鲁多称加拿大将对中国电动汽车征收 100% 关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理贾斯汀-特鲁多（Justin Trudeau）周一表示，加拿大将对进口中国电动汽车征收 100%的关税。【原文：Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said on Monday that Canada will impose a 100% tariff on the import of Chinese electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trudeau-says-canada-impose-100-tariff-chinese-evs-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D42RMB5VBFPHXIMB7MDWDSOZ6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 12:57:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月份核心资本货物订单下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份美国主要制造业资本货物的新订单出人意料地减少，上个月的数据也被下调，这表明企业设备支出的势头减弱，并延续到第三季度初。【原文：New orders for key U.S.-manufactured capital goods unexpectedly fell in July and data for the prior month was revised lower, suggesting a loss of momentum in business spending on equipment that extended into the early part of the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-core-capital-goods-orders-dip-july-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAYKCXTKJ5LRXAZCHKNPLBW2UQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 12:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司预测 2050 年的石油需求将与目前相当，比英国石油公司的估计高出 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚（Exxon Mobil）周一表示，预计到 2050 年，原油需求将保持在每天 1 亿桶以上，与目前的水平类似，这一预测比欧洲最大的竞争对手英国石油公司（BP）高出 25%。【原文：Exxon Mobil said on Monday it expects crude demand to stay above 100 million barrels per day (bpd) through 2050, similar to today's levels, a forecast 25% higher than top European rival BP .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-forecasts-2050-oil-demand-match-todays-25-above-bp-estimate-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3KMB7ZSGJINDMRYLFJC6LAHIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 12:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[McKesson 将以约 25 亿美元收购佛罗里达癌症专科部门的控股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[药品分销商麦可森公司（McKesson）周一表示，将以 24.9 亿美元现金收购社区癌症中心佛罗里达癌症专科研究所（FCS）业务和行政服务部门的控股权。【原文：Drug distributor McKesson said on Monday it would buy a controlling stake in community cancer center Florida Cancer Specialists &amp; Research Institute's (FCS) business and administrative services unit for $2.49 billion in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drug-distributor-mckesson-buy-controlling-stake-core-ventures-about-25-bln-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SRER4N6IFKO3LZV6466NBUGUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 12:16:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃利奥特在信中为西南航空领导层换届陈述理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）告诉西南航空公司的投资者，该公司需要新的外部领导层，并表示希望与西南航空公司共同打造 "更美好的未来"，但同时也准备继续推进计划中的代理权争夺战。【原文：Elliott Investment Management is telling Southwest Airlines investors the company needs new outside leadership and that it wants to engage to shape a "better future" but is also ready to press ahead with a planned proxy fight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/elliott-lays-out-its-case-letter-leadership-change-southwest-airlines-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6BWLPVE4JIQ5FWG45V5UWYN3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 11:36:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多伦多证券交易所期货因商品价格上涨而上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于原油和金属价格上涨，与加拿大主要股票指数挂钩的期货周一上涨，而投资者则对美国联邦储备委员会主席周五发表的支持在 9 月份启动降息周期的言论感到高兴。【原文：Futures linked to Canada's main stock index rose on Monday due to a rise in crude and metal prices, while investors cheered the U.S. Federal Reserve Chair's comments on Friday that endorsed the start of the rate-cut cycle in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tsx-futures-edge-up-higher-commodity-prices-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2J272ART5P3VCSDKTKXEMVISQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:45:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Temu 公司所有者 PDD 控股公司季度收入未达预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，中国点点客控股公司（PDD Holdings）的季度营收不及市场预期，国内电子商务平台拼多多（Pinduoduo）的业务也因消费疲软而受挫，导致该公司股价在盘前交易中下跌近14%。【原文：China's PDD Holdings missed market estimates for quarterly revenue on Monday, as frail consumer spending dented business at its domestic e-commerce platform Pinduoduo, sending the company's shares down nearly 14% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/temu-owner-pdd-holdings-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYPXC7F4EZKWVOMDG47I2EZFBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:36:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技巨头敦促马来西亚暂停社交媒体平台许可证计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个包括谷歌、Meta 和 X 在内的亚洲行业组织呼吁马来西亚政府暂停一项要求社交媒体服务申请许可证的计划，理由是拟议的法规不明确。【原文：An Asian industry group that includes Google , Meta and X has called on the Malaysian government to pause a plan that will require social media services to apply for a license, citing a lack of clarity over the proposed regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tech-giants-urge-malaysia-pause-plan-social-media-platform-licenses-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TARYYBNWTBMAVPLB4S4UB4OPMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期货因 9 月降息希望而上涨；英伟达业绩可期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货走高，投资者主要关注人工智能热门公司英伟达（Nvidia）的业绩以及本周晚些时候将公布的一份关键通胀报告，同时对美国央行 9 月份降息的信心依然高涨。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Monday, with investors focused mainly on results from AI-favorite Nvidia and a key inflation report due later in the week, while confidence in a September interest-rate cut by the central bank remained high.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-up-september-rate-cut-hopes-nvidia-results-view-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDMLTTQIANO4NFCDBBAJGX4ZNE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储已转向就业市场风险，现在政策必须跟上]]></title><description><![CDATA[2022 年，当美联储的工作重心转向抗击通胀时，它不得不快速提高利率，以使货币政策赶上快速上涨的物价。【原文：In 2022, when the Federal Reserve's focus shifted to combating inflation, it had to ratchet up interest rates fast to get monetary policy caught up with fast-rising prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-shift-job-market-risks-is-done-now-policy-has-catch-up-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5S6OQYDZYJPLTMBVEYMVPP6O2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格案考验联邦贸易委员会主席汗保护工人的努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，联邦贸易委员会主席莉娜-卡恩（Lina Khan）提出的利用反垄断法保护工人的倡议面临关键考验，该机构将辩称，杂货连锁店克罗格（Kroger）与其竞争对手阿尔伯森（Albertsons）的合并将削弱工会工人的谈判能力。【原文：Federal Trade Commission Chair Lina Khan's initiative to use antitrust laws to protect workers faces a key test on Monday when the agency will argue the merger between grocery chain Kroger and its rival Albertsons would crush unionized workers' bargaining power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kroger-case-tests-ftc-chair-khans-bid-protect-workers-2024-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5SWENUU45LDDCUM6IDEZBZOCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>