<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 17:34:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 17:34:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[检察官称，阿达尼斯在向道达尔能源公司出售与贿赂有关的资产时知道美国的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[检察官在路透社查阅的法律文件中指控，高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）和萨加尔-阿达尼（Sagar Adani）在将印度最大太阳能园区的一部分出售给法国道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）时，知道他们的可再生能源公司因涉嫌贿赂正在接受美国调查。【原文：Gautam and Sagar Adani knew their renewable energy company was under U.S. investigation for suspected bribery when they sold part of India's largest solar park to France's TotalEnergies, prosecutors allege in legal documents reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/adanis-knew-us-probe-when-they-sold-bribe-linked-assets-totalenergies-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHUII65CGNKKRAWR4YKJYEG4JU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 17:11:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，Robinhood 首席法务官加勒格排除了担任美国证券交易委员会主席的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood Markets 的首席法务官丹-加拉格尔（Dan Gallagher）是美国证券交易委员会的前委员，据说曾是唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）领导下的该委员会主席的热门人选。【原文：Robinhood Markets' Chief Legal Officer Dan Gallagher, a former commissioner of the Securities and Exchange Commission who was reportedly the frontrunner to become its chair under Donald Trump, told CNBC on Friday he was not interested in the role.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/robinhoods-chief-legal-officer-gallagher-rules-out-becoming-sec-chair-cnbc-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPLTPZBC4NNK3NFVXXFKT4P554</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 17:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行私人银行部门任命新客户顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行私人银行部门周五表示，业内资深人士菲利普-爱德华兹（Phillip Edwards）和劳伦-斯图默（Lauren Stuhmer）将加入其棕榈滩办事处，担任私人客户顾问。【原文：Bank of America's private banking arm said on Friday industry veterans Phillip Edwards and Lauren Stuhmer would join its Palm Beach office as private client advisers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bofas-private-banking-arm-names-new-client-advisers-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WG3MSE764VPTJJP3FUZMIPN7AE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 16:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，花旗集团获得在沙特阿拉伯设立地区总部的许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份内部备忘录，美国花旗集团已获准在沙特阿拉伯利雅得设立地区总部。【原文：U.S. bank Citigroup has received approval to establish its regional headquarters in Saudi Arabia's Riyadh, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-gets-license-regional-headquarters-saudi-arabia-memo-shows-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MHFF6O6AJPPRGPFECJLMVMJQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 16:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者信心指数回升，显示大选后党派倾向发生变化]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在总统大选中获胜后，共和党人的情绪大幅上扬，带动 11 月份美国消费者情绪连续第四个月上升。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment ticked up for a fourth straight month in November, led by a big upswing in sentiment among Republicans following Donald Trump's victory in the presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-ticks-up-shows-post-election-partisan-flip-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PMFVU76WZOKRMEFYF67I3HH3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 16:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储文件质疑贴现窗口污名化概念]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据纽约联储的最新研究，最不愿意动用美国中央银行贴现窗口来充实资本的银行，实际上是那些面临最高倒闭风险的银行。【原文：The banks most reluctant to tap the U.S. central bank's discount window to shore up their capital are in fact those who face the highest failure risk, according to new research from the New York Federal Reserve that turns the notion of bank emergency borrowing stigma on its head.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/new-york-fed-paper-challenges-notion-discount-window-stigma-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4HSJ54X45M4RCROHBVX3XME7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 15:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟大使表示，欧盟已准备好应对特朗普领导下美国再次出现的贸易紧张局势]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟驻美国大使约维塔-内柳普希安（Jovita Neliupšienė）周五表示，欧盟已准备好应对当选总统唐纳德-特朗普第二任政府执政期间可能出现的任何新的与美国的贸易紧张局势。【原文：The European Union is prepared to react to any renewed trade tensions with the United States that may emerge under President-elect Donald Trump's second administration, the EU's ambassador to the U.S., Jovita Neliupšienė, said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-ready-react-any-renewed-us-trade-tensions-under-trump-ambassador-says-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MH3OIGQQW5O2ZJ4EBD2Z2SJNRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 15:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sirius XM 在纽约取消订阅诉讼案中被判负有责任]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长莱蒂娅-詹姆斯（Letitia James）起诉天狼星 XM 控股公司，指控这家卫星广播和流媒体公司让客户很难取消订阅，纽约州法官认为天狼星 XM 控股公司应承担责任。【原文：A New York state judge found Sirius XM Holdings liable in New York Attorney General Letitia James' lawsuit accusing the satellite radio and streaming company of making it too hard for customers to cancel subscriptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/sirius-xm-found-liable-new-york-lawsuit-over-subscription-cancellations-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUZUSLOKEZKIJEPJ3T4XSHSW5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 15:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥零售商 Elektra 再次暂停交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥主要证券交易所周五在股票转手前恢复了零售商 Elektra 的暂停交易，Elektra 警告称任何交易都将损害其业务。【原文：Mexico's main stock exchange on Friday reinstated a trading suspension on retailer Elektra before shares changed hands, with Elektra warning that any trading would harm its business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trading-mexican-retailer-elektra-again-suspended-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PGAING56NK6BA35TN27QCY2WE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 15:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回涉及 Facebook 的证券欺诈诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五回避了是否允许股东继续提起证券欺诈诉讼的决定，该诉讼指控 Meta 旗下的 Facebook 在滥用社交媒体平台用户数据方面误导投资者。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court sidestepped on Friday a decision on whether to allow shareholders to proceed with a securities fraud lawsuit accusing Meta's Facebook of misleading investors about the misuse of the social media platform's user data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-tosses-case-involving-securities-fraud-suit-against-facebook-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PT7RIXBRUNLKHGXTVDCW2XHASI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 15:08:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月商业活动指数升至 31 个月高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[受明年当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府有望降低利率和采取更多有利于商业的政策的提振，衡量美国商业活动的一项指标在 11 月份创下了 31 个月以来的新高。【原文：A measure of U.S. business activity raced to a 31-month high in November, boosted by hopes for lower interest rates and more business-friendly policies from President-elect Donald Trump's administration next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-activity-gauge-rises-31-month-high-november-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIBHCOIEKNOJJFYA7R6SON3VDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 14:55:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大道明银行任命内部人士为全球首席审计师，以应对监管部门的强力监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大道明银行周五表示，已任命内部人士米歇尔-迈尔斯（Michelle Myers）为其全球首席审计师，12 月 9 日起生效。【原文：Canada's TD Bank said on Friday it had appointed insider Michelle Myers as its global chief auditor, effective Dec. 9.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadas-td-bank-names-insider-global-chief-auditor-amid-regulatory-glare-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKJKBSXOUJISXLHEEUGBALO5F4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 14:50:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谢因鲍姆总统称墨西哥不是中国产品的后门]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉美国家墨西哥总统周五表示，中国产品不能通过墨西哥进入美国和加拿大，墨西哥政府将在即将举行的贸易会议上明确这一点。【原文：Chinese products are not entering the United States and Canada through Mexico, the president of the Latin American nation said on Friday, and the government will make that clear in upcoming trade meetings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-not-backdoor-chinese-products-president-sheinbaum-says-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LL4KTUD4EFPTVLOVF66R3HA574</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 14:47:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称，UPS 因对业务部门估值不当将支付 4500 万美元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）周五表示，美国联合包裹服务公司（United Parcel Service）将因对一个业务部门估值不当而支付高达 4500 万美元的罚款。【原文：The United Parcel Service will pay up to a $45 million penalty for improperly valuing a business unit, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ups-pay-45-million-penalty-improperly-valuing-business-unit-sec-says-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JV6SNKNHJJM5VFXXNDFLREHPF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 14:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国因涉嫌强迫中国劳工而禁止进口更多食品和金属]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周五在网上发布公告称，由于中国涉嫌强迫维吾尔族人劳动，美国又禁止了30家公司的食品、金属和其他产品的进口。【原文：The United States banned food, metal and other imports from 30 more companies over China's alleged forced labor involving the Uyghurs, according to a government notice posted online on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-bars-more-imports-over-chinas-alleged-forced-labor-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTKPY6SPF5KJNIJABHSKQ7XSUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 13:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博世将裁员 5,550 人，德国汽车业再遭重创]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗伯特-博世（ROBG.UL）周五表示，公司计划裁员多达5550人，这是德国汽车行业陷入困境的最新迹象。【原文：Robert Bosch (ROBG.UL) said on Friday the company plans to cut up to 5,550 jobs, the latest sign of struggle in Germany's creaking auto sector, which is grappling with competition from cheaper Chinese rivals and weak demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bosch-axe-5550-jobs-latest-blow-german-auto-sector-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AR4F36NH5NSVGTFLKBPIZXIKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 13:33:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车劳工代表投票决定从 12 月初开始举行有限罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据地区 IG Metall 工会周五发表的一份声明，大众汽车的劳工代表已投票决定从 12 月初开始举行有限罢工。【原文：Volkswagen labour representatives have voted for limited strikes from early December, according to a statement from regional IG Metall trade union on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-labour-representatives-vote-limited-strikes-early-december-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIMHPN22SVN3FB2SRX656SBWIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 13:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔将以 13.3 亿美元出售个人防护设备业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔周五表示，将以约 13.3 亿美元的现金向 Protective Industrial Products 公司出售其个人防护设备业务。【原文：Honeywell said on Friday it would sell its personal protective equipment business to Protective Industrial Products for about $1.33 billion in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/honeywell-sell-personal-protective-equipment-business-133-billion-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5VTUI6FLYJNDXEWOATPNJ73KHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 12:41:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁是破产的 Northvolt 债权人？]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电动汽车电池制造商 Northvolt 在美国申请破产保护，负债 58 亿美元，现金只有 3000 万美元。【原文：Northvolt, the Swedish maker of battery cells for electric vehicles, filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the United States with debts of $5.8 billion and only $30 million in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/who-are-bankrupt-northvolts-creditors-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJZTICNEENOETLOJI2KU44BXWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 12:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国新制裁可能意味着欧盟通过俄罗斯天然气工业银行支付能源费用的终结]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯经济学家周五表示，美国对莫斯科的新制裁可能会关闭欧洲客户支付俄罗斯天然气的唯一途径，增加俄罗斯外汇市场的波动性，并将莫斯科推向中国政府的轨道。【原文：New U.S. sanctions on Moscow may shut down the only way European customers can pay for Russian gas, increase volatility on Russia's FX market and push Moscow closer to Beijing's orbit, Russian economists said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-us-sanctions-probably-spell-end-eu-energy-payments-through-russias-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKHBJ4EW3NKJFONX32A5R6CSWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 12:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国调查摩根大通与伊朗对冲基金的联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，美国财政部正在调查摩根大通与一家对冲基金的关系，据说该对冲基金是伊朗石油交易商侯赛因-沙姆哈尼（Hossein Shamkhani）网络的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department is looking into JPMorgan Chase's relationship with a hedge fund that is said to be a part of Iranian oil trader Hossein Shamkhani's network, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-probes-jpmorgans-links-with-iranian-hedge-fund-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPTZWS2LUBMM3E62MOSFKNLYR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构将考虑调查苹果和谷歌的移动浏览器]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国竞争监管机构的一份报告称，苹果可能阻碍了智能手机浏览器的创新，该机构建议利用其新权力调查苹果和谷歌在移动生态系统中的双头垄断。【原文：Apple could be holding back innovation in smartphone browsers, according to a report by Britain's competition regulator, which recommended that Apple's and Google's duopoly in mobile ecosystems should be investigated with its new powers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-regulator-will-consider-probing-apples-googles-mobile-browsers-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICVPOQ6KWBJ4VBBVXSF2JTJOA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:46:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在商业活动数据和地缘政治紧张局势面前，期货市场因谨慎而下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在商业活动调查和乌克兰与俄罗斯之间日益紧张的地缘政治局势前保持谨慎，美国股指期货周五下滑，但华尔街主要股指有望实现周线上涨。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Friday as investors remain cautious ahead of a business activity survey and increasing geopolitical tensions between Ukraine and Russia, but Wall Street's main indexes were poised for weekly gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-slip-caution-ahead-business-activity-data-geopolitical-tensions-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5G73YLVWNIWXFRKF3BN6DCOQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:33:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投诉撤销后，欧盟监管机构取消了对苹果电子书规则的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在投诉人撤回对 iPhone 制造商的投诉后，欧盟反垄断监管机构于周五结束了对苹果公司针对电子书和有声读物应用程序开发商的竞争规则长达四年之久的调查。【原文：EU antitrust regulators on Friday closed a four-year long investigation into Apple's rules for competing e-book and audiobook apps developers after the complainant withdrew its complaint against the iPhone maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-regulators-scrap-probe-into-apples-e-book-rules-after-complaint-was-withdrawn-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDSLHVMYSVLOPEGSFHQ4PS64AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gap 股价大涨，因乐观的销售预期预示着假日季的良好开端]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gap 股价周五盘前飙升 15%，原因是其四个品牌在近两年后都恢复了增长，这促使该服装零售商在假日购物季的强劲开端上调了年度销售预期。【原文：Gap shares soared 15% premarket on Friday, as a return to growth at all four of its brands after nearly two years encouraged the apparel retailer to lift its annual sales forecast in a robust start to the holiday shopping season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/gap-shares-surge-upbeat-sales-expectations-signal-promising-start-holiday-season-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDQTDFUB7JKFFLCCTFGWLZRMPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：欧元/美元逼近平价，比特币盯上 10 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5JO4DCZKBOXLPNT55CIPZ6XMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国 FDA 发现广泛使用的哮喘药物会影响大脑]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社审查的一份科学报告，美国政府研究人员发现，默克公司（Merck &amp; Co）最初销售的一种广泛处方的哮喘药可能与一些患者的严重精神健康问题有关。【原文：U.S. government researchers have found that a widely prescribed asthma drug originally sold by Merck &amp; Co may be linked to serious mental health problems for some patients, according to a scientific presentation reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-finds-widely-used-asthma-drug-impacts-brain-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JKITC5AVJOPJMQKKOZO6ZDW4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金连续第三周获得资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月20日，美国投资者连续第三周抢购股票基金，这主要是受企业盈利预期上升的乐观情绪提振，不过由于美联储对利率前景持谨慎态度以及俄罗斯与西方之间的地缘政治紧张局势，投资者的资金流入受到了抑制。【原文：U.S. investors snapped up equity funds for a third successive week through Nov. 20, buoyed by optimism over rising corporate earnings expectations, although the inflows were restrained due to a cautious Federal Reserve rate outlook and geopolitical tensions between Russia and the West.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-gain-inflows-third-week-row-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YRPUG7KMVLU3P2LEG64K6KJSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车因驱动力损失召回超过 14.5 万辆美国电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，由于驱动力损失，韩国现代汽车公司将在美国召回约145235辆电动汽车。【原文：South Korean carmaker Hyundai Motor is recalling about 145,235 electrified vehicles in the United States due to a loss of drive power, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-recalls-over-145000-electrified-us-vehicles-loss-drive-power-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFMOWT6XSBP5BGVIQNAGWCK5DQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治紧张局势导致全球股票基金每周资金流入放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至11月20日的一周里，由于俄罗斯与西方之间的地缘政治紧张局势，全球股票基金的资金流入放缓，投资者还对美国明年的利率政策前景感到焦虑。【原文：Inflows into global equity funds slowed in the week ending Nov. 20 due to geopolitical tensions between Russia and the West, with investors also anxious about the U.S. interest rate policy outlook for next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPVLTKSMH5JR5HTSVCZHPRNXHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>