<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:38:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:38:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美洲 "壮丽 "熊]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORQ7ALWLDJNHJOIBBKZAPR3UDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国贸易机构称，美国加征关税可能导致日本汽车出口损失 170 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际贸易中心周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普决定对汽车行业征收25%的关税后，日本可能失去170亿美元的汽车出口潜力。【原文：Japan could lose $17 billion in car export potential in the U.S. following President Donald Trump's decision to introduce 25% tariffs on the automotive sector, the International Trade Centre said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japan-could-lose-17-billion-car-exports-due-us-tariffs-says-un-trade-agency-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U7JY3PAT5PH5ATNCFRX742P2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:29:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对美国加征关税进行报复后，华尔街期货失守]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周五大幅下跌，预示着华尔街将遭受更多损失，因为在特朗普政府全面征收关税导致美国股市缩水2.4万亿美元的一天之后，中国采取了新的关税报复措施。【原文：U.S. stock futures fell sharply on Friday, signaling more losses on Wall Street, after China retaliated with fresh tariffs a day after the Trump administration's sweeping levies knocked off $2.4 trillion from U.S. equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-futures-lose-ground-after-china-retaliates-against-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76DS4WZQTRICTHQCBS56HHRUVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼集团高管称，石油巨头受困于欧佩克+增产，而非美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃尼公司（Eni）的高层管理人员弗朗切斯科-加泰伊（Francesco Gattei）周五表示，在欧佩克+国家（OPEC+）的八个成员国意外同意在五月增加石油产量之后，石油巨头们的日子不好过，而美国政府征收的关税对石油行业的影响不大。【原文：Oil majors are suffering after eight OPEC+ countries unexpectedly agreed to increase oil output in May, while tariffs imposed by U.S. administration had a muted effect on the sector, Eni's top executive Francesco Gattei said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-majors-suffering-opec-output-hike-not-us-tariffs-eni-exec-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWJ6ETAK3ZLSPPUC7KHX354K4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:21:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在全球贸易战中实施报复，对美国商品全面征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五宣布对美国商品征收 34% 的额外关税，这是与唐纳德-特朗普总统贸易战的最严重升级，加剧了人们对经济衰退的担忧，并引发了全球股市暴跌。【原文：China announced additional tariffs of 34% on U.S. goods on Friday, the most serious escalation in a trade war with President Donald Trump that has fed fears of a recession and triggered a global stock market rout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/europe-prepares-response-trump-tariffs-global-markets-plunge-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOKNK2JOLFOSXM2FBM4RBVGJGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将从 4 月 10 日起对所有美国商品加征 34% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国财政部周五表示，将从4月10日起对所有美国商品征收34%的额外关税，作为对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收全面关税的反制措施。【原文：China's finance ministry said on Friday it will impose additional tariffs of 34% on all U.S. goods from April 10 as a countermeasure to sweeping tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-impose-tariffs-34-all-us-goods-april-10-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PZJJBMRMRJFFEJYG4CBPUHNOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:14:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁期限临近，西班牙对委内瑞拉石油的进口量增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府设定的关键制裁期限的临近，西班牙 1 月和 2 月从委内瑞拉进口的原油量同比增长了约 59%。【原文：Spain's crude oil imports from Venezuela in January and February rose roughly 59% from a year earlier as a key sanctions deadline set by U.S. President Donald Trump's administration approaches.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/spains-imports-venezuelan-oil-rise-us-sanctions-deadline-approaches-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3L3B7YQGFKWHBVROOFBQZZ6W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税、经济不确定性助推首席执行官与激进分子达成更多和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要对中国征收关税，Yeti Holdings 的股价在 12 月和 3 月再次暴跌。【原文：Shares of Yeti Holdings tumbled in December and again in March when President Donald Trump threatened tariffs against China, where the company had some of its biggest factories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-economic-uncertainty-fuel-more-settlements-between-ceos-activists-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAGL4EE27JMFLKJT2HTXKIRVHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件称越南越捷航空公司将与波音公司签署飞机融资协议并加强合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部日程表，越南廉价航空公司 VietJet 将于下周在华盛顿与投资基金 KKR 的合作伙伴签署一份 2 亿美元的飞机融资协议，飞机制造商波音公司也将出席会议。【原文：Vietnamese budget airline VietJet is set to sign a $200 million aircraft finance deal with a partner of investment fund KKR at a meeting in Washington next week attended by planemaker Boeing, according to an internal schedule seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietnams-vietjet-sign-aircraft-finance-deal-boost-cooperation-with-boeing-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2D63VMBRZJI7HA2Y6KE3PG2GFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街在寻找市场触底的蛛丝马迹]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者正在寻找美国股市的抛售可能已经达到顶峰的迹象，但他们表示，勾选标记尚未全部勾选，还有进一步痛苦的空间。【原文：Investors are looking for signs the selling in the U.S. stock market may have reached a crescendo, but say that the check marks are not yet all ticked and there is room for further pain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-searches-elusive-signs-that-market-bottom-reached-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3OMSIMPMJJ55GXULPM7CUQBRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔将在关税纷争和市场下跌之际发表讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国在全球范围内全面征收新关税，市场因此受到冲击，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周五将加入央行内部日益激烈的争论，即特朗普政府的新政策更有可能引发更高的通胀，还是会严重削弱经济增长和就业，以至于美联储不得不做出回应。【原文：With sweeping new U.S. tariffs now in play globally and markets shaken as a result, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday will add his voice to a growing debate at the central bank over whether the Trump administration's new policies are more likely to stoke higher inflation or undercut growth and employment so much the Fed will have to respond.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-weigh-amid-tariff-fray-market-drop-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4E3FUTAMZPLZA3NN3E5YGGBVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克里姆林宫称俄罗斯必须防范特朗普征收关税后的世界市场动荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[克里姆林宫周五表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普本周征收关税，俄罗斯必须采取额外措施，尽量减少全球市场动荡对其经济造成的负面影响。【原文：Russia must take extra measures to minimise the negative impact on its economy from global market turbulence due to tariffs imposed this week by U.S. President Donald Trump, the Kremlin said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/kremlin-says-russia-must-guard-against-world-market-turbulence-after-trump-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLBWPUGIHFIYVBN7O77G6IKYUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:59:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱索托就 "令人震惊 "的关税问题寻求与美国接触]]></title><description><![CDATA[莱索托贸易部长表示，莱索托周五慌忙组建了一个代表团，准备前往华盛顿与美国就关税问题进行交涉，因为美国可能会取消莱索托近一半的出口产品，这对莱索托的经济可能是致命的打击。【原文：Lesotho scrambled to put together a delegation on Friday to head to Washington to engage with the United States on tariffs that risk wiping out nearly half of its exports, its trade minister said, in what could be a death blow to its economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/baffled-lesotho-seeks-engage-with-us-shocking-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUEJNODI2NI57KVVSP7W6IV6HY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理称正在制定中国公司将达尔文港出售给 "澳大利亚人 "的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞周五表示，澳大利亚政府正在制定一项计划，让澳大利亚养老金公司以国家利益为由从中国所有者手中购买达尔文港这一具有战略意义的港口。【原文：Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said on Friday his government was working on a plan for Australian superannuation firms to buy the strategically located Darwin port from its Chinese owner on national interest grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/australia-pm-says-working-plan-chinese-company-sell-darwin-port-australian-hands-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOTTFNXNUZKE5OS5BJY5VZ7IVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:35:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济衰退担忧加剧，日本银行股全球溃败加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对全球经济衰退的担忧席卷市场，周五日本银行股暴跌，创下至少40年来最严重的单周跌幅，而美国和欧洲的银行股继续下跌，全球银行股的大跌变得不祥。【原文：A global selloff in bank shares turned ominous with a collapse in Japanese bank stocks on Friday to their worst weekly loss in at least 40 years while U.S. and European lenders continued to decline, as fear of a global recession swept markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-rout-bank-shares-intensifies-recession-fears-mount-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDRO4PKA75JZ5LHIGS6J7G4CHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南非称特朗普的关税取消了《非洲增长和机会法》贸易倡议]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非政府周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普本周宣布的关税实际上取消了非洲国家根据美国贸易倡议《非洲增长与机会法案》（AGOA）所享有的利益。【原文：South Africa's government said on Friday that tariffs announced by President Donald Trump this week effectively nullified the benefits African countries enjoy under U.S. trade initiative the African Growth and Opportunity Act (AGOA).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/south-africa-says-trumps-tariffs-effectively-nullify-agoa-benefits-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDS73OEWHJIM5NRROJGINQKNAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:23:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾推出 87 亿美元帮助企业应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾政府周五宣布向企业和行业提供至少 2,880 亿新台币（87.4 亿美元）的财政援助，以应对美国关税的影响，其中包括出口信贷。【原文：Taiwan's government on Friday announced at least T$288 billion ($8.74 billion) in financial help for companies and industries to deal with the impact of U.S. tariffs, including export credits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/taiwan-unveils-87-billion-help-companies-deal-with-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CEF372CYFPJJPWOCO4IYEW7GI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:21:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 IndusInd 银行如何因追求利润和控制不严而陷入危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[多个消息来源称，印度印度银行多年来在追求利润增长的过程中忽视了既定的印度衍生品会计惯例，导致资产负债表出现 1.75 亿美元的窟窿，并引发了该银行三十年历史上最大的危机。【原文：IndusInd Bank ignored established Indian derivative accounting practices for years as it chased profit growth, resulting in a $175 million balance-sheet hole and the biggest crisis for the lender in its three-decade history, multiple sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/how-indian-bank-indusinds-push-profits-lax-controls-drove-it-crisis-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JY5V6UD6NLYHEDD2IFOHXCTVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院裁定，Meta 可在肯尼亚因埃塞俄比亚暴力事件相关帖子被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯尼亚一家法院裁定，可以在这个东非国家起诉 Facebook 的母公司 Meta，因为该公司被指控在推广导致邻国埃塞俄比亚发生种族暴力的内容方面扮演了重要角色。【原文：A Kenyan court has ruled that Facebook's parent company Meta can be sued in the East African country over its alleged role in promoting content that led to ethnic violence in neighbouring Ethiopia, a plaintiff in the case said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-can-be-sued-kenya-over-posts-related-ethiopia-violence-court-rules-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFBU7A64KVIUPJUIFVZIH6QOSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:41:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国粮农组织称三月份世界粮食价格稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国粮食及农业组织周五称，3月份全球粮食商品价格上涨，植物油价格的大幅上涨抵消了谷物和糖价格的下跌。【原文：Global food commodity prices edged up in March, with a sharp rise in vegetable oils offsetting declines in cereals and sugar, the United Nations' Food and Agriculture Organization said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/world-food-prices-steady-march-uns-fao-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QMTB4RUT5N5HH5JWFTYFNMARU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲律宾毒品战争受害者家属进行反击，敦促调查网络攻击事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲律宾毒品战争受害者家属称，他们成为了一场 "协调一致 "的网络骚扰活动的目标，他们周五敦促执法人员调查这些攻击事件，并找出责任人，帮助他们采取法律行动。【原文：Families of Philippine drug war victims who say they have been targeted by a "coordinated" campaign of online harassment urged law enforcers on Friday to investigate the attacks and identify those responsible to help them pursue legal action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/families-philippine-drug-war-victims-fight-back-urge-probe-into-online-attacks-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6LNK4HV5BKTDNEEGSYFBHLJSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税将加剧萎靡不振的石化行业的困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内官员和分析师表示，美国大规模征收新的进口关税可能会进一步削弱全球石化产品生产商的需求，并加速该行业因利润疲软而削减产能。【原文：Sweeping new U.S. import tariffs threaten to further erode demand for global petrochemical producers and accelerate capacity cuts in an industry plagued by weak margins, industry officials and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-tariffs-poised-exacerbate-woes-ailing-petchems-sector-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGWUA4YHHROFZGZXYWXYA43HEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲银行在关税大跌中扩大跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收关税引发的股市大幅下挫中，欧洲贷款机构的股票跌幅扩大。【原文：Shares in European lenders extended losses on Friday amid a deep selloff in equities sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-banks-extend-losses-amid-tariff-selloff-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SX3EVJZOVBI27N733LM5ZNGVLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:24:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税，欧洲股市在残酷的一周结束时下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对贸易伙伴全面征收关税后，投资者对全球经济衰退的前景忧心忡忡。【原文：European shares dipped on Friday, heading for a steep weekly loss, as investors grappled with prospects of a global recession after U.S. President Donald Trump announced sweeping tariffs on trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-shares-drop-end-brutal-week-after-trumps-tariff-blow-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCMCL6NNRVIJVBBJC4GLGPFHPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:22:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院裁定，维基媒体必须删除被视为诽谤的印度内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[维基百科运营商被印度法院勒令从其托管的一家国内通讯社的页面上删除被认为具有诽谤性的言论，这是对这一流行的在线百科全书发出的最新指令。【原文：The operator of Wikipedia has been ordered to remove statements deemed defamatory by an Indian court from the page of a domestic news agency it hosts, the latest such directive to the popular online encyclopedia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/wikimedia-must-remove-india-content-deemed-defamatory-court-rules-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIDOIRZDM5L6PBIXAZ3MCBL3J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[快递业的繁荣吸引俄罗斯人从事快递工作以寻找外快]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃琳娜和维克多的公寓里堆满了五颜六色的大背包和两辆被他们称为 "铁骑 "的自行车。他们辞去了固定的工作，寻求更高的薪水和更灵活的工作时间，做起了全职快递员。【原文：Elena and Viktor's apartment is packed with large, colourful rucksacks and the two bicycles they call their "iron horses". They have quit their regular jobs, seeking better pay and more flexible hours to work full time as delivery couriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/delivery-boom-draws-russians-courier-jobs-search-extra-cash-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7A7T3NENWNPRDDEQC5OWLXY7NU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本银行业萎靡不振，投资者对全球大跌作出反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收关税的影响，日本银行周五大幅下挫，全球股市延续了惩罚性抛售，这有助于推动美国国债反弹，并支撑黄金接近历史最高点。【原文：Japanese banks tanked on Friday and stocks globally extended a punishing selloff in the wake of U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs, helping drive a rally in U.S. Treasuries and supporting gold near a record peak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-selloff-quotes-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6456VHGZQFJGTM6A2M2LOHNNBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:50:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚行首席经济学家：美国关税可能导致全球经济增长大幅放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲开发银行首席经济学家表示，美国全面的新关税制度有可能导致美国和全球经济增长放缓，出口市场萎缩，并有可能促使美联储做出反应。【原文：The United States' sweeping new tariff regime risks slowing both U.S. and global growth, shrinking export markets and potentially prompting a Federal Reserve response, the Asian Development Bank's chief economist said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-tariffs-risk-slowing-global-growth-significantly-adb-chief-economist-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XTY5VQC6FIYHFPZE6LPHMATQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:48:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据每日 MF 报道，高盛集团将牵头为普拉达与范思哲的交易融资 25 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据意大利《MF》日报周五报道，以高盛为首的多家银行准备向普拉达提供 25 亿欧元（约合 27.7 亿美元）的融资额度，以帮助这家意大利时装集团收购卡普里控股公司旗下的范思哲。【原文：A pool of banks led by Goldman Sachs is ready to give Prada a 2.5-billion-euro ($2.77 billion) financing line to help the Italian fashion group in its acquisition of Capri Holdings-owned Versace, Italian daily MF reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/goldman-sachs-lead-25-billion-euro-financing-prada-versace-deal-daily-mf-reports-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHUMQ2CNUBOPJCM5UVKQDC6XL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:40:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税引发担忧，摩根大通将全球经济衰退几率上调至 60]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街券商摩根大通（J.P. Morgan）表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）大刀阔斧地征收互惠关税，今年美国和全球经济衰退的风险已从之前的40%上升至60%。【原文：The risk of a U.S. and global recession this year have risen to 60% from 40% earlier on the heels of President Donald Trump's sweeping reciprocal tariffs, Wall Street brokerage J.P. Morgan said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/jpmorgan-lifts-global-recession-odds-60-us-tariffs-stoke-fears-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFCWBD2JGFLWFAOX5ACLRGICO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:37:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>