<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:08:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:08:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空不会使用人工智能制定个性化机票价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周五表示，在面临美国立法者的尖锐批评后，该公司将不会使用人工智能为乘客设定个性化机票价格。【原文：Delta Air Lines said Friday it will not use artificial intelligence to set personalized ticket prices for passengers after facing sharp criticism from U.S. lawmakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/delta-will-not-use-ai-set-personalized-ticket-prices-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XX4QAHWXBIVRBGFVLDYBWG3IA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官基本驳回贝莱德公司要求驳回各州就气候推动措施提起诉讼的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一名美国法官基本驳回了贝莱德提出的驳回德克萨斯州和其他 12 个共和党领导的州提起的诉讼的请求，该诉讼称贝莱德和其他大型资产管理公司通过减少煤炭生产和提高能源价格的气候行动主义违反了反垄断法。【原文：A U.S. judge on Friday largely rejected a request by BlackRock to dismiss a lawsuit filed by Texas and 12 other Republican-led states that said the company and other large asset managers violated antitrust law through climate activism that reduced coal production and boosted energy prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-judge-mostly-rejects-blackrock-bid-dismiss-states-lawsuit-over-climate-push-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHGRIJRBANOWLPODAO7JOXEIOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:54:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 在关税问题挥之不去之际，人工智能涨势和强劲财报支撑华尔街]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着第二季度财报公布过半，股市接近历史高点，公司业绩让投资者对人工智能交易感到放心，尽管关税担忧抑制了买盘，但人工智能交易还是给华尔街注入了活力。【原文：With more than half of second quarter earnings reported and stocks near record highs, company results have reassured investors about the artificial intelligence trade that has energized Wall Street, even if tariff worries curtailed buying.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-ai-gains-strong-earnings-support-wall-street-tariff-woes-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I63722CLBNJTDCHUDJRGDFZSLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利 7 月新车销量下降 5.11]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利交通部周五公布的数据显示，7月份意大利新车销量同比下降5.11%，表明欧盟第三大经济体的市场持续疲软。【原文：Sales of new cars in Italy fell by 5.11% year-on-year in July, transport ministry data showed on Friday, indicating a persistently weak market in the European Union's third largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/italys-new-car-sales-down-511-july-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2NEXFEEHJITNIQJXIE5FTK6BM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:41:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，欧盟反垄断监管机构将批准 Prosus 和 Just Eat 外卖公司的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的消息人士称，欧盟反垄断监管机构将有条件批准荷兰技术投资商 Prosus 以 41 亿欧元（47.4 亿美元）收购 Just Eat Takeaway。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are set to clear with conditions Dutch technology investor Prosus' 4.1-billion-euro ($4.74 billion) acquisition of Just Eat Takeaway , sources with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-antitrust-regulators-set-clear-prosus-just-eat-takeaway-deal-sources-say-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOBOHCPK2VNJVDMYW4KKU3JMXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:28:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美联储带头努力放宽 "巴塞尔协议三终局 "资本要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美联储已开始制定新的风险资本规则，旨在减轻美国最大银行的负担，而不是拜登时代的计划。【原文：The Federal Reserve has begun developing a new risk-based capital rule aimed at easing the burden on the largest U.S. banks than a Biden-era plan, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/fed-spearheads-effort-ease-basel-iii-endgame-capital-requirements-bloomberg-news-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWMB3UO5EBK5PJXXPNPN43FVT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[压力测试表明，欧盟银行可抵御全球贸易战引发的经济衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲银行管理局周五在提交其最新的银行业健康检查结果时表示，欧盟各国的银行实力雄厚，足以抵御地缘政治和贸易紧张局势带来的经济冲击。【原文：Banks across the European Union are strong enough to weather an economic shock driven by geopolitical and trade tensions, the European Banking Authority said on Friday as it presented the outcome of its latest health check of the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-banks-can-weather-recession-driven-by-global-trade-war-stress-test-shows-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EA3XWIV7LNLXHFTURN637E2WF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对巴西咖啡征收 50%的关税预计将重新调整贸易，使更多咖啡豆销往中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府对巴西咖啡征收高额进口关税，看来将重新调整世界头号种植国和出口国咖啡豆的贸易路线，使中国受益，并促使贸易商寻找进入美国的间接路线。【原文：The Trump administration's steep import tariff on Brazilian coffee looks set to reshuffle trade routes for beans from the world's top grower and exporter, benefiting China and incentivizing traders to look for indirect routes into the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trumps-50-brazil-coffee-tariff-expected-rejig-trade-send-more-beans-china-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DULDIH7DFIYNP2SEC5Z7GC72Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发巴西化工企业 "深切担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚（ExxonMobil）和陶氏化学（Dow Chemical）等美国大型企业在巴西开展业务，代表巴西化工企业的一个协会对美国将巴西出口产品的关税提高到 50%的行政命令表示 "深切关注"。【原文：An association representing chemical companies in Brazil, where large U.S. firms like ExxonMobil and Dow Chemical operate, expressed "deep concern" regarding a U.S. executive order raising tariffs on Brazilian exports to 50%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-tariffs-spark-deep-concern-among-brazil-chemical-firms-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUUYTH23B5KDRK4SECFW2KDI5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：消息人士称，美国政府动荡导致数千项出口审批受阻]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，美国公司向包括中国在内的全球各地出口商品和技术的数千份许可证申请陷入了僵局，因为负责审批这些申请的机构发生了动荡，几乎陷入瘫痪。【原文：Thousands of license applications by U.S. companies to export goods and technology around the globe, including to China, are in limbo because turmoil at the agency in charge of approving them has left it nearly paralyzed, two sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-government-turmoil-stalls-thousands-export-approvals-sources-say-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XJFQPBCW5NK5LKYWQCQXNMG5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴拿马港口公司表示将与巴拿马政府讨论港口出售事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马港口公司（PPC）周五表示，将在适当的时候与巴拿马政府就其在巴拿马运河附近运营的两个重要港口的出售过程进行沟通。【原文：Panama Ports Company (PPC) said on Friday that it will communicate with the Panama government at an appropriate time in the sale process of two key ports that it operates near the Panama Canal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/panama-ports-says-it-will-discuss-ports-sale-with-panama-government-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVCEYD7YIFNF5N75N5JM47DNUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:18:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月建筑支出延续跌势]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于抵押贷款利率上升和库存增加，单户住宅项目支出大幅减少，6 月份美国建筑支出进一步下降。【原文：U.S. construction spending dropped further in June amid a sharp decline in outlays on single-family housing projects because of higher mortgage rates and rising inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-construction-spending-extends-decline-june-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGQ2UEAMZVK37ON52UOQR6T3QE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:25:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制造业延续低迷；工厂就业人数为五年来最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于关税提高了进口原材料的价格，7 月份美国制造业连续第五个月萎缩，工厂就业人数降至五年来的最低水平。【原文：U.S. manufacturing contracted for a fifth straight month in July and factory employment dropped to the lowest level in five years amid tariffs that have raised prices of imported raw materials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-manufacturing-extends-slump-factory-employment-lowest-5-years-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCRGDIBK3RJA7NLNMU4CCFZQUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自由全球称维珍媒体 O2 仍将在整合中发挥作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[自由全球（Liberty Global）表示，英国维珍媒体 O2（其与西班牙电信的合资企业）仍将在光纤整合中发挥作用，此前西班牙电信表示已取消分拆该网络的计划。【原文：Liberty Global said Britain's Virgin Media O2 - its joint venture with Telefonica - would still play a role in fibre consolidation after the Spanish company said a plan to spin off the network had been scrapped.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/liberty-global-says-virgin-media-o2-will-still-play-role-consolidation-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34QKXI6OCBJZTMCVEYF6VIF64A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国梅尔茨：将与美国谈判钢铁出口配额问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希-默茨（Friedrich Merz）周五表示，在双方上月达成贸易协议后，欧盟将与美国就钢铁问题进行谈判，重点是在不征收过高关税的情况下出口的配额。【原文：German Chancellor Friedrich Merz on Friday said the European Union will negotiate with the United States on steel, focusing on quotas that can be exported without too high tariffs, after the two sides struck a trade deal last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/germanys-merz-will-negotiate-steel-export-quotas-with-us-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVALXWH3CRLM3LOJTXISLXKTEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟等待特朗普就汽车等行业关税下达更多命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟官员周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最近的行政命令只规定了对欧盟征收15%的所谓 "对等 "关税，并不适用于汽车和其他商定的例外情况。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's recent executive order only sets out his so-called "reciprocal" tariff for the EU at 15% and does not apply to cars and other agreed carve-outs, EU officials said on Friday, adding they expect further more detailed orders to follow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-waits-more-trump-orders-sector-tariffs-like-cars-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMQFAJZD5NNRLEOO4FK7ZTVFX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:37:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特 7 月美国销量增长超过 9%，得益于对 SUV 和皮卡的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特公司周五公布，受皮卡和 SUV 持续需求的推动，7 月份美国汽车销量同比增长 9.3%。【原文：Ford on Friday reported a 9.3% rise in U.S. auto sales for July compared to the previous year, helped by sustained demand for pickup trucks and SUVs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fords-us-july-sales-rise-over-9-suv-pickup-demand-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IF773RCQGJLKZEPKWYNWEUPV2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[X 称英国网络安全法危及言论自由]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体网站 X 周五表示，英国的网络安全法由于执行力度过大，有压制言论自由的风险，并补充说需要进行重大改革。【原文：Britain's online safety law risks suppressing free speech due to its heavy-handed enforcement, social media site X said on Friday, adding that significant changes were needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uks-online-safety-law-is-putting-free-speech-risk-x-says-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEEY5XKWLZODLKGWIO6TBZ2AWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:26:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 大涨，人工智能驱动的广告战略赢得华尔街赞誉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit 公布的季度财报超出了市场预期，提振了投资者对该平台基于人工智能的广告工具和强大的用户参与度的信心，该公司股价在周五收盘前大涨 15%。【原文：Reddit's shares jumped 15% before the bell on Friday after it reported quarterly results that exceeded Street expectations, boosting investor confidence in the platform's AI-based advertising tools and strong user engagement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/reddit-surges-ai-driven-ad-strategy-wins-praise-wall-street-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HH2B4JSNRNMVXAAYFCHPJWRPWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:12:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月就业增长大幅放缓，失业率攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份的就业增长速度大大低于预期，而且上个月的数据被大幅下调，这表明劳动力市场可能出现停滞迹象。【原文：U.S. job growth slower much more than expected in July, and the data from the prior month was revised sharply lower, indicating the labor market could be showing signs of stalling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-job-growth-sharply-slows-july-unemployment-rate-ticks-higher-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MK3KTFPHI5PALO3QSLXK4HV7CA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月就业增长大幅放缓，失业率升至 4.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份的就业增长放缓幅度超过预期，而上个月的数据被大幅下调，这表明劳动力市场急剧放缓。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed more than expected in July while the prior month's data was revised sharply lower, pointing to a sharp moderation in the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-job-growth-slows-sharply-july-unemployment-rate-rises-42-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAAHOQ2ZHVOFTNJN4XICCQ32B4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:39:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于弗吉尼亚州和南卡罗来纳州的电力需求，多米尼克公司的季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受弗吉尼亚州和南卡罗来纳州电力需求上升的影响，多米尼克能源公司周五公布的第二季度营收和利润均超出预期。【原文：Dominion Energy on Friday beat second-quarter revenue and profit estimates, helped by rising power demand in Virginia and South Carolina.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/dominion-tops-quarterly-estimates-power-demand-virginia-south-carolina-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGU44LQIERMULGILGEILCL24SA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟品牌求助于隐晦的关税条款来缓解特朗普关税的打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅和越来越多的欧洲时装和化妆品公司正在探索利用一项已有数十年历史的不起眼的美国海关条款--"首次销售 "规则--来减轻美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税影响。【原文：L'Oreal and a growing number of European fashion and cosmetics companies are exploring use of an obscure, decades-old U.S. customs clause known as the "First Sale" rule as a potential way to soften the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-brands-turn-obscure-customs-clause-soften-blow-trumps-tariffs-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMMYVHBHMROU3P7NZGRMLQ2J6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:35:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[L3Harris 与 Joby Aviation 合作开发军用飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[防务公司 L3Harris Technologies 周五表示，该公司正与空中出租车制造商 Joby Aviation 合作开发一种用于防务的垂直起降飞机。【原文：Defense firm L3Harris Technologies is working with air taxi maker Joby Aviation to develop a vertical take-off and landing aircraft for defense applications, the companies said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/l3harris-joby-aviation-partner-develop-military-aircraft-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBW4OZHOXZLRDNHIGQUZTHVR4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于生活必需品需求稳定，高露洁-棕榄公司季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[高露洁-棕榄公司周五公布的第一季度销售额和利润超出预期，原因是对口腔和个人护理产品等必需品的强劲需求克服了价格上涨和关税的不确定性。【原文：Colgate-Palmolive beat first-quarter sales and profit estimates on Friday, as resilient demand for its essentials such as oral and personal care products overcame rising prices and tariff uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/colgate-palmolive-beats-quarterly-estimates-steady-demand-essentials-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4L4N43ZHZO37OG3QERQ2P5AFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:22:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dupixent销售额增长，Regeneron第二季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Regeneron Pharmaceuticals 周五公布的第二季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于湿疹治疗大片 Dupixent 的强劲需求，该公司股价在盘前交易中上涨近 3%。【原文：Regeneron Pharmaceuticals beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue and profit on Friday helped by robust demand for its blockbuster eczema treatment, Dupixent, sending its shares up nearly 3% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/regeneron-beats-second-quarter-results-estimates-dupixent-sales-boost-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMOZL5XKJZJ4BARSIWCHTBVOSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金因贸易协议乐观情绪而每周流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 7 月 30 日的一周里，美国股票基金三周来首次吸引资金流入，这主要是受到对美欧贸易协议的乐观情绪以及迄今为止乐观的企业财报季的推动。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted money inflows for the first time in three weeks in the week through July 30, fueled by optimism over a U.S.–EU trade deal and an upbeat corporate earnings season so far.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-weekly-inflows-trade-deal-optimism-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUZILM3M25MY7KNG6427D44UMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:21:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[持不同意见的美联储官员将投票与对劳动力市场的担忧联系在一起]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周的美国央行政策会议上，赞成降息的两位美联储理事周五表示，他们之所以这样做，主要是由于对就业市场的担忧日益加剧，同时预期与贸易关税有关的任何价格上涨都不会导致持久的价格压力。【原文：The two Federal Reserve governors who favored an interest rate cut at the U.S. central bank's policy meeting this week said on Friday they did so largely due to rising concerns about the job market, amid expectations that any price increases related to trade tariffs will not lead to lasting price pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/dissenting-fed-officials-tie-votes-labor-market-concerns-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLPMSSSE4JNRHA2E53ZZ7HJTN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CNH 工业公司业绩喜人，成本削减缓解了设备需求的下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[农用和建筑设备生产商 CNH Industrial 周五公布的第二季度利润和收入均高于华尔街预期，原因是该公司不断降低成本的努力帮助抵消了销售和生产下降带来的压力。【原文：Farm and construction equipment maker CNH Industrial reported second-quarter profit and revenue above Wall Street estimates on Friday, as its ongoing effort to reduce costs helped offset pressures from lower sales and production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cnh-industrial-posts-upbeat-results-cost-cuts-cushion-slump-equipment-demand-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GU6YPYARMRJXNIPG5C3XQHMCDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪 7 月产量同比下降 0.9%，扩张速度放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[比亚迪 7 月份的汽车产量同比下降了 0.9%，结束了连续 16 个月的增长势头，而这也使这家中国汽车制造商一跃成为全球最大的电动汽车制造商。【原文：BYD's vehicle production fell 0.9% in July from a year earlier, ending a 16-month growth streak that has catapulted the Chinese automaker into the world's largest electric vehicle maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byds-july-production-falls-09-yy-expansion-spree-slows-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EM6IHGESCNLHTPQ2VBVYAZYDCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:42:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>