<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:04:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:04:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 开始向部分 ChatGPT Plus 用户推出高级语音模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软支持的人工智能初创公司 OpenAI 周二在 X 上发表文章称，OpenAI 正开始向一小部分 ChatGPT Plus 用户推出高级语音模式。【原文：OpenAI is starting to roll out an advanced voice mode to a small group of ChatGPT Plus users, the Microsoft-backed artificial intelligence startup said on Tuesday in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-starts-roll-out-advanced-voice-mode-some-chatgpt-plus-users-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6K3ES2FA7JM3VH62YNAR6UN5LY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:45:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行因员工处方药费用被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo &amp; Co）在周二提起的诉讼中被指控对其员工医疗保险计划管理不善，迫使数万名美国员工多付了处方药费用。【原文：Wells Fargo &amp; Co was accused in a lawsuit filed on Tuesday of mismanaging its employee health insurance plan and forcing tens of thousands of U.S. employees to overpay for prescription drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/wells-fargo-sued-over-employee-prescription-drug-costs-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOZBRKAJPZPJDEPUYTX65KJFFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:38:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Copa 航空公司称委内瑞拉将暂停往返巴拿马的航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马 Copa 航空公司周二表示，委内瑞拉已决定从周三晚间起暂时中止巴拿马与委内瑞拉之间的所有商业航班。【原文：Copa Airlines said on Tuesday that Venezuela has decided to temporarily suspend all commercial flights between Panama and Venezuela beginning on Wednesday evening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/copa-airlines-says-venezuela-suspend-flights-panama-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WCQR7AFMZI2ZMPNZ3OQSXDCX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:32:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行监管机构希望加强对资产管理公司持有银行股份的控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行监管机构正在考虑制定一个更严格的框架，规定黑石（Blackrock）和先锋（Vanguard）等大型资产管理公司如何证明它们没有影响其持有大量股份的银行。【原文：A U.S. bank regulator is considering a stricter framework for how large asset managers like Blackrock and Vanguard can prove they are not influencing banks where they hold large stakes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-regulator-looks-tighten-control-asset-managers-bank-stakes-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TE5FRZPP5ZIFJFCGG6GVPPYHNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ameriprise 因涉嫌盗用客户数据起诉 LPL Financial]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ameriprise Financial 公司周二表示，它已向美国一家地方法院提起对 LPL Financial 公司的诉讼，指控该公司收集和滥用客户机密信息，违反了法律、监管和行业义务。【原文：Ameriprise Financial said on Tuesday it has filed a lawsuit in a U.S. district court against LPL Financial , alleging it harvests and misuses confidential client information in violation of legal, regulatory and industry obligations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ameriprise-sues-lpl-financial-over-alleged-misappropriation-client-data-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJLYK5XX6NKKPMTEDPL4OBN5HE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Axios 报道，小埃德加-布朗夫曼（Edgar Bronfman Jr.]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Axios 周二援引消息人士的话报道，前华纳音乐董事长小埃德加-布朗夫曼（Edgar Bronfman Jr.【原文：Former Warner Music chairman Edgar Bronfman Jr. is still in talks with bankers about a potential bid for Paramount Global's parent, National Amusements, Axios reported on Tuesday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/edgar-bronfman-jr-still-pursuing-deal-paramount-axios-reports-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D654CODEGJKV7OVMZINO4ZN3AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:24:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员希望 FAA 对波音公司的监督进行彻底审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院商务委员会主席希望联邦航空管理局对其对波音公司和其他制造商的监督进行彻底审查，这引起了人们对政府对飞机制造商审查的严重质疑。【原文：The chair of the Senate Commerce Committee wants the Federal Aviation Administration to conduct a thorough review into its oversight of Boeing and other manufacturers, raising serious questions about the government's scrutiny of the planemaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-senator-wants-faa-conduct-thorough-review-into-boeing-oversight-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPVYWP6SS5JSVHAXKKO7I2EMQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上诉法院推翻 Appian 对 Pegasystems 作出的 20 亿美元判决]]></title><description><![CDATA[软件公司 Pegasystems 周二说服弗吉尼亚州一家上诉法院，在 Pegasystems 涉嫌窃取 Appian 商业机密的法庭诉讼中，撤销了陪审团对竞争对手 Appian 作出的 20 亿美元的裁决。【原文：Software company Pegasystems convinced a Virginia appeals court on Tuesday to throw out a $2 billion jury verdict for rival Appian in a court battle over Pegasystems' alleged theft of Appian's trade secrets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/appians-2-bln-verdict-against-pegasystems-overturned-by-appeals-court-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DKHDBXQTJOXVIP4M3CXI3W3OI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 向美国受薪员工提供新一轮自愿买断服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉普车制造商斯泰兰特周二表示，将向其美国受薪员工提供新一轮自愿买断，这是公司首席执行官卡洛斯-塔瓦雷斯（Carlos Tavares）对其美国业务采取的一系列削减成本措施中的最新举措。【原文：Jeep-maker Stellantis said on Tuesday it is offering a new round of voluntary buyouts to its U.S. salaried workers, the latest in a series of cost-cutting measures CEO Carlos Tavares is placing on its American operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-offering-new-round-voluntary-buyouts-us-salaried-workers-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCA3ZORMSFL2ZLXIKML36KUCWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:39:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉诺福克南方公司以阻止美铁客运航线延误]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周二对诺福克南方公司提起民事诉讼，指控该运输公司违反联邦法律，延误了美国铁路公司（Amtrak）在纽约市和新奥尔良市之间新月路线上的客运列车。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department filed a civil suit on Tuesday against Norfolk Southern alleging that the transport company is delaying passenger trains on Amtrak’s Crescent Route between New York City and New Orleans in violation of federal law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-norfolk-southern-stop-delays-amtrak-passenger-route-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CZDJ5YRUBJNJIFQROYX7XDJGQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:33:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅第二季度销售额增长 5.3%，低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国化妆品巨头欧莱雅公布的第二季度销售额增长 5.3%，低于预期，这可能会进一步激怒已经对重要的中国市场缺乏反弹感到担忧的投资者。【原文：French cosmetics giant L'Oreal reported a 5.3% rise in second-quarter sales, below expectations and likely further rattling investors already worried about the lack of rebound in the important Chinese market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loreal-2q-sales-grow-53-slower-than-forecast-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6K5YMKXYZJI5HHKZLQMTEICW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:05:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦表示，哈里斯将恪守拜登反对美国中产阶级增税的誓言]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vice President Kamala Harris would adhere to President Joe Biden's vow not to raise taxes on middle-income taxpayers and has helped to determine the Biden-Harris' administration's approach to tax fairness, including higher taxes on the wealthy and corporations, U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/harris-would-adhere-bidens-vow-against-middle-class-us-tax-hikes-yellen-says-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOA7J6VCT5LOVKLJPRPNCVSBJA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车第二季度利润因喷气客机增产成本和空间费用而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲空中客车公司（Airbus）周二公布的第二季度利润大幅下降，原因是投资于喷气式客机增产的成本，再加上太空系统业务的费用在很大程度上超过了收入的增长。【原文：Europe's Airbus reported sharply lower second-quarter profits on Tuesday as the cost of investing in higher jetliner production, coupled with largely pre-announced charges in its Space Systems business, outweighed higher revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-second-quarter-profit-falls-jetliner-ramp-up-costs-space-charge-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLJLDOL335J3LPBJEMGZBZ2PAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:57:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州州长表示不能支持新日铁合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州州长乔希-夏皮罗（Josh Shapiro）周二表示，他不能支持新日铁以目前的形式收购美国钢铁公司，因为美国钢铁工人工会（United Steelworkers union）对这一合并表示不满。【原文：Pennsylvania Governor Josh Shapiro said on Tuesday that he cannot support Nippon Steel's bid to buy U.S. Steel in its current form because the United Steelworkers union is unhappy with the merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/pennsylvania-governor-says-cannot-support-nippon-us-steel-merger-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIRWV43U5ZKMVGIWAH2WXJ6DDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:53:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，Blackstone 有意收购购物中心所有者 Retail Opportunity]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，私募股权投资公司 Blackstone 正处于收购 Retail Opportunity Investments Corp (ROIC) 的早期谈判阶段，ROIC 是美国购物中心的所有者，市值约 17 亿美元。【原文：Private equity firm Blackstone is in early-stage talks to acquire Retail Opportunity Investments Corp (ROIC) , an owner of U.S. shopping centers with a market value of about $1.7 billion, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/blackstone-bid-acquire-shopping-center-owner-retail-opportunity-sources-say-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWLPCNLDCJJ7BL53BDQZNRAOPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:50:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通晋升波瑞提和诺瓦克为股东参与事务联席主管，更多激进活动迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周二任命资深银行家阿尔弗雷多-波雷蒂（Alfredo Porretti）和达伦-诺瓦克（Darren Novak）共同领导其全球股东参与和并购资本市场部，而此时企业正越来越多地寻求帮助，以抵御激进投资者推动的变革。【原文：JPMorgan Chase on Tuesday tapped veteran bankers Alfredo Porretti and Darren Novak to co-head its global shareholder engagement and M&amp;A capital markets group at a time corporations are increasingly looking for help to defend against activist investors pushing for changes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-promotes-porretti-novak-co-head-shareholder-engagement-more-activist-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SOPMWC4CBLP7FZ53BVJ5VK4EY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本新任货币外交官继续采取干预措施稳定日元汇率]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新任最高货币外交官三村敦志（Atsushi Mimura）告诉路透社，日本将保留其对日元汇率的基本态度，干预仍是应对汇率过度波动的一种选择。【原文：Japan will retain its basic approach on the yen with intervention remaining an option to tackle excessively volatile moves in the exchange rate, the country's new top currency diplomat Atsushi Mimura told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/japans-new-currency-diplomat-keeps-intervention-table-stabilise-yen-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDWAIKUM6VLMBKNILXT6A6OQ3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空开始提供高级座位]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）周二表示，它将开始提供高级座位选择，这标志着其传统业务模式的转变，使该航空公司的股价上涨了 7%。【原文：Spirit Airlines said on Tuesday it will begin to offer premium seating options, marking a shift from its traditional business model, sending the carrier's shares up 7%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-start-offering-premium-seating-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RZYBSKUDFNAVHIXTYLV7BUTPI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:45:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+可能在8月1日的JMMC会议上坚持产量政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+"小组的五位消息人士告诉路透社记者，尽管近期油价大幅下跌，但本周欧佩克+小组不太可能对当前的减产协议做出任何修改，并从10月份开始解除部分减产协议。【原文：An OPEC+ panel is unlikely this week to make any changes to its current deal to cut production and to start unwinding some cuts from October, despite recent sharp declines in oil prices, five sources from the producer group told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-likely-stick-output-policy-aug-1-jmmc-meeting-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIGEXWH7AZJXNOVZVQNLB645XQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月消费者信心指数上升；通胀预期稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份，美国消费者信心指数意外上升，但由于对通货膨胀和借贷成本上升的担忧挥之不去，消费者信心指数仍处于过去两年来的较低水平。【原文：U.S. consumer confidence unexpectedly rose in July, but remained in the tight range of the past two years amid lingering worries about inflation and higher borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-confidence-rises-july-inflation-expectations-steady-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2ZZPSSZJZP4VHSGPPBJZABY64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月份职位空缺减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 6 月份的职位空缺小幅下降，上个月的数据被上调，这表明支撑经济的劳动力韧性仍在继续。【原文：U.S. job openings fell marginally in June and data for the prior month was revised higher, pointing to continued labor resilience that is underpinning the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-edge-lower-june-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHQCQPO4RZMNLEJJDPC22O4ZWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顶级基金经理称 "华丽七重奏 "的下跌可能拖累美股]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利投资管理公司（MSIM）的一位高管告诉路透社，受此前推动大盘创下历史新高的七只超级大盘股下挫拖累，今年美股可能下跌10%至13%。
"独立来看，市场估值似乎有所扩大，因此每年下跌或回调10%至13%是很有可能的，"吉塔尼亚-坎德哈里（Jitania Kandhari）说。【原文：U.S. stocks could drop by between 10% and 13% this year, dragged down by a selloff in seven mega-cap stocks that previously pushed broader markets to record highs, a senior executive at Morgan Stanley Investment Management (MSIM) told Reuters.
"The market valuations on a standalone basis look extended, and therefore an annual drawdown or correction of 10% to 13% is very possible," Jitania Kandhari】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/drop-magnificent-seven-could-drag-down-us-stocks-top-fund-manager-says-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XF5XBRIQEBMSBOJVEROACXYLWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 将支付 14 亿美元了结得克萨斯州面部识别数据诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 已同意向得克萨斯州支付 14 亿美元，以解决该州指控 Facebook 母公司未经同意非法使用面部识别技术收集数百万得克萨斯人生物特征数据的诉讼。【原文：Meta Platforms has agreed to pay $1.4 billion to Texas to resolve the state’s lawsuit accusing the Facebook parent of illegally using facial-recognition technology to collect biometric data of millions of Texans without their consent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/meta-platforms-pay-14-bln-settle-texas-lawsuit-over-facial-recognition-data-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3MJG6GB4JI5XMYKRVZJL5NJME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:55:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[清洁空气技术需求放缓，康宁第三季度利润疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[特种玻璃生产商康宁公司周二预计，本季度利润将大幅低于华尔街预期，原因是对其清洁空气技术的需求放缓，尽管该公司的光纤产品销售强劲。【原文：Specialty glass maker Corning forecast current-quarter profit largely below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, blaming a slowdown in demand for its clean-air technologies, even as it saw robust sales for its optical fiber products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/corning-sees-weak-q3-profit-slow-demand-clean-air-tech-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYUGKBA36NMDZAY6V55OY3G5P4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称开始对华征收新关税的时间将至少推迟两周]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室周二表示，美国对包括电动汽车及其电池、计算机芯片和医疗产品在内的一系列中国进口产品大幅加征关税的部分措施将被推迟至少两周。【原文：The U.S. Trade Representative's office said Tuesday some of the steep U.S. tariff increases on an array of Chinese imports, including electric vehicles and their batteries, computer chips and medical products will be delayed by at least two weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-says-start-new-china-tariffs-will-be-delayed-by-least-two-weeks-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7WGZMQUPRNEHI7UCNHOXGGAUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Enverus 公司称，第二季度美国石油和天然气企业兼并仍在快速进行]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源研究机构 Enverus 周二发布的数据显示，第二季度美国石油和天然气补丁交易持续火爆，交易额突破 300 亿美元，大额美元交易推高了交易价值。【原文：U.S. oil and gas patch deals continued to run hot in the second quarter, topping $30 billion with big dollar tie-ups pushing values higher, according to data released on Tuesday by energy researcher Enverus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-gas-mergers-continue-furious-pace-q2-says-enverus-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYUYXKOCWRP5DB26AIXUMEJCVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因数据中心需求增长，美国电力公司第二季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电力公司周二公布的第二季度利润超出预期，主要得益于数据中心对发电人工智能等技术的电力需求增加。【原文：American Electric Power beat second-quarter profit estimates on Tuesday, aided by higher electricity demand from data centers powering technology like generative AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/american-electric-power-beats-q2-profit-estimates-data-center-demand-boost-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EEZ3FUF3JMXZEOA56QOKHJNOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:27:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 JD 体育公司表示，不要放弃耐克]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国体育和时尚零售商 JD Sports 是耐克最大的客户之一，该公司一位高级管理人员周二向耐克投出了信任票，称耐克 "会好起来的"。【原文：British sports and fashion retailer JD Sports , one of Nike's largest customers, gave the world's biggest sports brand by revenue a vote of confidence on Tuesday, with a senior executive saying it "will be just fine".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dont-write-off-nike-says-britains-jd-sports-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWRRAOOWENIZLJR6KAL4H7GAKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月房价保持不变，年涨幅为 10 个月来最小]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于抵押贷款利率上升抑制了需求，增加了住房供应，5 月份美国独户住宅价格持平，年增幅为 10 个月来最小。【原文：U.S. single-family home prices were unchanged in May and the annual increase was the smallest in 10 months as higher mortgage rates stifled demand, boosting housing supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-home-prices-unchanged-may-annual-gain-smallest-10-months-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTHPE2EE5RNCPEDXLYCRQZH5DQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:04:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[租赁需求强劲，美国塔提高关键利润指标的年度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产投资信托公司美国大厦周二上调了对年度调整后运营资金（AFFO）的预期，并在租赁业务强劲需求的帮助下，第二季度营收超过预期。【原文：Real estate investment trust American Tower raised its forecast for annual adjusted funds from operations (AFFO) and beat second-quarter revenue estimates on Tuesday, helped by strong demand for its leasing business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/american-tower-raises-annual-forecast-key-profit-metric-strong-leasing-demand-2024-07-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4IDHJA6UBKRJJ54I3O7FU3CRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>