<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:39:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:39:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：特朗普对电动汽车的打压在电池带如影随形]]></title><description><![CDATA[当时宣布了大约二十几个电池项目，有望为共和党占主导地位的各州注入数以万计的就业机会。到去年，美国人对电动汽车的热情减退，导致汽车制造商推迟或取消了一些项目。现在，特朗普总统最近的政策变化又给电池带带来了新的影响。【原文：Roughly two dozen battery projects were announced, promising to inject tens of thousands of jobs in Republican-dominated states. By last year Americans’ waning enthusiasm for EVs led automakers to delay or scrap some projects. Now, the additional fallout from President Trump’s recent policy changes is descending on the Battery Belt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trumps-crackdown-evs-hits-home-battery-belt-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNZK3X7R3JP53KW4WMEAABHIHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国有铁矿石买家因担心禁令而出售必和必拓的货物]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，必和必拓的几批铁矿石在中国上市销售，至少有一批卖给了当地一家贸易商，这有可能化解澳大利亚国内对中国政府禁止全球最大矿商销售铁矿石的担忧。【原文：Several cargoes of BHP iron ore were put up for sale in China on Thursday and at least one was sold to a local trader, potentially defusing concerns in Australia that Beijing had imposed a ban on iron ore sales from the world's biggest miner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-state-iron-ore-buyer-offers-bhp-cargoes-sale-amid-ban-fears-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B767FDB76FPL5JJWBG6LP67CIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空的麻烦暴露了低成本航空公司溢价战略的局限性]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空的财务困境表明，提升档次并不是解决低成本航空公司所面临挑战的灵丹妙药，低成本航空公司正在努力应对不断增加的运营成本、不断变化的客户偏好以及来自美国三大航空公司的激烈竞争。【原文：Spirit Airlines' financial troubles reveal that going upscale is not a panacea for the challenges facing low-cost carriers, which are grappling with mounting operating costs, changing customer preferences and stiff competition from the Big Three U.S. airlines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spirits-troubles-expose-limits-premium-strategy-low-cost-carriers-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZOSJWRHNJPDJAZUSMTRV2HQNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 在数据迷雾中，投资者从银行财报中寻找经济线索]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于联邦政府停摆导致新数据流中断，投资者将在下周关注各大银行的季度财报，以帮助判断美国经济的健康状况。【原文：Investors will look to major banks' quarterly earnings reports in the coming week to help gauge the U.S. economy's health as the federal government shutdown has interrupted the flow of new data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-seek-economic-clues-bank-earnings-amid-data-fog-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZPISTOYU5IEVGANYCA2PKKBJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对政治风险和美国停摆持谨慎态度，全球股票基金流入减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 10 月 8 日的一周内，全球股票基金流入量降至三周以来的最低点，原因是在法国政府垮台和美国政府持续停摆的风险影响下，投资者在近期市场大涨之后稍事喘息。【原文：Global equity fund inflows cooled to a three-week-low in the week to October 8 as investors took a breather after the recent market rally amid risks surrounding the collapse of the French government and the ongoing government shutdown in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OWUOAPSEJIGRA66RZ55GKXFPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者信心数据公布前美国股指期货微涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货走高，预示着短暂停顿后的反弹，投资者重新关注人工智能推动的今年以来引导市场的势头，同时等待消费者情绪数据为经济提供新的线索。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Friday, signaling a rebound after a brief pause as investors refocused on AI-driven momentum that has steered markets this year, while awaiting consumer sentiment data for fresh clues on the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-index-futures-tick-up-ahead-consumer-sentiment-data-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFJYJSW22RK6JIOG3DIN7I6MDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:59:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国石油公司赢得液化天然气货物仲裁案后，Venture Global 股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国石油公司（BP）在针对美国供应商的仲裁案中胜诉，原因是该公司未能根据长期供应协议交付液化天然气，该协议本应于 2022 年底开始执行。【原文：Venture Global shares slumped 17% in premarket trading on Friday after BP won its arbitration case against the U.S. supplier over its failure to deliver liquefied natural gas under a long-term supply deal that was due to start in late 2022.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venture-global-shares-slide-after-bp-wins-arbitration-case-over-lng-cargoes-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBW64BDINZNTNKWYMTHIH6GPWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:56:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行：数字欧元可能导致银行挤兑，损失高达 7000 亿欧元存款]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）周五的一项模拟研究显示，在商业银行发生挤兑时，数字欧元可能会导致多达 7000 亿欧元（8108.8 亿美元）的存款流失，从而使欧元区的十几家贷款机构陷入流动性紧张的困境。【原文：A digital euro could drain up to 700 billion euros ($810.88 billion) in deposits during a run on commercial banks, pushing around a dozen euro zone lenders into a liquidity squeeze, a European Central Bank simulation showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/digital-euro-could-drain-up-700-billion-euros-deposits-bank-run-ecb-says-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEKCNSXRCZJFRLLUFEDA3MS43Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:56:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 9 月中国产电动汽车销量同比增长 2.8]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国乘用车联席会周五公布的数据显示，随着特斯拉新款六座电动汽车开始在华交付，特斯拉9月份在华电动汽车销量同比增长2.8%，结束了连续两个月的下滑态势。【原文：Tesla 's China-made electric vehicle sales increased 2.8% in September from a year earlier, ending a two-month decline as its new six-seater began deliveries in China, data from the China Passenger Car Association showed on Friday, while the U.S. automaker's European sales had a partial rebound.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-september-china-made-ev-sales-rise-28-year-year-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YN2RLWIM5FO3XCCNXF27KXMRTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国政府对供应链实施出口管制后，中国电池股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国宣布将控制锂电池零部件的出口，此举加强了中国对能源储存和电动汽车关键技术的控制，随后中国电池制造商的股价周五大幅下跌。【原文：Shares of Chinese battery makers plunged on Friday after the country announced that it would control exports of lithium battery parts, a move that tightens its grip on the technology critical for energy storage and electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-battery-shares-slide-after-beijing-imposes-export-controls-over-supply-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4E4FFCX4RO43MZI4ZBJVB2WK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车第三季度销量因欧洲和电动汽车而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车集团周五公布的第三季度全球交付量增长了 1%，原因是新车型促进了西欧市场的销售。【原文：Volkswagen Group reported a 1% increase in third-quarter global deliveries on Friday as new models helped sales in Western Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagens-third-quarter-sales-lifted-by-europe-evs-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIDYS37YIBNG5HOO6S4JLGCLVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场分析师对日本执政联盟分裂的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本执政联盟周五解体，小伙伴公明党反叛自民党新任强硬派领导人高市真奈，此举使她的首相候选人资格受到质疑。【原文：Japan's ruling coalition broke up on Friday, with junior partner Komeito rebelling against the Liberal Democratic Party's new hardline leader Sanae Takaichi in a move that cast doubt over her premiership bid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/market-analysts-reaction-japans-ruling-coalition-split-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUAIMFYRQZIN5M6E6M2VCXVH4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:26:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国机器人制造商 AgiBot 计划明年在香港上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，中国仿人机器人制造商AgiBot计划明年在香港首次公开募股，目标估值为400亿至500亿港元（合51.4亿至64亿美元）。【原文：Chinese humanoid robot maker AgiBot plans to launch an initial public offering in Hong Kong next year, eyeing a valuation of HK$40 billion to HK$50 billion ($5.14 billion to $6.4 billion), sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-robot-maker-agibot-plans-hong-kong-ipo-next-year-sources-say-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCDSWTFMLRJNPKKLGQCQOSZQJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:20:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国就高通公司涉嫌违反反垄断法展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周五表示，中国已对美国半导体制造商高通公司展开调查。【原文：China has initiated an investigation into U.S. semiconductor manufacturer Qualcomm, the country's market regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-opens-probe-into-qualcomm-suspected-anti-trust-violation-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FF5QGALN7JLPXGQUFM247EHS54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国启动监管谷歌搜索的新权力]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国周五指定谷歌在网络搜索领域具有 "战略市场地位"，这是英国首次运用新的权力来应对大型科技公司的主导地位，并为其认为必要的干预措施铺平道路。【原文：Britain on Friday designated Google with "strategic market status" in online search, the first time it has deployed new powers to tackle the dominance of big tech and paving the way for interventions it deems necessary.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uk-gains-new-powers-over-google-with-search-market-designation-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIND63GCSVPN3EUSKTGJPL6LDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，投资者将目光投向大名鼎鼎的公司之外，创纪录地向太空投资 35 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据专注于太空领域的投资公司 Seraphim Space 周五发布的一份报告显示，在更多初创企业和持续国防开支的推动下，第三季度全球太空投资达到创纪录的 35 亿美元。【原文：Global space investment hit a record $3.5 billion in the third quarter, driven by a wider range of startups and continued defense spending, according to a report released Friday by space-focused investment firm Seraphim Space.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/investors-pour-record-35-billion-into-space-investors-look-beyond-big-names-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7EEVMQXTNLTJDSEF2DXKXHYXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行研究发现美国关税拖累欧盟信心和就业]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行研究人员周五在一篇博文中写道，只有少数欧元区工人担心美国关税会危及他们的工作，但这仍可能给本已疲软的经济带来拖累。【原文：Only a small minority of euro zone workers fear that U.S. tariffs will jeopardise their jobs but that could still create a drag for an already sluggish economy, European Central Bank researchers wrote in a blog post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-tariffs-drag-eu-confidence-jobs-ecb-study-finds-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPKLJOUTGJKKRB2KFZ7XPTFG7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因关税相关成本影响预期，李维斯下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 的股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌了 7.7%，原因是与关税相关的成本超过了欧洲和美洲市场对宽腿牛仔裤的强劲需求，这家牛仔布生产商的年度利润预期未能达到投资者的预期。【原文：Levi Strauss's shares slipped 7.7% in premarket trading on Friday after the denim maker's annual profit forecast failed to meet investor expectations, as tariff-linked costs outweighed strong demand for wide-leg denims in Europe and the Americas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/levi-strauss-slips-tariff-related-costs-weigh-forecast-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6HFGDP4WDBMTNN2NEC35ZPJHHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Five：政治的危险]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国和日本的政治动荡笼罩着市场，美国银行拉开了最新财报季的序幕，而政府关门仍在继续，决策者们聚集在华盛顿参加国际货币基金组织（IMF）和世界银行的年会。【原文：Political turmoil in France and Japan looms large over markets as U.S. banks kick off the latest earnings season, while the government shutdown drags on and policymakers gather in Washington for the IMF and World Bank annual meetings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/take-five/global-markets-themes-graphic-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSSFRSJEQBM2ZGVUFU2JZBK5TU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国银行转向美国金融公司 BNY 进行国际汇款]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国的储蓄银行正在求助于一家领先的美国金融公司来帮助客户进行国际支付，此举旨在抵御后起的低成本竞争者，引起了人们对欧洲金融服务主权的担忧。【原文：Germany's savings banks are turning to a leading U.S. financial firm to help customers with international payments, a move aimed at fending off upstart low-cost competitors that has raised concerns over the sovereignty of Europe's financial services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/german-banks-turn-us-financial-firm-bny-international-money-transfers-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJA4R5FH5ZII3JWX2QHSOBG7RI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:36:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚称取消芯片关税豁免会损害竞争力和美国供应链]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份政府报告称，马来西亚周五警告称，美国取消对其半导体出口的关税豁免可能会损害其竞争力，并使供应网络紧张。【原文：Malaysia warned on Friday that any removal of tariff exemptions on its semiconductor exports by the United States could hurt its competitiveness and strain supply networks, according to a government report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/malaysia-says-removing-chip-tariff-exemption-could-harm-competitiveness-us-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCDX3Y4YXZLGBNL6ILSXKRIVEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Papa John's 高层表示将印度列为优先考虑的素食地区]]></title><description><![CDATA[约翰爸爸国际公司（Papa John's International）的高管们表示，该公司将印度列为其全球优先市场之一，并根据当地人的口味推出了素食占多数的处女菜单，预计此举将促进公司的长期增长。【原文：Papa John's International is placing India among its priority markets globally and tailoring its offerings to local tastes with its maiden majority-vegetarian menu, executives said, in a move the U.S. pizza chain expects will fuel long-term growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/papa-johns-puts-india-priority-list-with-vegetarian-fare-executives-say-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U27JDDNSNJNANBAVYG6WUENYIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长称希腊力争今年敲定雪佛龙天然气勘探合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊能源部长周五表示，希腊正在努力争取与美国石油巨头雪佛龙及其希腊合作伙伴 Helleniq Energy 在年底前敲定希腊近海能源勘探合同。【原文：Greece is working hard to finalise a contract with U.S. oil major Chevron and its Greek partner Helleniq Energy for energy exploration offshore Greece by the end of the year, the country's energy minister said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/greece-seeks-finalise-chevron-gas-exploration-contract-this-year-says-minister-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERRLXQ2Y55JLLG52PDAEB3VZZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球金融监管机构将加强对人工智能的监控]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着银行和金融业其他部门加大人工智能的使用，全球金融监管机构已经制定了更密切监控风险的计划。【原文：Global financial regulators have laid out plans for closer monitoring of the risks as banks and other parts of the financial industry ramp up the use of artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-financial-watchdogs-ramp-up-monitoring-ai-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWSU75JYPBKD3KSXKH6TF6HHRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将从 10 月 14 日起对美国船只征收额外港口费]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国交通部周五表示，自10月14日起，美国公司和个人拥有或运营的船舶，或在美国建造或悬挂美国国旗的船舶，将被征收额外的港口费。【原文：Vessels owned or operated by U.S. firms and individuals - or those built in the United States or that fly the U.S. flag - will be charged additional port fees per voyage starting on October 14, China's transport ministry said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-hit-us-ships-with-additional-port-fees-october-14-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQM4URMMWFLJFPPX6TTDGJ22EA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 第三季度出货量增长 13%，达到 130 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 汽车制造商周五表示，第三季度全球出货量同比增长 13%，估计达到 130 万辆。【原文：Stellantis' global shipments rose 13% year-on-year in the third quarter to an estimated 1.3 million units, the automaker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-third-quarter-shipments-rise-13-13-million-vehicles-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2D2NFRTFVMMPHMZ3CFFBZWHGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：比尔-盖茨与泛美卫生组织考虑为低收入国家提供减肥药物的方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[盖茨基金会和泛美卫生组织告诉路透社，这两个全球健康组织都在研究如何让低收入国家更容易获得减肥药物，如诺和诺德的Wegovy和礼来的Mounjaro。【原文：The Gates Foundation and the Pan American Health Organization are both working on ways to make weight-loss drugs like Novo Nordisk's Wegovy and Eli Lilly's Mounjaro more accessible in lower-income countries, the global health groups told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bill-gates-paho-consider-ways-bring-weight-loss-drugs-lower-income-countries-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5UP7XSW25I5DINGA4AUNS5VNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美紧张局势的最新症结是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）和中国国家主席习近平将于本月访问首尔，在中美举行会谈之前，中国政府正在积累谈判筹码，宣布新的出口管制措施，以加强对高科技制造业供应链的控制。【原文：Beijing is stacking up its bargaining chips ahead of expected U.S.-China talks when Presidents Donald Trump and Xi Jinping visit Seoul this month, announcing new export controls to tighten its grip over high-tech manufacturing supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/what-are-latest-sticking-points-us-china-tensions-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RACNVINLSRIF7NZOKANWOUPVKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金创纪录的上涨为投资者创造了新规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着人工智能驱动的股市大涨和比特币的火热，投资者不得不重新思考世界上最古老的资产类别之一--黄金的驱动力是什么，投资者正在检验对黄金的既定看法。【原文：Investors are testing well-established views about gold, which is surging to new records, as an AI-driven stocks rally and red-hot bitcoin force a rethink of what's driving one of the world's oldest asset classes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/global-markets-gold-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5XU46NO6ZPE7FZAMNRNPFNR3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[基金经理薪酬飙升让艾斯勒资本公司损失惨重]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者和业内人士表示，由于员工成本飙升侵蚀了交易利润，艾斯勒资本公司决定关闭其旗舰多策略对冲基金，这暴露出总部位于伦敦的基金在试图快速发展和复制规模更大、根基稳固的美国公司时所面临的困难。【原文：Eisler Capital's decision to close its flagship multi-strategy hedge fund as soaring staff costs eroded trading profit exposes the difficulty London-based funds face when trying to grow rapidly and replicate bigger, entrenched U.S. players, investors and industry insiders say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/soaring-fund-manager-pay-cost-eisler-capital-dear-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INUU2NKUYVJX3KPJDLHWJVMJGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>