<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:04:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:04:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大服务业采购经理人指数显示年底经济活动萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P全球公司周一公布的加拿大服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）数据显示，由于邮政工人罢工影响了经济活动，加上未完成的工作数量下降，12月份加拿大服务业经济三个月来首次出现恶化。【原文：Canada's services economy deteriorated for the first time in three months in December as a postal workers' strike weighed on activity and work outstanding tumbled, S&amp;P Global's Canada services PMI data showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadas-services-pmi-shows-activity-shrinking-year-end-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VMV5IVQVBIS3AFF3ML6R6WUMU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:34:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称有关其关税政策变化的报道是错误的]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一驳斥了一份报纸的报道，该报道称他的助手们正在探讨只涵盖关键进口商品的关税计划。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump on Monday refuted a newspaper report that said his aides were exploring tariff plans that would only cover critical imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-reporting-changes-his-tariff-policy-is-wrong-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YRZFDHF3BK6THWMI5ZRUXAAI4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:31:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国出口禁令将锑价推向新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着贸易紧张局势日益加剧，中国最新的出口禁令改变了关键材料市场的态势，消费者开始寻求替代供应，锑的价格可能会创下历史新高。【原文：Antimony prices are likely to hit record levels as consumers seek alternative supplies following China's latest export ban with growing trade tensions changing the dynamics around markets for critical materials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-export-ban-push-antimony-prices-new-highs-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAYIKA7EEZPQZATMZTYZY62UT4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储库克进一步降息需谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（Fed Reserve）理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）周一表示，鉴于经济稳健，且通胀比之前预期的更加坚挺，美联储在进一步降息时可以谨慎行事。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve can be cautious with any further interest rate cuts given a solid economy and inflation proving stickier than previously expected, Fed Governor Lisa Cook said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-cook-further-rate-cuts-can-come-cautiously-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2VJ5IWAMJOVPF2HNDWI7WXNUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降价、更便宜的融资刺激需求，Lucid 电动汽车交付量超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lucid 集团周一公布了创纪录的第四季度交付量，超过了华尔街的预期，因为这家由沙特阿拉伯支持的汽车制造商受益于对其豪华电动轿车的强劲需求。【原文：Lucid Group reported record fourth-quarter deliveries on Monday, surpassing Wall Street expectations, as the Saudi Arabia-backed automaker benefited from strong demand for its luxury electric sedans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lucid-beats-estimates-ev-deliveries-price-cuts-cheaper-financing-spur-demand-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUTMHBA7BNM4XOSBX54JFETXXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构就高风险住房贷款起诉伯克希尔旗下公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）周一起诉沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的一个部门，指控该部门逼迫人们向伯克希尔的人造房屋业务克莱顿房屋公司（Clayton Homes）申请高风险、负担不起的贷款以购买房屋。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau Monday sued a unit of Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway on Monday for allegedly pushing people into risky, unaffordable loans to buy homes from Clayton Homes, Berkshire's manufactured housing business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-regulator-sues-berkshire-unit-over-risky-home-loans-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMESGTP7NRORZOEQFJMXZIQA54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空重返 "三大 "航空公司行列，券商预测 2025 年业绩强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，券商 Jefferies 和 TD Cowen 将美国航空公司的股票评级上调为 "买入"，认为随着该公司走出充满挑战的一年，其股价有望在 2025 年强劲上涨。【原文：American Airlines' stock is poised for a strong 2025 as the carrier emerges from a challenging year, according to brokerages Jefferies and TD Cowen, who upgraded the stock to a "buy" rating on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-back-big-3-carriers-brokerages-predict-strong-2025-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHSBATAW3NNWXJPBB2XW22N35M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:55:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰任命 Lisa McGeough 为美国首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行（HSBC）周一任命丽莎-麦基夫（Lisa McGeough）为首席执行官兼美国业务总裁，成为十多年来领导该行美国业务的首位女性首席执行官。【原文：HSBC on Monday named Lisa McGeough as chief executive officer and president of its U.S. operations, making her the first woman CEO leading the bank's operations in the region in more than a decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-names-lisa-mcgeough-us-ceo-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIBEUN4UEBPSNN7CFS2G663YGE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》报道：特朗普助手瞄准关键领域征收进口关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周一报道，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的助手们正在探讨适用于所有国家但只涵盖关键进口商品的关税计划。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's aides are exploring tariff plans that would be applied to every country but only cover critical imports, the Washington Post reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-aides-target-critical-areas-import-duties-washington-post-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAZUMH4IVBIVHP3PI33KZGOLGA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:06:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salesforce 数据显示，受人工智能影响的购物促进了在线假日销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据Salesforce的一份报告，人工智能驱动的聊天机器人在2024年假日季帮助消费者购买和退货，使美国的在线销售额同比增长了近4%。【原文：Artificial intelligence-powered chatbots helped consumers purchase and return products during the 2024 holiday season, boosting online sales in the United States by nearly 4% year-over-year, according to a report by Salesforce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ai-influenced-shopping-boosts-online-holiday-sales-salesforce-data-shows-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYG357VWU5PYXP7M4OVESR6UAE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，迪士尼接近达成将 Hulu + 直播电视业务并入 Fubo 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道称，华特迪士尼公司和流媒体服务提供商 FuboTV 即将达成一项交易，合并双方的在线直播电视业务。【原文：Walt Disney Co and streaming provider FuboTV are nearing a deal to combine their online live TV businesses, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-nears-deal-merge-hulu-live-tv-business-into-fubo-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTW2FGUI75JL5KPQJD4BNWJROQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司和日本钢铁公司向法院起诉拜登阻止 149 亿美元的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）阻止日本公司以 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁制造商后，美国钢铁公司和新日本制铁公司周一表示，他们已提起两起诉讼。【原文：U.S. Steel and Nippon Steel said on Monday they had filed two lawsuits after U.S. President Joe Biden blocked the $14.9 billion buyout of the American steelmaker by the Japanese company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-nippon-steel-file-two-lawsuits-after-biden-blocks-149-billion-deal-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S65MI5XCTJPNVGUA7F2J5UB7LU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[当地媒体报道，智利 Codelco 公司 2024 年铜产量 "略有 "增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的铜金属生产商智利科德尔科公司（Codelco）董事长马克西莫-帕切科（Maximo Pacheco）周一在接受当地一家报纸采访时说，2024 年该公司的铜产量与前一年相比 "略有增加"。【原文：Copper production at Chile's Codelco, the world's largest producer of the metal, was "slightly higher" in 2024 when compared to the previous year, Chairman Maximo Pacheco said in an interview with a local newspaper on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chiles-codelco-copper-production-slightly-increases-2024-local-press-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NIHY5OORZI4VGTYRS6YI5FGM4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:52:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片股上涨，期货走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货在上周尾盘反弹的基础上继续走高，投资者因对人工智能的持续乐观而买入科技股，并等待可能为美国货币政策路径定调的关键经济数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Monday, building on a late rally last week, as investors bought into technology stocks on continued optimism around AI and awaited crucial economic data that could set the tone for the U.S. monetary policy path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-higher-chip-stocks-rise-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTBT6KPE3JMKVA565NCVMAMCOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：特朗普上台前交易提振美国收益率，人民币走势震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUOXNJMWPRIPJI2NS2B2HRMHFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:23:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼、福克斯和华纳兄弟将请求法院解除对推出 Venu 体育服务的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[三家大型媒体公司将于周一请求美国上诉法院推翻阻止其 Venu 体育流媒体服务推出的裁决，并辩称地区法院法官以反垄断为由阻止其计划的首次亮相是错误的。【原文：Three major media companies will ask the U.S. Court of Appeals on Monday to reverse a ruling that blocked the launch of their Venu Sports streaming service, arguing that a district court judge was wrong to halt its planned debut on antitrust grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/disney-fox-warner-bros-ask-court-lift-ban-launch-venu-sports-service-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVUHUMJWYBOULPVFIQXUZGWCVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:17:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 和 WWE 旨在推动全球摔跤热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 下一次涉足现场直播节目是从周一开始的，届时该公司将播出第一集《Raw》，这是世界摔跤娱乐公司每周的精彩节目，三十年来一直是美国电视的主打节目。【原文：Netflix's next venture into live programming starts Monday when the company streams its first episode of "Raw," the weekly World Wrestling Entertainment spectacle that has been a staple of U.S. television for three decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/netflix-wwe-aim-fuel-wrestling-fervor-worldwide-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIC6VBQJF5ONVGM5KMIYLA2HNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯南克等人表示，特朗普的政策可能不会导致通货膨胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括历任美国总统顾问在内的一些知名经济学家一致认为，当选总统唐纳德-特朗普扩大关税、减税和遏制移民的计划可能不会像早期分析所认为的那样引发通货膨胀。【原文：A number of leading economists, including advisers to past U.S. presidents, have coalesced around the view that President-elect Donald Trump's plans to broaden tariffs, cut taxes and curb immigration may not prove as inflationary as early analysis had suggested.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-policies-may-not-prove-inflationary-bernanke-others-say-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOYHNDQ575P35MO2SYWMNJUYDE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受高价刺激，阿根廷人到国外寻找更便宜的耐克和巨无霸食品]]></title><description><![CDATA[在智利圣地亚哥的购物中心和巴西的海滩上，阿根廷人正在抢购服装、电子产品和 caipirinhas，因为以美元计算的国内成本因当地比索走强而飙升，阿根廷人正在利用海外价格便宜的优势。【原文：In the shopping malls of Santiago de Chile and the beaches of Brazil, Argentines are snapping up clothes, electronics and caipirinhas, taking advantage of cheaper prices overseas as domestic costs in dollar terms spike on a stronger local peso.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/stung-by-high-prices-argentines-seek-cheaper-nikes-big-macs-abroad-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNTRNBKEBZMN7GVPC5A43SBT5E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面对保守派的反弹，董事会多元化停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[2020 年乔治-弗洛伊德遇害后，投资者梅洛迪-霍布森（Mellody Hobson）回忆起《财富》500 强公司的董事们经常打电话来，要求推荐董事会中的多元化候选人。她说，现在这种情况 "非常零散"。【原文：In the aftermath of George Floyd's killing in 2020, investor Mellody Hobson recalls frequent calls from directors at Fortune 500 companies for references to diverse candidates for boards. Now, she says, it's "very sporadic."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boardroom-diversity-stalls-face-conservative-backlash-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCWITMYRGZNGJPGAULG34PMQ3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总理办公室称，意大利与 SpaceX 的会谈不是梅洛尼-特朗普会晤的主题]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利总理办公室表示，意大利总理乔治亚-梅洛尼周末访问美国期间，没有讨论罗马与埃隆-马斯克的 SpaceX 公司就可能提供 Starlink 服务一事进行的会谈。【原文：Italian Prime Minister Georgia Meloni did not discuss Rome's talks with Elon Musk's SpaceX over the possible supply of its Starlink services during her weekend visit to the United States, the PM's office said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/italys-talks-with-spacex-not-topic-meloni-trump-meeting-pm-office-says-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAH3WFO5HZNL3PKFHHD24YHK2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在冬季风暴后取消 1,300 多个航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一场冬季风暴给美国广大地区带来了冰雪和严寒，美国航空公司取消了 1300 多个航班。【原文：Airlines in the United States canceled more than 1,300 flights on Monday after a winter storm brought snow, ice and freezing temperatures to a broad swath of the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-cancel-over-1300-flights-after-winter-storm-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2HEWCAEYNJU5NV4BMCUL7GYEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国交易所要求大型基金经理限制股票抛售]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士称，中国的主要证券交易所要求一些大型共同基金在今年年初限制股票抛售，因为中国政府正试图在世界第二大经济体进入困难时期之际安抚市场。【原文：China's main stock exchanges asked some large mutual funds to restrict stock selling at the start of the year, three sources familiar with the matter said, as authorities sought to calm markets heading into a tricky period for the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-exchanges-ask-big-fund-managers-restrict-stock-selling-sources-say-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYANKZA3OBM5BHXFJ6JOH5YLYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 08:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：加元平静，特鲁多走向出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LC6QE32U4JOGTOT4O4OBCKGHOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国争相支撑下滑的人民币和股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，中国的证券交易所和中央银行慌忙为暴跌的人民币和下跌的股市辩护，试图安抚对唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫和中国政府重振经济的能力感到担忧的投资者。【原文：China's stock exchanges and central bank scurried to defend a tumbling yuan and falling stock markets on Monday, trying to soothe investors concerned about Donald Trump's return to the White House and Beijing's ability to revive the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-scrambles-shore-up-sliding-yuan-stock-markets-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2IKPHPMUZMGLAL2Q4TUYNICPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街银行退出气候组织令倡导者担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周，美国的贷款机构急于退出全球银行业顶级气候联盟之一，这招致了运动人士的嘲讽，他们担心该行业正在失去对化石燃料采取行动的决心。【原文：U.S. lenders have been rushing in recent weeks to leave one of the world's top banking sector climate coalitions, drawing scorn from campaigners who worry the industry is losing resolve to take action on fossil fuels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/exodus-by-wall-street-banks-climate-group-worries-advocates-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6ICLM4U6BIT7IRTSBU7CLIHJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 要求富士软对贝恩 "违反 NDA "申请禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权基金 KKR 周一表示，已致函富士软公司，要求其向法院提起诉讼，以制止贝恩资本在贝恩和 KKR 争夺这家软件制造商的过程中违反保密协议的行为。【原文：U.S. private equity fund KKR said on Monday it sent a letter to Fuji Soft asking it to make a court filing to stop what it said was Bain Capital's violation of a non-disclosure agreement amid Bain and KKR's acquisition battle for the software maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-asks-fuji-soft-file-injunction-against-bains-breach-nda-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5JFS2Y5ZVKHTMUYCQHCWBLGXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:46:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡数据中心公司 Digital Edge 融资逾 16 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于新加坡的数据中心公司 Digital Edge 周一表示，该公司已通过股权和债务融资相结合的方式筹集了超过 16 亿美元的新资金，为下一阶段的发展提供资金。【原文：Singapore-headquartered data centre company Digital Edge said on Monday it had raised over $1.6 billion in new capital via a combination of equity and debt financing to fund its next phase of growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/singaporean-data-centre-company-digital-edge-raises-over-16-billion-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56X3RJUAJVKRFD67NIAXH7DRTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国吉利控股公司的目标是到 2027 年年销量超过 500 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国吉利控股集团（GEELY.UL）周日表示，该公司的目标是到2027年汽车年销量超过500万辆，比2023年有大幅提升。【原文：China's Geely Holding Group (GEELY.UL) on Sunday said it aims to sell more than 5 million vehicles annually by 2027, a big jump from 2023, which it hopes to achieve by accelerating consolidation of its sprawling brands and improving efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-geely-holding-targets-over-5-million-units-annual-sales-by-2027-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZXJEP7LBFOOBNQ6FCVO3HT5DM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新服务业采购经理人指数显示，中国服务业活动创 7 个月新高，但美国贸易担忧削弱了乐观情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项私营部门调查显示，受国内需求激增的推动，中国服务业活动在12月份以七个月来最快的速度扩张，但来自国外的订单却出现下降，这反映出经济面临的贸易风险正在增加。【原文：China's services activity expanded at the fastest pace in seven months in December, driven by a surge in domestic demand, but orders from abroad declined, reflecting growing trade risks to the economy, a private sector survey showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-services-activity-hits-7-month-high-us-trade-fears-dent-optimism-caixin-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F56KNVEFVZPVBFAZSJUO6RTJ54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:54:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>