<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:46:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:46:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司在 MAX 中空门塞爆炸后面临多项调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[继 1 月 5 日阿拉斯加航空公司一架 737 MAX 9 飞机发生面板爆炸事故后，波音公司正面临美国监管机构和检察官对其安全和质量做法的更严格审查。【原文：Boeing is facing heightened scrutiny from U.S. regulators and prosecutors into its safety and quality practices following the Jan. 5 panel blowout on an Alaska Airlines 737 MAX 9.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-faces-multiple-probes-after-mid-air-max-door-plug-blowout-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYBNMD6GCFJLDDS72BZCNBMHAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:41:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼重申她愿意在必要时加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备局局长米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周五重申了她的观点，即在政策利率保持稳定的情况下，通胀率将进一步下降，但她表示，今年通胀率没有改善，如果进展停滞或逆转，她仍愿意加息。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman on Friday repeated her view that inflation will fall further with the policy rate held steady, but said she has seen no improvement on inflation this year and remains willing to hike rates should progress stall or reverse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-bowman-repeats-shes-willing-hike-rates-if-needed-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDLFIPX5CROFNNZSCCF3OCZDYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海底捞餐饮运营商 Super Hi 股价大涨 38%，强势登陆美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Super Hi International 在纳斯达克首次上市就大涨了 38%，使这家中国连锁火锅店海鲜楼的运营商估值达到约 17.4 亿美元。【原文：Super Hi International , jumped 38% in its debut on Nasdaq, giving the operator of Chinese hotpot restaurant chain Haidilao a valuation of about $1.74 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/haidilao-restaurant-operator-super-his-shares-surge-38-strong-us-market-debut-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VR7JA426PVLNLBLEK2GIJA2K5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:10:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在人工智能的推动下，BuzzFeed 首席执行官转而采用以股票为基础的多数薪酬制度]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字媒体公司 BuzzFeed 首席执行官乔纳-佩雷蒂（Jonah Peretti）周五表示，在努力推动采用人工智能以加快扭亏为盈的同时，他的薪酬中将有很大一部分是股票期权。【原文：A major part of BuzzFeed CEO Jonah Peretti's compensation will now be in stock options, the digital media firm said on Friday, amid efforts to boost the adoption of artificial intelligence to speed up a turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/buzzfeed-ceo-moves-majority-stock-based-compensation-amid-ai-push-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJGUUFIPV5O5HIV5A6QFVTGO4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席鲍威尔 COVID-19 检测呈阳性，在家办公]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储发言人在一份电子邮件声明中说，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔周四的 COVID-19 检测呈阳性，目前正在家中工作。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell tested positive for COVID-19 on Thursday and is currently working from home, a Fed spokesperson said in an emailed statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-chair-powell-tests-positive-covid-19-working-home-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K62K76COHBL3LEBQAGZTTHHU44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:57:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本周备忘录股狂热之后，GameStop 因增资计划而暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[零售业的宠儿 GameStop 上周五大跌 26%，因为这家陷入困境的电子游戏零售商表示，将利用本周的 "备忘录股 "热潮出售最多 4,500 万股股票。【原文：Retail darling GameStop slumped 26% on Friday after the struggling videogame retailer said it would sell up to 45 million shares, taking advantage of the meme-stocks frenzy this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestop-tumbles-capital-raise-plans-after-meme-stocks-frenzy-this-week-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LA3RQW4MNNIPJLJD24I57PNJKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音股东投票选举首席执行官卡尔霍恩连任董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据初步统计，波音公司股东在公司年度会议上投票选举即将离任的首席执行官戴夫-卡尔霍恩（Dave Calhoun）连任该公司董事会成员。【原文：Boeing Co shareholders voted to re-elect outgoing Chief Executive Dave Calhoun to the planemaker's board at the company's annual meeting, as per a preliminary tally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-shareholders-vote-re-elect-ceo-calhoun-board-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYGXKMQTOFJPND4ZLI4JARIX5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定，可要求 Citgo 股份竞标者如何满足债券持有人的要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国地区法院法官周五裁定，在美国法院举行的决定炼油商 Citgo Petroleum (PDVSAC.UL) 所有权的股票拍卖会上，可以要求竞标者说明其具有约束力的报价是否涵盖委内瑞拉债券持有人在另一起法院诉讼中提出的索赔。【原文：Bidders in a U.S. court auction of shares that will decide the ownership of oil refiner Citgo Petroleum (PDVSAC.UL) can be required to say if their binding offers cover claims by Venezuela bondholders in a separate court action, a U.S. District Court judge ruled on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/citgo-share-bidders-can-be-asked-how-accommodate-bondholder-claims-judge-rules-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOJ6R2PZYVJHJJSA6UW7ADJSKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[下周德克萨斯州五月份电力需求将创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州电网运营商周五预计，随着家庭和企业为躲避春季热浪而开动空调，下周德克萨斯州的用电量将可能打破五月份的记录。【原文：Power use in Texas will likely break records for the month of May next week as homes and businesses crank up their air conditioners to escape a spring heat wave, the state's electric grid operator projected on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/texas-power-demand-hit-record-high-month-may-next-week-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMFI4OXQIBMEBBYWRNFGQYHCP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:17:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大广播公司（CBC）报道：加拿大安全情报局局长警告中国可利用 TikTok 监视用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[据加拿大广播公司（CBC News）周五报道，加拿大安全情报局局长警告加拿大人不要使用视频应用程序 TikTok，称从其用户那里收集的数据 "可供中国政府使用"。【原文：The head of Canada's Security Intelligence Service warned Canadians against using video app TikTok, saying data gleaned from its users "is available to the government of China," CBC News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-security-intelligence-chief-warns-that-china-can-use-tiktok-spy-users-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHBGLOI5PNNX5K7P2IEECN5TKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储宣布推出新的供应链压力指标]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行正在加强其追踪供应链状况的数据产品。【原文：The Federal Reserve Bank of New York is bolstering its data offerings tracking the state of supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ny-fed-announces-launch-new-supply-chain-pressure-metrics-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KROBSOCMRNLMDKM4R4DK5M4R7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行将以 29 亿美元收购华联银行的多户贷款组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿联邦银行（Washington Federal Bank）周五同意以约 29 亿美元的价格向美国银行（Bank of America）出售商业多户房地产贷款组合，帮助这家地区性贷款机构减少在这一问题领域的风险敞口。【原文：Washington Federal Bank agreed on Friday to sell a portfolio of commercial multi-family real estate loans to Bank of America for about $2.9 billion, helping the regional lender cut its exposure to the troubled sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bank-america-buy-wafds-multi-family-loan-portfolio-29-bln-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPHWLLGKUJOOBGJHFLAKRK3EOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业反弹后，美国对 G7 俄罗斯钻石禁令态度冷淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[七位消息人士称，在非洲国家、印度宝石抛光商和纽约珠宝商的反对下，美国正在重新评估禁止俄罗斯钻石进入七大民主国家集团的最严格内容。【原文：The United States is re-evaluating the strictest elements of a ban on Russian diamonds from the Group of Seven major democracies, after opposition from African countries, Indian gem polishers and New York jewellers, seven sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-lukewarm-g7-russian-diamond-ban-after-industry-backlash-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MJTFE2DTJPLHIYRRF7QDOBDKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：特斯拉董事长认为马斯克薪酬方案获得股东投票面临挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，特斯拉董事会主席表示，该公司需要攀登 "珠穆朗玛峰"，因为它面临着股东对迁往得克萨斯州和首席执行官埃隆-马斯克 560 亿美元薪酬协议的投票。【原文：Tesla's chair of the board said the company needs to climb "Mount Everest" as it faces shareholder votes on relocating to Texas and CEO Elon Musk's $56 billion pay deal, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-chair-sees-challenges-getting-shareholder-vote-musks-pay-package-ft-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EI2ZUUW66JPLZP5MWYNL2VB4HA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:31:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，微软计划通过订阅服务发布下一版《使命召唤]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，微软计划在其订阅服务中发布新一期的《使命召唤》电子游戏，而不是长期以来只采用自选销售的方式。【原文：Microsoft plans to release the coming installment of "Call of Duty" videogame to its subscription service instead of the longtime approach of only selling it à la carte, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-plans-release-next-call-duty-version-subscription-service-wsj-reports-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4P5VZSIF3NL4ZAWPZV26IKGBE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会将暂停审理针对 SpaceX 的案件，等待该公司提出法律挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家劳资关系委员会告诉德克萨斯州的一名联邦法官，将暂停审理指控 SpaceX 非法解雇批评首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的工程师的案件，同时该火箭制造商将继续声称该机构的内部执法程序是非法的。【原文：The U.S. National Labor Relations Board told a Texas federal judge that it will suspend a case accusing SpaceX of illegally firing engineers critical of CEO Elon Musk while the rocket maker pursues claims that the agency's in-house enforcement proceedings are illegal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/us-labor-board-will-suspend-case-against-spacex-pending-companys-legal-challenge-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIYTHLPZNRLHPBSQZGG3YRF74Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金创八周来最大单周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 5 月 15 日的七天内，美国股票基金吸引了大量资金流入，原因是在美国就业数据低迷和通胀数据低于预期的情况下，市场对美联储降息的预期推波助澜。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted significant inflows in the seven days to May 15, fuelled by expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts following subdued U.S. jobs data and a softer-than-anticipated inflation reading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-draw-largest-weekly-inflow-eight-weeks-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTG7RGX5DBIFVPD7FP4HHTGHLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:06:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官认为欧洲因人工智能电力需求而面临 "巨大问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德公司首席执行官周五表示，支持人工智能（AI）技术的数据中心所需的巨大电力供应将造成各国之间的竞争问题，并使欧洲处于不利地位。【原文：The enormous power supply required by data centres to support artificial intelligence (AI) technologies will create competitive issues among countries and put Europe at a disadvantage, the CEO of BlackRock said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/blackrock-ceo-sees-giant-issue-europe-due-ai-power-needs-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZICQKKQ4CNLFPNEWA4YEX63NFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，大众与雷诺结束开发经济型电动汽车的谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，大众汽车已退出与雷诺联合开发经济型电动版 Twingo 汽车的谈判，这使欧盟汽车制造商抵御中国竞争对手的努力遭遇挫折。【原文：Volkswagen has walked away from talks with Renault to jointly develop an affordable electric version of the Twingo car, two sources familiar with the situation said, in a setback for the EU carmakers' efforts to fend off Chinese rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-renault-end-talks-develop-affordable-ev-sources-say-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRILZHGCXVJVLJWEHE65UYMJXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息希望和疲软的美国经济数据吸引全球股票基金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 5 月 15 日的七天里，全球股票基金连续第三周受到强劲需求的推动，原因是美国就业报告疲软，通胀数据低于预期，这增加了人们对美联储可能在今年开始降息的预期。【原文：Global equity funds experienced strong demand for the third consecutive week, in the seven days to May 15, bolstered by a softer U.S. jobs report and lower-than-expected inflation figures, which increased expectations that the Federal Reserve may begin cutting rates this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IREWT4SOMFLG7AIHIAB6C2PTUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 预计第一季度收入下降，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 预计第一季度的净销售额将比去年同期有所下降，原因是顾客转向在网上购买视频游戏和收藏品，而该零售商主要依靠实体店。【原文：GameStop expects first-quarter net sales to drop from a year ago, as customers transition to buying video games and collectibles online, while the retailer largely relies on brick and mortar stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestop-expects-first-quarter-revenue-drop-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPSPGD7HI5JUFI7YM32M6HF7H4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与 OpenAI 合作后 Reddit 股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit 与人工智能公司 OpenAI 建立合作关系后，其股价周五上涨了 14%，该合作有望通过人工智能增强的体验为社交媒体平台吸引更多用户，并吸引更多广告收入。【原文：Shares of Reddit rose 14% on Friday, following a partnership with artificial intelligence firm OpenAI that is expected to draw in more users for the social media platform with AI-enhanced experience and attract more advertising revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/reddit-stock-jumps-after-openai-partnership-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JCK7EVDR5NWFOLG3XGTBMXAPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国道指逼近 4 万点，中国抗击住宅市场萧条]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFR5IQTCW5MFJITE4I74HJMZ6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:11:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢比走软可能无法阻止加拿大央行与美联储的分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项草根民意调查显示，七位分析师的估计中值显示，在货币下跌威胁到通胀前景之前，加拿大央行愿意在美联储首次降息之前降息三次。【原文：The Bank of Canada would be willing to cut interest rates three times ahead of the Federal Reserve's first move before a declining currency threatens to endanger the inflation outlook, the median estimate of seven analysts in a straw poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/weaker-loonie-may-not-deter-bank-canada-diverging-fed-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKMTNST225MPJBYVPR4RQCZUVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Endeavor 130 亿美元交易凸显避开少数股东的推动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[Endeavor 集团决定不让小股东否决将这家娱乐集团私有化的 130 亿美元交易，这是公司控股投资者为避免支付更高的交易价格而冒险提起诉讼的最新例子。【原文：Endeavor Group's decision to deny minority shareholders the ability to veto a $13 billion deal to take the entertainment conglomerate private is the latest example of a company's controlling investors risking lawsuits to avoid paying a higher deal price.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/endeavors-13-billion-deal-highlights-push-sidestep-minority-shareholders-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAI7DXJ545IBDD74IG3WZ3SYA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管消费者监督机构在美国最高法院胜诉，但该机构的权力仍在砧板上]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院保护消费者金融保护局--美国消费者金融监督机构--的裁决赢得了强有力的联邦监管支持者的赞誉。但他们对法院的赞誉可能是短暂的。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court's decision safeguarding the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau - the nation's consumer finance watchdog - earned plaudits from supporters of robust federal regulation. But their praise for the court may prove short-lived.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/despite-consumer-watchdogs-us-supreme-court-win-agency-powers-still-chopping-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDUF3A7DHBNJLC7CWJSOLGKROQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:03:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易回暖，高盛寻求扩大私募股权投资信贷额度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国投资银行高盛（Goldman Sachs）正大举进军私募股权和资产管理公司的贷款市场，计划进行海外扩张，帮助填补地区性银行动荡和瑞士信贷（Credit Suisse）出售后留下的空白。【原文：U.S. investment bank Goldman Sachs is muscling into the lending market for private equity and asset managers, planning an overseas expansion as it helps fill a void left by turmoil at regional banks and the sale of Credit Suisse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-looks-expand-private-equity-credit-lines-dealmaking-picks-up-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEGVX4FIGBNI7JPXW3R3YXKM6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港允许在本地商店使用中国数字人民币]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港事实上的中央银行负责人周五表示，香港将允许中国大陆的试点数字货币在香港的商店中使用，这标志着在地缘政治紧张局势不断加剧的情况下，中国政府将人民币国际化的努力又向前迈进了一步。【原文：Hong Kong will allow mainland China's pilot digital currency to be used in shops in the city, the head of its de facto central bank said on Friday, marking a step forward for Beijing's efforts to internationalise the yuan amid rising geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/hong-kong-allows-chinas-digital-yuan-be-used-local-shops-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNJIEYF77NIJVHTXOQLFVNFR5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 09:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通称，必和必拓需要以每股约 32 英镑的价格收购盎格鲁集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通分析师在一份报告中说，必和必拓集团需要将其最新报价提高约30%，以反映英美资源集团及其主要铜资产的公允价值。【原文：BHP Group would need to boost its latest offer around 30% to reflect fair value for Anglo American and its key copper assets, JPMorgan analysts said in a note.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bhp-needs-bid-about-32-pounds-share-anglo-jpmorgan-says-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GHH54DUS4BOBFPNRCJVDV2LTPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 09:46:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期货走低，反弹势头有所减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货下滑，在消费者通胀数据不及预期、美联储降息希望的支撑下，华尔街一周的大幅上涨接近尾声。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Friday, near the end of a week of sharp Wall Street gains underpinned by hopes of Federal Reserve interest rate cuts after softer-than-expected consumer inflation data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-lower-rally-loses-some-steam-2024-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYZUDF55CNODRPIVSVJ4IXSPQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 09:29:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>