<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:11:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:11:11 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称从未向摩根大通的戴蒙提供美联储主席职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周六表示，他从未提议提名摩根大通首席执行官杰米·戴蒙担任美联储主席一职，这与本周的一份报道相矛盾。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Saturday said he never offered to nominate JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon for the job of Federal Reserve chair, contradicting a report this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-he-never-offered-fed-chair-job-jpmorgans-dimon-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LKKN2XPEVKJLBHH5MEOS37J44</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普誓言对八个欧洲国家征收关税以示对格陵兰岛的立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周六誓言，将在欧洲盟国对美国实施关税升级浪潮直至美国获准购买格陵兰岛，此举加剧了围绕这座丹麦广袤北极岛屿未来归属的争端。【原文：President Donald Trump on Saturday vowed to implement a wave of increasing tariffs on European allies until the United States is allowed to buy Greenland, escalating a row over the future of Denmark's vast Arctic island.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-vows-tariffs-eight-european-nations-over-greenland-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RFQ6EYQ7SFNY3GPVXSRL43CLAU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院就美联储委员丽莎·库克任命案展开角逐，测试特朗普经济权力的边界]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，在唐纳德·特朗普总统第二任期开始四个月后，美国最高法院就表明了其意图保护美联储免受政治干预的立场。本周三，当大法官们审议特朗普解雇美联储理事丽莎·库克的合法性时，他们维护美国央行独立性的决心将面临考验。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court signaled four months into Donald Trump's second presidential term last year its interest in shielding the Federal Reserve from political interference. When the justices on Wednesday consider the legality of his bid to fire Fed Governor Lisa Cook, their willingness to preserve the U.S. central bank's independence will be ​put to the test.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/supreme-court-tests-limits-trumps-power-over-economy-fight-over-feds-lisa-cook-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K36EAWN3AFNNLI5AI6WRR42KQ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国首席执行官们对特朗普的政策提出温和反对]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国商会首席执行官苏珊娜·克拉克于昏暗的宴会厅发表演讲时，她呼吁企业高管在捍卫自由市场对抗政府管控时"无所畏惧"，并强调美国必须保持"对世界的开放，对全球人才、商品、思想和创新的开放"。【原文：Speaking before a darkened ballroom on Thursday, U.S. Chamber of Commerce CEO Suzanne Clark called on executives to be "fearless" in defense of free markets over government control and said the U.S. must remain "open to the world, open to the global exchange of talent and goods and ideas and innovation."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/american-ceos-push-back-trump-mildly-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLNDXE7SGNKC7MSJ7AQY3V6ISY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克要求OpenAI和微软归还高达1340亿美元的"不当得利"]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的法庭文件显示，埃隆·马斯克正向OpenAI和微软索赔高达1340亿美元，他主张自己有权获得这两家公司因其早期支持人工智能初创企业而获得的"不当得利"。【原文：Elon Musk is seeking up to $134 billion from OpenAI and Microsoft , arguing he deserves the "wrongful gains" that they received from his early support of the artificial-intelligence startup, according to a court filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musk-seeks-up-134-billion-openai-microsoft-wrongful-gains-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JO4CNN6IHNJATCSU6D4HXCFEMA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道称欧盟将禁止中国供应商进入关键基础设施领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周六报道，欧盟正着手逐步淘汰该地区关键基础设施中的中国制造设备，禁止华为、中兴等公司进入电信网络、太阳能系统和安检扫描仪领域。【原文：The European Union is moving to phase out Chinese‑made equipment from the zone's critical infrastructure, barring companies such as Huawei and ZTE from telecom networks, solar systems and security scanners, the Financial Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-bar-chinese-suppliers-critical-infrastructure-ft-reports-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OEF7ZZ64ZKQJO733PV2PSBMCY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 05:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国称美国芯片关税短期影响有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国产业通商资源部长官周六表示，美国宣布对特定先进计算芯片征收25%关税的决定，对韩国企业影响有限。【原文：South Korea's trade minister said on Saturday that a U.S. proclamation imposing a 25% tariff on certain advanced computing chips would have a limited impact on South Korean companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-says-us-chip-tariff-have-limited-immediate-impact-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P34VGHCFS5JKJMYINMSZITMFEM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 05:18:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普购入价值1亿美元债券，包括奈飞和华纳兄弟债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普最新披露的文件显示，他在11月中旬至12月下旬期间购入了价值约1亿美元的市政债券和公司债券，其中包括在奈飞公司与华纳兄弟探索公司宣布合并仅数周后，就购入了高达200万美元的两家公司债券。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump purchased about $100 million in municipal and corporate bonds from mid-November to late December, his latest disclosures showed, including up to $2 million in Netflix and Warner Bros Discovery bonds just weeks after the companies announced their merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-warner-bros-bonds-among-100-million-purchased-by-trump-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RERBHFNA6RI7XBQMRNOVYOP75I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:51:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《金融时报》报道，中国禁止出口后，英伟达H200芯片零部件供应商已暂停生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周五报道，在海关官员阻止新获批的人工智能处理器进入中国后，英伟达H200芯片的零部件供应商已暂停生产。【原文：Suppliers of parts for Nvidia's H200 have paused production after Chinese customs officials blocked shipments of the newly approved artificial intelligence processors from entering China, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-suppliers-halt-h200-output-after-china-blocks-chip-shipments-ft-reports-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZXC7TZT4BPB5DR62SKZRNNFZQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:42:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街银行面临考验：特朗普呼吁限制信用卡利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国多家银行周二面临棘手的政治考验：如何回应特朗普总统限制信用卡利率的要求。据多位行业人士透露，金融界正为此措手不及，不知如何应对。【原文：U.S. banks on Tuesday face a tricky political test in how to address a call from President Donald Trump to cap credit card interest rates - leaving the ​finance industry scrambling on how to proceed, according to several industry sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/wall-street-banks-face-test-with-trumps-call-credit-card-rate-cap-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOXN6KDZG5OUXD5SGETBBBMLWU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:40:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球体育赛事面临"AI垃圾信息"的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能风险管理平台Alethea针对人工智能生成虚假内容激增现象（被称为"AI垃圾内容"）的研究警告称，日益复杂的数字虚假信息正对体育团队、联赛及球迷构成风险。【原文：A study by AI risk management platform Alethea into the surge in artificial intelligence-generated fake content, dubbed "AI slop," has warned sports teams, leagues and fans of the risks posed by increasingly sophisticated digital misinformation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/global-sports-face-challenges-ai-slop-misinformation-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMMFZGZYHBOSLE7ABXASUPYLO4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，美国正考虑采取行政措施限制信用卡利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周五报道，白宫正考虑采取行政措施，以落实美国总统唐纳德·特朗普关于限制信用卡利率的呼吁。该报道援引知情人士消息称。【原文：The White House is weighing an executive action to enact U.S. President Donald Trump’s call for a cap on credit card interest rates, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-weighs-executive-action-cap-credit-card-rates-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNFVJKSSPZOGTFXIYTOO77FOI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铁路监管机构称联合太平洋与诺福克南方合并申请材料不完整]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国地面运输委员会周五将联合太平洋公司与诺福克南方公司850亿美元合并提案退回要求修订，称其缺少必要信息。此次审查中，美国运输监管机构将根据2001年出台的更严格合并规则，界定"增强竞争"的具体含义。【原文：The U.S. Surface Transportation Board on Friday sent back Union Pacific’s proposed $85 billion merger with Norfolk Southern for revision, saying it lacked required information, as part of a review in which the U.S. transport regulator will define what enhanced competition means under tougher merger rules adopted in 2001.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-rail-regulator-says-union-pacific-norfolk-southern-merger-filing-incomplete-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4LWXFDTPRIXVDXZ7TI6N4XDNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的杰斐逊表示，他认为鲍威尔是"最高尚正直的人"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会副主席菲利普·杰斐逊周五回应司法部对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的传票时表示，他认为鲍威尔"具有最高尚的诚信品质"。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson, responding to the Department of Justice subpoena of Fed Chair ​Jerome Powell, said on Friday he considered Powell to be "of the ‌highest integrity."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-jefferson-says-he-considers-powell-be-of-highest-integrity-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YYTEVZPFFPWHLTF4UIVMC5JVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：美国正加速扩大雪佛龙在委内瑞拉的开采许可，能源部长赖特向路透社透露]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯·赖特周五向路透社表示，美国正全力加速推进为雪佛龙公司在委内瑞拉的石油生产项目颁发扩容许可证。【原文：The U.S. is moving as fast as it can to grant Chevron an expanded license for its oil production in Venezuela, U.S. Energy Secretary Chris Wright told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-moving-fast-expand-chevrons-venezuela-license-energy-secretary-wright-tells-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WH4FKSDSTFPG5ABMR4WM4RA5YA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州总检察长就深度伪造图像问题向xAI公司发出停止令]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州总检察长罗伯·邦塔周五向埃隆·马斯克的xAI公司发出停止令，要求其立即停止生成和传播未经同意的性影像。【原文：California's attorney general, Rob Bonta, on Friday sent a cease and desist letter to Elon Musk's xAI, demanding that it stop the generation and distribution of non-consensual sexual images.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/california-ag-sends-cease-desist-letter-xai-deepfake-images-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYHXFSNQZNOHPLDWO46MY6KPDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:37:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌请求美国法官推迟强制其共享数据的命令，以便进行上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[据法庭文件显示，谷歌母公司Alphabet周五请求法官推迟要求该公司向竞争对手共享数据的裁决，同时该公司正就一项认定其在在线搜索领域非法垄断的裁决提出上诉。【原文：Alphabet's Google asked a judge on Friday to postpone making the company share data with rivals while it challenges a ruling that the company holds an illegal monopoly in online search, according to court papers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-asks-us-judge-defer-order-forcing-it-share-data-while-it-appeals-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCI6KFEGGZPJBD3EOQYIFSLME4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州总检察长致函要求xAI停止生产深度伪造内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州总检察长罗伯特·邦塔周五向xAI公司发出停止令，要求该公司立即停止其Grok人工智能聊天机器人生成并传播未经同意的性化图像的行为。【原文：California Attorney General Robert Bonta on Friday sent a cease and desist letter to xAI demanding the company stop the creation and distribution of AI-generated non-consensual sexualized imagery by its Grok AI chatbot.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/california-ag-sends-letter-demanding-xai-stop-producing-deekfake-content-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBZFG6QFEVOURFR7QKH652BFZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:07:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020年美联储面临疫情冲击时，部门分歧与决策独立性成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在新冠疫情暴发之初，美国联邦储备委员会大幅降息并实施大规模债券购买计划，向金融市场注入流动性，试图抵消这场公共卫生危机对经济造成的实际和潜在破坏。【原文：At the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, the U.S. Federal Reserve slashed interest rates and used massive bond purchases to flood financial markets with liquidity to try to offset the actual and potential economic devastation from the health emergency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-2020-division-independence-were-concerns-face-pandemic-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4WZ6EURWJPY5NJYXPP5KXJSJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会将审查科技巨头的人才收购交易，彭博社报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周五援引美国联邦贸易委员会主席安德鲁·弗格森的话报道称，该机构正密切关注大型科技公司通过招聘初创企业员工而非直接收购公司来获取人才的行为。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is scrutinizing big tech firms that hire employees of a startup instead of buying the companies outright, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing the agency's Chairman Andrew Ferguson.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-ftc-scrutinize-big-techs-talent-acquisition-deals-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3UX37DJFBIRHGPUESX7U2PV3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:52:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰斐逊称当前政策立场"定位良好"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储副主席菲利普·杰斐逊周五似乎暗示，他支持在1月27日至28日的央行会议上维持短期借贷成本不变。他表示，鉴于美联储降息已使货币政策处于中性区间，他对未来一年的经济、劳动力市场和通胀持"谨慎乐观"态度。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson on Friday appeared to signal his support for leaving short-term borrowing costs unchanged at the central bank's January 27-28 ​meeting, saying he is "cautiously optimistic" about the economy, the labor market and inflation ‌in the coming year now that the Fed's rate cuts have put monetary policy in the range of neutral.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-jefferson-says-current-policy-stance-well-positioned-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLAA5U2IJRLOPK4LU2EYZGIYWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称巴西对Banco Master的调查可能长达六个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西联邦检察官预计将耗时四至六个月分析近期针对破产贷款机构Banco Master展开的调查行动所收集的证据，检察总长办公室一位知情人士周五透露。【原文：Brazil's federal prosecutors will likely take four to six months analyzing evidence gathered in the latest operation probing liquidated ​lender Banco Master, a person in the prosecutor general's office ‌with knowledge of the case said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/banco-master-probe-brazil-may-take-up-six-months-source-says-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHCPQCCC3VKF7EUL7UGHWTV4HE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:10:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫寻求为美国最大电网举行紧急电力拍卖]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周五敦促美国最大的电网系统启动紧急电力拍卖，以防范大面积轮流停电。由于数据中心对能源的需求增长速度超过了美国新建发电厂的能力，当前电力供应面临严峻挑战。【原文：The White House on Friday urged the largest U.S. electric grid to conduct an emergency power auction to protect against rolling blackouts as energy demand from data centers grows faster than the country can build new generation plants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/white-house-seeks-emergency-power-auction-largest-us-electric-grid-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KQEUTDTMZNKZPENXXDJ3SKOCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，委内瑞拉银行将获得3亿美元石油资金用于外汇市场交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，委内瑞拉政府通知该国四家银行，将分配存放在卡塔尔账户中的3亿美元石油收入，使这些银行能够向需要外汇支付材料费的委内瑞拉公司出售美元。两名金融消息人士和一名分析师透露了这一消息。【原文：Four Venezuelan banks were notified this week by the ​country's government that they will split $300 million of oil revenues deposited in an account in ‌Qatar, enabling them to sell dollars to Venezuelan companies that need foreign exchange to pay for materials, two financial sources and an analyst said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuelan-banks-will-get-300-million-oil-money-sell-exchange-market-sources-say-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJ7T6XNHYBJLVJYTVGRXUCN4XE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称壳牌、三菱正探讨出售其在LNG Canada股权的方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，石油巨头壳牌和日本综合企业三菱商事正就其在价值400亿加元（288亿美元）的加拿大液化天然气项目中的持股进行出售方案的探讨。【原文：Oil major Shell and Japanese conglomerate Mitsubishi Corp are exploring sale options for their respective stakes in the C$40 billion ($28.8 billion) LNG Canada project, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-mitsubishi-exploring-sale-options-their-stakes-lng-canada-sources-say-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPSFCPPZE5LHTHIIX7RQZQGFKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:30:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克与瑞安航空CEO就飞机上星链Wi-Fi费用问题发生争执]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克周五称瑞安航空首席执行官迈克尔·奥利里是"彻头彻尾的蠢货"，理应被解雇。此前这位航空公司老板拒绝在瑞安航空飞机上安装马斯克的星链互联网服务，由此引发的公开争执进一步升级。【原文：Elon Musk on Friday called Ryanair CEO Michael O'Leary an "utter idiot" who should be fired, escalating a public spat that began after the airline boss ruled out installing Musk's Starlink internet service on Ryanair aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/musk-ryanair-ceo-clash-over-cost-starlink-wi-fi-planes-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYCUFXKWDNIHBONFJEVTKVEVWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:41:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际石油公司敦促委内瑞拉加快改革步伐，以期掌控该国石油出口权。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据参与谈判的消息人士透露，国际石油公司的高管和律师正游说美国和委内瑞拉政府，要求修改这个欧佩克成员国的碳氢化合物法律，使他们有权自由出口在委内瑞拉生产的石油。【原文：Oil executives and lawyers for international oil companies are lobbying the U.S. and Venezuelan governments for changes in the OPEC member's hydrocarbon law that would give them the right to freely export the oil they produce in Venezuela, sources involved in the talks said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/international-oil-companies-push-quick-reforms-venezuela-give-them-control-over-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USC2K7SWGZP5HNNIHQQTYTMB3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI将开始在ChatGPT的免费和Go版本中测试广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI周五表示，计划在其聊天机器人ChatGPT的免费版和Go版中开始测试广告功能。【原文：OpenAI said on Friday it plans to start testing ads in its chatbot ChatGPT's free and Go tiers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-begin-testing-ads-chatgpts-free-go-tiers-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O446QTEKNZMVLJRXDC4BSJMGHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称美国正探讨以委内瑞拉重质原油换取美国中质原油的计划，以补充战略储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两名消息人士周五透露，美国能源部正探讨一项计划，拟用委内瑞拉重质原油交换美国中质酸性原油，以补充战略石油储备。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy is exploring a plan to exchange heavy Venezuelan oil for U.S. medium, sour crude to fill up the Strategic Petroleum Reserve, two sources said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-explores-plan-swap-heavy-venezuelan-oil-us-medium-crude-fill-emergency-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UL3MIDM5CBP7PNH2OKYH42C7C4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:15:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西捷航空因乘客强烈反对将取消不可调节靠背的经济舱座椅]]></title><description><![CDATA[西捷航空周五宣布，将在部分波音737客机上取消不可调节的经济舱座椅。此前社交媒体上涌现大量投诉和视频，显示旅客膝盖紧贴前排座椅。【原文：WestJet Airlines said on Friday it will scrap non-reclinable economy seating on certain Boeing 737 jets, following a slew of complaints and videos on social media showing travelers' knees pressed up against the seats ahead of them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/westjet-reverses-course-non-adjustable-economy-seats-following-backlash-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4G6NUYQFMZO6TGW7USEXJDIUCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:09:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>