<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:04:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:04:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[高盛退出全球银行气候联盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）表示，它已经退出了一个旨在使银行贷款和投资活动与全球应对气候变化的努力保持一致的行业联盟，这是美国金融公司最近一次高调退出该组织。【原文：Goldman Sachs said it has quit a sector coalition aimed at aligning bank lending and investment activities with global efforts to fight climate change, marking the latest high-profile departure of a U.S. financial firm from the group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/goldman-sachs-quits-global-climate-coalition-banks-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOGEEQZ6UBPPTEKVXLWBFGCJ6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 14:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称育碧股东正就可能的收购条款进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，育碧娱乐公司（Ubisoft Entertainment SA）的股东正在考虑如何在不削弱创始家族控制权的情况下，安排对这家《刺客信条》视频游戏制造商的可能收购。【原文：Shareholders of Ubisoft Entertainment SA are considering how to structure a possible buyout of the Assassin's Creed video game maker without reducing the founding family's control, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/ubisoft-shareholders-talks-over-possible-buyout-terms-sources-say-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RG62WWD2WJJWTN3AI6N74EDJPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 14:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月就业人数显示就业增长在 10 月小幅下滑后有所加快]]></title><description><![CDATA[在受到飓风和罢工的严重制约之后，美国 11 月份的就业增长猛增，但这可能并不意味着劳动力市场状况发生了实质性转变，劳动力市场状况继续稳步放宽，并为美联储本月再次降息提供了余地。【原文：U.S. job growth surged in November after being severely constrained by hurricanes and strikes, but probably does not signal a material shift in labor market conditions that continue to ease steadily and gives the Federal Reserve leeway to cut interest rates again this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-nov-payrolls-show-job-growth-accelerated-after-october-hiccup-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42O3ELLMC5JILIUFMFTG6PE64I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月就业增长加速；失业率升至 4.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国的就业增长在受到飓风和罢工的严重制约后，于11月出现了猛增，但这可能并不意味着劳动力市场状况发生了实质性转变，劳动力市场继续稳步放宽，并允许美联储在本月再次降息。【原文：U.S. job growth surged in November after being severely constrained by hurricanes and strikes, but this probably does not signal a material shift in labor market conditions that continue to ease steadily and allows the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates again this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-job-growth-accelerates-november-unemployment-rate-rises-42-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6UJU4Z2UJN2ZMPCRLGFJXPDTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 11 月失业率跃升至 6.8%，创近 8 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，尽管加拿大经济净增了50,500个就业岗位，但11月份加拿大失业率仍超乎预期地升至6.8%，创下除大流行病时期外的近八年新高，这可能会增加下周大幅降息的可能性。【原文：Canada's unemployment rate rose more than expected to 6.8% in November, a near-eight-year high excluding the pandemic years, even as the economy added a net 50,500 jobs, data showed on Friday, likely boosting chances of a large interest rate cut next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadas-jobless-rate-jumps-near-8-year-high-68-november-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NT7SFG62GJIKFHUCYGBUV4Z6YM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：OpenAI 寻求通过放弃与微软的 "AGI "条款来释放投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，OpenAI 正在讨论放弃一项规定，即当这家初创公司实现 "人工通用智能 "时，微软将被排除在其最先进的模型之外，因为该公司正寻求获得数十亿美元的未来投资。【原文：OpenAI is in discussions to ditch a provision that shuts Microsoft out of its most advanced models when the start-up achieves "artificial general intelligence", as it seeks to unlock billions of dollars of future investment, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-seeks-unlock-investment-by-ditching-agi-clause-with-microsoft-ft-reports-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHH7AVKCY5IEJBF4NDXE5ZP3VQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:47:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称英伟达的商业行为成为欧盟反垄断关注的焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接知情人士透露，欧盟反垄断监管机构正在询问英伟达的竞争对手和客户，这家美国人工智能芯片制造商捆绑其产品是否会给自己带来不公平的优势，此举可能会导致正式调查。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are asking Nvidia rivals and customers if the U.S. artificial intelligence chipmaker bundles its products that may give it an unfair advantage, people with direct knowledge of the matter said, in a move that may lead to a formal investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidias-business-practices-eu-antitrust-spotlight-sources-say-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYBZLEJAHVKHNJJ4TW6GJV5N2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普京颁布天然气支付令后，卢布对美元汇率反弹突破 100]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔-普京颁布了一项法令，为俄罗斯天然气的欧洲买家提供了新的支付选择，从而使外汇流动得以恢复，此后俄罗斯卢布兑美元汇率反弹突破 100，周五报 99.50。【原文：The Russian rouble rebounded past 100 to the U.S. dollar, trading at 99.50 on Friday, after a decree by President Vladimir Putin which opened new payment options for European buyers of Russian gas, allowing foreign currency flows to resume.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/rouble-rebounds-past-100-vs-us-dollar-after-putins-gas-payments-decree-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IKPVM3TAJNK7K3DHFAFKMQ64U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:39:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称英国石油公司为美国天然气管道系统股份寻找买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位知情人士透露，英国石油公司（BP）正在为其美国天然气管道网络的股份寻找买家。【原文：BP is seeking buyers for a stake in its U.S. natural gas pipeline network, four people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bp-seeks-buyers-us-natural-gas-pipeline-system-stake-sources-say-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWWNC4BDRFLYFGBJLJXUU2XFUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:56:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WH 集团获股东批准分拆史密斯菲尔德食品公司并在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部设在香港的世界最大猪肉生产商 WH 集团周五表示，其股东已批准将史密斯菲尔德食品公司分拆为一家美国上市公司。【原文：Hong Kong-based WH Group , the world's largest pork producer, said on Friday that its shareholders had approved spinning off Smithfield Foods into a listed company in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/wh-group-get-shareholders-nod-spin-off-list-smithfield-foods-us-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDOMPWLMNVIT7OZJKB4FPNDWIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经济增长乐观，美国股票基金连续第五周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月4日，美国投资者连续第五周抢购股票基金，原因是华尔街主要股指反弹、对经济强劲增长的乐观情绪以及对美联储本月连续第三次降息的预期。【原文：U.S. investors snapped up equity funds for a fifth successive week through Nov. 4, motivated by a rally in Wall Street's main indexes, optimism for strong economic growth, and expectations of a third consecutive Federal Reserve rate cut this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-attract-inflows-fifth-straight-week-growth-optimism-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GPRKHKEKFLN3EXQF22S2QJFXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:22:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息称瓦罗能源公司正在洽谈收购 Preem 在瑞典的炼油厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位业内消息人士告诉路透社，欧洲能源公司 Varo Energy 正在洽谈收购 Preem 在瑞典的两家炼油厂，押注于日益增长的低碳生物燃料需求。【原文：European energy firm Varo Energy is in talks to acquire Preem's two Swedish refineries in a bet on growing demand for low-carbon biofuels, four industry sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/varo-energy-talks-buy-preems-swedish-refineries-sources-say-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODEKJ2PNYNNJBBWJO5RD6D5YNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间交易长债收益率在非农数据公布前回落，法国反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJV5VCRQNVOBJDJDW5B2NLBNAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的 NASA人选是 SpaceX 的福音，但将面临政治挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[贾里德-艾萨克曼（Jared Isaacman）是航天工业中以商业为核心的快速发展的核心人物。【原文：Jared Isaacman is a central figure of a speedy, commercial-focused side of the space industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-nasa-pick-boon-spacex-will-face-political-challenges-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJ75TMLFKJKNLLQTSJJ3I5MYLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储发言人最后名单应在会前封锁开始前公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会官员在 12 月 17 日至 18 日的会议前将进入平静期，预计新的就业数据将从 10 月份的疲软读数中反弹，而且官员们越来越感觉到劳动力市场仍处于稳健状态。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve officials head into the quiet period ahead of their Dec. 17-18 meeting with new jobs numbers expected to show a rebound from the weak reading in October and a growing sense among officials that the labor market remains in solid shape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/final-slate-fed-speakers-due-before-pre-meeting-blackout-begins-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LRFFLBJCN5MUZNURY3WCP2UVSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 因液压控制问题召回 30 多万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构周五表示，由于液压控制单元存在问题，可能导致包括防抱死制动器在内的系统失灵，Stellantis公司将在美国召回317630辆汽车。【原文：Stellantis is recalling 317,630 vehicles in the U.S. due to a problem with the hydraulic control unit that may cause systems including the anti-lock brake to fail, the U.S. auto safety regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-recalls-over-300000-us-vehicles-due-issues-with-hydraulic-control-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUWJ5S5FKRK5DCDC5NFLMDCWJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受中国影响，西方国家争相调整关键矿产供应链]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国对战略矿产的贸易限制开始对西方公司造成冲击。【原文：China's trade restrictions on strategic minerals are starting to hit Western companies where it hurts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/rattled-by-china-west-scrambles-rejig-critical-minerals-supply-chains-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LPBWZ5A35LMVPSNUWWXT7T6CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场等待 11 月就业数据，期货价格持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，与华尔街主要股指挂钩的期货基本持平，投资者在月度就业报告公布前保持谨慎，该报告预计将成为评估美联储利率走势的关键。【原文：Futures linked to Wall Street's main indexes were largely flat on Friday, with investors cautious ahead of a monthly jobs report expected to be key in assessing the Federal Reserve's interest-rate trajectory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-steady-markets-await-november-jobs-data-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXUSJYVNPZNI7PRW5HPQGAL5NM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注经济增长，无视政治动荡，全球股票基金资金流入强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至12月4日的一周内，尽管法国和韩国政局动荡，但在美国经济增长前景强劲和科技股乐观情绪的推动下，全球股票基金的资金流入显著增加。【原文：Global equity funds saw a notable rise in inflows in the week through Dec. 4, driven by a record-setting rally fueled by strong U.S. economic growth prospects and optimism about tech stocks, despite political turmoil in France and South Korea.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKU7HJKY4VPY5B5BYCTOO6C5MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，欧元区第三季度生产率增长依然疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟统计局（Eurostat）周五公布的数据显示，尽管欧元区经济略有增长，但第三季度生产率增长依然疲软，延续了多年来的低迷状态。【原文：Euro zone productivity growth remained weak in the third quarter despite a modest expansion in the bloc's economy, continuing a poor run that has lasted years, data from Eurostat showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-productivity-growth-remains-weak-q3-data-shows-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6V4LPHMYUZN37CZ7SGULHLNM7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 高管被枪杀两天后，警方在纽约全力搜捕嫌犯]]></title><description><![CDATA[在掌握了越来越多的线索后，纽约警方请求公众帮助他们寻找蒙面袭击者。【原文：Armed with a growing file of clues, New York police were asking the public for help in their search for the masked assailant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/police-scour-new-york-suspect-two-days-after-unitedhealth-executive-gunned-down-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MO2732ZNDJOPTIKAAQKVJYDHLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行称，现金流入创 2023 年 3 月以来最大单周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国银行周五发布的一份报告显示，截至本周三的一周内，投资者投入了1,364亿美元现金，这是自2023年3月以来最大的单周流入量，当时市场受到地区银行业危机的冲击。【原文：Investors ploughed $136.4 billion into cash in the week to Wednesday, the biggest weekly inflow since March 2023, when markets were rattled by a regional banking crisis, according to a report from Bank of America on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-bofa-urgent-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYHLL7BWLNLXDBEFNYLBNBHKAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司 11 月交付 84 架飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[在经历了夏季的低迷之后，空中客车公司在 11 月份交付了 84 架飞机，朝着年底目标又迈进了一步。【原文：Airbus delivered 84 planes in November as the planemaker moved back towards end-year targets after a downturn over the summer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-delivers-84-planes-november-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCGQDBX4YFNA3KPT226I2ZDMTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 07:54:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[天然气价格冲击将加剧欧洲工业的痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着寒冷天气消耗掉库存，与亚洲争夺液化天然气的竞争加剧，以及俄罗斯供应减少的前景日益逼近，欧洲陷入困境的工业正准备在即将到来的冬季迎接新一轮天然气价格冲击。【原文：Europe's struggling industries are bracing for a new gas price shock over the coming winter months, as colder weather depletes stocks, competition with Asia for liquefied natural gas intensifies, and the prospect of reduced Russian supplies looms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/gas-price-shock-set-add-europes-industrial-pain-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAHXV3BJEJNR7O5NLIMAFPAYZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 07:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holcim 计划分拆美国公司在瑞士上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士建材生产商 Holcim 周五表示，明年将北美业务分拆给股东时，除计划在纽约上市外，还将在瑞士证券交易所上市。【原文：Holcim will list shares in its North American business on the SIX Swiss stock exchange in addition to the planned New York flotation when it is spun off to shareholders next year, the Swiss building materials maker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/holcim-plans-us-spin-off-have-swiss-listing-too-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RQHUJJT3NBLP5IWNHIZEOX3ZXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 06:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普推动交易反弹，投行看好 2025 年收入热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的数据显示，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫将推动交易复兴，明年全球投资银行业务收入将增至3160亿美元，比2024年增长约5.7%。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's return to the White House is seen fuelling a dealmaking revival that could bolster investment banking income to $316 billion globally next year, a jump of about 5.7% on 2024, data seen by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investment-banks-eye-2025-income-boom-trump-drives-deal-rebound-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NW5DMS5QWNJQHHCEPSXSJEGWKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 06:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价风险警惕的市场倒计时招聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEOF2FYYGBLXRNCJTXTMXCXPQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，英国雷诺兹称与美国的平衡贸易降低了特朗普征收关税的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引英国商业部长乔纳森-雷诺兹（Jonathan Reynolds）的话报道称，英国与美国的平衡贸易应能降低美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对英国产品征收关税的风险。【原文：Britain's balanced trade with the U.S. should reduce the risk of tariffs that President-elect Donald Trump will introduce on its products, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing the country's business minister Jonathan Reynolds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uks-reynolds-says-balanced-trade-with-us-reduces-risk-trump-tariffs-ft-reports-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMVEVTMNQJLN7KN3P6AVW2CE4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在韩国的危机手册中，货币稳定至关重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[在韩国总统尹锡烈于周二晚宣布戒严令，使韩国陷入数十年来最严重的危机后几分钟，他的财政部长就惊呆了，他知道自己的首要任务是：全力以赴捍卫货币。【原文：Minutes after South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol declared martial law on Tuesday night, plunging the country into its worst crisis in decades, his stunned finance minister knew his priorities: throw everything at defending the currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/south-koreas-crisis-playbook-currency-stability-is-paramount-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNMHLI4ZJRLJNBSGXV5QA5GWSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:18:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[压力重重欧洲央行的五个问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着通胀率走低，欧洲央行下周似乎将再次降息，而金融市场则希望了解，更具挑战性的环境是否会加快降息步伐。【原文：The European Central Bank looks set to cut rates again next week as inflation heads down, and financial markets are keen for a sense of whether a more challenging environment will spark speedier moves ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/pressures-five-questions-ecb-2024-12-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LE4DLUZA2ZPCHOIQI67B775IVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>