<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:05:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:05:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[自由港麦克莫兰公司有望从特朗普的铜关税中获益，而同行的选择不多]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果唐纳德-特朗普总统的铜关税政策得以实现，自由港麦克莫兰公司（Freeport-McMoRan）的年利润将增加 16 亿美元。【原文：Freeport-McMoRan could see a $1.6-billion boost to annual profit if President Donald Trump's copper tariff materializes, a benefit driven by the firm's role as the largest U.S. producer with more expansion options than rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/land-use-biodiversity/freeport-mcmoran-poised-gain-trumps-copper-tariff-against-peers-with-few-options-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHNNG4RQRRN5RPBPEBAPQHJCSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:54:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月预算数据显示特朗普关税征收额有望增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五将在其六月份的预算数据中披露唐纳德-特朗普总统关税收入的力度，因为多波新进口关税的征收开始成为政府的一个重要收入来源。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department on Friday will reveal the strength of President Donald Trump's tariff revenues in its June budget data, as collections from multiple waves of new import duties start to build into a substantial government revenue source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-tariff-collections-expected-grow-june-us-budget-data-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F76N32NP3ZK57AMXJLUNULQNJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资者回避气候和社会改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[晨星公司（Morningstar）的数据显示，在截至 6 月 30 日的 12 个月里，要求美国公司进行环境和社会改革的股东决议的支持率平均下降到 16%，只有三年前的一半。【原文：Support for shareholder resolutions pressing U.S. companies for environmental and social reforms fell to 16% on average for the 12 months ended June 30, half the rate of three years ago, data from Morningstar shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-investors-back-away-climate-social-reforms-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H772EZPHZZNMZNG22QJR26PM7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国月神人工智能公司发布开源模型，以夺回市场地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创企业月神人工智能公司（Moonshot AI）周五发布了一个新的开源人工智能模型，加入了本土竞争对手发布类似模型的浪潮，试图在竞争激烈的国内市场上夺回一席之地。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence startup Moonshot AI released a new open-source AI model on Friday, joining a wave of similar releases from local rivals, as it seeks to reclaim its position in the competitive domestic market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinas-moonshot-ai-releases-open-source-model-reclaim-market-position-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GY3HABX63VJD7AXZWGD267VDGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员称美联航和捷蓝航空的合作可能会损害竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员理查德-布卢门撒尔（Richard Blumenthal）说，美国联合航空公司和较小的捷蓝航空公司之间拟议的合作可能会损害竞争，导致消费者的选择更少、更贵。【原文：Democratic Senator Richard Blumenthal said a proposed partnership between United Airlines and smaller JetBlue Airways could harm competition and lead to fewer and more expensive options for consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-senator-says-united-jetblue-partnership-could-harm-competition-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6XH52RSVJPTXPCKZGU2UJBDYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:22:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西淡化美国关税对 2025 年经济增长的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西政府周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普本周早些时候宣布对来自南美国家的所有商品征收50%的关税，预计这对巴西今年的经济增长影响不大。【原文：Brazil's government expects the 50% tariff U.S. President Donald Trump announced earlier this week on all goods from the South American country to have little impact on its economic growth this year, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-downplays-impact-us-tariffs-2025-growth-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPY7LE2WQFI37JFBUBPETJWWCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:17:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球商业团体称，最新一轮关税后美国关税税率可能超过 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周宣布征收进口关税后，国际商会（International Chamber of Commerce）估计，美国消费者将面临超过20%的有效关税率，这是自20世纪初以来的最高水平。【原文：U.S. consumers face an effective U.S. tariff rate of more than 20%, the highest since the early 1900s, the International Chamber of Commerce has estimated following President Donald Trump's import levy announcements this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-tariff-rate-may-be-more-than-20-after-latest-round-global-business-group-says-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAEVWTFUM5L2XOOJKGPQGWYKFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游说团体称欧洲葡萄酒可能被排除在与美国的贸易协议之外]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲葡萄酒业的主要游说团体周五表示，在欧盟与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府之间达成的任何贸易协定中，欧洲葡萄酒都可能无法享受优惠待遇。【原文：European wines may not benefit from preferential treatment in any trade agreement between the EU and the administration of U.S. President Donald Trump, the industry's main lobby group said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/wine-lobby-group-urges-eu-keep-wine-us-trade-talks-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DVSRKKMVJPITBNADBOJVF7RBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴黎检察官联系警方，调查社交媒体平台 X]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴黎检察院周五表示，在推进今年早些时候启动的针对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 社交媒体平台（涉嫌算法偏见）的调查时，已与警方取得联系。【原文：The Paris public prosecutor's office said on Friday it had contacted police as it advanced its probe launched earlier in the year against Elon Musk's X social media platform over alleged algorithmic bias.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/paris-prosecutor-contacts-police-probe-into-social-media-platform-x-advances-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKPZJDAGPFKB7DP2JLNIPLG4SE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:48:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国报告敦促采取更有力的措施检测人工智能驱动的深度伪造行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国国际电信联盟（International Telecommunications Union）周五在一份报告中敦促各公司必须使用先进的工具来检测和消除错误信息和深度伪造内容，以帮助应对日益增长的选举干扰和金融欺诈风险。【原文：Companies must use advanced tools to detect and stamp out misinformation and deepfake content to help counter growing risks of election interference and financial fraud, the United Nations’ International Telecommunication Union urged in a report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/un-report-urges-stronger-measures-detect-ai-driven-deepfakes-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFPTWSMVOZKCZCIOMXUZML3DHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:32:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰与美国同行一道退出银行气候联盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国贷方汇丰银行周五表示，已决定退出银行业的主要气候联盟，但仍 "坚定地 "致力于到本世纪中叶实现整个业务的净零排放目标。【原文：British lender HSBC said on Friday it had decided to leave the banking sector's main climate coalition but remained "resolute" in targeting net-zero emissions across its business by mid-century.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/hsbc-joins-us-peers-leaving-bank-climate-coalition-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AD4AU2TJWNLWPA5KQ3AAGECW6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼集团与迪拜 Khazna 公司合作在意大利建设数据中心园区]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利能源集团埃尼公司（Eni）和迪拜的卡兹纳公司（Khazna）周五表示，双方已签署初步协议，将在意大利北部联合开发一个 500 兆瓦（MW）的数据中心园区。【原文：Italian energy group Eni and Dubai-based Khazna have signed a preliminary agreement to jointly develop a 500-megawatt (MW) data centre campus in northern Italy, the two companies said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/eni-dubai-based-khazna-team-up-build-data-center-campus-italy-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV7GYTRMP5NNLP33KI3W4F5UGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，尽管面临欧盟罚款风险，Meta 不会进一步调整 "付费或同意 "模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的人士周五表示，Meta Platforms 不太可能对其付费或同意模式做出更多改变，这意味着它几乎肯定会受到欧盟新的反垄断指控和每日巨额罚款的打击。【原文：Meta Platforms is very unlikely to offer more changes to its pay-or-consent model, meaning it is almost certain to be hit by fresh EU antitrust charges and hefty daily fines, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-wont-tweak-pay-or-consent-model-further-despite-risk-eu-fines-sources-say-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7SNJ2ETLBIFVIWTUSTCMEV5VU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:16:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马首席执行官希望就美国汽车进口关税达成 "可控 "协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝马公司首席执行官周五表示，他对欧盟和美国将很快就汽车进口关税达成一项 "可管理的 "协议感到乐观，该协议可能包括一个以出口抵消进口的机制。【原文：BMW's CEO said on Friday he was optimistic that the European Union and the United States would soon reach a "manageable" agreement on auto import tariffs, potentially including a mechanism to offset imports with exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-ceo-hopeful-manageable-deal-us-auto-import-tariffs-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SO72N2ITU5ILXAJPVGJYRTNWAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税威胁引发谨慎情绪，美国股票基金流入减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至7月9日的一周里，尽管股市因人工智能领域需求上升而创下新纪录，但由于对唐纳德-特朗普总统威胁对贸易伙伴征收新关税持谨慎态度，美国股票基金的净投资额大幅下降。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw a significant drop in net investments in the week through July 9 on caution over President Donald Trump's threats of fresh tariffs on trading partners, even though stocks surged to new records on rising demand in the artificial intelligence sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-fund-inflows-ease-caution-over-tariff-threats-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONKJYGBUWROEFGPNFXBGMUXEUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受人工智能反弹和关税延迟影响，全球股票基金迎来第二周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至7月9日的七天里，全球股票基金连续第二周吸引资金流入，这主要是受到与人工智能相关的股票反弹，以及美国将关税推出时间推迟到8月份可能会对正在进行的贸易谈判产生积极影响的预期的推动。【原文：Global equity funds drew inflows for a second consecutive week in the seven days to July 9, boosted by a rally in AI-linked stocks and expectations that pushing the U.S. tariff rollout to August could positively affect ongoing trade talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXJAWN2BERIATLWSH7NRNT4AJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币创新高，监管乐观情绪再起，加密货币股受提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在美国上市的加密货币股票在盘前交易中上涨，比特币飙升至历史新高，原因是越来越多的人乐观地认为监管障碍将很快开始缓解。【原文：U.S.-listed cryptocurrency stocks rose in premarket trading on Friday as bitcoin surged to a record high on growing optimism that regulatory hurdles would soon begin to ease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoins-record-high-lifts-crypto-stocks-renewed-regulatory-optimism-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I43IHFRAERNETP3CUYPMF3OSME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标加拿大重回关税漩涡]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTZ5WZHXIRJZDBOWK7EK4ZZRVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：特朗普的 1 亿美元加密货币神秘人]]></title><description><![CDATA[在向唐纳德-特朗普总统的世界自由金融公司（World Liberty Financial）加密货币业务发送资金的数字钱包中，一个鲜为人知的实体上个月成为了最大的谜团。【原文：Of all the riddles wrapped in the digital wallets sending funds to President Donald Trump’s World Liberty Financial crypto business, a little-known entity last month became the biggest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-100-million-crypto-mystery-man-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLZQXJEZUVJDFPE3VANQD2VEJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高价股和债券给市场带来关税威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[关于美国关税对经济增长可能产生的长期影响，全球市场的说法不一，投资者认为，这种分歧意味着，一旦孰是孰非明朗化，股票或债券都可能出现大幅回调。【原文：Global markets are telling conflicting stories about the possible longer-term impact of U.S. tariffs on growth, a schism that investors say means either stocks or bonds could see a steep correction once it's clear which is right.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/high-priced-stocks-bonds-raise-tariff-threat-markets-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZJ6VVOMIWBN7LMHHY2ZUDEU46I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟等待特朗普来信，市场消化最新关税炮弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟周五收到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的一封信，信中概述了美国在最近几天扩大关税战后对其最大贸易和投资伙伴征收关税的计划。【原文：The European Union braced on Friday to receive a letter from U.S. President Donald Trump, outlining planned duties on his largest trade and investment partner after a broadening of his tariff war in recent days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-waits-trump-letter-markets-digest-latest-tariff-salvo-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DE4ZI3WLQFLALBBQXBKPRRXOLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球牛仔布需求强劲，李维斯上调业绩预期，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[李维斯（Levi Strauss）周五在盘前交易中股价大涨超过 7%，此前这家牛仔布生产商上调了年度营收和利润预期，指望其门店和网站的强劲需求能抵消美国关税对利润率的冲击。【原文：Levi Strauss shares surged more than 7% in premarket trading on Friday after the denim maker raised its annual revenue and profit forecasts, counting on robust demand at its stores and website to offset a margin hit from U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/levi-strauss-shares-jump-after-raising-forecasts-strong-global-denim-demand-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCSLGNRVANMDJKRIEHEHE5DCSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:49:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 拒绝批准细胞疗法，Capricor 股价下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周五表示，已拒绝批准 Capricor Therapeutics 公司治疗心脏病的细胞疗法，导致该公司股价在早盘交易中暴跌 30%。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has declined to approve Capricor Therapeutics' cell therapy for a heart condition, the company said on Friday, sending its shares tumbling 30% in early trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-declines-approve-capricors-muscle-disorder-therapy-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLOEX4VK5NII7E6LMYNSLKTVCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫审查大规模联邦裁员计划，旨在迅速采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员称缩编是 "当务之急"。【原文：A White House official called the downsizing an "immediate priority."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/white-house-reviews-mass-federal-layoff-plans-aims-swift-action-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVDT2NDCXZI2JFGF26BFZJE5HQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:11:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国安全监管机构对 27,000 多辆 Polestar 2 汽车展开召回调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，已开始对27816辆瑞典电动汽车制造商Polestar的Polestar 2汽车进行召回调查，原因是后视摄像头图像丢失。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday it had opened a recall query covering 27,816 of Sweden-based EV maker Polestar's Polestar 2 vehicles over a loss of rear-view camera image.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/nhtsa-opens-recall-query-into-more-than-27000-polestar-2-vehicles-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XAPZV3OENNOYBBFTTV6SSF7T2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:10:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RealSense 脱离英特尔，获 5000 万美元资金推动机器人领域的人工智能视觉发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[计算机视觉技术公司RealSense周五表示，它已经完成了从英特尔公司的分拆，并获得了5000万美元的早期融资，以加速向快速增长的机器人领域扩张。【原文：Computer vision technology firm RealSense said on Friday it has completed its spinout from Intel Corp and secured $50 million in early-stage funding to accelerate expansion into the rapidly growing robotics sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/realsense-spins-out-intel-secures-50-million-drive-ai-vision-robotics-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWP4PNLIJNMI3JDYDIL4HSW7PU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 财报、通胀数据支撑美股强劲反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[未来一周，美国股市将面临企业财报季启动和一份关键通胀报告的考验，因为投资者希望进一步了解关税对经济的影响。【原文：A rally that has taken U.S. stocks to record highs will be tested in the coming week by the kick-off of corporate earnings season and a key inflation report as investors hope to learn more about the economic fallout from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-earnings-inflation-data-confront-resilient-us-stocks-rally-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADPFCMYNZVN7XKVDPGSLNWRFBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税大棒导致华尔街期货走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五下跌，原因是唐纳德-特朗普总统发起了新一轮关税攻势，在下周财报季到来之前令投资者感到恐慌。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Friday as President Donald Trump launched fresh salvoes in his tariff offensive, rattling investors ahead of earnings season next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-tariff-barrage-knocks-wall-st-futures-lower-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7AEUCU5FRNTVAWQFN6WEJHK4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 09:54:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲证券监管机构警告加密货币公司误导客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲证券监管机构周五警告加密货币公司不要在产品受监管程度方面误导客户，这是欧洲当局试图限制加密货币相关风险的最新迹象。【原文：Europe's securities regulator warned crypto companies on Friday not to mislead customers about the extent to which their products are regulated - the latest sign of European authorities trying to limit crypto-related risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/european-securities-regulator-warns-about-crypto-firms-misleading-customers-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74LU3HGHXJNNXIHT5MZDLUQGXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 09:53:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[劳资协议会称福特同意保护科隆的工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车制造商福特公司已与德国工会 IG Metall 达成协议，在 2032 年前保护其科隆生产基地所有员工的工作岗位，通过自愿裁员实现公司的重组目标。【原文：U.S. carmaker Ford has agreed with German union IG Metall to protect the jobs of all employees at its site in Cologne through 2032, with voluntary redundancies allowing the company to achieve its restructuring aims, its works council said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/ford-agrees-deal-shield-cologne-jobs-works-council-says-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACDEOOX4VJNAFE7PXUVIHFD4F4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 09:29:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>