<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:07:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:07:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[会议纪要显示，美联储在决策者对通胀持谨慎态度的情况下下调利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储10月28-29日的会议纪要周三显示，尽管决策者们警告说，降低借贷成本可能会有损于为平息四年半来一直高于美国央行2%目标的通胀率而进行的斗争，但上个月美联储仍出现了降息的分歧。【原文：A divided Federal Reserve cut interest rates last month even as policymakers cautioned that lower borrowing costs could risk undermining the fight to quell inflation that has been above the U.S. central bank's 2% target for four and a half years, the minutes from the October 28-29 meeting showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-cut-rates-amid-policymakers-caution-about-inflation-minutes-show-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TP5Z33GAG5OWHDDKSBQHH7TRS4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯普京呼吁成立国家人工智能工作组]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗拉基米尔-普京总统周三呼吁成立一个国家工作组，协调俄罗斯在国产生成式人工智能模型方面的工作，他说这对维护俄罗斯主权至关重要。【原文：President Vladimir Putin on Wednesday called for a national task force to coordinate Russia's work on homegrown generative artificial intelligence models, which he said were vital to preserving Russian sovereignty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russias-putin-calls-national-ai-task-force-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTLIFE5O6BISRFZHZ36QFCG6BU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华将在北卡罗来纳州建立生产中心，创造 700 个就业岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士制药公司诺华周三表示，将扩大在北卡罗来纳州的业务，并在那里建立一个生产中心，作为未来五年计划在美国基础设施投资 230 亿美元的一部分。【原文：Novartis will expand its operations in North Carolina and build a manufacturing hub there as part of a planned $23 billion of U.S. infrastructure investment over the next five years, the Swiss pharmaceuticals company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/novartis-build-manufacturing-hub-north-carolina-creating-700-jobs-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMOH4LNZJRNZPG2YWZG74S4SU4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:51:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国因停摆无法收集数据而取消 10 月份就业报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工统计局（Bureau of Labor Statistics）周三表示，在最近结束的政府停摆阻碍了家庭调查数据的收集之后，该局将不再发布备受关注的 10 月份就业报告，而是将该月的非农就业数据与 11 月份的报告合并发布。【原文：The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics said on Wednesday it would not be publishing the closely watched employment report for October, but will combine nonfarm payrolls for that month with November's report after the recently ended government shutdown prevented the collection of data for the household survey.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-canceling-octobers-employment-report-after-shutdown-prevented-data-collection-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUNL7AF7PVLIXDJJXYVNIMWQRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:46:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道官员称特朗普的半导体关税计划可能推迟]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国官员私下表示，他们可能不会很快征收承诺已久的半导体关税，这可能会推迟唐纳德-特朗普总统经济议程的核心内容。【原文：U.S. officials are privately saying that they might not levy long-promised semiconductor tariffs soon, potentially delaying a centerpiece of President Donald Trump’s economic agenda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-semiconductor-tariff-plan-likely-delayed-officials-say-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSRDZPQPSVMI5JLND35SWT7JHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:40:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳音乐与人工智能公司 Udio 达成和解，计划建立联合平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳音乐集团（Warner Music Group）周三表示，已与人工智能公司 Udio 就版权侵权案达成和解，双方将联合推出一个新的人工智能歌曲创作平台。【原文：Warner Music Group has settled a copyright infringement case with artificial intelligence company Udio and will jointly launch a new platform for AI song creation, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/warner-music-settles-with-ai-firm-udio-plans-joint-platform-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZSLTO7ZPAZPURF7TF5N2DVTPFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:23:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次批评美联储主席鲍威尔，称 "我真想炒了他的鱿鱼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三对美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）没有更快降息的批评加倍，他说："老实说，我很想炒了他的鱿鱼："老实说，我真想炒了他"【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday doubled down on his criticism of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell for not lowering interest rates more quickly, saying: "I'll be honest, I'd love to fire his ass."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-he-would-love-fire-fed-chair-powell-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMYSYZDZYFPUTOOUC45VSMDM6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿美石油公司与美国签署价值超过 300 亿美元的初步协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[石油巨头沙特阿美石油公司（Saudi Aramco）周三表示，在沙特王储访问华盛顿期间，该公司已与美国公司签署了 17 项初步协议，总价值可能超过 300 亿美元。【原文：Oil giant Saudi Aramco said on Wednesday it had signed 17 preliminary deals with U.S. companies with a potential overall value of more than $30 billion, during a visit to Washington by the Saudi Crown Prince.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/aramco-signs-preliminary-us-deals-worth-more-than-30-billion-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHQLXIYLNJIGHJESLOVQRQXVHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:15:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[浑水公司的卡森-布洛克（Carson Block）说，他看多 Snowline Gold 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[浑水公司（Muddy Waters）创始人卡森-布洛克（Carson Block）周三表示，他已持有加拿大金矿公司 Snowline Gold Corp 的多头头寸，这标志着这位著名的做空者将离开。【原文：Muddy Waters' founder Carson Block said on Wednesday he has taken a long position in Canadian gold miner Snowline Gold Corp , marking a departure for the famed short seller.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/muddy-waters-carson-block-says-he-is-long-snowline-gold-corp-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTDNKDXKSNP6TEDTOWJAFFFDRE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:09:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于炼油商反对，特朗普政府可能推迟削减生物燃料进口信贷]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑将削减进口生物燃料激励措施的提议推迟一到两年，因为美国炼油商认为此举可能会提高成本并导致燃料供应紧张。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering delaying for one or two years its proposed cuts in incentives for imported biofuels amid pressure from U.S. refiners who argue the move could raise costs and tighten fuel supplies, according to two sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-may-delay-biofuel-import-credit-cuts-refiners-balk-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFPPPSISJBL2NHVLPAGWSNNZQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:43:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe 和高通公司与 Humain 合作为中东地区开发生成式人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[Adobe 公司和高通公司周三表示，他们正在与沙特阿拉伯主权财富基金支持的人工智能公司 Humain 合作，帮助这家人工智能公司开发用于生成阿拉伯语和更广泛中东地区内容的工具。【原文：Adobe and Qualcomm said on Wednesday they are partnering with Humain, the artificial intelligence firm backed by Saudi Arabia's sovereign wealth fund, to help the AI company develop tools for generating content in Arabic and for the broader Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/adobe-qualcomm-partner-with-humain-generative-ai-middle-east-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FVUWKFKCNJMRGNGB74MM2I3ZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能音乐公司 Suno 在最新一轮融资中估值 24.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Suno 周三表示，它已在由 Menlo Ventures 领投的一轮融资中筹集了 2.5 亿美元，这家人工智能音乐公司的估值为 24.5 亿美元，它的目标是开发更复杂的歌曲创作工具。【原文：Suno said on Wednesday it has raised $250 million in a funding round led by Menlo Ventures, valuing the artificial intelligence music company at $2.45 billion, as it aims to develop more sophisticated tools for song creation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ai-music-company-suno-valued-245-billion-latest-funding-round-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBI3MT4RFNK5BKSGP6DMGMFAVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国将禁止以盈利为目的转售门票以保护球迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国周三表示，将禁止以营利为目的转售音乐会、体育赛事和其他现场活动的门票，扰乱票贩子和从其活动中获益的平台。【原文：Britain said on Wednesday it would ban the resale of tickets to concerts, sport and other live events for profit, disrupting ticket touts and the platforms that benefit from their activities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-ban-resale-tickets-profit-protect-fans-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3T55ODF2VMCVIAIAHBRSUAJF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称瑞士宝盛银行将用 Temenos 产品取代瑞士 IT 系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士宝盛银行（Julius Baer）已选择软件供应商 Temenos 替换其在瑞士本土市场老化的核心银行系统，四位熟悉内情的人士表示，这是该银行在监管要求不断提高的情况下更新关键基础设施的一次尝试。【原文：Julius Baer has chosen software provider Temenos to replace its ageing core banking system in the Swiss home market, four people familiar with the matter said, in a quest by the bank to update critical infrastructure amid mounting regulatory requirements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/julius-baer-replace-swiss-it-system-with-temenos-product-sources-say-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EX7AZYCSSBOJ7EYIX6U64E66BQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能机器人为普京献舞 几天前，另一个俄罗斯机器人步履蹒跚]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在俄罗斯最大的银行储蓄银行（Sberbank）为展示公司技术进步而举办的展览上，一个人工智能机器人为弗拉基米尔-普京总统翩翩起舞。【原文：An AI-powered robot danced for President Vladimir Putin on Wednesday at an exhibition put on by Sberbank, Russia's largest bank, designed to showcase the company's technological advances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ai-powered-robot-dances-putin-days-after-another-russian-robot-stumbles-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDQQXY6ZHJPRHBDL5EBCYHRFO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：AMD、思科和沙特 Humain 公司成立人工智能合资企业，获得首个大客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[先进微设备公司（Advanced Micro Devices）、思科系统公司（Cisco Systems）和沙特阿拉伯人工智能初创公司Humain周二在接受路透社采访时表示，三家公司正在组建一家合资企业，在中东地区建设数据中心，并且已经找到了第一家客户。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices , Cisco Systems and Saudi Arabian artificial intelligence startup Humain are forming a joint venture to build data centers in the Middle East and have landed their first customer, CEOs at the three companies told Reuters in an interview on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/amd-cisco-saudis-humain-launch-ai-joint-venture-land-first-major-customer-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPUAFALDBFMH5GM2JTC6LIT5HA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:22:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[基督教科技平台 Gloo 在纳斯达克首次亮相，估值达 5.86 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[以基督教为重点的科技平台 Gloo 周三在纳斯达克首次上市时股价平开，估值为 5.86 亿美元，这是近几周一系列冷淡上市交易中的又一例。【原文：Christian-focused tech platform Gloo was valued at $586 million as its shares opened flat in their Nasdaq debut on Wednesday, adding to a string of lukewarm listings in recent weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/christian-tech-platform-gloo-valued-586-million-muted-nasdaq-debut-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEYSZSLLU5NYVIEUHNTMC5GEBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利 SQM 公司预计 2025 年锂需求将增长 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利锂生产商SQM的高管周三表示，他们预计今年的锂需求将超过150万吨，比2024年增长25%。【原文：Executives from Chilean lithium producer SQM on Wednesday said they expect lithium demand this year to reach over 1.5 million metric tons, representing 25% growth from 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chiles-sqm-expects-25-lithium-demand-growth-2025-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOY4L7LJL5NR7HP7W55TVSWACA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[施耐德电气与美国数据中心达成 23 亿美元交易，助力人工智能热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[施耐德电气（Schneider Electric）周三表示，该公司已与两家美国数据中心运营商签署了价值近 23 亿美元的新协议，因为人工智能的采用激增推动了对基础设施的需求。【原文：Schneider Electric said on Wednesday that it had signed new deals worth almost $2.3 billion with two U.S. data centre operators, as surging adoption of artificial intelligence boosts infrastructure demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/schneider-electric-seals-23-billion-us-data-centre-deals-power-ai-boom-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CC5H3AT3LFPY5H53GAN7CKMK4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blockfusion 将通过 4.5 亿美元的 SPAC 交易在纽约上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据中心运营商 Blockfusion 周三表示，该公司将通过与空白支票公司 Blue Acquisition Corp 合并的方式在美国上市，交易价值为 4.5 亿美元，投资者对该行业的热情持续高涨。【原文：Data center operator Blockfusion said on Wednesday it would list in the United States through a merger with blank-check firm Blue Acquisition Corp in a deal valued at $450 million, as investor appetite for the sector continues to surge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blockfusion-list-new-york-via-450-million-spac-deal-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4MKP6GD6FNHVIV3O4SY7NOGRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Kraken 秘密申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的加密货币交易所之一 Kraken 周三表示，它已秘密申请在美国首次公开募股，因为数字资产公司希望在 2026 年中期选举前开拓新的上市市场。【原文：Kraken, one of the world's largest cryptocurrency exchanges, said on Wednesday it has confidentially filed for an initial public offering in the U.S., as digital asset companies look to tap the new listings market before the 2026 midterm elections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/crypto-exchange-kraken-confidentially-files-us-ipo-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXRM5JI2BVJATLHSZ74BAV5UKM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:08:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席米兰呼吁将国债豁免于银行杠杆率规则之外]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周三呼吁监管机构将美国国债豁免于一项关键的银行杠杆比率，并认为监管机构应比之前提出的计划更进一步。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran on Wednesday called for regulators to exempt U.S. Treasury bonds from a key bank leverage ratio, arguing agencies should go further than previously proposed plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-miran-calls-exempting-treasuries-bank-leverage-rule-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTNBZLAPYJKGNKYJXYERF7Z2LY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[米兰称，放松监管可能导致美联储资产负债表规模缩小]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周三表示，减轻金融公司的监管负担可能会让美国央行在未来再次缩减资产负债表的规模。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran said on Wednesday that easing financial firms' regulatory burden could allow the U.S. central bank to shrink the size of its balance sheet again in the future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/easing-regulations-could-lead-smaller-fed-balance-sheet-miran-says-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJS4CV2CLZLWJN3ZM44QJ5JL34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源部长称铀浓缩不是与沙特阿拉伯达成的民用核协议的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）周三表示，铀浓缩不是与沙特阿拉伯达成的民用核能协议的一部分。【原文：Uranium enrichment is not part of the deal on civil nuclear energy reached with Saudi Arabia, U.S. Energy Secretary Chris Wright said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/uranium-enrichment-not-part-civil-nuclear-deal-with-saudi-arabia-us-energy-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXWJCZBQNVMHRHFOOQ5MES6J6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国人口普查局将于下周发布 9 月份零售销售和耐用品订单报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部人口普查局周三表示，将于下周公布9月份零售销售、食品服务和耐用品订单报告。这两份报告都因政府关门而推迟发布。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department's Census Bureau said on Wednesday it would publish both September retail sales and food services and durable goods orders reports next week. Both were delayed by the government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-census-bureau-release-sept-retail-sales-durable-goods-orders-reports-next-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2FBNLK44VLZ5GUREUWKW2KZ74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:43:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国旅游业有望借助国际足联世界杯获得巨大成功]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025 年，由于对唐纳德-特朗普总统贸易政策的不安以及对更严格的边境审查的担忧，游客们纷纷远离美国，而 2026 年国际足联世界杯的举办将为美国的国际旅游业带来急需的推动力。【原文：International tourism to the U.S. could get a much-needed boost from the 2026 FIFA World Cup after a sluggish 2025, when visitors stayed away amid unease over President Donald Trump's trade policies and concerns about tougher border scrutiny.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/us-tourism-expected-score-big-with-fifa-world-cup-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMMMRKTGDVMHRBJ25QAP7ODNXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉加经委会报告显示，尽管美国实行关税政策，拉丁美洲和加勒比地区之间的贸易仍将在 2025 年实现增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国拉丁美洲和加勒比经济委员会（拉加经委会）周三发布的一份报告显示，尽管美国对拉丁美洲和加勒比地区广泛征收关税，但其影响比最初预期的要弱，2025年该地区之间的贸易可能会增长。【原文：Trade between Latin America and the Caribbean will likely grow in 2025 despite broad U.S. tariffs across the region, which have had a weaker impact than initially expected, a report by UN's Economic Commission for Latin America and the Caribbean (ECLAC) revealed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trade-between-latin-america-caribbean-due-grow-2025-despite-us-tariff-policy-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLNXMYWEQ5LD5C57YJPVCCG5FE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府提名莱文巴赫为 CFPB 主任]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据参议院收到的通知，美国政府已提名斯图尔特-莱文巴赫（Stuart Levenbach）担任消费者金融保护局局长，任期五年。【原文：The U.S. administration has nominated Stuart Levenbach to be director of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau for a five-year term, according to a notice provided to the Senate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-administration-nominates-levenbach-cfpb-director-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URK2TYA36NIWFN26P3ZRDSP7BI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：欧盟计划如何放宽对大科技公司的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周三公布了对欧洲数字规则手册的全面修改，批评人士称，这些修改将使大型科技公司更容易获取个人数据，并削弱实施了二十年的隐私保护措施。【原文：The European Commission on Wednesday unveiled sweeping changes to Europe's digital rulebook that critics say would give major technology companies easier access to personal data and weaken privacy protections in place for two decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/how-eu-plans-ease-rules-big-tech-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45IKKD4R6ZK7XHKTR3TLTNBPSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大卫-贝克汉姆与美国银行签署体育合作协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[前英格兰足球队队长大卫-贝克汉姆（David Beckham）与美国银行（Bank of America）签署了一项多年合作协议，在 2026 年北美世界杯足球赛之前推广全球体育项目。【原文：Former England soccer captain David Beckham signed a multi-year partnership with Bank of America to promote global sports programs ahead of the 2026 FIFA World Cup in North America, he and the bank said about the deal, which was first reported by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/david-beckham-signs-sports-partnership-deal-with-bank-america-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MNMJJR5LJLSVOZOJ7L2B7RAVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>