<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:28:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:28:52 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[全球贸易压力增大，中国出口意外下滑至2月以来最差水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 10 月份的出口出人意料地下滑，原因是海外订单减少，而此前几个月，中国为抵御美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税而采取了前置措施。【原文：China's exports unexpectedly slumped in October as overseas orders tapered off following months of front-loading to beat President Donald Trump's tariffs, and as buyers watched to see how a volatile month in U.S.-China trade ties would play out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-exports-unexpectedly-slide-worst-since-feb-global-trade-pressure-mounts-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NCFVVCUJFLVLBJU3KC5PVYDDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国与乌兹别克斯坦达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，美国和乌兹别克斯坦已达成经贸协议，乌兹别克斯坦计划在未来三年内采购和投资350亿美元，在未来十年内采购和投资超过1000亿美元，用于美国的一些行业。【原文：The United States and Uzbekistan have reached a trade and economic deal, President Donald Trump said on Thursday, stating that Uzbekistan plans to purchase and invest $35 billion in the next three years and more than $100 billion in the next 10 years in some U.S. sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-says-us-uzbekistan-reach-trade-deal-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHOLXPIVXVNGRMPP3PZN7UAHKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应忧虑加重，石油将迎来第二周下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心供应过剩和美国需求放缓，石油价格在连续三天下跌后于周五略有回升，但似乎将迎来第二周的下跌。【原文：Oil edged up on Friday following three days of declines on worries about excess supply and slowing demand in the U.S., though prices appeared to be headed for a second week of losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-heads-second-weekly-loss-supply-concerns-weigh-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PULJJJVRZFIUXCOME54XSAC3B4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，美国将阻止英伟达向中国出售缩小版人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《The Information》周四援引三位熟悉内情的人士的话报道，白宫已通知其他联邦机构，不允许英伟达向中国出售其最新的缩小版人工智能芯片。【原文：The White House has informed other federal agencies that it will not permit Nvidia to sell its latest scaled-down AI chips to China, The Information reported on Thursday, citing three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-block-nvidias-sale-scaled-back-ai-chips-china-information-says-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSSBFFO4QZK3XKWPLDD3QB4IIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:47:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[低迷情绪令科技股周线下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于投资者对人工智能股的涨势感到不安，科技股市场迎来了七个月来最严重的单周跌幅，而债券和日元等更安全的资产则走高。【原文：Tech-heavy stock markets were bracing for their heaviest weekly falls in seven months on Friday as investors have turned uneasy about how far the rally in artificial intelligence stocks has run, while safer assets such as bonds and the yen went higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPALNDD7DBLYZE7RVFW5LUE3VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:37:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克计划建立特斯拉超大型人工智能芯片工厂，并考虑与英特尔建立潜在合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周四表示，特斯拉可能需要建造 "一座巨大的芯片工厂 "来生产人工智能芯片，并公开表示这家电动汽车制造商可以与英特尔合作。【原文：CEO Elon Musk on Thursday said Tesla probably will have to build "a gigantic chip fab" to make artificial intelligence chips and publicly mused the EV maker could work with Intel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-plans-tesla-mega-ai-chip-fab-mulls-potential-intel-partnership-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LB4LPFPWNFIH5AANKSTJQZK7YU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示美国就业市场出现裂痕，美元处于守势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲早盘，美元回落，领跌主要货币，原因是缺乏美国劳动力市场官方数据的投资者抓住了私营部门调查疲软的迹象。【原文：The dollar retreated in early Asia trade on Friday, leading declines among major currencies as investors lacking official data on the U.S. labour market seized upon signs of weakness in private sector surveys.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-defensive-data-show-cracks-us-jobs-market-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FE7X6O7LD5OQDGEVKJXJSORIUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敲定周五开始削减国内航班 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周四以政府停摆期间空中交通管制的安全问题为由，命令航空公司从美国东部时间周五上午6点（格林尼治标准时间11点）开始将40个高流量机场的国内航班运营削减4%。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration on Thursday ordered airlines to cut domestic flight operations by 4% at 40 high-traffic airports starting at 6 a.m. ET (1100 GMT) on Friday, citing safety concerns about air traffic control during the government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-finalizes-domestic-flight-cuts-start-4-friday-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3R742EMWZLZRNIH4OXU7O5RQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈弗分析公司预计美国每周申请失业救济人数温和增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈弗分析公司（Haver Analytics）周四估计，上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数略有增加，表明尽管宣布的裁员人数激增，但10月份劳动力市场状况稳定。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased marginally last week, Haver Analytics estimated on Thursday, pointing to stable labor market conditions in October despite a surge in announced layoffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-moderately-haver-analytics-estimates-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUHOZFOZYJJR3EDYQLYDD7PFCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哪些机场受到美国强制削减航班的影响？]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一份文件显示，美国联邦航空管理局周四告诉各航空公司，从周五开始在 40 个客流量大的机场削减 4% 的航班。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration told airlines on Thursday to cut 4% of flights at 40 high-traffic airports starting Friday, according to a document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/which-airports-are-affected-by-forced-us-flight-reductions-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SX4GXBGFNKUPEEQTVRNG7XKIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商 Stellantis 终止与澳大利亚 Alliance Nickel 的供应协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚联盟镍业公司（Alliance Nickel）周五表示，汽车制造商 Stellantis 将终止他们从 NiWest 项目供应电池级镍和钴的交易，该交易将于 12 月 3 日生效，理由是错过了里程碑期限。【原文：Australia's Alliance Nickel said on Friday carmaker Stellantis will terminate their supply deal for battery-grade nickel and cobalt from the NiWest project, effective December 3, citing missed milestone deadlines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carmaker-stellantis-pulls-plug-supply-deal-with-australias-alliance-nickel-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JKOAT4RFJOTPBHYHONDYR76MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[暂停港口收费，特朗普政府寻求与中国就航运问题进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周四表示，将就中国在造船业和海洋物流业的主导地位问题与中国进行谈判，同时正式计划暂停向与中国有联系的船只征收为期一年的美国港口费，作为缓解贸易紧张局势的更广泛协议的一部分。【原文：The Trump administration said on Thursday it would pursue negotiations with China over its dominance of shipbuilding and ocean logistics as it formalized plans for a one-year pause on U.S. port fees on China-linked vessels as part of a broader deal to reduce trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-seeks-negotiate-with-china-shipping-it-pauses-port-fees-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LS53JUI6ZNPVD2ECZJLJZUEZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 23:55:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆萨莱姆：美联储降息支持就业市场是正确的]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周四表示，美国央行降息以帮助就业市场是正确的。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis President Alberto Musalem said on Thursday the U.S. central bank has been right to cut interest rates to help the job market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-right-cut-rates-support-job-market-musalem-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXPQENKVYFLYZK3I6NSZ4SZX7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 23:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛晋升总经理的高管人数为 2021 年以来最多]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街贷款公司高盛（Goldman Sachs）在一份公司备忘录中表示，明年将有 638 名高管晋升为董事总经理，这是自 2021 年以来的最高值，因为该银行受益于整个行业投资银行业务的回暖。【原文：Wall Street lender Goldman Sachs will promote 638 executives to managing director next year, the highest since 2021, a company memo said, as the bank benefits from a pickup in investment banking across the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-promote-highest-number-executives-managing-director-since-2021-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PL75K6HLNMQ7OFCAXPGCPXYTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳航上半年国内收入下滑，原因是非资源企业需求放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚航空公司（Qantas Airways）周五表示，由于非资源型企业客户的需求低于预期，该公司预计2026财年上半年的国内业务收入将处于预测区间的下限。【原文：Australia's Qantas Airways said on Friday it expects domestic unit revenue for the first half of fiscal 2026 to land at the lower end of its forecast range, citing weaker-than-anticipated demand from non-resource corporate clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/qantas-flags-softer-1h-domestic-revenue-non-resource-corporate-demand-slows-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUGDN2RUGVOG7EXSHBWBGOS56M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:46:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司第三季度净利润增长 2.7]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国营石油公司（Petrobras）周四公布，第三季度净利润为 60.3 亿美元，与去年同期相比增长 2.7%。【原文：Brazilian state-run oil firm Petrobras on Thursday posted a $6.03 billion net profit for the third-quarter, a 2.7% increase when compared to the same period a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazils-petrobras-posts-27-increase-third-quarter-net-profit-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMWD2MOIWRNKJGGWW3JUO3DCLQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会称，UPS飞机坠毁调查将调查维修历史]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国安全调查人员周四表示，他们正在调查 UPS 一架货机的维修历史，这架飞机周二在肯塔基州路易斯维尔坠毁，造成至少 13 人死亡。【原文：U.S. safety investigators said on Thursday they are probing the maintenance history of a UPS cargo plane that was in Texas for repairs weeks before crashing in flames in Louisville, Kentucky, on Tuesday, killing at least 13 people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ups-plane-crash-investigation-will-probe-maintenance-history-ntsb-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2APCCR3HDJJY3EZK4I64SFRLVA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受库存清理影响，Microchip 预计季度净销售额低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[微芯科技公司（Microchip Technology）周四预测第三季度净销售额低于华尔街预期，表明随着汽车和工业市场客户继续清理过剩库存，对其芯片的需求不温不火。【原文：Microchip Technology forecast third-quarter net sales below Wall Street estimates on Thursday, indicating tepid demand for its chips as customers in the automotive and industrial markets continue to clear excess inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microchip-forecasts-quarterly-net-sales-below-estimates-inventory-clearing-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXXP2ZLM5FNPFBAQINLUF6KCSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Monster Beverage 因无糖能量饮料需求强劲，季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[怪兽饮料公司（Monster Beverage）周四公布的第三季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于无糖能量饮料和新口味饮料在经济不确定的情况下仍保持强劲的需求。【原文：Monster Beverage beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue and profit on Thursday, helped by resilient demand for its sugar-free energy drinks and new flavors even amid economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/monster-beverage-beats-quarterly-results-estimates-strong-demand-sugar-free-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXEZDJVNFJO3RC2J6OQLOI6D7I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 不确定性抨击风险偏好]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市、债券收益率和美元周四全线下跌，原因是市场再次担心人工智能泡沫和对美国劳动力市场强劲程度的担忧。【原文：U.S. stocks, bond yields and the dollar all fell on Thursday, dragged down by renewed fears of an AI bubble and worries over the strength of the U.S. labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4K3HTFFNBKCBLZ6ZGGL6QIGS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:05:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉股东批准伊隆-马斯克 8,780 亿美元薪酬计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周四大获全胜，股东们批准了未来十年高达 8,780 亿美元的薪酬方案，支持他将这家电动汽车制造商打造成人工智能和机器人巨头的愿景。【原文：Tesla CEO Elon Musk scored a resounding victory on Thursday as shareholders approved a pay package of as much as $878 billion over the next decade, endorsing his vision of morphing the EV maker into an AI and robotics juggernaut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/tesla-shareholders-approve-878-billion-pay-plan-elon-musk-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAHXQTQ5CNN4JLE4SBI23AOH5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰官员表示相信 Nexperia 芯片将在未来几天内走向世界]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰经济部长文森特-卡雷曼斯（Vincent Karremans）周四表示，他相信荷兰芯片制造商Nexperia生产的计算机芯片将在未来几天内到达欧洲和世界其他地区的客户手中。【原文：The Netherlands' economy minister, Vincent Karremans, said on Thursday he trusts computer chips made by Dutch chipmaker Nexperia will reach customers in Europe and the rest of the world in the coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dutch-official-says-he-trusts-nexperia-chips-will-reach-world-coming-days-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KRPK53ZVVNXBBOVJ3L2HVN56Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:46:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚麦格理半年利润增长；扩大股票回购规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦格理集团（Macquarie Group）周五公布，在资产管理、银行和金融服务部门强劲业绩的帮助下，上半年利润有所增长，并表示将进一步回购价值高达 20 亿澳元（13.0 亿美元）的股票。【原文：Macquarie Group posted a rise in first-half profit on Friday, helped by strong performance in its asset management and banking and financial services arms, and said it would further buy back up to A$2 billion ($1.30 billion) worth of shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-macquarie-half-year-profit-rises-expands-share-buyback-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IS2IVJJOWNINPGBX5YUHWS72EQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:43:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司获得哈萨克斯坦阿斯塔纳航空公司 15 架梦想飞机订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周四表示，已收到哈萨克斯坦航空公司阿斯塔纳航空（Air Astana）最多15架787梦想飞机的订单。【原文：Boeing said on Thursday it had received an order for up to 15 787 Dreamliners from Kazakhstan carrier Air Astana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-gets-15-dreamliner-aircraft-order-kazakhstans-air-astana-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOT7IDS5WVOXHN5DMCGFVIIYYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府宣布在中亚与波音公司达成交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府周四宣布了向中亚国家哈萨克斯坦、塔吉克斯坦和乌兹别克斯坦的航空公司出售多达37架波音飞机的新交易。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration announced Thursday new deals to sell up to 37 Boeing airplanes to airlines in the Central Asian nations of Kazakhstan, Tajikistan and Uzbekistan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-administration-announces-boeing-deals-central-asia-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASAOEE24AJIVJAV7K3EIM2GBWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:37:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，天空电视台（Sky）所有者康卡斯特（Comcast）正在洽谈收购 ITV 的广播部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，天空电视台（Sky News）的所有者康卡斯特公司（Comcast）正在洽谈收购英国广播公司 ITV 的媒体和娱乐部门。【原文：Sky News-owner Comcast is in talks to buy British broadcaster ITV's media and entertainment unit, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/sky-owner-comcast-talks-buy-itvs-broadcasting-arm-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3EH636SA3NPUNEQ3XNB3G3TE5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈马克认为目前无需加息以降低通胀率]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联储主席贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周四表示，她并不认为美国央行需要加息来应对她认为过高的通胀压力，同时她也承认这一观点可能会发生变化。【原文：Cleveland Federal Reserve President Beth Hammack said on Thursday she does not think the U.S. central bank needs to raise interest rates to combat inflation pressures she considers too high, while acknowledging how that view might change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-hammack-sees-no-need-hike-rates-lower-inflation-this-time-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3MXA34YWRLWTMHR32BJN5WGKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:33:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新闻集团季度收入超出预期，原因是道琼斯和数字房地产服务部门实现增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[媒体集团新闻集团周四公布的第一季度营收超出华尔街预期，主要得益于道琼斯和数字房地产服务部门的增长。【原文：Media conglomerate News Corp beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter revenue on Thursday, bolstered by growth at its Dow Jones and digital real estate services segments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/news-corp-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUH7D2O6E5L6LJNKIOIAZSH2B4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[停止向中国客户销售后，MP 材料公司季度亏损扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[稀土公司 MP Materials 周四表示，作为获得美国政府财政支持协议的一部分，该公司停止向中国客户销售稀土，导致其第三季度亏损扩大。【原文：Rare earths company MP Materials said on Thursday its third-quarter loss widened as it stopped sales to Chinese customers as part of an agreement to receive U.S. government financial backing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/mp-materials-quarterly-loss-widens-after-stopping-sales-chinese-customers-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJZU5VMX6FKUZBPYIEGIY3E3TE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国页岩油生产商 EOG Resources 第三季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油天然气资源公司（EOG Resources）周四公布的第三季度利润超过了分析师的预期，因为产量的增加帮助这家美国石油天然气生产商抵消了原油价格的下跌。【原文：EOG Resources beat analysts' estimates for third-quarter profit on Thursday, as a rise in output helped the U.S. oil and gas producer offset a drop in crude prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-shale-producer-eog-resources-beats-third-quarter-profit-estimates-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBEBQGZAKRMI5I3HILJ5ABN7DI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:21:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>