<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 11:04:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 11:04:20 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普暂停进口关税后，美国公司竞相争取进口关税豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家表示，华盛顿对《美国-墨西哥-加拿大协定》（USMCA）所涵盖商品进口关税的临时宽免引发了寻求贸易协定豁免的美国公司激增。【原文：Washington's temporary relief for import tariffs on goods covered under the U.S.-Mexico-Canada Agreement (USMCA) has triggered a spike in US companies seeking exemption under the trade deal, industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-companies-race-secure-import-tariff-exemptions-after-trump-pause-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MP4IYSOMKJOTLM3CEMERKRUEFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 10:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特拉华州立法者在批评声中就公司法改革进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[特拉华州的立法者预计将于本周四投票通过对该州公司法的全面改革，以保护其有利于商业的声誉，但反对者称该法案是对亿万富翁的恩赐。【原文：Delaware lawmakers are expected to vote to overhaul the state's corporate law on Thursday to protect its business-friendly reputation, but opponents have called the bill a giveaway to billionaires.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/delaware-lawmakers-vote-corporate-law-overhaul-face-criticism-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3N6CUOZKJK3VAWSGZCS4MD6XM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 10:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[退伍军人事务部的调整扰乱了部分美国退伍军人的心理健康服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[乔伊-科尔特斯（Joey Cortez）曾在美国空军服役 24 年，自 8 月份以来，他一直在等待退伍军人事务部的心理健康专家为他看病，但就在这时，他又经历了一次新的焦虑。【原文：Joey Cortez, who served 24 years in the U.S. Air Force, had been waiting since August to see a mental health specialist from the Department of Veterans' Affairs, when he experienced a fresh jolt of anxiety.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/va-shake-up-disrupts-mental-health-services-some-us-veterans-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHXNFKX4XNPTJAGZSE5TSNNZBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 10:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拳击赢得 2028 年洛杉矶夏季奥运会参赛资格--国际奥委会]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，国际奥委会全票通过将拳击列入 2028 年洛杉矶奥运会项目，结束了多年来人们对拳击运动奥运前景的怀疑。【原文：Boxing was included on Thursday in the Los Angeles 2028 Olympics programme after a unanimous vote from the International Olympic Committee, ending years of doubt over the sport's Olympic future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/boxing-earns-spot-los-angeles-2028-summer-games-ioc-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62G6U7L5IJN6TDJIJR7WFSA5XU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:30:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拳击赢得 2028 年洛杉矶夏季奥运会参赛资格--国际奥委会]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，国际奥委会全票通过将拳击列入 2028 年洛杉矶奥运会项目，结束了多年来人们对拳击运动奥运前景的怀疑。【原文：Boxing was included on Thursday in the Los Angeles 2028 Olympics programme after a unanimous vote from the International Olympic Committee, ending years of doubt over the sport's Olympic future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/boxing-earns-spot-los-angeles-2028-summer-games-ioc-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62G6U7L5IJN6TDJIJR7WFSA5XU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:30:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国寻求驱逐亲巴勒斯坦的乔治敦大学学生]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府拘留了一名在华盛顿乔治城大学（Georgetown University）学习的印度男子，并在认为他对美国外交政策造成危害后试图将其驱逐出境。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has detained an Indian man studying at Washington's Georgetown University and is seeking to deport him after deeming him a harm to U.S. foreign policy, the student's lawyer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-seeks-deport-pro-palestinian-georgetown-university-student-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UPKEECWCZOMHHCF47V4BFS4E4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 02:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国寻求驱逐亲巴勒斯坦的乔治敦大学学生]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府拘留了一名在华盛顿乔治城大学（Georgetown University）学习的印度男子，并在认为他对美国外交政策造成危害后试图将其驱逐出境。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has detained an Indian man studying at Washington's Georgetown University and is seeking to deport him after deeming him a harm to U.S. foreign policy, the student's lawyer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-seeks-deport-pro-palestinian-georgetown-university-student-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UPKEECWCZOMHHCF47V4BFS4E4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 02:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[批评特朗普的联邦调查局特工被控共享机密文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，一名联邦调查局特工本周在纽约机场被捕，并被指控非法披露机密文件。【原文：An FBI agent who accused the bureau of political bias during Donald Trump’s first presidential term was arrested this week at a New York airport and charged with illegally disclosing confidential documents, court filings show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fbi-agent-who-criticized-trump-charged-with-sharing-confidential-documents-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOIR3GHBXZO6JLX3WBQ6IWGYYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 01:14:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达州市长撤销因电影院放映《无主之地》而驱逐电影院的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈阿密海滩市市长史蒂文-迈纳（Steven Meiner）周三表示，他放弃了因一家艺术影院放映奥斯卡获奖影片《没有别的土地》（No Other Land）而将其驱逐出城市地产的威胁。【原文：Miami Beach Mayor Steven Meiner said on Wednesday he dropped his threat to evict an art house cinema from city property for screening Oscar-winning "No Other Land," a film about the Israeli displacement of a Palestinian community in the Israeli-occupied West Bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/florida-mayor-drops-threat-evict-cinema-screening-no-other-land-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4AGXZ6WZJNNRNNDEUEZJ3VIAQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 23:48:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫呼吁最高法院约束阻碍特朗普议程的法官]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三抨击 "激进 "的联邦法官，并呼吁美国最高法院对他们进行约束，唐纳德-特朗普总统及其盟友对曾作出不利于其政府裁决的法官的攻击不断升级。【原文：The White House blasted "activist" federal judges and called on the U.S. Supreme Court to rein them in on Wednesday as President Donald Trump and his allies escalated their attacks against judges who have ruled against his administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-calls-supreme-court-rein-judges-blocking-trumps-agenda-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMVZB4DFAZOPZJUTJ46L4HVXPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 23:44:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国共和党议员对五角大楼可能进行的指挥权调整表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国国会领导五角大楼监督委员会的两位共和党议员周三罕见地发表了一份联合声明，对特朗普政府可能对美军司令部进行的调整表示震惊。【原文：The top two Republican lawmakers who lead the Pentagon's oversight committees in the U.S. Congress issued a rare, joint statement on Wednesday expressing alarm about a potential shake-up in U.S. military commands by the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-republican-lawmakers-voice-alarm-over-possible-pentagon-command-shake-up-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4UZ76UOWNNMFJWWYMJYIZ34AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 23:39:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称特朗普将签署命令关闭教育部]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将于周四签署一项行政命令，旨在关闭教育部，兑现竞选时的一项重要承诺。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will sign an executive order on Thursday that aims to shut down the Department of Education, fulfilling a key campaign pledge, the White House said in a fact sheet on the measure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-sign-order-shut-down-department-education-white-house-says-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZNBV6RSPRLGJCQCGHLNKK6L7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国因变性政策暂停资助宾夕法尼亚大学]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三表示，特朗普政府已因宾夕法尼亚大学的变性体育政策而暂停向该校提供 1.75 亿美元的资助，这是其迫使学校与其政策保持一致的最新努力。【原文：The Trump administration has suspended $175 million in funding to the University of Pennsylvania over its transgender sports policies, the White House said on Wednesday, its latest effort to force schools to fall in line with its policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-suspends-funding-university-pennsylvania-over-transgender-policy-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXFQLMGTH5LC3IZFESA46BRZJU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔：关税将推迟通胀进程，评估影响为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周三表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提高关税将推迟今年在降低通胀方面取得的进展，但美联储的基本判断是，与关税相关的价格影响将是短暂的，很快就会在经济中发挥作用。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said on Wednesday that President Donald Trump's tariff increases would delay progress in bringing down inflation this year, but the Fed's base case is that tariff-related price impacts will be transitory, working through the economy quickly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tariffs-delay-inflation-progress-too-soon-gauge-impact-feds-powell-says-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4CXLGLBG5NLDISGII6KBV64QM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:32:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）麾下 DOGE 成员在美国国际开发署（USAID）担任高级职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封电子邮件，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）政府效率部的一名成员将在美国国际开发署（U.S. Agency for International Development）担任高级职务，而在该机构解散过程中发挥了重要作用的皮特-马洛克（Pete Marocco）将重返国务院。【原文：A member of Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency will take up a top role at the U.S. Agency for International Development, while Pete Marocco, who played a major role in the dismantling of the agency, will return to the State Department, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/member-elon-musks-doge-takes-up-senior-post-usaid-email-says-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PS55AGT4AFKEDHU7AYZWS7MDG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:30:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州大学因预计特朗普削减开支而冻结招聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚大学校长周三表示，该校已在全系统范围内冻结招聘，并进行了额外的裁员，以努力减轻联邦资金大幅削减所带来的影响。【原文：The University of California has imposed a system-wide hiring freeze and made additional cuts, its president said on Wednesday, as part of efforts to try to mitigate the impact of sharp cuts in federal funding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/university-california-sets-hiring-freeze-anticipation-trump-cuts-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK4J43S7ZVM6FPSC5XCH4HSP34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:23:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院民主党人要求撤销疾控中心的大规模解雇决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院七名民主党人周三要求唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府恢复他上任以来解雇的美国疾病控制和预防中心的所有员工。【原文：Seven U.S. Senate Democrats demanded on Wednesday that President Donald Trump's administration reinstate all of the employees it fired from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention since he took office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-senate-democrats-demand-reversal-cdc-mass-firings-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LPHCOGKRZJ3BJYLZW2LN2WYXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国高端妓院网络头目被判入狱四年]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，大波士顿地区和华盛顿郊区一家高档妓院网络的经营者被判处四年监禁，该妓院的数百名顾客包括政客、公司高管、律师和军官。【原文：The operator of a high-end brothel network in the greater Boston area and the suburbs of Washington, whose hundreds of customers included politicians, corporate executives, lawyers and military officers, was sentenced on Wednesday to four years in prison.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ringleader-high-end-us-brothel-network-gets-4-years-prison-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HY7V5W6BZMIDMP2N3NRGOH3PI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院民主党人敦促特朗普撤销联邦贸易委员会的解雇决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[二十多位美国民主党参议员周三呼吁唐纳德-特朗普总统撤销解雇美国联邦贸易委员会两位民主党成员的决定。【原文：More than two dozen Democratic U.S. senators called on President Donald Trump on Wednesday to rescind his termination of the two Democratic members of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senate-democrats-urge-trump-reverse-federal-trade-commission-firings-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJJ4FUN2E5NILGBB366OUCXGHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:49:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官驳回禁止政府专家组接管 USIP 的临时令请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，一名美国法官驳回了一项临时命令的请求，该命令禁止唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府效率部（Donald Trump's cost-cutting Department of Government Efficiency）进一步接管美国和平研究所（U.S. Institute of Peace）。【原文：A U.S. judge on Wednesday denied a request for a temporary order barring President Donald Trump's cost-cutting Department of Government Efficiency from furthering any effort to take over the U.S. Institute of Peace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/judge-denies-request-temporary-order-bar-doge-usip-takeover-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QY5HTAXM7VN2XC2OYYHN2OIJZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:32:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局可能要求波音公司的 "星际客机 "进行第三次无人驾驶测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司的 "星际客机"（Starliner）太空舱去年在国际空间站上留下了两名美国国家航空航天局（NASA）宇航员，在再次搭载宇航员之前，波音公司可能需要进行第三次无人试飞，美国国家航空航天局的官员说，该太空船的第一批乘员本周必须乘坐 SpaceX 公司的太空舱返回地球。【原文：Boeing's troubled Starliner capsule that left two NASA astronauts on the International Space Station last year may need to fly a third uncrewed test flight before it carries astronauts again, agency officials said as the spacecraft's first crew had to return to Earth on a SpaceX capsule this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/nasa-may-require-boeings-starliner-fly-third-uncrewed-test-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BHQR4R625IGZJNPBWHM2D7BOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国律师事务所Paul Weiss因特朗普行政命令被客户解雇]]></title><description><![CDATA[律师事务所保罗-魏斯（Paul Weiss）周三在一份法庭文件中表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本月发布了针对该事务所的行政命令，一名面临刑事贿赂指控的前高管已解雇了该事务所作为其辩护律师的职位。【原文：Law firm Paul Weiss said in a court filing on Wednesday that a former executive facing criminal bribery charges has fired it as his defense counsel because of U.S. President Donald Trump's executive order this month targeting the firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-law-firm-paul-weiss-fired-by-client-over-trump-executive-order-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SL53SYKUYRN2TJDOJTVXYMAIDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国客运铁路公司 Amtrak 首席执行官突然下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amtrak 首席执行官斯蒂芬-加德纳（Stephen Gardner）周三表示，在担任美国客运铁路公司负责人四年多之后，他将立即卸任，理由是担心该公司无法继续得到唐纳德-特朗普总统政府的支持。【原文：Amtrak CEO Stephen Gardner said Wednesday he will step down immediately after more than four years as head of the U.S. passenger railroad, citing concerns about maintaining the carrier's support from President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-passenger-railroad-amtrak-ceo-abruptly-steps-down-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5T35EFT5IRK4BMNBPGX3NDNYS4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:20:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称让联邦贸易委员会委员离职的 "时机已到]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普解雇联邦贸易委员会两位民主党委员的决定辩护，称让他们离职的 "时机已经成熟"。【原文：The White House on Wednesday defended U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to fire two Democratic commissioners at the Federal Trade Commission, saying the "time was right" to let them go.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-says-time-was-right-let-ftc-commissioners-go-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEE72XU4OBJMXM4MUM63R2KAVM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会起诉特朗普政府停止学生贷款偿还计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一个主要的教师工会对教育部提起诉讼，指控共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府非法关闭了数百万学生贷款者使用的收入驱动还款计划。【原文：A major U.S. teachers union has filed a lawsuit against the Department of Education accusing Republican President Donald Trump's administration of unlawfully shutting down access to income-driven repayment plans used by millions of student loan borrowers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/union-sues-trump-administration-halting-student-loan-repayment-plans-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFEJQ3XSRZNUVEDWHGLW2NKNBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:52:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对峙之后，法官拒绝禁止 DOGE 进入美国和平研究所]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国和平研究所指控马斯克团队的成员强行占领大楼之后，一名联邦法官周三允许科技亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的政府效率部（Department of Government Efficiency）接管美国和平研究所。【原文：A federal judge on Wednesday allowed the takeover of the U.S. Institute of Peace by tech billionaire Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency, after USIP accused members of Musk's team of occupying the building by force.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-institute-peace-sues-trump-doge-over-executive-order-firings-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJ6IYDUJUVPIDPCUIU7C7YPFCY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:39:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府指责法官在委内瑞拉驱逐案中越权行事]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国首席大法官约翰-罗伯茨（John Roberts）斥责共和党总统要求弹劾一名联邦法官之后一天，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周三在一份文件中指责一名联邦法官越权要求提供有关委内瑞拉移民驱逐航班的更多细节。【原文：Donald Trump's administration accused a federal judge on Wednesday of overstepping his judicial authority in demanding more details about deportation flights of Venezuelan migrants in a filing made a day after U.S. Chief Justice John Roberts rebuked the Republican president for calling for the judge's impeachment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-accuses-judge-overstepping-venezuela-deportations-case-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7D6FQVFJ75L5NOH4INGRIPNUEE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将于 2026 年底前在 74 个机场安装跑道安全技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）表示，到 2026 年底，将在 74 个机场安装增强型安全技术，帮助检测跑道入侵。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said it will install enhanced safety technology to help detect runway incursions at 74 airports by the end of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-install-runway-safety-technology-74-airports-by-end-2026-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMCEUSKWG5KD3DUY44M36V7HN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:50:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发布州和地方备灾行政命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周三发布了一项行政命令，涉及州和地方基础设施应对野火和飓风等自然灾害以及网络攻击等其他威胁的准备工作。【原文：President Donald Trump issued an executive order on Wednesday related to state and local infrastructure preparedness for responding to natural disasters such as wildfires and hurricanes, along with other threats like cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-issues-state-local-preparedness-executive-order-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNWFEFRXDFJJRAXSDLEH5FO2GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 放宽部分处方药续保规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）旗下的药房福利管理公司 Optum Rx 周三表示，将放宽续订约 80 种药物处方时获得保险授权的要求，旨在减少患者和医生的文书工作。【原文：UnitedHealth Group's pharmacy benefit manager, Optum Rx, said on Wednesday it would ease requirements to get insurance authorization when renewing prescriptions on about 80 drugs, aiming to reduce paperwork for patients and doctors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealths-unit-reduces-prescription-reauthorization-requirements-by-up-25-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6ONDKOQ2BPXFL2O5RB3FVXYII</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>