<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 00:22:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 00:22:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国打击伊朗关键核设施后，石油价格创五个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于华盛顿周末与以色列联手攻击伊朗核设施的举动激起了对供应的担忧，石油价格周一跃升至一月份以来的最高点。【原文：Oil prices jumped on Monday to their highest since January as Washington's weekend move to join Israel in attacking Iran's nuclear facilities stoked supply worries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-hits-five-month-high-after-us-hits-key-iranian-nuclear-sites-2025-06-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYXCHIAJFBNMDMTKNQHVCRJIHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 00:16:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球等待伊朗回应，亚洲股市下跌，石油上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，华尔街股票期货下滑，油价短暂触及五个月高点，投资者焦急地等待着伊朗是否会对美国袭击其核基地进行报复，从而给全球经济活动和通货膨胀带来风险。【原文：Wall Street share futures slipped on Monday and oil prices briefly hit five-month highs as investors anxiously waited to see if Iran would retaliate to U.S. attacks on its nuclear sites, with resulting risks to global activity and inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCRCRJCMCZPCHFFKIFEGNTSYBM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 23:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新闻集团称将与首席执行官续约至 2030 年 6 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[新闻集团在周日的一份声明中表示，将与首席执行官罗伯特-汤姆森续约，他将继续担任首席执行官至 2030 年 6 月。【原文：News Corp said it is extending the contract of Chief Executive Robert Thomson, which will see him continue as CEO through June 2030, the company said in a statement on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/news-corp-extend-ceos-contract-through-june-2030-company-says-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YE6L7XFZQZOIFOPBBINHWNL44A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 22:02:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国将在新工业战略中削减企业能源开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国将根据周一公布的新工业战略，致力于削减数千家公司的电费，以响应企业界降低高昂能源成本的呼吁。【原文：Britain will aim to cut the electricity bills of thousands of companies under a new industrial strategy to be published on Monday, heeding calls from business to lower high energy costs that they say have damaged competitiveness and hindered growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/britain-cut-companies-energy-bills-new-industrial-strategy-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQI5DZYNLBLG7PRK7FNCDB4VTA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 21:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉的机器人出租车如何与 Waymo 和 Zoox 竞争？]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商特斯拉周日在德克萨斯州奥斯汀市开始试运行其期待已久的机器人出租车服务，这是与 Alphabet 旗下 Waymo 公司摊牌的第一步，后者是目前唯一一家在美国提供全自动付费乘车服务的公司。【原文：Electric car maker Tesla started a trial of its long-awaited robotaxi service in Austin, Texas, on Sunday, the first step toward what could be a showdown with Alphabet's Waymo, the only player currently offering fully autonomous paid rides in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/how-teslas-robotaxi-efforts-stack-up-against-waymo-zoox-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYD3L33OTRKO3LBHQY2O4JVRN4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 21:22:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，纽约梅隆银行与北方信托接触，商讨潜在合并事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周日报道，纽约梅隆银行上周与北方信托公司进行了接触，表达了与其规模较小的竞争对手合并的兴趣。【原文：Bank of New York Mellon Corp approached Northern Trust last week to express interest in merging with its smaller rival, the Wall Street Journal reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-new-york-mellon-approached-northern-trust-discuss-potential-merger-wsj-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKVHYYRX4NIVHCGECS5VHWIUEM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:22:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克表示，机器人出租车将于周日下午在德克萨斯州奥斯汀市启动]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周日表示，特斯拉已开始在得克萨斯州奥斯汀测试机器人出租车，乘客只需支付 4.20 美元的统一费用，这家电动汽车制造商希望推出这一备受期待的服务，并在自动驾驶技术竞赛中占据一席之地。【原文：Tesla has started testing robotaxis with passengers in Austin, Texas, CEO Elon Musk said on Sunday, with customers paying a flat fee of $4.20, as the electric vehicle maker looks to roll out the much-anticipated service and gain a foothold in the self-driving technology race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-says-robotaxi-launch-austin-texas-sunday-afternoon-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNVSNGYQ5BOIZEJTUVPCNNUUSY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币下跌 4%，至 99,237 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国东部时间周日上午10:52（北京时间14:52），全球市值最大的加密货币比特币下跌4.13%，报99,237美元。【原文：Bitcoin, the world's largest cryptocurrency by market value, was down by 4.13% at $99,237 at 10:52 a.m. ET (1452 GMT) on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bitcoin-falls-4-99237-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2WHM3W5CJNLFK3HTAX5D57K6I</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 15:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德实验性减肥药的数据显示副作用大多较轻]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德公司周日表示，其试验性减肥药CagriSema的两项后期试验的全部结果显示，副作用主要是轻度至中度，包括血糖水平在内的其他结果都是积极的。【原文：Novo Nordisk on Sunday said full results from two late-stage trials of its experimental weight-loss drug CagriSema show that side effects were mainly mild-to-moderate and other outcome results, including blood sugar levels, were positive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/data-novo-nordisk-experimental-weight-loss-drug-show-mostly-mild-side-effects-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JO3JRPPLWVNJHKGDHHUH7FBEF4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基公司表示将继续在霍尔木兹海峡航行]]></title><description><![CDATA[马士基集团在周日的一份声明中说，马士基公司的船只继续通过霍尔木兹海峡航行，但在美国一夜之间袭击伊朗核设施之后，该公司准备根据现有信息重新评估这一做法。【原文：Maersk vessels continue to sail through the Strait of Hormuz but the company was ready to re-evaluate this based on available information, the group said in a statement on Sunday, following U.S. strikes on Iranian nuclear facilities overnight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/maersk-continues-sail-through-strait-hormuz-company-says-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4B2S4DVYVN7JIAWAD6UJYKFEQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 12:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国打击伊朗提高供应风险溢价，石油将高开]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场分析师说，在美国周末袭击伊朗之后，石油在周日晚间恢复交易时每桶可能上涨3-5美元，只有在伊朗采取强硬报复行动并导致石油供应严重中断的情况下，涨势才有望加快。【原文：Oil is likely to rise by $3-5 per barrel when trading resumes on Sunday evening after the U.S. attacked Iran at the weekend, market analysts said, with gains expected to accelerate only if Iran retaliates hard and causes a major oil supply disruption.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-open-higher-us-strikes-iran-boost-supply-risk-premium-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JRNZDTFRTBNK5LGDY3DTW7NYAI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 11:42:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉涉足承诺已久的机器人出租车服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）对特斯拉未来的设想将于周日进行公开测试，届时德克萨斯州奥斯汀的十几辆自动驾驶汽车将开始提供有限的付费机器人出租车服务。【原文：Elon Musk's vision of Tesla's future is set for a public test on Sunday, when a dozen or so self-driving cars in Austin, Texas start a limited, paid robotaxi service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-tiptoes-into-long-promised-robotaxi-service-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YM45DC6BR5P27GZM72P2FTKBJY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国将向美国提出对芯片制造商在华业务可能受限的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国最高贸易谈判代表周日表示，他本周在华盛顿与美国官员就关税谈判进行第三轮技术性讨论时，将提出对美国可能限制中国芯片制造商的担忧。【原文：South Korea's top trade negotiator said on Sunday he would raise concerns about potential U.S. restrictions on chipmakers in China when he meets U.S. officials in Washington this week for the third round of technical discussions in tariff talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/south-korea-raise-concerns-us-over-potential-curbs-chipmakers-china-operations-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JX7SBOMH5JKXTHZIIG7PUG3VZM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:32:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递称创始人弗雷德里克-史密斯已去世]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递公司（FedEx Corp）的创始人兼前首席执行官弗雷德里克-史密斯（Frederick Smith）于上周六去世。【原文：FedEx Corp's founder and former CEO, Frederick Smith, has died, the logistics giant said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fedex-says-founder-frederick-smith-has-died-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGVR34JPYZL6FLKVEQNHOGQXP4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 04:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对美国袭击伊朗核场址的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周六表示，对伊朗三个核基地的攻击 "非常成功"。特朗普在 "真理社交 "网站上发帖补充说，"所有飞机都在安全返航的途中"，他在帖子的最后说，"现在是和平的时刻"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Saturday said that a "very successful attack" on three nuclear sites in Iran had been carried out. In a posting on Truth Social, Trump added, "All planes are safely on their way home" and he ended his posting saying, "Now is the time for peace."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/view-investors-react-us-attack-iran-nuclear-sites-2025-06-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAYE4LEPZ5MKRDVOE5V2UUCIKY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:44:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国将发布旨在促进增长的十年工业战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国准备在下周公布一项为期 10 年、耗资数十亿英镑的工业战略，旨在支持重点行业、创造就业机会并推动长期经济增长。【原文：Britain is poised to publish a 10-year, multibillion-pound industrial strategy next week aimed at backing priority sectors, creating jobs and driving long-term economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/uk-issue-10-year-industrial-strategy-aimed-boosting-growth-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QTFPAXEF5LFJAVMTEULD7LFSU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:14:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司预计第三季度将取得orforglipron肥胖症治疗成果]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周六表示，其试验性药片orforglipron有助于糖尿病患者减轻体重和降低血糖，该公司计划在第三季度公布该药在无糖尿病的超重和肥胖人群中的试验结果。【原文：Eli Lilly said on Saturday its experimental pill orforglipron helped diabetics lose weight and lower their blood sugar, and the company aims to announce in the third quarter trial results for the drug in overweight and obese people without diabetes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-expects-orforglipron-obesity-results-third-quarter-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRPTTRWMJJLHXF26PYJWCC2DBE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 13:06:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[教皇利奥警告政治家们人工智能带来的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[教皇利奥周六警告政治家们人工智能（AI）的兴起所带来的挑战，并将其对年轻人的潜在影响作为首要关注点。【原文：Pope Leo warned politicians on Saturday of the challenges posed by the rise of artificial intelligence (AI), addressing its potential impact on younger people as a prime concern.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/pope-leo-warns-politicians-challenges-posed-by-ai-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APTKHGK4KFO5ZPVOBJ4EN4CMT4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:38:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国科技公司拥抱特朗普，欧洲人寻求 "数字主权]]></title><description><![CDATA[在柏林一个由慈善机构 Topio 经营的市场摊位上，志愿者们帮助人们清除手机中受美国科技公司影响的内容。自唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）就职以来，排队寻求他们服务的人越来越多。【原文：At a market stall in Berlin run by charity Topio, volunteers help people who want to purge their phones of the influence of U.S. tech firms. Since Donald Trump's inauguration, the queue for their services has grown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/europeans-seek-digital-sovereignty-us-tech-firms-embrace-trump-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72W7V27TCVKMTHNOL3K4XSK7GQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东紧张局势令投资者提高警惕，权衡最坏情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果美国进一步卷入中东冲突，投资者正在考虑一系列不同的市场情景，如果能源价格暴涨，可能会产生连锁反应。【原文：Investors are mulling a host of different market scenarios should the U.S. deepen its involvement in the Middle East conflict, with the potential for ripple effects if energy prices skyrocket.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/middle-east-tensions-put-investors-alert-weighing-worst-case-scenarios-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UZI2C37ZFMUDMXZU4N4HUDJOQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 05:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾央行称美国债务增长过快可能影响对国债的信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾央行行长周六警告说，美国债务的快速上升可能对美国国债的前景 "不利"，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易政策也让投资者变得谨慎。【原文：Taiwan's central bank governor warned on Saturday that rapidly rising U.S. debt could be "unfavourable" to the outlook for U.S. Treasuries and that U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies have made investors cautious.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-central-bank-says-us-debt-rising-too-fast-may-impact-trust-treasuries-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAGZPPZQOZJDHHFDIJEY3DZRUQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:16:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国首席贸易特使计划于 6 月 22 日至 27 日访问美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国贸易部周六表示，韩国贸易部长杨汉九将于 6 月 22 日至 27 日访问美国。【原文：South Korea's trade minister Yeo Han-koo will visit the United States from June 22 to 27, the trade ministry said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-koreas-chief-trade-envoy-plans-us-visit-june-22-27-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75E6KNX6DJNJVM3OLJWTNJZJ3E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，丰田将从 7 月起将美国汽车价格上调 200 多美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，日本汽车制造商丰田汽车公司将从7月起把在美国销售的部分汽车价格提高200多美元。【原文：Japanese carmaker Toyota Motor Corp will raise prices of some vehicles it sells in the U.S. by more than $200 from July, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-raise-us-auto-prices-by-more-than-200-july-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBCJ3OUYEJKHFPXLFS3FE7DF3Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称马拉松公司正在评估得克萨斯州加尔维斯顿湾炼油厂的受损情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉工厂运营情况的人士称，马拉松石油公司周五继续评估其位于得克萨斯州得克萨斯城、日产 63.1 万桶的加尔维斯顿湾炼油厂（Galveston Bay Refinery）因 6 月 14 日火灾而关闭的残余加氢装置（RHU）所遭受的损失。【原文：Marathon Petroleum continued assessing damage on Friday to the shut residual hydrotreating unit (RHU) at its 631,000-barrel-per-day (bpd) Galveston Bay Refinery in Texas City, Texas, from a June 14 fire, said people familiar with plant operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/marathon-assessing-damage-galveston-bay-texas-refinery-sources-say-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">77ZESKRYLVIYZNTIGASCLEEYN4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国之音母公司再解雇 600 多名员工，可能敲响丧钟]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国之音的母机构周五表示，已向超过 639 名员工发出解聘通知，自 3 月份以来人员减少了 85%，这实际上意味着一个为反纳粹宣传而成立的广播网络的终结。【原文：The parent agency of Voice of America said on Friday it had issued termination notices to over 639 more staff, completing an 85% decrease in personnel since March and effectively spelling the end of a broadcasting network founded to counter Nazi propaganda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/voice-america-parent-terminates-over-600-more-staff-likely-death-knell-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QECOUVU5FZITNNYPVCNAXNIFNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 23:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称可能不得不改变解雇美联储主席鲍威尔的主意]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他可能不得不改变解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的想法。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he may have to change his mind about firing Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-he-may-have-change-his-mind-about-firing-fed-chair-powell-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75F7I5BQKVLY5CBHLPZQOINRDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 22:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府表示暂停执行拜登时代的农民工规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周五表示，将暂停执行前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）政府的一项农民工规定，并称该规定 "负担沉重"。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration said on Friday it was suspending enforcement of a farmworker rule from former President Joe Biden's administration while labeling that rule as "burdensome."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trump-administration-says-it-is-suspending-enforcement-biden-era-farmworker-rule-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVUITCXSPFMPDBGVYMM54FORHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 22:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果公司高管就收购 Perplexity 举行了内部会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，苹果公司高管已经就竞购人工智能初创公司Perplexity的可能性举行了内部会谈。【原文：Apple executives have held internal talks about potentially bidding for artificial intelligence startup Perplexity, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-executives-held-internal-talks-about-buying-perplexity-bloomberg-news-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AT2PWCHU5NNTLNTEGSEHOC7ITQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:31:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国高速公路安全官员审查特斯拉的机器人出租车部署计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）上个月曾致函特斯拉，就其部署自动驾驶机器人出租车的计划提出问题，特斯拉已对此作出回应。【原文：Tesla has responded to a letter the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration sent last month asking questions about its plans to deploy its self driving robotaxi, the agency said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-highway-safety-officials-reviewing-teslas-robotaxi-deployment-plans-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FT4ZENA4NNRVPNRO26SZZDNGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛支付 1,000 万美元了结美国联邦贸易委员会有关汇款欺诈的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛已同意支付 1,000 万美元，以了结美国联邦贸易委员会的民事诉讼，该诉讼指控这家全球最大的零售商忽视了欺诈者利用其汇款服务骗取消费者数亿美元的警告信号。【原文：Walmart has agreed to pay $10 million to settle a U.S. Federal Trade Commission civil lawsuit accusing the world's largest retailer of ignoring warning signs that fraudsters used its money transfer services to fleece consumers out of hundreds of millions of dollars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/walmart-pay-10-million-settle-us-ftc-lawsuit-over-money-transfer-fraud-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMQTDHDNTNO4RIZKGLVR46YSYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>