<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 06:06:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 06:06:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚批准 Chemist Warehouse-Sigma Healthcare 58 亿美元的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚竞争监管机构周四批准了私营连锁药店 Chemist Warehouse 对 Sigma Healthcare 的反向收购，为经过长达一年的等待后成立一家价值 88 亿澳元（约合 57.8 亿美元）的实体铺平了道路。【原文：The Australian competition regulator, on Thursday, cleared privately owned pharmacy chain Chemist Warehouse's reverse takeover of Sigma Healthcare , paving the way to create an A$8.8 billion ($5.78 billion) entity after a year-long wait.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/australia-clears-chemist-warehouse-sigma-healthcare-58-bln-deal-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPNW6PREWZPGXFESPXHZ63355I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 05:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长称泰国将受益于任何中美贸易战]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国商业部长披差-那立他潘周四表示，泰国经济将从任何中美贸易战中获益，并补充说，东南亚国家与中美两国关系良好，无需在争端中偏袒任何一方。【原文：Thailand's economy stands to gain from any U.S.-China trade war, Thai Commerce Minister Pichai Naripthaphan said on Thursday, adding the Southeast Asian country had good relations with both nations and would not need to take sides in a dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thailand-would-benefit-any-us-china-trade-war-says-minister-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKI5P665CBNZHN4OS74APTGZJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 05:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标德国政治剧增加特朗普给欧洲带来的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2J66KVLYNNS5CHL3USUJCJD3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 05:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息称波音和空客将共享台湾华航客机订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内消息人士告诉路透社，台湾的中华航空公司即将决定在空中客车公司和波音公司之间拆分价值数十亿美元的长途客机订单，而货机订单则悬而未决。【原文：Taiwan's China Airlines is nearing a decision to split a multi-billion-dollar order for long-distance passenger jets between Airbus and Boeing, while an order for freighters hangs in the balance, industry sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-airbus-share-taiwans-china-airlines-passenger-jet-order-sources-say-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2SKPS2TSVNYXA4ARPMHFJFPKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 04:15:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普影响，亚洲股市涨跌不一；美联储决议前美元坚挺]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚太股市周四涨跌不一，投资者在权衡唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）就任总统的影响的同时，也在关注美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）和其他主要央行在当天晚些时候做出的货币政策决定。【原文：Asia-Pacific equity markets were mixed on Thursday as investors weighed the implications of a Donald Trump presidency, while also eyeing monetary policy decisions from the U.S. Federal Reserve and other major central banks later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEHSLE3SGFK4NJ47NA2O63NF5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 04:12:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普胜选加剧日本央行风险，日元再度下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在美国总统大选中获胜引发的美元反弹，可能会加大日本央行的压力，迫使其尽快在 12 月加息，以防止日元跌回三十年来的低点。【原文：A dollar rally triggered by Republican Donald Trump's victory in the U.S. presidential election could heighten pressure on the Bank of Japan to raise interest rates as soon as December to prevent the yen from sliding back toward three-decade lows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/trump-victory-heightens-risks-boj-yen-renews-slide-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERIRKQWNYBIRFBPLKBP7RMFADQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 04:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与西方国家的贸易战迫在眉睫，中国 10 月出口超预期增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于预计美国和欧盟将进一步加征关税，制造商急于将库存运往主要出口市场，更广泛的贸易战威胁迫在眉睫，中国10月份的出货量创下两年多来的最快增速。【原文：China's outbound shipments grew at the fastest pace in over two years in October as manufacturers rushed inventory to major export markets in anticipation of further tariffs from the U.S. and the European Union, with the threat of a broader trade war looming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-oct-exports-soar-past-forecast-trade-war-with-west-looms-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMLOWEDIYVOYHBST2WCFFOSCHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 04:01:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普当选总统对亚洲企业的利害关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）当选为美国总统，为他在被选出白宫四年后的出色回归画上了圆满的句号。【原文：Donald Trump has been elected U.S. president, capping a remarkable comeback four years after he was voted out of the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/whats-stake-asian-companies-trump-presidency-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DWHEU3IP5KSRPHNVPTOMRVTFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 04:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鉴于特朗普可能征收关税，台湾将帮助企业从中国转移]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾经济部长郭台铭（Kuo Jyh-huei）周四表示，鉴于即将上任的美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）承诺对中国征收的关税可能对企业造成巨大影响，台湾将帮助企业从中国转移生产。【原文：Taiwan will help companies relocate production from China given the likely large impact on them from tariffs incoming U.S. President Donald Trump has promised to impose on the country, Economy Minister Kuo Jyh-huei said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-will-help-companies-move-china-given-likely-trump-tariffs-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTCB3BHI65L7LIZKZMRGYBBHZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 03:25:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓集团高管要求特朗普政府加快审批速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓集团（Rio Tinto）的一位高管周四在谈到其停滞不前的亚利桑那州铜矿时说，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的新政府应把重点放在加快许可程序上，以确保有足够的铜用于能源转型。【原文：U.S. president-elect Donald Trump's new administration should focus on speeding up the permitting process to ensure there is enough copper for the energy transition, said a Rio Tinto executive on Thursday, referring to its stalled Arizona mine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/rio-tinto-exec-asks-trump-administration-speed-up-permitting-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTYFBC5S5JJ5LAEDBIYTPGTS3M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 03:24:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[头号出口国越南为特朗普带来的波动做好准备，不确定性占据上风]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南官员和供应链专家告诉路透社记者，特朗普新总统上台后，越南将面临贸易波动，因为越南可能从中美贸易紧张局势加剧中受益，但也可能成为美国保护主义措施的 "附带损害"。【原文：Vietnam faces trade volatility with a new Trump presidency, officials and supply chain experts told Reuters, as the country could benefit from increased U.S.-China trade tensions but may also become "collateral damage" of U.S. protectionist measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uncertainty-prevails-top-exporter-vietnam-braces-volatility-with-trump-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQNA24SAMVL6JFSXALBL45CVM4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 03:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在 160 亿美元 YPF 判决纠纷中站在阿根廷一边]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府站在阿根廷一边，敦促联邦法官不要强迫这个资金短缺的国家放弃其在石油和天然气公司 YPF 51% 的股份，以部分履行 161 亿美元的法院判决。【原文：The U.S. government sided with Argentina in urging a federal judge not to force the cash-strapped country to give up its 51% stake in oil and gas company YPF to partially satisfy a $16.1 billion court judgment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sides-with-argentina-dispute-over-16-billion-ypf-judgment-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3B3HYTCHVMFPGQQHV2TEUO2OY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 01:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者关注美国大选余波，油价重拾升势]]></title><description><![CDATA[继美国总统大选引发的抛售之后，油价周四有所上扬，原因是特朗普就任总统和墨西哥湾沿岸飓风对石油供应造成的风险超过了美元走强和库存增加的影响。【原文：Oil prices edged up on Thursday following a sell-off triggered by the U.S. presidential election, as risks to oil supply from a Trump presidency and a hurricane building in the Gulf Coast outweighed a stronger U.S. dollar and higher inventories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-regain-ground-investors-eye-us-election-fallout-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJUUU4MLMRLQJASDQBHVGQDW74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 01:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行和美联储决议公布前，美元坚挺令同业受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场继续消化共和党人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在美国总统大选中获胜的消息，美元周四在四个月高点附近徘徊，而投资者则在关注美联储即将做出的几项央行决定。【原文：The dollar hovered off a four-month high on Thursday as the market continued to digest Republican Donald Trump's win in the U.S. presidential election, while investors eyed several central bank decisions that will be topped off by the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/firm-dollar-keeps-peers-back-foot-ahead-boe-fed-decisions-2024-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPXVGQG27BLQPNS4WHSAJLTKSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商为特朗普上台后的新关税和电动汽车变革做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业协会和高管表示，汽车制造商正准备应对当选总统唐纳德-特朗普对来自墨西哥和可能来自其他国家的汽车征收新关税，并推翻许多现有的支持电动汽车的政策。【原文：Automakers are bracing for President-elect Donald Trump to impose new tariffs on vehicles from Mexico and potentially from other countries and to reverse many existing pro-electric vehicle policies, industry associations and executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/automakers-brace-new-tariffs-ev-changes-under-trump-presidency-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTK7PTPWD5KE5JNHZ5WAYLUWAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 23:25:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[S3 表示，特朗普媒体做空者损失 4.2 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融分析公司 S3 Partners 周三发布的一份报告显示，自特朗普媒体&amp; 科技集团的股票开始追踪唐纳德-特朗普的当选赔率以来，押注该股的投资者已经损失了 4.2 亿美元。【原文：Investors betting against Trump Media &amp; Technology Group have lost $420 million since the stock began tracking the election odds of Donald Trump, according to a report released on Wednesday by financial analytics firm S3 Partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-media-short-sellers-hammered-by-420-million-loss-s3-says-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LUCIPXC65KA3K3EQSKO4PRLVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 23:21:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息来源：GlobalFoundries 准备获得芯片法案的最终奖项]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士透露，GlobalFoundries 和至少两家其他芯片制造商即将获得拜登政府颁发的《芯片与科学法案》最终奖项。【原文：GlobalFoundries and at least two other chipmakers are poised to receive their final Chips and Science Act awards from the Biden administration, a person briefed on the matter said, a sign of progress amid growing concerns about the pace of the award rollout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/globalfoundries-poised-get-final-chips-act-award-source-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISGMSF2ZCBP2BL6FJE77HRU5WY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 23:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团称，特朗普胜选可能在 2025 年前对油价造成压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行（Citi）周三预测，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的第二个任期可能会在2025年之前对石油造成下行压力，预计布伦特原油平均价格为每桶60美元，主要原因是潜在的贸易关税和石油供应增加。【原文：Citi forecasted on Wednesday that U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's second term could exert downward pressure on oil through 2025, with Brent crude forecasted to average at $60 per barrel, primarily due to potential trade tariffs and increased oil supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trumps-victory-may-pressure-oil-prices-through-2025-citi-says-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVADM73CCVPAFG3IAFEYU2VWAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 23:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行称美国大选对澳大利亚通胀的影响尚难判断]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚最高央行行长周四表示，现阶段很难判断美国大选对澳大利亚通胀的影响，但决策者将密切关注并在必要时做出反应。【原文：Australia's top central banker said on Thursday it was hard to judge the inflation implications of the U.S. election for Australia at this stage, but policymakers would be watching closely and responding as necessary.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rba-says-inflation-implications-us-election-australia-hard-judge-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYW5PAL7YFJ7JFEXUUAAIPMQDA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 23:07:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，半数日本企业计划在 2025 年将工资提高 3% 或更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项调查显示，略多于半数的日本公司希望在下一个营业年度将工资提高 3% 或更多，但大多数公司对首相石破茂提出的在五年内将最低工资提高 40% 以上的要求表示反对。【原文：Slightly more than half of Japanese firms are looking to raise wages by 3% or more for the next business year, a Reuters survey showed, but a majority of companies baulked at Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba's quest to hike minimum pay by over 40% in five years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/half-japan-firms-target-wage-hike-3-or-more-2025-reuters-survey-shows-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISKYKHB6DJOX7G233766SWVGNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 23:07:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡银行星展集团第三季度净利润同比增长15%，创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡最大的银行星展集团周四发表声明称，在总收入增长的推动下，该集团第三季度净利润同比增长15%，达到30.3亿新元（22.7亿美元），创历史新高。【原文：DBS Group , Singapore's biggest bank, posted on Thursday a 15% jump in net profit in the third quarter from a year earlier to a record high of S$3.03 billion ($2.27 billion) driven by total income growth, according to a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/singapore-bank-dbs-groups-third-quarter-net-profit-jumps-15-year-record-high-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TH42IP4DB5K2FLGA2DZOEWRSFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 22:47:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Evercore ISI 认为标准普尔 500 指数到 2025 年中期将达到 6600 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[Evercore ISI 周三预测，到 2025 年年中，S&amp;P 500 指数将升至 6,600 点，并称唐纳德-特朗普 "决定性地、毫无争议地 "赢得美国总统选举，共和党可能大获全胜，"这是谁也无法预料的"。【原文：Evercore ISI on Wednesday forecast the S&amp;P 500 will rise to 6,600 by mid-2025, saying a "decisive and uncontested" win by Donald Trump as U.S. president and a potential Republican sweep "was nobody's base case."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/evercore-isi-sees-sp-500-6600-by-mid-2025-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQLWANKNGRKIVP2GKKHHIJV56I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 22:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车需求疲软，芯片制造商 Wolfspeed 预计营收低于预期，股价下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wolfspeed 公司周三预测的季度收入低于预期，并表示将因计划关闭一家工厂而计提 1.74 亿美元的重组费用，因为这家芯片制造商正在应对汽车客户的低迷需求。【原文：Wolfspeed forecast quarterly revenue below estimates on Wednesday and said it would book $174 million in restructuring charges for the planned closure of a facility, as the chipmaker deals with sluggish demand from automotive customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmaker-wolfspeed-projects-revenue-below-estimates-weak-auto-demand-shares-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EURL5SU3NOCZKNZUUL5MP62XI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 22:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于大片减少，AMC 娱乐公司收入下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[AMC 娱乐公司周三报告称，受好莱坞电影公司大片上映数量减少的影响，其连锁影院第三季度收入下降，上座率下降。【原文：AMC Entertainment on Wednesday reported a fall in third-quarter revenue and saw a decline in attendance at its theater chain, hurt by fewer blockbuster releases from Hollywood studios.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/amc-entertainment-posts-revenue-decline-due-fewer-big-releases-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZVAQXVETZP2LPNKDJHCYRGH34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 22:14:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[产量增加，马拉松石油公司第三季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国页岩油生产商马拉松石油公司（Marathon Oil）周三公布的第三季度利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于产量增加和石油需求的恢复性增长。【原文：U.S. shale producer Marathon Oil beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter profit on Wednesday, helped by higher production and resilient demand for oil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/marathon-oil-beats-q3-profit-estimates-higher-production-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IC7QMT2FOFP73BZK32D7U7R6AU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 22:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大下令清盘 TikTok 加拿大业务，但仍可继续使用应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大周三以国家安全风险为由，下令关闭 TikTok 在该国的业务，但补充说，政府并未阻止加拿大人访问这款短视频应用，也未阻止他们创建内容。【原文：Canada on Wednesday ordered the wind up of TikTok's business in the country citing national security risks, but added the government was not blocking Canadians' access to the short-video app or their ability to create content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/canada-orders-wind-up-tiktoks-canadian-business-app-access-continue-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ3ZBDKBAFLFVDJND63N2XJ5XE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 22:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价为美国收益率、美元和通胀走高做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-pix-graphic-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FOWBQFYGFPTVEH4ZY2SRSQGUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 21:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行年度利润因竞争和成本压力而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行（National Australia Bank）周四公布的年度现金利润下降，基本符合市场预期，因为这家澳大利亚第二大银行正在努力应对激烈的住房贷款竞争和不断攀升的存款成本。【原文：National Australia Bank on Thursday reported a decline in annual cash profit, largely in line with market expectations, as the country's second-largest lender grappled with intense home-lending competition and escalating deposit costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/national-australia-bank-annual-profit-falls-competition-costs-bite-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTQMJNXS2RNDVMBVEKY6ZAR6XA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 21:43:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众美容需求放缓，Coty 年度利润低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[科蒂公司（Coty）周三表示，由于美国和澳大利亚等主要市场对美容产品的需求疲软，抵消了香水业务的增长，预计全年利润将低于预期。【原文：Coty on Wednesday said it expects annual profit to come in at the low end of its forecast, as weak demand for beauty products in major markets such as the United States and Australia offset gains in the fragrance segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coty-sees-annual-profit-low-end-forecast-mass-beauty-demand-slows-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MHU7D3QL5IELOGPOMSLNH4ZGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 21:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Corteva 季度业绩不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受南美作物保护产品需求疲软的影响，美国农用化学品公司 Corteva 周三公布的第三季度利润未达预期。【原文：U.S. agrichemicals firm Corteva missed third-quarter profit estimates on Wednesday, hurt by weak demand for crop protection products in South America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/corteva-misses-quarterly-estimates-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGF4HNA3QNJKXIFFUVNJUMAKEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 21:25:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>