<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 04:35:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 04:35:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行的小森表示，外国竞购日本公司的热潮才刚刚开始]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行日本投资银行业务联席主管 Yuta Komori 表示，外国对日本公司的收购要约很可能会加速，重点是那些管理层发生重大变化的公司。【原文：A surge in foreign takeover bids for Japanese firms is likely to accelerate, with a focus on those undergoing significant change in management, said Bank of America's co-head of Japan investment banking, Yuta Komori.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/surge-foreign-bids-japanese-firms-only-just-beginning-says-bofas-komori-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WN6OQYFS2FMIDO4OTPTIVYNM7U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 03:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚经济陷入慢车道，家庭支出拖后腿]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于惩罚性借贷成本和顽固的通货膨胀挤压了消费者，政府支出成为经济增长的主要驱动力，澳大利亚经济在 6 月份仍处于低迷状态。【原文：Australia's economy stayed stuck in the slow lane in the June quarter as punishing borrowing costs and stubborn inflation squeezed consumers, leaving government spending as the main driver of growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-economy-grows-meagre-02-q2-household-spending-drags-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFJ7PAQ4VNNM5KLPRNTCZ3WM6I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 01:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新PMI显示中国8月服务业活动扩张放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项私营部门调查显示，尽管正值暑期旅游高峰，但中国服务业活动的增长在8月份仍有所放缓，这促使一些企业在担心成本上升的情况下裁员。【原文：Growth in China's services sector activity slowed in August despite the summer travel peak, prompting some firms to cut staff amid concerns about rising costs, a private-sector survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-services-activity-expansion-slows-august-caixin-pmi-shows-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JKMXW6KYZK35ALTIVWPOZ7NOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 01:49:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利比亚争端有结束迹象，需求令人担忧，石油跌幅扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，油价下跌，延续了前一天超过4%的跌势，原因是人们预期导致利比亚出口中断的政治争端可能得到解决，以及对全球需求增长下降的担忧。【原文：Oil prices fell on Wednesday, extending the previous day's more than 4% plunge, on expectations the political dispute that has halted Libyan exports may be resolved and concerns over lower global demand growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-extends-losses-signs-end-libyan-dispute-demand-concerns-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBPPUEKQRFKXPOQP7YPNMR7WSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 01:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济增长忧虑再起，科技股黯淡无光，股市跌跌不休]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，亚洲股市和全球股市期货在科技股大跌后下跌，美元和日元因安全买盘而上涨，美国国债收益率走低，因为投资者对全球最大经济体的前景感到担忧。【原文：Asian shares and global stock futures fell on Wednesday in the wake of a tech selloff, while the dollar and yen rose on safety bids and U.S. Treasury yields edged lower as investors fretted over the outlook for the world's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PW6NKAEUI5IR7GUO7V7GTKXINY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 8 月服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示服务业活动扩大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项私营部门调查显示，尽管全球前景暗淡，但得益于海外销售的增长，日本 8 月份的服务业活动延续了涨势。【原文：Japan's service-sector activity extended gains in August, a private sector survey showed on Wednesday, thanks to an uptick in overseas sales despite a darkening global outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-service-activity-extends-gains-aug-pmi-shows-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKEQX2O2XROTJAHN6MZS3BKZLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本已昂贵的全球房价将因降息而得到适度提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对分析师进行的一项调查显示，由于预期抵押贷款利率将进一步下降，并有助于小幅提高昂贵房产的可负担性，大多数主要市场的房价将在今明两年小幅上涨。【原文：House prices in most key markets will rise modestly this year and next on expectations mortgage rates will fall further and help to marginally improve affordability of expensive property, a Reuters poll of analysts showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/already-expensive-global-house-prices-get-modest-boost-rate-cuts-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5PXRHWB7VOFFI5QUD22F53CQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁表示，美国钢铁公司的核心管理层和大部分董事会成员将由美国公民担任]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大的钢铁制造商新日铁正在寻求收购美国钢铁公司，该公司周三表示，如果收购顺利进行，美国钢铁公司的核心高级管理层和大多数董事会成员都将是美国公民。【原文：Japan's biggest steelmaker Nippon Steel , which is seeking to acquire U.S. Steel , said on Wednesday if its purchase goes ahead core senior management as well as a majority of board members at the U.S. company would be U.S. citizens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/core-management-majority-board-members-us-steel-will-be-us-citizens-nippon-steel-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AZTXF6MAJOW3MM3OUS2H6BOVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国安全专员呼吁对谢因和特穆进行调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国消费品安全委员会网站周二发布的一封信称，美国消费品安全委员会的两位领导人呼吁该机构对电子商务零售商Shein和Temu进行调查，因为这两个网站上销售了 "致命的婴幼儿产品"。【原文：Two leaders of the U.S. Consumer Products Safety Commission are calling for the agency to investigate e-commerce retailers Shein and Temu after "deadly baby and toddler products" were sold on both websites, according to a letter posted on the U.S. CPSC website on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-safety-commissioners-call-investigation-into-shein-temu-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYHW7D5WPBKEVIW5TKQOX5K37U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 23:27:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在股价表现不佳的情况下，Snap 将专注于广告业务和增强现实技术的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[Snap 首席执行官埃文-斯皮格尔（Evan Spiegel）在周二的一份说明中告知员工，Snap 将集中精力拓展表现不佳的广告业务，并使之多样化，重点关注增强现实技术。【原文：Snap will concentrate on expanding and diversifying its underperforming advertising business with a focus on augmented reality, CEO Evan Spiegel informed employees in a note on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/snap-focus-growing-ads-business-augmented-reality-amid-poor-stock-performance-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNDLE3LDA5JJPEFSI5X6OSEXNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道挪威财富基金可能撤资在加沙战争和被占领土上援助以色列的公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威 1.7 万亿美元的财富基金可能不得不剥离那些违反基金监督机构对帮助以色列在巴勒斯坦被占领土开展业务的企业道德标准的新的、更严格解释的公司的股份。【原文：Norway's $1.7 trillion wealth fund may have to divest shares of companies that violate the fund watchdog's new, tougher interpretation of ethics standards for businesses that aid Israel's operations in the occupied Palestinian territories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/norway-wealth-fund-may-divest-companies-that-aid-israel-gaza-war-occupied-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I57KH265YBJWZOQHKOKVAVRO7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部报告称，美国小型企业激增，景气改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周二发布的一份报告显示，随着通胀缓解，美国小企业在经历了 "大流行病 "后的艰难时期后，今年的创业申请量激增，该行业的景气度也有所改善。【原文：U.S. small business startup applications are surging this year with sentiment improving in the sector after a rocky post-pandemic period as inflation eases, a U.S. Treasury report showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-small-business-surges-sentiment-improves-treasury-report-says-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDBE2Y55QZMCBEZBMCNT6V4EBM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:54:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲 经济增长担忧、科技行业低迷带来九月忧虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZDHARWPHFOCJGK264CPSXKAL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:49:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salesforce 收购人工智能语音代理公司 Tenyx，加入人工智能人才争夺战]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业云计算公司Salesforce周二表示，已同意收购开发人工智能语音代理的Tenyx公司，以推进其人工智能驱动的解决方案。【原文：Enterprise cloud firm Salesforce on Tuesday said it has agreed to acquire Tenyx, which develops artificial intelligence-powered voice agents, to advance its AI-driven solutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/salesforce-acquire-ai-voice-agent-firm-tenyx-joining-ai-talent-race-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMW7TDVGWBKWXCB7UCF62BJSVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡马拉-哈里斯将提议为新成立的小型企业提供高达 50,000 美元的税收减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[副总统卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）将于本周三提议为新成立的小型企业提供最高达 5 万美元的税收减免，这比现有的减免措施增加了十倍，也是她一个多月前参加总统竞选后旨在赢得美国中产阶级支持的最新经济政策。【原文：Vice President Kamala Harris will propose a tax deduction of up to $50,000 for new small businesses on Wednesday, a tenfold increase over existing relief and her latest economic policy aimed at winning over middle-class Americans after jumping into the presidential race over a month ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/kamala-harris-propose-50000-tax-deduction-new-small-businesses-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUY7OHWQ55KH7E7AI6U65Q2ZIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会指控六家信用评级机构未保存记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周二指控六家信用评级机构 "在记录保存方面存在重大失误"。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Tuesday charged six credit rating agencies with "significant recordkeeping failures."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-sec-charges-six-credit-rating-agencies-with-recordkeeping-failures-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRV32LGPJNIUHKZXCS4JB4MUXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:51:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，英伟达遭到美国司法部传唤]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周二援引熟悉调查情况的人士的话报道称，英伟达（Nvidia）已收到美国司法部的传票，监管机构正在寻找这家人工智能重镇违反反垄断法的证据。【原文：Nvidia has received a subpoena from the U.S. Department of Justice as the regulator seeks evidence that the AI-heavyweight violated antitrust laws, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/nvidia-hit-with-subpoena-us-justice-department-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5UHWDIDGFIXBIOVJ7XUKMGWWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司合作伙伴 BioAge 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[与礼来公司（Eli Lilly）合作开发肥胖症疗法的生物技术初创公司 BioAge Labs 周二表示，该公司已申请在美国首次公开募股。【原文：BioAge Labs, a biotech startup collaborating with Eli Lilly for its obesity therapy, said on Tuesday it had filed for an initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/eli-lilly-partner-bioage-files-us-ipo-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GBXPQ46IFI7DGGG52E4S4UZ6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:14:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星链科技称遵守巴西禁止访问 X 的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的卫星宽带公司 Starlink 周二表示，该公司正在遵守巴西最高法院法官亚历山大-德-莫赖斯（Alexandre de Moraes）的命令，禁止在该国访问社交媒体平台 X。【原文：Elon Musk's satellite broadband company, Starlink, on Tuesday said that it is complying with Brazil's top court judge Alexandre de Moraes' order to block access to social media platform X in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/starlink-says-its-complying-with-order-block-access-x-brazil-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETL6SMS4PBNJVI44VRI6ZJD6ZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[九月伊始，美国股市暴跌，投资者对芯片持冷淡态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，华尔街主要股指下滑，S&amp;P 500 指数跌幅超过 2%，纳斯达克综合指数跌幅超过 3%，原因是投资者对人工智能的乐观情绪有所减弱，而在不温不火的经济数据公布后，大盘抛售加速。基准 S&amp;P 500 指数、纳斯达克和道指创下 8 月初以来的最大单日跌幅。【原文：Wall Street's main indexes slid on Tuesday, with the S&amp;P 500 down more than 2% and the Nasdaq Composite down over 3% as investors softened their optimism about AI in a broad market sell-off that accelerated after tepid economic data. The benchmark S&amp;P 500 index, Nasdaq and Dow registered their biggest daily drop since early August.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-stocks-tumble-investors-pause-ai-rally-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6XKYSQPXRMGNLOD6JCXLMMAD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:03:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Unite Here 工会称美国 7 个城市仍有 9,300 多名工人在罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[Unite Here 工会周二称，美国七个城市的 9376 名酒店员工仍在罢工，而巴尔的摩和西雅图的罢工已经结束。【原文：The Unite Here union said on Tuesday 9,376 of U.S. hotel workers have remained on strike in seven cities, while strikes in Baltimore and Seattle have concluded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/unite-here-union-says-more-than-9300-workers-remain-strike-7-cities-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRUTUX2XXZKVDGVH32VME4T7LM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[劳动节后美国企业借款人涌入债券市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国企业借款人涌入投资级和垃圾债券市场，抢在美联储本月利率决定和即将到来的美国总统大选的预期市场波动之前。【原文：U.S. corporate borrowers flooded the investment-grade and junk bond market on Tuesday, getting ahead of expected market volatility on this month's rates decision by the Federal Reserve and the upcoming U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-corporate-borrowers-rush-bond-market-post-labor-day-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHD5LZSSFBN35IS5HVIXROQPVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[驾驶季节结束，石油价格暴跌，美国汽油价格跌至近三年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽油期货周二下跌近6%，创下自2021年12月以来的最低点，原因是驾驶季节的结束拖累了汽车燃料的需求，而更广泛的石油市场则出现抛售。【原文：U.S. gasoline futures fell nearly 6% on Tuesday to their lowest since December 2021, as the end of the driving season weighed on demand for the motor fuel amid a sell-off in the broader oil market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-gasoline-slumps-near-3-year-low-end-driving-season-oil-slump-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDQGM3A5RFLCREM533VEY6QHWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:26:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者暂停人工智能涨势，英伟达和芯片指数下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，人工智能重量级公司英伟达（Nvidia）的股价暴跌，华尔街芯片指数暴跌7%，原因是在经济数据不温不火的大背景下，投资者对人工智能的乐观情绪有所减弱。【原文：Shares of AI heavyweight Nvidia tumbled on Tuesday, with Wall Street's chip index slumping 7% as investors softened their optimism about AI in a broad market sell-off following tepid economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/nvidia-chip-index-tumble-investors-pause-ai-rally-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPDIVCF46VLG5OSYYLTEJSNXIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称人工智能可能在未来十年拖累油价]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）周二表示，人工智能可能会通过改善物流降低成本，增加可盈利的可采资源量，从而促进供应，从而在未来十年损害石油价格。【原文：Artificial intelligence could hurt oil prices over the next decade by boosting supply by potentially reducing costs via improved logistics and increasing the amount of profitably recoverable resources, Goldman Sachs said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-likely-weigh-oil-prices-over-next-decade-goldman-says-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAIBXON6RNO6TCT4CGTEQYZEFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:23:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商比亚迪否认暂停墨西哥建厂计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商比亚迪周二表示，该公司没有推迟有关在墨西哥建厂计划的 "任何决定"，否认了当天早些时候的报道。【原文：China's electric automaker BYD said on Tuesday that it has not postponed "any decision" regarding its planned factory in Mexico, denying a report from earlier in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-denies-report-pause-mexico-plant-plans-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOPSDWFPSNNXZAXADCKFQMWAKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:20:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团聘请 Achintya Mangla 主管投资银行融资业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周二看到的一份备忘录，花旗集团已聘请 Achintya Mangla 担任投资银行融资主管，这个新设立的职位将向银行主管 Viswas Raghavan 汇报工作。【原文：Citigroup has hired Achintya Mangla as head of financing for investment banking, a newly created role that will report to the head of banking Viswas Raghavan, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-hires-achintya-mangla-head-investment-banking-financing-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLI5Q5YBDNIEFN6HYYE3CUZL4Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:15:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[弗里波特液化天然气公司产量增加，美国 8 月液化天然气出口反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融公司 LSEG 周二提供的初步数据显示，8 月份美国液化天然气出口反弹走高，原因是美国第二大液化天然气出口设施在停运后产量上升，其他工厂的维护活动也有所减少。【原文：Exports of U.S. liquefied natural gas bounced higher in August as output from the country's second-largest export facility rose following an outage and maintenance activities at other plants wound down, preliminary data from financial firm LSEG showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-lng-exports-rebound-august-higher-output-freeport-lng-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUSTXDL5BVLI5EK3YAKJFHQAUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:29:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储文件称未来一年美国住房通胀可能下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[据旧金山联邦储备银行周二发布的研究报告称，随着房屋供需差距的缩小，美国住房通胀在未来一年可能会有所缓解。【原文：U.S. housing inflation is likely to ease in the coming year as the gap between supply and demand for homes narrows, according to research published on Tuesday by the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-housing-inflation-likely-fall-year-ahead-fed-paper-says-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VRAIKMJZURJLFPH3EJZVRUS7LM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯泰兰特任命吉普北美公司新负责人，并作出其他高管变动]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商斯泰兰特周二任命鲍勃-布罗德多夫（Bob Broderdorf）为吉普北美地区负责人。【原文：Automaker Stellantis on Tuesday named Bob Broderdorf as the head of Jeep North America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-names-new-head-jeep-north-america-makes-other-executive-changes-2024-09-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGYCNGZHBBNU3J2W7FGEU4ZGYI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>