<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:08:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:08:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[企业投入数十亿美元推进人工智能基础设施建设]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）将向 OpenAI 投资高达 1000 亿美元，并为其提供数据中心芯片，这笔交易使这家芯片制造商获得了世界上最著名的人工智能公司的财务股份，而 OpenAI 已经是这家公司的重要客户。【原文：Nvidia is set to invest up to $100 billion in OpenAI and supply it with data center chips, in a deal that gives the chipmaker a financial stake in the world's most prominent AI company, which is already an important customer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/companies-pouring-billions-advance-ai-infrastructure-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHEEPBXQPJJARBM65WHZSHIUH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标疼痛阈值]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W62FZZJN3ZPIRMC7WNRP2NU5JU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音为争取欧盟批准 Spirit 交易提供补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据欧盟委员会网站的最新消息，波音公司已提出补救措施，以争取欧盟批准回购全球最大的独立航空结构公司 Spirit AeroSystems。【原文：Boeing has offered remedies in a bid to secure EU approval to buy back Spirit AeroSystems , the world's largest standalone aerostructures company, according to an update on the European Commission website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/boeing-offers-remedies-bid-eu-approval-spirit-deal-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TG337TL7LNJAZN3VPKXB5YNLLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，关税和法国动荡将导致欧洲经济放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的关键数据显示，欧元区经济增长继续保持稳定，因为德国的预算宽松支撑了市场情绪，并抵消了法国的动荡。【原文：Euro zone economic growth continues to hold up as Germany's budget largesse props up sentiment and offsets turmoil in France, but more weakness may be ahead as U.S. tariffs start to exert their full effect, key data showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/wrapup-europe-succumb-slowdown-driven-by-tariffs-french-turmoil-reports-show-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUPMY2YGZFPKDOXUS66ES56JYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:24:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道埃森哲拟在印度安得拉邦新建园区，计划增加 1.2 万个工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，技术咨询公司埃森哲（Accenture）已提议在印度南部的安得拉邦（Andhra Pradesh）建立一个新的园区，旨在最终为其在印度的员工队伍增加约 12,000 个工作岗位。【原文：Tech consultancy Accenture has proposed setting up a new campus in the southern Indian state of Andhra Pradesh, aiming to eventually add about 12,000 jobs to its workforce in India, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/accenture-proposes-new-campus-indias-andhra-pradesh-eyes-adding-12000-jobs-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6NTK7WBP5MSBDPX2IZ7UQ3KUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货在科技股推动的反弹后持稳；鲍威尔成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货基本持平，此前科技股大涨推动华尔街连续第三个交易日创下收盘纪录新高，而投资者则在等待美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）有关经济的讲话。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were largely unchanged on Tuesday after a tech-driven rally drove Wall Street to record closing highs for the third straight session, while investors awaited Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's remarks on the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-hold-steady-after-tech-fueled-rally-powell-focus-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATQXAGWZRFNAHJ4Y2SXSYNXSAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：百事公司部分投资者对艾略特分拆装瓶计划持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事公司的一些投资者支持激进股东埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）的建议，即全球食品饮料公司削减成本，放弃桂格（Quaker）等沉睡的品牌，但对对冲基金最大胆的想法--将这家苏打水生产商的装瓶网络一扫而空--则持谨慎态度。【原文：Some investors in PepsiCo support suggestions by activist shareholder Elliott Investment Management that the global food and beverage company cut costs and ditch sleepy brands like Quaker, but sound more cautious about the hedge fund's boldest idea - to hive off the soda maker's bottling network.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/some-pepsico-investors-cautious-elliotts-plan-spin-out-bottling-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIMZX5ZM4RPL7HKPCXMDW4PZFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊就联邦贸易委员会声称其欺骗 Prime 用户一案开庭审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（U.S. Federal Trade Commission）将于本周二在西雅图举行的庭审中试图证明，亚马逊在未经同意的情况下注册了数千万 Prime 客户，并用过于复杂的取消注册方法锁定了他们，从而欺骗了数千万 Prime 客户。【原文：Amazon duped tens of millions of Prime customers by signing them up without consent and locking them in with overly complex cancellation methods, the U.S. Federal Trade Commission will seek to show at a trial starting in Seattle on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/amazon-trial-begins-ftc-claims-it-duped-prime-subscribers-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2XMYU6EOJN23BBJEQCCWKFN74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:09:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车将于 2030 年在美国开始生产新型混合动力车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-begin-production-new-hybrid-model-united-states-by-2030-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2XJRGTYHFILZOM7QKTR7DE4I4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:07:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达 1000 亿美元 OpenAI 交易中的问题多于答案]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）向 OpenAI 投资高达 1000 亿美元，同时计划向 ChatGPT 创建者提供数百万个市场领先的人工智能芯片，这在科技行业几乎没有先例。【原文：Nvidia's move to invest up to $100 billion into OpenAI at the same time it plans to supply millions of its market-leading artificial intelligence chips to the ChatGPT creator has little precedent in the tech industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/more-questions-than-answers-nvidias-100-billion-openai-deal-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IVNH6AN2SROV7POGYFF2L3XWVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新的 H-1B 签证收费引发离岸外包讨论，硅谷招聘陷入混乱]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府对 H-1B 签证收取新的高额费用，促使硅谷及其他地区的公司内部就更多工作岗位转移到海外的可能性进行了高层会谈，而这恰恰是该政策想要阻止的结果。【原文：The Trump administration's hefty new visa fees for H-1B workers have prompted high-level talks inside companies in Silicon Valley and beyond on the possibility of moving more jobs overseas - precisely the outcome the policy was meant to stop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/silicon-valley-hiring-turmoil-after-new-h-1b-visa-fees-move-spurs-offshoring-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UK3XHUKT6NITPHVAAJL3O7MK7A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空破产威胁小镇航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）因一年内第二次破产而削减或取消阿诺德帕尔默地区机场的服务，宾夕法尼亚州拉特罗布（Latrobe）的居民可能很快就不得不驱车 65 英里前往匹兹堡，才能飞到任何地方。【原文：If Spirit Airlines slashes or eliminates service at Arnold Palmer Regional Airport due to the carrier's second bankruptcy in a year, residents of Latrobe, Pennsylvania, may soon have to drive 65 miles to Pittsburgh if they need to fly anywhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spirit-airlines-bankruptcy-threatens-small-towns-flights-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKFHNRWYKVLRFIF4ZCVB5VFLPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达斥资 1000 亿美元打造 OpenAI 引发重大反垄断问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家称，主导人工智能芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）与领先的人工智能公司 OpenAI 之间价值 1000 亿美元的合作关系，可能会使两家公司获得对竞争对手不公平的优势。【原文：The $100 billion partnership between dominant AI chipmaker Nvidia and leading artificial intelligence company OpenAI could give both companies an unfair advantage over their competitors, experts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/nvidias-100-billion-openai-play-raises-big-antitrust-issues-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5M6VPTG4OBPDDI5O74ZEX7X5NY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，J&J 将从非美国市场撤出胃酸倒流设备]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二援引强生公司发给医生的一封信报道，强生公司将从美国以外的市场撤回一种治疗胃酸倒流疾病的设备。【原文：Johnson & Johnson will withdraw a device to treat acid reflux disease from markets outside the U.S., Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a company letter sent to doctors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/jj-withdraw-acid-reflux-device-non-us-markets-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KV7KUHGVSFORRMZMF5NOMKKFSI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国监管机构就违规内容传唤字节跳动和阿里巴巴旗下平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国网络空间管理局周二表示，中国网络空间监管机构传唤了字节跳动旗下新闻平台头条号和阿里巴巴旗下互联网浏览器运营商 UCWeb，原因是内容违规。【原文：China's cyberspace regulator summoned ByteDance's news platform Toutiao and Alibaba's internet browser operator UCWeb over content violations, the Cyberspace Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-regulator-summons-bytedance-alibabas-platforms-over-content-violations-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LLKKN6CDRKG7FTJ4KGLD6MJ3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:27:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济合作与发展组织（OECD）称美国关税冲击尚未全面爆发，经济增长尚可维持]]></title><description><![CDATA[经合组织（OECD）周二表示，全球经济增长好于预期，但美国进口关税冲击的全部影响仍未显现，因为人工智能投资暂时支撑了美国的经济活动，财政支持也缓解了中国的经济放缓。【原文：Global growth is holding up better than expected, but the full brunt of the U.S. import tariff shock is still to be felt as AI investment props up U.S. activity for now and fiscal support cushions China's slowdown, the OECD said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/oecd-says-full-brunt-us-tariff-shock-yet-come-growth-holds-up-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UGMCQAWLRODRMOPJEAZANKOSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部对阿根廷的支持暂时为比索和米莱提供了友好的支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）承诺采取 "大规模、强有力 "的行动，利用有 91 年历史的美国危机基金来稳定阿根廷摇摆不定的货币，这可能会帮助比索站稳脚跟，至少暂时如此。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent's pledge of "large and forceful" actions to stabilize Argentina's wobbling currency by using a 91-year-old U.S. crisis fund could help the peso find its footing, at least for a while.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-treasurys-support-argentina-gives-peso-milei-friendly-leg-up-now-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RU6EDZQXDRKP5CWEJOTQI3HAKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:03:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 DHL 从周四起恢复飞往美国的商业包裹服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国敦豪快递公司（DHL）将从本周四起恢复向美国运送企业标准包裹的服务，这是该公司因美国即将对低价值包裹征收关税而暂停这项服务约四周后的又一举措。【原文：Germany's DHL will resume the shipment of standard parcels for businesses to the United States from Thursday, roughly four weeks after suspending the service over looming U.S. customs duties for low-value packages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/germanys-dhl-resume-us-bound-business-parcel-service-thursday-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HT6ETP23ZNWBPCEF7IUWRSD4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 08:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰诺制药商肯维股价反弹，特朗普的主张面临回击]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将泰诺（Tylenol）生产商肯维（Kenvue）的常用止痛药与怀孕期间的自闭症风险联系在一起，但肯维的股票在周二的欧洲交易中仍然上涨。【原文：Tylenol-maker Kenvue stock rose in European trading on Tuesday, even after U.S. President Donald Trump linked its popular pain medication to autism risk during pregnancy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/tylenol-maker-kenvue-shares-bounce-trump-claims-face-pushback-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3WRYX2OKNMWHBZKJUJJSMXQ7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 08:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国贸易特使会见美国中西部代表团，农业出口成为谈判重点]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周二表示，中国高级贸易谈判代表李成钢会见了美国中西部地区的政界和商界领袖，分析人士推测该地区的食品出口将是任何中美贸易协议的关键。【原文：Senior Chinese trade negotiator Li Chenggang met political and business leaders from the U.S. Midwest, the commerce ministry said on Tuesday, with analysts speculating the region's food exports will be key to any U.S.-China trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/china-trade-envoy-meets-us-midwest-delegation-agriculture-exports-loom-large-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RQ5J3DO4VKZBJVL3COON2HK7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国捷豹路虎因网络攻击停产四周]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国最大的汽车制造商捷豹路虎（JLR）在 9 月初遭到网络攻击后，将其工厂的关闭时间延长至 10 月 1 日，这次攻击导致其运营瘫痪，小型供应商也陷入困境。【原文：Britain's biggest car maker Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) is extending the closure of its factories until October 1 following a cyber attack in early September which has left its operations paralysed, and smaller suppliers struggling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uks-jaguar-land-rover-cyber-attack-shutdown-hit-four-weeks-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGIMFCXSCVL7TP7CAE7YWC5V3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官解除特朗普对 Revolution Wind 项目的禁令后，Orsted 股价大涨 12]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，在美国联邦法官裁定奥尔斯特可以恢复上个月被美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府叫停的已基本完工的革命风电项目后，奥尔斯特的股价最高上涨了12%。【原文：Shares in Orsted rose as much as 12% in early trade on Tuesday after a U.S. federal judge ruled that it can resume work on the almost completed Revolution Wind project halted by U.S. President Donald Trump's administration last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/orsted-shares-jump-12-after-us-judge-lifts-trump-ban-revolution-wind-project-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXULB56SVBJABDKVLEW65QSY4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国贸易协议到期对非洲经济意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[非洲官员和企业高管对与美国的一项重要免税贸易计划即将于 9 月底到期感到焦虑不安，而华盛顿方面却没有任何关于是否延长该计划的消息。【原文：African officials and business executives are fretting over the impending expiry of a crucial, duty-free trade programme with the United States at the end of September, without any word from Washington on whether it will be extended or not.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/what-does-expiry-us-trade-deal-mean-african-economies-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UI7IJISPVJM7BBQDTPHHIOSKKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国诺玛公司以 10 亿美元向美国公司出售水管理业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车和工业供应商 Norma 公司周二表示，将把利润丰厚的水管理业务出售给美国竞争对手 Advanced Drainage Systems 公司，交易价值 10 亿美元。【原文：German automotive and industrial supplier Norma will sell its lucrative water management business to U.S. rival Advanced Drainage Systems in a deal valued at $1 billion, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/advanced-drainage-systems-buy-norma-groups-water-management-business-1-billion-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3X7AW7R35ND3GXSTIUHAP55CU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:27:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Raspberry Pi 公司上半年盈利下降，但需求仍在增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[单板计算机制造商树莓派（Raspberry Pi）表示，其下半年开局良好，收益高于去年同期，需求也有所增长，但截至 6 月底的 6 个月调整后收益下降了 7%，为 1940 万美元。【原文：Raspberry Pi , the single-board computer maker, said its second half had started well, with earnings ahead of last year and demand strengthening as it reported a 7% drop in adjusted earnings to $19.4 million for the six months to end-June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uks-raspberry-pi-sees-demand-strengthening-after-first-half-earnings-drop-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5D5CFZ3LKFMO5DDYJBQUHYM6YY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASM 国际公司下调 2025 年下半年收入展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[计算机芯片设备制造商 ASM International 在本周二的投资者日之前下调了 2025 年下半年的收入目标。【原文：Computer chip equipment maker ASM International cut its revenue target for the second half of 2025, ahead of its investor day on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asm-international-cuts-h2-2025-revenue-outlook-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4MX3AFTQRNQHA5Q6XHOBA7524</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:23:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一些中国企业在经营困难的情况下假装按规定缴纳社会保险费]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一项具有里程碑意义的解释中，中国最高法院最近强化了雇主和工人之间为逃避社会保险缴费而采取的变通办法是无效的，此举既承诺为枯竭的养老金计划提供资金，又威胁到就业和企业。【原文：In a landmark interpretation, China's top court recently reinforced that workarounds between employers and workers to evade social insurance contributions are invalid, a move that both promises to fund depleted pension plans and threatens jobs and businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/some-chinese-firms-pretend-comply-with-mandated-social-insurance-payments-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVGBP34AMRIIZMNKAQEFAYW4FY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南首次公开募股市场和股市反弹未能激起外国投资者的兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[在股价上涨、监管变化和信贷激增的推动下，越南的首次公开募股（IPO）市场正在升温，但尽管指数提供商富时罗素（FTSE Russell）有望提升该市场的评级，却未能激起外国投资者的新兴趣。【原文：Vietnam's IPO market is heating up, fuelled by a share rally, regulatory changes and a credit splurge, but has failed to stir fresh interest from foreign investors despite the prospect that the market could be upgraded by index provider FTSE Russell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vietnams-ipo-market-stocks-rally-fail-stir-foreign-investors-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZRMIK7FRRM2VMC5STQ6U4FILI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 05:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，土耳其计划购买数百架波音客机和洛克希德-马丁战斗机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，土耳其总统塔伊普-埃尔多安（Tayyip Erdogan）计划购买数百架波音客机和洛克希德-马丁（Lockheed Martin）战斗机，并推动在该国生产这些飞机的部分零部件。【原文：Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan plans to buy hundreds of Boeing airliners and Lockheed Martin fighters and also push for some of their parts to be produced in the country, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/turkey-plans-buy-hundreds-boeing-airliners-lockheed-martin-fighters-bloomberg-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53CNWHGHMBIZTGATAOHITBDV3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 05:07:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星展银行支持的家庭办公室平台资产达到 7.8 亿美元，到 2026 年底将翻一番]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡最大银行星展集团（DBS Group）旗下的星展私人银行（DBS Private Bank）周二表示，其银行支持的多家族办公室平台在推出两年后管理的资产已达到10亿新元（7.8亿美元），并有望在2026年底达到20亿新元。【原文：DBS Private Bank, part of Singapore's biggest bank DBS Group , said on Tuesday its bank-backed multi-family office platform has reached S$1 billion ($780 million) in assets under management two years after launch and is on track to hit S$2 billion by end-2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dbsbacked-familyoffice-platform-hits-780-million-assets-double-by-end2026-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDMQCAVSIVJXPOYBCOC75OEFRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 05:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>