<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 20:34:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 20:34:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2024 财年预算赤字高达 1.8 万亿美元，为历史第三大赤字]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五表示，2024 财年美国预算赤字将增至 1.833 万亿美元，创下 COVID-19 时代以外的最高纪录，原因是联邦债务利息首次突破 1 万亿美元，以及社会保障退休计划、医疗保健和军事支出的增长。【原文：The U.S. budget deficit grew to $1.833 trillion for fiscal 2024, the highest outside of the COVID-19 era, as interest on the federal debt topped $1 trillion for the first time and spending grew for the Social Security retirement program, health care and the military, the Treasury Department said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-budget-deficit-tops-18-trillion-fiscal-2024-third-largest-record-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DWUF22UZJO2PL333U6Y6AY65Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 20:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克新任首席执行官任命同为 Chipotle 校友的人担任高级营销职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克周二宣布聘请食品营销资深人士特蕾西-利伯曼（Tressie Lieberman）担任其高级营销职务，这是新任首席执行官布莱恩-尼科尔（Brian Niccol）一系列高管调整中的最新人事变动。【原文：Starbucks on Tuesday announced it hired food marketing veteran Tressie Lieberman to take its top marketing job, the latest in a spate of executive reshuffling by new CEO Brian Niccol.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-new-ceo-taps-fellow-chipotle-alum-top-marketing-role-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHRFGYZ3TRM4DOVI67BVDQ6KCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 19:18:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官批准谷歌要求暂时搁置 Play 商店全面改革的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌周五表示，加利福尼亚州的一名联邦法官批准了谷歌的请求，暂停执行命令，该命令要求 Alphabet 旗下公司在 11 月 1 日前对其安卓应用商店 Play 进行彻底改革，以便让消费者在下载软件时有更多选择。【原文：Google said on Friday that a federal judge in California granted its request to pause his order directing the Alphabet unit to overhaul its Android app store Play by Nov. 1 to give consumers more choice over how they download software.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-grants-google-request-put-play-store-overhaul-temporary-hold-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIVHHPIG3NL4RIS6R22MUOVVPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 18:58:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席博斯蒂克表示不急于将利率降至中性水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周五表示，他将在降息问题上保持耐心，以确保通胀率不会超过美国央行2%的目标。
"博斯蒂克在密西西比州杰克逊市举行的密西西比州经济教育委员会美国企业论坛上说："我并不急于求成。"我们必须让通胀率回到 2% 的目标；我不希望我们的通胀率超过 2%。【原文：Atlanta Federal Reserve Bank President Raphael Bostic said Friday he will be patient on cutting rates to make sure inflation does not stall out above the U.S. central bank's 2% target.
"I'm not in a rush to get anywhere," Bostic told the Mississippi Council on Economic Education Forum on American Enterprise in Jackson, Mississippi. "We must get inflation back to our 2% target; I don't want us to g】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bostic-says-he-is-no-rush-get-rates-down-neutral-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIUTQBZU7NL7HC43HQZ27A7MP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 18:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 发布可检查其他人工智能模型工作的人工智能模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[Facebook 的所有者 Meta 公司周五表示，它将从其研究部门发布一批新的人工智能模型，其中包括一个 "自学评估器"，它可能为减少人工智能开发过程中的人工参与提供了一条途径。【原文：Facebook owner Meta said on Friday it was releasing a batch of new AI models from its research division, including a "Self-Taught Evaluator" that may offer a path toward less human involvement in the AI development process.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/meta-releases-ai-model-that-can-check-other-ai-models-work-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZ22CMYW7JLBJM67WFK27GEZIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 17:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定，Meta 必须面对马萨诸塞州社交媒体成瘾诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州一名法官驳回了 Meta Platforms 公司要求驳回该州指控该社交媒体公司故意在其 Instagram 平台上设置让年轻用户上瘾的功能，并就其产品对青少年心理健康造成的危害欺骗公众的诉讼。【原文：A Massachusetts judge has rejected Meta Platforms' bid to dismiss a lawsuit by the state alleging the social media company purposely deployed features on its Instagram platform to addict young users and deceived the public about the dangers its product posed to teenagers' mental health.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/meta-must-face-massachusetts-social-media-addiction-lawsuit-judge-rules-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KZ4TRBSQBNT5IZONI746YSV7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:51:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员要求司法部和国防部调查麦肯锡并审查合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群美国议员要求司法部和国防部（Department of Defense）调查麦肯锡未披露其与中国政府合作的情况，称这家咨询巨头可能面临利益冲突，需要进行审查。【原文：A group of U.S. lawmakers have asked the Department of Justice and the Department of Defense (DoD) to investigate McKinsey's failure to disclose its work with China's government, saying that the consulting giant might face conflicts of interest that require reviewing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-lawmakers-ask-justice-defense-departments-probe-mckinsey-review-contracts-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJSULZ26VRLM5LMZZWWRN7TAGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[导致 CVS Health 首席执行官林奇离职的事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 首席执行官凯伦-林奇（Karen Lynch）在执掌公司近四年后即将卸任，因为这家医疗保健集团面临着股东要求其改善经营业绩的压力。【原文：CVS Health CEO Karen Lynch is stepping down after nearly four years at the helm, as the healthcare conglomerate faces shareholder pressure to improve its business performance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/events-leading-up-cvs-health-ceo-lynchs-departure-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WELROPW4BPJDGSX2QJWJE3HMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:28:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国单户住宅建筑增至五个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[9 月份，美国独户住宅建造量飙升至 5 个月来的新高，但由于市场上新房供应过剩以及潜在购房者仍在等待较低的抵押贷款利率，未来的建造许可量仅有小幅增长。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding surged to a five-month high in September, but permits for future construction rose only marginally amid excess supply of new homes on the market and prospective buyers holding out for lower mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-single-family-homebuilding-rises-five-month-high-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7RW2225KJJP7A356VKBASY2JY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 14:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金因银行盈利和降息希望而吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至10月16日的一周内，美国投资者对股票基金进行了大量投资，原因是美国贷款机构第三季度盈利强劲，以及对美联储可能在11月降息和通胀降温迹象的乐观情绪。【原文：U.S. investors made large investments in equity funds in the week to Oct. 16, buoyed by strong third-quarter earnings from U.S. lenders and optimism over a potential Federal Reserve rate cut in November and signs of cooling inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-draw-big-inflows-bank-earnings-rate-cut-hopes-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LABYF6HRBP4ZLZ5XYYIRQQ3GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 13:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局称新的波音安全审查将耗时约三个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦航空管理局周五在一份声明中表示，该局对波音公司安全流程的新审查将耗时约三个月。【原文：A new Federal Aviation Administration review of Boeing's safety processes will take about three months, the agency said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-says-new-boeing-safety-review-will-take-about-three-months-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U655QCTBCNMPBD5APY5AUY5QY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 13:23:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Cellular 将以 10 亿美元向 Verizon 出售部分频谱资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国蜂窝电话公司周五表示，已同意将其部分频谱许可出售给 Verizon 公司，交易金额为 10 亿美元。【原文：United States Cellular said on Friday it has agreed to sell some of its spectrum licenses to Verizon in a $1 billion deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-cellular-sell-select-spectrum-assets-verizon-1-bln-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHLPKF734BI3DKMKKUSKT2AI5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:55:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯全球销售主管将于 10 月底退出董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿迪达斯周五发表声明称，负责全球销售的董事会成员阿瑟-豪尔德（Arthur Hoeld）将于 10 月底从这家德国体育用品公司的执行董事会卸任。【原文：Adidas' board member for global sales, Arthur Hoeld, will step down from the German sportswear company's executive board at the end of October, it said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-global-sales-exec-step-down-board-end-october-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YECDJOVMOZMGJPGNFHHJCOTJUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:53:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢首席执行官弗莱克西的扭亏计划面临消费者疲软的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司在新任首席执行官洛朗-弗莱克西（Laurent Freixe）的领导下，计划进行重组，并更加专注于顶级品牌，这一计划受到了投资者的欢迎，但在消费需求疲软的背景下，执行扭亏为盈战略将是一项艰巨的任务。【原文：Nestle's plans under new CEO Laurent Freixe to restructure and sharpen its focus on its top brands were welcomed by investors, but executing a turnaround strategy against a backdrop of weak consumer demand will be a tough task.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nestle-ceo-freixes-turnaround-plan-faces-challenge-weak-consumer-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AL5IANMLENKZJJMSQVIODZWUPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德公司在美国自愿撤回尿道癌药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司（Gilead Sciences）周五表示，在与监管机构协商后，该公司将主动撤回美国对 Trodelvy 用于先前接受过治疗的一种尿道癌患者的批准。【原文：Gilead Sciences said on Friday it was voluntarily withdrawing the U.S. approval for Trodelvy in previously treated patients with a type of urothelial cancer after consultation with the regulator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/gilead-voluntarily-withdraws-urothelial-cancer-drug-us-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOZX4FDLWVMXHHLQQZIPUHWSCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道受波音罢工影响，Spirit 航空公司将解雇 700 名工人 21 天]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空系统公司（Spirit AeroSystems）的一位发言人告诉路透社，由于美国飞机制造商波音公司长达一个多月的罢工侵蚀了该供应商的现金和库存空间，该公司将于周五告知员工，公司将对700名员工进行为期21天的休假。【原文：Spirit AeroSystems will tell employees on Friday that it will furlough 700 workers for 21 days as an over month-long strike at U.S. planemaker Boeing eats into the supplier's cash and inventory space, a spokesperson told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-aero-furlough-700-workers-21-days-due-boeing-strike-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHBGCV3SXRLZHPHVFQB62Z2XFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第五季银行利润因贷款损失准备金增加而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fifth Third Bancorp 周五公布第三季度利润下降，原因是该银行预留了更多资金以应对潜在的贷款违约，导致其股价在盘前交易中下跌 3%。【原文：Fifth Third Bancorp reported a fall in its third-quarter profit on Friday, as the bank set aside more money to cover for potential loan defaults, sending its shares down 3% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fifth-third-bancorps-profit-falls-higher-loan-loss-provisions-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANXWMXBYCJO4BAXVPBB7WJFB5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:56:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于客户消费强劲，美国运通利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运通周五公布的第三季度利润高于华尔街预期，原因是其信用卡消费的增长抵消了信贷损失准备金增加所带来的冲击。【原文：American Express reported third-quarter profit above Wall Street estimates on Friday, as higher spending on its cards offset a hit from bigger provisions for credit losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/amex-profit-beats-estimate-robust-customer-spending-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEANXAPSIZKOPKJ5MILV4IRXSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和中国需求疲软，宝洁公司季度销售额不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝洁公司周五公布的第一季度销售额未达华尔街预期，原因是其主要市场--美国和中国--的消费者转而购买价格更低廉的家居和个人护理品牌。【原文：Procter &amp; Gamble missed Wall Street expectations for first-quarter sales on Friday, as consumers in its major markets, the United States and China, switched to cheaper household and personal care brands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pg-misses-quarterly-sales-estimates-weakening-demand-us-china-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IFFFD2YAJIAVIQJQKDBMAHGJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CVS 将由长期高管大卫-乔伊纳接替首席执行官凯伦-林奇]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 周五任命公司资深人士大卫-乔伊纳（David Joyner）为新任首席执行官，接替凯伦-林奇（Karen Lynch）。【原文：CVS Health on Friday named company veteran David Joyner as new CEO, succeeding Karen Lynch who stepped down from the helm of the struggling healthcare giant after an agreement with the board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-name-long-time-exec-david-joyner-new-ceo-wsj-reports-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJIG3YKU4BMURPZVPGOQT3II4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国财政大臣里夫斯首次出访 IMF 将强调稳定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞秋-里夫斯（Rachel Reeves）下周将作为英国财政大臣首次出访华盛顿的国际货币基金组织年会，她将在此次出访中强调对稳定的承诺，而两年前英国曾是债券市场风暴的中心。【原文：Rachel Reeves will stress a commitment to stability in her first trip as Britain's finance minister to the International Monetary Fund's annual meetings in Washington next week, two years after the country was at the centre of a bond market storm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/britains-reeves-stress-stability-first-imf-trip-finance-minister-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHCYX43PMNOHNC45JL45XITHGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度计划抑制笔记本电脑进口，以促进本地制造业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解此事的政府消息人士称，印度有望在 1 月后限制笔记本电脑、平板电脑和个人电脑的进口，此举旨在推动苹果等公司增加国内生产。【原文：India is expected to limit imports of laptops, tablets and personal computers after January, two government sources with direct knowledge of the matter said, a move to push companies such as Apple to increase domestic manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/india-plans-laptop-import-curbs-boost-local-manufacturing-sources-say-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJF5GX2S6BLWHF2FFEZXG5HRCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州天然气管道缓解瓶颈，为提高页岩气产量铺平道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源高管们表示，一条新的管道将得克萨斯州西部的页岩天然气输送到美国墨西哥湾沿岸的出口枢纽，缓解了今年导致当地价格崩溃的限制因素，并将有助于为提高美国石油产量铺平道路。【原文：A new pipeline carrying shale natural gas from west Texas toward export hubs on the U.S. Gulf Coast has eased constraints that crashed local prices this year, and will help pave the way for higher U.S. oil production, energy executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/texas-natural-gas-pipeline-eases-bottlenecks-paves-way-higher-shale-output-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BS2AFNNMZIJRFZ33JOAVPWR6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货上涨，科技股上涨，Netflix 盈利强劲后跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，华尔街期货攀升，其中纳斯达克 100 指数上涨，科技股普遍走高，Netflix 在发布乐观业绩后大涨。【原文：Wall Street futures climbed on Friday, led by gains in those tracking the Nasdaq 100 as technology shares broadly advanced, while Netflix surged following upbeat results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-futures-rise-tech-stocks-gain-netflix-jumps-after-strong-earnings-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVMW4WQU6FII5MJ3M3QMTP472I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普交易大放异彩，中国数据暗流涌动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和全球市场前瞻（作者：Harry Robertson【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by Harry Robertson】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPDSZ6NIDZJSBKPDPY2Y3BPXB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 动荡一周后，华尔街聚焦半导体市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[在国外两家行业领军企业的报告出现分歧，引发了几天来的交易波动之后，美国半导体公司在未来几周将受到投资者的密切关注。【原文：U.S. semiconductor companies will get a closer look from investors in coming weeks, after diverging reports from two industry leaders abroad set off a volatile few days of trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-wall-street-zeroes-semiconductors-after-turbulent-week-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UE43Z7Q2BMPBCG3I6VRIPBHE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:04:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局对 240 万辆特斯拉汽车的全自动驾驶碰撞事故展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，已对 240 万辆特斯拉汽车展开调查，因为其中一辆采用全自动驾驶（FSD）技术的汽车撞死了一名行人。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday it has opened an investigation into 2.4 million Tesla vehicles after one of them with Full Self-Driving (FSD) technology fatally struck a pedestrian.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-opens-probe-into-24-mln-tesla-vehicles-over-full-self-driving-collisions-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMJPURGBNVKUTLUOACDASPTGTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:41:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国钢铁出口将持续高涨，贸易摩擦恐将加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士和分析师称，中国钢铁企业的出口量已接近十年来的最高水平，2025 年他们将继续加大出货量，以应对产能过剩和国内需求疲软的问题，这有可能加剧日益加剧的贸易摩擦。【原文：Chinese steelmakers, already exporting at near-decade high volumes, are set to keep pushing out shipments in 2025 to manage overcapacity and soft domestic demand, industry insiders and analysts say, threatening to worsen mounting trade frictions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/elevated-china-steel-exports-set-persist-threaten-worsen-trade-friction-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q25EMNP2OFKRJLC42SXVSJGLDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:15:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，富士软董事会支持 KKR 收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经新闻》周五称，日本富士软公司董事会决定坚持 KKR 提出的 5,584 亿日元（37.2 亿美元）收购要约，尽管贝恩提出了更高的还价。【原文：The board of Japan's Fuji Soft has decided to stick with a 558.4 billion yen ($3.72 billion) buyout offer from KKR , the Nikkei newspaper said on Friday, despite having received a higher counter-offer from Bain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/fuji-soft-board-supports-kkr-buyout-offer-nikkei-reports-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJP53E2IQFMRND6G4DRZ4VGG7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大烟草公司提议支付近 240 亿美元以解决加拿大诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲利普-莫里斯公司（Philip Morris）周五表示，卷烟制造商菲利普-莫里斯公司、英美烟草公司和日本烟草公司将支付 325 亿加元（约合 236 亿美元），以了结在加拿大的一场旷日持久的烟草诉讼案，这也是法院指定调解人提出的计划的一部分。【原文：Cigarette makers Philip Morris , British American Tobacco and Japan Tobacco will pay C$32.5 billion ($23.6 billion) to settle a long-running tobacco lawsuit in Canada, as part of a court-appointed mediator's proposed plan, Philip Morris said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/court-mediator-proposes-236-bln-settlement-by-philip-morris-bat-jti-units-canada-2024-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3MDKPIKGVJ43NX7VPIGRYWESM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>