<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:20:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:20:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称，美国在印度承诺削减俄罗斯石油进口后，将取消对印度进口商品征收的25%单独关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫官员周一表示，特朗普政府将取消因印度购买俄罗斯石油而对其进口商品加征的25%附加关税，同时将针对该国的特定关税从25%下调至18%。【原文：The Trump administration is dropping a 25% additional tariffs imposed on Indian imports over its purchases of Russian oil, in addition to lowering a country-specific tariff to 18% from 25%, a White House official said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-dropping-25-separate-tariff-indian-imports-after-pledge-cut-russian-oil-white-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SQZED6A7IJJVRN63DPHXLNSDBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:54:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工统计局称，部分政府停摆将推迟1月就业报告发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工统计局周一表示，由于联邦政府部分停摆，备受关注的1月份就业报告将不会在周五发布。【原文：The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics said on Monday the closely watched employment report for January will be not be released on Friday because of a partial shutdown of the federal government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/partial-us-government-shutdown-will-delay-januarys-employment-report-bls-says-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ554USJSZPJVJF6XHZBMUZE5E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:49:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Telia与Lyse将合并挪威移动无线网络以降低成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电信集团Telia与挪威Lyse公司（移动运营商Ice所有者）周一宣布，双方已同意将其在挪威的移动无线接入网络整合至一家合资企业。【原文：Swedish telecoms group Telia and Norway's Lyse [RIC:RIC:LYSEK.UL], owner of mobile operator Ice, have agreed to combine their Norwegian mobile radio access networks into a jointly held firm, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/telia-lyse-combine-norwegian-mobile-radio-networks-save-costs-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6Z6YIHYL5K55FISYFI2FTSJYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利1月新车销量同比增长6.2%]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利交通部周一公布的数据显示，2026年意大利新车市场开局良好，1月销量同比增长6.18%，达到约14.2万辆。【原文：The market for new cars in Italy began on a positive note in 2026, with January sales up 6.18% year-on-year to around 142,000 vehicles, transport ministry data showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/italy-new-car-sales-up-by-62-year-on-year-january-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRJD3EOPMJNXNAJGZ3RTCANAWM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自特朗普对印度加征关税以来印美关税情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周一表示，他已与印度达成贸易协议，新德里方面还同意停止购买俄罗斯石油，转而增加从美国及可能从委内瑞拉的采购。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he had agreed on a trade deal with India, and that New Delhi also agreed to stop buying Russian oil and buy more from the U.S. and potentially Venezuela.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indiaus-tariffs-since-trump-imposed-duties-india-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E27MB2ROVBOQPEIU5PGS4PERHE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:45:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求加快武器交付后，美国防务公司增加支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国主要国防承包商今年正大幅增加资本支出，以响应特朗普总统的威胁——为加快武器交付进度，他要求限制股息和股票回购。【原文：Major U.S. defense contractors are significantly ramping up capital expenditure this year in response to President Donald Trump's threat to limit dividends and share buybacks in his push to speed up weapons deliveries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-defense-firms-boost-spending-after-trump-calls-expedited-arms-deliveries-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLKCHESGTVI2XIHZXMTPA56HQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉1月在意大利新车销量同比激增，此前2025年销量曾出现下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利交通部周一公布的数据显示，特斯拉在意大利的新车注册量1月份同比增长75%，此前该品牌在整个2025年的注册量曾下滑18%。【原文：Tesla's new car registrations in Italy rose 75% year-on-year in January, after posting an 18% drop over the whole of 2025, data from the Italian transport ministry showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tesla-new-car-sales-italy-jump-year-on-year-january-after-2025-drop-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPDGAWN2MRO2NH32W2PYRV7PNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美印达成贸易协议，将降低关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周一表示，他已与印度达成贸易协议，印度同时同意停止购买俄罗斯石油，转而增加从美国及可能从委内瑞拉的进口。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he had agreed on a trade deal with India, and that India also agreed to stop buying Russian oil and buy more from the United States and potentially Venezuela.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/trump-says-agreed-trade-deal-with-india-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXTAJLHI6FJJFG4WDFVTM6DXCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，嘉能可即将任命花旗为与力拓合并谈判的顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，瑞士矿业巨头嘉能可即将聘请花旗集团担任其潜在收购交易的牵头投行，该交易可能促成全球最大矿业巨头诞生，其市值将超过2000亿美元。【原文：Swiss miner Glencore is close to engaging Citi as its lead investment bank on its potential acquisition by Rio Tinto that could create the world's largest miner worth over $200 billion, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/glencore-close-appointing-citi-adviser-rio-tinto-merger-talks-sources-say-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3XLFYGQBNOB7IOOIRTL5YD4AA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:43:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[灰姑娘金属白银在飙升至历史高位后失去支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[白银被誉为贵金属界的灰姑娘，长期遭受冷落，偶尔闪耀光芒后又迅速黯然失色。在分析师眼中，这个市场充斥着童话故事，而白银正完美印证了这般声名。【原文：Silver has been dubbed the Cinderella of precious metals, spending long periods overlooked before sweeping into the spotlight and disappearing in short order. In a market analysts say is beset by fairy tales, it is living up to that reputation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/cinderella-metal-silver-loses-footing-after-surge-record-high-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GFMJT6MRZPM7MLE2CQ3AMGOUY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snowflake与OpenAI达成2亿美元人工智能合作协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪花公司周一宣布，已与OpenAI达成价值2亿美元的合作协议，将先进的人工智能模型直接集成到其云数据平台中。随着企业越来越多地借助人工智能从海量数据中挖掘洞察，此举旨在满足市场需求。【原文：Snowflake said on Monday it has entered a $200 million partnership with OpenAI to integrate advanced artificial intelligence models directly into its cloud data platform, as enterprises increasingly turn to AI to extract insights from vast troves of data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/snowflake-partners-with-openai-200-million-ai-deal-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VOKLE5L4XJJDXNFDOBVZ26YCSE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:55:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络安全公司Wiz称，面向人工智能代理的社交媒体平台"Moltbook"存在重大安全漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[据网络安全公司Wiz周一发布的研究报告显示，一个由人工智能驱动的机器人在社交网络上热议代码并八卦其人类主人的新平台存在重大漏洞，导致数千名真实用户的私人数据遭泄露。【原文：A buzzy new social network where artificial intelligence-powered bots appear to swap code and gossip about their human owners had a major flaw that exposed private data on thousands of real people, according to research published on Monday by cybersecurity firm Wiz.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/moltbook-social-media-site-ai-agents-had-big-security-hole-cyber-firm-wiz-says-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3OO4FZ2HNI6RCOPNZ3TROM3DE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制造业1月强劲反弹，订单增长势头强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国1月份工厂活动时隔一年首次增长，新订单大幅回升，但制造业仍未摆脱困境，因进口关税推高原材料价格并加剧供应链紧张。【原文：U.S. factory activity grew for the first time in a year in January, with new orders rebounding sharply, but manufacturing is still not out of the woods as import tariffs raised raw material prices and strained supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-manufacturing-rebounds-january-amid-strong-order-growth-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EFWN5Q5YVKLJH6CSDYAXWSPWM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据CNBC报道，华纳兄弟股东可能于3月就与奈飞的交易进行投票表决。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国全国广播公司财经频道周一报道，华纳兄弟探索公司很可能在3月份就以827亿美元将旗下流媒体和影视制作资产出售给奈飞的交易举行股东投票。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery is likely to hold a shareholder vote on the $82.7 billion deal to sell its streaming and studio assets to Netflix in March, CNBC reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-shareholders-likely-hold-vote-netflix-deal-march-cnbc-reports-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SU55TTAO4ZNDFJVVGW62HJX2LY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，工会对美国炼油厂协议的最后马拉松式提议既未接受也未拒绝]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周一透露，美国钢铁工人联合会（USW）尚未接受或拒绝马拉松石油公司就美国炼油厂和化工厂新四年劳资协议提出的最终报价。【原文：The United Steelworkers union (USW) has neither accepted nor rejected the last offer from Marathon Petroleum for a new four-year labor agreement for U.S. refineries and chemical plants, people familiar with the talks said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/union-neither-accepts-nor-rejects-last-marathon-offer-us-refinery-pact-sources-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">US3DO5V5ABOOVEIBSALV5LTZ64</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:12:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[先锋集团宣布新一轮全面降低基金费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球第二大资产管理公司、低成本基金先驱先锋集团周一宣布，将下调旗下53只指数型共同基金和交易所交易基金的费用，这是该公司过去12个月内实施的第二次大规模降费。【原文：Vanguard, the world's second-largest asset manager and a pioneer of low-cost funds, said ​on Monday it is cutting fees on 53 of its index-based mutual funds ‌and exchange-traded funds, marking its second sweeping fee reduction in the past 12 months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/vanguard-announces-new-round-sweeping-fund-fee-cuts-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6K5L2FGQGRIGVLCSMWSOSL5FZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尔利指控Allegro在波兰电商领域操纵价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰电商平台Erli周一发表声明称，已起诉规模更大的竞争对手Allegro，指控其滥用市场支配地位，通过强制卖家在平台外抬高价格来实施垄断行为。【原文：Polish e-commerce platform Erli has sued larger rival Allegro , accusing it of abusing its dominant position by effectively forcing sellers to raise their prices outside its platform, Erli said on Monday in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/erli-accuses-allegro-price-manipulation-poland-e-commerce-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLBI4J5HXVNYFGA23QIPSRM6V4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:53:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，1月份委内瑞拉石油出口在美国控制下大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据显示，在尼古拉斯·马杜罗被美国捕获以及石油封锁解除后，委内瑞拉1月份石油出口量从12月的49.8万桶/日增至约80万桶/日，这使得贸易商得以承运大部分出口货物。【原文：Venezuelan oil exports rose to some 800,000 barrels per day (bpd) in January, from 498,000 bpd in December, after the U.S. capture of Nicolas Maduro and the ending of an oil blockade which has let traders carry most exports, shipping data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuelas-oil-exports-bounce-800000-bpd-january-under-us-control-shipping-data-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXTTIXL4U5KWHM22QMT4UVWVT4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步因司机身份争议与法国社会保障机构展开谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步周一表示，正与法国社会保障机构Urssaf进行磋商。此前有媒体报道称，该机构已认定这家美国公司应将其司机视为雇员。【原文：Uber said on Monday it was in talks with French social security agency Urssaf, which a media report said had concluded the U.S.-based company should treat its drivers as employees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uber-talks-with-french-social-security-agency-after-driver-status-dispute-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7EHZNFPRFI6PLDPKLIH3FDALI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普启动120亿美元矿产储备计划以对抗中国，彭博社报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周一报道，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普计划启动一项战略性关键矿物储备计划，并投入120亿美元启动资金。该报道援引知情人士消息称。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is set to launch a strategic critical minerals stockpile with $12 billion in seed money, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-launches-12-billion-minerals-stockpile-counter-china-bloomberg-news-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCXAFECIWFIRBFYZ2XUAKBKYEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Revvity在第四季度业绩大超预期后，预测2026年利润与营收将高于市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[医疗设备制造商Revvity周一公布的财报远超市场预期，不仅第四季度业绩表现亮眼，其对2026年营收和利润的预测也高于华尔街预期。该公司押注诊断业务将持续强劲增长，尽管学术研究资金持续疲软。【原文：Medical equipment maker Revvity handily beat fourth-quarter estimates and forecast 2026 revenue and profit above Wall Street expectations on Monday, betting on continued strength in its diagnostics business even as weakness in academic research funding persists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/revvity-forecasts-2026-profit-revenue-above-estimates-after-blowout-fourth-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGNO7WPAANJ3NDNVFDUTWE7EPY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国页岩油生产商德文能源与科特拉将以580亿美元达成合并协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国页岩生产商德文能源公司和科特拉能源公司周一宣布，将以580亿美元的全股票交易方式合并，由此诞生美国最大的独立页岩生产商之一。【原文：U.S. shale producers Devon Energy and Coterra Energy are set to merge in a $58 billion all-stock deal to create one of the largest independent shale producers in the country, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/us-shale-producers-devon-coterra-merge-58-billion-deal-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6X6SIBPECVJM5ACK6Y5U7GAYLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品季度利润超预期，得益于鸡肉需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国肉类加工企业泰森食品公司周一公布的季度财报显示，其盈利超出市场预期。尽管牛肉业务亏损严重，但强劲的鸡肉产品需求抵消了这一不利影响。【原文：U.S. meatpacker Tyson Foods reported bigger-than-expected quarterly earnings on Monday, as strong demand for its chicken products overshadowed hefty losses in its beef business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tyson-foods-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-chicken-demand-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FU5AJT27D5PE7L7IQFDWUCXRZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局扩大对约130万辆福特F-150皮卡的调查，涉及变速箱问题。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周一表示，已将针对127万辆福特F-150皮卡的安全调查范围扩大，此前有报告称该车型存在后轮锁死状态下意外降档的情况。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Monday it had expanded a safety-related investigation into 1.27 million Ford F-150 pickup trucks following reports of unexpected downshifts with rear-wheel lockup.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-expands-probe-into-about-13-million-ford-f-150-pickups-over-transmission-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KHAJJYQHRPF7KTFX5526B7ZLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通预计到2026年底金价将达到每盎司6300美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通在周一发布的一份报告中表示，随着央行和投资者需求的持续增长，预计到2026年底金价将达到每盎司6300美元。【原文：J.P. Morgan expects gold prices to reach $6,300 per ounce by the end of 2026, as demand from central banks and investors continues, it said in a note on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jp-morgan-expects-gold-prices-reach-6300oz-by-end-2026-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHDWDKWYWRMXLAS45XLXOJIJKA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:58:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者一月份争相购买黄金及黄金矿业ETF寻求避险]]></title><description><![CDATA[1月份，投资者纷纷涌向黄金、其他贵金属及黄金矿业公司的交易所交易基金，在地缘政治不确定性加剧、美元进一步走弱预期升温以及对美国降息押注增加的背景下寻求避险。【原文：Investors flocked to exchange-traded funds of gold, other precious metals and gold miners in January, seeking safety amid geopolitical uncertainty, expectations of further dollar weakness, and growing bets on U.S. interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/investors-flock-gold-gold-miner-etfs-january-bid-safety-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPIXRSINXZLCPJQI6SZ4FCYBQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:55:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金属熔毁]]></title><description><![CDATA[作者：马克·琼斯，全球市场通讯员【原文：By Marc Jones, Global Markets Correspondent】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23MPXYI7W5PSFIBNUTMTMN3FDE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:48:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大宗商品暴跌引发全球市场震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统提名凯文·沃什担任下一任美联储主席引发抛售潮，贵金属连续第二个交易日暴跌。【原文：A selloff ​unleashed by President Donald Trump's choice of Kevin Warsh for the next U.S. Fed chair sent precious metals tumbling for a second session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/slump-commodities-rattles-global-markets-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UT6UBO4NYFNOZIFEBH77RKBRTA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:44:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼主题乐园助力收益超出华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼公司凭借旗下主题公园及电影《疯狂动物城2》的强劲表现，在截至12月的假日季度财报中超出市场对营收和盈利的预期，其股价在周一盘前交易中上涨4%。【原文：Walt ​Disney's theme parks and the movie "Zootopia 2" helped the company beat revenue and earnings estimates for the ‌holiday quarter ended in December, sending its shares up 4% in premarket trading on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-theme-parks-help-boost-earnings-above-wall-street-forecasts-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTRZPJC6BBKQFBJFLSCCS55ZMU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:42:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在欧洲的注册量显示1月份几乎没有复苏迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉在欧洲部分主要市场的1月新车注册量几乎未见复苏迹象——该月通常是全年销量最低的月份之一。瑞典和丹麦市场有所增长，但法国和挪威市场则出现下滑。【原文：Registrations of new Tesla cars in some of its largest European markets showed little signs of recovery in January, one of the lowest-volume months, rising in Sweden and Denmark but falling in France and Norway.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/tesla-registrations-europe-show-little-recovery-january-2026-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNO65UICJNPPZPXF7ORWNFFK5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:42:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>