<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:35:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:35:41 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴西斯特凡尼公司寻求在美洲和欧洲进行收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[公司创始人兼全球首席执行官马尔科-斯特凡尼尼（Marco Stefanini）表示，总部位于巴西的全球技术咨询公司斯特凡尼尼集团计划在2027年底前斥资20亿雷亚尔（约合3.5亿美元）进行收购。【原文：The Stefanini Group, a global tech consultancy firm based in Brazil, plans to spend 2 billion reais ($350 million) on acquisitions by the end of 2027, said Marco Stefanini, the company's founder and global CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-stefanini-looking-acquisitions-americas-europe-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLDFJD65DVNSDFD4VAH4HVRYBA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国黑人农民在关税动荡中迎接冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为第四代农民，弗吉尼亚州居民小约翰-博伊德（John Boyd Jr）通常会在繁忙的春季准备他的土地，种植甜玉米种子和大豆。【原文：As a fourth generation farmer, Virginia resident John Boyd Jr typically spends the busy spring season prepping his land to plant sweet corn seeds and soybeans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/black-us-farmers-brace-impact-amid-tariffs-turmoil-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RVDLZPTYNLUBPQQH25CFH3E7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼日利亚法官将 Binance 逃税案延期至 5 月 12 日审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼日利亚一名法官周三将针对全球最大加密货币交易所的逃税案延期至下个月，因为税务部门要求允许通过电子邮件向 Binance 送达法庭文件。【原文：A Nigerian judge on Wednesday adjourned a tax evasion case against the world's largest crypto exchange until next month after the revenue service asked for permission to serve court documents by email to Binance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nigerian-judge-adjourns-binance-tax-evasion-case-may-12-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SI32A43L4NPBNPJ756ZIDUNJGI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国移动预计 2025 年资本支出为 67 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥电信巨头 America Movil 的一位高管周三表示，该公司 2025 年的资本支出将为 67 亿美元，低于 2024 年 71 亿美元的资本支出。【原文：An executive of Mexican telecoms giant America Movil said Wednesday that the company's capital expenditure for 2025 would be $6.7 billion, below the $7.1 billion capex in 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/america-movil-forecasts-67-bln-capex-2025-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4LQYM7A6FK4HHLDIUKZN6ZHHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，关税引发的波动导致衍生品相关保证金催缴激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据提供交易后服务的 OSTTRA 公司的数据，在特朗普政府本月宣布对美国征收高于预期的关税后，对冲基金和其他市场参与者的衍生品相关保证金催缴额几乎增加了两倍，在暂停 90 天后又有所下降。【原文：The value of derivative-related margin calls at hedge funds and other market participants nearly tripled after the Trump administration announced larger-than-expected U.S. tariffs this month, before declining after a 90-day pause, according to OSTTRA, which provides post-trade services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/tariff-induced-volatility-caused-spike-derivative-related-margin-calls-data-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSCSLUFFLRL7JDPHYC7MOJVCUM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:57:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通任命主要商业银行部门新领导层]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周三表示，在继续重组商业银行业务的同时，已任命安德鲁-克雷斯（Andrew Kresse）和布莱恩-兰姆（Brian Lamb）领导该部门的两个关键部门。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has appointed Andrew Kresse and Brian Lamb to lead two key sectors in its commercial banking business, the largest U.S. lender said on Wednesday, as it continues to reorganize the unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-names-new-leadership-key-commercial-banking-units-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYKPVXI3H5LN7OKS3QYIEUZWFE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:48:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛恢复对 SNAP 订单收取最低购物篮费]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，并经沃尔玛证实，沃尔玛将恢复对有资格获得美国政府援助的顾客和订阅沃尔玛+ 援助计划的顾客收取最低购物篮费。【原文：Walmart is reinstating a minimum basket fee for customers who qualify for U.S. government assistance and those subscribed to its Walmart+ Assist program, according to a memo seen by Reuters and confirmed by Walmart.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/walmart-reinstates-minimum-basket-fee-snap-orders-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EZCQZI4BROQZAEUMTYGSIIJHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院将就经济萎缩之际控制特朗普关税的议案进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦政府报告称，在总统关税政策的混乱影响下，美国经济出现了三年来的首次萎缩，几个小时后，美国参议院准备在周三就一项阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统一系列关税措施的决议进行投票。【原文：The U.S. Senate was poised on Wednesday to vote on a resolution to block a host of President Donald Trump's tariffs, hours after the federal government reported that the nation's economy contracted for the first time in three years amid the chaos of the president's tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-vote-bill-rein-trump-tariffs-economy-contracts-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBDPIXY34RJQVJRZRLZA5NT5HE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalData 收到 ICG 和 KKR 管理的基金的收购提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国 GlobalData 公司周三表示，已收到私募股权集团 ICG 和 KKR 管理的基金提出的初步收购建议，公司股价最高上涨了 35.9%。【原文：Britain's GlobalData said on Wednesday it had received preliminary takeover proposals from funds managed by private equity groups ICG and KKR , sending its shares up as much as 35.9%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/globaldata-gets-takeover-proposals-funds-managed-by-icg-kkr-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DK5WZ775TZNWNJYGWFUS7NAGD4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，意法半导体拒绝让股东投票选举意大利董事会候选人的要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，两位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，意法半导体（STMicroelectronics）拒绝了意大利政府任命其候选人进入该芯片制造商监事会的新尝试。【原文：STMicroelectronics has rebuffed a fresh Italian government attempt to appoint its candidate to the chipmaker's supervisory board, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/stmicro-rejects-call-let-shareholders-vote-italian-board-candidate-sources-say-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5ITTIVICVNEXDUFFEW2CMZCJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:34:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司呼吁恢复飞机及零部件免税地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司周三呼吁尽快恢复 30 多个国家之间的 1979 年协议，该协议几十年来一直确保飞机和零部件的免税贸易，直到最近爆发贸易战。【原文：Airbus called on Wednesday for a swift return to a 1979 agreement between more than 30 countries that for decades ensured duty-free trading for aircraft and parts until the recent eruption of a trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-calls-return-duty-free-status-aircraft-parts-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUP5A4PL6JKPRGP7MCP6YBMPNY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:29:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 IBM 和雷神公司可能获得空中交通控制系统现代化合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三表示，雷神科技公司（Raytheon Technologies）和国际商业机器公司（IBM）可能会获得国家空中交通控制系统现代化的合同。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Wednesday that the companies Raytheon Technologies and IBM may get the contract to modernize the nation's air traffic controller system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trump-says-ibm-raytheon-might-get-contract-modernize-air-traffic-controller-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAXC4OKC4JPVJIKKWG5LWH5FFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:11:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储前高级央行官员称应放弃现行政策框架]]></title><description><![CDATA[一组前世界顶级央行行长表示，美联储应取消近五年来对就业的偏向，并更加严格地关注通货膨胀，这是在美国央行进行自身战略审查时提出的建议。【原文：A group of former top world central bankers says the Federal Reserve should scrap its nearly five-year-old bias towards jobs and keep a stricter focus on inflation, a recommendation offered as the U.S. central bank conducts its own strategy review.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-should-ditch-current-policy-framework-group-former-top-central-bankers-says-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZF4YBS7DTNMJ7NS5RATA4FZNSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EssilorLuxottica 考虑将部分生产迁往美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[眼镜制造商依视路（EssilorLuxottica）首席执行官周三表示，由于美国征收关税，包括雷朋（Ray-Ban）在内的眼镜品牌可能会将部分生产转移到美国。【原文：Eyewear maker EssilorLuxottica , whose brands include Ray-Ban, could move part of its production to the United States as a result of U.S. tariffs, its chief executive said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/essilorluxottica-consider-moving-part-its-production-us-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTNR4SCFPJKCZNV7OO34UJUCLM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：英伟达首席执行官称特朗普应修改人工智能芯片出口规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三报道，英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）表示，他希望特朗普政府能够改变从美国出口人工智能技术的相关规定，以便企业更好地利用未来的机遇。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang said he would like the Trump administration to change the regulations related to exporting AI technology from the U.S. for businesses to better capitalize on future opportunities, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-ceo-says-trump-should-revise-ai-chip-export-rules-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRAPPCF2FRJKXH4LUITHNQEE7I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:46:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司第一季度业绩超出预期，维持目标不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲空中客车公司公布的第一季度收入和核心利润强于预期，并重申了今年的目标，同时强调现在量化关税的影响还为时过早。【原文：Europe’s Airbus posted stronger-than-expected revenues and core profit for the first quarter and reaffirmed targets for the year, while stressing it was too early to quantify the impact of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-first-quarter-earnings-beat-forecasts-maintains-targets-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35SCJ7VJKRM3DCL5EGMKDNKUVM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citadel Securities 向美国证券监管机构举报 24 小时交易风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citadel 证券公司向美国证券交易委员会递交了一份关于资本市场监管的愿望清单，其中包括对交易所计划的 24 小时交易风险的警告。【原文：Citadel Securities has sent the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission a wish list for capital markets regulation, including warnings about the risks of 24-hour trading planned by exchanges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/citadel-securities-flags-us-securities-regulator-about-24-hour-trading-risks-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5BJXUDF4BPIDGEYJWSTAVMJ7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管季度盈利超预期，但欧洲钢铁企业仍面临贸易和价格风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲顶级钢铁制造商在第一季度的盈利中表现出比预期更强的韧性，但他们警告说，全球贸易紧张局势、欧洲价格疲软和市场波动正在给今年下半年的前景蒙上阴影。【原文：Europe's top steelmakers showed more resilience than expected in their first-quarter earnings, but warned that global trade tensions, weak European prices and market volatility are clouding the outlook for the rest of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/european-steelmakers-flag-trade-price-risks-despite-quarterly-earnings-beats-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NO4OFZIARVIHBIT6AYZYHLIELA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:39:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISS 称摩根士丹利投资者应拒绝扩大股权激励的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[机构股东服务公司（Institutional Shareholder Services）敦促投资者拒绝摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）提出的扩大股权激励补偿计划的建议，因为代理顾问对华尔街的反击正在升级。【原文：Institutional Shareholder Services has urged investors to reject Morgan Stanley's proposal to expand its equity incentive compensation plan, as the proxy adviser escalates its pushback against Wall Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-investors-should-reject-proposal-expand-equity-incentives-iss-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHP56F3VEFJK5PKNVSBPXB65OQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:12:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASM International 表示已开始在美国生产工具。]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰芯片制造设备供应商ASM国际公司首席执行官周三表示，该公司已开始在当地为美国芯片制造商生产工具，以应对美国的关税背景。【原文：Dutch chip-making equipment supplier ASM International has started local production of tools for U.S. chipmakers in response to the U.S. tariffs backdrop, its Chief Executive said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/asm-international-says-it-started-manufacturing-tools-us-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI4CF7G4EBNZLCK36MFOBWMDQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌希望今年与苹果达成双子座协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌首席执行官桑达尔-皮查伊（Sundar Pichai）周三在反垄断庭审中作证时表示，谷歌希望在今年年中之前与苹果达成协议，在新手机上采用其 Gemini 人工智能技术。【原文：Google hopes to enter an agreement with Apple by the middle of this year to include its Gemini AI technology on new phones, CEO Sundar Pichai said in testimony at an antitrust trial on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-hopes-reach-gemini-deal-with-apple-this-year-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZMJCA6CQVJ7TGGG4KF4KA4H2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲主要银行发出谨慎信号，不祥前景影响利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，欧洲大型贷款机构的第一季度利润大丰收，它们仍保持着雄心勃勃的业绩目标，但除了乐观的标题数字外，银行老板们还在考虑未来盈利前景面临的一系列威胁。【原文：Big European lenders are retaining ambitious performance targets after bumper first-quarter profits this week, but beyond the upbeat headline numbers, bank bosses are contemplating a welter of threats to their future earnings prospects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/europes-major-banks-signal-caution-ominous-outlook-tempers-profit-wins-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTWWWS2RHFLCVBT4SLLB74C7QY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:53:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：国际货币基金组织为何阻止哥伦比亚获得信贷额度？]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周六表示，已为哥伦比亚获得其 81 亿美元的灵活信贷额度设定了条件，该额度是用于预防和缓解危机的预防性工具，实际上切断了该国获得该现金的渠道。【原文：The International Monetary Fund said on Saturday it had set conditions for Colombia's access to its $8.1-billion Flexible Credit Line, a precautionary tool for crisis prevention and mitigation, effectively cutting access for the country from that cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/why-did-imf-block-colombias-access-credit-line-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDUO5Y4A6ZLN3DARQ7TGYSFVSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:49:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会将投票禁止被认为存在安全风险的中国实验室测试美国电子产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会将于5月22日投票敲定一项新规定，禁止被认为对美国国家安全构成风险的中国实验室测试在美国使用的智能手机、相机和电脑等电子设备。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission will vote May 22 to finalize a new rule that will bar Chinese labs deemed risks to U.S. national security from testing electronic devices like smartphones, cameras and computers for use in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fcc-vote-bar-chinese-labs-deemed-security-risks-testing-us-electronics-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7OZA5TDLFJSHBY62XOHRRCNBA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:30:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部交易员建议终止联邦债务上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部借款咨询委员会（TBAC）周三的会议纪要显示，美国财政部的一级交易商表示，他们更希望终止联邦债务上限，因为这可能会增加偿债成本和市场波动，并可能损害美元的储备资产地位。【原文：The U.S. Treasury's primary dealers say they would prefer to end the federal debt ceiling, as it likely increases debt service costs and market volatility and may hurt the dollar's reserve asset status, minutes of the Treasury Borrowing Advisory Committee (TBAC) showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasury-dealers-recommend-ending-federal-debt-ceiling-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XS3OTI2SCVKOZEID7HHXYWK46Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月消费支出激增，通胀降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于家庭为避免关税导致的价格上涨和短缺而加大了机动车辆的购买，3月份美国消费者支出稳健增长，但这并没有改变经济学家们认为经济已进入低速增长的观点。【原文：U.S. consumer spending increased solidly in March as households boosted purchases of motor vehicles to avoid higher prices and shortages due to tariffs, but that did little to change economists' views that the economy had shifted into lower gear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-spending-surges-march-inflation-cools-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6QSEEKH45KETPVHGB5DUEMOWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:16:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cotality 数据显示：澳大利亚 4 月房价创纪录，销售量因关税风险而放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚房地产顾问公司Cotality周四表示，尽管美国关税风险和大选的不确定性导致销售和挂牌量下滑，但澳大利亚4月份的房地产价格仍创下历史新高。【原文：Australia's property prices hit a record in April although U.S. tariff risks and election uncertainty led to a slump in the sales and listings volume, property consultant Cotality said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-home-prices-set-record-april-sales-volume-slows-tariff-risk-cotality-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWNIBPH54ZLBHHS7EKT5T5LITI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:15:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国未决房屋销售创一年多来最大增幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[受抵押贷款利率下降的推动，3 月份美国旧房购买合同创下一年多来的最大增幅。【原文：Contracts to buy U.S. previously owned homes surged by the most in more than a year in March, boosted by a decline in mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-pending-home-sales-post-biggest-gain-more-than-year-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAO76X6PMBKNPGSRDE5KEAW45I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约银行要求员工在 9 月前每周上班四天]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的纽约梅隆银行执行委员会的一份备忘录，该银行要求其员工在 9 月 2 日之前从目前的每周三天返回办公室四天。【原文：Bank of New York Mellon has asked its employees to return to the office four days a week by September 2 from a current three days, according to a memo from the bank's executive committee seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/bny-asks-employees-return-office-four-days-week-by-september-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3RWTBYURZLHZCOLKYJCMZU3YM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道发言人证实，TikTok 计划在芬兰建造价值 10 亿欧元的数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 发言人周三证实，TikTok 计划投资 10 亿欧元（11.4 亿美元）在芬兰建立第一个数据中心，将欧洲用户的数据存储转移到芬兰大陆。【原文：TikTok plans to invest 1 billion euros ($1.14 billion) to build its first data centre in Finland as it moves data storage for European users to the continent, a TikTok spokesman confirmed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/tiktok-plans-build-1-bln-euro-data-centre-finland-spokesman-confirms-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPIWUN62SRO4PG3VICJ472PPF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:56:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>