<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:43:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:43:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称消费者保护局仍无法监控金融公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封内部邮件显示，陷入困境的美国消费者金融保护局（Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）的高层官员尽管承诺参与所有法律要求的工作，但仍不允许员工恢复对金融公司的监督。【原文：Top officials at the embattled U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau have not allowed staff to resume supervising financial companies despite committing to engage in all legally-required work, according to an internal email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/consumer-bureau-still-blocked-monitoring-financial-firms-email-says-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DV6GDOVNQ5PO7BXHJ4ATDO75UA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员希望马斯克和 FAA 代理局长就空中交通系统作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员埃德-马基（Ed Markey）周一敦促立法者传唤 SpaceX 公司首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）和联邦航空管理局代理局长就空中交通管制 IT 系统作证。【原文：Democratic Senator Ed Markey on Monday urged lawmakers to call SpaceX CEO Elon Musk and the acting head of the Federal Aviation Administration to testify about air traffic control IT systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senator-wants-musk-acting-faa-chief-testify-air-traffic-systems-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYHG5Q4W5JJ3ZE2XSETG2IX7L4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空要求美国最高法院撤销禁止捷蓝航空结盟的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司要求美国最高法院推翻下级法院的一项判决，该判决认定美国航空公司与捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）在美国东北部的合作关系已经破裂，违反了联邦反垄断法。【原文：American Airlines has asked the U.S. Supreme Court to reverse a lower-court decision that found its now-scrapped U.S. Northeast partnership with JetBlue Airways violated federal antitrust law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/american-airlines-asks-us-supreme-court-reverse-ruling-barring-jetblue-alliance-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RHJDSRPHZPALBE2NO5I64OXVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:28:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称特朗普政府将终止洛杉矶和费城地区办事处的大楼租约]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封电子邮件，美国证券交易委员会周一通知工作人员，特朗普政府正准备终止其洛杉矶和费城地区办事处的大楼租约。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission informed staff on Monday the Trump administration is preparing to terminate building leases for its regional offices in Los Angeles and Philadelphia, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-says-trump-administration-terminate-building-leases-los-angeles-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEVM6QR67FKF3PQUZNKUZ3B7B4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品及药物管理局称，野生海岸公司因禽流感污染风险召回生猫食品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周一表示，Wild Coast 公司正在召回一批冷冻生食猫用鸡肉配方，因为这些产品可能受到禽流感病毒的污染。【原文：Wild Coast is recalling lots of its frozen raw chicken formula for cats as it could potentially be contaminated by the bird flu virus, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/wild-coast-recalling-raw-cat-food-bird-flu-contamination-risk-fda-says-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64X3SJ2PRJJODBLRURGQWRXEBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:51:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定 ITG 欠雷诺美国公司 2.515 亿美元的佛罗里达烟草和解金]]></title><description><![CDATA[特拉华州一名法官周一命令 ITG Brands 向竞争对手卷烟生产商雷诺美国公司支付 2.515 亿美元，这与十年前 ITG 从雷诺公司购买四个卷烟品牌后达成的佛罗里达州烟草和解协议有关。【原文：A Delaware judge on Monday ordered ITG Brands to pay rival cigarette maker Reynolds American $251.5 million in connection with a Florida tobacco settlement, following ITG's purchase of four cigarette brands from Reynolds a decade ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/itg-owes-reynolds-american-2515-million-florida-tobacco-settlement-judge-rules-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KU3B7JZISVIR7BYO3ADKLC2L74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:20:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普政府官员将向国会通报美国国际开发署的情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，两位熟悉该计划的消息人士称，美国国际开发署候任副署长 Pete Marocco 将于周三与国会议员会面，讨论对外援助问题。【原文：Pete Marocco, deputy administrator-designate at the U.S. Agency for International Development, will meet with members of Congress on Wednesday to discuss foreign assistance, two sources familiar with the plan said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/trump-administration-official-brief-congress-usaid-sources-say-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUAHPNLOKZPCBFPQN6XLX2BXIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:59:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员要求卢比奥回答有关计划购买特斯拉 Cybertruck 的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员理查德-布卢门撒尔（Richard Blumenthal）周一要求美国国务卿马可-鲁比奥（Marco Rubio）回答有关据报道计划斥资 4 亿美元购买装甲版特斯拉 Cybertrucks 以运送外交官的问题。【原文：Democratic Senator Richard Blumenthal on Monday asked U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio to answer questions about a reported plan to spend $400 million to purchase armored versions of Tesla Cybertrucks to transport diplomats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-senator-asks-rubio-answer-questions-planned-tesla-cybertruck-purchase-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DE5MTBVINBP4REDHJ4NC4MKUBM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼负责人绕过国会规定，恢复本宁堡的名称]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防部长周一下令美国陆军将摩尔堡改回其原名本宁堡（Fort Benning），撤消因种族正义抗议而在 2023 年进行的更名。【原文：U.S. Defense Secretary on Monday ordered the U.S. Army to rename Fort Moore back to its original name of Fort Benning, undoing a 2023 name change that was driven by racial justice protests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-chief-restores-name-fort-benning-sidesteps-congressional-provision-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2E7KE6R5FKDTNTVLPXLQHT76I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党州长招募被特朗普解雇的政府工作人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）试图通过快速的大规模裁员和买断来减少联邦工作人员数量之际，一些民主党州长正在吸引新失业人员转而为州政府工作。【原文：As U.S. President Donald Trump seeks to reduce the size of the federal workforce through rapid-fire mass layoffs and buyouts, some Democratic governors are courting the newly unemployed to come to work for state governments instead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-governors-recruit-government-workers-laid-off-by-trump-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJUSXMQIQFMI5H4ADA7NIVHHUA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局调查华盛顿特区机场的错误碰撞警报]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）正在调查为什么周六有几名机组人员在抵达华盛顿里根国家机场时收到了飞机可能就在附近的故障警报。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration is investigating why several flight crews on Saturday received faulty alerts of potentially nearby aircraft on arrival at Washington's Reagan National Airport.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-faa-investigating-false-aircraft-alerts-washington-dc-airport-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6UDONERZFI4BGJIZSQBEBMUOA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:20:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[裁员之际，华盛顿的远程联邦工作人员受到气球和糖果的欢迎]]></title><description><![CDATA[这一幕让一些联邦工作人员感到不快，也让他们觉得语气不对。【原文：It was a scene some federal workers found upsetting and tone deaf.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/remote-federal-workers-washington-greeted-with-balloons-candy-amid-layoffs-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JS6BACN4FNJBTHE65GRB5MLZTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥七月四日游行枪击案男子认罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，一名男子周一承认犯有谋杀罪，他于 2022 年在芝加哥郊区的独立日游行中发动大规模枪击，造成 7 人死亡。【原文：A man pleaded guilty to murder on Monday for a 2022 mass shooting at an Independence Day parade in a Chicago suburb that killed seven people, local media reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/man-pleads-guilty-chicago-july-4th-parade-shooting-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LS2ED5PUXJMT7O44XDALMLUUNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:08:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，华盛顿最高联邦检察官称其办公室将追查所有枪支案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部备忘录，华盛顿特区的联邦检察官周一接到命令，必须追查移交给他们的每一起枪支案件，并寻求对每一个被控犯有此类罪行的人进行审前拘留。【原文：Federal prosecutors in Washington, D.C., were ordered on Monday to pursue every firearms case referred to them and to seek pretrial detention against every person charged with such an offense, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/top-federal-prosecutor-washington-says-his-office-will-pursue-all-gun-cases-memo-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2RKY6OHFNLRNO45YUHTGSCYNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:18:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司希望禁止直升机飞越华盛顿特区机场附近的部分航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年 1 月，一架陆军直升机与美国航空公司的支线喷气式飞机在华盛顿里根国家机场附近相撞，造成 67 人死亡。【原文：A group representing U.S. airlines wants a series of safety changes after a fatal collision between an Army helicopter and American Airlines regional jet killed 67 people in January near Washington's Reagan National Airport.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-want-helicopters-barred-some-routes-near-dc-airport-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEOA5RZVQVNQZBX366NDMDZJZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月份建筑支出意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[受多户住宅建设支出下降的影响，1 月份美国建筑支出意外下降。【原文：U.S. construction spending unexpectedly fell in January, pulled down by a decline in outlays on multi-family homebuilding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-construction-spending-unexpectedly-declines-january-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53EZGD4TQFLTFCA5MN4RBOQOVM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国卫生机构称员工必须回复卫生部电子邮件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部周一告诉员工，他们必须回复特朗普政府要求他们总结过去一周工作的电子邮件，这推翻了该部门此前的立场。【原文：The U.S. Department of Health and Human Services told employees on Monday that they were required to respond to an email from the Trump administration demanding they summarize their work over the past week, reversing its earlier position.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-health-agency-now-says-employees-must-respond-doge-email-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2Q32OCV4BMXDAN73WD6DOODIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2 月份美国制造业保持稳定，但关税风暴正在酝酿之中]]></title><description><![CDATA[2 月份，美国制造业保持稳定，但衡量工厂门口价格的一项指标跃升至近三年来的新高，而且材料交付所需的时间也在延长，这表明进口关税可能很快会阻碍生产。【原文：U.S. manufacturing was steady in February, but a measure of prices at the factory gate jumped to near a three-year high and it was taking longer for materials to be delivered, suggesting that tariffs on imports could soon hamper production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-stable-february-storm-brewing-tariffs-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSISBK65BNKHJBRRIJKQXRYUZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回有关印第安纳大学偏见报告政策的争议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一拒绝审理一个保守派团体以言论自由为由对印第安纳大学监控和报告学校认为是偏见动机事件的政策提出的质疑。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Monday to hear a conservative group's challenge on free speech grounds to Indiana University's policy for monitoring and reporting what the school considers to be bias-motivated incidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-turns-away-dispute-over-indiana-university-bias-reporting-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYY6Y7PXSZKGHAKH5ND7OXWEJM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，特朗普将宣布投资事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周一下午 1:30 /格林尼治标准时间 18:30 发布 "投资公告"，但未提供任何其他细节。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will make an "investment announcement" at 1:30 p.m./1830 GMT on Monday, the White House said without offering any other details.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-make-investment-announcement-white-house-says-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFCQ367WFNOVDFHHOGHSUG5JEM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 13:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者监督机构被特朗普政府架空，赔付陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一家权益组织称，特朗普政府将美国消费者金融保护局搁置起来的决定，使得一笔用于帮助据称受到学生贷款服务机构纳维利特公司（Navient）伤害的借款人的 1 亿美元资金陷入困境。【原文：The Trump administration's decision to put the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau on ice has left a $100 million pot of money intended for borrowers allegedly harmed by the student loan servicer Navient sitting in limbo, according to an advocacy organization.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/consumer-watchdog-payouts-limbo-agency-defanged-by-trump-administration-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWP7UEU6C5IT3IM4HSAMQ54GBM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:16:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在太阳能电池板下放牧的绵羊帮助美国农民度过农作物价格低迷期]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷恩斯一家四代人中，去年第一次没有种植一粒棉花种子。查德-雷恩斯（Chad Raines）把拖拉机停了下来，把得克萨斯州的大部分农田租给了邻居。【原文：For the first time in four generations, the Raines family didn't plant a single cotton seed last year. Chad Raines parked his tractor and rented out most of his Texas farmland to a neighbor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/sheep-grazing-under-solar-panels-help-us-farmers-survive-crop-price-slump-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UV7UPDMO4FKZ5NQWTUHBP7ZEZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:10:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 3 月 14 日最后期限到来之前，美国国会尚未达成避免停摆的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[距离 3 月 14 日的最后期限还有不到两周的时间，美国国会的共和党和民主党似乎还远未达成避免政府关门的协议，而政府关门将使华盛顿陷入更深的动荡。【原文：With less than two weeks to go before a March 14 deadline, Republicans and Democrats in the U.S. Congress appear to be nowhere close to a deal to avert a government shutdown that would throw Washington into deeper turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-congress-nowhere-close-deal-avert-shutdown-ahead-march-14-deadline-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCWWKKWHEJP73EVNFQHKFDV4CU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球时报》称中国准备对美国关税威胁采取反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家控制的《环球时报》报道，中国正准备对将于周二生效的美国新进口关税采取反制措施，这增加了世界前两大经济体之间爆发全面贸易战的可能性。【原文：China is preparing countermeasures against fresh U.S. import tariffs set to take effect on Tuesday, China's state-controlled Global Times reported, raising the prospect of an all-out trade war between the world's top two economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-preparing-countermeasures-us-tariff-threat-global-times-says-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQSCHT62BFJDJGJSYUCG3H4HGY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 03:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长希望将政府支出从 GDP 中剔除]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周日表示，他将从国内生产总值（GDP）报告中剔除政府支出，但没有说明这一变化可能在多长时间内发生，同时他也否认了可能出现经济衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said on Sunday he would strip out government spending from the gross domestic product (GDP) report, but gave no indication how soon this change might happen, while dismissing fears of a possible recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-commerce-secretary-wants-remove-government-spending-gdp-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUF33FFSUZL4NJF7LGLWXJQCCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 03:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税紧张局势加剧，铁矿石创逾六周新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国与第一大消费国中国之间的贸易紧张局势加剧，铁矿石期货周一连续第六个交易日下跌，尽管乐观的中国制造业数据缓解了跌势。【原文：Iron ore futures fell for a sixth straight session on Monday amid rising trade tensions between the U.S. and top consumer China, although upbeat Chinese manufacturing data cushioned the fall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/iron-ore-more-than-6-week-low-mounting-us-tariff-tensions-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2TZYEYF4BPIHJMMZ4MW5JZ6MA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 03:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国制造业数据向好，乐观情绪有所升温，石油价格回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周一上涨了 1%，原因是全球最大的原油进口国中国的制造业数据向好，使人们对燃料需求重新感到乐观，尽管美国可能加征关税给全球经济增长带来的不确定性依然存在。【原文：Oil prices rose 1% on Monday as upbeat manufacturing data from China, the world's biggest crude importer, led to renewed optimism for fuel demand, although uncertainty about global economic growth from potential U.S. tariffs loomed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-recovers-upbeat-chinese-manufacturing-data-increases-some-optimism-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XS64OAT25VOYVGV4HQPAKZO3DA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:12:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国际开发署（USAID）官员警告说，特朗普的外援封锁会造成不必要的死亡，然后又说他被放假了]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国际开发署（U.S. Agency for International Development）的一名高级官员在周日的一封电子邮件中警告说，特朗普政府解散该机构将导致不必要的死亡--但不到30分钟后，他就给自己的员工发邮件说，他已经被安排休假。【原文：A senior official with the U.S. Agency for International Development in an email on Sunday warned that the Trump administration's dismantling of the agency will result in unnecessary deaths -- only to email his staff less than 30 minutes later to say that he had been placed on leave.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/usaid-official-warns-unnecessary-deaths-trumps-foreign-aid-block-then-says-hes-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4WFWQSG3JPGPFLEJA3RQS6SAI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称，七国集团正在敲定伊萨卡总统下台计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[处于收购战中心的日本零售巨头 Seven &amp; i 控股公司正在敲定一项计划，让公司总裁下台，由公司首位外国总裁接任。【原文：Seven &amp; i Holdings , the Japanese retail giant at the centre of a takeover battle, is finalising a plan for its president to step down and be replaced by the company's first foreign chief.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/seven-i-finalising-plan-president-isaka-step-down-nikkei-says-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5G27DTCQO5KUPD65H2326K2O7U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部表示不会执行反洗钱法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周日表示，将不会执行一项要求数百万企业实体披露其真实受益所有人身份的反洗钱法。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department said on Sunday it would not enforce an anti-money laundering law that obliges millions of business entities to disclose the identities of their real beneficial owners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasury-department-says-it-will-not-enforce-anti-money-laundering-law-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJCM4ZVOZZJX5BQNQNLH564GEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>