<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 05:07:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 05:07:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理称预计美国将继续征收 10%的基准关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴尼塞（Anthony Albanese）周五表示，澳大利亚可能仍将对所有出口美国的产品征收10%的关税，但政府将继续努力通过谈判争取豁免。【原文：Australia will likely still be subjected to the 10% tariff rate on all exports to U.S. but the government will continue to try and negotiate for an exemption, Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-pm-says-he-expects-10-us-baseline-tariff-stay-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNUY3FAC7NIDXO6NWSS3JOLQVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 04:42:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 市场焦点转向特朗普关税倒计时]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZBPFGE73BK4FC7673I6MVUR4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 04:40:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[低值货物免税漏洞的终结扰乱了从中国空运到美国的货物运输]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易团体和分析师表示，自美国在 5 月初取消对来自中国的低价值包裹免税以来，来自亚洲的航空货运量下降了两位数。【原文：Air cargo shipment volume from Asia has declined by double digits since the U.S. cancelled a tax-free exemption for low-value packages from China early in May, trade groups and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/end-tax-free-loophole-low-value-goods-disrupts-air-shipments-us-china-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BID7KYGA3VLLRIPZREZ4GX3CAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 04:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国敦促对辅助驾驶技术慎之又慎、快之又快]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的汽车制造商在推动辅助驾驶技术方面正在超越外国竞争对手，以吸引渴望快速创新的驾车者。【原文：China's automakers are outpacing foreign rivals in their push for assisted-driving technology, eager to woo motorists hungry for rapid innovation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-urges-caution-speed-assisted-driving-technology-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTFXHTR7JRLA7JZ7ZLNTP5OMCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 04:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市震荡，美元走低，关税最后期限成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管隔夜华尔街创下历史新高，但由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）要求贸易协议的最后期限即将在下周到来，大多数亚洲股市周五仍在挣扎。【原文：Most Asian equity markets struggled on Friday, despite record highs for Wall Street overnight, as U.S. President Donald Trump's deadline for trade deals loomed next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXKDRAVRVRNLRK2OPYP73E7BB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 03:15:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本受高温影响的抹茶产量难以满足全球急剧增长的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[抹茶爱好者们，请准备好你们的钱包！【原文：Matcha lovers, brace your wallets!】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-heat-stressed-matcha-tea-output-struggles-meet-soaring-global-demand-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUHWOKLOYNKBXKJ3R4ZFB6QOEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 02:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易压力增大，美元兑欧元、日元保持坚挺]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的标志性减税法案通过最后一关，以及各国在与美国达成贸易协议方面的压力增大之后，美元周五保持涨势。【原文：The dollar held gains on Friday after President Donald Trump got his signature tax cut bill across the final hurdle and pressure mounted on countries to secure trade deals with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-holds-firm-against-euro-yen-us-trade-pressure-mounts-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWYDXCMPBVOWPE7MHPKNVJUF4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 01:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业市场稳固，关税不确定，油价持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五油价变化不大，因为稳健的就业市场增强了美国联邦储备委员会维持利率不变的理由，投资者也在等待唐纳德-特朗普总统对各国征收关税计划的明朗化。【原文：Oil prices were little changed on Friday as a solid job market bolstered the case for the U.S. Federal Reserve keeping interest rates on hold, with investors also awaiting clarity on President Donald Trump's plans for tariffs on various countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-steady-solid-job-market-tariff-uncertainty-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JUHAHBFXFIFFDQSFLCOKXO6CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于经济放缓，预计澳大利亚央行将于 7 月 8 日第三次降息：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对经济学家进行的一项调查显示，通胀缓解和经济放缓将促使澳大利亚储备银行在 5 月份放宽政策的幅度超过预期，这些经济学家预计澳大利亚储备银行将在周二第三次降息 25 个基点。【原文：Easing inflation and a slowing economy will prompt the Reserve Bank of Australia to ease policy more than predicted in May, according to a Reuters poll of economists who expect the central bank to deliver a third 25 basis point rate cut on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rba-expected-cut-rates-third-time-july-8-economy-slows-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZJWC2TJUX5L2DOEUBSDDAXBJNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:09:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，埃克森公司和赫斯公司就雪佛龙交易纠纷的仲裁员已达成裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，埃克森美孚与赫斯公司之间法律纠纷的仲裁人已就圭亚那的一个大型油田项目做出裁决，该裁决将决定雪佛龙公司是否能继续推进收购赫斯公司的计划。【原文：The arbitrators in a legal dispute between Exxon Mobil and Hess have reached a decision related to a major oilfield project in Guyana, according to two sources familiar with the matter, with the ruling determining whether Chevron can move forward with its planned acquisition of Hess.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/arbitrators-exxon-hess-dispute-over-chevron-deal-have-reached-decision-sources-2025-07-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCATSWQIYBJD7LBM72UUUCG5AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际咖啡组织（ICO）负责人称三年内可缓解全球咖啡供应压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际咖啡组织（ICO）执行主任瓦努西亚-诺盖拉（Vanusia Nogueira）周四在巴西举行的一次活动上说，随着受创纪录高价刺激的新种植园开始生产，全球咖啡供应可能在三年内得到改善。【原文：Global coffee supply could improve in three years as new plantations spurred by record high prices start producing, International Coffee Organization (ICO) Executive Director Vanusia Nogueira said on Thursday at an event in Brazil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/global-coffee-supply-relief-possible-three-years-ico-head-says-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XK2TLFZBB5NCJGRQG4TU3C6RQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 23:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AutoMotive 新数据显示，特斯拉 6 月份在英国的销量同比增长 12]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究机构 New AutoMotive 周五的数据显示，特斯拉 6 月份在英国的新车销量同比增长了 12%，因为这家美国汽车制造商上个月开始交付其升级版 Model Y。【原文：Tesla's new car sales in Britain grew 12% year-on-year in June, data from research group New AutoMotive showed on Friday, as the U.S. automaker started deliveries of its updated Model Y last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-uk-sales-rise-12-june-year-ago-new-automotive-data-shows-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RILX64TXENJWTCUBAOVBY6PIIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 23:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行将 2025 年布伦特原油价格预期上调至每桶 72 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）周四表示，由于需求前景改善，该公司将2025年的布伦特油价预期上调了6美元，至每桶72美元，并将2026年的布伦特油价预期上调了10美元，至每桶70美元。【原文：Barclays on Thursday said it raised its Brent oil price forecast by $6 to $72 per barrel for 2025 and by $10 to $70 a barrel for 2026 on an improved outlook for demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/barclays-raises-brent-forecast-72-per-barrel-2025-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYVVFIZVIZIA5PKO4BT46N75GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 23:04:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司新任首席财务官马拉维的基本年薪为 105 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周四表示，新上任的首席财务官耶稣-"杰伊"-马拉维（Jesus "Jay" Malave）将获得 105 万美元的基本年薪，并有资格获得目标值分别为 126 万美元和 650 万美元的年度和长期奖励。【原文：Boeing Co said on Thursday that incoming CFO Jesus "Jay" Malave would receive $1.05 million as an annual base salary and he would be eligible for annual and long-term incentive awards with target values of $1.26 million and $6.5 million, respectively.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-new-cfo-malave-receive-105-million-annual-base-salary-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCCSY2F3GZJ2HDJWDWW5N2QBTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 22:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[清洁能源支持者抨击美国预算法案是一种挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，清洁能源的倡导者谴责众议院最终通过了唐纳德-特朗普总统的减税法案，认为这是能源转型道路上的一次逆转，而化石燃料利益集团则欢欣鼓舞。【原文：Advocates of clean energy on Thursday decried the final passage of President Donald Trump's tax cut bill by the House of Representatives as a reversal of course on the energy transition, while fossil-fuel interests rejoiced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/clean-energy-backers-blast-us-budget-bill-setback-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6R2275B67VOTFN4EZIYLB6N2UA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司获得价值 28 亿美元的美国战略卫星合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周四表示，该公司已获得一份价值 28 亿美元的美国战略合同，用于开发和生产两颗卫星，并可选择再生产两颗。【原文：Boeing Co said Thursday it had secured a $2.8 billion U.S. strategic contract to develop and produce two satellites with options for two more.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-secures-28-billion-us-strategic-satellite-contract-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHQO7VFLFZIAVCYLNKIBNBYXIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国解除对中国商飞的通用电气喷气发动机许可证暂停令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国商务部周四通知通用电气航空航天集团（GE Aerospace），再次允许该公司向中国商飞（COMAC）运输喷气发动机，取消了几周前颁发的许可证暂停令。【原文：The U.S. Department of Commerce informed GE Aerospace on Thursday that it was once again allowed to ship jet engines to China's COMAC, lifting license suspensions issued several weeks ago, according to a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-lifts-license-suspensions-ge-jet-engines-chinas-comac-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PTJTGCATJIVBBEDCLD5ZO7Z6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行将于 7 月 9 日把利率维持在 3.25%，但今年将再降息一次：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[接受路透社调查的大多数经济学家预计，新西兰储备银行将在7月9日维持利率不变，预测中值显示今年将再降息一次，每次25个基点，而5月份的调查显示降息两次。【原文：The Reserve Bank of New Zealand will leave interest rates unchanged on July 9, a majority of economists polled by Reuters expected, with the median forecast showing just one more 25 basis point cut this year compared with two in a May survey.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rbnz-hold-rates-325-july-9-cut-once-more-this-year-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSRYLL3LHNO6ZNZ7ZJJZI4ACSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电动汽车减税政策将于 9 月 30 日到期]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是美国电动汽车税收抵免的终点。【原文：It is the end of the line for U.S. electric vehicle tax credits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-electric-vehicle-tax-breaks-will-expire-sept-30-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZ2LD2MCGBKZJDBQUXSHDLRCFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国众议院批准特朗普的巨型预算法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党控制的美国众议院周四通过了唐纳德-特朗普总统的大规模减税和支出法案。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives passed President Donald Trump's massive tax-cut and spending bill on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/view-us-house-approves-trumps-mega-budget-bill-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDLWB6UZ3ZMHLH6WJOUJL4WTHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对零售商而言，美越贸易协定留下了问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家周四表示，美国和越南宣布的一项贸易协议给耐克和阿迪达斯等从东南亚国家工厂采购鞋类和服装的运动服装零售商带来了新的问号。【原文：A trade deal announced by the U.S. and Vietnam creates new question marks for sportswear and clothing retailers like Nike and Adidas that source shoes and clothes from factories in the Southeast Asian country, industry experts said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retailers-us-vietnam-trade-deal-leaves-questions-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLED6I3CVVIERDNJY2UD7EZHBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:21:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长认为 100 个国家将被征收 10%的互惠关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，约有100个国家可能会被征收10%的互惠关税，他还补充说，预计在7月9日的最后期限之前会有 "大量 "贸易协议宣布，关税税率可能会大幅提高。【原文：About 100 countries are likely to see a reciprocal tariff rate of 10%, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday, adding that he expects "a flurry" of trade deals announced before a July 9 deadline that could see tariff rates increase sharply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasury-chief-sees-100-countries-getting-10-reciprocal-tariff-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WN4OPN4PCVIBFIZ5UPOABCAXBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的税收法案避免了一次债务危机，却使未来的财务困境更加严重]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的减税和支出法案于周四在国会获得通过，避免了美国政府违约的近期前景，但却使美国的长期债务问题变得更加严重。【原文：President Donald Trump's tax-cut and spending bill, which passed Congress on Thursday, averts the near-term prospect of a U.S. government default but makes America’s long-term debt problems even worse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-tax-bill-averts-one-debt-crisis-makes-future-financial-woes-worse-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGU5IHS6CJOC5LSICR5AA5CWCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联航和捷蓝航空要求美国驳回精神航空对合作关系的投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）和美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周四要求美国交通部驳回精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）就两家公司拟议的合作关系提出的申诉。【原文：JetBlue Airways and United Airlines on Thursday asked the U.S. Transportation Department to reject a complaint filed by Spirit Airlines over their proposed partnership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/united-jetblue-ask-us-reject-spirit-airlines-complaint-over-partnership-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UHP4XIY7FPNXBNFBOCHC2GHRE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:42:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 在人工智能人才争夺战中挖走首席执行官格罗斯后，Sutskever 将领导 Safe Superintelligence 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[伊利亚-苏茨克沃（Ilya Sutskever）在失去首席执行官丹尼尔-格罗斯（Daniel Gross）后，接管了他去年创办的人工智能初创公司安全超级智能公司（SSI）。【原文：Ilya Sutskever has taken over the reins of Safe Superintelligence (SSI), the artificial intelligence startup he launched last year, after losing CEO Daniel Gross to an intensifying talent war in the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sutskever-lead-safe-superintelligence-after-meta-poaches-ceo-gross-ai-talent-war-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZYYQUKBEVN3BMKND3FZATHIJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商连续第 10 周减少石油和天然气钻机数量]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周四在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第10周削减石油和天然气钻机数量，这是自2020年7月以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating for a 10th week in a row for the first time since July 2020, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-cut-oil-gas-rigs-10th-week-row-baker-hughes-says-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JHZTALX3VVMWFH44LPQBSNYBPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球音乐和维珍音乐首席执行官回击批评 Downtown Music 交易的人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）旗下维珍音乐集团（Virgin Music Group）的两位联合首席执行官周四回击了对该公司斥资 7.75 亿美元收购 Downtown Music 的批评，称这笔交易将创建一家为独立唱片公司提供广泛服务的公司。【原文：The two co-chief executives of Universal Music Group's Virgin Music Group on Thursday pushed back against critics of its $775 million acquisition of Downtown Music, saying the deal would create a company providing a wide range of services to independent labels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/universals-virgin-music-ceos-push-back-against-critics-downtown-music-deal-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JR6L672AJNIYPPVHFRXRI6ISAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普如何开始塑造就业市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统第二次入主白宫已有约半年时间，他开始通过政策调整来塑造美国部分就业市场，包括积极打击移民和裁减联邦工作人员。【原文：Roughly half a year into his second stint in the White House, President Donald Trump is starting to shape portions of the U.S. job market through his policy changes, including aggressive crackdowns on immigration and reductions in the federal workforce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-trump-is-starting-shape-job-market-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIU4RTC5SZI4ZL6O2JHI6BGTT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UPS 向其美国司机提供自愿买断方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[包裹巨头 UPS 周四表示，作为其历史上最大规模网络重组的一部分，它将向全职美国司机提供自愿买断服务。【原文：Parcel giant UPS said on Thursday it will offer voluntary buyouts to its full-time U.S. drivers as part of the largest network reconfiguration in its history — a sweeping overhaul that includes cutting 20,000 jobs and closing 73 facilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/ups-offers-voluntary-buyout-packages-its-us-drivers-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XA3QVZ6UYNNVLBNRRQ7RQEMXPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，特朗普政府将在秋季重点讨论美联储主席的接替问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四告诉CNBC，特朗普政府将在今年秋天集中精力寻找美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）的继任者，并补充说官员们有 "很多不错的人选"。【原文：The Trump administration will focus on finding a replacement for Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell this fall, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told CNBC on Thursday, adding that officials had "a lot of good candidates."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-will-focus-fed-chair-replacement-fall-bessent-says-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJTTHBPYDFMONLOWF5N6WOC4E4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>