<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 20:05:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 20:05:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，没有传统汽车销售经验的特斯拉 IT 高管正在负责销售工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟知内情的人士透露，特斯拉的销售团队正在由一位相对鲜为人知的信息技术高管管理，这家电动汽车制造商正在努力应对销量下滑的困境。【原文：A relatively little-known information technology executive is running Tesla's sales team as the electric carmaker grapples with a sales freefall, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-it-exec-with-no-traditional-car-sales-experience-is-running-sales-sources-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CQQAPMENZJ5NEIG7XUSAHNCPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币行业在关键一周市值突破 4 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据CoinGecko的数据，加密货币行业的市值在上周五达到了4万亿美元，这是一个里程碑，反映了加密货币从一个新兴资产类别转变为全球投资版图的核心部分。【原文：The crypto sector's market value hit $4 trillion on Friday, according to CoinGecko, marking a milestone that reflects its shift from a nascent asset class to a central part of the global investment landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/crypto-sector-breaches-4-trillion-market-value-during-pivotal-week-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIM5I5X6UJOCVAJROCTJE7RWRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:46:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储古尔斯比：新关税公告可能推迟降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，不断 "滴滴答答 "地宣布新的关税，削弱了关税对价格只有一次性影响的观点，而且在关税最终走向不明确的情况下，央行将需要更多时间来决定降息是否合适。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee on Friday said the constant "drip drip" of new tariff announcements undercuts the idea that tariffs have only a one-time impact on prices, and without clarity on where they will end up the central bank will need more time to decide if rate cuts are appropriate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-new-tariff-announcements-may-delay-rate-cuts-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62HA27PZGBO5BLTIHISTTRORLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:38:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙赢得埃克森案，但失去了时间、石油和数十亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚在阻止雪佛龙 550 亿美元收购赫斯交易的仲裁中败诉，但这家美国顶级石油生产商成功地将这一合作推迟了一年多，使其竞争对手损失了数十亿圭亚那石油收入，并减缓了整合速度。【原文：Exxon Mobil has lost its arbitration challenge to block Chevron's $55 billion Hess acquisition deal, but the top U.S. oil producer managed to delay the tie-up by over a year, costing its rival billions in lost Guyana oil revenue and slowing integration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-wins-exxon-case-loses-time-oil-billions-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGZZPHIOENKSLIAHFCKJPTE6Y4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署稳定币法律，加密货币行业瞄准主流应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五签署了一项法律，为与美元挂钩的加密货币--稳定币--建立监管制度，这是一个里程碑，可能会为数字资产成为日常支付和转移资金的方式铺平道路。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday signed a law to create a regulatory regime for U.S.-dollar-pegged cryptocurrencies known as stablecoins, a milestone that could pave the way for the digital assets to become an everyday way to make payments and move money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-signs-stablecoin-law-crypto-industry-aims-mainstream-adoption-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXDVAODWBNO2RBJPJMC3XH4UYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:31:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软有可能签署欧盟人工智能实践准则，Meta 则拒绝接受指导方针]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司总裁周五告诉路透社，微软很可能会签署欧盟的实践准则，以帮助企业遵守该集团具有里程碑意义的人工智能规则。【原文：Microsoft will likely sign the European Union's code of practice to help companies comply with the bloc's landmark artificial intelligence rules, its president told Reuters on Friday, while Meta Platforms rebuffed the guidelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-likely-sign-eu-ai-code-practice-meta-rebuffs-guidelines-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGAUMHYU5RMTDEKEBRVQJVLDMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃勒尔表示，如果特朗普提出要求，他愿意领导美联储，但目前还没有联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[主张立即降息的美联储理事克里斯-沃勒（Chris Waller）周五表示，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提出要求，他将接受美国央行行长一职，但迄今为止特朗普尚未就此事与他联系。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Chris Waller, an advocate for an immediate interest rate cut, said on Friday he would accept the job as head of the U.S. central bank if asked by President Donald Trump, but so far Trump has not contacted him about it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/waller-says-hes-willing-to-lead-fed-if-trump-asks-no-contact-so-far-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHOLRIMT45NYHDXBCCILIDS4DY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 启动 5000 万美元基金，支持非营利组织和社区组织]]></title><description><![CDATA[ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 周五表示，该人工智能公司正在发起一项 5000 万美元的基金，以支持非营利组织和社区组织。【原文：ChatGPT maker OpenAI is launching a $50 million fund to support nonprofit and community organizations, the artificial intelligence company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/openai-launches-50-million-fund-support-nonprofits-community-organizations-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VO4R4FWRIFN7ZI57UBLCVOBFXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:52:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年上半年对冲基金吸引创纪录资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金提供商 HFR 的数据显示，今年上半年全球对冲基金的资金流入量达到了 2015 年以来最强劲的水平，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）新贸易政策的影响下，对冲基金在动荡的市场中越来越受欢迎。【原文：Global hedge funds had their strongest inflows in the first half of the year since 2015, gaining popularity in turbulent markets amid U.S. President Donald Trump's new trade policies, data from provider HFR showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hedge-funds-lure-record-inflows-first-half-2025-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2TEOONGKNPTNDQLICXMN26IDA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:25:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商 12 周来首次增加石油/天然气钻井平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周增加了石油和天然气钻机，这是 12 周以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week added oil and natural gas rigs for the first time in 12 weeks, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-add-oilgas-rigs-first-time-12-weeks-baker-hughes-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOZJJDJGRNN57IBCKZZYQ3XY6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:51:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称加拿大钢铁进口关税违反世贸组织规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国驻渥太华大使馆周五批评加拿大本周对中国进口钢铁征收关税，称这违反了世界贸易组织（WTO）规则，扰乱了全球贸易秩序。【原文：The Chinese embassy in Ottawa criticized duties slapped by Canada this week on Chinese imported steel, saying on Friday they violated World Trade Organization (WTO) rules and disrupted the global trade order.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/canadas-steel-import-duties-violate-wto-rules-says-china-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LOH3ZIVSRK5JNSXDHAYXY2A54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税迫使希腊橄榄油生产商寻求新市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[当美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在春季发出征收关税的威胁时，希腊橄榄油生产商康斯坦丁诺斯-帕帕佐普洛斯几乎没有浪费时间。他立即开始在全球寻找替代买家。【原文：Greek olive oil producer Konstantinos Papadopoulos wasted little time when the threat of U.S. tariffs was floated by President Donald Trump in the spring. He immediately started looking for alternative buyers around the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-tariffs-force-greek-olive-oil-producers-seek-new-markets-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMLL7ZMYEZOXNIRGWBXL73RYM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，美国 FDA 将要求 Sarepta 停止基因疗法 Elevidys 的发货]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉此事的消息人士周五告诉路透社，美国食品和药物管理局正计划要求 Sarepta Therapeutics 公司自愿停止其基因疗法 Elevidys 的所有发货。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration is planning to request Sarepta Therapeutics to voluntarily stop all shipments of its gene therapy, Elevidys, a source familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-ask-sarepta-stop-shipments-gene-therapy-elevidys-source-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUOVMR2DIBON3HKLF7DF5RK2UA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:11:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙进入圭亚那油田解决了公司面临的最大挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙即将进入圭亚那丰富的近海油田，这解决了困扰这家美国大型企业的最大问题之一：未来几年的增长将来自哪里。【原文：Chevron’s imminent entry into Guyana’s rich offshore oilfields solves one of the biggest problems dogging the U.S. major: where its growth will come from beyond the next few years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-entry-guyana-oilfields-solves-companys-top-challenge-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR244FUOW5IWRHV53NBIPTB75I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）修订全球预测，但警告贸易紧张局势仍给前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五警告说，与贸易紧张局势有关的风险继续给全球经济前景蒙上阴影，尽管贸易有所增长，金融状况有所改善，但不确定性仍然很高。【原文：The International Monetary Fund warned on Friday that risks related to trade tensions continue to cloud the global economic outlook and uncertainty remains high despite some increased trade and improved financial conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imf-eyes-revised-global-forecast-warns-trade-tensions-still-cloud-outlook-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDTJVYFAUBNQDFXEINMVAKRQKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，摩根大通着眼于新的研究领域，覆盖私营企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士周五告诉路透社记者，摩根大通已开始发布关于著名私营企业转型行业的研究报告。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has begun publishing research notes on prominent private companies transforming industries, a person familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-eyes-new-research-frontier-with-coverage-private-firms-source-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KE4PCCHKVRKRRPDK3BSA7NQDMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：特朗普解除制裁后，美国公司将制定叙利亚能源总体规划]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷液化天然气公司（Argent LNG）首席执行官乔纳森-巴斯（Jonathan Bass）周五表示，美国贝克休斯公司（Baker Hughes）、亨特能源公司（Hunt Energy）和阿根廷液化天然气公司（Argent LNG）将为叙利亚的石油、天然气和电力部门制定一项总体规划。【原文：U.S.-based firms Baker Hughes , Hunt Energy and Argent LNG will develop a masterplan for Syria's oil, gas and power sector, Argent LNG CEO Jonathan Bass said on Friday, in a partnership aimed at rebuilding energy infrastructure shattered by 14 years of civil war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-firms-develop-syria-energy-masterplan-after-trump-lifts-sanctions-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOGNDA2N3ZIA7CE4672KRM72NQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:44:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：特朗普推动对所有欧盟商品征收 15-20% 的最低关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）正在推动在与欧盟达成的任何协议中将最低关税设定为15%至20%，并补充说，即使达成协议，美国政府目前也在考虑将对等关税税率设定为超过10%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is pushing for a minimum tariff of 15% to 20% in any deal with the European Union, the Financial Times reported on Friday, adding that the administration is now looking at a reciprocal tariff rate that exceeds 10%, even if a deal is reached.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-pushes-15-20-minimum-tariff-all-eu-goods-ft-reports-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PY4AZA6GM5IWHFI3ZK4YQEYRFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3M 工厂收到肯塔基州监管机构发出的 PFAS 传票]]></title><description><![CDATA[3M 公司周五发布的季度报告显示，该公司的辛西安娜工厂在 5 月份收到了一份传票，要求提供有关该工厂使用或释放的全氟辛烷磺酸（PFAS）和所谓有害物质的信息。【原文：3M's Cynthiana facility received a subpoena in May seeking information about PFAS and alleged hazardous substances used or released at the site, the company's quarterly report on Friday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/3m-plant-receives-pfas-subpoena-kentucky-regulator-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTLHJDS6ZJKG5CGPSVRAOVCPQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:40:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡称网络间谍组织以关键基础设施为目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡周五表示，它正在应对一个被安全专家称为与中国有关的间谍组织对其关键基础设施的网络攻击。【原文：Singapore said on Friday that it was responding to cyberattacks on its critical infrastructure by an espionage group alleged by security experts to be linked to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/singapore-says-cyber-espionage-group-targeting-critical-infrastructure-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UL5WKZSWNIYFLKMUGKL54DMRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟监管机构接受手机制造商让步，康宁免于反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构周五接受了玻璃制造商康宁的提议，即放弃与手机制造商和玻璃加工公司的排他性协议，废除采购条款，以结束长达八个月的调查，避免可能的罚款。【原文：EU antitrust regulators on Friday accepted glass maker Corning's offer to waive exclusive deals with mobile phone makers and glass processing companies and scrap purchasing clauses to end an eight-month long investigation and stave off a possible fine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/corning-staves-off-antitrust-fine-eu-regulators-accept-concessions-mobile-phone-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUDCDNZKIVI33LVKNYAELLOJOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:58:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[G20 公报的要点和遗漏]]></title><description><![CDATA[二十国集团（G20）财政首脑周五达成公报，强调了中央银行独立性的重要性以及世界贸易组织在推进贸易问题方面的作用。【原文：G20 finance chiefs agreed a communique on Friday that underscored the importance of central bank independence and the role of the World Trade Organisation in advancing trade issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/main-points-omissions-g20-communique-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5NIL6XSWNJI5J7RH5JUIJOOXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国官员：中国汽车制造商应在电动汽车行业追求 "理性竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国工业部周五发表声明称，中国一位高级官员周四表示，主要汽车制造商应推动电动汽车行业的 "理性竞争"。【原文：Major automakers should push for "rational competition" in the electric vehicle industry, a senior Chinese official said on Thursday, according to a statement from the industry ministry published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-automakers-should-pursue-rational-competition-ev-industry-official-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAYEMBFRIRN4XH3KMNP3SKK3Q4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:43:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 股价下跌，原因是营收预期未给投资者留下深刻印象]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 股价在周五早盘交易中下跌超过 5%，原因是投资者对这家流媒体巨头因美元走软而非客户需求强劲而上调营收预期感到失望。【原文：Netflix shares declined more than 5% in early trading on Friday, as investors were disappointed by the streaming giant's revenue forecast raise being driven by a weaker dollar instead of strong customer demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/netflix-shares-drop-revenue-forecast-leaves-investors-unimpressed-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VRMZUOG5AVKDJK6QWCBATQXMW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国小组共和党高层反对恢复英伟达 H20 芯片出货]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会众议院中国问题特别委员会主席约翰-穆莱纳尔（John Moolenaar）周五在给美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）的信中反对恢复向中国销售 Nvidia H20 等效图形处理器。【原文：John Moolenaar, chairman of the House Select Committee on China, on Friday objected to the resumption of Nvidia H20 equivalent graphics processing unit sales to China in a letter to U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-republican-china-panel-objects-resumption-nvidia-h20-chip-shipments-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMOCPCVC6ZMKTIE4K4XHSZEDJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月消费者信心指数上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份，美国消费者情绪有所改善，虽然通胀预期继续下降，但家庭仍认为未来价格压力会有大幅上升的风险。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment improved in July, and while inflation expectations continued to decline, households still saw substantial risk of price pressures increasing in the future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-improves-july-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEWFX3TYGFKXXIDEMDZR2BVDFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷首席执行官布卢姆就另一项节约计划展开会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一封信称，保时捷首席执行官奥利弗-布卢姆（Oliver Blume）已开始就新一轮成本削减措施进行谈判，以帮助这家德国汽车制造商应对中国市场的挑战和美国的关税争端。【原文：Porsche CEO Oliver Blume has initiated negotiations on another round of cost-cutting measures to help the German carmaker cope with challenges in China and the U.S. tariff dispute, according to a letter seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-ceo-blume-initiates-talks-another-savings-programme-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QD26QXJDIFO53ENY5RAQ7TYYQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管关税导致价格飙升，美国钢铁企业第二季度业绩喜忧参半]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税的不确定性影响下，钢材价格的上涨和需求的不平衡将使美国顶级钢铁制造商的第二季度业绩喜忧参半。【原文：Top U.S. steelmakers' second-quarter fortunes are likely to be a mixed bag, caught between a fillip from higher steel prices and uneven demand amid uncertainty over U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-steelmakers-eye-mixed-second-quarter-despite-tariff-led-price-spikes-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBDO2IE7DRMYVNJPY62ZYB3ORA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 分析师：雪佛龙在赫斯交易仲裁中胜过埃克森]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司将继续以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司，在此之前，雪佛龙在一场具有里程碑意义的法律战中战胜了更大的竞争对手埃克森美孚，获得了圭亚那海岸数十年来最大的石油发现。【原文：Chevron will proceed with its $53 billion acquisition of Hess after it prevailed in a landmark legal battle against larger rival Exxon Mobil to gain access to the largest oil discovery in decades off the coast of Guyana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/view-analysts-chevron-winning-arbitration-over-exxon-hess-deal-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7IGJ4AJKQ5I5ZDQTFUFO2WPM4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，美国医疗保险公司寻求实现自 2018 年以来奥巴马医改保费的最大跃升]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据健康研究公司 KFF 的分析，受保费税收抵免即将到期和医疗商品可能被征收关税的影响，美国保险公司要求对奥巴马医保计划的保费进行自 2018 年以来最大的一次上调。【原文：U.S. insurers are requesting the biggest premium increases for Obamacare plans since 2018, according to an analysis by health-research firm KFF, prompted by the looming expiry of premium tax credits and potential tariffs on medical goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-health-insurers-seek-largest-jump-obamacare-premiums-since-2018-study-shows-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGHEK2YBANLALKYCI7WVJFMOJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:16:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>