<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:33:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:33:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[任天堂 Switch 的中文在线服务将于 2026 年 3 月 31 日停止运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[腾讯任天堂 Switch 周二表示，其中国在线服务将从 2026 年 3 月 31 日起逐步停止任天堂 eShop 的运营。【原文：Tencent Nintendo Switch said on Tuesday that its Chinese online service would gradually cease operations for the Nintendo eShop starting from March 31, 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-online-service-nintendo-switch-cease-operations-march-31-2026-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5MOIZC5GBJSJBJTIF6FXZPF5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价特朗普关税威胁震荡加元、比索和人民币]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3FTAIQPKFN2BGNURWMMD3YJ34</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:14:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储会议纪要或显示关于降息幅度的争论已经开始]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储官员表示，他们目前可能会继续降低利率，投资者仍预计他们将在美国央行12月17-18日的会议上这样做。【原文：Federal Reserve officials say they are likely to keep reducing interest rates for now, and investors still expect them to do so at the U.S. central bank's Dec. 17-18 meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-minutes-may-show-start-debate-over-how-far-go-rate-cuts-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALJWCDWLXBKFRNPG4XUZMS6ZO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:09:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国新的消费者保护措施开始实施，假日旅行者须知]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你觉得去年的假期旅行太疯狂，那就系好安全带吧。【原文：If you thought last year’s holiday travel was insane, well, buckle your seatbelt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/tips-holiday-travelers-new-us-consumer-protections-kick-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKN53SVOBJJRFFDRFP6IRDOIRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者权衡特朗普的关税威胁，期货走势低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货持平，投资者在连续几个交易日的上涨后暂停交易，并权衡唐纳德-特朗普对主要贸易伙伴征收关税可能对当地经济产生的影响。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were flat on Tuesday, as investors paused following several sessions of gains and weighed the implications Donald Trump's tariffs on top trade partners could have on the local economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-muted-investors-weigh-trumps-tariff-threats-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CB2IQ3WJK5KGLDJIX772JGCKQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:57:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司因挑战加剧而调整多元化政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[在来自保守派团体的压力不断增加的背景下，沃尔玛成为最新一家削减一些旨在提高工作场所种族和民族代表性的多元化、公平和包容（DEI）计划的美国公司。【原文：Walmart became the latest U.S. company to cut back some diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) programs meant to boost racial and ethnic representation at workplaces against the backdrop of rising pressure from conservative groups.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-companies-tweak-diversity-policies-challenges-mount-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GF5D5CH2BFMVZGVVBSNIJNPNTE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:52:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息称日本首相石破敦促拜登批准日美钢铁交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟知内情的消息人士透露，日本首相石破茂已致信美国总统拜登，请求他批准新日铁收购美国钢铁公司的交易，以免破坏两国最近为加强关系所做的努力。【原文：Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba has sent a letter to President Joe Biden asking him to approve Nippon Steel's acquisition of U.S. Steel, to avoid marring recent efforts to strengthen ties between the countries, according to two sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japan-pm-ishiba-urges-biden-approve-nippon-us-steel-deal-sources-say-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTBM4CWVLVJ35GT2M7GUEVA4C4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:49:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称拜登将提议扩大肥胖症药物的医疗保险和医疗补助覆盖范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员周二表示，美国总统乔-拜登将提议扩大数百万医疗保险和医疗补助计划（Medicare and Medicaid）患者的抗肥胖药物覆盖范围，这将使部分患者的自付费用减少多达 95%。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden will propose expanding coverage of anti-obesity drugs for millions on Medicare and Medicaid, which could cut out-of-pocket expenses for some by as much as 95%, a White House official said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/biden-propose-expanded-medicare-medicaid-coverage-obesity-drugs-official-says-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTJTN7EAIVM4JCYET25WLXOYUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:33:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司高管表示，美国石油生产商不太可能转向 "钻井、宝贝、钻井 "模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil）的一位高管周二表示，在当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的领导下，美国石油和天然气生产商不太可能大幅提高产量，因为各公司仍将专注于资本约束。【原文：U.S. oil and gas producers are unlikely to radically increase production under president-elect Donald Trump as companies remain focused on capital discipline, a senior executive at Exxon Mobil said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-oil-producers-unlikely-shift-drill-baby-drill-mode-says-exxon-executive-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUNEGLOOWVMXXOP322KVVRIJR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:29:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[东京电视台称 Fortress 看中了 Seven & i 的超市业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[东京电视台周二在其网站上称，丰泰投资集团正在考虑从 Seven &amp; i 控股公司手中收购伊藤洋华堂连锁超市的中间控股公司。【原文：Fortress Investment Group is considering buying an intermediate holding company that has the Ito-Yokado supermarket chain under its wing from Seven &amp; i Holdings , TV Tokyo said on its website on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fortress-eyes-seven-is-supermarket-operations-tv-tokyo-says-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSH2BQDE4ZN6PFIXGNKSUMHYQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:25:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：私募股权争夺富士软的背后是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[KKR 在与另一家私募股权投资巨头贝恩资本（Bain Capital）争夺日本小有名气的 IT 公司富士软（Fuji Soft）的过程中占据了上风。【原文：KKR has gained the upper hand in its clash with another private equity giant, Bain Capital, to take little-known Japanese IT firm Fuji Soft private.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/whats-behind-private-equity-battle-fuji-soft-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QADE2ZWBVBKC7JWNQRIDSGOZQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:23:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院小组批评航空公司座位费上涨，将传唤高管作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院一个小组周二批评了航空公司不断上涨的座位分配和行李费，并将于 12 月 4 日传唤航空公司高管作证。【原文：A U.S. Senate panel on Tuesday criticized rising airline fees for seat assignments and luggage and will call air carrier executives to testify on Dec. 4.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-senate-panel-criticizes-rising-airline-seat-fees-will-call-execs-testify-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SRKOAJL6JOE5JVIVAYWJ76FKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敲定授予英特尔 78.6 亿美元芯片制造权]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周二表示，将最终确定向英特尔提供 78.6 亿美元的政府补贴，低于 3 月份宣布的 85 亿美元，此前这家总部位于加利福尼亚州的芯片制造商赢得了五角大楼另外提供的 30 亿美元补贴。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Tuesday it was finalizing a $7.86 billion government subsidy for Intel , down from $8.5 billion  announced in March after the California-based chips maker won a separate $3 billion award from the Pentagon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-finalizes-786-billion-chips-manufacturing-award-intel-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBFYOFB35VJPXJ32VXTW4IQAJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦格理银行因严重控制失误被英国监管机构罚款 1600 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融监管机构周二对澳大利亚麦格理银行伦敦分行处以 1300 万英镑（1633 万美元）的罚款，原因是该行一名员工在 2020 年至 2022 年期间记录虚假交易并隐瞒交易损失。【原文：Britain's financial watchdog on Tuesday fined the London branch of Australian lender Macquarie Bank 13 million pounds ($16.33 million) for failings that enabled an employee to record fictitious trades and conceal his trading losses between 2020 and 2022.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/uk-watchdog-fines-macquarie-bank-16-mln-serious-control-failures-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TV3XCIVNE5IKJDMBTX7TFRBCPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科尔首席执行官意外离职将加剧假日购物季前的困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[科尔百货公司（Kohl's）在公布季度业绩的前一天突然宣布首席执行官离职，这对投资者来说是个不小的打击，因为他们希望这家陷入困境的连锁百货公司能在关键的假日购物季到来之前做出积极的预测。【原文：Kohl's surprise CEO departure announcement a day before its quarterly results will play on the minds of investors, who were looking out for a positive forecast from the struggling department store chain ahead of the key holiday shopping season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kohls-surprise-ceo-departure-amplify-woes-ahead-holiday-shopping-season-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUAHGQQ4W5P5LGKGQF3U6TPULM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业热潮让瑞士移民问题成为欧盟贸易谈判的难题]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士正竭力控制来自其最大贸易伙伴欧盟的移民，因为该国的低税商业模式带动了就业热潮，使人口增长成为政治上的烫手山芋。【原文：Switzerland is scrambling to keep a lid on immigration from its top trade partner, the European Union, as a jobs boom powered by the country's low-tax business model turns population growth into a political hot potato.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/job-boom-creates-swiss-immigration-headache-eu-trade-talks-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3KX246ABRJBDE6ONM53CEYLYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:31:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BPM 银行董事会召开会议，开始讨论联合信贷银行的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[BPM 银行周二召开董事会，就竞争对手意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）主动向这家意大利第三大银行提出的 100 亿欧元（105 亿美元）收购要约进行初步讨论。【原文：Banco BPM gathers its board on Tuesday for an initial discussion on the 10 billion euro ($10.5 billion) unsolicited takeover offer that rival UniCredit has launched for Italy's third-largest bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/banco-bpms-board-meets-start-discussing-unicredits-takeover-bid-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53H72PIUP5NTFM4U6ARE6LPQ4U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:15:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据安莎社报道，BPM 银行董事会成员称联合信贷银行的出价充满敌意]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）的一位董事会成员周二告诉意大利安莎通讯社（ANSA），联合信贷银行对意大利 Banco BPM 的出人意料的收购是充满敌意的。【原文：UniCredit's surprise bid for Italy's Banco BPM is hostile, a board member of the smaller lender told Italian newswire ANSA on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/banco-bpm-board-member-says-unicredit-bid-is-hostile-ansa-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQVZZSXB7FNCLMTKVFVWD4PDOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普承诺征收关税，欧洲汽车制造商业绩下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，欧洲汽车制造商股价下跌，交易商对美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收巨额关税做出了反应，这一消息加剧了市场对潜在全球贸易战的担忧。【原文：European automakers shares fell in early trading on Tuesday, as traders reacted to President-elect Donald Trump pledging big tariffs on Canada, Mexico and China, news that fueled jitters over a potential global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eurpoean-automakers-fall-trump-pledges-tariffs-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQOXBZFGRVIDZD3L6Y7OQP6IEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:20:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者表示知道如何交易特朗普 2.0]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普在社交媒体上承诺对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收新的关税后，投资者们周二重新拾起了他们的贸易战战术手册，相信他们的投资组合这次能更好地应对唐纳德-特朗普。【原文：Investors dusted off their trade war playbooks on Tuesday, confident their portfolios were better-prepared for Donald Trump this time after the U.S. President-elect took to social media and pledged new tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-say-they-know-how-trade-trump-20-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVQNA5SXL5L4LGRWLAUINSKDPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团被美国起诉贿赂后的重大后果]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国起诉阿达尼集团亿万富豪董事长高塔姆-阿达尼涉嫌行贿和欺诈，为集团旗下公司阿达尼绿色能源公司赢得合同之后，一些国家和投资者要么取消了与阿达尼集团的交易，要么停止了对阿达尼集团的投资。【原文：Some nations and investors have either scrapped deals or halted investments in the Adani Group, after the United States indicted its billionaire chairman Gautam Adani for alleged bribery and fraud to win contracts for a group company, Adani Green Energy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/major-fallout-indias-adani-group-after-us-bribery-indictment-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYHO3K5PHZNUPPAB4VMPC6ECIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为推出 Mate 70 智能手机，美国新芯片禁令迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国科技巨头华为技术公司（HWT.UL）周二发布了 Mate 70 系列智能手机，推进了其在高端智能手机领域的东山再起，同时展示了自己的操作系统，彻底摆脱了美国技术的束缚。【原文：Chinese tech giant Huawei Technologies (HWT.UL) unveiled its Mate 70 smartphone series on Tuesday, advancing its comeback in the premium smartphone space while showcasing its own operating system in a clean break away from U.S. technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/huawei-launches-mate-70-smartphone-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52Z3CLQNCVOJDKYOTIECPZX3IQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼就女性薪酬诉讼案达成 4300 万美元和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[原告律师周一在一份声明中表示，华特迪士尼已同意支付 4,330 万美元，以了结一项指控其加利福尼亚州女员工在八年时间里比男员工少挣 1.5 亿美元的诉讼。【原文：Walt Disney has agreed to pay $43.3 million to settle a lawsuit alleging that its female employees in California earned $150 million less than their male counterparts over an eight-year period, the plaintiffs' lawyers said in a statement on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/disney-settles-suit-over-womens-pay-43-million-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNEAT3RGUZORBNHAOAG6HFAR2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:34:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在保守派的压力下，沃尔玛将撤销部分多元化政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛的一位发言人周一表示，沃尔玛计划削减部分多元化、公平和包容性（DEI）举措，加入了越来越多感受到保守团体压力的企业行列。【原文：Walmart plans to cut back some of its diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) initiatives, a spokesperson for the retailer said on Monday, joining a growing list of firms feeling the heat from conservative groups.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-roll-back-some-diversity-policies-amid-pressure-conservatives-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27MXCTYXDBKSNCS6OG4VD4QDLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗氏将收购美国 Poseida Therapeutics 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士罗氏公司周二表示，将以每股 9 美元的价格收购总部位于加利福尼亚州的生物制药公司 Poseida Therapeutics，收购完成后的股权总价值将达到 10 亿美元。【原文：Roche will acquire California-based biopharmafirm Poseida Therapeutics for $9 per share at closing, for a total equity value of $1 billion, the Swiss company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/roche-acquire-us-based-poseida-therapeutics-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZRJ47CU7FL67LT5EUNQOHCHXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:29:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌提议重新调整欧洲搜索结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一些较小的竞争对手抱怨 Alphabet 旗下公司之前的调整导致其网站流量下降，以及欧盟反垄断监管机构考虑根据新的欧盟技术规则对该公司提出指控之后，谷歌提出对其在欧洲的搜索结果进行更多调整。【原文：Google has proposed more changes to its search results in Europe after some smaller rivals complained about lower traffic to their sites resulting from previous tweaks by the Alphabet unit and as EU antitrust regulators consider levying charges against the company under new EU tech rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-proposes-fresh-tweaks-search-results-europe-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XWVJ4UOPVPOJK6Q7TR5JBZBZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，日产寻求投资者以取代雷诺持有的部分股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周二报道，日产汽车公司正在寻找长期投资者，如银行或保险集团，以帮助其取代雷诺被稀释的部分股权。【原文：Nissan Motor is looking for a long-term investor, such as a bank or insurance group, to help it replace some of Renault's diluted stakeholding, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-seeks-investor-replace-some-renaults-equity-holding-ft-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPOAJHIHQNPTDMZVMEGIAVWAMA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，花旗集团在寻求全面改革银行时削减了晋升职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周二报道，花旗集团正在减少年终晋升的人数，因为该公司正在进行长期重组，以缩减员工人数，从而降低成本。【原文：Citigroup is cutting the number of year-end promotions it awards as it seeks to hold costs down amid a long-term restructuring to shrink headcount, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-slashes-promotions-it-seeks-overhaul-bank-ft-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RGANKMYPFLFBBGSWR2AQ5VTKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价特朗普加征关税引发市场恐慌]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIHESWFEDRIXLAMZLIUKXRLTWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:32:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿达尼绿色能源公司称未与道达尔能源公司讨论新的财务承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿达尼绿色能源公司（Adani Green Energy）周二表示，目前尚未与道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）商讨新的财务承诺，而在此前一天，这家法国石油巨头还表示将暂停对阿达尼集团的新投资。【原文：Adani Green Energy said on Tuesday there is no new financial commitment under discussion with TotalEnergies , a day after the French oil major said it was pausing new investments into the Adani Group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/adani-green-energy-says-no-new-financial-commitment-under-discussion-with-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2GVC6LZCNIHDPXX6OT7W4UA24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 04:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>