<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:20:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:20:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[科瑞维股价暴跌，资本支出翻倍引发利润率担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[CoreWeave股价周五盘前暴跌约12%，此前该公司宣布计划将今年资本支出翻倍，引发投资者对其利润率压力及人工智能战略实际回报的担忧。【原文：Shares of CoreWeave slumped around 12% before the bell on Friday, after the company's plans to double capital expenditure this year fueled investor concerns about margin pressure and effective returns from its artificial intelligence push.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coreweave-shares-slump-doubling-capital-expenditure-sparks-margin-concerns-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CI4ECLVDLVKPNN3S4DQXRBUAMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:16:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[露露柠檬创始人威尔逊加码代理权争夺战，敦促提名更多董事]]></title><description><![CDATA[露露乐蒙创始人奇普·威尔逊周五在致股东的信中表示，他提议更换这家运动休闲品牌的三名以上董事，此举加剧了他此前发起的代理权争夺战。【原文：Lululemon Athletica founder Chip Wilson has proposed to replace more than three directors at the athleisure maker, he said in a letter to shareholders on Friday, ramping up his earlier proxy fight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/lululemon-founder-wilson-ramps-up-proxy-fight-urges-nomination-more-directors-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RK4VBHOTGNPGXDYZR3JHW34YDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿尔巴尼亚如何未能成功封禁TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体平台TikTok在本月一年禁令到期后重返阿尔巴尼亚。这一事件凸显了在政治分裂地区实施禁令的复杂性，并引发了对网络安全和审查制度的质疑。【原文：Social media platform TikTok is back in Albania after a year-long ban expired this month, in a case illustrating the complexity of imposing bans in a politically fragmented region and sparking questions over online safety and censorship.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/tiktok-returns-albania-after-government-imposed-ban-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYO6Y3XUDVPYLBRL77S44LTXB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[目标在五月底前从谷物食品中去除人工色素]]></title><description><![CDATA[塔吉特公司周五宣布，将在五月底前仅销售不含经认证合成色素的谷物产品，成为最新一家在人工色素整治浪潮中收紧标准的零售商。【原文：Target said on Friday it would sell only cereals made without certified synthetic colors by the end of May, becoming the latest retailer to tighten standards amid a crackdown on artificial dyes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/target-remove-synthetic-color-cereals-by-may-end-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEDQHMOMKBKEXLORSUV6PRMZWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:51:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴尔股价飙升，因其预测人工智能服务器收入将翻倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[戴尔科技股价周五盘前交易中大幅上涨，此前该公司预测其人工智能服务器业务在2027财年的营收将翻倍，凸显出人工智能基础设施需求的激增。【原文：Shares of Dell Technologies jumped in premarket trading on Friday after the company forecast revenue from its AI server business will double in fiscal 2027, underscoring surging demand for infrastructure catering to artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dell-shares-jump-forecast-it-will-double-ai-server-revenue-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GAFEQ2GADVN63KZHBXSTAO3LKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:47:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，大众汽车旗下柴油发动机部门Everllence的初步竞标价约为94亿美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位知情人士透露，大众汽车（Volkswagen VOWG_p.DE）旗下柴油发动机部门Everllence已收到估值约80亿欧元（合94.4亿美元）的收购要约，该报价包含债务，高于部分分析师的预期。【原文：Volkswagen VOWG_p.DE has received bids valuing its diesel engine division Everllence at around 8 billion euros ($9.44 billion) including debt, according to three people familiar with the discussions, above what some analysts had estimated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-receives-preliminary-bids-diesel-engine-unit-everllence-around-94-billion-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APBC76NU4ZOYRPDDK7CNE2L2H4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:36:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金资金流入降至五周低点，人工智能担忧加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至2月25日的七天内，全球股票基金资金流入量降至五周低点，因投资者对人工智能带来的高昂成本及潜在干扰日益担忧，转而采取谨慎态度。【原文：Global equity fund inflows eased to a five-week low in the seven days to February 25 as investors turned cautious amid growing unease over the heavy costs and potential disruption linked to artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBUSYMY3E5NQFN63UPJDY4Y4IQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tether称因涉犯罪活动冻结42亿美元稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于萨尔瓦多的稳定币发行商泰达币（Tether）表示，已冻结约42亿美元的加密货币代币，因其与"非法活动"有关联，这些活动主要发生在过去三年间。全球各地当局正努力打击加密货币相关的犯罪行为。【原文：El Salvador-based stablecoin issuer Tether said it has frozen about $4.2 billion of its crypto tokens over links to "illicit activity", mostly in the past three years, as authorities around the world try to crack down on crypto-related crime.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tether-says-it-has-frozen-42-billion-its-stablecoin-over-crime-links-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJI3MD7KONP6LGDD26DAPH5HMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞标：人工智能恐怖故事]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克·多兰和ROI团队本周末最期待阅读、观看和收听的内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPPEYVLDR5KVVFEQDXWOT2J4LA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货因人工智能担忧而走低，纳斯达克指数准备迎接大幅月度下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五下跌，因人工智能领域日益加剧的担忧拖累科技股，纳斯达克指数面临2025年3月以来最大月度跌幅，投资者正等待当日晚些时候公布的关键通胀数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slid on Friday as growing AI unease weighed on technology stocks, with the Nasdaq staring at its steepest monthly drop since March 2025, and investors awaited key inflation data later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-falter-ai-jitters-nasdaq-braces-steep-monthly-fall-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74PQCZJXFVJADDDNNPZH4FT63U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:43:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Healthpeak Properties旗下Janus Living公开提交美国IPO申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产投资信托公司Janus Living周五正式提交美国IPO申请文件，众多企业发行方正争相抢占三月上市窗口期。【原文：Real estate investment trust Janus Living publicly filed paperwork for a U.S. IPO on Friday, as corporate issuers line up to tap the March window.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthpeak-properties-janus-living-makes-us-ipo-filing-public-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQ734WN2B5MG7OH2GZBZSZ73O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师上调油价预期，因地缘政治风险；供应过剩担忧限制上涨空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[持续的地缘政治紧张局势引发的供应风险，促使分析师上调了今年的油价预测，尽管市场担忧供应过剩将持续对油价构成压力。【原文：Supply risks from ongoing geopolitical tensions have prompted analysts to raise their oil price forecasts for the year, despite concerns that an oversupply will continue to weigh on the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/analysts-hike-oil-outlook-geopolitical-risks-oversupply-concerns-limit-upside-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRXJLGH76RO4VG5EAW7NIN24SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通获利了结人民币升值行情]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通分析师表示，随着中国央行周五下调美元远期合约购买成本以抑制人民币近期升值势头，他们将平仓离岸人民币多头头寸。【原文：JPMorgan's analysts said they were closing their long offshore Chinese yuan position after the country's central bank cut the cost of buying dollar forwards on Friday in a bid to tame the yuan's recent rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-takes-profit-chinese-yuan-rally-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLC6ZVVMABJRBPD6IML723K3GI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据Axios报道，目标公司计划从谷物食品中去除人工色素]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Axios周五报道，塔吉特百货要求其销售的所有谷物产品必须在五月底前停止使用经认证的合成色素。【原文：Target will require every cereal it sells to be made without certified synthetic colors by the end of May, Axios reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/target-drop-synthetic-colors-cereals-axios-reports-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4DEA44LIBJPFM24ORUSG42FHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望：人工智能颠覆阴云笼罩市场，美国就业数据即将公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能颠覆各行业的前景，将在未来一周持续令美国股市保持紧张状态，华尔街正寻求更多洞见，以了解这项新兴技术将如何在经济领域引发连锁反应。【原文：Prospects for artificial intelligence to disrupt business sectors should keep the U.S. stock market on edge in the coming week, as Wall Street looks for more insight into how the emerging technology will reverberate through the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-ai-disruption-looms-over-markets-with-us-jobs-data-tap-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGK22SK7EZJXPCJQPL7S7D6IOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼人类学纷争：周五最后期限临近，销售额与人工智能战争悬而未决]]></title><description><![CDATA[五角大楼与顶尖人工智能实验室Anthropic之间的激烈争端即将达到顶点，争议焦点在于军方如何在战争中运用人工智能。【原文：An explosive feud between the Pentagon and top artificial intelligence lab Anthropic is set to come to a head over concerns about how the military could use AI at war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/pentagon-anthropic-feud-has-sales-ai-warfare-stake-friday-deadline-looms-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKFAA7NCXNKGZNKTAWZL5IPXK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着消费者寻求享受美食，餐饮业成为美国就业增长的亮点]]></title><description><![CDATA[纸面上看，美国消费者去年都在勒紧裤腰带，就连零售业巨头也步履维艰。但堂食餐厅和部分得来速连锁店却门庭若市，顾客们或为享受特别款待，或为品尝平价慰藉美食而纷至沓来。【原文：On paper, American consumers spent last year tightening their belts, and even retail heavyweights stumbled. But sit-down restaurants and some drive-through chains buzzed with patrons seeking a special treat or cheap comfort food.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/restaurants-emerge-bright-spot-us-job-growth-consumers-seek-treats-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIZX2AQCTBPAXN4VOCZ7COPJ7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[跳舞机器人为巴塞罗那老年人提供陪伴与支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴塞罗那居民艾琳·维格利森已有二十多年未曾跳舞，直到三个月前，一台机器人搬进了她的家。【原文：Barcelona resident Irene Veglison had not danced for more than two decades until a robot moved into her home three months ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/dancing-robots-bring-support-company-barcelona-elderly-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPSGUK6AQVOVZBKVOOES6UXLAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:49:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴斯夫正就其美国子公司提出的关税退还法律索赔展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴斯夫首席执行官表示，若该化工集团发现其美国子公司具备法律诉求，将在美国最高法院推翻特朗普总统多项关税措施后，就进口关税补偿问题提起诉讼。【原文：BASF's CEO said if the chemical group finds its U.S. subsidiary has a legal claim, it will sue for import tariff reimbursement after the U.S. Supreme Court quashed many of President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/basf-is-looking-into-legal-claims-by-us-unit-tariff-reimbursement-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSEKY6A7XJON5DODGTC5OZ375A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:42:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟收购战尘埃落定，奈飞、派拉蒙股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五盘前交易时段，奈飞股价飙升逾9%，投资者对其退出华纳兄弟探索公司收购战的决定表示欢迎；与此同时，派拉蒙股价上涨约10%，因其在争夺全球最珍贵影视资产的竞争中胜出。【原文：Netflix jumped more than 9% premarket on Friday as investors cheered its decision to exit the fight for Warner Bros Discovery, while Paramount rose about 10% on winning the race for some of the world's most prized TV and film assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/netflix-paramount-shares-jump-months-long-fight-warner-bros-ends-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQTPY7ACHVLR3OTU2WBTD23VT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚赌场运营商星娱乐集团上半年亏损收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚星娱乐集团周五公布，2026财年上半年亏损幅度有所收窄，得益于第二季度交易量在季节性因素推动下实现增长。【原文：Australia's Star Entertainment Group reported a smaller loss for the first half on Friday, supported by seasonally stronger trading volumes for the second quarter of fiscal 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-star-entertainment-narrows-first-half-loss-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJLERMLJQNKMZHCFRWMRX2PPRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解读：中国能采取哪些措施来抑制人民币升值？]]></title><description><![CDATA[人民币兑美元汇率正大幅升值，这得益于出口的强劲增长，同时美国利率下降和美元走软也助推了这一趋势。【原文：China's yuan is surging against the U.S. dollar, boosted by booming exports and aided by falling U.S. interest rates and the wobbly greenback.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/what-can-china-do-slow-down-its-rising-currency-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EF7WGNHH45N7LERNOOCYEFYZ6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瓦锡兰首席执行官寄望特朗普数据中心计划提振业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[芬兰能源公司瓦锡兰首席执行官向路透社表示，美国数据中心推动自建供电设施的举措将提振对该公司环保产品的需求，并助力未来两年服务人员招聘实现"两位数"百分比增长。【原文：A push for U.S. datacentres to use their own power will boost demand for Wartsila's more environmentally friendly products and help underpin a "double-digit" percentage increase in hiring of servicing staff over the next two years, the Finnish energy company's CEO told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/wartsila-ceo-eyes-boost-trump-datacenter-push-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NH56KCCPGRIF7D35JLKTM5BM4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Insta360制造商称将在美国国际贸易委员会裁决后"不受限制"地进口和销售产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于深圳的Arashi Vision公司（旗下拥有Insta360系列相机产品）周五表示，在美国际贸易委员会作出最终裁决后，该公司"将继续不受限制地向美国进口和销售现有产品"。【原文：Shenzhen-based Arashi Vision , which makes the Insta360 line of camera products, on Friday said it "will continue to import and sell existing products in the U.S. without restrictions" after a final ruling by USITC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/insta360-maker-says-it-will-import-sell-products-us-without-restrictions-after-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCOQYATJYBJUJLUWPRWOUBKHQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:41:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[European shares set for eighth straight month of gains, buoyed by earnings]]></title><description><![CDATA[European shares were steady on Friday and were set to log an eighth straight month of gains as better-than-expected corporate updates supported risk appetite despite lingering tariff and AI-disruption concerns.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-shares-set-eighth-straight-month-gains-buoyed-by-earnings-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTM5A7H63VMQ3K7G25PQXHWTHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CPP, Equinix to buy Nordic data center operator atNorth in $4 billion deal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canada Pension Plan Investment Board and Equinix have agreed to acquire Nordic data center operator atNorth from private equity firm Partners Group in a deal valued at about $4 billion, the companies said in a joint statement on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/cpp-equinix-buy-nordic-data-center-operator-atnorth-4-billion-deal-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7QMIWDE65ISXFIFJ4WM2AEMBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[起亚美国因座椅靠背框架问题召回约8.5万辆美国车辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kia America is recalling 85,448 vehicles in the U.S. over failure of a seat back frame failing to properly restrain an occupant during a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kia-america-recall-about-85000-us-vehicles-over-seat-back-frame-issue-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA4TUCHW55KKHKSMICRNKRSAXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度贸易部长表示，印度致力于与美国达成最优贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度贸易部长周五表示，印度希望与美国达成最有利的贸易协议，以确保在竞争中占据优势。此前，由于特朗普总统的关税政策被裁定无效，华盛顿敲定的协议命运仍不明朗。【原文：India wants to secure the best trade deal with the U.S. to ensure it has an edge over competitors, India's trade minister said on Friday, as the fate of deals finalised by Washington remain uncertain after President Donald Trump's tariffs were invalidated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-focused-getting-best-trade-deal-with-us-indian-trade-minister-says-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYC2ZUQYWVIBXMUVK2E2LRKYXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:19:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Poland plans social-media ban for children under 15, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰计划出台新法规，禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体，并将要求平台承担年龄核查责任。教育部长芭芭拉·诺瓦茨卡周五接受彭博新闻社采访时透露了这一消息。【原文：Poland plans to introduce new legislation to ban social media for children under 15 years of age and will hold platforms responsible for age verification, Education Minister Barbara Nowacka told Bloomberg News in an interview published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/poland-plans-social-media-ban-children-under-15-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3X7WNILBXNL3XFUPL642QGFMT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间要闻：人工智能困境与"公开战争"]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗基·斯威夫特带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGJ3VD2YNVJ3DG43DEOKDYMOVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:39:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>