<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:26:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:26:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院委员会推进农业法案草案，民主党人支持率不高]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党领导的美国众议院农业委员会于周四深夜通过了其版本的 1.5 万亿美元农业支出法案，但民主党的投票却寥寥无几，延长了两党在关键的营养、农业和气候政策上的僵持。【原文：The Republican-led U.S. House of Representatives Agriculture Committee passed its version of a $1.5 trillion farm spending bill late Thursday night with few Democratic votes, prolonging a standoff between the parties over key nutrition, agriculture, and climate policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-committee-advances-farm-bill-draft-with-little-support-democrats-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZB7UVA4MRBP6BANQDJFPNBAM5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:25:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国财政部长表示，实施全球最低税率协议是德国的首要任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国财政部长克里斯蒂安-林德纳（Christian Lindner）周五表示，实施全球最低税率协议的第二支柱是德国的优先事项，在就第一支柱达成协议之前，不应讨论进一步的想法。【原文：The implementation of the second pillar of the global minimum tax deal is Germany's priority and further ideas should not be discussed until there is an agreement on the first pillar, German Finance Minister Christian Lindner said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/implementation-global-minimum-tax-deal-is-germanys-priority-finmin-says-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSLH7RWNPBID7OGXGX4B7EYK6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:11:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Lucid 将裁员 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Lucid 集团周五表示，将裁员 6%，约 400 人。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Lucid Group said on Friday it would reduce workforce by 6%, or around 400 employees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-lucid-cut-workforce-by-6-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PXWE5PMDBLGBDPR3RLO4SVZVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀忧虑打压华尔街后期货回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货上涨，在上一交易日收盘下跌后反弹，原因是有迹象表明通胀持续存在，在长周末到来之前重燃了对货币政策的谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday, rebounding after closing lower in the previous session on signs of persistent inflation that rekindled monetary policy caution ahead of a long weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-recover-after-inflation-jitters-dent-wall-street-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKO5CLOEBVMXNAPE6BVWL3Q52I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国加快股票交割的预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国市场将在 5 月 28 日（周二）迎来一场动荡，在美国证券交易委员会（SEC）于 2023 年 2 月通过一项新规则后，美国股票、公司市政债券和其他证券的结算时间将减半至一天，即 T+1。【原文：U.S. markets are set for an upheaval on Tuesday, May 28, when the settlement time for U.S. equities, corporate municipal bonds and other securities will be halved to one day, or T+1, following the adoption of a new Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) rule in February 2023.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/what-expect-us-moves-towards-faster-stock-settlement-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFMIYOYVCFLUTFI5J7W3BPROXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储梅斯特：央行行长应承认在不那么确定的世界中存在盲点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在为美联储工作和帮助领导美联储的近 40 年中，克利夫兰联储主席洛雷塔-梅斯特（Loretta Mester）是美国中央银行就经济和货币政策提供更详细、更丰富评论的革命的一部分。【原文：In nearly 40 years working for and helping lead the Federal Reserve, Cleveland Fed President Loretta Mester was part of a revolution that saw the U.S. central bank offer ever more detailed and plentiful commentary on the economy and monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/central-bankers-should-acknowledge-blind-spots-less-certain-world-feds-mester-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPP7AMICV5IZBPF5JEW4YF5TIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:06:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国降息预期影响，全球股票基金每周资金流入强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[受通胀放缓的乐观情绪和美国联邦储备委员会下半年降息预期的推动，全球股票基金在截至5月22日的一周内获得了强劲的资金流入。【原文：Global equity funds secured robust inflows in the week ended May 22, driven by optimism over slowing inflation and expectations of U.S. Federal Reserve rate cuts in the latter half of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3R22FEHZZJIZGUMFO3KNOEFUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债务负担不断加重，部分债券投资者在 11 月大选前感到恐慌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在今年的总统大选之前，投资者认为巨额财政赤字看不到尽头，因此他们正准备迎接美国政府债务的大量发行，随着时间的推移，这可能会使预期的债券反弹相形见绌。【原文：Investors are bracing for a flood of U.S. government debt issuance that over time could dwarf an expected rally in bonds, as they see no end in sight for large fiscal deficits ahead of this year's presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/rising-us-debt-burden-spooks-some-bond-investors-ahead-november-election-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDBTRPKG4JMX7FTQAFT5IUPFJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美联储担忧压倒人工智能主题，黄金反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-graphic-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCUVF6GFJROZXFLI2PZHLA47TU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[流亡中国商人 10 亿美元诈骗案周五在美国开审]]></title><description><![CDATA[流亡海外的中国商人郭万里（Miles Guo）的欺诈案预计将于周五在曼哈顿开庭，检察官将发表开庭陈述，称郭万里通过一个欺诈性的商业帝国骗取了投资者和客户超过 10 亿美元。【原文：Exiled Chinese businessman Miles Guo's fraud trial is expected to kick off on Friday in Manhattan with an opening statement from prosecutors, who say he conned investors and customers out of more than $1 billion through a fraudulent business empire.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/exiled-chinese-businessmans-1-bln-fraud-trial-begin-us-friday-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FV2XXZWPYNJB3FRWFSJK55PQ2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本电产更正了过去的业绩，因为部分销售额被 "夸大 "了]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本电机制造商日本电产株式会社周五将两年的营业利润下调了约 6700 万美元，原因是该公司一家子公司的部分销售额被 "虚报"。【原文：Japanese electric motor manufacturer Nidec Corp revised down two years of operating profit by about $67 million on Friday after determining that some sales were "recorded in an inflated manner" at a subsidiary.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japans-nidec-corrects-past-results-after-some-sales-were-inflated-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJX3YGWQXJNOZM6UJIVRPZ4364</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:54:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在高呼和 K-pop 歌声中，三星工会举行罕见集会，要求公平工资]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在 K-pop 表演和舞曲的背景下，2000 多名三星电子的工会工人聚集在首尔，举行了一场罕见的集会，要求这家韩国科技巨头支付公平的工资。【原文：Against a backdrop of K-pop performances and dance music, more than 2,000 unionised workers from Samsung Electronics gathered in Seoul on Friday, holding a rare rally to demand the South Korean technology giant pay fair wages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amid-chants-k-pop-samsung-union-stages-rare-rally-fair-wages-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYGZSCDJKVJAPODYFNSQPRI7KQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，KKR 将无条件获得欧盟对意大利电信交易的反垄断许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[据直接知情人士透露，美国投资公司 KKR 在同意保留与意大利电信（TIM）竞争对手的商业协议后，有望获得无条件的欧盟反垄断许可，以收购该公司的固话网络。【原文：U.S. investment firm KKR is expected to gain unconditional EU antitrust clearance to buy Telecom Italia's (TIM) fixed-line network after agreeing to keep commercial agreements with TIM rivals, people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/kkr-set-unconditional-eu-antitrust-okay-telecom-italia-deal-sources-say-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIUWOXKJQZP2VGST4UGFAGRQPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:38:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道首席财务官称西门子可能将西门子能源股份转让给养老基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子集团财务总监告诉路透社，西门子股份公司可能会将其在西门子能源公司剩余的 17.1% 股份转让给集团的养老基金，以避免通过配售稀释公司股份的价值。【原文：Siemens AG will likely transfer its remaining 17.1% stake in Siemens Energy to the group's pension fund to avoid diluting the value of the company's shares via a placement, the group's finance chief told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/siemens-cfo-will-likely-transfer-remaining-siemens-energy-stake-pension-fund-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24DLCCHN2VIRZIECC4T4OU33KY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:13:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最后期限临近，盎格鲁铜资产争夺战考验必和必拓的决心]]></title><description><![CDATA[英美资源集团（Anglo American）的投资者要求必和必拓对整个公司提出更简单的收购要约或提供现金甜头，以达成可能成为矿业史上最大交易的协议，这将考验必和必拓为其投资组合增加更多铜矿的决心。【原文：BHP's resolve to add more copper to its portfolio will be tested by Anglo American investors' demands for a simpler offer for the whole company or a cash sweetener to clinch a deal that could become the biggest in mining history.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/battle-anglos-copper-assets-tests-bhps-resolve-deadline-looms-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EW6HVPUGJ5PCLA5NVRPPCUNXMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[七国集团（G7）主席称全球跨国公司最低税率协议注定失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利经济部长吉安卡洛-乔盖蒂（Giancarlo Giorgetti）在周五开始的七国集团（G7）金融峰会前表示，有关全球跨国公司最低税的协议将无法按原计划在 6 月前敲定。【原文：An accord over a global minimum tax on multinationals will not be finalised by June as previously planned, Italy's Economy Minister Giancarlo Giorgetti said ahead of a G7 finance summit starting on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-minimum-tax-deal-multinationals-set-fail-g7-chair-says-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CVEYYE5WBITBCKCVFKNFCLGKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空客为电动卡车配备客机驾驶舱，研究更安全的滑行方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司正在展示一种不同寻常的车辆--一辆装有 A350 客机基本控制装置的卡车--该公司希望借此展示自动滑行将如何使机场更加安全，因为人们对接连发生的喷气式客机在地面相撞事件的担忧与日俱增。【原文：Airbus is showing off an unusual vehicle - a truck fitted with basic A350 airliner controls - that it hopes can demonstrate how automated taxiing will make airports safer as concern grows over a spate of jetliners colliding on the ground.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/airbus-fits-electric-truck-with-airliner-cockpit-study-safer-taxiing-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYGXFFSQAVNJ5LB7TU5CMIIQB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:12:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：竞争对手退出，捷克在线杂货商 Rohlik 加速德国扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[创始人兼首席执行官托马斯-库普尔（Tomas Cupr）告诉路透社，随着外国在线食品杂货配送竞争对手退出德国，总部位于捷克共和国的 Rohlik Group 正在欧洲最大的经济体加紧发展，并有望在未来 12 个月内实现收支平衡。【原文：As foreign online grocery delivery rivals exit Germany, Czech Republic-based Rohlik Group is ramping up in Europe's biggest economy and is on track to break even within the next 12 months, founder and chief executive Tomas Cupr told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/czech-online-grocer-rohlik-ramps-up-german-expansion-rivals-quit-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6OMMI6ITNMQFO54ZX2USLKHTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金看好亚洲市场，日本公司成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周的一次对冲基金会议上，日本股市成为焦点，占据了亚洲顶级投资理念的大部分，资产经理们强调了日本公司为提高资本效率所做的努力，以及东京股市创纪录的上涨。【原文：Japanese stocks were in focus at a hedge fund conference this week, accounting for most of the top Asia investment ideas as asset managers highlighted Japan Inc's efforts to improve capital efficiency as well as the record run for Tokyo shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-companies-hog-spotlight-hedge-funds-tout-their-top-asia-picks-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCK7B6D2MJMMLAWNNDLV7TEMLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示特斯拉削减上海的 Model Y 产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[据行业数据和一位知情人士透露，自 3 月份以来，特斯拉上海工厂最畅销的 Model Y 电动汽车的产量已减少了两位数。【原文：Tesla has cut output of its best-selling Model Y electric car by a double-digit percentage number at its Shanghai plant since March, according to industry data and a source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-slashes-model-y-production-shanghai-data-shows-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPAKSYUTBFOFVBWBCGKAXUE6J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本工厂产出增长，通胀使日本央行退出复杂化：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，日本 4 月份的工厂产出可能连续第二个月增长，同时零售销售也有所回升，这凸显了经济复苏的萌芽迹象。【原文：Japanese factory output likely grew for a second straight month in April while retail sales picked up, a Reuters poll showed on Friday, highlighting budding signs of an economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-factory-output-seen-up-inflation-complicates-boj-exit-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFIXVA63VJNKNGZE6XADZUQKHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》：耶伦对生活成本上升表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五称，美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）对生活成本大幅上涨表示担忧。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen expressed concern over substantial increases in living costs, the Financial Times said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/uss-yellen-expresses-concern-over-rising-living-costs-ft-says-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAXX3N4PK5PK7PMMLKNV4J2MOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 04:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价利率失意破坏市场周五气氛]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWAHRSF56VP5VJIZTERKOG7GA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 04:31:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称英伟达在华为芯片之争中下调中国价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的消息人士透露，英伟达为中国市场开发的最先进人工智能芯片起步不利，充足的供应迫使其定价低于中国科技巨头华为的竞争对手芯片。【原文：Nvidia's most advanced AI chip it developed for the China market has got off to a weak start, with abundant supply forcing it to be priced below a rival chip from Chinese tech giant Huawei, according to sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-cuts-china-prices-huawei-chip-fight-sources-say-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJEYXQR4QVLI7JP67TVCTFKVWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 03:34:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，克里斯汀-约翰逊成为美国联邦存款保险公司新任主席的主要候选人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引一位知情人士的话报道，商品期货交易委员会民主党委员克里斯汀-约翰逊（Kristin Johnson）已成为领导联邦存款保险公司（FDIC）的主要候选人。【原文：Kristin Johnson, a Democratic commissioner at the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, has emerged as a leading candidate to lead the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp (FDIC), Bloomberg News reported on Thursday citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/kristin-johnson-emerges-leading-candidate-be-new-us-fdic-chair-bloomberg-news-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RE6RWWKSAZO6ZKEUXXTQ2CM53Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 02:55:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市下跌，美元上涨，降息赌注动摇]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市下跌，美元走高，原因是强劲的美国经济数据增强了利率在更长时间内保持较高水平的前景，以及美联储将慢慢削减利率，使投资者远离风险资产。【原文：Asian stocks fell on Friday, while the dollar advanced as strong U.S. economic data bolstered the prospect of interest rates staying higher for longer and the Federal Reserve taking its time in cutting rates, keeping investors away from risky assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-corrected-wrapup-1-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMALAFE2Z5M2RPRYYD5YGYDLXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 02:17:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息押注消退，美元将迎来周涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元创下一个半月以来的最大单周涨幅，这主要得益于出人意料的强劲美国经济指标和美联储会议纪要的鹰派基调。【原文：The dollar headed for its largest weekly rise in a month and a half on Friday, helped by surprisingly strong U.S. economic indicators and a hawkish tone in Federal Reserve minutes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-set-weekly-gain-rate-cut-bets-ebb-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MM4NXT4T3NIDXEAJEBDHPSAHNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:43:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽油需求坚挺，抵消了对利率的担忧，石油价格持平]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五盘初，油价持稳，原因是在通胀持续高企的情况下，市场人士对美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）关于利率的最新评论进行了评估，而美国季节性燃料需求的坚挺也为油价提供了支撑。【原文：Oil prices were steady early in the session on Friday as players took stock of the U.S. Federal Reserve's latest comments on interest rates amid sticky inflation, while firming seasonal U.S. fuel demand lent support.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-flat-firming-us-gasoline-demand-offsets-rate-jitters-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LHA63EHEJJJVCFFKX437FX7HM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美光在 Netlist 专利案中被判赔 4.45 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一个陪审团周四表示，芯片制造商美光科技欠计算机内存公司 Netlist 4.45 亿美元的赔偿金，因为美光侵犯了 Netlist 在高性能计算内存模块技术方面的专利权。【原文：Chipmaker Micron Technology owes computer-memory company Netlist $445 million in damages for violating Netlist's patent rights in memory-module technology for high-performance computing, a U.S. jury said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/micron-hit-with-445-million-us-verdict-netlist-patent-trial-2024-05-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCPYCTFPKVMFNMSIIH65TBVYIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:34:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 4 月通胀率进一步放缓至 2.2%，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周五公布的数据显示，由于食品通胀较为温和，4月份日本核心通胀率连续第二个月放缓，但仍远高于央行设定的2%的目标。【原文：Japan's core inflation slowed for a second straight month in April due to milder food inflation while staying comfortably above the central bank's 2% target, government data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-april-inflation-slows-further-22-matches-forecast-2024-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXYRMCDFQRL6BHM4CQ23DFEFMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 23:38:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>