<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 19:05:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 19:05:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[民主党人称特朗普非法扣留州电动汽车充电资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[环境与公共工程委员会的九位参议员周二表示，特朗普政府非法扣留了之前发放给各州的 30 亿美元电动汽车充电资金。【原文：A group of nine senators on the Environment and Public Works Committee said on Tuesday the Trump administration is illegally withholding $3 billion in previously awarded funds to states for electric vehicle charging.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democrats-say-trump-illegally-withholding-state-ev-charging-funds-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2YD4S3ZDFO2BAIT7APRN2EZZA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anduril 接管微软价值 220 亿美元的美国陆军耳机项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[帕尔默-卢基（Palmer Luckey）创办的国防科技初创公司 Anduril 周二表示，将接手微软为美国陆军开发和生产的混合现实头盔项目。【原文：Palmer Luckey-founded defense tech startup Anduril will take over the development and production of Microsoft's mixed-reality headset program for the U.S. Army, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/anduril-takes-over-microsofts-22-billion-us-army-headset-program-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6QQRKCXU5LSVC35MESPUEGJVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:52:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citadel 的格里芬认为关税对美国经济增长构成风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司 Citadel 创始人兼首席执行官肯-格里芬（Ken Griffin）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策对经济增长构成风险，可能会迫使其他国家寻找新的贸易联盟，同时他还批评了特朗普的 "狂妄言论"。【原文：Ken Griffin, founder and CEO of investment firm Citadel, said on Tuesday that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff policy is a risk to economic growth and may force other countries to find new trade alliances, as he criticized Trump's "bombastic rhetoric."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/citadels-griffin-sees-tariffs-posing-risk-us-growth-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMR32U6XKZLXPOMHZVB7AG6SOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 上调 2025 年美国石油产量预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（EIA）周二在其《短期能源展望》报告中称，美国今年的石油产量有望创下比此前预期更高的纪录，但它维持了对需求增长的预期。【原文：U.S. oil production is poised to set a larger record this year than prior estimates, the U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) said on Tuesday in its Short-Term Energy Outlook report, but it maintained its estimate for demand growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/eia-raises-us-oil-production-forecast-2025-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETNNMENARRJZVFEFEZB7HEPGZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:30:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通第一季度投资银行业务收费增长达十分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席运营官詹妮弗-皮普扎克（Jennifer Piepszak）表示，到目前为止，该公司第一季度的投资银行业务费用同比增长了十分之一。【原文：JPMorgan Chase Chief Operating Officer Jennifer Piepszak said the lender has seen investment banking fees grow by the mid-teens year over year so far in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-sees-investment-banking-fees-growth-up-mid-teens-q1-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3R73U4G5RKEZMB64UUYASPCO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥航空公司首席执行官称纽约首次公开募股的市场条件并不理想]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥航空公司首席执行官周二表示，目前的市场条件并不适合墨西哥航空公司在纽约上市，去年该公司的上市计划曾被推迟。【原文：Market conditions are currently not ideal for Mexican airline Aeromexico to list in New York, the firm's CEO said on Tuesday, after plans to go public were delayed last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/market-conditions-not-ideal-aeromexico-ipo-new-york-ceo-says-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAEKZ3OMNFK3RFM4A3WISPFZD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:11:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州选民批准的车辆数据访问措施经受住了法庭挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一名联邦法官驳回了代表汽车制造商的一个团体对马萨诸塞州选民批准的一项措施提出的质疑，该措施扩大了对车辆数据的访问，并允许独立商店维修日益复杂的汽车技术。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday rejected a challenge by a group representing automakers to a Massachusetts voter-approved measure that expanded access to vehicle data and allowed independent shops to repair increasingly sophisticated automotive technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/massachusetts-voter-approved-vehicle-data-access-measure-survives-court-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPUV6QI62JIJNOWO7W27YZGS2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汤森路透赢得人工智能版权 "合理使用 "裁决，一举击败竞争对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[特拉华州的一名联邦法官周二表示，美国版权法不允许汤森路透的一家前竞争对手复制该信息和技术公司的内容，以建立一个基于人工智能的竞争性法律平台。【原文：A federal judge in Delaware on Tuesday said that a former competitor of Thomson Reuters was not permitted by U.S. copyright law to copy the information and technology company's content to build a competing artificial intelligence-based legal platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/thomson-reuters-wins-ai-copyright-fair-use-ruling-against-one-time-competitor-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZ54RNUJMFLEHCMHM7EIWI73OM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称，2025 年和 2026 年美国电力使用量将创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（U.S. Energy Information Administration）在本周二发布的《短期能源展望》（Short Term Energy Outlook）报告中称，2025 年和 2026 年美国的电力消耗量将创下历史新高。【原文：U.S. power consumption will rise to record highs in 2025 and 2026, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said in its Short Term Energy Outlook on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-power-use-reach-record-highs-2025-2026-eia-says-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRCFDL4CSROPDJ4ZQ2EHD7IP7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟隐私监管机构称 DeepSeek 可能面临进一步监管行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲隐私监管机构周二表示，DeepSeek 未来可能会面临来自各国监管机构的更多行动，这凸显了该集团对中国廉价人工智能初创公司日益流行的担忧。【原文：DeepSeek may face more actions from national regulators in the future, Europe's privacy watchdog said on Tuesday, underscoring the bloc's concerns about the rising popularity of the cheap Chinese artificial intelligence startup.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/deepseek-may-face-further-regulatory-actions-eu-privacy-watchdog-says-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YTRON7PWJMIXFDSXA7CAPOUHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:38:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行首席财务官称剩余五项同意令]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行的一位高管周二表示，该行还有五项同意令要解决与贷款和销售行为有关的问题，他还补充说，最近终止的三项监管处罚表明该行一直在取得进展。【原文：A top Wells Fargo executive said on Tuesday that the bank has five consent orders remaining to resolve issues related to its lending and sales practices, and he added the recent termination of three regulatory punishments shows that the bank has been making progress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-cfo-says-five-consent-orders-are-remaining-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZPKDEFIG5K67GZWRMQPWYGPW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔表示，鉴于经济强劲，不急于进一步放宽政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在参议院银行委员会听证会上准备的开场白中表示，鉴于经济 "整体强劲"，失业率低，通胀率仍高于美联储2%的目标，美联储并不急于再次下调短期利率。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve is in no rush to cut its short-term interest rate again given an economy that is "strong overall," with low unemployment and inflation that remains above the Fed's 2% target, Fed Chair Jerome Powell said in opening remarks prepared for delivery at a Senate Banking Committee hearing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/powell-says-theres-no-rush-ease-more-given-strong-economy-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRNS6L4ONFNBLFZVAWKSDZXGDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:31:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Axios 报道，迪士尼正在对其多元化和包容性计划进行调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Axios 周二报道，华特迪士尼正在改变其多样性、公平性和包容性（DEI）计划，以更加关注业务成果。【原文：Walt Disney is changing its diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) programs to focus more closely on business outcomes, Axios reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-is-making-changes-its-diversity-inclusion-programs-axios-reports-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EFW7FELTNOQVOSWWE7T56CO3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:25:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瞻博网络否认美国司法部诉讼指控：阻止与 HPE 140 亿美元合并案]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份法庭文件，瞻博网络否认了美国司法部的指控，在此之前，美国司法部曾起诉阻止惠普企业公司（Hewlett Packard Enterprise）以 140 亿美元全现金收购这家网络设备制造商。【原文：Juniper Networks denied the allegations by the U.S. Department of Justice, after the agency sued to block Hewlett Packard Enterprise's $14 billion all-cash takeover of the networking gear maker, according to a court filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/juniper-networks-denies-allegations-us-doj-lawsuit-block-14-billion-merger-with-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIYSX7KTGNPCRF3HMMO42N5HOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克被密苏里州起诉，指控其有种族歧视行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，星巴克被美国密苏里州告上法庭，该州指控星巴克利用对多元化、公平和包容的承诺作为借口，非法实施种族歧视。【原文：Starbucks was sued on Tuesday by the U.S. state of Missouri, which accused the coffee chain of using a commitment to diversity, equity and inclusion as a pretext to illegally discriminate on the basis of race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/starbucks-sued-by-missouri-over-dei-alleged-racial-bias-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNY6WBC33BNQVMPJS5T4STXEPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:08:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，油田服务公司SLB重组，预计将裁员更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的消息人士和路透社看到的一封内部邮件称，顶级油田服务供应商 SLB 正在重组其业务中的某些职能，并继续裁员。【原文：Top oilfield services provider SLB is reorganizing certain functions within its business and continuing to reduce its workforce, according to a source familiar with the matter and an internal email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oilfield-services-company-slb-reorganizes-expects-more-job-cuts-source-says-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLIYR7K3J5IW7OLGZU6C6NPOSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:50:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI的阿尔特曼称马斯克的提议是 "试图扰乱我们 "的策略]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 首席执行官山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）周二在被要求就埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的收购要约发表评论时告诉路透社，控制 OpenAI 的非营利组织是非卖品。【原文：The nonprofit that controls OpenAI is not for sale, OpenAI CEO Sam Altman told Reuters on Tuesday when asked to comment about Elon Musk's offer to buy it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openais-altman-says-musk-offer-is-tactic-to-try-mess-with-us-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFSU3S3C5BJD5OJAE6H4FVHY4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:47:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[绿色和平组织对美国能源输送管道公司提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[该环保组织周二表示，国际绿色和平组织已在荷兰法院对美国输油管公司能源转运公司提起诉讼，并补充说，这是欧洲新法律的首次测试，该法律旨在遏制意在压制维权活动人士的诉讼。【原文：Greenpeace International has filed a lawsuit against U.S. pipeline company Energy Transfer in a Dutch court, the environmental group said on Tuesday, adding it was the first test of a new European law aimed at curbing lawsuits intended to silence rights activists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/greenpeace-files-suit-against-us-pipeline-company-energy-transfer-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7J7FLFYPFL75B4UP5VUP2WPJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各大航空公司敦促特朗普政府放弃乘客赔偿审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国各大航空公司周二要求美国交通部放弃拜登政府启动的一项审查，即航空公司是否应就航班中断向乘客支付赔偿金。【原文：Major U.S. airlines on Tuesday asked the U.S. Transportation Department to abandon a review launched by the Biden administration over whether carriers should be required to pay passengers compensation over flight disruptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/major-airlines-urge-trump-administration-abandon-passenger-compensation-review-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGDUHX3XRBNTZIK5I5QFXF4QO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国市场监管机构旨在暂停有关气候信息披露的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）代理主席周二表示，该机构正请求法院暂停就一项气候披露规则提起的诉讼，该规则由他的前任通过，并在争议中被迅速搁置。【原文：The acting chair of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Tuesday the agency was asking a court to pause proceedings in a lawsuit over a climate disclosure rule that was passed by his predecessor and swiftly stayed amid controversy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-market-watchdog-aims-pause-lawsuit-over-climate-disclosures-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCDI6772MBKPVBJ2FYMJPX4UBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片初创公司 Positron 募集 2350 万美元种子轮资金，欲与英伟达一较高下]]></title><description><![CDATA[旨在与英伟达（Nvidia）竞争的初创芯片制造商 Positron 周二表示，它筹集了 2350 万美元，用于扩大其美国制造的人工智能芯片的生产规模。【原文：Positron, a startup chip maker that aims to compete with Nvidia , said Tuesday it raised $23.5 million to scale production of its U.S.-made artificial intelligence chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-chip-startup-positron-raises-235-million-seed-round-take-nvidia-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y34J5T5OUJMCJCZH3X23YA3ILM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:19:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司称在 2023 年以来最繁忙的一月交付了 45 架飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二表示，该公司在 1 月份交付了 45 架飞机，高于上个月的 30 架，这是自 2023 年以来美国飞机制造商交付飞机最多的一个月。【原文：Boeing said on Tuesday that it had delivered 45 airplanes in January, up from 30 deliveries the previous month and the most deliveries in a month for the U.S. planemaker since 2023.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-says-it-delivered-45-aircraft-busiest-january-since-2023-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IENKDENLFZKWRKRI6OBVZ45WJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔：除美国联邦消费者保护委员会外，没有其他机构负责消费者保护执法工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一位资深民主党参议员要求确保消费者金融保护局继续获得资金时，美联储主席周二表示，除消费者金融保护局外，没有其他美国监管机构负责确保银行遵守防止欺骗消费者的规定。【原文：No U.S. regulator other than the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau is tasked with ensuring that banks abide by rules guarding against deceptive practices regarding consumers, the head of the Federal Reserve said on Tuesday as he was pressed by a senior Democratic senator to ensure the CFPB remains funded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-powell-no-agency-other-than-cfpb-tasked-with-consumer-protection-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWT5RIFOANNSTADFPWV36LD62M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:11:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行老板预计特朗普执政期间美国政策不确定性仍将持续，但仍看好经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行高管周二表示，随着唐纳德-特朗普总统第二届政府的组建，他们预计政策的不确定性将持续存在，但对经济前景仍持乐观态度。【原文：U.S. bank executives said on Tuesday they expected policy uncertainty to linger as President Donald Trump's second administration takes shape, but remained optimistic on the economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bank-bosses-expect-us-policy-uncertainty-persist-under-trump-stay-bullish-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJFCMWDVJRLKPG564XLMISVEL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 15:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISS 以特朗普的命令为由终止美国董事会的多元化考量]]></title><description><![CDATA[顶级代理顾问机构股东服务公司（Institutional Shareholder Services）周二表示，在提出投票建议时，将不再考虑美国公司董事会的性别、种族或民族多样性。【原文：Top proxy adviser Institutional Shareholder Services said on Tuesday it will no longer consider the gender, racial or ethnic diversity of U.S. company boards when making its voting recommendations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/iss-ends-diversity-considerations-us-boardrooms-citing-trump-orders-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AWXULULQBKMDFZYSAREECKUQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 15:41:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃利奥特斥资 25 亿美元入股菲利普斯 66，推动中游业务出售]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）周二表示，该公司已在美国炼油商菲利普斯 66 公司（Phillips 66）持有超过 25 亿美元的股份，并计划推动该公司的运营变革和中游业务的出售。【原文：Elliott Investment Management said on Tuesday it has built a stake of more than $2.5 billion in U.S. refiner Phillips 66 , and plans to push for operational changes and the sale of the company's midstream business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/elliott-builds-25-billion-stake-phillips-66-pushes-midstream-business-sale-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UK67VZQJBMFDAELLV4RTCBFVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 15:30:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者监察机构执法和监管负责人宣布辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的内部电子邮件显示，陷入困境的美国消费者金融保护局负责执法和监督的高级官员周二提出辞职，理由是唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府决定停止该机构的所有活动。【原文：The top officials for enforcement and supervision at the embattled U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau tendered their resignations on Tuesday, citing the decision by President Donald Trump's administration to halt all activity at the agency, according to internal emails seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-watchdogs-enforcement-supervision-heads-announce-resignation-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5FMZLOHFBFIA7BODU6JZHH3DQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 15:28:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛终止 IPO 多元化承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）周二表示，已终止与该投资银行首次公开募股业务相关的多元化、公平和包容性承诺。【原文：Goldman Sachs said on Tuesday it has ended a diversity, equity and inclusion pledge tied to the investment bank's initial public offering business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-ends-ipo-diversity-pledge-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6YMI2DKQRODFPF7JNSZAXALQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 15:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特首席执行官谴责特朗普关税带来的 "成本和混乱"]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司首席执行官吉姆-法利（Jim Farley）说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提出并实施的关税增加了 "大量成本和混乱"，尽管法利说他相信总统的目的是加强美国汽车业的整体实力。【原文：Ford Motor CEO Jim Farley said U.S. President Donald Trump's proposed and implemented tariffs have added "a lot of cost and a lot of chaos," although Farley said he believes the president aims to strengthen the American auto industry overall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-ceo-decries-cost-chaos-trump-tariffs-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDDL2GF7HRKETBPHXZ626R2TQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 14:51:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲刑警组织称，四名俄罗斯人在打击 Phobos 勒索软件行动中被捕]]></title><description><![CDATA[泛欧警察机构欧洲刑警组织（Europol）周二表示，上周逮捕了四名俄罗斯人，他们涉嫌部署 Phobos 勒索软件变种，向欧洲和其他地区的人勒索钱财。【原文：Four Russian nationals, who were suspected of deploying a variant of Phobos ransomware to extort payments from people in Europe and beyond, were arrested last week, the pan-European police agency Europol said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/four-russians-arrested-phobos-ransomware-crackdown-europol-says-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYZZH4HNPBJ37OCL5TYZFQOSBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 14:44:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>