<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 22:37:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 22:37:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司新任首席财务官马拉维的基本年薪为 105 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周四表示，新上任的首席财务官耶稣-"杰伊"-马拉维（Jesus "Jay" Malave）将获得 105 万美元的基本年薪，并有资格获得目标值分别为 126 万美元和 650 万美元的年度和长期奖励。【原文：Boeing Co said on Thursday that incoming CFO Jesus "Jay" Malave would receive $1.05 million as an annual base salary and he would be eligible for annual and long-term incentive awards with target values of $1.26 million and $6.5 million, respectively.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-new-cfo-malave-receive-105-million-annual-base-salary-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCCSY2F3GZJ2HDJWDWW5N2QBTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 22:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[清洁能源支持者抨击美国预算法案是一种挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，清洁能源的倡导者谴责众议院最终通过了唐纳德-特朗普总统的减税法案，认为这是能源转型道路上的一次逆转，而化石燃料利益集团则欢欣鼓舞。【原文：Advocates of clean energy on Thursday decried the final passage of President Donald Trump's tax cut bill by the House of Representatives as a reversal of course on the energy transition, while fossil-fuel interests rejoiced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/clean-energy-backers-blast-us-budget-bill-setback-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6R2275B67VOTFN4EZIYLB6N2UA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司获得价值 28 亿美元的美国战略卫星合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周四表示，该公司已获得一份价值 28 亿美元的美国战略合同，用于开发和生产两颗卫星，并可选择再生产两颗。【原文：Boeing Co said Thursday it had secured a $2.8 billion U.S. strategic contract to develop and produce two satellites with options for two more.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-secures-28-billion-us-strategic-satellite-contract-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHQO7VFLFZIAVCYLNKIBNBYXIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国解除对中国商飞的通用电气喷气发动机许可证暂停令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国商务部周四通知通用电气航空航天集团（GE Aerospace），再次允许该公司向中国商飞（COMAC）运输喷气发动机，取消了几周前颁发的许可证暂停令。【原文：The U.S. Department of Commerce informed GE Aerospace on Thursday that it was once again allowed to ship jet engines to China's COMAC, lifting license suspensions issued several weeks ago, according to a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-lifts-license-suspensions-ge-jet-engines-chinas-comac-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PTJTGCATJIVBBEDCLD5ZO7Z6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行将于 7 月 9 日把利率维持在 3.25%，但今年将再降息一次：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[接受路透社调查的大多数经济学家预计，新西兰储备银行将在7月9日维持利率不变，预测中值显示今年将再降息一次，每次25个基点，而5月份的调查显示降息两次。【原文：The Reserve Bank of New Zealand will leave interest rates unchanged on July 9, a majority of economists polled by Reuters expected, with the median forecast showing just one more 25 basis point cut this year compared with two in a May survey.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rbnz-hold-rates-325-july-9-cut-once-more-this-year-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSRYLL3LHNO6ZNZ7ZJJZI4ACSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电动汽车减税政策将于 9 月 30 日到期]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是美国电动汽车税收抵免的终点。【原文：It is the end of the line for U.S. electric vehicle tax credits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-electric-vehicle-tax-breaks-will-expire-sept-30-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZ2LD2MCGBKZJDBQUXSHDLRCFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国众议院批准特朗普的巨型预算法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党控制的美国众议院周四通过了唐纳德-特朗普总统的大规模减税和支出法案。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives passed President Donald Trump's massive tax-cut and spending bill on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/view-us-house-approves-trumps-mega-budget-bill-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDLWB6UZ3ZMHLH6WJOUJL4WTHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对零售商而言，美越贸易协定留下了问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家周四表示，美国和越南宣布的一项贸易协议给耐克和阿迪达斯等从东南亚国家工厂采购鞋类和服装的运动服装零售商带来了新的问号。【原文：A trade deal announced by the U.S. and Vietnam creates new question marks for sportswear and clothing retailers like Nike and Adidas that source shoes and clothes from factories in the Southeast Asian country, industry experts said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retailers-us-vietnam-trade-deal-leaves-questions-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLED6I3CVVIERDNJY2UD7EZHBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:21:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长认为 100 个国家将被征收 10%的互惠关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，约有100个国家可能会被征收10%的互惠关税，他还补充说，预计在7月9日的最后期限之前会有 "大量 "贸易协议宣布，关税税率可能会大幅提高。【原文：About 100 countries are likely to see a reciprocal tariff rate of 10%, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday, adding that he expects "a flurry" of trade deals announced before a July 9 deadline that could see tariff rates increase sharply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasury-chief-sees-100-countries-getting-10-reciprocal-tariff-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WN4OPN4PCVIBFIZ5UPOABCAXBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的税收法案避免了一次债务危机，却使未来的财务困境更加严重]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的减税和支出法案于周四在国会获得通过，避免了美国政府违约的近期前景，但却使美国的长期债务问题变得更加严重。【原文：President Donald Trump's tax-cut and spending bill, which passed Congress on Thursday, averts the near-term prospect of a U.S. government default but makes America’s long-term debt problems even worse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-tax-bill-averts-one-debt-crisis-makes-future-financial-woes-worse-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGU5IHS6CJOC5LSICR5AA5CWCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联航和捷蓝航空要求美国驳回精神航空对合作关系的投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）和美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周四要求美国交通部驳回精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）就两家公司拟议的合作关系提出的申诉。【原文：JetBlue Airways and United Airlines on Thursday asked the U.S. Transportation Department to reject a complaint filed by Spirit Airlines over their proposed partnership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/united-jetblue-ask-us-reject-spirit-airlines-complaint-over-partnership-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UHP4XIY7FPNXBNFBOCHC2GHRE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:42:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 在人工智能人才争夺战中挖走首席执行官格罗斯后，Sutskever 将领导 Safe Superintelligence 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[伊利亚-苏茨克沃（Ilya Sutskever）在失去首席执行官丹尼尔-格罗斯（Daniel Gross）后，接管了他去年创办的人工智能初创公司安全超级智能公司（SSI）。【原文：Ilya Sutskever has taken over the reins of Safe Superintelligence (SSI), the artificial intelligence startup he launched last year, after losing CEO Daniel Gross to an intensifying talent war in the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sutskever-lead-safe-superintelligence-after-meta-poaches-ceo-gross-ai-talent-war-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZYYQUKBEVN3BMKND3FZATHIJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商连续第 10 周减少石油和天然气钻机数量]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周四在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第10周削减石油和天然气钻机数量，这是自2020年7月以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating for a 10th week in a row for the first time since July 2020, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-cut-oil-gas-rigs-10th-week-row-baker-hughes-says-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JHZTALX3VVMWFH44LPQBSNYBPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球音乐和维珍音乐首席执行官回击批评 Downtown Music 交易的人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）旗下维珍音乐集团（Virgin Music Group）的两位联合首席执行官周四回击了对该公司斥资 7.75 亿美元收购 Downtown Music 的批评，称这笔交易将创建一家为独立唱片公司提供广泛服务的公司。【原文：The two co-chief executives of Universal Music Group's Virgin Music Group on Thursday pushed back against critics of its $775 million acquisition of Downtown Music, saying the deal would create a company providing a wide range of services to independent labels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/universals-virgin-music-ceos-push-back-against-critics-downtown-music-deal-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JR6L672AJNIYPPVHFRXRI6ISAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普如何开始塑造就业市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统第二次入主白宫已有约半年时间，他开始通过政策调整来塑造美国部分就业市场，包括积极打击移民和裁减联邦工作人员。【原文：Roughly half a year into his second stint in the White House, President Donald Trump is starting to shape portions of the U.S. job market through his policy changes, including aggressive crackdowns on immigration and reductions in the federal workforce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-trump-is-starting-shape-job-market-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIU4RTC5SZI4ZL6O2JHI6BGTT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UPS 向其美国司机提供自愿买断方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[包裹巨头 UPS 周四表示，作为其历史上最大规模网络重组的一部分，它将向全职美国司机提供自愿买断服务。【原文：Parcel giant UPS said on Thursday it will offer voluntary buyouts to its full-time U.S. drivers as part of the largest network reconfiguration in its history — a sweeping overhaul that includes cutting 20,000 jobs and closing 73 facilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/ups-offers-voluntary-buyout-packages-its-us-drivers-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XA3QVZ6UYNNVLBNRRQ7RQEMXPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，特朗普政府将在秋季重点讨论美联储主席的接替问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四告诉CNBC，特朗普政府将在今年秋天集中精力寻找美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）的继任者，并补充说官员们有 "很多不错的人选"。【原文：The Trump administration will focus on finding a replacement for Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell this fall, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told CNBC on Thursday, adding that officials had "a lot of good candidates."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-will-focus-fed-chair-replacement-fall-bessent-says-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJTTHBPYDFMONLOWF5N6WOC4E4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，金砖国家将启动担保基金以促进对成员国的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟知内情的人士告诉路透社，由发展中国家组成的金砖国家集团将宣布成立一个由新开发银行（NDB）支持的新担保基金，以降低融资成本并促进投资。【原文：The BRICS group of developing nations is set to announce a new guarantee fund backed by the New Development Bank (NDB) to lower financing costs and boost investment, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/brics-launch-guarantee-fund-boost-investment-member-nations-sources-say-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2XPM4B23ZIPLFRAWTT4IGRYZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士寻求与特朗普达成贸易协议，避免陷入欧盟困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政界人士和熟悉内情的人士表示，瑞士正在探讨可以做出哪些让步，以确保与华盛顿达成贸易协议，但瑞士必须谨慎行事，以保护其与主要贸易伙伴欧盟的利益。【原文：Switzerland is exploring what concessions it can make to secure a deal with Washington on trade, but it must tread carefully to protect its interests with key trading partner, the European Union, politicians and people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/switzerland-seeks-trade-deal-with-trump-without-getting-into-eu-bind-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TI7VWBXZTVLSROO2MW7OIU536M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[铂金价格在六月份的强劲反弹后上涨空间有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和交易商表示，在创纪录的季度涨势之后，铂金价格进一步上涨的空间有限，在汽车行业需求依然低迷的背景下，预计中国的进口将走软，南非的产量将有所恢复。【原文：Platinum prices have limited room to rise further after a record quarterly rally, analysts and traders said, with Chinese imports expected to soften and South African output to recover against a backdrop of still-muted auto sector demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/platinum-prices-have-limited-upside-after-junes-stellar-rally-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLMS72MKDFLH5ILWJFU6SJJJ2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 15:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织称美国税收和支出法案与削减赤字建议背道而驰]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）发言人朱莉-科扎克（Julie Kozack）周四表示，即将在国会进行最终投票的美国大规模税收和支出法案与国际货币基金组织关于华盛顿在中期内减少财政赤字的建议背道而驰。【原文：The massive U.S. tax and spending bill slated for a final vote in Congress runs counter to the International Monetary Fund's recommendations that Washington reduce fiscal deficits over the medium term, IMF spokesperson Julie Kozack said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imf-says-us-tax-spending-bill-runs-counter-deficit-cutting-advice-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHJVPGBAQVONLCT3IEN2SP66WQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 15:32:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：农产品为何阻碍印美贸易协议？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和印度的贸易谈判代表周三力争在唐纳德-特朗普总统规定的7月9日谈判截止日期之前敲定一项降低关税的协议，但在美国乳制品和农业方面的分歧仍未得到解决。【原文：U.S. and India trade negotiators were pushing on Wednesday to finalise a tariff-reducing deal ahead of President Donald Trump's July 9 negotiating deadline, but disagreements over U.S. dairy and agriculture remained unresolved.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/why-are-farm-goods-holding-up-india-us-trade-deal-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KD6ZRMRETFMUFPWZBNU4OHZ7GY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 15:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席博斯蒂克适应特朗普政策可能需要一年或更长时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联储主席拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周四表示，美国很可能面临一段通胀高企的时期，这有可能渗入消费者心理，企业可能需要一年或更长的时间来适应贸易和其他政策方面正在发生的转变，他阐明了在降息之前保持耐心的理由。【原文：The U.S. is likely facing a period of elevated inflation that risks seeping into consumer psychology, with companies likely needing a year or longer to adjust to the shifts underway in trade and other policies, Atlanta Fed president Raphael Bostic said on Thursday, spelling out the case for patience before any rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bostic-adjustment-trump-policies-could-take-year-or-more-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWDC64BEXJJOXGMHQMYK5HJHOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 15:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，4、5月份德国汽车对美出口下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车工业协会（VDA）周四表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收的进口关税打击了德国汽车制造商在其最重要的海外市场的销售，德国4月和5月对美国的汽车出口大幅下降。【原文：German car exports to the United States fell sharply in April and May as import tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump hit German automakers' sales in their most important foreign market, the VDA industry association said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/german-car-exports-us-slide-april-may-tariffs-hit-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLZ27NL65VKORAQC4QOTEF2X7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:58:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月工厂订单因飞机需求强劲而反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对飞机的需求强劲，5 月份美国制成品的新订单激增，第二季度过半时企业的设备支出似乎也很强劲。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods surged in May on strong demand for aircraft and business spending on equipment appeared to be strong halfway through the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-factory-orders-rebound-may-strong-aircraft-demand-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBIAV2YV7RIFRFLNZNXQKJCKVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，峰会与阿斯利康就 150 亿美元的合作协议进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，Summit Therapeutics 公司和阿斯利康公司正在讨论一项价值高达 150 亿美元的合作交易。【原文：Summit Therapeutics and AstraZeneca are discussing a partnership deal worth as much as $15 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/summit-considers-up-15-billion-partnership-with-astrazeneca-bloomberg-news-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBD6LYCSPNJLXA6FLTHJARE2EU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:39:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在辛特拉度假胜地，各国央行行长探讨其领域面临的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[在葡萄牙辛特拉山区举行的年度会议上，各国央行行长本周直面了他们控制全球货币体系所面临的日益严峻的挑战，从对美国联邦储备局的政治攻击到稳定币的崛起，不一而足。【原文：At their annual gathering in the hills of Portugal's Sintra, central bankers this week confronted rising challenges to their control of the global money system, from political attacks on the U.S. Federal Reserve to the rise of stablecoins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/sintra-getaway-central-bankers-mull-threats-their-domain-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IVAMXPKP4BIAXBHW7XXWU66CMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达将成为全球历史上最有价值的公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，随着华尔街对人工智能的乐观情绪加倍升温，英伟达有望成为历史上最有价值的公司，这家芯片制造商的市值达到 3.92 万亿美元。【原文：Nvidia was on track to become the most valuable company in history on Thursday, with the chipmaker's market capitalization reaching $3.92 trillion as Wall Street doubled down on optimism about AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-set-become-worlds-most-valuable-company-history-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZM3EO6SBVJGLCJDYCIDEBX4AA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相石破称特朗普总统在某些关税问题上可能存在误解]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂（Shigeru Ishiba）周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在一些关税相关问题上的观点可能是基于误解或错误信息，因为对日本进口商品征收24%互惠关税的暂停措施将于下周到期。【原文：Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba said on Thursday U.S. President Donald Trump's views on some tariff-related issues may be based on misunderstanding or misinformation, as a pause on a 24% reciprocal tariff on imports from Japan expires next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-pm-ishiba-says-president-trump-may-be-misinformed-some-tariff-issues-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEY7PPPBRBOMNMHISPCY5KGI6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:14:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西总统卢拉敦促南方共同市场深化与亚洲的关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周四表示，南美洲国家组成的南方共同市场集团应重点加强与亚洲国家的联系，他称亚洲是全球经济的 "活力中心"。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Thursday that the Mercosur bloc of South American countries should focus on strengthening its ties with Asian nations, which he described as the "dynamic center" of the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/brazils-lula-urges-mercosur-deepen-ties-with-asia-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EI725JUOGZMJ3OZL4BWSVD7AJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>