<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 15:33:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 15:33:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称退伍军人事务部最早将于 6 月开始大规模裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社查阅的一份备忘录，退伍军人事务部最早将于 6 月开始在这个政治敏感的机构进行大规模裁员。【原文：The Department of Veterans Affairs will begin mass layoffs at the politically sensitive agency as early as June, according to a memo reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/memo-says-mass-layoffs-veterans-affairs-will-begin-early-june-2025-03-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSN4LI442RNZ7N2CAN64MOLLHY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 15:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长卢特尼克表示，特朗普不会放松与芬太尼相关的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周日表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普不会放松对墨西哥、加拿大和中国因处理芬太尼而征收关税的压力。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will not let up his pressure on tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China related to their handling of fentanyl, U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/trump-will-not-ease-up-fentanyl-related-tariffs-us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-2025-03-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U4WZ3QT55LG7CSJKU6A7E6OVU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 13:49:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国特勤局称一夜之间在白宫附近击毙持枪男子]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国特勤局在一份声明中说，周日早些时候在白宫外发生冲突后，特勤局向一名持枪男子开枪，目前该男子正在当地医院接受治疗。【原文：The U.S. Secret Service shot an armed man outside the White House early on Sunday after a confrontation, and the man is now in an area hospital, it said in a statement.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-secret-service-shoots-armed-man-near-white-house-agency-says-2025-03-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22TWCMKW3NPQDKTUCIAUGQHCJA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 12:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯塔基州将城市露营定为犯罪，"无家可归者法庭 "试图逃避惩罚]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯塔基州去年通过了一项露营禁令，因为无家可归者和露营者的队伍不断壮大，令该州感到沮丧。随之而来的是人类的后果。【原文：The state of Kentucky passed a camping ban last year, frustrated by the growing ranks of homeless people and their encampments. Then came the human consequences.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/kentucky-makes-urban-camping-crime-homeless-court-seeks-avoid-punishment-2025-03-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2LCIRT2UNJLTBBJ2QWIKPNJIU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯塔基州将城市露营定为犯罪，"无家可归者法庭 "试图逃避惩罚]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯塔基州去年通过了一项露营禁令，因为无家可归者和露营者的队伍不断壮大，令该州感到沮丧。随之而来的是人类的后果。【原文：The state of Kentucky passed a camping ban last year, frustrated by the growing ranks of homeless people and their encampments. Then came the human consequences.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/kentucky-makes-urban-camping-crime-homeless-court-seeks-avoid-punishment-2025-03-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2LCIRT2UNJLTBBJ2QWIKPNJIU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州麻疹疫情爆发，家长抵制疫苗接种，医生反击]]></title><description><![CDATA[安娜-蒙塔尼兹博士正在拉伯克加班加点地联系那些对疫苗犹豫不决的家长，向他们解释一种大多数美国家庭从未见过的疾病所带来的严重风险，而这种疾病是可以通过免疫接种来预防的。【原文：Dr. Ana Montanez is working overtime in Lubbock to contact vaccine-hesitant parents, explaining the grave risks posed by a disease that most American families have never seen, and one that can be prevented through immunization.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/doctors-push-back-parents-embrace-kennedy-vitamin-texas-measles-outbreak-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47JGX5AL2ZOB5JKAO6XYHBEQTA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院共和党人推出为期六个月的临时拨款法案以避免停摆]]></title><description><![CDATA[控制美国众议院的共和党人周六公布了为期六个月的临时拨款法案，如果该法案获得国会通过，将避免政府在 3 月 14 日关门，并将目前的政府拨款延长至 2025 财年。【原文：Republicans who control the U.S. House of Representatives unveiled their six-month stopgap funding bill on Saturday, which if passed by Congress would avert a government shutdown on March 14 and extend current government funding through fiscal year 2025.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-republicans-unveil-six-month-stopgap-funding-bill-avert-shutdown-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLQVACF6DZJAJBJMB4UWHGSTXE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部解雇有组织犯罪缉毒工作组组长]]></title><description><![CDATA["亚当-科恩（Adam Cohen）在 LinkedIn 上写道："把坏人关进监狱是最不带政治色彩的事情。【原文："Putting bad guys in jail was as apolitical as it gets," Adam Cohen wrote on LinkedIn.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-justice-department-fires-head-organized-crime-drug-task-force-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVJFYC3ADFJYJB2H43TA3JABIQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家称，特朗普针对律师事务所的命令引发宪法关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[他们说，这些命令也可能是对过去与他作对的律师的特殊报复行为。【原文：The orders also may represent exceptional acts of retribution against lawyers who have crossed him in the past, they said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-orders-targeting-law-firms-raise-constitutional-concerns-experts-say-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHUQ3IEAANMAVA325QLU5PIW5I</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，疾控中心计划对疫苗和自闭症进行研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前还不清楚长期宣传反疫苗观点的卫生部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr）是否参与了计划中的研究，也不清楚研究将如何进行。【原文：It is unclear whether Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr, who has long promoted anti-vaccine views, is involved in the planned study or how it would be carried out.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-cdc-plans-study-into-vaccines-autism-sources-say-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OANFLY35QBLWHHE5DLFQJJ7YXM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学承诺解决特朗普政府在 4 亿美元资金被撤回后的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学临时校长表示，学校正在努力解决美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府的 "合理关切"，此前该校因校园反犹太主义指控而被取消了联邦政府的 4 亿美元拨款和合同。【原文：Columbia University's interim president said the school is working to address the "legitimate concerns" of U.S. President Donald Trump's administration after $400 million of federal government grants and contracts to the university were canceled over allegations of antisemitism on campus.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/columbia-university-promises-address-trump-administrations-concerns-after-400-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP2V5DFFYVM5LG54H6753OFZIY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南卡罗来纳州执行美国 15 年来首次行刑队死刑]]></title><description><![CDATA[南卡罗来纳州周五用行刑队处决了一名被定罪的杀人犯，这是美国15年来首次使用这种方式。【原文：South Carolina executed a convicted murderer by firing squad on Friday, the first use of the method in the United States in 15 years.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/south-carolina-carry-out-first-firing-squad-execution-us-15-years-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSLUGCYEY5LPPPERQQDJ3DAYH4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Politico 报道，美国卫生部长肯尼迪下周将会见食品公司负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.）计划于 3 月 10 日会见通用磨坊（General Mills）和百事可乐（PepsiCo）等知名食品公司的高管。【原文：U.S. Secretary of Health and Human Services Robert F. Kennedy Jr. plans to meet with senior executives from leading food companies like General Mills and PepsiCo on March 10, Politico reported on Saturday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-secretary-health-kennedy-meet-food-company-chiefs-next-week-politico-reports-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OM3PYYVFUVJDDLCB45NS6ZSAYI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党领导的各州加入针对特朗普大规模解雇联邦工作人员的法律斗争]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长和其他 19 个州的总检察长周四晚间对特朗普政府大规模解雇部分联邦工作人员提起诉讼，这是各州政府首次加入到与总统削减官僚机构的努力有关的法律斗争中。【原文：New York’s attorney general and 19 others filed a lawsuit Thursday night against the Trump administration’s mass firings of some federal workers, the first entry of states into the legal fight over the president’s efforts to slash the bureaucracy.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/democrat-led-states-join-legal-fight-over-trumps-mass-firings-federal-workers-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NA7DXBEIMVLF5GFMPS3AJT5PXE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[非政府环保组织就资金冻结问题起诉特朗普的环保局和花旗银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是非营利组织、州检察长和其他人士提起的一系列诉讼中的最新一起。【原文：It is the latest in a scores of cases filed by nonprofit groups, state attorneys general and others.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/environmental-ngo-sues-trumps-epa-citibank-over-funding-freeze-2025-03-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWZCBBKHOJML7GCSNG6725LHEI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家庭称特朗普政府违反了有关青少年性别治疗的法庭命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[变性青少年的家人和 LGBT 权益组织周五表示，美国卫生机构违反了法院的一项裁决，该裁决阻止他们执行唐纳德-特朗普总统的行政命令，即停止向为 19 岁以下人士提供性别转换治疗的医疗机构提供联邦资金。【原文：Families of transgender teens and LGBT advocacy groups on Friday said that U.S. health agencies had violated a court ruling that blocked them from enforcing President Donald Trump's executive order halting federal funding to healthcare providers that offer gender transition treatments to people under 19.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/families-say-trump-administration-violates-court-order-youth-gender-treatments-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACYGKDCA7BMULBTEAVE6ZHP3ZI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[她投票支持特朗普--特朗普解雇了她]]></title><description><![CDATA[珍妮弗-皮戈特（Jennifer Piggott）在 11 月大选期间曾自豪地在自家独栋楼房外挂起一面红蓝相间的特朗普竞选旗帜。现在，在她突然被公务员解雇后，她支持总统的日子结束了。【原文：Jennifer Piggott proudly hung a red-and-blue Trump campaign flag outside her one-story home during the November election race. Now, after she was abruptly fired from her civil service job, her days of supporting the president are over.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/doge-job-cuts-shake-trump-voting-west-virginia-town-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHGV6HBN2VNXXDWT4OH4C3XYDA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称美国劳工部恢复特朗普裁员目标工人的工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工部的一个工会周五表示，美国劳工部已经恢复了约 120 名面临解雇的员工的工作，这些员工是特朗普政府大规模解雇新近雇用的工人的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Department of Labor has reinstated about 120 employees who were facing termination as part of the Trump administration's mass firings of recently hired workers, a union said on Friday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-labor-department-reinstates-probationary-workers-targeted-dismissal-union-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVSJNCIRCNKDTIXKVBSZE4VHCQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国结束 5 万名运输安全管理局官员的集体谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周五表示，将终止为美国机场和其他交通枢纽检查站配备的约 5 万名运输安全管理局官员的集体谈判。【原文：The Trump administration said Friday it is ending collective bargaining for about 50,000 Transportation Security Administration officers that staff checkpoints at U.S. airports and other transportation hubs.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-ends-collective-bargaining-50000-airport-security-officers-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25GHDZCCQFNQLBPEYCQJQVDNMM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国务院雇员被控共享敏感信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份刑事起诉书，美国司法部周五宣布对一名国务院雇员提出刑事指控，该雇员被控与他在网上认识的人共享敏感的政府信息。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department on Friday announced criminal charges against a State Department employee accused of sharing sensitive government information with people he met online, according to a criminal complaint.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-state-dept-employee-arrested-conspiracy-charges-related-defense-information-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRNED2RO7VPLVBV3RIHOWWOBD4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[律师称美国最高情报机构开始实行多元化解聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家情报总监办公室参与多样性、平等、包容和无障碍项目的官员已被勒令辞职或解雇，其中两名官员的律师周五表示。【原文：Officials involved in diversity, equality, inclusion and accessibility programs at the U.S. Office of the Director of National Intelligence have been ordered to resign or be fired, the lawyer for two of the officials said on Friday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/deia-terminations-begin-us-office-director-national-intelligence-lawyer-says-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6W2S56GQNJ6REBX3NAL4X2J7Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普任命主播劳拉-英格拉哈姆和玛丽亚-巴蒂罗莫为肯尼迪中心董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他将任命福克斯新闻主持人劳拉-英格拉哈姆（Laura Ingraham）和福克斯财经主播玛丽亚-巴蒂罗莫（Maria Bartiromo）为约翰-肯尼迪表演艺术中心董事会成员。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he was appointing Fox News host Laura Ingraham and Fox Business anchor Maria Bartiromo to the board of the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-appoints-anchors-laura-ingraham-maria-bartiromo-kennedy-center-board-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R34HSDXRXBNK3FSFOETY6ZSI7U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普司法部解雇更多职业官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据社交媒体上的一篇帖子和熟悉此事的消息来源称，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周五解雇了美国司法部至少两名高级职业官员，其中包括负责处理总统赦免请求的办公室主任。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration on Friday fired at least two senior career officials at the U.S. Justice Department, including the head of the office that handles presidential pardon requests, according to a social media post and sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-justice-dept-fires-head-pardon-office-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKZLVOT6SFPYPKOOKFRNXYWPVU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》称，马斯克和卢比奥在内阁会议上发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，美国国务卿马可-卢比奥（Marco Rubio）和亿万富翁、白宫顾问埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周四在一次内阁会议上，就卢比奥实施的裁员幅度问题发生冲突，唐纳德-特朗普总统在一旁观看。【原文：U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio and billionaire White House adviser Elon Musk clashed on Thursday during a Cabinet meeting, as President Donald Trump watched, over the level of staff cuts that Rubio has carried out, the New York Times reported.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/musk-rubio-clash-cabinet-meeting-new-york-times-says-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMGROCEOTBNXTLHMXNGPXYLOMI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉恩-哈克曼在妻子死于罕见病毒几天后死于心脏病]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周五在新墨西哥州公布的尸检结果，奥斯卡获奖演员吉恩-哈克曼（Gene Hackman）在其妻子荒川贝茜（Betsy Arakawa）死于一种由老鼠传播的罕见病毒几天后，就已处于老年痴呆症晚期，并死于心脏病和其他因素。【原文：Oscar-winning actor Gene Hackman was in an advanced state of Alzheimer's and died of heart disease and other factors likely days after his wife, Betsy Arakawa, died of a rare virus spread by mice, according to autopsy results released on Friday in New Mexico.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/hackman-wife-lay-dead-days-possibly-weeks-says-sheriff-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKU4MOZILRNK5LQWWX2HICLNVQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称消费者保护局仍无法监控金融公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封内部邮件显示，陷入困境的美国消费者金融保护局（Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）的高层官员尽管承诺参与所有法律要求的工作，但仍不允许员工恢复对金融公司的监督。【原文：Top officials at the embattled U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau have not allowed staff to resume supervising financial companies despite committing to engage in all legally-required work, according to an internal email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/consumer-bureau-still-blocked-monitoring-financial-firms-email-says-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DV6GDOVNQ5PO7BXHJ4ATDO75UA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员希望马斯克和 FAA 代理局长就空中交通系统作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员埃德-马基（Ed Markey）周一敦促立法者传唤 SpaceX 公司首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）和联邦航空管理局代理局长就空中交通管制 IT 系统作证。【原文：Democratic Senator Ed Markey on Monday urged lawmakers to call SpaceX CEO Elon Musk and the acting head of the Federal Aviation Administration to testify about air traffic control IT systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senator-wants-musk-acting-faa-chief-testify-air-traffic-systems-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYHG5Q4W5JJ3ZE2XSETG2IX7L4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空要求美国最高法院撤销禁止捷蓝航空结盟的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司要求美国最高法院推翻下级法院的一项判决，该判决认定美国航空公司与捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）在美国东北部的合作关系已经破裂，违反了联邦反垄断法。【原文：American Airlines has asked the U.S. Supreme Court to reverse a lower-court decision that found its now-scrapped U.S. Northeast partnership with JetBlue Airways violated federal antitrust law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/american-airlines-asks-us-supreme-court-reverse-ruling-barring-jetblue-alliance-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RHJDSRPHZPALBE2NO5I64OXVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:28:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称特朗普政府将终止洛杉矶和费城地区办事处的大楼租约]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封电子邮件，美国证券交易委员会周一通知工作人员，特朗普政府正准备终止其洛杉矶和费城地区办事处的大楼租约。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission informed staff on Monday the Trump administration is preparing to terminate building leases for its regional offices in Los Angeles and Philadelphia, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-says-trump-administration-terminate-building-leases-los-angeles-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEVM6QR67FKF3PQUZNKUZ3B7B4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品及药物管理局称，野生海岸公司因禽流感污染风险召回生猫食品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周一表示，Wild Coast 公司正在召回一批冷冻生食猫用鸡肉配方，因为这些产品可能受到禽流感病毒的污染。【原文：Wild Coast is recalling lots of its frozen raw chicken formula for cats as it could potentially be contaminated by the bird flu virus, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/wild-coast-recalling-raw-cat-food-bird-flu-contamination-risk-fda-says-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64X3SJ2PRJJODBLRURGQWRXEBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:51:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>