<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 01:31:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 01:31:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美元兑日元汇率触及一个月高点，因美联储被认为需要时间降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑日元汇率周四升至一个月高点，原因是美国就业市场的强劲表现支持了美联储不必急于降息的观点。【原文：The dollar rose to a one-month high versus the yen on Thursday as robustness in the U.S. jobs market backed the idea that the Federal Reserve does not need to rush to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-hits-one-month-peak-yen-fed-seen-taking-time-with-rate-cuts-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTQOGYP6K5KIVJGKKP6BDUOSWY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本服务业连续第三个月扩张，但信心下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一项民间调查显示，日本服务业活动在 9 月份连续第三个月扩张，但速度略有放缓，信心也有所下降，这表明在制造业疲软的情况下，更广泛的经济出现了紧张。【原文：Japan's service sector activity expanded for the third straight month in September, but the pace slowed slightly and confidence dipped in a sign of the broader economic strains amid weakness in manufacturing, a private survey showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-service-sector-expands-third-month-confidence-dips-pmi-shows-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDPQDF774ZPTXALSAMMTQO5QKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:33:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东冲突加深导致石油上涨，全球供应前景限制涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四早盘，油价走高，原因是投资者权衡了中东冲突升级和原油流动中断的可能性，以及全球市场供应充足的情况。【原文：Oil prices ticked higher in early trade on Thursday as investors weighed the escalating conflict in the Middle East and the potential for disruption to crude flows, against an amply-supplied global market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-rises-middle-east-conflict-deepens-gains-capped-by-global-supply-outlook-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWISCAGVERLNRMD3DFALKKFL3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空董事购买 360 万股股票，反对更多领导层变动]]></title><description><![CDATA[西南航空董事拉克什-甘瓦尔（Rakesh Gangwal）在一位激进投资者日益增长的压力下被公司选入董事会，他买入了超过 1 亿美元的股票，并在周三表示，更多高层领导的变动将 "适得其反"。【原文：Southwest Airlines Director Rakesh Gangwal, who was picked by the company to join its board amid growing pressure from an activist investor, bought more than $100 million in stock and said on Wednesday more top level leadership changes would be "counterproductive."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-director-buys-36-mln-shares-opposes-more-leadership-changes-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJ5CIEQ7JNKK7L2RZZREBMQKCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:27:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚西太平洋银行将向 Resimac 集团出售汽车金融贷款记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[西太平洋银行（Westpac Banking Corp）周四表示，将向非银行贷款机构 Resimac Group 出售其汽车融资贷款账簿，预计出售完成时价值为 14 亿澳元（9.6362 亿美元）至 16 亿澳元。【原文：Westpac Banking Corp said on Thursday it would sell its auto finance loans book to non-bank lender Resimac Group for an expected value of A$1.4 billion ($963.62 million) to A$1.6 billion at completion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-westpac-sell-auto-finance-loan-book-resimac-group-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAJCNWB4CNPCDJ337FNBHCAGQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 23:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，由于销售放缓，丰田将把美国电动汽车生产推迟到 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周四报道，日本汽车制造商丰田汽车公司将以设计调整和销售放缓为由，把在美国肯塔基州工厂生产电动汽车的时间推迟到2026年上半年。【原文：Japanese automaker Toyota Motor would postpone the production of electric vehicles at its Kentucky plant in the US to the first half of 2026, citing design adjustments and slowing sales, the Nikkei business daily reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-delay-us-ev-production-2026-amid-slowing-sales-nikkei-reports-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQDXYH3LWVMTLF3KAXEFEMQQUU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 22:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网站显示特斯拉在美国停产最经济实惠的 Model 3 车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[据特斯拉电动汽车制造商网站周三称，该公司最经济实惠的 Model 3 紧凑型轿车在美国已不再接受订购。【原文：Tesla's most affordable Model 3 compact sedan was no longer available for order in the U.S., according to the EV maker's website on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-discontinues-most-affordable-model-3-variant-us-website-shows-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOPNHC2PCNIHXB5JFXKJ6LBK4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 22:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会对限制其加密货币监管的决定提出上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周三表示，它将对法院限制其监管加密货币市场能力的裁决提起上诉。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Wednesday it is appealing a court ruling that restricted its ability to regulate cryptocurrency markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sec-appeals-decision-that-restricted-its-crypto-oversight-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BGL37K3GVNQDCHW4EMG5F7Z5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 22:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元因日本首相 "不体面 "的利率言论而受到冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZNHJ5OLDZLMZFC33SHA6HLQIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+可以缓解伊朗石油冲击，但不能缓解更广泛的破坏]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果以色列摧毁伊朗的设施，欧佩克有足够的备用石油产能来弥补伊朗供应的全部损失，但如果伊朗报复性地打击其海湾邻国的设施，该生产国集团就会陷入困境。【原文：OPEC has enough spare oil capacity to compensate for a full loss of Iranian supply if Israel knocks out that country's facilities but the producer group would struggle if Iran retaliates by hitting installations of its Gulf neighbours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-could-cushion-iran-oil-shock-not-broader-disruption-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MUDOVYUWJIORBXXKEHUJHOCSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:37:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局在安全审查后结束对美国联合航空公司的强化监督]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周三表示，已完成对美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）的审查，并结束了对这家总部位于芝加哥的航空公司增加飞机和服务的强化监督和审批程序。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said Wednesday it has completed a review of United Airlines and ended its enhanced oversight and approval process for the Chicago-based carrier to add aircraft and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-ends-enhanced-oversight-united-airlines-after-safety-review-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLRAUTKF5BNBVEI5R4EZTJZQQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合太平洋公司称 FXE 发放部分美国-墨西哥谷物班车许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合太平洋公司（Union Pacific Corp）周三表示，与该公司互通的墨西哥铁路公司 Ferromex (FXE) 已恢复向位于得克萨斯州鹰口的美墨边境口岸的谷物穿梭列车发放许可证。【原文：Union Pacific Corp said on Wednesday that Ferromex (FXE), the Mexican railroad it interchanges with, has resumed issuing permits for grain shuttle trains at the U.S.-Mexico border crossing at Eagle Pass, Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/union-pacific-says-fxe-issuing-some-us-mexico-grain-shuttle-permits-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GIW7N7VHJO7ZDWCRWPAIJE7KY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 通知投资者不要投资包括 Sutskever 的 SSI 在内的五家人工智能初创企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，随着茁壮资本（Thrive Capital）和老虎环球（Tiger Global）等全球投资者向 OpenAI 投资 66 亿美元，这家 ChatGPT 制造商寻求的不仅仅是资金承诺--他们还希望投资者不要资助五家他们认为是密切竞争对手的公司。【原文：As global investors such as Thrive Capital and Tiger Global invest $6.6 billion in OpenAI, the ChatGPT-maker sought a commitment beyond just capital — they also wanted investors to refrain from funding five companies they perceive as close competitors, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-tells-investor-not-invest-five-ai-startups-including-sutskevers-ssi-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTIOQRJ4ABKHJMPM47Z73MLOBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登签署法案，豁免部分半导体工厂接受新的环境审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，乔-拜登总统于周三签署了一项立法，将豁免一些接受政府补贴的美国半导体制造设施接受新的联邦环境审查。【原文：President Joe Biden on Wednesday signed legislation that will exempt some U.S. semiconductor manufacturing facilities from new federal environmental reviews that are receiving government subsidies, the White House said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/biden-signs-bill-exempting-some-semiconductor-factories-new-environmental-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJX4NI7FSJIXDHX3ALRJARBJ3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:20:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯法院冻结美国摩根大通和梅隆银行的资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[莫斯科地区仲裁法院周三冻结了花旗银行俄罗斯分行持有的美国纽约梅隆银行的资金，以及摩根大通银行俄罗斯分支机构持有的摩根大通银行的资金，总额约为 3.72 亿美元。【原文：The Moscow Region Arbitration Court on Wednesday froze funds of the U.S. Bank of New York Mellon held by the Russian branch of Citibank as well as funds of JP Morgan Chase held by its Russian affiliate of Morgan Chase Bank amounting in total to about $372 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/russian-court-freezes-funds-us-banks-jp-morgan-mellon-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HFNBNBX5RJDXL3QOQXAMKJUFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 宣布对 Dockers 品牌进行战略审查，包括出售该品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss &amp; Co 周三宣布，该公司已开始对表现不佳的 Dockers 品牌进行战略审查，其中可能包括出售。【原文：Levi Strauss &amp; Co on Wednesday announced that it has initiated a strategic review of its underperforming Dockers brand, which could include a possible sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-announces-strategic-review-dockers-brand-including-sale-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNPOD3VGBJOPZCRPRS7H32TYSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:15:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴金称物价压力可能不会如预期般迅速消退]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周三表示，美国央行为使通胀率重返2%的目标而进行的斗争可能需要比预期更长的时间才能完成，这也限制了降息的幅度。【原文：The U.S. central bank's fight to return inflation to its 2% target may take longer than expected to complete and limit how far interest rates can be cut, Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-barkin-says-price-pressures-may-not-fade-fast-expected-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPEAYELV35PFNMQA45EQBSFYZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国港口罢工导致汉堡包和冷冻海鲜供应中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商和业内人士表示，由于国内供应有限，美国东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸港口的码头工人罢工正在阻止牛肉的进口，而餐馆和零售商越来越依赖牛肉来制作汉堡包。【原文：Dockworkers striking at U.S. East Coast and Gulf Coast ports are preventing imports of beef that restaurants and retailers increasingly rely on to make hamburgers due to limited domestic supplies, traders and industry members said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-port-strike-disrupts-hamburger-supplies-frozen-seafood-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5VZK32GLVPT3MCXKONDTBOOV4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券监管机构一把手离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）监管机构周三表示，该机构的执法总监即将离职，这标志着监管机构加强对华尔街和加密货币公司执法的三年任期即将结束。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's enforcement director is leaving the agency, the regulator said on Wednesday, marking the end of a three-year tenure during which the regulator stepped up enforcement against Wall Street and cryptocurrency firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-securities-regulators-top-cop-leave-agency-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35LTCVCBWNNBHEPXTDWEJHK2ZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[充足的石油供应抑制了业界对地缘政治紧张局势加剧的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[石油行业和市场对中东日益加剧的紧张局势反应平淡，这表明随着美国产量的增长和欧佩克+准备提高产量，石油供应已经非常充足。【原文：The oil industry and markets have had a muted reaction to rising tensions in the Middle East, a sign of just how well stocked oil supplies are as U.S. output grows and OPEC+ prepares to lift production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/plentiful-oil-supply-dampens-industry-reaction-rising-geopolitical-tensions-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6UBUS4OBBMA3LQIQW6WLAVIV4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国港口罢工期间咖啡集装箱堆积如山]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于港口工人罢工，数百个装有进口咖啡豆的集装箱在美国东海岸港口停止卸货，加剧了这个最大咖啡消费国的供应紧张状况。【原文：The unloading of hundreds of containers with imported coffee beans at the United States' East Coast ports has stopped due to the strike of portworkers, aggravating the tight supply in the largest coffee-drinking nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/coffee-containers-pile-up-us-ports-during-strike-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFTGEAE5VJNIHIYZXBDKWTSQGY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:31:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管发生了卡车司机罢工，但 9 月份哥伦比亚的 12 个月通胀率仍有所放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周三的一项民意调查显示，尽管受到卡车司机罢工的影响，哥伦比亚 9 月份的 12 个月通胀率预计将继续下降，而今年的通胀预期则保持稳定。【原文：Colombia's 12-month inflation is forecast to continue decelerating in September, despite the impact of a truckers' strike, according to a Reuters poll on Wednesday, while expectations for this year remain stable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-12-month-inflation-seen-slowing-september-despite-truckers-strike-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WOPLR5VZFL4PJVPAHJ4H5CRNE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 完成 66 亿美元融资，获得微软和 Nvidia 投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周三宣布，已从投资者处融资 66 亿美元，融资后估值达 1,570 亿美元，从而巩固了这家 ChatGPT 制造商作为全球最有价值私营公司之一的地位。【原文：OpenAI has raised $6.6 billion from investors at a post-money valuation of $157 billion, the company announced on Wednesday, cementing the ChatGPT maker's status as one of the most valuable private companies in the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-closes-66-billion-funding-haul-valuation-157-billion-with-investment-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMDTSR55GBL4JMGOURUCOSD6MY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:53:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准航空估值 104 亿美元，纽交所首次上市股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，StandardAero 的股票在市场上首次开盘就比首次公开发行价高出 29%，使这家由凯雷投资的航空维修服务提供商的市值达到约 104 亿美元。【原文：StandardAero's shares opened 29% above the initial public offering price in their market debut on Wednesday, giving the Carlyle-backed aviation maintenance services provider a market value of about $10.4 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/standardaero-valued-104-bln-shares-jump-nyse-debut-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IE5ZYMAXC5PDLDLZZHK4R5A6AI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国报告称密歇根核电站的腐蚀程度高于估计值]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国核电监管机构在周三公布的一份文件中称，希望重启密歇根州帕利塞德核反应堆的 Holtec 公司发现蒸汽发生器的腐蚀开裂 "远远超出 "估计。【原文：Holtec, the company wanting to reopen the Palisades nuclear reactor in Michigan, found corrosion cracking in steam generators 'far exceeded' estimates, the U.S. nuclear power regulator said in a document published on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-report-says-corrosion-michigan-nuclear-plant-above-estimates-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52TYXBCQWZLUXM6MFI6PKOPEGE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:24:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴尔金称 9 月降息前利率 "不同步"，通胀之战尚未结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周三表示，美国央行上月降息半个百分点，是承认其政策利率与经济现状 "脱节"，但不应被视为与通胀之战已经结束的迹象。【原文：The U.S. central bank's half-percentage-point interest rate cut last month was an acknowledgement that its policy rate was "out of sync" with where the economy stands, but shouldn't be taken as a sign that the battle with inflation is finished, Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-barkin-says-rates-were-out-sync-before-september-cut-inflation-fight-not-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGGY4FY2LFJH5KV6RSFPVX3NB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Charter 将免费提供 NBCUniversal 的 Peacock 流媒体服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Charter Communications 表示，根据一项新的多年期协议，该公司将从明年起向部分用户免费提供 NBCUniversal 的 Peacock 流媒体服务，此举旨在扩大有线电视和宽带公司的用户群。【原文：Charter Communications said it will offer NBCUniversal's Peacock streaming service to some customers at no extra cost from next year under a new multi-year deal, in a move to boost the cable and broadband firm's user base.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/charter-offer-nbcuniversals-peacock-streaming-service-no-extra-charge-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBZUHFWQRBMI5DUULASGC4J53M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:01:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊因 "联合雇佣 "司机遭美国劳工委员会投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会周三宣布，亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）被美国劳工委员会指控非法拒绝与代表承包商雇佣的司机的工会进行谈判。【原文：Amazon.com has been accused by a U.S. labor board of illegally refusing to bargain with a union representing drivers employed by a contractor, the agency announced on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-hit-with-us-labor-board-complaint-over-joint-employment-drivers-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCUGO3J4KBMF3G3XZ5VE76UQBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:54:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦法院维持让 KalshiEX 列出选举投注合同的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦上诉法院周三维持了下级法院的命令，允许纽约衍生品交易平台 KalshiEX LLC 列出允许美国人对选举结果下注的合约。【原文：A U.S. federal appeals court on Wednesday upheld a lower court's order that permitted New York derivatives trading platform KalshiEX LLC to list contracts that allow Americans to bet on election outcomes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-federal-court-upholds-ruling-letting-kalshiex-list-election-betting-contracts-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBBJIXQGMBKMBL6NVZZKDMU7N4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储警告辖区内房产面临巨大洪水风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周三发布的一份报告称，纽约、新泽西和康涅狄格地区的住宅面临着美国最严重的洪水风险。【原文：Homes in the New York, New Jersey and Connecticut areas face some of the most severe risk of flooding in the U.S., a report released on Wednesday by the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ny-fed-warns-big-flood-risk-properties-its-district-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GEYWT7P3QBLWZAGDPHLPY5OOVY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>