<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:05:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:05:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌反垄断裁决或给苹果带来 200 亿美元风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国法官裁定 Alphabet 旗下的搜索巨头非法垄断之后，苹果公司与谷歌之间利润丰厚的交易可能受到威胁。【原文：Apple's lucrative deal with Google could be under threat after a U.S. judge ruled that the Alphabet-owned search giant was operating an illegal monopoly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-antitrust-ruling-may-pose-20-billion-risk-apple-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLD6BB32IFMEPBDQBC3UGUC37M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waymo 将扩大洛杉矶和旧金山的自动驾驶打车服务区域]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的 Waymo 公司周二表示，正在扩大其在旧金山和洛杉矶的自动驾驶打车服务区域，以满足客户日益增长的需求。【原文：Alphabet's Waymo is expanding its autonomous ride-hailing service areas in San Francisco and Los Angeles to cater to growing demand from customers, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/waymo-expand-autonomous-ride-hailing-service-areas-los-angeles-san-francisco-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2DINXES2MVOLPIMSI5UCXSOGOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:55:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分歧调查显示墨西哥央行可能将利率维持在 11]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周二的一项调查中，大多数分析师认为墨西哥央行本周晚些时候可能会将基准利率维持在 11%，因为通货膨胀和本币近期的疲软扰乱了人们对关键贷款利率的预期。【原文：The Bank of Mexico will likely hold its benchmark interest rate at 11% later this week, according to a majority of analysts in a on Tuesday, as inflation and the recent weakness of the local currency muddle expectations for the key lending rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/divided-survey-shows-mexico-central-bank-likely-hold-interest-rate-11-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBWVK5WOFJMX5DZEEXKPQGOMP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:42:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NTSB 和波音公司无法确定是谁拆除了 737 MAX 9 的门栓]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会主席周二表示，国家运输安全委员会和波音公司还无法确定是谁拆除了阿拉斯加航空公司一架新型 737 MAX 9 飞机的门塞。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board and Boeing have not been able to determine who removed a door plug in a new 737 MAX 9 Alaska Airlines 737 MAX 9 that suffered a mid-air emergency in January, the board's chair said Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ntsb-boeing-have-not-been-able-identify-who-removed-737-max-9-door-plug-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIBDOFSBGZNIDIRIYLN62IQ3KA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:24:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在抛售 1,500 亿美元后，美国波动率挂钩基金的抛售可能趋于枯竭]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，波动性挂钩基金的抛售压力加剧了最近几天美国股市的跌势，这种压力可能有望缓解。【原文：Selling pressure by volatility-linked funds that exacerbated losses in U.S. stocks over recent days may be on track to ease, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/selling-us-volatility-linked-funds-may-be-drying-up-after-150-billion-dump-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYNV4YTMVNP5HAZBB4JEPEL7E4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:20:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PIMCO 的 Ivascyn 称美国可能避免经济衰退，但警告财政形势严峻]]></title><description><![CDATA[集团首席投资官丹尼尔-伊瓦辛（Daniel Ivascyn）表示，尽管有迹象表明美国经济将进一步走弱，但美国经济仍有望实现软着陆，但美国不断恶化的财政状况正促使美国债券巨头 PIMCO 越来越多地增持外国政府债务。【原文：The U.S. economy is still on track for a soft landing despite signs of further weakening, but the country's deteriorating fiscal profile is prompting U.S. bond giant PIMCO to increasingly add exposure to foreign government debt, said Group Chief Investment Officer Daniel Ivascyn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/pimcos-ivascyn-says-us-likely-avoid-recession-warns-dire-fiscal-picture-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLDIRW2UCVNSXFJSY2LZSJ5QDI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[施瓦布称，高交易量和关键供应商的技术问题引发了周一的故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘉信理财公司（Charles Schwab &amp; Co.【原文：Charles Schwab &amp; Co. said that high trading volumes and a technical issue with a key vendor triggered temporary outages on its trading platform on Monday, a day when its customers rushed to navigate an outsize market selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/schwab-says-high-volumes-technical-issue-with-key-vendor-triggered-mondays-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDVWQM6KZBMILDYANWGATCLLMU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团举报人被拒绝分得 4 亿美元罚金]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家联邦上诉法院周二表示，花旗集团的一位副总裁无权分享该银行因风险管理失误而同意于 2020 年 10 月支付的 4 亿美元民事罚款。【原文：A federal appeals court on Tuesday said a Citigroup vice president was not entitled to a share of a $400 million civil fine that the bank agreed to pay in October 2020 over its risk management failures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/citigroup-whistleblower-denied-share-400-million-penalty-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRQWQ4L36BJLZG3PNNF2HRIP4U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:29:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沉睡的公用事业板块成为美股动荡的避风港]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美股大跌中，公用事业公司股票成为投资者眼中难得的亮点，因为动荡的市场促使投资者不再追捧今年大部分时间领涨的高涨科技股。【原文：Shares of utilities companies are presenting investors with a rare bright spot in the U.S. stock selloff, as turbulent markets prompt a shift away from the high-flying technology stocks that have led gains for most of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/sleepy-utilities-sector-shines-haven-us-stock-turbulence-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPFOPGASJRMWRCSG6DX6RRVD6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构因皮珀桑德勒公司记录保存失误罚款 1,600 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler 投资银行公司周二表示，已同意向美国监管机构支付总额 1600 万美元的民事罚款，以解决对其记录保存做法的调查。【原文：Piper Sandler has agreed to pay a total of $16 million as a civil penalty to U.S. regulators to resolve investigations into its record-keeping practices, the investment banking firm said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regulators-fine-piper-sandler-16-mln-record-keeping-failures-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5YQEES4QBPTBMFD33VT4ITWYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:54:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国连锁药店因马斯克支持特朗普而避开特斯拉汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国连锁药店罗斯曼（Rossmann）周二表示，由于首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）支持美国共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump），公司车队将不再购买特斯拉汽车。【原文：German drugstore chain Rossmann said on Tuesday it would no longer buy Tesla cars for its corporate fleet due to CEO Elon Musk's support for U.S. Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/german-drugstore-chain-shuns-teslas-over-musks-support-trump-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VAE2X653BIUXCQ4QVOFCZGPWQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:34:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥 7 月通胀率升至一年多以来最高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二的一项民意调查显示，墨西哥7月份的总体通胀率可能再次加快，达到一年多来的最高水平，而核心指数预计将继续放缓。【原文：Mexico's headline inflation rate likely accelerated again in July to reach its highest level in more than a year, while the core index is forecast to continue to moderate, a Reuters poll showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-inflation-seen-ticking-up-july-highest-over-year-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHLLYWQIJJIU3FI6KKNOOPYWUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司机组人员担心乘客在 1 月 5 日的空中面板爆炸事故中丧生]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据安全专家周二公布的令人心碎的证词，阿拉斯加航空公司的空乘人员担心乘客在 1 月 5 日一架波音 737 MAX 9 飞机空中面板爆炸后的混乱中被吸出机舱。【原文：Alaska Airlines flight attendants feared passengers had been sucked out of the plane in the chaos following the Jan. 5 mid-air panel blowout on a Boeing 737 MAX 9 jet, according to harrowing testimony released by safety experts on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/frightened-alaska-air-crew-feared-passengers-were-lost-jan-5-mid-air-panel-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDMJHWP2CVJEDIL273JGYIQY7A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:57:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司开始与工会进行劳动合同谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）和美国运输工人全国谈判委员会（Teamsters National Negotiating Committee）周二表示，双方已开始就一份新合同进行集体谈判，该合同涵盖美国 10,000 名航空维修及相关工人。【原文：United Airlines and the Teamsters National Negotiating Committee began collective bargaining for a new contract covering 10,000 aviation maintenance and related workers in the U.S., the union said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-begins-labor-contract-negotiations-with-union-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LRRSC3OC7RJ2PJTBINGZNNQIFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 X 公司在新诉讼中指控广告商非法抵制]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体平台 X 周二起诉了一个全球广告联盟和几家大公司，其中包括玛氏公司（Mars）和 CVS Health，指控他们非法合谋抵制该网站并导致其收入损失。【原文：Elon Musk’s social media platform X on Tuesday sued a global advertising alliance and several major companies, including Mars and CVS Health, accusing them of unlawfully conspiring to boycott the site and causing it to lose revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/musks-x-accuses-advertisers-illegal-boycott-new-lawsuit-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQRDYCARZJL3HIJBNZUNY36TNE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国市场波动使 "缓冲 "ETF 成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[股市波动性的飙升对至少有一类资产管理公司来说可能是个好消息：那就是那些推出 "缓冲 "交易所交易基金（ETF）的公司，它们为投资者提供了以股市上涨换取下跌保护的机会。【原文：The spike in stock market volatility may be good news for at least one group of asset managers: those rolling out "buffer" exchange-traded funds (ETFs) that offer investors the chance to swap some stock market upside for downside protection.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-market-volatility-puts-buffer-etfs-spotlight-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OATXLY6KHRND7I6L4A6H5OCARQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，花旗集团从美国银行聘请的财富管理高管数月后离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士周二透露，花旗集团一位高管将离开花旗集团，该高管今年 4 月从美国银行加盟花旗集团。【原文：A Citigroup executive who joined the bank from Bank of America in April is leaving Citi, one source with knowledge of the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-wealth-executive-hired-bofa-leaves-after-months-source-says-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JOTXLSEZF5PFPCSCYX6IVQI5SE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:27:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌垄断裁决有助于苹果在反垄断案中的辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周早些时候，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司（Google）在与美国反垄断执法机构的斗争中败下阵来，苹果公司可能成为赢家。【原文：Apple could be the winner after Alphabet's Google lost its fight with the U.S. antitrust enforcers earlier this week, with a ruling that supports the iPhone maker's defense in its own antitrust court battle with U.S. prosecutors, legal experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/google-monopoly-ruling-could-help-apple-defense-antitrust-case-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2VHXBBMUROBTINTXAJ677RXQ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国企业债券市场发行将在市场波动中放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[据债券市场参与者称，在市场波动导致投资者减持公司债券，转而购买更安全的美国国债之后，一些公司债券发行商预计将在本周推迟销售。【原文：Some corporate bond issuers are expected to delay sales this week, after market volatility caused investors to trim corporate bond holdings in favor of safer U.S. Treasuries, according to bond market participants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-corporate-bond-market-issuance-set-slow-amid-market-volatility-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5E47N7X3MJLX5PLOXLZV6INI6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将从全球网络故障中恢复的困难归咎于达美航空]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司周二指责达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）为从全球网络故障中恢复而挣扎多日，导致该公司取消了 6000 多个航班。【原文：Microsoft on Tuesday blamed Delta Air Lines for its dayslong struggle to recover from a global cyber outage that led it to cancel more than 6,000 flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-blames-delta-its-struggle-recover-global-cyber-outage-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3F7U64RZ5KALIAYDURBNEYR2E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在谷歌具有里程碑意义的裁决中，对公司保存证据提出了警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一项具有里程碑意义的裁决认定，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司非法垄断了网络搜索，同时也对这家科技巨头掩盖案件潜在证据的行为进行了斥责，并就数据保护问题向其他公司发出了警告。【原文：A landmark ruling on Monday that Alphabet's Google illegally monopolizes Web search also came with a rebuke for the tech giant for obscuring potential evidence in the case, and a warning to other companies about safeguarding data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/landmark-google-ruling-warning-companies-about-preserving-evidence-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7PXQ4O2IRJUFFWY4EY5IPWCWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储调查显示，美国家庭债务水平在第二季度有所上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周二发布报告称，第二季度美国家庭总债务水平有所上升，但总体拖欠率趋于稳定，这表明借款人的状况仍然良好，足以支持经济发展。【原文：Total U.S. household debt levels edged up in the second quarter but overall delinquency rates stabilized, indicating that borrowers are still in decent enough shape to support the economy, a report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-household-debt-levels-edge-up-q2-ny-fed-survey-shows-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEEOHXV7VFIDBBCMJUGB5NFRAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰财富首席投资官：科技股抛售为低价买入创造了机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行私人银行首席投资官周二表示，科技股的大幅抛售为以更低的价格买入盈利公司创造了机会。【原文：The sharp sell-off in tech stocks has created opportunities to buy into profitable companies at a cheaper price, the chief investment officer of HSBC's private bank said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tech-sell-off-creates-opportunities-buy-cheaper-hsbc-wealth-cio-says-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73RD725I25PTXK7DJLE7Q2NXLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福克斯公司公布季度收入增长，利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[福克斯公司周二公布的季度利润超出华尔街预期，收入也有所增长，这得益于美国市场对其 Tubi 流媒体服务的稳定需求，福克斯股价在早盘交易中上涨了近 5%。【原文：Fox Corp topped Wall Street expectations for quarterly profit and reported a rise in revenue on Tuesday, helped by steady demand for its Tubi streaming service in the United States, sending its shares up nearly 5% in early trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fox-reports-rise-quarterly-revenue-beats-profit-estimates-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSNLO323LRPM7AGYJZEHU5C3JE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求放缓给销售带来压力，WK Kellogg 将精简生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[WK Kellogg 公司周二表示，随着生产的精简，该公司计划在 2026 年底前完全关闭其位于内布拉斯加州奥马哈的工厂。【原文：WK Kellogg plans to completely shutdown its Omaha, Nebraska, plant by the end of 2026 under a reorganization that will also reduce the cereal maker's headcount by more than 17%, it said on Tuesday, as it streamlines its production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/wk-kellogg-streamline-production-slowing-demand-pressures-sales-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRODS3HHWFKX3FRED3KOLFIPFE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:54:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[气温创历史新高，Sempra 第二季度利润增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公用事业公司森普拉（Sempra）周二公布，由于夏季用电高峰期电力需求强劲，该公司第二季度利润有所增长。【原文：U.S. utility Sempra posted a rise in second-quarter profit on Tuesday, as it benefited from strong demand for electricity during the peak summer months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/sempra-posts-higher-q2-profit-record-high-temperatures-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGRTEIEBZVP45IL6PRVVDFP7WM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:53:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构将开始审查 IBM 和 Hashicorp 合并案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hashicorp 周二表示，这家云软件供应商上周收到了英国竞争与市场管理局的通知，称将开始对该公司与国际商业机器公司（International Business Machines）的合并进行第一阶段审查。【原文：Hashicorp said on Tuesday the cloud software vendor received a notice from the UK's Competition and Markets Authority last week saying it would begin a phase one review of the company's merger with International Business Machines .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/uk-regulator-begin-review-ibm-hashicorp-merger-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VWL5VRY3VMEVCPCGME5LBXHRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:48:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银称 5000 亿日元利差交易平仓仅完成 50]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团（UBS）的一位分析师周二估计，影响全球市场的日元利差交易史诗般的平仓只完成了大约50%。【原文：An epic unwinding of the yen-funded carry trade that has reverberated through global markets is only about 50% done, a UBS analyst estimated on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-carrytrade-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GJQHX2HBRLZJGEFJI2XM5TXWU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场监管机构称特斯拉将在中国修复 170 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家市场监管机构周二表示，特斯拉正在通过无线软件更新对中国的 170 万辆汽车实施远程召回。【原文：Tesla is performing a remote recall of 1.7 million vehicles in China with an over-the-air software update, the state market regulator said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-fix-17-mln-vehicles-china-says-market-regulator-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPDS7IEHPBLQJP4ZZAQFFYN7LU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国运输安全委员会发布有关波音 737 MAX 9 中空紧急事件的文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会在周二上午公布了一些文件，这些文件是在对 1 月份一架近乎全新的波音 737 MAX 9 飞机空中面板爆炸事件举行听证会之前公布的。【原文：The U.S. National Transportation Safety Board released documents on Tuesday morning ahead of hearings into a January mid-air panel blowout of a near new Boeing 737 MAX 9 jet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transport-safety-board-releases-documents-boeing-737-max-9-mid-air-emergency-2024-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNSVGNMQOROBZJ45R2V4CMOSF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>