<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:18:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:18:40 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国运通预计2026年盈利前景乐观，因富裕客户消费保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运通周五公布的年度利润预测值普遍高于华尔街预期，凸显出这家信用卡巨头主要由富裕客户组成的用户群体在宏观经济不确定性加剧的背景下仍保持着强劲消费力。【原文：American Express forecast annual profit largely above Wall Street expectations on Friday, underscoring resilient spending by the credit card giant's largely affluent ​customer base amid broader economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/amex-projects-upbeat-2026-profit-steady-spending-by-affluent-customers-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCK24GV2O5PTPKBFTNMHMKHVUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:10:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飞机租赁商在风险累积中稳步前行]]></title><description><![CDATA[大西洋两岸的裂痕与动荡的市场或许令投资者心神不宁，但拥有全球半数机队的飞机租赁巨头们表示，他们的行业从未像现在这样充满韧性。【原文：A transatlantic rift and jittery markets may be unnerving investors, but the aircraft leasing giants that own half the global fleet say their industry has rarely felt more resilient.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/aircraft-lessors-steer-steady-course-risks-accumulate-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AOC4IFO4GFLX7NERPMHNPUH5LE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名前美联储官员沃什执掌美国央行]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周五提名前美联储理事凯文·沃什接替杰罗姆·鲍威尔担任美联储主席，鲍威尔的任期将于五月结束。此举让这位美联储的常年批评者获得了实践其货币政策"体制变革"理念的机会——此时正值特朗普政府推动加强对美联储控制权之际。【原文：President Donald Trump on Friday chose former Federal Reserve Governor Kevin Warsh to head the U.S. central bank when Jerome Powell's leadership term ends in May, giving a frequent Fed critic a chance to put his idea ​of monetary policy "regime change" into practice at a moment when the president has pushed for more control over the central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-picks-former-fed-official-warsh-run-fed-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QO67KNY4CBLRPKCC4Y4BR3VNSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最大电网用电需求预计将逼近冬季纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据运营商最新七日预测，美国最大电网PJM互联电网周五的电力需求预计将达到约141吉瓦的峰值，仅略低于该电网冬季历史最高纪录。【原文：Power demand on the largest U.S. electric grid on Friday is expected to peak at about 141 gigawatts, just shy of the all-time winter record on the PJM Interconnection, according to the operator's latest seven-day forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/demand-largest-us-electric-grid-forecast-close-winter-record-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZJWWZFZHBIVXCDRE5YITEZQZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：多强才算过强？]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克·多兰和ROI团队本周末最期待阅读、观看和收听的内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYHO4OY7CBIUJES7TKEJHWAICY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险经纪公司怡安因风险管理实力提升利润大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[保险经纪公司怡安周五报告称，受其风险管理服务需求强劲推动，第四季度经调整利润大幅增长。【原文：Insurance broker Aon reported a jump in fourth-quarter adjusted profit on Friday on the back of robust demand for its risk management offerings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/insurance-broker-aon-profit-jumps-risk-management-strength-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUGSPYX3IVJKJM5KLS3NOXNHSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得益于低成本石油生产，埃克森美孚第四季度利润超出华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚周五公布的第四季度财报超出华尔街预期，其在盈利丰厚的二叠纪盆地和圭亚那资产的原油产量提升，助力这家美国最大石油生产商业绩增长。【原文：Exxon Mobil beat Wall Street targets in fourth-quarter earnings reported on Friday, with higher oil production in profitable Permian Basin and Guyana assets helping to boost the No. 1 U.S. oil producer's results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-beats-wall-street-targets-q4-profit-with-help-lower-cost-oil-production-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGKN34S7HVMKFAK6XWPUE44N44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威瑞森预测年度利润将大幅增长，无线用户增长创六年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电信巨头威瑞森周五公布的年度利润和自由现金流预测超出市场预期，假日高峰期的激进促销策略助力该公司实现六年来最高的季度无线用户净增量。【原文：Verizon forecast annual profit and free cash flow above market expectations on Friday, as aggressive promotions during peak ​holiday period helped the U.S. carrier post its highest quarterly ‌wireless subscriber additions in six years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/verizon-forecasts-upbeat-annual-profit-wireless-subscriber-growth-hits-six-year-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJCW3FQALNJRXA2B74T3AYJDGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙第四季度盈利超预期，瞄准委内瑞拉投资机遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司第四季度利润下滑，但仍超出市场预期。该公司正致力于削减成本、提升运营效率，以应对2025年全年原油价格走低的局面。【原文：Chevron's fourth-quarter profits fell but came in ahead of estimates as it focused on cutting costs and making its operations more efficient to contend with lower crude prices throughout 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-beats-q4-profit-estimate-eyes-venezuela-investment-opportunities-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I72AOD52MZKOPARPE7PK7FZQSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:16:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典汽车零部件供应商奥托立夫预计2026年将无有机销售增长，第一季度盈利能力持续萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典汽车安全设备制造商奥托立夫周五预测，受汽车产量停滞影响，2026年公司将无有机销售增长，且第一季度盈利能力较去年同期大幅下滑。该公司同时公布第四季度利润下滑。【原文：Swedish car safety gear maker Autoliv , predicted on Friday no organic sales growth in 2026 amid stalling vehicle production, and much lower profitability in the first quarter than a year ago, as it reported a drop in fourth-quarter profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/autoliv-q4-adjusted-profit-matches-expectations-sees-2026-profit-margin-around-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVKLNCUIIZJ5XKDNAVSBL3P62Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望财报密集周，就业数据将考验美股走势，微软股价暴跌后市场承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[在科技巨头微软发布令人失望的财报拖累股市指数后，包括谷歌母公司Alphabet和亚马逊在内的又一批巨额企业财报，将在未来一周考验美国股市。【原文：Another huge batch of corporate earnings including from megacaps Alphabet and Amazon will test the U.S. stock market in the coming week after a disappointing report ​from heavyweight Microsoft weighed on equity indexes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-heavy-earnings-week-jobs-data-test-us-stocks-after-microsoft-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJEH2BRVPBOMXNX5BCTNNXU2VA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:06:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价预计将维持在每桶60美元附近，因供应过剩抵消了地缘政治风险的影响。]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五公布的调查显示，由于市场供应过剩的前景抵消了地缘政治紧张局势可能导致的货运中断影响，今年油价可能维持在每桶60美元附近。【原文：Oil prices are likely to hold near the $60 a barrel mark this year, as the prospect of oversupply in the market offsets the impact of geopolitical tensions that could disrupt cargoes, a Reuters poll showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-forceast-hover-near-60bbl-oversupply-outweighs-geopolitical-risks-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUL6TTSVJBKPFILNSIC3IWQWWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta因儿童剥削指控面临新墨西哥州诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms将于下周面临新墨西哥州提起的诉讼审判，该州指控其在平台上使儿童和青少年暴露于性剥削风险并从中牟利。这是首例针对这家社交媒体巨头的同类案件进入陪审团审理阶段。【原文：Meta Platforms is set to face trial next week in a lawsuit brought by the state of New Mexico accusing it of exposing children and teens to sexual exploitation on its platforms and profiting from it, the first case of its kind against the social media giant to reach a jury.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/meta-faces-new-mexico-trial-over-child-exploitation-claims-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBAZSIIDSJMXHO6IN7QJGOOVD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下跌，特朗普即将宣布美联储主席人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周五下跌，此前美国总统唐纳德·特朗普表示已确定美联储主席人选，有报道称前美联储理事凯文·沃什很可能成为其选择。【原文：U.S. stock index futures ​slid on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he has firmed up his choice to ‌lead the Federal Reserve, with reports suggesting that former central bank governor Kevin Warsh would be his likely pick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-fall-trump-set-announce-fed-chair-pick-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJ6YW4SSY5J7DDCEHXCJWIRLYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:27:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着油价飙升，欧佩克+计划将暂停增产措施延续至3月]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位代表向路透社透露，欧佩克+联盟很可能在周日的会议上维持暂停增产的决定，尽管受美国可能对欧佩克成员国伊朗发动军事打击的担忧影响，原油价格已攀升至每桶70美元以上。【原文：OPEC+ is likely to keep its pause on oil output increases for March when it meets on Sunday, five delegates told Reuters, even as crude climbs above $70 a barrel on concern the U.S. could launch a military strike on OPEC member Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-set-keep-oil-production-pause-march-prices-jump-sources-say-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKBCZZM7MZKADL7XF2MQHR3OZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:19:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，LVMH集团旗下干邑品牌轩尼诗已与工人达成薪酬协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[路威酩轩集团旗下干邑品牌轩尼诗——该集团规模最大的酒类品牌——已与工会达成薪酬协议，以补偿因去年销售疲软而损失的奖金，两名消息人士向路透社透露。【原文：LVMH's cognac maker Hennessy, the largest of its drink brands, has reached a pay deal with unions to compensate for bonuses lost last year due to weak sales, two sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/lvmhs-cognac-brand-hennessy-reaches-pay-deal-with-workers-sources-say-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGLNYQSEK5NBBIQKMJRX3NOGZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本外贸数据表明，其外汇市场干预仅限于口头警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[官方数据显示，日本政府上周未干预外汇市场，证实其捍卫日元的努力仅限于口头警告。【原文：Japan ​refrained from intervening in currency markets through last week, official data showed on ‌Friday, confirming that the government's efforts to defend the yen have been limited to verbal warnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-fx-market-intervention-limited-verbal-warnings-mof-data-shows-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3ELEHT6FNOIVCQ4ZVCIMBN4RI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博世警告2026年成本压力将加剧，推迟利润率目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大汽车零部件供应商博世（Bosch）周五警告称，2026年将面临又一个艰难年景，并推迟了实现7%利润率的目标。该公司预计，在全球关税冲击下，该行业的成本和竞争压力不会缓解。【原文：Bosch (ROBG.UL), the world's largest car parts supplier, on Friday warned of another tough year in 2026 and postponed a 7% margin target as it expects no let-up in cost and competitive pressure in a sector hit by tariffs worldwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bosch-warns-rising-cost-pressure-2026-delays-margin-target-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SX3B4G5OEFNB7ILEPEPPV3YSQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧元区经济2025年以稳健增长收官，尽管出口低迷且与美国贸易摩擦不断]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟统计局周五公布的数据显示，欧元区上季度经济增速超出预期，消费和投资加速增长抵消了出口疲软及美国贸易政策引发的特殊不确定性。【原文：The euro zone economy grew quicker than expected last quarter as consumption and investments kicked into higher gear, offsetting low exports and the exceptional uncertainty emanating from U.S. trade policy, Eurostat data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/euro-zone-economy-ends-2025-solid-footing-confirming-resilience-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK7N3SAKBBPZ7JH5UN2BGMBYGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰监管机构将调查Roblox平台对未成年人的风险问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰消费者保护监管机构ACM周五宣布，已对美国游戏平台Roblox展开调查，因其可能对欧盟未成年用户构成风险。【原文：The Netherlands' consumer protection regulator ​ACM has launched an investigation ‌into U.S. gaming platform Roblox over potential risks to underage users in the European Union, it said ‌on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/dutch-regulator-probe-roblox-over-risks-minors-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEX5FS2RZZMPDAQEXPCLT7TKYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:03:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[益博睿宣布10亿美元股票回购计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用数据与分析公司益博睿周五宣布启动一项新的10亿美元股票回购计划。【原文：Credit data and analytics company Experian on Friday announced the launch of a new $1 billion share repurchase programme.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/experian-unveils-1-billion-share-buyback-plan-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCQ6QPKKJ5OIDOQ76KKXVOJV64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:14:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国财政部长称，法国政府阻止了欧卫通信公司出售地面天线。]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国财政部长罗兰·莱斯库尔周五表示，他本周早些时候决定阻止法国卫星运营商欧卫通信（Eutelsat）——该企业是埃隆·马斯克旗下星链（Starlink）的竞争对手——出售地面天线，这些设备可实现与卫星的通信。【原文：French Finance Minister Roland Lescure said on Friday he had decided earlier this week to prevent French satellite operator Eutelsat , a rival to Elon Musk's Starlink, from selling ground antennas, which enable communication with satellites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/france-prevented-eutelsat-selling-ground-antennas-finance-minister-says-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3RWRFWLHBKOFBV254A6NSP3UU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：中国有条件批准DeepSeek收购英伟达H200芯片——消息人士透露]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，中国已批准顶级人工智能初创企业DeepSeek购买英伟达H200人工智能芯片，但监管条件仍在最终敲定中。【原文：China has given its top AI startup DeepSeek approval to buy Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips with regulatory conditions that are still being finalised, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-conditionally-approves-deepseek-buy-nvidias-h200-chips-sources-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FEZKY73N7RMWLKZACNKQUIZM2U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储提名将于周五公布，此前他在白宫会见了沃什]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普会见了前美联储理事凯文·沃什。这位美联储批评者曾表示，美国央行需要进行"体制变革"才能重获丧失的公信力。【原文：President Donald Trump met with former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, a Fed critic who has ​said the U.S. central bank needs "regime change" to regain lost credibility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-fed-pick-due-friday-after-meeting-warsh-white-house-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7EGWF7PZJI5BNI7MMFMCOYOIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经亚洲报道：苹果将在内存短缺背景下优先于2026年推出高端iPhone机型]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经亚洲周刊周五援引四位知情人士的消息报道称，苹果公司正优先推进2026年三款最高端iPhone机型的生产和发货，同时推迟标准机型的上市，此举源于营销策略调整及供应链限制。【原文：Apple is prioritizing production and shipment of its three highest-end iPhone models ​for 2026 while delaying the rollout of its standard ‌model due to a marketing strategy shift and supply-chain constraints, Nikkei Asia reported on Friday, citing four people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-prioritize-premium-iphone-launches-2026-nikkei-asia-reports-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOMF6VFYMFMWVN3OHWDOJ5FPSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞拍：小心你所祈求的]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔·斯图尔特·亨特带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFDJOWSVI5KW7ASZ6R52VMEPCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚表示，美国放弃最低价格要求不会影响其关键矿产战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚周五表示，将在美国放弃为关键矿产项目提供最低价格保障计划后，支持本国关键矿产供应链建设。【原文：Australia on Friday said it would support its critical mineral supply chains after the U.S. stepped back from plans to guarantee a minimum price for such projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-says-us-price-floor-backdown-wont-derail-its-critical-minerals-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVP7PVVK2NL55DLY7BAGAFW27M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币下跌，美联储主席猜测冲击风险资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币周五跌至两个月低点，因市场猜测美国联邦储备委员会下任主席可能收紧金融体系中的现金供应，打压加密货币并推高美元汇率。【原文：Bitcoin slumped to a two-month low on Friday as speculation the next chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve might tighten up on cash ​in the financial system hit cryptocurrencies and lifted the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-slips-fed-chair-speculation-hits-risky-assets-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMRNL647C5MC5J4JWLVIOY4H4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于欧元的一切：向欧洲央行提出的五个问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行将于下周四召开会议，政策制定者们松了一口气，因为特朗普总统要求购买格陵兰岛引发的美国加征新关税的威胁已然消退。【原文：The European Central Bank meets next Thursday with policymakers relieved that the threat of fresh U.S. tariffs over President Donald Trump's demands to buy Greenland proved short-lived.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/all-about-euro-five-questions-ecb-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUMCNDT4BJMTJGSMVP6E5Q3BOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名美联储人选以缓解市场不确定性，各方目光聚焦沃什]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普总统提名的美联储主席人选将驱散笼罩市场数月的不确定性阴云，为投资者预示杰罗姆·鲍威尔任期于五月结束后货币政策可能的发展方向。【原文：President Donald Trump's nomination to head the U.S. Federal ​Reserve will lift a cloud of uncertainty that has hung over markets for months, giving investors a signal ‌of how monetary policy may evolve once Jerome Powell's term ends in May.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-fed-nomination-ease-market-uncertainty-all-eyes-warsh-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPUWBV6YQBORNLVGPP6EJUAJLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>