<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:39:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:39:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[科尔首席执行官意外离职将加剧假日购物季前的困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[科尔百货公司（Kohl's）在公布季度业绩的前一天突然宣布首席执行官离职，这对投资者来说是个不小的打击，因为他们希望这家陷入困境的连锁百货公司能在关键的假日购物季到来之前做出积极的预测。【原文：Kohl's surprise CEO departure announcement a day before its quarterly results will play on the minds of investors, who were looking out for a positive forecast from the struggling department store chain ahead of the key holiday shopping season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kohls-surprise-ceo-departure-amplify-woes-ahead-holiday-shopping-season-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUAHGQQ4W5P5LGKGQF3U6TPULM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BPM 银行董事会召开会议，开始讨论联合信贷银行的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[BPM 银行周二召开董事会，就竞争对手意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）主动向这家意大利第三大银行提出的 100 亿欧元（105 亿美元）收购要约进行初步讨论。【原文：Banco BPM gathers its board on Tuesday for an initial discussion on the 10 billion euro ($10.5 billion) unsolicited takeover offer that rival UniCredit has launched for Italy's third-largest bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/banco-bpms-board-meets-start-discussing-unicredits-takeover-bid-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53H72PIUP5NTFM4U6ARE6LPQ4U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:15:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据安莎社报道，BPM 银行董事会成员称联合信贷银行的出价充满敌意]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）的一位董事会成员周二告诉意大利安莎通讯社（ANSA），联合信贷银行对意大利 Banco BPM 的出人意料的收购是充满敌意的。【原文：UniCredit's surprise bid for Italy's Banco BPM is hostile, a board member of the smaller lender told Italian newswire ANSA on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/banco-bpm-board-member-says-unicredit-bid-is-hostile-ansa-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQVZZSXB7FNCLMTKVFVWD4PDOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普承诺征收关税，欧洲汽车制造商业绩下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，欧洲汽车制造商股价下跌，交易商对美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收巨额关税做出了反应，这一消息加剧了市场对潜在全球贸易战的担忧。【原文：European automakers shares fell in early trading on Tuesday, as traders reacted to President-elect Donald Trump pledging big tariffs on Canada, Mexico and China, news that fueled jitters over a potential global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eurpoean-automakers-fall-trump-pledges-tariffs-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQOXBZFGRVIDZD3L6Y7OQP6IEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:20:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者表示知道如何交易特朗普 2.0]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普在社交媒体上承诺对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收新的关税后，投资者们周二重新拾起了他们的贸易战战术手册，相信他们的投资组合这次能更好地应对唐纳德-特朗普。【原文：Investors dusted off their trade war playbooks on Tuesday, confident their portfolios were better-prepared for Donald Trump this time after the U.S. President-elect took to social media and pledged new tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-say-they-know-how-trade-trump-20-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVQNA5SXL5L4LGRWLAUINSKDPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团被美国起诉贿赂后的重大后果]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国起诉阿达尼集团亿万富豪董事长高塔姆-阿达尼涉嫌行贿和欺诈，为集团旗下公司阿达尼绿色能源公司赢得合同之后，一些国家和投资者要么取消了与阿达尼集团的交易，要么停止了对阿达尼集团的投资。【原文：Some nations and investors have either scrapped deals or halted investments in the Adani Group, after the United States indicted its billionaire chairman Gautam Adani for alleged bribery and fraud to win contracts for a group company, Adani Green Energy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/major-fallout-indias-adani-group-after-us-bribery-indictment-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYHO3K5PHZNUPPAB4VMPC6ECIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为推出 Mate 70 智能手机，美国新芯片禁令迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国科技巨头华为技术公司（HWT.UL）周二发布了 Mate 70 系列智能手机，推进了其在高端智能手机领域的东山再起，同时展示了自己的操作系统，彻底摆脱了美国技术的束缚。【原文：Chinese tech giant Huawei Technologies (HWT.UL) unveiled its Mate 70 smartphone series on Tuesday, advancing its comeback in the premium smartphone space while showcasing its own operating system in a clean break away from U.S. technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/huawei-launches-mate-70-smartphone-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52Z3CLQNCVOJDKYOTIECPZX3IQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼就女性薪酬诉讼案达成 4300 万美元和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[原告律师周一在一份声明中表示，华特迪士尼已同意支付 4,330 万美元，以了结一项指控其加利福尼亚州女员工在八年时间里比男员工少挣 1.5 亿美元的诉讼。【原文：Walt Disney has agreed to pay $43.3 million to settle a lawsuit alleging that its female employees in California earned $150 million less than their male counterparts over an eight-year period, the plaintiffs' lawyers said in a statement on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/disney-settles-suit-over-womens-pay-43-million-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNEAT3RGUZORBNHAOAG6HFAR2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:34:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在保守派的压力下，沃尔玛将撤销部分多元化政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛的一位发言人周一表示，沃尔玛计划削减部分多元化、公平和包容性（DEI）举措，加入了越来越多感受到保守团体压力的企业行列。【原文：Walmart plans to cut back some of its diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) initiatives, a spokesperson for the retailer said on Monday, joining a growing list of firms feeling the heat from conservative groups.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-roll-back-some-diversity-policies-amid-pressure-conservatives-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27MXCTYXDBKSNCS6OG4VD4QDLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗氏将收购美国 Poseida Therapeutics 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士罗氏公司周二表示，将以每股 9 美元的价格收购总部位于加利福尼亚州的生物制药公司 Poseida Therapeutics，收购完成后的股权总价值将达到 10 亿美元。【原文：Roche will acquire California-based biopharmafirm Poseida Therapeutics for $9 per share at closing, for a total equity value of $1 billion, the Swiss company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/roche-acquire-us-based-poseida-therapeutics-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZRJ47CU7FL67LT5EUNQOHCHXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:29:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌提议重新调整欧洲搜索结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一些较小的竞争对手抱怨 Alphabet 旗下公司之前的调整导致其网站流量下降，以及欧盟反垄断监管机构考虑根据新的欧盟技术规则对该公司提出指控之后，谷歌提出对其在欧洲的搜索结果进行更多调整。【原文：Google has proposed more changes to its search results in Europe after some smaller rivals complained about lower traffic to their sites resulting from previous tweaks by the Alphabet unit and as EU antitrust regulators consider levying charges against the company under new EU tech rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-proposes-fresh-tweaks-search-results-europe-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XWVJ4UOPVPOJK6Q7TR5JBZBZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，日产寻求投资者以取代雷诺持有的部分股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周二报道，日产汽车公司正在寻找长期投资者，如银行或保险集团，以帮助其取代雷诺被稀释的部分股权。【原文：Nissan Motor is looking for a long-term investor, such as a bank or insurance group, to help it replace some of Renault's diluted stakeholding, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-seeks-investor-replace-some-renaults-equity-holding-ft-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPOAJHIHQNPTDMZVMEGIAVWAMA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，花旗集团在寻求全面改革银行时削减了晋升职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周二报道，花旗集团正在减少年终晋升的人数，因为该公司正在进行长期重组，以缩减员工人数，从而降低成本。【原文：Citigroup is cutting the number of year-end promotions it awards as it seeks to hold costs down amid a long-term restructuring to shrink headcount, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-slashes-promotions-it-seeks-overhaul-bank-ft-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RGANKMYPFLFBBGSWR2AQ5VTKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价特朗普加征关税引发市场恐慌]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIHESWFEDRIXLAMZLIUKXRLTWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:32:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿达尼绿色能源公司称未与道达尔能源公司讨论新的财务承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿达尼绿色能源公司（Adani Green Energy）周二表示，目前尚未与道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）商讨新的财务承诺，而在此前一天，这家法国石油巨头还表示将暂停对阿达尼集团的新投资。【原文：Adani Green Energy said on Tuesday there is no new financial commitment under discussion with TotalEnergies , a day after the French oil major said it was pausing new investments into the Adani Group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/adani-green-energy-says-no-new-financial-commitment-under-discussion-with-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2GVC6LZCNIHDPXX6OT7W4UA24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 04:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian 获得 66 亿美元有条件贷款，以在佐治亚州建设电动汽车工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian 周一表示，该公司已获得美国能源部有条件批准的高达 66 亿美元的贷款，用于在佐治亚州建设这家电动汽车制造商的生产设施。【原文：Rivian said on Monday it has received conditional approval for a loan of up to $6.6 billion from the U.S. Department of Energy to build the electric vehicle maker's production facility in Georgia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-gets-66-bln-conditional-loan-approval-build-georgia-ev-plant-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHKSFPGQMJMQ5BM5VHDNSUWSNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 04:05:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税承诺给汽车和科技公司带来麻烦]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周一承诺对美国的三大贸易伙伴--加拿大、墨西哥和中国--征收关税，详细说明了他将如何履行可能引发贸易战的竞选承诺。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump on Monday pledged tariffs on the United States' three largest trading partners - Canada, Mexico and China - detailing how he will implement campaign promises that could trigger trade wars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/companies-that-might-be-affected-by-trumps-promised-tariffs-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PA2NX2XVVRIDVGIGNVQ6DNOHBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 04:01:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌、Meta 敦促澳大利亚推迟儿童社交媒体禁令法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌和 Facebook 的所有者 Meta Platforms 周二敦促澳大利亚政府推迟一项法案，该法案将禁止 16 岁以下儿童使用大多数形式的社交媒体，并称需要更多时间来评估其潜在影响。【原文：Google and Facebook-owner Meta Platforms urged the Australian government on Tuesday to delay a bill that will ban most forms of social media for children under 16, saying more time was needed to assess its potential impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-meta-urge-australia-delay-bill-social-media-ban-children-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DM2YN7Z3YFNGRDDLVEXFLALJD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:39:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，高通对收购英特尔的兴趣有所降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道，高通公司收购芯片制造商英特尔的兴趣据说已经降温。【原文：Qualcomm's interest in acquiring chipmaker Intel is said to have cooled, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qualcomms-interest-acquiring-intel-has-cooled-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6COFEEOHG5JM3IFMGXAQLKITQ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发出关税威胁后，中国表示 "没有人会赢得贸易战]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要在1月20日上任后对所有中国进口商品征收10%的额外关税后，中国驻华盛顿大使馆周一表示，美国和中国都不会在贸易战中获胜。【原文：Neither the United States nor China would win a trade war, the Chinese Embassy in Washington said on Monday, after U.S. President-elect Donald Trump threatened to slap an additional 10% tariff on all Chinese imports when he takes office on Jan. 20.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/no-one-will-win-trade-war-china-says-after-trump-tariff-threat-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAVB6KVGSJINBNHLGOBJ65UT64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[结束以色列-真主党冲突的潜在协议导致石油下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，油价下滑，延续了上一交易日的跌势，原因是投资者对以色列与真主党之间可能达成的停火进行了评估，从而对石油的风险溢价造成了压力。【原文：Oil prices slipped in early trade on Tuesday, extending declines from the previous session as investors took stock of a potential ceasefire between Israel and Hezbollah, weighing on oil's risk premium.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-falls-potential-deal-end-israel-hezbollah-conflict-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAFMYLFZ4NOZDMNYOUHM62SNKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:41:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贿赂指控后，惠誉将部分阿达尼债券列入负面观察名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[在阿达尼集团（Adani Group）的一些主要高管因贿赂指控被美国当局起诉后，评级机构惠誉（Fitch）已将该公司的部分债券评级列入可能下调的观察名单。【原文：Ratings agency Fitch has put some of Adani Group's bonds on watch for a possible downgrade after some of the firm's key executives were indicted by U.S. authorities on bribery charges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/fitch-places-adani-energy-adani-electricity-mumbai-watch-negative-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7AYFUXDVQNJVHMQBBPZDUPUBYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:24:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普誓言对墨西哥和加拿大征收关税后美元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他将签署一项行政命令，对所有从墨西哥和加拿大进入美国的产品征收25%的关税，此后美元兑主要对手货币周二普遍上涨。【原文：The U.S. dollar rose broadly against major rivals on Tuesday after President-elect Donald Trump said he would sign an executive order imposing a 25% tariff on all products coming in to the United States from Mexico and Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-gains-after-trump-vows-tariffs-against-mexico-canada-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXT6B2ONGNKHVBQOJBFPWQTMCU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:01:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西反垄断机构裁定苹果必须取消应用内支付限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西反垄断监管机构 Cade 周一表示，苹果公司必须取消对应用内购买支付方式等的限制，该监管机构将着手调查拉丁美洲电子商务巨头 MercadoLibre 提起的投诉。【原文：Brazilian antitrust regulator Cade said on Monday that Apple must lift restrictions on payment methods for in-app purchases, among other things, as the watchdog moved to proceed with an investigation into a complaint filed by Latin America e-commerce giant MercadoLibre.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-antitrust-body-rules-apple-must-lift-restrictions-in-app-payments-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFSEGDCH3ZLWZGFHIXIASIYX2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 00:39:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场对特朗普关税誓言的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，在他上任的第一天，他将对来自墨西哥和加拿大的所有产品征收 25% 的关税，并对来自中国的商品额外征收 10% 的关税。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump said on Monday that on his first day in office he would impose a 25% tariff on all products from Mexico and Canada, and an additional 10% tariff on goods from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/markets-react-trumps-tariff-vow-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45WVGD5XJVKZNF3M3WECOIRJ74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 00:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发出关税警告，美元反弹；股市走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁加拿大和墨西哥将对所有进口到美国的商品征收 25% 的关税后，美元兑主要货币汇率周二上涨。【原文：The dollar rose against major peers on Tuesday after U.S. President-elect Donald Trump threatened Canada and Mexico with a 25% tariff on all imports into the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VM55XRB3FIY5HWPKZGNWKDO24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 00:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储卡什卡利：12 月降息 "合理]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周一表示，他对下月再次降息持开放态度。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis President Neel Kashkari, typically on the hawkish end of the U.S. central bank's policy spectrum, said on Monday he is open to cutting interest rates again next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kashkari-interest-rate-cut-december-is-reasonable-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7EXBFAIGNOWDFYQTF43KBIP3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 00:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普承诺对加拿大和墨西哥征收 25% 的关税，对中国征收更高的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他将在上任第一天对来自墨西哥和加拿大的所有产品征收 25% 的关税，并对来自中国的商品额外征收 10% 的关税，理由是对非法移民和非法毒品贸易的担忧。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump said on Monday that on his first day in office he would impose a 25% tariff on all products from Mexico and Canada, and an additional 10% tariff on goods from China, citing concerns over illegal immigration and the trade of illicit drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-promises-25-tariff-products-mexico-canada-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGUK37Y7LBIOJLJY6Y53TRIAXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着 1 月 19 日撤资截止日期的临近，TikTok 即将做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦上诉法院预计将在 12 月 6 日前裁定是否支持要求中国字节跳动公司在明年初之前剥离其在美国的流行短视频应用 TikTok，否则将面临禁令的法律。【原文：A U.S. federal appeals court is expected to rule by Dec. 6 whether to uphold a law requiring Chinese-based ByteDance to divest its popular short video app TikTok in the U.S. by early next year or face a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tiktok-decision-coming-soon-jan-19-divestment-deadline-looms-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXSMP3JGKBKRVM347V5BFFE6O4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国指控前 Wamco 联席首席信息官肯尼思-利奇欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[西部资产管理公司（Western Asset Management Co）前联席首席投资官肯尼思-利奇（Kenneth Leech）周一被美国当局指控实施了一项欺诈性的 "樱桃挑选 "计划，即在分配交易时不适当地偏向一些客户的账户而不是其他客户的账户。【原文：Kenneth Leech, the former co-chief investment officer of Western Asset Management Co, was charged by U.S. authorities on Monday with running a fraudulent "cherry-picking" scheme where he improperly favored some clients' accounts over others when allocating trades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-charges-former-wamco-co-cio-kenneth-leech-with-fraud-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7JSHRS7D25LY5AGZM26LRYLPCQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:24:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>