<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:46:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:46:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：美国不会在 8 月最后期限前匆忙达成贸易协议，将与中国谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一表示，在8月1日达成贸易协议或面临高额关税的最后期限到来之前，特朗普政府更关注贸易协议的质量而非时机。【原文：The Trump administration is more concerned with the quality of trade agreements rather than their timing, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Monday ahead of an Aug. 1 deadline for securing a trade deal or facing steep tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-not-rushing-trade-deals-ahead-august-deadline-will-talk-with-china-bessent-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S256HJS7QVP5JJ32BABN5AAYGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部贝森特说美联储需要作为一个机构接受审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一表示，需要将整个美联储作为一个机构进行审查，看它是否取得了成功。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Monday said the entire Federal Reserve needed to be examined as an institution and whether it had been successful.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasurys-bessent-says-federal-reserve-needs-be-examined-an-institution-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YXLCWG5RFNUJAW34U6D6T55TU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西承认 8 月 1 日前可能无法与美国达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西财政部长周一表示，巴西不会放弃与美国的谈判，但承认可能无法在8月1日前达成协议，届时唐纳德-特朗普总统对巴西商品征收50%关税的规定将生效。【原文：Brazil's finance minister said on Monday that his country will not give up negotiating with the United States, but acknowledged that a deal may not be reached by August 1, when President Donald Trump's 50% tariffs on Brazilian goods are due to take effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-acknowledges-possibility-no-us-trade-deal-by-august-1-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOPNNAJ5XBJHZOSJUSP7L5TBB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:58:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗珀科技公司因软件需求强劲而上调年度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗珀科技公司（Roper Technologies）周一上调了对全年收入和调整后利润的预期，在宏观经济不确定的情况下，寄希望于其庞大的软件产品组合能够恢复企业支出。【原文：Roper Technologies raised its forecasts for annual revenue and adjusted profit on Monday, betting on resilient enterprise spending on its vast portfolio of software products amid macroeconomic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/roper-technologies-raises-annual-forecasts-strong-software-demand-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMTASKNKXVKT7JRI4AMDG2OMDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:43:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制药公司百健将在北卡罗来纳州再投资 20 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）发出关税威胁之际，美国制药商百健（Biogen）周一表示，将对其在北卡罗来纳州的现有生产设施追加投资 20 亿美元，以扩大其在美国的业务。【原文：Biogen will invest an additional $2 billion in its existing manufacturing in North Carolina, the drugmaker said on Monday, as it seeks to expand its presence in the U.S. amid President Donald Trump's tariff threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drugmaker-biogen-invest-2-billion-more-north-carolina-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZK6MJ7FWKNIUHOLVMKFTOYNNAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团称，外国投资者 5 月份购买了近 1000 亿欧元的欧元区债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行（Citi）援引欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）的数据称，5 月份欧元区债券从集团外部获得了近 1,000 亿欧元（合 1,164 亿美元）的买盘，这是欧元资产受益于从美国市场转移的最新迹象。【原文：Euro zone bonds saw nearly 100 billion euros ($116.4 billion) of buying from outside the bloc in May, Citi said citing European Central Bank data, the latest sign that euro assets are benefitting from a shift away from U.S. markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/foreign-investors-buy-nearly-100-bln-euros-euro-zone-bonds-may-citi-says-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQIWZXVX4BLTRBQ47UQXXQLYSQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:38:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩洛哥央行探索数字货币跨境支付]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩洛哥央行行长阿卜杜拉蒂夫-朱阿里（Abdellatif Jouahri）周一表示，摩洛哥央行正在探索使用自己的数字货币进行点对点和跨境支付。【原文：Morocco's central bank was exploring the use of its own digital currency for peer-to-peer and cross border payments, bank governor Abdellatif Jouahri said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/moroccos-central-bank-explores-digital-currency-cross-border-payments-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMGV7IDKARIULF367TPXC23KRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:27:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Verizon因高端计划需求而上调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Verizon 周一上调了其年度利润预期的下限，原因是对其高级计划的强劲需求推动了第二季度盈利好于预期。【原文：Verizon raised the lower end of its annual profit forecast on Monday, as strong demand for its higher-tier plans powered better-than-expected earnings in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/verizon-boosts-annual-profit-forecast-demand-premium-plans-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47FN3FQOTJKCLIRHG5L2PY6EUE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价日本首相坚守岗位，日元反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6L7WWR5JZNPTRL7324T3SNBP2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:47:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在波音公司做出保证后，瑞安航空决定不改变 MAX 10 订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空公司首席执行官迈克尔-奥利里（Michael O'Leary）周一表示，在得到波音公司关于MAX 10飞机将按时交付的保证后，瑞安决定不将定于2027年初交付的MAX 10飞机换成较小的MAX 8飞机。【原文：Ryanair has decided not to switch MAX 10 aircraft due for delivery in early 2027 to the smaller MAX 8 aircraft following reassurances from Boeing that they will arrive on time, Chief Executive Michael O'Leary said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ryanair-decides-against-switching-max-10-order-after-boeing-offers-reassurances-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2GWCE6W25MYDFUM54NLPLXSRQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[商业游说团体称美国关税可能使意大利损失高达 0.8% 的 GDP]]></title><description><![CDATA[在跨大西洋贸易谈判继续进行之际，意大利主要的商业游说团体周一表示，美国对欧盟商品征收30%的关税可能会使意大利2027年的国内生产总值减少0.8%。【原文：U.S. tariffs of 30% on European Union goods could shave up to 0.8% off Italy's gross domestic product in 2027, the country's main business lobby said on Monday, as transatlantic trade negotiations continued.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-tariffs-could-cost-italy-up-08-gdp-business-lobby-says-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6O76P3TRHZLUBDXIFMBMGOGJLE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:43:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Figma 目标估值 137 亿美元，科技公司 IPO 反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[Figma 在美国首次公开募股的目标估值为 136.5 亿美元，这家基于云计算的设计软件公司正在为首次公开募股做准备，这可能会为已经恢复生机的科技上市市场注入新的动力。【原文：Figma is targeting a valuation of $13.65 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, as the cloud-based design software firm prepares for a debut that could inject fresh momentum into a tech listings market already roaring back to life.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/figma-aims-137-billion-valuation-tech-ipos-bounce-back-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJLXT7JA6NP7FJFMWYQPVEKAJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税协议前景黯淡，欧盟将加强报复计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据欧盟外交官称，随着与华盛顿达成一项可接受的贸易协定的前景逐渐暗淡，欧盟正在探索一套更广泛的针对美国的可能反制措施。【原文：The European Union is exploring a broader set of possible counter-measures against the United States as prospects for an acceptable trade agreement with Washington fade, according to EU diplomats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-ramp-up-retaliation-plans-us-tariff-deal-prospects-dim-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWI2DTTTDNINBGUN4XAPMP4VMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货因贸易希望而上涨；财报进入高潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国与其主要合作伙伴之间达成贸易协议的前景提振，华尔街期货周一走高，同时财报季步伐加快，多家工业和科技公司将于本周发布财报。【原文：Wall Street futures edged higher on Monday, buoyed by prospects of trade deals between the U.S. and its key partners, while the earnings season picked up pace with several industrial and tech firms set to report this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-rise-trade-hope-earnings-kick-into-high-gear-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44JI36RGA5KYFAOZVSJMCJPZEM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:28:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳入标准普尔 500 指数后区块链跃升，成为金融科技领域的新里程碑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在支付公司被纳入基准 S&amp;P 500 指数后，由亿万富翁杰克-多西（Jack Dorsey）领导的 Block 公司的股价在周一收盘前上涨了近 10%，这标志着金融科技领域的一个里程碑。【原文：Tech billionaire Jack Dorsey-led Block's shares rose nearly 10% before the bell on Monday after the payments firm was added to the benchmark S&amp;P 500 , marking a milestone for the fintech sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/block-jumps-after-sp-500-inclusion-new-milestone-fintech-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABVJLRBD5ZPFXECLH4IZXMRDCY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一家美国吉他弦制造商应对贸易战的战略内幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[当美国各地的公司都在想方设法应对特朗普的贸易战时，D'Addario & Co. 公司的高管们正在建立一个自由贸易区，并改变货运路线以避免关税。【原文：As companies all over the U.S. seek ways to cope with Trump's trade war, D'Addario & Co. executives are setting up a free trade zone and rerouting shipments to avoid tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/inside-us-guitar-string-makers-strategy-navigate-trade-war-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B26JHASIZ5I7ZLFFAP76YH6SYI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由加密货币巨头支持的以太币机器将在纳斯达克首次亮相，融资超过 16 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[以太币储备公司（The Ether Reserve）是一家由知名加密投资者支持的新加密企业，将通过与空白支票公司 Dynamix Corporation 合并的方式在纳斯达克上市，预计将筹集超过 16 亿美元的资金。【原文：The Ether Reserve, a new crypto venture backed by prominent crypto investors, will list on the Nasdaq through a merger with blank-check firm Dynamix Corporation and is expected to raise over $1.6 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ether-machine-backed-by-crypto-giants-set-raise-over-16-billion-nasdaq-debut-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OA27K672OBI5FKQW7TFVJAH3AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国需求强劲，多米诺餐厅季度销售额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在宏观经济不确定性持续存在的情况下，多米诺比萨周一在菜单上推出新产品和促销活动的推动下，第二季度美国同店销售额超出分析师预期，股价在盘前交易中上涨近 5%。【原文：Domino's Pizza surpassed analysts' expectations for second-quarter U.S. same-store sales on Monday, driven by new items on the menu and promotions, amid persisting macroeconomic uncertainties, sending shares up nearly 5% in premarket trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dominos-beats-quarterly-sales-estimate-strong-us-demand-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JT6ECIBGKBOQDIIJOZ3ZDR7B5Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国住宅建筑商在成本上升和关税不确定的情况下进入 2025 年下半年]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着季度财报的临近，美国住宅建筑商正面临着一些不利因素，包括建筑材料成本上升、利率居高不下，以及对唐纳德-特朗普总统提出的大规模驱逐措施可能对建筑业造成重大影响的担忧。【原文：U.S. homebuilders are navigating several headwinds as they approach quarterly earnings reports, including rising costs of construction materials, persistently high interest rates, and concerns that President Donald Trump’s proposed mass deportation efforts could significantly impact the construction industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-homebuilders-head-into-back-half-2025-with-rising-costs-tariff-uncertainty-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXSXGRP7HNLJJAZQQ5KZYKXQGM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 投资者与扎克伯格的和解让特拉华州不再受热捧]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，Meta Platforms 股东与公司领导层在最后一刻达成和解，结束了一场耗资 80 亿美元的诉讼，马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）也免于就 Facebook 用户数据被侵犯的指控出庭作证。这也让一直饱受科技和商界领袖批评的特拉华州消了气。【原文：A last-minute settlement between Meta Platforms shareholders and the company's leadership last week ended an $8 billion trial and spared Mark Zuckerberg from testifying about alleged violations of Facebook users' data. It also took the heat off the state of Delaware, which has been plagued by criticism from technology and business leaders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-investors-settlement-with-zuckerberg-takes-heat-off-delaware-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEFIQV5I45OPPEYV4TLV7FB4E4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡夫亨氏撤销 2015 年大型合并，寻求重振老品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡夫亨氏可能剥离增长较慢的品牌（如 Velveeta 奶酪），这是一次冒险的最后努力，目的是通过扭转十年前并购失败的局面来提高收益。【原文：Kraft Heinz's potential spinoff of slower-growing brands such as Velveeta cheese is a risky last-ditch effort to boost returns by reversing its unsuccessful decade-old merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/kraft-heinz-seeks-revive-old-brands-by-undoing-2015-mega-merger-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIOI7XB3TBKKLLBBRRSGSLRIOA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NHTSA结束对454,840辆日产汽车发动机故障的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周一表示，在日本汽车制造商于6月发布召回计划后，该局正在结束对454840辆日产汽车发动机故障的初步评估。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Monday that it is closing a preliminary evaluation into 454,840 Nissan vehicles over engine failure after the Japanese automaker issued a recall in June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-closes-engine-failure-probe-into-454840-nissan-vehicles-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z35O4BRR4BNTFEFJAO4PG5SD3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:50:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署稳定币法律后，加密货币相关股票上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普签署了一项监管美国稳定币的法案，该法案生效后，以太坊价格上涨，与加密货币相关的公司股价周一跳涨。【原文：Shares of crypto-linked companies jumped on Monday, as ether prices advanced after President Donald Trump signed into law a bill regulating stablecoins in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/crypto-linked-stocks-advance-after-trump-signs-stablecoin-law-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THJBBCNEARNFXNIRZVHF7RXX6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:42:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 X 公司否认法国关于欺诈性数据提取和算法滥用的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体平台 X 周一表示，它否认法国当局对其算法操纵和 "欺诈性数据提取 "的所有指控，并补充说，它没有同意法国刑事调查提出的要求。【原文：Elon Musk's social media platform X said on Monday it denied all allegations made by French authorities over manipulation of its algorithm and "fraudulent data extraction," adding that it has not acceded to the demands made in a French criminal investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/musks-x-denies-french-allegations-fraudulent-data-extraction-algorithm-abuse-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YUM3YGJKJILVN6ZA3IEF5L67E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:53:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SS&C 将以约 10 亿美元收购凯雷旗下英国基金网络 Calastone]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融软件供应商 SS&amp;C Technologies 周一表示，将以约 7.66 亿英镑（10.3 亿美元）的价格收购凯雷旗下的英国基金网络和数据业务 Calastone。【原文：Financial software provider SS&amp;C Technologies said on Monday it will acquire Carlyle's British fund network and data business Calastone for about 766 million pounds ($1.03 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ssc-buy-carlyles-british-fund-network-calastone-about-1-billion-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5ZGCEEH5BOWLKNWMSJ47DRGYI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济增长和外国对收益的狂热为日本财政提供了回旋余地]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本周末举行的大选使世界上负债最多的发达国家扩大政府开支和赤字的前景成为现实，尽管目前外国投资者和不断增长的经济可能使其债券收益率不会大幅飙升。【原文：A weekend election in Japan has made real the prospect of bigger government spending and deficits in the world's most indebted developed nation, although for now foreign investors and a growing economy could keep its bond yields from spiking sharply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/growth-foreign-fervour-yield-give-japan-fiscal-wiggle-room-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUCVB2XSOVMXVDDZ7NGJF35DWE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称富国银行被禁止出境的银行家涉及刑事案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国外交部周一表示，被禁止出境的富国银行银行家毛晨岳涉及刑事案件，有义务配合调查。【原文：China's foreign ministry said on Monday that Chenyue Mao, the Wells Fargo banker who has been blocked from leaving the country, was involved in a criminal case and obliged to cooperate with the investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/china-says-wells-fargo-banker-under-exit-ban-is-involved-criminal-case-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DHANMVSDVIH7J7X2KVMRXS7DY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:34:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港调查路易威登数据泄露事件，41.9万人受影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港私隐监察机构周一表示，它正在调查路易威登的数据泄露事件，该事件影响到约41.9万名客户。【原文：Hong Kong's privacy watchdog said on Monday that it was investigating a data leak at Louis Vuitton affecting about 419,000 customers, just after a cyberattack on the luxury brand in South Korea in June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hong-kong-investigates-louis-vuitton-data-leak-that-affected-419000-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZNR3DBPVFOMRIWLLLZJRN3V74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将帮助法国展示巴黎圣母院的数字复制品]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司总裁布拉德-史密斯（Brad Smith）周一表示，微软正在与法国政府合作，为法国游客最多的古迹--巴黎圣母院大教堂制作一个数字复制品。【原文：Microsoft is teaming up with the French government to create a digital replica of Paris' Notre-Dame Cathedral, France's most visited monument, the U.S. tech company's president, Brad Smith, said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-help-france-showcase-paris-notre-dame-cathedral-digital-replica-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ABIKKEUBROMREH6C46KEI6QMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:52:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，汽车制造商 Stellantis 半年净亏损 26.8 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商斯泰兰特周一表示，预计 2025 年上半年将净亏损 23 亿欧元（26.8 亿美元）。【原文：Automaker Stellantis expects a net loss of 2.3 billion euros ($2.68 billion) for the first half of 2025, it said on Monday, as it forecast an initial hit of 0.3 billion euros from U.S. import tariffs on its half-year results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carmaker-stellantis-sees-half-year-net-loss-268-billion-hit-by-tariffs-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XS5RXGAGVJLHFOSRMQNX2KQCJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>