<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:05:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:05:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称星座公司正与宾夕法尼亚州商谈三哩岛重启事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，三位熟悉讨论情况的消息人士称，星座能源公司正在与宾夕法尼亚州州长办公室和州立法者进行谈判，以帮助资助其三里岛核电站（上世纪 70 年代的核泄漏事故发生地）部分设施的可能重启。【原文：Constellation Energy is in talks with the Pennsylvania governor's office and state lawmakers to help fund a possible restart of part of its Three Mile Island power facility, the site of a nuclear meltdown in the 1970s, three sources familiar with the discussions said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/constellation-talking-pennsylvania-three-mile-island-restart-sources-say-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFJYOHHSSVPVPJQVWKSVP4ZAWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：为股市反弹奠定基础，服务业采购经理人指数即将公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SKZG6UN2JMZVD3JXFQDYVBLY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:47:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院官员的代表报告称，在 Citgo 母公司的拍卖中出现了多次竞标]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责监督出售过程的法院官员代表周二表示，炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份的第二轮竞标 "很成功"，美国联邦法院上个月收到了几份有竞争力的竞标。【原文：The second bidding round for shares in refiner Citgo Petroleum's parent was "successful," with several competitive bids received last month by a U.S. federal court, a representative of the court officer overseeing the sale process said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/court-officers-rep-reports-several-competitive-bids-auction-citgo-parent-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPGVJUYHZROYREXYM7NLYN6RJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，人工智能编码初创公司 Magic 在新一轮融资中寻求 15 亿美元的估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士告诉路透社，美国一家开发人工智能模型编写软件的初创公司Magic正在洽谈一轮超过2亿美元的融资，估值达15亿美元，这距离它上一次融资仅过去了几个月。【原文：Magic, a U.S. startup developing artificial-intelligence models to write software, is in talks to raise over $200 million in a funding round valuing it at $1.5 billion, just several months after its last capital raise, three sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-coding-startup-magic-seeks-15-billion-valuation-new-funding-round-sources-say-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUOWA5OC4NLMTGS7YEEZ3WLXPI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称埃克森-赫斯仲裁小组即将成立]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，埃克森美孚针对雪佛龙公司以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司的索赔案成立了一个三人仲裁小组，该小组的最后一名成员已经选定。【原文：The final member has been chosen for a three-person arbitration panel meant to settle Exxon Mobil's claim against Chevron's $53 billion purchase of Hess Corp , two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/exxon-hess-arbitration-panel-nears-formation-sources-say-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVV6MWOYGVNS7EWV45XNLPPIDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:12:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，作为人工智能协议的一部分，苹果公司有望获得 OpenAI 董事会观察员的职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，作为上个月宣布的具有里程碑意义的人工智能协议的一部分，苹果公司将在 OpenAI 董事会中担任观察员。【原文：Apple will get an observer role on OpenAI's board as part of a landmark AI agreement announced last month, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/apple-poised-get-openai-board-observer-role-part-ai-pact-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZGKZJPXJVNJBNLXKH7POMQIYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Rivian 否认与大众汽车进行生产谈判的媒体报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二有媒体报道称，美国电动汽车公司正在与大众汽车公司进行早期谈判，以扩大双方在最近宣布的软件合资企业之外的合作关系，Rivian否认了这一报道。【原文：Rivian denied a media report on Tuesday that said the U.S. electric vehicle company was in early talks with Volkswagen to extend their partnership beyond a recently announced software joint venture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-denies-media-report-production-talks-with-vw-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVF7DULEBBMFJCR43CEMGEFMBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:37:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果前律师因内幕交易被美国证券交易委员会罚款 115 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二裁定，苹果公司前高级律师在承认内幕交易罪后避免了牢狱之灾，他必须在美国证券交易委员会的相关民事案件中支付 115 万美元的罚款。【原文：The former senior Apple lawyer who avoided prison time after pleading guilty to insider trading must pay a $1.15 million fine in a related U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission civil case, a federal judge ruled on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/apple-ex-lawyer-ordered-pay-115-million-sec-fine-insider-trading-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIAXPJYB4FIUVNALE6KVSC6SZ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:13:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特通过新的租赁政策敦促其经理购买更多电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社查阅的福特汽车公司上周发送的一封内部邮件，福特汽车公司正试图让更多的经理人购买电动汽车。【原文：Ford Motor is trying to get more of its managers to buy electric vehicles, according to an internal email the automaker sent last week that was reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-urges-its-managers-buy-more-evs-with-new-leasing-policy-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3O4PP6255KJ7K3LVLOCBRID7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《财富》杂志报道，沃尔玛已就出售其关闭的医疗诊所进行了谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《财富》周二援引多位熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道，沃尔玛已与潜在买家就出售已关闭的医疗诊所进行了谈判。【原文：Walmart has held talks with potential buyers to sell its already shuttered medical clinics, Fortune reported on Tuesday, citing multiple sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/walmart-has-held-talks-sell-its-shuttered-medical-clinics-fortune-reports-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TA7DV7BDIRLIFEW4SD24XFSRVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:58:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，Vista Equity 正在商谈将 Pluralsight 移交债权人事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉此事的人士和路透社查阅的基金文件显示，私募股权公司 Vista Equity 正在商谈将其公司 Pluralsight 的控制权让给贷款人。【原文：Private equity firm Vista Equity is in talks to cede control of its company Pluralsight to lenders, according to three people familiar with the matter and fund documents reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/vista-equity-talks-hand-over-pluralsight-creditors-sources-say-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6Q2PWUMRJJMQ3LO2WMY6ZPMZOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准礼来公司的阿尔茨海默氏症药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周二为礼来公司用于治疗早期阿尔茨海默病患者的多那尼单抗开了绿灯，使其成为第二种获准用于延缓这种脑损伤疾病进展的药物。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration on Tuesday gave a green light to Eli Lilly's donanemab for patients with early Alzheimer's, making it the second approved drug for slowing the progress of the brain-wasting disease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-lillys-alzheimers-drug-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4ZAB7QQEFJGJGKB34KV5JYDAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:55:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Progressive 将支付 4,800 万美元，以了结低估失事汽车价值的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[Progressive 同意支付 4800 万美元，以了结一项集体诉讼，该诉讼指控该保险公司系统性地低估了车辆失事的纽约司机的索赔金额。【原文：Progressive agreed to pay $48 million to settle a class action lawsuit accusing the insurer of systematically undervaluing the claims of New York drivers whose vehicles were wrecked.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/progressive-pay-48-million-settle-claims-it-undervalued-wrecked-cars-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XX53ZCTN55ORPH6KEFMQ27KGJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，伊坎旗下炼油企业 CVR 正在参与 Citgo 股份竞拍]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉内情的人士透露，由亿万富翁投资者卡尔-伊坎（Carl Icahn）控制的炼油企业 CVR Energy 已在委内瑞拉 Citgo Petroleum 母公司正在进行的股份拍卖中提交了一份具有约束力的报价。【原文：Oil refiner CVR Energy , controlled by billionaire investor Carl Icahn, has submitted a binding offer in an ongoing auction of shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned Citgo Petroleum, according to three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/icahn-owned-oil-refiner-cvr-bidding-citgo-share-auction-sources-say-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QJOUCZL5JPKLHOEPCYVTACKSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[开发银行因气候条款和混合债券获得评级提升]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉（Fitch）周二表示，冻结受气候灾害影响国家的债务偿付不会影响这些银行的信用评级，而且将不再对新的 "混合 "债券设定评级上限，世界银行和其他顶级开发银行因此获得双重激励。【原文：The World Bank and other top development banks got a double boost on Tuesday as Fitch said debt payment freezes for climate-disaster hit countries would not hit the banks' credit rating and it would no longer cap ratings on new 'hybrid' bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/development-banks-get-ratings-boost-climate-clauses-hybrid-bonds-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFZEY44XS5M3POWQ5GYDMFV54Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储银行监督权在法院诉讼后变得更加不确定]]></title><description><![CDATA[最高法院的一宗案件颠覆了政府监管机构的工作方式，将美联储银行监管者推入了更大的不确定性和潜在风险之中，尽管这一裁决不应使央行在压力时期为市场提供支持的能力复杂化。【原文：A Supreme Court case upending how government regulators do their work thrusts Federal Reserve bank overseers into extended uncertainty and potential risk, although the ruling should not complicate the central bank’s ability to provide support to markets in times of stress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/fed-bank-oversight-powers-grow-more-uncertain-wake-court-action-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCDV5R4JVNISDH4WO6LLDLLULM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将阻止 Tempur Sealy 40 亿美元的床垫公司交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周二表示，它将提起诉讼，阻止床垫制造商 Tempur Sealy International Inc 与零售商 Mattress Firm 之间价值 40 亿美元的合并。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Tuesday it will sue to block the $4 billion merger between mattress manufacturer Tempur Sealy International Inc and retailer Mattress Firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-block-tempur-sealys-4-billion-mattress-firm-deal-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBHD5FTTIFNLVBUWEAQC3EP5QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国隔夜融资利率创一月以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储周二公布的数据显示，衡量美国回购协议（repo）市场中银行与其他参与者之间贷款借贷成本的指标周一创下了自一月份以来的最高水平。【原文：A measure of the borrowing costs on loans between banks and other participants in the U.S. repurchase agreement (repo) market hit its highest level since January on Monday, New York Federal Reserve data released on Tuesday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-overnight-funding-rate-hits-highest-since-january-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X54YGXJHINOGNMCWGHV5GALWRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:34:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官的金融冲突导致针对大银行的诉讼重启]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国上诉法院驳回了一起指控 10 家大银行向投资者多收公司债券费用的反垄断诉讼，称初审法官本应回避，因为他的妻子拥有其中一家银行的股票。【原文：A U.S. appeals court threw out the dismissal of an antitrust lawsuit accusing 10 large banks of overcharging investors on corporate bonds, saying the trial judge should have been recused because his wife owned stock in one of the banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judges-financial-conflict-leads-revived-lawsuit-against-big-banks-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZU6OBPSYBP6JLN3CTYFLM52CM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:59:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田第二季度美国汽车销量因 SUV 需求增长 9]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车北美分公司周二公布，受经济型和高端跨界 SUV 需求的推动，第二季度美国汽车销量增长约 9.2%。【原文：Toyota Motor North America posted an about 9.2% rise in second-quarter U.S. auto sales on Tuesday, aided by demand for its affordable and premium crossover SUVs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyotas-q2-us-auto-sales-up-9-suv-demand-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HT7OFLB5NNO2TDC2TASMBRQTFE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:40:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比认为实体经济出现警告信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周二表示，他看到了一些经济疲软的 "警示信号"，并补充说，美国中央银行的目标是在不给劳动力市场造成压力的情况下降低通胀。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee on Tuesday said he sees some "warning signs" of weakening in the economy, adding that the U.S. central bank's goal is to get inflation down without stressing the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-sees-warnings-signs-real-economy-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDI4FLG22RIZTKMYS53EGXVFIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:31:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，Robinhood 考虑在美国和欧洲提供加密货币期货]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道称，Robinhood Markets 正在考虑未来几个月在美国和欧洲推出加密货币期货。【原文：Robinhood Markets is considering offering cryptocurrency futures in the U.S. and Europe in the coming months, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/robinhood-considering-offering-crypto-futures-us-europe-bloomberg-reports-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7W52LEHPCNOWPAB67L6W4NO73U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车第二季度美国汽车销量增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司周二公布，第二季度美国汽车销量增长放缓，原因是面向日租公司的车队销量下降，以及 CDK 公司发生的网络事件影响了全国各地的经销商。【原文：General Motors on Tuesday posted a slower rise in second-quarter U.S. sales, hurt by lower fleet sales to daily rental companies and a cyber incident at CDK that impacted dealers across the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gms-second-quarter-us-auto-sales-growth-slows-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45ITI3WJLNLLVLWH7Y6RLM5LN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:03:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦敦证券交易所集团宣布与道琼斯建立多年新闻和数据合作伙伴关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦证券交易所集团（London Stock Exchange Group）与道琼斯公司（Dow Jones）周二宣布，双方将建立多年的新闻和数据合作关系，其中将包括《华尔街日报》的内容。【原文：The London Stock Exchange Group announced a multi-year news and data partnership with Dow Jones that will include content from the Wall Street Journal, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/lseg-announces-multi-year-news-data-partnership-with-dow-jones-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27T7CSSUIRJOVIBEE7EMN6F6QA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:44:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国工作场所安全机构建议保护人们免受极端高温伤害]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周二公布了一项期待已久的提案，要求美国许多雇主保护 3600 万工人免受极端高温的影响。【原文：The Biden administration on Tuesday unveiled a long-awaited proposal that would require many U.S. employers to protect 36 million workers from extreme heat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-workplace-safety-agency-proposes-protections-extreme-heat-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CHUQZKB7VP6BPV2QXYKWTJHDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:33:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月职位空缺增加；裁员人数上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 5 月份的职位空缺在前两个月出现大幅下降后有所增长，但在经济活动放缓的情况下，裁员人数有所增加。【原文：U.S. job openings increased in May after posting outsized declines in the prior two months, but layoffs picked up amid slowing economic activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-increase-may-layoffs-rise-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C33K7YPBPRL47IMMNIEAAKCMKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国阻止 Tempur Sealy 40 亿美元收购零售商 Mattress Firm]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士周二透露，美国联邦贸易委员会正准备提起诉讼，阻止床垫制造商 Tempur Sealy International Inc 与零售商 Mattress Firm 之间价值 40 亿美元的合并。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is preparing to sue to block the $4 billion merger between mattress manufacturer Tempur Sealy International Inc and retailer Mattress Firm, a source familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-block-tempur-sealys-4-bln-buy-retailer-mattress-firm-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QT3VXX2SSJLWDEFPR5ID4E2ZAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔称美联储在降息前需要更多通胀下降的证据]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周二表示，美国央行在降息前仍需要更多数据，以确保近期疲软的通胀读数能够真实反映潜在的价格压力。【原文：The U.S. central bank still needs more data before cutting interest rates to ensure that recent weaker inflation readings give a true picture of what is happening to underlying price pressures, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-says-more-evidence-falling-inflation-needed-before-rate-cuts-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QANNF66U5ZOHLGAWJFKQU62W3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:01:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回对工作场所安全机构的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周二拒绝审理俄亥俄州一家公司对联邦工作场所安全监管机构的权力提出的质疑，因为大法官们避免了另一项削减联邦机构权力的法律努力。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Tuesday to hear a challenge by an Ohio company to the power of the federal workplace safety regulator as the justices avoided another legal effort to pare back the authority of federal agencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-rejects-challenge-workplace-safety-agency-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACEREDEUFZMHPMINJT5NABSNDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:59:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将六家公司列入贸易限制名单，其中四家培训中国军队]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国政府发布的公告，美国周二将六家公司列入贸易限制名单，其中四家公司与中国军队的训练有关。【原文：The United States added six companies to its trade restriction list on Tuesday, including four for their links to the training of China's military forces, according to a government posting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-adds-six-companies-trade-restriction-list-four-training-chinas-military-2024-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDVK37WC6ZNZRJWOBTJS5SB6UA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>