<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:17:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:17:25 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官：中国钢铁产量停滞不前，淡水河谷正准备满足印度需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷首席执行官古斯塔沃-皮门塔（Gustavo Pimenta）告诉路透社记者，淡水河谷正准备满足印度不断增长的铁矿石需求，到本十年末，印度的钢铁产量将翻一番。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale is preparing to meet rising iron ore demand from India, which could double its steel production by the end of the decade, Chief Executive Gustavo Pimenta told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/vale-gearing-up-meet-indian-demand-china-steel-output-stagnates-ceo-says-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXWJYAADFJKEJB2QX2IT42GJCI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:04:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡 Grab 将向远程驾驶公司 Vay 投资 6000 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡公司 Grab Holdings 周一表示，将向远程驾驶公司 Vay Technology 投资 6000 万美元，使其股价在盘前交易中上涨超过 6%。【原文：Grab Holdings will invest $60 million in remote driving firm Vay Technology, the Singaporean firm said on Monday, sending its shares up more than 6% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/singapores-grab-invest-60-million-remote-driving-firm-vay-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBKZWTNFFROITHFNHQQSD2KKNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通警告称，零售业连创新高后反弹动力不足]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（J.P. Morgan）分析师在一份报告中写道，在经历了近年来最长的连涨之后，散户投资者正在缩减他们的风险押注，这标志着情绪的转变，可能会削弱美股高歌猛进的势头。【原文：Retail investors are dialing back their risky bets after the longest bullish streak in recent years, J.P. Morgan analysts wrote in a note, marking a shift in sentiment that could sap momentum in high‑flying U.S. stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retail-rally-running-out-steam-after-record-streak-jp-morgan-warns-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIZDLOVJY5MDLE5DZ7IOBISALA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:44:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢克石油公司的国际资产面临美国制裁的干扰]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯第二大石油生产商卢克石油公司（Lukoil）在美国制裁和华盛顿拒绝批准将其海外资产出售给瑞士大宗商品贸易商贡渥集团（Gunvor）之后，其国际业务正面临着日益严重的中断。【原文：Russia's second-largest oil producer, Lukoil , is facing growing disruptions to its international operations following U.S. sanctions and Washington's refusal to approve the sale of its overseas assets to Swiss commodity trader Gunvor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/lukoil-international-assets-facing-disruptions-us-sanctions-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K22SOEJ5IFPENJZXPWQTB4CPZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品公司预测鸡肉需求抵消牛肉困境，全年收入将增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）周一预计全年营收将高于分析师预期，该公司押注鸡肉产品的需求将抵消牛肉业务的疲软。【原文：Tyson Foods on Monday forecast annual revenue above analysts' estimates, betting on demand for chicken products to offset weaknesses in its beef business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tyson-foods-forecasts-annual-revenue-rise-chicken-demand-offsets-beef-woes-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O453UARRERO7TH3XTOWZRNLMT4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银将标普 500 指数 2026 年年末目标定为 7500 点，因人工智能驱动反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银全球研究公司（UBS Global Research）周一表示，华尔街由人工智能驱动的涨势将延续到2026年，该券商将S&amp;P 500指数明年的年终目标定为7500点，押注于强劲的企业盈利和集中但有弹性的科技行业的收益。【原文：Wall Street's artificial intelligence-driven rally will extend into 2026, UBS Global Research said on Monday, as the brokerage set the S&amp;P 500 index's year-end target for next year at 7,500, betting on strong corporate earnings and gains in a concentrated but resilient technology sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-sets-sp-500s-2026-year-end-target-7500-ai-driven-rally-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORVTVUEUPNJW5LCVFJQQNXOMPQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易平台 eToro 盈利超预期，散户投资者搭上市场繁荣快车]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，股票和加密货币交易平台 eToro 的第三季度利润超出预期，尽管存在泡沫担忧，但散户投资者仍保持买入势头，使股价在收盘前上涨了 8%。【原文：Stock and crypto trading platform eToro beat estimates for third-quarter profit on Monday as retail investors maintained their buying streak despite bubble worries, sending shares up 8% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trading-platform-etoro-beats-profit-estimates-retail-investors-ride-market-boom-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUXGDSPUNRKFJMRJECTWKYKEBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:21:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税和全球挤压影响，美国铝溢价创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[受陡峭的进口关税和全球供应紧张的影响，消费者在美国实物市场上购买铝的溢价已创下历史新高。【原文：Premiums for consumers buying aluminium on the physical market in the U.S. have hit record highs, driven by steep import tariffs and tight supplies globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/aluminium-premium-hits-record-us-tariffs-global-squeeze-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67AYPYKWERIO5BPRTV5BUIRY7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：重开反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPRS25NRDFJ37EUAQ2MBU3L7GU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tsavorite 用于扩展工作流程的人工智能芯片获得超过 1 亿美元的预购订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Tsavorite Scalable Intelligence周一表示，它已从美国、亚洲和欧洲的企业和云提供商那里获得了超过1亿美元的预购订单，以部署其用于扩展人工智能工作负载的芯片。【原文：AI startup Tsavorite Scalable Intelligence said on Monday it has secured more than $100 million in pre-orders from enterprises and cloud providers across United States, Asia and Europe to deploy its chips, which are used to scale AI workloads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsavorite-secures-more-than-100-million-pre-orders-ai-chips-scale-workflows-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKJHNABCXFJC5IZJ3XWFHXWSXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》报道，OpenAI 在推动核心人工智能产品之外，还考虑开发消费者健康工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》周一援引接近该公司的消息人士的话报道，OpenAI 正在权衡打造消费者健康产品，包括一款生成式人工智能个人健康助理，因为这家 ChatGPT 制造商的目标是超越其核心产品。【原文：OpenAI is weighing building consumer health products, including a generative AI-powered personal health assistant, as the ChatGPT maker aims to move beyond its core offerings, Business Insider reported on Monday, citing sources close to the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/openai-considers-consumer-health-tools-push-beyond-core-ai-offerings-business-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KF5RHF466RKPBH5WAF3YKU3Q4I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:54:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛数据显示，基金将消费类股票降至全球大流行病低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周一看到的一份高盛公司（Goldman Sachs）的报告显示，上周对冲基金对经济的乐观情绪有所减弱，他们对酒店和餐馆等依赖消费者消费能力的公司的投资降至五年来的最低点。【原文：Hedge funds' economic optimism faded last week and their exposure to companies that depend on consumer spending power such as hotels and restaurants fell to five-year lows, according to a Goldman Sachs note seen by Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hedge-flow-funds-cut-consumer-stocks-global-pandemic-lows-goldman-data-shows-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5HYZLYWWNIVLNIK4HD3XUKZBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求不振，特斯拉中国销量跌至三年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，特斯拉在中国的销量降至 26,006 辆，创下三年来的最低水平，这家美国电动汽车制造商正努力应对这个竞争激烈的市场不温不火的需求。【原文：Tesla's sales in China dropped to 26,006 vehicles in October, their lowest in three years, as the U.S. electric vehicle maker struggles with tepid demand in the hyper-competitive market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-china-sales-fall-3-year-low-amid-tepid-demand-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7GM6LDTNJP3ZGRIMXQKUQVX2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利表示，决策者需要对进一步缩减开支保持开放心态]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联储主席玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周一表示，美国薪资增长放缓的原因可能更多是由于工人需求减弱，而非移民政策收紧导致劳动力减少。【原文：Slowing payroll growth in the U.S. is likely due more to weaker demand for workers than the drop in the labor force from tightened immigration policy, an important distinction in the U.S. Federal Reserve's debate about further interest rate cuts, San Francisco Fed President Mary Daly said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-says-policymakers-need-keep-an-open-mind-about-further-cuts-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTFTNFP7HNOMTK5VRGYCYJRXRQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:08:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴里克上调股息，扩大回购范围，因金价创新高而利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴里克矿业公司（Barrick Mining）周一上调了股息，并扩大了股票回购计划，此前该公司的季度调整后利润超出预期，原因是金价上涨帮助抵消了产量的下降。【原文：Barrick Mining on Monday raised its dividend and expanded its share buyback program, after beating quarterly adjusted profit estimates as stronger gold prices helped offset a decline in production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/barrick-mining-beats-estimates-third-quarter-profit-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AN23YP4SQVN7BK5ONNCXHSWKSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 以 22 亿美元将航空零部件公司 Novaria Group 出售给 Arcline]]></title><description><![CDATA[KKR 公司和卖方周一告诉路透社，KKR 已达成一项协议，以 22 亿美元的价格将航空航天和国防硬件制造商 Novaria 集团出售给以工业为重点的私募股权公司 Arcline Investment Management。【原文：KKR has struck a deal to sell aerospace and defense hardware maker Novaria Group to industrials-focused private equity firm Arcline Investment Management for $2.2 billion, the company and the seller told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/kkr-sells-aerospace-parts-firm-novaria-group-arcline-22-billion-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGSKJYYP4BJDZEE6F4D3MZPXVY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[资金谈判仍在继续，美国参议员就反对维修权问题向国防工业提出挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）在众议院和参议院谈判人员努力敲定 2026 财年《国防授权法案》之际，不断向国防工业施压，要求他们停止反对军事维修权立法。【原文：Democratic U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren is escalating pressure on the defense industry to stop opposing military right-to-repair legislation, as House and Senate negotiators work to finalize the fiscal 2026 National Defense Authorization Act.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senator-challenges-defense-industry-right-to-repair-opposition-funding-talks-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYQR5QKMUZJE5LFQOC6GFOJXEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙投资者日聚焦后赫斯战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，雪佛龙高管和大股东们将在纽约参加这家石油生产商的投资者日活动，投资组合经理们将迫切希望听到首席执行官迈克-沃思（Mike Wirth）的计划，即最终从赫斯（Hess）的收购中获得回报，并开始一个新的增长阶段。【原文：When Chevron executives and top shareholders convene in New York City on Wednesday for the oil producer's investor day, portfolio managers will be eager to hear CEO Mike Wirth's plan to finally reap rewards from the Hess acquisition and begin a new phase of growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-investor-day-puts-spotlight-post-hess-strategy-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4T3BI5ZYFRMZTFBJ4ZIK7EO5MI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约市商业房地产业在租金冻结的威胁下寻求与马姆达尼合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约房地产业的成员一直在为佐赫兰-马姆达尼的可负担性和住房政策所带来的连锁反应做准备，现在正寻求与纽约市当选市长进行接触，因为他正试图冻结房租并刺激城市的发展。【原文：Members of the New York real estate industry have been bracing for the ripple effects of Zohran Mamdani's affordability and housing policies and are now seeking to engage with the New York City mayor-elect as he attempts to freeze rent and spur development in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/new-york-city-commercial-real-estate-industry-seeks-work-with-mamdani-rent-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFBOWLXATBLQTJCRQ5CJAMKNMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：加密货币财务公司转向边缘代币，引发对波动性的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在市场饱和、情绪低落的情况下，专注于囤积比特币和其他主要加密货币的公司面临压力，新进入者正在向不太受欢迎的代币进军，这激起了人们对波动性增加的担忧。【原文：As companies focused on stockpiling bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies come under pressure amid market saturation and souring sentiment, new entrants are pushing into less popular tokens, stoking worries over increased volatility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/crypto-treasury-companies-pivot-fringe-tokens-stoking-volatility-fears-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3SZQ3N4AJIFRDBNOHZLQQW67A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府关门有望结束，美国股指期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿在结束创纪录的美国政府停摆问题上取得了进展，这使得经济数据发布受阻，并加剧了人们对经济状况的担忧。【原文：U.S. stock index futures advanced on Monday following signs of progress in Washington to end a record U.S. government shutdown that has stalled economic data releases and intensified concerns over the state of the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-rise-hopes-end-government-shutdown-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJB55TFK4BNQHMAPAFIJSBAX2A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 10:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国10月份集装箱进口下降，关税引发谨慎情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[供应链技术提供商笛卡尔周一表示，由于进口商对唐纳德-特朗普总统不断变化的关税政策持谨慎态度，10月份美国集装箱货物进口量同比下降7.5%，来自中国的货运量骤降16.3%。【原文：U.S. imports of containerized goods fell 7.5% year-over-year in October, as shipments from China plunged 16.3% amid importer caution over President Donald Trump's evolving tariff policies, supply chain technology provider Descartes said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-container-imports-fall-october-amid-tariff-driven-caution-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAH3SBUCRJOXJLLCQYTRDKENIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 10:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员敦促星巴克首席执行官重启工会谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员和众议员周一表示，26 名参议员和 82 名众议员已致信星巴克首席执行官布莱恩-尼科尔，敦促该公司恢复与工会的谈判。【原文：Twenty-six U.S. senators and 82 House representatives have written to Starbucks CEO Brian Niccol, urging the company to resume talks with its workers union, the lawmakers said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-lawmakers-urge-starbucks-ceo-restart-union-talks-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">745URLB6TFPRFPQR22SVW4MOOY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 10:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国律师事务所第三季度需求激增 - 报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据对公司财务数据的最新分析，第三季度美国大型和中型律师事务所的客户需求 "急剧飙升"，为 2025 年的盈利奠定了基础。【原文：Large and midsized U.S. law firms enjoyed a “sharp spike” in client demand during the third quarter, setting the stage for a profitable 2025, according to a new analysis of firm financial data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/us-law-firms-saw-demand-surge-third-quarter-report-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">627QBDBWQZKGZE6QMGSFARTVFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 10:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲核电企业期待美国实现更快增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利小型模块化反应堆初创公司Newcleo正在考虑放弃在英国建造20座反应堆、总价值约160亿欧元（190亿美元）的计划，转而在美国建造这些反应堆。【原文：Italian small modular reactor startup Newcleo is considering ditching plans to construct 20 reactors in Britain worth an estimated 16 billion euros ($19 billion) and building them in the U.S. instead as European nuclear firms rush to benefit from measures to support the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/italian-smr-firm-newcleo-looking-build-20-reactors-us-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOT5RBHZ4RJWHKHBRQOXTLYDBA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 10:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国有条件批准 Codelco-SQM 锂合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周一表示，有条件批准智利国营铜业巨头--科尔多铜业公司（Codelco）与当地锂生产商 SQM 成立一家与锂相关的合资企业。
 .【原文：China's market regulator said on Monday that it granted conditional approval for a lithium-related joint venture between Chile's state-run copper giant-Codelco and local lithium producer SQM 
 .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/china-grants-conditional-approval-codelco-sqm-lithium-joint-venture-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZKPTLKPRVI75FAQPCZNXSBEZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 09:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英格兰银行提出新建议，软化稳定币立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[英格兰银行周一提议，允许广泛使用的稳定币发行商将支持数字代币的资产的最多 60% 投资于短期政府债务，这是一系列新规则的一部分，表明英格兰银行对该行业的态度有所软化。【原文：The Bank of England on Monday proposed that issuers of widely used stablecoins be allowed to invest up to 60% of the assets backing the digital tokens in short-term government debt, part of a raft of new rules that suggest a softening in its approach to the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bank-england-proposes-new-rules-stablecoins-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYOFOEAE5FJDXMG5BIAJW2EICU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 09:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国批准 31 亿美元的数据中心投资项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国投资委员会周一表示，泰国批准了四个数据中心项目，总价值达 31 亿美元。【原文：Thailand on Monday approved four data centre projects worth $3.1 billion, the Board of Investment said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thailand-says-approves-31-billion-of-data-centre-investments-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMDYCHHY3RNJDEV5EYAQPSALYI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 08:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国最大的进口博览会上，美国参展商希望贸易战的最坏时期已经过去]]></title><description><![CDATA[据几位出口商和行业官员称，美国对华农产品出口商对两国领导人上月达成框架协议后两国贸易将恢复正常感到乐观。【原文：U.S. exporters of agricultural goods to China are optimistic that trade between the two countries will return to normalcy after a framework agreement reached last month by their leaders, according to several exporters and industry officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-largest-import-expo-us-exhibitors-hopeful-worst-trade-war-is-over-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQEYVXKC75JEJDS463L4K3DFNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 08:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德放弃竞购美塞拉后股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德（NOVOb.CO）股价周一早盘上涨，该公司周六放弃了对美国减肥药公司 Metsera 的竞购，结束了与竞争对手辉瑞公司的竞购战。【原文：Shares in Novo Nordisk NOVOb.CO rose in early trade on Monday, after the Wegovy-maker on Saturday dropped its bid for U.S. weight loss drug company Metsera, ending a bidding war with rival Pfizer .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novo-nordisk-shares-rise-after-dropping-metsera-bid-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSDBURDFFVLSBGKGDVAB3NVFOQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 08:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>