<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:10:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:10:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：格陵兰协议希望带来缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国股市大涨，国债收益率下跌。此前，美国总统特朗普表示已就格陵兰岛达成协议框架，并宣布原定于2月1日对多个欧洲国家加征的关税将不再实施。【原文：U.S. stocks jumped and Treasury yields fell on Wednesday after President Donald Trump said a framework of an agreement over Greenland had been reached, and that tariffs on several European countries scheduled for February 1 will no longer be imposed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JFVFFH5MBL2PMRI6HJAEFZXPA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储主席人选可能只剩一人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，他即将选定美联储新任主席，并补充说他倾向于让白宫经济顾问凯文·哈塞特继续留任现职。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday ​indicated he was close to choosing the new chair of the Federal Reserve, adding he liked the idea ‌of keeping White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett in his current post.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-may-be-down-one-candidate-head-fed-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXQPEK6K5VLVTNTAKNZ7NQ6HNY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:51:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称已接到信用卡公司的来电]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，他已接到多家信用卡公司的来电，称这些公司应该"给民众一些喘息空间"。这位共和党领导人同时重申了限制信用卡利率的提案。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Wednesday he has had calls from credit-card companies, ​saying those firms should "give people a break," as the Republican ‌leader doubled ‌down on a proposal to cap credit-card interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/trump-says-he-has-received-calls-credit-card-companies-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PT3CBONW6RMUXE2MCH5M4LSUB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:36:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金德摩根季度利润超预期，得益于强劲天然气需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[金德摩根公司周三公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，这得益于其管道输送的天然气量增加。【原文：Kinder Morgan beat Wall Street expectations for fourth-quarter profit on Wednesday, helped by higher volumes of natural ​gas transported through its pipelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pipeline-operator-kinder-morgan-beats-fourth-quarter-profit-estimates-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBA5F6637BMXHJXG45QQDBONEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[F/m Investments公司寻求美国证券交易委员会批准，将国库券ETF份额代币化]]></title><description><![CDATA[F/m Investments周三表示，该公司已向监管机构提交申请，寻求批准在其美国国债3个月期票据（TBIL）ETF中，将代币化股票的所有权记录在许可型区块链上。【原文：F/m Investments said on Wednesday that the asset manager has filed with a regulator for approval to record ownership of tokenized shares ​in its U.S. Treasury 3-month bill (TBIL) ETF on a permissioned ‌blockchain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fm-investments-seeks-sec-approval-tokenize-treasury-bill-etf-shares-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQCO2DYTWBNTBDV4IE5IZKGZBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[铜价攀升，供应紧张，需求成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三铜价在前一交易日大幅下跌后回升，投资者关注美国以外地区的库存紧张状况，尽管交易员质疑需求能否持续。【原文：Copper prices rose on Wednesday after a sharp decline in the previous session, as investors focused on tight inventories outside the U.S., even as traders questioned whether demand would be sustained.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/copper-climbs-with-tight-stocks-demand-focus-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6UY6H6XHZODJDUHFD766SFKFE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院委员会将就票价问题举行听证会，邀请摇滚歌手基德·洛克及Live Nation公司高管出席]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商务委员会下周将就打击票务不公问题举行听证会，届时票务巨头Ticketmaster母公司Live Nation的高管及艺人基德·洛克将出席作证，一名参议院助理向路透社透露。【原文：A U.S. Senate Commerce panel will hold a hearing next week on efforts to crackdown on unfair ticketing issues that will include an executive from Ticketmaster-parent company Live Nation and entertainer Kid Rock, a Senate aide told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-senate-committee-hold-ticket-pricing-hearing-with-kid-rock-live-nation-exec-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNFSGQIEXRIMZPJ6P76KMATYRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:08:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，苹果公司将对Siri进行全面升级，将其打造为内置聊天机器人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周三报道，苹果计划在今年晚些时候对Siri进行全面升级，将其打造为该公司首个人工智能聊天机器人。【原文：Apple plans to revamp Siri later this year by turning the digital assistant into the company's first artificial intelligence chatbot, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-revamp-siri-built-in-chatbot-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWTP2MSTHJPG5LU5CE5LDR2PVU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者反应：特朗普总统撤回关税威胁，称已就格陵兰岛交易达成框架协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三撤回了对若干国家征收关税的威胁，这些国家此前因对格陵兰岛的立场而受到威胁。他表示已与北约就该岛未来达成协议框架。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday withdrew a threat to impose tariffs on a number of nations for their stance on Greenland, saying he had reached the outlines of a deal with NATO on the island's future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/view-investor-reaction-us-president-trump-withdraws-tariff-threat-says-greenland-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRFRV6T4YVOQJBQLE3ABYKQBM4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联航在芝加哥奥黑尔机场与美国航空的争端升级中划下"红线"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联航周三在芝加哥奥黑尔国际机场与美航的长期争端升级，首席执行官斯科特·柯比承诺将增开"所需数量的航班"，以阻止美航在2026年以牺牲美联航利益为代价获得更多登机口。【原文：United Airlines escalated its long-running battle with American Airlines at Chicago's O'Hare International Airport on Wednesday, with CEO Scott Kirby pledging to add "as many flights as are required" to stop American from gaining additional gates at United's expense in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/united-draws-line-sand-escalating-chicago-ohare-fight-with-american-airlines-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4IIWPLIXJL2BGPN6XJ44ZQAHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:55:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员称联邦航空管理局并非波音MAX 7、10型飞机认证的障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局局长周三表示，该机构并非阻碍波音公司为两款新型波音737 MAX机型获得认证的障碍。【原文：The head of the Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday the agency is not the roadblock to Boeing winning certification of two new variants of the Boeing 737 MAX.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-official-says-faa-not-roadblock-boeing-max-7-10-certification-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYR4XXLOWVMYBCEHQETIZ3WKHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:51:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车报告现金流增强，尽管保时捷业务受挫且中国市场销售疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管欧洲最大汽车制造商大众汽车正面临中国市场销量疲软、美国关税担忧以及豪华运动品牌保时捷经营困境的三重压力，该公司周三公布的数据显示，2025年其净现金流仍将达到60亿欧元（约合70亿美元），超出市场预期。【原文：Volkswagen on Wednesday reported better-than-expected net cash flow in 2025 of 6 billion euros ($7 billion), despite Europe's largest carmaker struggling with weak China sales, U.S. tariff worries and difficulties at luxury sports brand Porsche.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/volkswagen-reports-stronger-cash-flow-despite-porsche-woes-weak-china-sales-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BT4SZX7DFKWBGERK4G4YTN2K4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《Politico》报道，法院裁定TikTok目前可在加拿大继续运营。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《政客》周三报道，加拿大联邦法院已推翻政府关闭TikTok加拿大业务的命令，允许该平台至少暂时继续运营。【原文：Canada's federal court has overturned a government order to close TikTok's Canadian operations, allowing it to continue to operate at least for now, Politico reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/court-rules-tiktok-can-continue-operate-canada-now-politico-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2B2WLTOBBL5LLBODJW323GKTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Archegos创始人黄比尔为造成银行100亿美元损失的巨额欺诈案请求赦免]]></title><description><![CDATA[Archegos资本管理公司创始人黄比尔已就其基金崩盘案的定罪寻求总统赦免，该事件导致华尔街银行损失逾100亿美元。【原文：Bill Hwang, the founder of Archegos Capital Management, has sought a presidential pardon for his conviction in the collapse of his fund that cost Wall Street banks more than $10 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/archegos-bill-hwang-requests-pardon-massive-fraud-that-cost-banks-10-billion-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLLT6WCS3VNHXNHCGBMCEOEABU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:44:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者称，对华尔街房东的限制可能推高房价]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者表示，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普限制华尔街投资者收购独栋住宅的行政令，可能刺激住房需求，却难以缓解住房供应紧张——而住房供应紧张正是推高房价的关键因素。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's executive order restricting Wall Street investors from buying up single-family homes could boost demand for homes while doing little to ​address tight housing supply, a key reason for house price inflation, investors said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/curbs-wall-street-landlords-could-stoke-house-prices-say-investors-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLMGVSLPTBLPXOILI26LGO2NIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能公司Eightfold因协助企业秘密评分求职者而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[由风险投资支持的人工智能招聘平台Eightfold AI正面临加州诉讼，该公司服务于微软、PayPal等众多《财富》500强企业，被指控在求职者不知情的情况下编写用于筛选应聘者的报告。【原文：Eightfold AI, a venture capital-backed artificial intelligence hiring platform ​used by Microsoft , PayPal and many other Fortune 500 companies, is being sued in California for ‌allegedly compiling reports used to screen job applicants without their knowledge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ai-company-eightfold-sued-helping-companies-secretly-score-job-seekers-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVPQA6EQY5KNVBG6RKW7VJ2H6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝索斯的蓝色起源公司将部署数千颗卫星，用于建设全新的"TeraWave"通信网络。]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰夫·贝索斯的太空公司蓝色起源周三宣布，计划在太空部署5408颗卫星构建通信网络，为数据中心、政府及企业提供服务，由此进军由埃隆·马斯克的SpaceX主导的卫星星座市场。【原文：Jeff Bezos' space company Blue Origin on Wednesday announced a plan to deploy 5,408 satellites in space for a communications network that will serve data centers, governments and businesses, jumping into a satellite constellation market dominated by Elon Musk's SpaceX.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/bezos-blue-origin-deploy-thousands-satellites-new-terawave-communications-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CRJXP2U5BKJZKOODXTR27LB5A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，欧盟将同时评估奈飞与派拉蒙对华纳兄弟的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周三报道，欧盟反垄断监管机构预计将同时审查奈飞与派拉蒙天空舞影业对华纳兄弟探索公司的竞购提案，这将形成一场不同寻常的正面交锋式并购审查。【原文：The European Union's antitrust regulators are expected to scrutinize rival bids by Netflix and Paramount Skydance for Warner Bros. Discovery at the same time, setting up an unusual head-to-head competition review, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eu-weigh-netflix-paramount-bids-warner-bros-same-time-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PO6ZMJYEQZJXNMY62F7BMQPDBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车推出EX60电动SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车周三表示，其新款电动中型SUV EX60的定价将与同款插电式混合动力车型持平。这家瑞典车企同时驳斥了外界担忧——即任何与格陵兰相关的美国关税措施都可能打乱其计划。【原文：Volvo Cars said on Wednesday that its new electric mid-sized SUV, the EX60, will have a similar price tag to the plug-in hybrid version of the same model, as the Swedish automaker dismissed concerns that any Greenland-linked U.S. tariffs could disrupt its plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-unveils-its-ex60-electric-suv-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTSRTBFLBBPUHHWOYMIV6KU4LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[育碧宣布大规模重组，更新目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电子游戏发行商育碧周三宣布将进行重组，公司将拆分为五个创意部门，同时修订其财务展望。【原文：French video game publisher Ubisoft will undergo a reorganization, splitting the company into five creative divisions, it said on Wednesday while also revising its financial outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ubisoft-unveils-sweeping-restructuring-updates-targets-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2EPXN3ICRNKXLDIBBXKPXWEYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康集团将为其奥巴马医改计划客户提供返利]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团首席执行官斯蒂芬·赫姆斯利在周三发布的书面证词中表示，该公司将于2026年向其奥巴马医改计划参保人提供返利。【原文：UnitedHealth Group Inc. will provide rebates to its Obamacare plan members in 2026, company CEO Stephen Hemsley said in a prepared testimony released Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-offer-rebates-its-obamacare-customers-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEM2HEU3AVPV7INXOXCHPEDAAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英杰华集团高管在达沃斯表示，公司避开数据中心投资，专注于服务领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[另类投资公司英仕集团周三表示，其副总裁兼首席投资官称，该公司正回避对数据中心的大规模投资，认为该领域竞争过于激烈，转而选择能提供更高回报且能规避地缘政治风险的领域。【原文：Alternative investment firm Investcorp is eschewing big investments in data centres, a space it considers too crowded, its vice president and CIO said on Wednesday, opting instead for sectors offering better returns and shelter from geopolitical risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/investcorp-shies-away-data-centre-investment-focuses-services-executive-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2RQGPSBJBKKNEWF5NQ5QR63X4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田关联公司就叉车发动机排放作弊指控达成4.36亿美元和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[三家丰田关联公司就一起美国集体诉讼达成和解，涉及金额约4.36亿美元。该诉讼指控其在九款叉车发动机中存在排放作弊行为。【原文：Three Toyota affiliates reached a settlement worth an estimated $436 million of a proposed U.S. class action accusing them of emissions cheating in nine engines for forklift trucks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/toyota-affiliates-436-million-settlement-over-alleged-forklift-engine-emissions-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNSP5AAIFRIX7GKHHHZUKQIQRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普引发的市场动荡冲击新兴市场债券销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[据投资者透露，在特朗普总统强力推动收购格陵兰岛引发市场广泛恐慌后，贝宁计划发行的政府债券已被搁置，而格鲁吉亚债券发行的时机也悬而未决。【原文：Benin's planned government bond sale has been put on hold while the timing for one from Georgia is also in flux, according to investors, after U.S. President Donald ​Trump's aggressive push to take control of Greenland caused widespread market jitters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-market-jitters-hit-emerging-market-bond-sales-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYDEGUQESVL4TPFQ5ESCU4XEOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储主席候选人都很棒，直到他们上任为止]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普表示，他已面试了多位实力雄厚的美联储主席候选人，但抱怨称提名人选一旦上任往往会改变立场。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said he has interviewed several strong candidates for Federal Reserve chair, but complained that nominees tend to change once they take office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-says-fed-chair-candidates-are-great-until-they-get-job-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWLJNFDVFVJTVDRUQJ3B6J2GSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国10月建筑支出因翻修工程而反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国10月建筑支出增幅超预期，这可能反映了房屋翻修活动的增长，而其他领域的建筑活动则表现疲软。【原文：U.S. construction spending increased more than expected in October, likely reflecting home renovations, with activity elsewhere weak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-construction-spending-rebounds-october-amid-renovations-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQWRZOD7ZRPVBLBXE3LPMBZWVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:33:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动空中出租车制造商Archer与塞尔维亚合作，共同开拓全球市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿彻航空周三宣布，已与塞尔维亚达成合作，成为该国首选的电动垂直起降飞机合作伙伴，此举旨在拓展全球市场。【原文：Archer Aviation said on Wednesday it had partnered with Serbia as the country's preferred electric vertical take-off and landing aircraft partner, in a move to expand into global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/electric-air-taxi-maker-archer-partners-with-serbia-global-markets-push-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIWWRI5DRZKONPKNQ4WO7OCPHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟议员因格陵兰问题抗议而搁置美欧贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲议会决定暂停审议欧盟与美国的贸易协定，以抗议美国总统唐纳德·特朗普要求收购格陵兰岛的行径，以及对反对其计划的欧洲盟友实施关税威胁的举动。【原文：The European Parliament has decided to suspend its work on the European Union's trade deal with the United States in protest at U.S. President Donald Trump's demands to acquire Greenland and threats of tariffs on European allies who oppose his plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-parliament-suspends-work-eu-us-trade-deal-after-trumps-repeated-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQ7TACHH6VOSFIVHRWQJHRGMTY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：高盛晋升消费零售银行家，本·弗罗斯特出任投行主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[据内部备忘录显示，高盛已将顶级消费零售银行家本·弗罗斯特晋升为投资银行部主席，此前他主导了该行去年在该领域两笔最大交易的运作。【原文：Goldman Sachs has elevated top consumer retail banker Ben Frost to chairman of investment banking, according to an internal memo, after leading the bank's work on two of the biggest deals in the sector last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-promotes-consumer-retail-bankers-ben-frost-named-chairman-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53CIBYBGBBJUHMZJFWX4V62CEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:17:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月待售房屋签约量跌至五个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[12月美国二手房购买合同意外下滑，跌至五个月低点，这可能是因为对劳动力市场的担忧以及持续的入门级住房短缺抵消了抵押贷款利率的下降。【原文：Contracts to purchase previously owned U.S. homes unexpectedly fell in December, hitting a five-month low, likely as worries over the labor market and a persistent shortage of entry-level houses offset lower mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-pending-home-sales-slump-five-month-low-december-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEGLDTMU6JIFXJIGPIJ4RHYRBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:01:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>