<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 20:34:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 20:34:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，银行监管机构就银行股权问题向贝莱德发出新的最后期限要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周日援引三位知情人士的话报道，美国联邦存款保险公司（Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation）给贝莱德公司（BlackRock）规定了一个新的最后期限，即在 2 月 10 日之前解决该公司持有的银行股票的监管问题。【原文：The Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation gave a fresh deadline of Feb. 10 to BlackRock to resolve an issue regarding oversight into the firm's stock in banks, Bloomberg News reported on Sunday, citing three people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-regulator-gives-blackrock-new-deadline-bank-stakes-bloomberg-reports-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKXJ3SGWBFIZZI5MBGIGXUS6KI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 17:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 TCS 预计银行业复苏后零售业和制造业将复苏]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度第一大软件服务出口商塔塔咨询服务公司的一位高层管理人员说，该公司预计，继银行和金融服务部门出现类似的增长之后，其在北美的零售和制造业客户将增加在技术方面的支出。【原文：India's Tata Consultancy Services expects its retail and manufacturing clients in North America to step up spending on tech, following a similar upturn in its banking and financial services segment, a top executive of the nation's No. 1 software-services exporter, said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indias-tcs-expects-retail-manufacturing-revival-after-banking-recovery-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46ZYZG73G5LJHBRJ5ENK3EAZ6A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 07:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登政府推迟执行阻止新日铁、美国钢铁交易的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府将暂缓执行本月行政命令中要求新日铁放弃以 149 亿美元竞购美国钢铁公司的规定。
 两家公司周六表示。【原文：The Biden administration will hold off enforcing a requirement laid out in an executive order this month that Nippon Steel abandon its $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel 
 , the companies said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/biden-admin-delays-enforcement-order-blocking-nippon-steel-us-steel-deal-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FLD5HQ5LFMS7KYAVVABVNBKCM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 01:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果董事会建议股东投票反对取消多元化计划的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据苹果公司提交的代理文件，该公司董事会建议投资者投票反对股东提出的取消公司多元化、公平与包容（DEI）计划的提案。【原文：Apple's board of directors recommended investors vote against a shareholder proposal to abolish the company's Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) programs, according to a proxy filing from the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apples-board-recommends-shareholders-vote-against-proposal-eliminate-diversity-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYEW6UJDZZJ7XB6BAGTUAKFNBI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 01:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德与 LEO 制药公司合作开发炎症性疾病项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司（Gilead Sciences）周六表示，该公司与丹麦 LEO Pharma 公司建立了合作伙伴关系，共同开发治疗炎症性疾病患者的项目。【原文：Gilead Sciences said on Saturday that it entered into a partnership with Denmark's LEO Pharma to develop programs to treat patients with inflammatory diseases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/gilead-leo-pharma-partner-develop-programs-inflammatory-diseases-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOQNGV24OZKG3CDMQSD3KJRDH4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 17:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，赞比亚证监会就中国房地产债券不当销售制裁渣打银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位知情人士透露，赞比亚证券交易委员会（SEC）已经对渣打银行进行了制裁，原因是渣打银行在亚洲国家房地产危机最严重的时候向该行的一位当地财富客户错误地销售了一家中国房地产公司的债券。【原文：Zambia's Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has sanctioned Standard Chartered for mis-selling a Chinese property company's bonds to one of the bank's local wealth clients at the height of the Asian country's real-estate crisis, according to a source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/zambias-sec-sanctions-standard-chartered-over-china-property-bond-mis-selling-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OC3WB77ENJLJPEVZENW5DM62KE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:02:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 警告称，如果美国最高法院允许禁令，将会产生更广泛的后果]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 及其中国母公司字节跳动（ByteDance）的律师在最高法院就一项法律进行辩论时提出了警告，该法律将强制在美国销售短视频应用程序或禁止其使用：如果美国国会可以这样对待 TikTok，那么它也可以这样对待其他公司。【原文：The lawyer for TikTok and its Chinese parent company ByteDance offered a warning during Supreme Court arguments over a law that would compel the sale of the short-video app or ban it in the United States: If Congress could do this to TikTok, it could come after other companies, too.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tiktok-warns-broader-consequences-if-us-supreme-court-allows-ban-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3BTGJXDMFKZ3EOVETEEE72LDY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 11:09:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报刊称瑞士前财长对扩大后的瑞银集团规模提出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士前财政部长乌利-毛雷尔（Ueli Maurer）周六表示，瑞银收购瑞士信贷后，可能会被认为对瑞士来说过于庞大，需要采取措施降低这家扩大后的银行的风险。【原文：UBS could be seen as being too big for Switzerland following its takeover of Credit Suisse, former Swiss Finance Minister Ueli Maurer said on Saturday, with measures needed to reduce the risks of the enlarged bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/former-swiss-finance-minister-warns-about-size-enlarged-ubs-newspaper-says-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFQA46VKQNMZBETTLBM3E2FCNA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 08:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百健公司拟以 4.42 亿美元收购赛捷公司剩余股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一份文件显示，制药公司百健将以每股7.22美元的价格收购其尚未持有的Sage Therapeutics公司的所有流通股，这使得后者的股价在盘后交易中上涨了34%。【原文：Drugmaker Biogen will buy all outstanding shares of Sage Therapeutics that it does not already own for $7.22 apiece, a filing showed on Friday, sending the latter's stock up 34% in extended trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/biogen-proposes-buy-remaining-stake-sage-442-million-deal-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YYOXFWIVRKCBEB64RTKGZ5NC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国提出 2026 年医疗保险优势保险公司支付标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周五提出了 2026 年由私营保险公司经营的医疗保险优势计划的补偿标准，该标准将使支付额增加 2.2%，而去年则下降了 0.2%。【原文：The U.S. government on Friday proposed 2026 reimbursement rates for Medicare Advantage plans run by private insurers that will result in a 2.2% increase in payments, compared with a decline of 0.2% last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-proposes-payment-rate-2026-medicare-advantage-insurers-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBG7QO6GNBKRLNALNBN7MQLHUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部研究证实，美国鸡肉和猪肉工厂工人面临更高的健康风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部周五发布的两份研究报告显示，美国鸡肉和猪肉工厂的工人比其他制造业工人面临更高的患肌肉骨骼疾病（如腕管综合征）的风险。【原文：Workers in U.S. chicken and pork plants face higher risks than other manufacturing workers for musculoskeletal disorders such as carpal tunnel syndrome, according to two studies the U.S. Department of Agriculture issued on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-chicken-pork-plant-workers-face-higher-health-risks-usda-studies-confirm-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26XV2SOZHBMGBFZXPAG6EMPMVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷蒙多：台积电开始在亚利桑那州生产 4 纳米芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长吉娜-雷蒙多（Gina Raimondo）告诉路透社记者，台湾积体电路制造股份有限公司已开始在亚利桑那州为美国客户生产先进的 4 纳米芯片，这是拜登政府半导体努力的一个里程碑。【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co has begun producing advanced 4-nanometer chips for U.S. customers in Arizona, Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo told Reuters, a milestone in the Biden administration's semiconductor efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-begins-producing-4-nanometer-chips-arizona-raimondo-says-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SI5BYKBY4JNHRKHQXTDPE5HZII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 22:13:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁认为 2025 年世界经济将保持稳定增长，通货紧缩仍将持续]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周五告诉记者，IMF将在1月17日发布《世界经济展望》时预测全球经济将稳步增长，通货紧缩将持续。【原文：The International Monetary Fund will forecast steady global growth and continuing disinflation when it releases its World Economic Outlook on Jan. 17, IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva told reporters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-chief-sees-steady-world-growth-2025-continuing-disinflation-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2JMU3YUWRKUBDDHJYDZ3ZB6HE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 22:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国航空机构称近 1.2 万人受数据发布影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国航空机构周五表示，从 2016 年 4 月到 2024 年 7 月，有 11929 人受到了未经授权发布的招聘申请数据记录的影响。【原文：The U.N. aviation agency on Friday said that 11,929 individuals had been affected by the unauthorized release of recruitment application data records from April 2016 to July 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/un-aviation-agency-says-almost-12000-people-affected-by-release-data-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4U2RZTFW6RLURJOEGOMNUNLF2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 22:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[减肥药开发商 Metsera 在提交的美国 IPO 文件中披露了更大范围的亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[由 ARCH Venture Partners 支持的减肥药开发商 Metsera 周五在其美国首次公开募股的文件中披露了更大范围的亏损。【原文：Weight-loss drug developer Metsera, backed by ARCH Venture Partners, revealed a wider loss in its paperwork for a U.S. initial public offering on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/metsera-files-us-ipo-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAVPA4BDN5LTNPWTYKIELRR3SA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 22:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空恢复亚特兰大枢纽航班，取消 700 个航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周五表示，在极端的冬季天气迫使所有五条跑道关闭两个多小时之后，亚特兰大哈兹菲尔德-杰克逊枢纽的起飞和到达航班已经恢复。【原文：Delta Air Lines said on Friday that departures and arrivals at its Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta hub have resumed after extreme winter weather forced the closure of all five runways for more than two hours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-resumes-flights-atlanta-hub-cancels-700-flights-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KKO7KDSD6ZKYNN3LSFYCR7NSH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 21:47:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会对马斯克起诉 OpenAI 一案作出评价]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五就埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）试图阻止OpenAI转为上市公司的诉讼发表了看法，指出一些法律理论可以支持他关于OpenAI和微软参与反竞争行为的主张。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission weighed in on Friday on Elon Musk's lawsuit seeking to block OpenAI's conversion to a public company, pointing out legal doctrines that could support his claim that OpenAI and Microsoft engaged in anticompetitive practices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ftc-weighs-musks-lawsuit-against-openai-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOPMQCLO5VLAHGML3AEZIG4LAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 21:40:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院大法官就 TikTok 申请避免禁令一事进行权衡]]></title><description><![CDATA[最高法院的九位大法官周五听取了 TikTok 及其中国母公司字节跳动对一项法律提出的质疑，该法律将以国家安全为由在 1 月 19 日前强制销售或禁止这一广泛使用的短视频应用程序。【原文：The Supreme Court's nine justices heard arguments on Friday in a challenge by TikTok and its Chinese parent company ByteDance to a law that would force a sale or ban the widely used short-video app by Jan. 19 on national security grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-justices-weigh-tiktok-bid-avoid-ban-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMSB4EVVVJLHTGKKHNEKDVM6SU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 21:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业报告推动国债收益率飙升，市场为 5%门槛做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[近期美国国债收益率的飙升可能会获得更大的动力，因为一份强劲的就业报告增强了人们对利率将在更长时间内保持高位的预期，并使基准 10 年期国债收益率触及 5%--一些人担心这一水平可能会动摇更广泛的市场。【原文：A recent surge in U.S. Treasury yields may gain even more momentum after a strong jobs report reinforced expectations that interest rates will stay high for longer and raised the spectre of benchmark 10-year yields hitting 5% — a level that some fear could rattle broader markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/jobs-report-fuels-treasury-yield-surge-markets-brace-5-threshold-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4VBVLIPNJP5PBSMKZVKIMA6XA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 21:13:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，HPE 为埃隆-马斯克的 X 公司获得价值 10 亿美元的人工智能服务器交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，惠普企业公司已达成一项价值超过 10 亿美元的协议，将为埃隆-马斯克的社交媒体平台 X 提供为人工智能工作优化的服务器。【原文：Hewlett Packard Enterprise has struck a deal worth over $1 billion to provide Elon Musk's social media platform X with servers optimized for artificial intelligence work, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/hpe-secures-1-bln-ai-server-deal-elon-musks-x-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7MYAE2KPJMB5OGOX6Z4MS7TXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:53:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊将终止部分多元化和包容性计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五看到，亚马逊公司在 12 月份给员工的一份备忘录中表示，公司将终止部分多元化和包容性计划。【原文：Amazon.com is ending some of its diversity and inclusion programs, the company said in a December memo to employees seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/amazon-is-ending-some-diversity-inclusion-programs-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAJJCSE2W5K4ROWNARXZRV5YME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:34:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因房东拒绝将房屋出租给带孩子的母亲，美国起诉 Airbnb]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Airbnb 因一名房东拒绝将公寓租给一位有三个学龄儿童的母亲而被美国政府起诉。【原文：Airbnb was sued by the U.S. government on Friday over a host's refusal to rent an apartment to a mother with three school-age children.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-airbnb-after-host-rejected-rental-mother-with-children-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6LF5RCGYVIXTLUS54AI4C5YGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:17:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Blackstone 正酝酿以 40 多亿美元出售 Liftoff]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉此事的人士周五表示，收购公司 Blackstone 正在权衡 Liftoff 的战略选择，包括出售，该移动应用程序营销提供商的估值可能超过 40 亿美元（包括债务）。【原文：Buyout firm Blackstone is weighing strategic options, including a sale, for Liftoff that could value the mobile app marketing provider at more than $4 billion, including debt, two people familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/blackstone-mulls-4-billion-plus-sale-liftoff-sources-say-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74FYIQFONNMZVKSGNDLM6X2EKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Semafor 报道，好时公司将宣布首席执行官米歇尔-巴克离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Semafor 周五援引知情人士的话报道，巧克力生产商好时公司计划宣布首席执行官米歇尔-巴克（Michele Buck）离职。【原文：Chocolate maker Hershey plans to announce the departure of CEO Michele Buck, Semafor reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hershey-set-announce-ceo-michele-buck-step-down-semafor-reports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RNFL4WYGNN7HNNHBRWTSGSBE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉阻止企业旅游公司合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国已起诉阻止美国运通全球商务旅行集团与 CWT Holdings 之间的拟议合并，称这笔价值 5.7 亿美元的交易将消除最大和第三大商务旅行管理服务提供商之间的竞争。【原文：The U.S. has sued to block a proposed merger between American Express Global Business Travel Group and CWT Holdings, saying the $570 million deal would eliminate competition between the largest and third largest providers of business travel management services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-block-corporate-travel-company-merger-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBDYJWSVQNJWBFYGG3W7LTWSXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将在特朗普就职典礼前终止多元化计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周五在公司内部论坛上发布了一份致员工的备忘录，称将终止其多元化、公平与包容（DEI）计划，包括招聘、培训和挑选供应商的计划。【原文：Meta Platforms is ending its diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) programs, including those for hiring, training and picking suppliers, it said in a memo to employees posted on an internal company forum on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/meta-end-diversity-programs-ahead-trump-inauguration-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RV3HXX7EFRI37CUVWVK6NZ5G3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西给 Meta 公司 72 小时解释对事实核查计划的修改]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西副检察长豪尔赫-梅西亚斯（Jorge Messias）周五表示，巴西政府将要求梅塔公司在周一之前对该计划做出解释。【原文：Brazil's government will give Meta until Monday to explain the program, Solicitor General Jorge Messias said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-gives-meta-72-hours-explain-changes-fact-checking-program-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHZATBMRFJN6VIDOIDVCDK6NVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税担忧影响，1 月份美国消费者通胀预期飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者预计未来 12 个月及以后的通胀率将上升，这可能反映出人们担心当选总统唐纳德-特朗普即将上任的政府承诺对进口商品征收的广泛关税可能会提高家庭的物价。【原文：U.S. consumers expect inflation to increase over the next 12 months and beyond, likely reflecting concerns that broad tariffs on imports pledged by President-elect Donald Trump's incoming administration could raise prices for households.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-inflation-expectations-soar-january-tariff-fears-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVK53OQ62JOXZMCVJWDSDQ6GWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国负责人对 Blackrock 退出气候组织表示不满，敦促其他人留下]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国秘书长安东尼奥-古特雷斯（Antonio Guterres）的发言人周五表示，他对全球最大的资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock BLK.N）退出应对气候变化的全球倡议感到失望，并敦促其他公司 "坚持到底"。【原文：U.N. Secretary-General Antonio Guterres is disappointed that the world's biggest asset manager, BlackRock BLK.N, has left a global initiative to combat climate change, his spokesperson said on Friday, urging other companies to "stay the course."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/un-chief-upset-blackrock-quit-climate-group-urges-others-stay-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEUUUVPHGZITTGFLQA7MT57FCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，特朗普将脱离家族企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引特朗普公司的道德计划报道称，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普上任后将不会参与特朗普组织的日常管理。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump won't be involved in the day-to-day management of the Trump Organization once he takes office, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing an ethics plan from the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-will-separate-himself-family-business-wsj-reports-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXJ2ZFF3U5PQ7DX5GUY2SAXFEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>