<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:04:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:04:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[加州大学因预计特朗普削减开支而冻结招聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚大学校长周三表示，该校已在全系统范围内冻结招聘，并进行了额外的裁员，以努力减轻联邦资金大幅削减所带来的影响。【原文：The University of California has imposed a system-wide hiring freeze and made additional cuts, its president said on Wednesday, as part of efforts to try to mitigate the impact of sharp cuts in federal funding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/university-california-sets-hiring-freeze-anticipation-trump-cuts-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK4J43S7ZVM6FPSC5XCH4HSP34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:23:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院民主党人要求撤销疾控中心的大规模解雇决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院七名民主党人周三要求唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府恢复他上任以来解雇的美国疾病控制和预防中心的所有员工。【原文：Seven U.S. Senate Democrats demanded on Wednesday that President Donald Trump's administration reinstate all of the employees it fired from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention since he took office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-senate-democrats-demand-reversal-cdc-mass-firings-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LPHCOGKRZJ3BJYLZW2LN2WYXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国高端妓院网络头目被判入狱四年]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，大波士顿地区和华盛顿郊区一家高档妓院网络的经营者被判处四年监禁，该妓院的数百名顾客包括政客、公司高管、律师和军官。【原文：The operator of a high-end brothel network in the greater Boston area and the suburbs of Washington, whose hundreds of customers included politicians, corporate executives, lawyers and military officers, was sentenced on Wednesday to four years in prison.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ringleader-high-end-us-brothel-network-gets-4-years-prison-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HY7V5W6BZMIDMP2N3NRGOH3PI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院民主党人敦促特朗普撤销联邦贸易委员会的解雇决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[二十多位美国民主党参议员周三呼吁唐纳德-特朗普总统撤销解雇美国联邦贸易委员会两位民主党成员的决定。【原文：More than two dozen Democratic U.S. senators called on President Donald Trump on Wednesday to rescind his termination of the two Democratic members of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senate-democrats-urge-trump-reverse-federal-trade-commission-firings-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJJ4FUN2E5NILGBB366OUCXGHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:49:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官驳回禁止政府专家组接管 USIP 的临时令请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，一名美国法官驳回了一项临时命令的请求，该命令禁止唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府效率部（Donald Trump's cost-cutting Department of Government Efficiency）进一步接管美国和平研究所（U.S. Institute of Peace）。【原文：A U.S. judge on Wednesday denied a request for a temporary order barring President Donald Trump's cost-cutting Department of Government Efficiency from furthering any effort to take over the U.S. Institute of Peace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/judge-denies-request-temporary-order-bar-doge-usip-takeover-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QY5HTAXM7VN2XC2OYYHN2OIJZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:32:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局可能要求波音公司的 "星际客机 "进行第三次无人驾驶测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司的 "星际客机"（Starliner）太空舱去年在国际空间站上留下了两名美国国家航空航天局（NASA）宇航员，在再次搭载宇航员之前，波音公司可能需要进行第三次无人试飞，美国国家航空航天局的官员说，该太空船的第一批乘员本周必须乘坐 SpaceX 公司的太空舱返回地球。【原文：Boeing's troubled Starliner capsule that left two NASA astronauts on the International Space Station last year may need to fly a third uncrewed test flight before it carries astronauts again, agency officials said as the spacecraft's first crew had to return to Earth on a SpaceX capsule this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/nasa-may-require-boeings-starliner-fly-third-uncrewed-test-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BHQR4R625IGZJNPBWHM2D7BOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国律师事务所Paul Weiss因特朗普行政命令被客户解雇]]></title><description><![CDATA[律师事务所保罗-魏斯（Paul Weiss）周三在一份法庭文件中表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本月发布了针对该事务所的行政命令，一名面临刑事贿赂指控的前高管已解雇了该事务所作为其辩护律师的职位。【原文：Law firm Paul Weiss said in a court filing on Wednesday that a former executive facing criminal bribery charges has fired it as his defense counsel because of U.S. President Donald Trump's executive order this month targeting the firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-law-firm-paul-weiss-fired-by-client-over-trump-executive-order-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SL53SYKUYRN2TJDOJTVXYMAIDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国客运铁路公司 Amtrak 首席执行官突然下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amtrak 首席执行官斯蒂芬-加德纳（Stephen Gardner）周三表示，在担任美国客运铁路公司负责人四年多之后，他将立即卸任，理由是担心该公司无法继续得到唐纳德-特朗普总统政府的支持。【原文：Amtrak CEO Stephen Gardner said Wednesday he will step down immediately after more than four years as head of the U.S. passenger railroad, citing concerns about maintaining the carrier's support from President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-passenger-railroad-amtrak-ceo-abruptly-steps-down-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5T35EFT5IRK4BMNBPGX3NDNYS4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:20:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称让联邦贸易委员会委员离职的 "时机已到]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普解雇联邦贸易委员会两位民主党委员的决定辩护，称让他们离职的 "时机已经成熟"。【原文：The White House on Wednesday defended U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to fire two Democratic commissioners at the Federal Trade Commission, saying the "time was right" to let them go.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-says-time-was-right-let-ftc-commissioners-go-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEE72XU4OBJMXM4MUM63R2KAVM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会起诉特朗普政府停止学生贷款偿还计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一个主要的教师工会对教育部提起诉讼，指控共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府非法关闭了数百万学生贷款者使用的收入驱动还款计划。【原文：A major U.S. teachers union has filed a lawsuit against the Department of Education accusing Republican President Donald Trump's administration of unlawfully shutting down access to income-driven repayment plans used by millions of student loan borrowers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/union-sues-trump-administration-halting-student-loan-repayment-plans-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFEJQ3XSRZNUVEDWHGLW2NKNBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:52:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对峙之后，法官拒绝禁止 DOGE 进入美国和平研究所]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国和平研究所指控马斯克团队的成员强行占领大楼之后，一名联邦法官周三允许科技亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的政府效率部（Department of Government Efficiency）接管美国和平研究所。【原文：A federal judge on Wednesday allowed the takeover of the U.S. Institute of Peace by tech billionaire Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency, after USIP accused members of Musk's team of occupying the building by force.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-institute-peace-sues-trump-doge-over-executive-order-firings-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJ6IYDUJUVPIDPCUIU7C7YPFCY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:39:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府指责法官在委内瑞拉驱逐案中越权行事]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国首席大法官约翰-罗伯茨（John Roberts）斥责共和党总统要求弹劾一名联邦法官之后一天，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周三在一份文件中指责一名联邦法官越权要求提供有关委内瑞拉移民驱逐航班的更多细节。【原文：Donald Trump's administration accused a federal judge on Wednesday of overstepping his judicial authority in demanding more details about deportation flights of Venezuelan migrants in a filing made a day after U.S. Chief Justice John Roberts rebuked the Republican president for calling for the judge's impeachment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-accuses-judge-overstepping-venezuela-deportations-case-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7D6FQVFJ75L5NOH4INGRIPNUEE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将于 2026 年底前在 74 个机场安装跑道安全技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）表示，到 2026 年底，将在 74 个机场安装增强型安全技术，帮助检测跑道入侵。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said it will install enhanced safety technology to help detect runway incursions at 74 airports by the end of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-install-runway-safety-technology-74-airports-by-end-2026-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMCEUSKWG5KD3DUY44M36V7HN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:50:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发布州和地方备灾行政命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周三发布了一项行政命令，涉及州和地方基础设施应对野火和飓风等自然灾害以及网络攻击等其他威胁的准备工作。【原文：President Donald Trump issued an executive order on Wednesday related to state and local infrastructure preparedness for responding to natural disasters such as wildfires and hurricanes, along with other threats like cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-issues-state-local-preparedness-executive-order-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNWFEFRXDFJJRAXSDLEH5FO2GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 放宽部分处方药续保规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）旗下的药房福利管理公司 Optum Rx 周三表示，将放宽续订约 80 种药物处方时获得保险授权的要求，旨在减少患者和医生的文书工作。【原文：UnitedHealth Group's pharmacy benefit manager, Optum Rx, said on Wednesday it would ease requirements to get insurance authorization when renewing prescriptions on about 80 drugs, aiming to reduce paperwork for patients and doctors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealths-unit-reduces-prescription-reauthorization-requirements-by-up-25-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6ONDKOQ2BPXFL2O5RB3FVXYII</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 11:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁是特朗普政府移民诉讼案的法官詹姆斯-博斯伯格？]]></title><description><![CDATA[这位暂时阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府援引战时权力驱逐移民的美国法官多年来一直在处理涉及敏感安全或政治问题的高风险案件--有时会做出有利于特朗普的裁决。【原文：The U.S. judge who temporarily blocked President Donald Trump’s administration from invoking wartime powers to deport migrants has for years handled high-stakes cases involving sensitive security or political issues - sometimes ruling in Trump's favor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/who-is-james-boasberg-judge-trump-administration-immigration-fight-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBFELVG2FVMFJK5UQO5L3TWXWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 10:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储在预计经济增长放缓、通胀暂时蹿升的情况下保持政策利率前景不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三如期维持利率稳定，但美国央行决策者表示，在经济增长放缓、最终导致通胀下滑的背景下，他们仍预计在今年年底前将借贷成本降低半个百分点。【原文：The Federal Reserve held interest rates steady on Wednesday, as expected, but U.S. central bank policymakers indicated they still anticipate reducing borrowing costs by half a percentage point by the end of this year in the context of slowing economic growth and, eventually, a downturn in inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/with-interest-rates-hold-feds-economic-projections-take-center-stage-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNOFB4D2EVNWZDBO42JZ4YIZMI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 10:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战迫在眉睫，特朗普将宴请美国顶级石油公司总裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将于周三在白宫接待石油行业的高层管理人员，他将阐述在原油价格下跌和贸易战迫在眉睫的情况下促进国内能源生产的计划。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will host top oil executives at the White House on Wednesday as he charts plans to boost domestic energy production in the midst of falling crude prices and looming trade wars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-host-top-us-oil-chief-executives-trade-wars-loom-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJLGZRY5SBO4FFAXWADV45EFAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 10:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普向普京靠拢，美国暂停部分反俄破坏行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普政府推动俄罗斯结束乌克兰战争之际，美国多个国家安全机构停止了打击俄罗斯破坏、造谣和网络攻击的协调工作，从而减轻了对莫斯科的压力。【原文：Several U.S. national security agencies have halted work on a coordinated effort to counter Russian sabotage, disinformation and cyberattacks, easing pressure on Moscow as the Trump Administration pushes Russia to end its war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-suspends-some-efforts-counter-russian-sabotage-trump-moves-closer-putin-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJBFNQNGT5PRLAURW4XVBDLXYE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 06:06:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普渡制药公司为 74 亿美元阿片类药物和解申请新的破产计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[破产制药商普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）周二提交了一份新的破产计划，这是去年在美国最高法院受挫后，该公司朝着最终达成至少 74 亿美元的阿片类药物和解协议迈出的重要一步。【原文：Bankrupt drugmaker Purdue Pharma filed a new bankruptcy plan on Tuesday, a major step towards finalizing a proposed opioid settlement of at least $7.4 billion after a setback in the U.S. Supreme Court last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/purdue-pharma-files-new-bankruptcy-plan-74-billion-opioid-settlement-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DT334CAHWRLNLKSOOZFGGNJC5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 05:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普削减美国新闻机构被批向中国和对手让步]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国立法者和人权倡导者说，在中国政府急于扩大其势力范围之际，特朗普政府解散美国政府资助的新闻机构，包括美国之音和自由亚洲电台，是对华盛顿来之不易的全球软实力的重大打击。【原文：U.S. lawmakers and rights advocates say the Trump administration's drive to dismantle U.S. government-funded news outlets, including Voice of America and Radio Free Asia, is a major blow to Washington's hard-earned soft power globally at a time when Beijing is rushing to expand its sphere of influence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-cuts-us-news-outlets-criticized-ceding-ground-china-adversaries-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIQ3ISKTPNKY5IQ247SERLOG6M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 04:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止特朗普的环保局收回气候拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一名美国法官暂时阻止美国环境保护局收回作为 200 亿美元气候资助计划一部分发放的赠款，共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已采取行动终止该计划。【原文：A U.S. judge on Tuesday temporarily blocked the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency from recovering grant funds issued as part of a $20 billion climate funding program that Republican President Donald Trump's administration has moved to terminate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-trumps-epa-clawing-back-climate-grants-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR2XXCBJ4NP2PPLOLETVV2JHOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止特朗普的环保局收回气候拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一名美国法官暂时阻止美国环境保护局收回作为 200 亿美元气候资助计划一部分发放的赠款，共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已采取行动终止该计划。【原文：A U.S. judge on Tuesday temporarily blocked the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency from recovering grant funds issued as part of a $20 billion climate funding program that Republican President Donald Trump's administration has moved to terminate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-trumps-epa-clawing-back-climate-grants-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR2XXCBJ4NP2PPLOLETVV2JHOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府取消对联邦合同中 "隔离设施 "的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总务管理局发布的一份备忘录显示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已经取消了对联邦承包商等候室、餐厅和饮水机等 "隔离设施 "的明确禁令。【原文：The administration of U.S. President Donald Trump has removed an explicit ban on "segregated facilities" like waiting rooms, restaurants and drinking fountains for federal contractors, a memo issued by the U.S. General Services Administration showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-removes-ban-segregated-facilities-federal-contracts-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KORKRBDCFKM7DJ2O3VVVN4MSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 02:20:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国指控海地黑帮头目伊佐劫持一名美国公民为人质]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国华盛顿检察官办公室周二发表声明称，美国检察官指控海地黑帮头目约翰逊-安德烈（Johnson Andre）（绰号 "伊佐 "Izo）在海地劫持一名美国公民为人质。【原文：Prosecutors in the United States have charged powerful Haitian gang leader Johnson Andre, known as Izo, with taking a U.S. citizen hostage in Haiti, according to a statement from the U.S. Attorney's Office in Washington released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-charges-haitian-gang-leader-izo-with-hostage-taking-us-citizen-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALLFXPR2ZBI5PBWTJBBJLHT7MY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 01:57:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被特朗普解雇的两位联邦贸易委员会民主党委员是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周二解雇了联邦贸易委员会的两位民主党委员。【原文：President Donald Trump fired the two Democratic commissioners at the Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/who-are-two-democratic-ftc-commissioners-fired-by-trump-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OFB7QKNM5L3DI434DGM5VP3CI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 01:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令，将联邦紧急事务管理局的备灾工作移交给各州和地方政府]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二签署了一项行政命令，试图将备灾责任转移给州政府和地方政府，从而深化他对联邦紧急事务管理局的改革。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday signed an executive order that seeks to shift responsibility for disaster preparations to state and local governments, deepening his drive to overhaul the Federal Emergency Management Agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-signs-order-shift-disaster-preparations-fema-states-local-governments-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JHWGZVIQRPBJNK4OC4VUYPFUI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2022 年得克萨斯州 53 名移民因偷渡死亡，两人被判有罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[司法部表示，得克萨斯州圣安东尼奥的一个联邦陪审团周二判定两名墨西哥男子有罪，他们在 2022 年 6 月酷热难耐的天气中将 53 名移民挤在一辆卡车上偷运致死的事件中扮演了重要角色。【原文：A federal jury in San Antonio, Texas on Tuesday convicted two Mexican men for their roles in the smuggling death of 53 migrants packed into a truck during sweltering heat in June 2022, the Justice Department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/two-convicted-smuggling-death-53-migrants-texas-2022-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLRLP5HQTFMETNEOOQCCATKSOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 23:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府正在权衡疾病预防控制中心艾滋病预防部门的未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生部周二表示，正在审查疾病控制和预防中心的艾滋病预防部门是否与其他机构重叠，但尚未就该部门的未来做出最终决定。【原文：The U.S. health department said on Tuesday it is reviewing the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's HIV prevention division for overlap with other agencies but no final decision had been made about its future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-weighing-future-cdcs-hiv-prevention-division-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2G75PDUWFPJ7OPK4VQ4V7K67U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 23:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部长称针对特斯拉财产的袭击为 "国内恐怖主义]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部长帕姆-邦迪（Pam Bondi）周二谴责了最近对特斯拉财产的暴力袭击，并补充说司法部已经起诉了几名肇事者。【原文：U.S. Attorney General Pam Bondi on Tuesday condemned recent violent attacks on Tesla property, adding the Department of Justice has already charged several perpetrators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-attorney-general-calls-attacks-against-tesla-property-domestic-terrorism-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECQR565XRVK6ZHJPF3CEUVMKFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 23:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>