<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:06:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:06:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贸易紧张局势缓解，日本投资者连续第六周增持外资股]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本投资者连续第六周增持海外股票，因为有迹象表明美国和中国愿意缓和贸易紧张局势，这进一步刺激了他们对海外股票的持续追捧。【原文：Japanese investors raised their foreign stock holdings for a sixth straight week as their sustained appetite for overseas equities was further bolstered by signs that the U.S. and China were willing to ease trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japanese-investors-raise-foreign-stock-holdings-sixth-week-easing-trade-tensions-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ32SFDNUJPCTEO34RYBNMX56U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moneycontrol 称凯雷集团出售印度 PNB 住房公司全部股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据商业新闻网站 Moneycontrol 周四援引条款表报道，美国私募股权投资集团凯雷集团已通过大宗交易出售了其持有的印度 PNB 住房金融公司全部 10.44% 的股份。【原文：U.S. private equity group Carlyle Group has sold its entire 10.44% stake in India's PNB Housing Finance via block deals, business news website Moneycontrol reported on Thursday, citing a termsheet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyle-group-sells-full-stake-indias-pnb-housing-moneycontrol-says-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXPVUBIPDJIUZP7H5SZHC5TX3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丹斯克银行第一季度净利润超预期，维持业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦最大的银行丹斯克银行周五公布的第一季度净利润超出预期，并维持全年利润展望不变。【原文：Denmark's biggest lender Danske Bank reported first-quarter net profit above expectations on Friday and kept its full-year profit outlook unchanged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/danske-banks-q1-net-profit-beats-forecasts-maintains-outlook-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DXFLHQ4EFM5JPMRVGEVDNJNZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行认为加息窗口正在缩小，但尚未关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行的加息周期正面临着自行长上田一夫两年前执掌日本央行以来的最大考验，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税迅速缩小了进一步提高仍处于低位的借贷成本的窗口。【原文：The Bank of Japan's rate-hike cycle is facing its biggest test since Governor Kazuo Ueda took the helm two years ago, with U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs rapidly narrowing the window for further increases in still-low borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-sees-window-rate-hikes-narrowing-not-closed-yet-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFNZJBQV4VI7FIY773HHOIP4MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三菱预计年度利润下降 26%，理由是缺乏资本收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本贸易公司三菱商事（Mitsubishi Corp）周五预测，截至 3 月份的全年净利润将下降 26%，降至 7000 亿日元（48.2 亿美元），理由是没有重大资本收益。【原文：Japanese trading house Mitsubishi Corp forecast on Friday its net profit for the year ending March would fall 26% to 700 billion yen ($4.82 billion), citing the absence of major capital gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-mitsubishi-annual-profit-down-1-misses-forecasts-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2E3AS66NVNKTLOAGUPKKXN47PA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:22:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普拟对小包裹征税，一些零售商放弃美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国终止了对小包裹的关税豁免，一些零售商停止了向美国客户的销售，而另一些零售商则在寻求临时变通办法，希望关税率能够降低。【原文：As the United States ends a tariff exemption for small parcels, some retailers have stopped selling to U.S. customers while others are seeking temporary workarounds in the hope the tariff rate may be reduced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trump-moves-tax-small-parcels-some-retailers-give-up-us-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDRZOJNBTFJW7LP3ILYZXYSWRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[StanChart 第一季度利润增长 10%，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周五公布的季度利润增长了 10%，原因是财富、市场和全球银行业务的强劲表现提高了收入，但渣打也表示，关税的增加可能会对信贷质量造成压力。【原文：Standard Chartered on Friday reported a 10% rise in quarterly profit as strong wealth, markets and global banking businesses boosted revenue, though it also said increased tariffs would likely weigh on credit quality.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stanchart-books-10-rise-first-quarter-profit-beats-estimate-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WI3X5SLK5RORXHPYISNOD4JFFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:55:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻北京迹象明显，苹果凶多吉少]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23T3GXARNFM43DOXGLTQ6RGBUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令，旨在削减对 NPR 和 PBS 的拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，唐纳德-特朗普签署了一项行政命令，旨在削减对新闻机构全国公共广播电台（NPR）和公共广播公司（PBS）的拨款，这是美国总统最近一次试图利用联邦拨款作为打击他不看好的机构的筹码。【原文：Donald Trump signed an executive order that aims to cut funding to news outlets NPR and PBS, the White House said, marking the U.S. president's latest attempt to use federal funding as leverage against institutions he does not view favorably.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/trump-signs-order-that-aims-cut-funding-npr-pbs-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7R3BYGRIJJ2RL3TUOKQDGPWTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国低值套餐关税豁免结束，但美国收税问题依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府终止了美国对来自中国和香港的低价值货物的免税准入，取消了Shein、Temu和其他电子商务公司以及芬太尼和其他非法货物贩运者所享有的 "微量 "豁免。【原文：The Trump administration ended U.S. duty-free access for low-value shipments from China and Hong Kong, removing the "de minimis" exemptions availed of by Shein, Temu and other e-commerce firms as well as traffickers of fentanyl and other illicit goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-low-value-package-tariff-exemption-ends-questions-remain-over-us-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7ZM2XSKJZO23HNYE3DTPTI22I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴塞尔协议老板表示，资本规则的 "瑞士终结 "对瑞银并不不公平]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行业监管机构负责人表示，瑞士现行的银行资本规则并没有不公平地惩罚瑞士的贷款机构与其他地方的竞争对手，从而回击了瑞银集团为反对政府强化这些规则的计划而提出的论点。【原文：The head of the world's banking watchdog said Switzerland's existing rules on bank capital do not unfairly penalise its lenders versus rivals elsewhere, pushing back on arguments UBS has made to oppose government plans to toughen them up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/basel-boss-signals-swiss-finish-capital-rules-is-not-unfair-ubs-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3M5WWXKGJNTTEBS3IQYKVO3BE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发的不确定性被认为抑制了美国 4 月份的就业增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）激进的关税政策导致经济不确定性加剧，美国4月份的就业增长可能放缓，不过企业继续囤积工人，使劳动力市场暂时保持活跃。【原文：U.S. job growth likely slowed in April amid heightened economic uncertainty because of President Donald Trump's aggressive tariff policy, though companies continued to hoard workers, keeping the labor market humming for now.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/tariff-induced-uncertainty-seen-curbing-us-job-growth-april-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5KCRWNQK5N3BHIDF72XJGNODU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本第一季度国内生产总值可能因内需疲软、进口激增而萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易政策使经济增长前景黯淡，日本经济可能在第一季度出现一年来的首次萎缩，原因是内需疲软和进口超过出口。【原文：Japan's economy probably contracted for the first time in a year in the first quarter, weighed down by softer domestic demand and imports outperforming exports, a Reuters poll showed, as U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies dim the growth outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-q1-gdp-likely-contracted-soft-domestic-demand-import-surge-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5RBRBNR6FKBPA4WUEFPWDNSRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对华黑名单错误百出、细节过时]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对 2023 年和 2024 年被列入美国实体名单的近 100 家中国和香港公司进行了审查，发现超过四分之一的公司包含错误的详细信息，如错误的名称和地址以及过时的信息。【原文：A Reuters review of almost 100 Chinese and Hong Kong companies added to the U.S. entity list in 2023 and 2024 found more than a quarter contained erroneous details, such as incorrect names and addresses and outdated information.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-blacklist-china-is-riddled-with-errors-outdated-details-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6RRVFWPY5ILTMNQNPRU4XYADU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易紧张局势出现缓和迹象，亚洲股市上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市和美国期货市场上涨，原因是有迹象表明中美之间可能进行贸易谈判，这提振了风险情绪，此前科技风向标苹果和亚马逊的财报乏善可陈，加剧了人们对关税影响的担忧。【原文：Asian stock markets and U.S. futures rose on Friday as signs of possible trade talks between the U.S. and China lifted risk sentiment after lacklustre earnings from tech bellwethers Apple and Amazon fuelled worries about the impact of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIECMAKSFVIRBF62HPOIIR6KYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国表示愿意与美国进行贸易谈判，油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲早盘时段，中国表示其与美国谈判的大门是敞开的，这提高了世界两大经济体之间激烈的贸易战出现缓和的希望，油价随之上扬。【原文：Oil prices pulled ahead in early Asian hours on Friday after China said its door is open for talks with the United States, raising hopes of a de-escalation in a bitter trade war between the world's two largest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-china-says-its-open-trade-talks-with-us-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYBF2UUZFVPZLOJKTMZCF656LY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税担忧缓解，美元有望实现第三周上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元连续第三周上涨，因为有迹象表明华盛顿与一些贸易伙伴的谈判取得了进展，而且好于预期的数据缓解了人们对世界最大经济体投资的担忧。【原文：The U.S. dollar headed for a third-straight weekly gain as signs of progress in Washington's talks with some of its trading partners and better-than-expected data eased concerns over investments in the world's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-poised-third-weekly-gain-tariff-concerns-ease-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7M7VT3ZXNNETL7OQDG2WD34LE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify 向苹果公司提交应用程序更新，并为在美国购买提供外部链接]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify 周四表示，它已向苹果公司提交了一个应用程序更新，其中包含购买订阅的外部链接，此前美国法官裁定 iPhone 制造商违反了要求其允许应用程序下载更多竞争的命令。【原文：Spotify said on Thursday it has submitted an app update to Apple with an external link to buy subscriptions, after a U.S. judge ruled that the iPhone maker violated the order that required it to allow greater competition for app downloads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spotify-submits-app-update-apple-with-external-link-purchases-us-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NK6F6S4LFNMYPNF3YXWV7DINPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称美国渴望就关税问题进行谈判，北京的大门是 "敞开的]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周五表示，美国已与中国接触，寻求就唐纳德-特朗普总统征收145%关税一事进行谈判，中国政府的大门是敞开的，欢迎双方进行讨论，这标志着贸易战可能出现缓和。【原文：The United States has approached China to seek talks over President Donald Trump's 145% tariffs and Beijing's door is open for discussions, China's Commerce Ministry said on Friday, signalling a potential de-escalation in the trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-says-us-eager-negotiate-tariffs-beijings-door-is-open-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J43JSB3EQFL45CY52ORCZF4UUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:53:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚银行在经济和政治交织的背景下面临盈利考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[面对迫在眉睫的降息、持续的通胀忧虑和不断上升的抵押贷款压力，澳大利亚最大的银行下周将面临关键的盈利考验，因为它们要应对好坏参半的息差前景。【原文：Australia's biggest banks face a pivotal earnings test next week as they navigate mixed interest margin prospects in the face of looming rate cuts, persistent inflation concerns and rising mortgage stress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-banks-face-critical-earnings-test-amid-economic-political-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJTWQEJRA5P5THVALRFEPCOILQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究公司称，中国电动汽车制造商在欧盟销售更多插电式混合动力汽车以规避关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的数据显示，包括比亚迪和奇瑞（CHERY.UL）在内的中国汽车制造商正在欧盟销售更多的插电式混合动力汽车，以规避对中国产电动汽车征收的进口关税。【原文：Chinese carmakers including BYD and Chery (CHERY.UL) are selling more plugin-hybrids in the European Union to avoid import tariffs on Chinese-made electric cars, data released on Friday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-ev-makers-sell-more-plugin-hybrids-eu-avoid-tariffs-research-firm-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5EOWG5BGBNBTA77U2APK3ERFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥计划到 2030 年逐步将每周工作时间减少到 40 小时]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥劳动和社会保障部长马拉特-博拉诺斯（Marath Bolanos）周四表示，墨西哥政府将逐步把每周标准工作时间减少到 40 小时，此举预计将于 2030 年 1 月全面生效。【原文：Mexico's government will gradually reduce the standard work week to 40 hours, Labor and Social Security Minister Marath Bolanos said on Thursday, in a move expected to take full effect by January 2030.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/mexico-plans-gradual-reduction-40-hour-work-week-by-2030-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOXCLK3BKNMHHABLJNP44HKPR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:53:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称大规模国库储备是美国贸易谈判的工具之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财政部长表示，日本可以利用其持有的 1 万多亿美元的美国国债作为与华盛顿进行贸易谈判的一张牌，这也是日本作为美国的一个庞大债权国首次明确提高其影响力。【原文：Japan could use its $1 trillion-plus holdings of U.S. Treasuries as a card in trade talks with Washington, its finance minister said, raising explicitly for the first time its leverage as a massive creditor to the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3LMDXEWZVIU3NUCARL65LUAJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:20:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛勒战略公司连续第五个季度亏损，宣布发行 210 亿美元股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于所持加密货币出现未实现亏损，比特币最大的企业持有者战略公司周四公布了连续第五个季度的亏损报告。【原文：Strategy , the biggest corporate holder of bitcoin, reported a fifth consecutive quarterly loss on Thursday due to an unrealized loss on its cryptocurrency holdings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/saylors-strategy-reports-fifth-consecutive-quarterly-loss-announces-21-billion-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IZSL6STOZITJDH22XNMYG4P2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GoDaddy 季度收入增长，宣布回购 30 亿美元股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[GoDaddy 周四公布第一季度收入增长近 8%，原因是人工智能功能的增加促进了对其互联网托管服务的需求。【原文：GoDaddy on Thursday reported a nearly 8% increase in first-quarter revenue, as the addition of artificial intelligence features boosted demand for its internet hosting services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/godaddy-posts-rise-quarterly-revenue-announces-3-billion-share-buyback-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7WKHHFIWVLKLEB5Q7YNCMMIEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音生产放缓导致精神航空第一季度收入下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空航天供应商 Spirit AeroSystems 周四报告称，受主要客户波音公司大多数项目生产放缓的影响，第一季度营收下降。【原文：Aerospace supplier Spirit AeroSystems on Thursday reported a drop in first-quarter revenue, hurt by slower production across most programs at its key customer Boeing .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-aero-first-quarter-revenue-falls-amid-slower-boeing-production-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQUADVRJZJMCFAVIULBWM5IHNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税不确定，摩托罗拉解决方案公司预计第二季度利润疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[安全和企业安保服务供应商摩托罗拉解决方案公司周四预测第二季度利润低于华尔街预期，表明由于美国加征关税可能引发价格上涨，对其安全和安保服务的需求正在减少。【原文：Safety and enterprise security services provider Motorola Solutions forecast second-quarter profit below Wall Street estimates on Thursday, signaling dwindling demand for its safety and security services due to potential price increases triggered by the U.S. imposed tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/motorola-solutions-forecasts-weak-second-quarter-profit-amid-tariff-uncertainty-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LJFQYXFKBLOLDXNEYBAEVCISM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 科技补品]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGIR6YA5NNI3NGH5UYS46EQEWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:14:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瞻博网络公布季度收入增长，网络设备需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[瞻博网络（Juniper Networks）周四公布，受人工智能热潮推动，云计算客户对其网络设备的需求稳定，第一季度营收增长 11%。【原文：Juniper Networks reported an 11% rise in first-quarter revenue on Thursday, driven by steady demand from cloud customers for its networking equipment, fueled by the artificial intelligence boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/juniper-reports-rise-quarterly-revenue-robust-networking-gear-demand-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDYPGYF5JBJXHHFGARRWXTQDU4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:13:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软更换股东案律师事务所，聘用特朗普对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软聘请了一家律师事务所，对特朗普政府打击法律行业的行为进行反击，放弃了另一家选择与白宫和解的知名律师事务所。【原文：Microsoft has hired a law firm that is fighting back against the Trump administration's legal industry crackdown, dropping another prominent firm that chose to settle with the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-swaps-law-firms-shareholder-case-hiring-trump-adversary-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUWH25UPLBI7LDMLPAP5W7GX7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:07:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>