<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:05:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:05:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Engie 仍认为美国对可再生能源的需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电力集团 Engie 执行副总裁 Edouard Neviaski 周一表示，Engie 仍认为美国对可再生能源项目有着强烈的需求，并预计美国仍将是该公司投资组合中不可或缺的一部分。【原文：French power group Engie still sees strong appetite in the U.S. for renewable energy projects and expects the country to remain an integral part of the company's portfolio, Executive Vice President Edouard Neviaski said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/engie-still-sees-strong-us-appetite-renewables-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELTWDYHLIJMW5KJRO2IX7RH2ZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:54:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司与尼尔森签署新合作协议，结束争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[媒体巨头派拉蒙全球公司与尼尔森公司签署了一项新协议，尼尔森将为哥伦比亚广播公司的母公司提供跨平台的测量和分析服务，结束了双方长期以来的争执。【原文：Media giant Paramount Global and Nielsen have signed a new deal that would see the research firm provide measurement and analytics services across the CBS parent company's platforms, ending a long-running dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-global-nielsen-sign-new-partnership-ending-dispute-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTHJFNBQGVL3PJ4OKH5CPQP3DQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:50:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[厄瓜多尔总统宣布对墨西哥商品征收 27% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[厄瓜多尔总统丹尼尔-诺沃亚周一宣布，厄瓜多尔政府将对墨西哥商品征收 27% 的关税，以促进厄瓜多尔企业获得公平待遇。【原文：Ecuador's President Daniel Noboa announced on Monday that his government will apply a 27% tariff on Mexican goods in an effort to promote fair treatment for his country's companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/ecuador-president-announces-27-tariff-mexican-goods-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6E5Q7SSEOBKATJUJY5MMPF5KMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:49:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北美航空航天联盟敦促特朗普暂停对加拿大征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[北美最大的航空航天工会负责人周一告诉路透社记者，美国应该像对墨西哥那样暂停对加拿大征收关税，因为行业高管们正在权衡对飞机零部件和喷气式飞机征收新关税的影响。【原文：The United States should pause tariffs on Canada as it did on Mexico, the head of the largest North American aerospace union told Reuters on Monday, as industry executives weighed the impact of fresh duties on plane parts and jets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/north-american-aerospace-union-presses-trump-pause-tariffs-canada-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XM4IELDUL5NO3J2Y3GL2QHX7RQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普警告可能增加对华关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一警告说，他可能会在周六对中国征收的10%关税基础上再增加关税，而且 "我们将在未来24小时内与中国对话"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump warned on Monday he might increase tariffs on China beyond the 10% he imposed on Saturday and that "we will speak to China" probably over the next 24 hours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-warns-tariffs-china-may-increase-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BROJFHF225ISZPEMEJGUTBWR5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称马斯克只是在获得批准后才采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）只是在做获得批准的事情。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said billionaire Elon Musk, who the president had charged with shrinking the U.S. government, is only doing things that have approval.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-musk-only-acting-with-approval-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWM74NMTKNLLXEUINZIUDAKAB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:17:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称新成立的美国主权财富基金可能收购 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一签署了一项行政命令，命令美国财政部和商务部创建一个主权财富基金，并表示该基金可能会收购 TikTok。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Monday ordering the U.S. Treasury and Commerce Departments to create a sovereign wealth fund and said it may purchase TikTok.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/trump-signs-executive-order-create-sovereign-wealth-fund-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5OE4GQQB5IQFDOPOC2IJRUW5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢比奥称赞巴拿马退出中国基础设施计划的举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务卿马可-鲁比奥（Marco Rubio）周一对巴拿马决定不再参与中国的全球基础设施计划表示欢迎，并称此举是巴拿马与美国关系 "向前迈出的一大步"。【原文：U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio on Monday welcomed Panama's decision to let its participation in China's global infrastructure plan expire, calling the move "a great step forward" for its ties with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/rubio-hails-panamas-move-exit-chinese-infrastructure-plan-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKHH7GP3XJPNPLSEQMH2BHXSSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:51:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国黄金磁铁：银行从以亚洲为中心的枢纽空运金条，从溢价中获益]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球金银银行正将黄金从迪拜和香港等迎合亚洲消费者的交易中心空运到美国，以利用美国黄金期货相对于现货价格的异常高溢价。【原文：Global bullion banks are flying gold into the United States from trading hubs catering to Asian consumers, including Dubai and Hong Kong, to capitalize on the unusually high premium that U.S. gold futures are enjoying over spot prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-gold-magnet-banks-fly-bullion-asia-focused-hubs-benefit-premium-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y56WLW4P6RLEPC6CYBXSZQ3EVE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利菲拉格慕与前巴宝莉首席执行官戈贝蒂分道扬镳]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品集团 Salvatore Ferragamo 表示，首席执行官 Marco Gobbetti 在执掌集团三年多一点的时间后，将于下月卸任。【原文：Italian luxury goods group Salvatore Ferragamo said CEO Marco Gobbetti would step down next month after little over three years in charge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/italys-ferragamo-says-ceo-gobbetti-step-down-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGRUMWMCABIQVLIUHSPSKE2RX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[局长被解雇后，美国消费者局不会在法庭上为拜登时代的规则辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局在其局长被唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇后，拒绝在法庭上为拜登政府时期的规定辩护。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau is refusing to defend Biden administration-era rules in court after its director was fired by President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-bureau-wont-defend-biden-era-rules-court-after-chief-was-fired-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJAIPGQBXZNMNF6OCUC2MIATQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，欧洲几乎吸收了美国上个月所有的液化天然气出口量]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融公司LSEG的初步数据显示，由于寒冷天气推动了需求增长，以及超冷天然气价格上涨，1月份美国对欧洲的液化天然气（LNG）出口量猛增。【原文：U.S. exports of liquefied natural gas (LNG) to Europe jumped in January as cold weather drove up demand and prices for the superchilled gas rose, preliminary data from financial firm LSEG showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/europe-soaked-up-nearly-all-us-lng-exports-last-month-data-show-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IO2NCH62ZNLBHIL2D2544GB2SY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税标题刺激市场波动激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对加拿大、墨西哥和中国采取的初步关税行动引发了市场波动性的上升，从股票到货币的各类资产都急于防范波动的加剧。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's initial tariff actions against Canada, Mexico and China sparked a rise in broad market volatility and a rush to take guard against increased ructions across asset classes from stocks to currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-volatility-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DZJLKZLIZP3BEWEIRG3PIAOAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:13:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard 削减费用；预计 2025 年将为投资者节省 3.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[资产管理公司先锋（Vanguard）周一表示，该公司正在降低旗下所有基金的投资成本，这是有史以来规模最大的一次削减，预计今年将为投资者节省超过 3.5 亿美元。【原文：Asset manager Vanguard said on Monday it was lowering the cost of investing across its fund lineup in its largest cut ever and estimated that this would translate into savings of more than $350 million for its investors this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/vanguard-slashes-fees-expects-its-investors-will-save-350-million-2025-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJHZMQYT6VJIVBR6OQFEOUS5EE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从尊尼获加到科罗娜啤酒，大型酒类企业可能受到关税打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对来自墨西哥、加拿大和中国的商品全面征收新关税之后，包括尊尼获加（Johnnie Walker）和科罗娜（Corona）啤酒在内的酒精饮料制造商可能会被卷入一场潜在的贸易战。【原文：Makers of alcoholic beverages, including Johnnie Walker and Corona beer, could be caught in the crosshairs of a potential trade war after U.S. President Donald Trump imposed sweeping new tariffs on goods from Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/johnnie-walker-corona-beer-major-alcohol-firms-could-see-tariff-hit-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">662YP3PQIZN7VNCN3FEYU6S7LM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯表示，在关税不确定的情况下，美联储在利率问题上可以保持耐心]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周一表示，由于特朗普政府宣布的新贸易关税可能会推高通胀压力，央行目前并不急于降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said Monday there's no urgency for the central bank to lower rates right now, as new trade tariffs announced by the Trump Administration could drive up inflation pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-collins-says-fed-can-be-patient-rates-amid-tariff-uncertainty-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWKPVRGWDZLMFPN5KUOB5BZDPY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:26:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》称，加拿大对墨西哥式关税缓和并不乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约时报》周一援引一位加拿大政府高级官员的话说，加拿大对能否获得像墨西哥一样的为期一个月的美国关税暂缓期并不乐观。【原文：Canada is not optimistic it can get the same kind of one-month reprieve from U.S. tariffs that was granted to Mexico, the New York Times cited a senior Canadian government official as saying on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-not-optimistic-about-mexico-style-tariff-reprieve-says-new-york-times-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHLOKQWTOJJDBNG6MYBHLTBX2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:23:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月建筑支出超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受独户住宅建设的推动，12 月份美国建筑支出增幅超过预期，但高抵押贷款利率可能会抑制新住宅建设的进一步增长。【原文：U.S. construction spending increased more than expected in December, boosted by single-family homebuilding, but high mortgage rates could curb further gains in new residential construction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-construction-spending-beats-expectations-december-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">725L5EFDJ5MF5HZCPEXZPVAEGM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:42:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安大略省在最新一次加拿大关税抗议中取消了 Starlink 合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大安大略省周一宣布取消与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的星链公司（Starlink）签订的价值 1 亿加元（约合 6812 万美元）的合同，这是对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布加征关税的最新报复性举措。【原文：The Canadian province of Ontario on Monday announced it was cancelling a C$100 million ($68.12 million) contract with Elon Musk's Starlink, the latest retaliatory move against tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ontario-cancels-starlink-contract-latest-canadian-tariffs-protest-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRV34E4FEJKQ3FEJF63YWULOPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税推动华尔街下跌，美元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收关税只是全球贸易战的开端，会抑制经济增长，导致全球股市大跌，华尔街周一开盘走低。【原文：Wall Street opened lower on Monday following a worldwide selloff driven by concern that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on Canada, Mexico and China are just the opening salvo in a global trade war that would curb economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3ZA3VVVUVIFLOYHVWYC77HHHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥向投资者作出保证，坚称可承受金融冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥财政部长罗赫略-拉米雷斯-德拉奥（Rogelio Ramirez de la O）周一表示，在美国宣布对墨西哥商品征收25%的关税后，墨西哥有足够的资源吸收金融冲击并应对全球挑战。【原文：Mexico has enough resources to absorb financial shocks and navigate global challenges after the United States announced 25% tariffs on its goods, Finance Minister Rogelio Ramirez de la O said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-offers-assurances-investors-insists-it-can-absorb-financial-shocks-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKLNDRKDN5PXXADTZGR4OSIZF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:12:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1 月份美国制造业反弹；投入品支付价格指数大幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于订单强劲，美国制造业在 1 月份出现了两年多来的首次增长，但衡量工厂支付原材料价格的一项指标却稳中有升，而且在唐纳德-特朗普总统于上周末对来自加拿大和墨西哥的商品加征关税之后，价格可能会进一步上涨。【原文：U.S. manufacturing grew for the first time in more than two years in January amid strong orders, but a measure of prices paid by factories for raw materials rose solidly, and more increases are likely after President Donald Trump imposed tariffs on goods from Canada and Mexico at the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-rebounds-january-inputs-prices-paid-measure-surges-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6U7KBK7FORI2HGTYNHKLZLN3SA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:05:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在瑞典和挪威市场份额下降，马斯克阴影笼罩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的汽车登记数据显示，特斯拉一月份在瑞典和挪威的市场份额有所下降，这家美国电动汽车制造商在亿万富翁首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）高调涉足政坛后面临着人气考验。【原文：Tesla lost market share in Sweden and Norway in January, car registration data showed on Monday as the U.S. electric vehicle maker faces a test of popularity following billionaire CEO Elon Musk's high-profile foray into politics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-loses-market-share-sweden-norway-musk-looms-large-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AO55U35DYZJVPPK52R2DGA3GFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼影业从哥伦比亚广播公司收回《幸运之轮》和《危情时刻》的发行权]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼影业公司周一在致哥伦比亚广播公司的一封信中表示，由于哥伦比亚广播公司制片厂未能履行合同条款，索尼影业公司已承担起热门电视节目《幸运之轮》和《危情时速》的全球发行职能。【原文：Sony Pictures has assumed global distribution functions for hit TV shows "Wheel of Fortune" and "Jeopardy!" citing failure by CBS Studios to live up to contract terms, the company said in a letter to CBS on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/sony-pictures-takes-back-distribution-rights-wheel-fortune-jeopardy-cbs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SYPHVA2VJNKVO6TCDGF6HZITQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:51:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特一月份美国销量下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特公司周一表示，由于内燃（ICE）汽车需求下降，该公司一月份在美国的销量下降了 6.3%。【原文：Ford's January sales in the U.S. fell 6.3% owing to lower demand for its internal combustion (ICE) vehicles, the company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-us-sales-dip-january-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHKGOZWG7JIP7KXHE6BRYMWMCE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战风险削弱信心，加拿大 1 月份工厂采购经理指数下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国贸易关税迫在眉睫，加拿大制造业活动在 1 月份的增长速度有所放缓，这降低了人们对前景的信心，尽管客户为抢在美国征税之前采取行动，导致出口订单出现了 17 个月以来的首次增长。【原文：Canadian manufacturing activity increased at a slower pace in January as looming U.S. trade tariffs reduced confidence in the outlook, even as moves by clients to get ahead of the taxes led to the first increase in export orders in 17 months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadian-factory-pmi-dips-january-trade-war-risk-dents-confidence-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AY3LHA7QENKJHM5HBQOHSA5SD4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在全球需求的推动下，Cboe 计划将股票交易时间延长至 24 小时]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cboe 全球市场公司（Cboe Global Markets）周一宣布，计划将美国股票交易扩展至每周五天、每天 24 小时的形式，以满足全球对美国股票市场的需求。【原文：Cboe Global Markets on Monday announced plans to expand U.S. equities trading to a 24-hour, five-days-a-week format to meet the global demand for the country's stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cboe-plans-extend-equities-trading-24-hours-amid-global-demand-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HRRGVHBARPCFKJY6QNV2G3CPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RTX 前首席执行官格雷戈里-海耶斯卸任董事长一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[RTX 前首席执行官格雷戈里-海耶斯（Gregory Hayes）周一表示，将辞去执行董事长和董事会成员的职务。【原文：Former RTX CEO Gregory Hayes will step down as executive chairman and member of the board, the aerospace and defense major said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/former-rtx-ceo-gregory-hayes-step-down-chairman-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGIH7ZEJD5OTRJSNEUNS2PN52A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚 Ecopetrol 公司与西方石油公司在二叠纪盆地续建合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚能源公司 Ecopetrol 周一表示，它已与西方石油公司达成协议，续签其在美国得克萨斯州二叠纪盆地的石油合资企业。【原文：Colombian energy company Ecopetrol said on Monday it has reached an agreement to renew its oil joint venture with Occidental Petroleum in the U.S. Permian basin in Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/colombias-ecopetrol-renews-joint-venture-with-occidental-petroleum-permian-basin-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISWNIR63UBNHNPUPHZ7HSRXTE4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达阵交易Robinhood 推出超级碗预测合约]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 周一表示，该公司将推出赛事合同，让美国用户就超级碗的比赛结果下注，试图利用美国最具标志性的体育赛事之一的博彩狂热。【原文：Robinhood is rolling out event contracts to let U.S. users wager on the outcome of the Super Bowl clash, it said on Monday, seeking to tap into the betting mania around one of the most iconic sporting events in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trading-touchdowns-robinhood-launches-super-bowl-prediction-contracts-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWFTR5WHGFMRDJTU4C53C4EDFI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>