<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:35:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:35:52 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：欧元不惧关税，但债券却裹足不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMW4GCEYM5IH7EKPVBXBNYDV5Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:13:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kenvue 首席执行官卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰诺制药公司 Kenvue 周一表示，Thibaut Mongon 已辞去首席执行官和董事会成员的职务。【原文：Tylenol maker Kenvue said on Monday Thibaut Mongon had stepped down as chief executive officer and board member.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kenvue-ceo-steps-down-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC6ALOAGPNKULPBV7W3SRMGY4I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[获得安宏资本支持的 NIQ Global 在美国 IPO 的目标估值高达 71 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[消费者情报公司 NIQ Global 在美国首次公开募股的目标估值高达 70.8 亿美元，因为在经济放缓之后，私募股权支持的上市企业开始大量涌入。【原文：Consumer intelligence company NIQ Global is targeting a valuation of up to $7.08 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, as private equity-backed listings start to trickle in after a slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/advent-backed-niq-global-targets-up-71-billion-valuation-us-ipo-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCYDMA7AJNIQRNU4QTSBXEPS5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[教科书出版商麦格劳-希尔（McGraw Hill）在美国首次公开募股中的目标估值为 42 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国出版商麦格劳-希尔（McGraw Hill）周一表示，其首次公开募股（IPO）的目标估值为 42 亿美元。【原文：U.S. publisher McGraw Hill is targeting a valuation of $4.2 billion in its IPO, the company said on Monday, adding to a recent line up of public market hopefuls that are looking to tap an improvement in investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/textbook-publisher-mcgraw-hill-targets-42-billion-valuation-us-ipo-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUROFNZHSROHPCHUDEE3ARWD3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:34:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币法案将于本周推进，使该行业更接近主流]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，随着一系列对行业有利的法案在国会取得进展，加密货币行业将向主流化迈进一步，为数字资产有可能进一步融入传统金融铺平道路。【原文：The crypto industry will take a step closer to going mainstream this week as a series of industry-friendly bills progress through Congress, paving the way for digital assets to potentially be further integrated into traditional finance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/crypto-bills-set-advance-this-week-take-industry-closer-mainstream-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLVEJEMRLNJIXPOAV7OT3HAKKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货在数据和财报大潮前因新关税威胁而摇摆不定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周一下滑，原因是唐纳德-特朗普总统针对欧盟和墨西哥的新关税威胁，在本周经济数据和第二季度财报密集公布之前，打压了投资者的情绪。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Monday, as President Donald Trump's fresh tariff threats targeting the European Union and Mexico dampened investor sentiment ahead of a week packed with economic data and second-quarter earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-wobble-fresh-tariff-threats-ahead-data-earnings-deluge-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSNYQR4X5VOSVBULHCSDVWTF4Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:17:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：为什么特朗普推动美联储政策利率保持在 1%会给美国经济带来麻烦？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，美联储应将基准利率设定在 1%，以降低政府借贷成本，从而使政府能够为其支出和减税法案所预期的高额且不断增加的赤字提供资金。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump says the Federal Reserve should set its benchmark interest rate at 1% to lower government borrowing costs, allowing the administration to finance the high and rising deficits expected from his spending and tax-cut bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/why-trumps-push-1-fed-policy-rate-could-spell-trouble-us-economy-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D56UFUSZFBMODKZG3S7JZ44W44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:15:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大量国债即将发行？货币市场基金说 "来吧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在提高债务上限后的未来 1 年半时间里，预计将有超过 1 万亿美元的美国短期票据涌入市场，因为财政部在为国家巨额财政赤字提供资金的同时，还要补充其减少的现金余额。【原文：More than $1 trillion in U.S. short-term bills are expected to flood the market over the next 1-1/2 years following the increase in the debt ceiling, as the Treasury replenishes its diminished cash balance while funding the country's huge fiscal deficit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/slew-t-bills-coming-money-market-funds-say-bring-em-on-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UU3RM2C4JFN7DLZNRPP6WZIIUQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:11:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普监管下的美国银行并购希望重燃]]></title><description><![CDATA[据金融高管和分析师称，北方信托的收购猜测重新燃起了业界对美国大型银行和地区性银行之间交易的希望，推动了可能导致合并的探索性对话。【原文：Takeover speculation in Northern Trust has revived industry hopes of deals among large U.S. and regional banks, propelling exploratory conversations that could lead to consolidation, according to financial executives and analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/us-bank-ma-hopes-revive-under-trump-regulators-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXP5Z75JQJNOPEQ3UWATJJQS2U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 投资者与扎克伯格因涉嫌侵犯隐私权，将在价值 80 亿美元的庭审中一决雌雄]]></title><description><![CDATA[马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）预计将作为明星证人出席本周开始的一场价值 80 亿美元的不寻常审判，这位 Meta 首席执行官被指控将 Facebook 作为非法企业运营，允许未经用户同意获取其数据。【原文：Mark Zuckerberg is expected to appear as a star witness in an unusual $8 billion trial that kicks off this week at which the Meta CEO is accused of operating Facebook as an illegal enterprise that allowed users' data to be harvested without their consent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-investors-zuckerberg-square-off-8-billion-trial-over-alleged-privacy-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFK6NH227BPVHPWBLNNUDTFW6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的支出法案可能会增加保险公司的成本，缩小医疗补助的覆盖范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的支出法案将提高行政成本，并使联合健康保险公司（UnitedHealthcare）和 CVS Health 旗下的 Aetna 等经营医疗补助健康计划的保险公司更难管理成本。【原文：President Donald Trump's spending bill is set to raise administrative costs and make managing costs more difficult for insurers like UnitedHealthcare and CVS Health's Aetna that operate Medicaid health plans, experts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trumps-spending-bill-will-likely-boost-costs-insurers-shrink-medicaid-coverage-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYITXGZ62FJ6VKSIH6EJGW7BWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟和韩国寻求美国贸易协议以减轻关税打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普表示，他将从下月起对从欧盟和墨西哥进口的大部分商品征收 30% 的关税，并对日本和韩国发出类似警告。【原文：Trump said he would impose a 30% tariff on most imports from the EU and Mexico from next month, adding to similar warnings for Japan and South Korea.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/eu-south-korea-seek-us-trade-deals-soften-tariff-blow-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2I7D3VM4FNL5IMIP2GLDA6JNE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:52:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币交易所急于将特朗普的硬币上市--造成许多输家和一些大赢家]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Coinbase 在其网站上向用户保证，在允许任何新数字货币进行交易之前，都会对其进行 "严格 "的审查。这有时是一个漫长的过程，目的是通过审查与项目相关的人员以及市场操纵或其他欺诈行为的风险来保护客户。【原文：Crypto exchange Coinbase assures users on its website that it puts any new digital coin through "rigorous" vetting before allowing it to trade. It's an at-times lengthy process meant to protect customers by examining the people connected to the project and the risk of market manipulation or other scams.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/crypto-exchanges-rushed-list-trumps-coin-leaving-many-losers-some-big-winners-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHZ4EQ5FKNO6PCM2JBUZDIRED4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:52:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报道称 Broadcom 放弃在西班牙投资微型芯片工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[据欧洲新闻社周日援引未具名消息人士的话报道，由于与西班牙政府的谈判破裂，美国芯片制造商博通公司（Broadcom）退出了在西班牙投资微型芯片工厂的计划。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Broadcom has pulled out of plans to invest in a microchip plant in Spain as talks with the government have broken down, news agency Europa Press reported on Sunday citing unidentified sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/broadcom-scraps-microchip-plant-investment-spain-report-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HPX6BM5MJLCTI3ZEBE7ZG4ZY4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼要求电子商务平台向卖家征税]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一公布的新规定，印尼财政部将要求电子商务平台对中小卖家的销售额征收所得税。【原文：Indonesia's finance ministry will require e-commerce platforms to collect and pass on an income tax on sales made by small- and medium-sized sellers, according to new regulations published on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-require-e-commerce-platforms-collect-tax-sellers-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGEMZHF445PR3LODE7LDSUQPZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 08:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[G20 金融监督机构提出气候计划，但在分歧中按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，二十国集团（G20）的金融稳定监督机构就如何应对气候风险提出了一项新计划，但由于美国的退缩而暂停了进一步的政策工作，这对推进针对气候相关风险的统一金融政策的努力构成了考验。【原文：The G20's financial stability watchdog delivered a new plan on how to tackle climate risks on Monday, but paused further policy work amid a retreat by the United States that has tested efforts to advance a united financial policy on climate-related risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/g20s-financial-watchdog-lays-out-climate-plan-presses-pause-amid-divisions-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5RBNPC3GRIPXONG7IC4B7V67M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 08:17:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布加征关税后德国汽车制造商股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁从 8 月 1 日起对欧盟进口产品征收 30% 的关税，但并未提及对汽车的特殊待遇，德国汽车制造商的股票周一下跌。【原文：Shares in Germany's carmakers fell on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened a 30% tariff on EU imports from August 1, with no mentioning of a special treatment for autos, which remain subject to a 27.5% duty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shares-german-carmakers-fall-after-trump-tariff-announcement-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUT47CKO3RPULHPGG3UEW7WSCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁对欧盟和墨西哥征收新关税，欧洲股市下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最近威胁要对欧盟和墨西哥征收高额关税，令投资者惶恐不安，欧洲股市周一下跌，汽车行业领跌。【原文：European shares fell on Monday, led by automobiles, as the U.S. President Donald Trump's latest threat to impose steep tariffs on the European Union and Mexico kept investors on edge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-shares-fall-trumps-new-tariff-threats-eu-mexico-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWGLA75BGRIOTBOLUW3AUFXVOM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克表示不支持特斯拉与 xAI 合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克周一在 X 上发表文章称，他不支持特斯拉与他的人工智能初创公司 xAI 合并。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk said in a Monday post on X he does not support a merger between Tesla and his artificial intelligence startup xAI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-says-he-does-not-support-merger-between-tesla-xai-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYV7VLDNORPPDNVZW4ANEJHEJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:23:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员称欧盟与美国即将达成良好贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易委员马洛斯-塞夫科维奇（Maros Sefcovic）周一表示，欧盟和美国的贸易谈判正接近一个对双方都有利的结果。【原文：The European Union and United States are approaching a good outcome for both sides in their trade talks, EU trade commissioner Maros Sefcovic said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-us-approaching-good-trade-deal-eu-commissioner-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMPBH6P7CNODRL5TVSRSJBULBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度航空致命空难调查 "远未结束" 首席执行官在初步报告发布数日后表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度航空公司首席执行官坎贝尔-威尔逊（Campbell Wilson）周一在一份内部备忘录中说，印度航空公司对上个月在艾哈迈达巴德市失事的梦幻客机的调查 "远未结束"，并补充说，印度航空公司仍对进一步的调查持开放态度，并告诫不要 "过早下结论"。【原文：The investigation of the crashed Air India Dreamliner in Ahmedabad city last month is "far from over", the airline's Chief Executive Campbell Wilson said in an internal memo on Monday, adding that the airline remains open to further inquiries and cautioned against "premature conclusions".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fatal-air-india-crash-probe-far-over-says-ceo-days-after-prelim-report-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKEJSG3LCNKF3IZOS5OPRUZEHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国准备命令航空公司检查波音飞机的燃料开关]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国交通部对外媒体发言人周一表示，韩国交通部正准备命令国内所有运营波音喷气机的航空公司根据美国联邦航空管理局2018年的一项建议检查燃油开关。【原文：South Korea's transport ministry is preparing to order all airlines in the country that operate Boeing jets to examine fuel switches in accordance with a 2018 advisory from the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration, the ministry's foreign media spokesperson said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/south-korea-preparing-order-airlines-check-fuel-switches-boeing-jets-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD7XJSFFDBPHNDTHBEM6FL7M44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葛兰素史克寻求 FDA 批准扩大 RSV 疫苗在成人中的使用范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国制药商葛兰素史克公司（GSK）周一表示，它已向美国食品和药物管理局提交了一份申请，要求将其呼吸道合胞病毒（RSV）疫苗的使用范围扩大到50岁以下的高危成人。【原文：British drugmaker GSK said on Monday it had submitted an application to the U.S. Food and Drug Administration to extend the use of its respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) vaccine to adults under the age of 50 at a higher risk of the disease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/gsk-seeks-fda-nod-expanded-use-rsv-vaccine-adults-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQUQ2VNK4FMDFAN2DOIFEOBQGE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行将标普 500 指数年底目标价上调至 6250 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行资本市场（RBC Capital Markets）周日将 S&amp;P 500 指数的年终目标从 5730 点上调至 6250 点，这是今年以来第二次上调目标，理由是投资者情绪更加浓厚，对 2026 年经济前景的关注度也越来越高。【原文：RBC Capital Markets on Sunday raised its S&amp;P 500 index year-end target to 6,250 from 5,730, its second hike this year, citing stronger investor sentiment and growing focus on 2026 economic prospects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rbc-lifts-sp-500-year-end-price-target-6250-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOIWXTCXEVN3VLJHRGBZKLY7XE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡四年来最大规模首次公开募股后，数据中心 NTT DC REIT 首秀不温不火]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡的 NTT DC REIT 是一家数据中心房地产投资信托公司，在新加坡四年来最大的首次公开募股中，该公司借助人工智能的热潮募集了 7.73 亿美元，但周一的首次公开募股却表现平平。【原文：Singapore's NTT DC REIT , a data centre real estate investment trust, had a lacklustre market debut on Monday after riding a wave of AI interest to raise $773 million in the city-state's biggest IPO in four years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/data-centre-ntt-dc-reit-opens-flat-debut-after-singapores-biggest-ipo-4-years-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SU2QFRFARJPPKEK6VXM4SRXVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:17:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国有条件批准 Synopsys 收购 Ansys]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据中国市场监管部门周一发布的一份声明，该部门有条件地批准了软件公司 Synopsys 收购 Ansys 的交易。【原文：China's market regulator has granted a conditional approval for software firm Synopsys to acquire Ansys , according to a statement released by the regulator on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-grants-conditional-approval-synopsys-acquire-ansys-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUDCYV5T4BKWLOHLFFM4HIK6QQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利外长称欧盟准备向美国征收 21 亿欧元关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利外交部长安东尼奥-塔亚尼（Antonio Tajani）周一在接受报纸采访时说，如果两国无法达成贸易协议，欧盟已经准备好了一份对美国商品征收价值210亿欧元（约合245.2亿美元）关税的清单。【原文：The European Union has already prepared a list of tariffs worth 21 billion euros ($24.52 billion) on U.S. goods if the two countries fail to reach a trade deal, Italy's Foreign Minister Antonio Tajani said in a newspaper interview on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-ready-hit-us-with-21-bln-euro-tariff-list-italy-foreign-minister-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEBP2R6S5FNORMBGPFPURWZ5DQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[扭亏为盈一年后，博柏利投资者看到了进步]]></title><description><![CDATA[乔希-舒尔曼（Josh Schulman）就任巴宝莉首席执行官一年后，受命扭转这一英国奢侈品牌的颓势，尽管销售额仍在下降，但投资者对复苏的早期迹象表示满意。【原文：A year after Josh Schulman became Burberry's CEO with a mandate to turn the British luxury brand around, investors say they're pleased with early signs of recovery even though sales are still falling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/year-into-turnaround-burberry-investors-see-progress-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPHFAEEPNFNI3KWFNK7K3MMKEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标利用关税抢占头条的艺术]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDOVTZY44JNYBPJUWOMQAEKRZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 04:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币首次突破 12 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，比特币首次突破 12 万美元关口，成为全球最大的加密货币的一个重要里程碑，因为投资者押注于本周该行业长期寻求的政策胜利。【原文：Bitcoin crossed the $120,000 level for the first time on Monday, marking a major milestone for the world's largest cryptocurrency as investors bet on long-sought policy wins for the industry this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-crosses-120000-record-high-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJ4D6Q4LOBLHPINEEFAIFQ3JC4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 03:54:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>