<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 18:05:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 18:05:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，默多克支持的 REA 将收购英国 Rightmove 的报价提高到近 79 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，由鲁伯特-默多克（Rupert Murdoch）的新闻集团控股的 REA 集团已将其对英国房地产门户网站 Rightmove 的收购要约提高到约 59 亿英镑（78.6 亿美元）。【原文：REA Group , majority-owned by Rupert Murdoch's News Corp , has sweetened its takeover offer for Britain's real estate portal Rightmove to about 5.9 billion pounds ($7.86 billion), the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/murdochs-rea-raises-offer-rightmove-nearly-79-bln-ft-reports-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBWBOQKIFBOKTGXQH3AIHABVRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国钢铁工人联合会会议上，成员和领导者淡化了选举分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周举行的钢铁工人联合会（United Steelworkers）工会官员会议上，总统政治被排除在议程之外，这与以往大选年的聚会有所不同，也表明了美国工人联合会成员与工会老板在候选人问题上的分歧。【原文：At a meeting of United Steelworkers union officials this week, presidential politics was off the agenda, a departure from past election-year gatherings and a sign of the division between USW members and union bosses over the candidates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/united-steelworkers-conference-members-leaders-play-down-election-divide-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4EFXTHTLFKPZGFSKF4FPMTKAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国药房福利管理公司为何受到抨击？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五表示，它正在起诉美国三大药房福利管理公司，指控它们滥用权力，操纵药品供应链，人为抬高胰岛素的成本。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Friday it was suing the country's three largest pharmacy benefit managers, accusing them of abusing their power and rigging the pharmaceutical supply chain to artificially inflate the cost of insulin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/why-are-us-pharmacy-benefit-managers-under-fire-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URIDWKGU2ZN6JBDYGBAOZS25WA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:25:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼表示，基于高于目标的通胀数据，对大幅降息持有异议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周五表示，她不同意美国央行本周降息半个百分点，而是赞成降息四分之一个百分点，因为通胀率仍高于2%的目标，她担心公众会将更大的举措误解为 "过早地宣布胜利"。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman said on Friday she dissented over the U.S. central bank's half-percentage-point interest rate cut this week, favoring a quarter-percentage-point reduction instead, because inflation remains above the 2% target and she worried the public would misinterpret the larger move as "a premature declaration of victory."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bowman-says-dissent-large-rate-cut-based-above-target-inflation-data-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REGMG52F7RKWTOBO4RLRRVQLVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 董事长 Elkann 因涉嫌税务欺诈被扣押 7,500 万欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利都灵检察院周五表示，一名意大利法官因涉嫌税务欺诈调查，扣押了包括 Stellantis 和法拉利主席约翰-埃尔坎在内的五人价值约 7500 万欧元（8400 万美元）的资产。【原文：An Italian judge has seized assets worth around 75 million euros ($84 million) from five people including Stellantis and Ferrari Chair John Elkann over an investigation into alleged tax fraud, the Turin prosecutor's office said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-chair-elkann-targeted-75-mln-euro-seizure-over-alleged-tax-fraud-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZUQ6YHO7NOGBDZOAWD7AZNGZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:42:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席沃勒尔疲软的通胀数据巩固了降息 50 个基点的理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）是该央行为抑制通胀而加息的斗争中较为激烈的声音之一，他说他支持本周进行更大幅度的降息，因为他现在担心物价上涨的速度会低于美联储的目标。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Christopher Waller, one of the more ardent voices in the central bank's battle to hike interest rates to tame inflation, said he supported a larger rate cut this week because he is now worried the pace of price increases is undershooting the Fed's target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-waller-weak-inflation-data-cemented-case-50-basis-point-cut-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ESRCQVUJZLIJCH5RRWQGHACUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准阿斯利康的流感疫苗用于自我注射]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周五表示，已批准阿斯利康公司的流感鼻腔喷雾疫苗用于自我注射，使其成为首款可供患者自我注射的疫苗。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Friday it has approved AstraZeneca's influenza nasal spray vaccine for self-administration, making it the first of its kind that patients can give themselves.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-astrazenecas-flu-vaccine-self-administration-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J63EYEL25RKTVEJ2TYCACOUUV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:22:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会就胰岛素价格过高起诉药品 "看门人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五起诉了美国三大药房福利管理公司，指控它们引导糖尿病患者使用价格更高的胰岛素，以便从制药公司获得数百万美元的回扣。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission sued the country's three largest pharmacy benefit managers on Friday, accusing them of steering diabetes patients towards higher priced insulin in order to reap millions of dollars in rebates from pharmaceutical companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-ftc-sues-drug-gatekeepers-over-high-insulin-prices-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEBJZP3U6BN6RIL4SJMO5ZVXRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼亚法院认定可就主持人裁员起诉 Meta 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯尼亚一家法院周五裁定，Facebook 母公司 Meta 可在这个东非国家因承包商解雇数十名内容审核员而被起诉。【原文：A Kenyan court ruled on Friday that Facebook's parent company Meta could be sued in the East African nation over the dismissal of dozens of content moderators by a contractor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/kenya-court-rules-meta-can-be-sued-over-layoffs-by-contractor-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2YUVNLTWNK3LFOALYZTY6BS34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:32:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院以微弱票数通过废除拜登政府的环保局尾气排放规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院周五以微弱优势投票通过废除 3 月份通过的清洁汽车规则，该规则规定到 2032 年将整个车队的尾气排放量在 2026 年的基础上减少 50%。【原文：The U.S. House of Representatives on Friday voted narrowly to repeal clean vehicle rules adopted in March to cut fleetwide tailpipe emissions by 50% over 2026 levels by 2032.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-votes-narrowly-repeal-biden-administration-epa-tailpipe-emissions-rules-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZ3T2SR6MZMRZHVVXQEK5OBAUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:30:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航空公司称首架空中客车 A321XLR 将于 10 月下半月交付]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司最远程窄体喷气机 A321XLR 的首次交付将推迟到 10 月份，这显然与该飞机制造商的交付目标相差数周。【原文：The first delivery of Airbus' longest-range narrowbody jet, the A321XLR, is poised to slip into October, apparently missing the planemaker's delivery target by several weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/first-airbus-a321xlr-delivery-due-second-half-october-airline-says-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTIKSGPUYJMIJEZSDTQFUMOGJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:29:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司寻求推迟恢复每天两班的中国航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司周五要求美国交通部允许其推迟恢复每天两班从美国飞往中国的航班，理由是世界上最大的两个经济体之间的旅行需求滞后。【原文：American Airlines on Friday asked the U.S. Transportation Department to allow it to delay resuming two daily flights to China from the United States, citing lagging travel demand between the world's two largest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-seeks-delay-resuming-two-daily-china-flights-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPMF6KKZNNLEBJ7EL63SHCLM3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局批准泽弗拉公司治疗罕见遗传病的方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周五表示，美国食品和药物管理局批准了 Zevra Therapeutics 公司治疗一种罕见致命遗传性疾病的药物，使其成为首个获得批准的治疗该疾病的药物。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved Zevra Therapeutics' drug for a rare and fatal genetic disorder, making it the first treatment to get a nod for the condition, the health regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-zevras-genetic-disorder-treatment-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH47VH3WKFPFZLFKKNMIZP75AY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:14:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美联储放宽银行资本计划面临联邦存款保险公司的反击]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）对一项具有里程碑意义的银行资本提案的淡化版本正面临着来自银行业最高监管机构联邦存款保险公司（Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation）的阻力。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve's watered-down version of a landmark bank capital proposal is facing resistance from the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, a top banking regulator, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-relaxed-bank-capital-plan-faces-fdic-pushback-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">456BC4GOWZOATO2NSL3VF3VEN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肥胖药数据令人失望，诺和诺德股价下跌逾 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德周五下跌超过4%，创下自8月10日以来的最低水平，因为这家丹麦制药商报告了其肥胖症试验性药物monlunabant的2a期试验结果低于市场预期。【原文：Novo Nordisk fell more than 4% on Friday to their lowest level since Aug. 10 after the Danish drugmaker reported results from a Phase 2a trial of its experimental obesity pill monlunabant that came in below market expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-shares-drop-more-than-4-disappointing-obesity-pill-data-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63FEX22WCZNHHNQ6G75LMKVG3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债券基金连续第 16 周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至9月18日的一周里，美国债券基金连续第16周吸引资金流入，原因是市场预期美联储将在本周的会议上大幅降息。【原文：U.S. bond funds attracted inflows for a 16th straight week in the week ended Sept. 18, on expectations that the Federal Reserve would deliver an outsized rate cut in its meeting during the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-bond-funds-draw-inflows-16th-straight-week-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TB3U7N2YERLXBG7M2ZP36JFW3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 13:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[iPhone 预购需求激增，俄罗斯人未受价格上涨影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位经销商周五告诉路透社记者，俄罗斯对新款 iPhone 的预购需求比上一代高出 15%，尽管价格比西方至少贵 50%。【原文：Pre-order demand in Russia for the new iPhone is 15% higher than for its predecessor, one reseller told Reuters on Friday, even though it is at least 50% more expensive than in the West.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russians-unfazed-by-higher-prices-iphone-pre-order-demand-soars-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ND4K6UWUYBKDTH6RAREWFDXDBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 13:32:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储封锁期将随着沃勒周五在 CNBC 的亮相而解除]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周早些时候的一次关键利率决议之后，美联储围绕美国央行会议的公众评论禁制期于周五解除，美联储理事克里斯-沃勒（Chris Waller）将于美国东部时间上午 11:30（格林尼治标准时间 15:30）出席 CNBC 会议。【原文：The Federal Reserve's blackout period on public comment around meetings of the U.S. central bank lifts on Friday after a key interest rate decision earlier in the week, with Governor Chris Waller scheduled to appear on CNBC at 11:30 a.m. EDT (1530 GMT).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-blackout-period-lifts-with-waller-due-cnbc-1130-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THGP2CN7VVPEBJVERHSG2LI7I4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 13:24:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大零售销售额超过 7 月预期，8 月有望进一步增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大统计局周五公布的数据显示，在汽车和零部件经销商销售额增长的带动下，加拿大7月份的零售销售额比6月份增长了0.9%，而8月份的销售额可能会进一步攀升。【原文：Canadian retail sales grew by 0.9% in July from June, led by higher sales at motor vehicle and parts dealers, while sales likely climbed further in August, data from Statistics Canada showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadian-retail-sales-beat-july-estimates-seen-up-further-august-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHRLCMGVF5JCRPJJ2CHEEX4AL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 13:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金在美联储降息前吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 9 月 18 日的一周内，全球投资者纷纷抢购股票基金，预计美联储将降息以启动期待已久的减息周期。【原文：Global investors scooped up equity funds in the week to Sept. 18, anticipating the Federal Reserve's interest rate cut to initiate its long-awaited reduction cycle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXDMIQRVTZIJVA2G3RDVWUD6KU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 7 月零售销售因汽车销售增长 0.9%；预计 8 月增长 0.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[9月20日（路透社）--加拿大统计局周五表示，受机动车和零部件经销商销售额增长的带动，加拿大7月份零售销售额为663.8亿加元（489.5亿美元），比6月份增长0.9%。该机构在一份速报中估计，8月份的销售额可能增长0.5%。【原文：Sept 20 (Reuters) - Canadian retail sales grew by 0.9% in July from June at C$66.38 billion ($48.95 billion), led by higher sales at motor vehicle and parts dealers, Statistics Canada said on Friday. Sales were likely up 0.5% in August, the agency said in a flash estimate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canada-july-retail-sales-up-09-autos-seen-up-05-august-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L42GOEFLAJNA7MJSX7OG4GUN7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者如何购买黄金以及黄金市场的驱动因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，黄金创下每盎司 2,600 美元以上的历史新高，因为美国进一步降息的前景和全球地缘政治的不确定性增强了黄金的吸引力。【原文：Gold hit a record high above $2,600 per ounce on Friday, as the prospect of more U.S. interest rate cuts and global geo-political uncertainty boosted its appeal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/how-investors-buy-gold-what-drives-market-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BUM5PDSORPZJPF7A46ISC7ORU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:38:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[锁定期满，特朗普媒体下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Truth Social 母公司 Trump Media &amp; Technology Group 的股票在周五的盘前交易中下跌了 4.5%，原因是该公司对内线销售的锁定期到期，从而延续了本周的大幅下挫。【原文：Shares of Trump Media &amp; Technology Group fell 4.5% in premarket trading on Friday as the Truth Social parent extended this week's steep selloff after a lock-up on insider sales expired.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-media-slides-lock-up-expires-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFLQ5EROQ5LF5HGSRYX4E3JXEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:35:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储将在 11 月和 12 月降息 25 个基点，更快接近中性水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项即时调查显示，100 多位经济学家中的绝大多数认为，美国联邦储备委员会将在 11 月和 12 月把联邦基金利率下调 25 个基点。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve will cut the federal funds rate by 25 basis points in both November and December, according to a strong majority of over 100 economists in a snap Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-cut-rates-by-25bps-nov-dec-approach-neutral-level-sooner-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJ64PFJLEZKNLHD3735GGYLQY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:21:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利因中国、内存和英特尔问题下调 ASML 评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）周五下调了计算机芯片设备制造商ASML的盈利预期，这是继内存芯片市场疲软以及对中国芯片制造商和英特尔需求的担忧之后，最新一家下调预期的券商。【原文：Morgan Stanley on Friday downgraded earnings estimates for computer chip equipment maker ASML , the latest brokerage to do so following weakness in the memory chip market and concerns over demand from Chinese chipmakers and Intel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/morgan-stanley-latest-downgrade-asml-china-memory-intel-concerns-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2QNYRX5XZK5LP5463ZH2EJLOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大银行：人工智能可能在短期内提升通胀压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[作者：Promit Mukherjee 和 David Ljunggren【原文：By Promit Mukherjee and David Ljunggren】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/bank-canada-ai-could-boost-inflationary-pressures-short-term-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STU5B2R3NNOBBJCPMREQU4CJSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:17:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺基亚称德国法院在其与亚马逊的专利纠纷中作出有利于其的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[芬兰网络设备制造商和电信专利持有者诺基亚周五表示，慕尼黑一家法院裁定亚马逊在未获得许可的情况下使用了诺基亚的专利视频技术。【原文：A Munich court has ruled that Amazon is using Nokia's patented video technologies without a license, the Finnish network equipment maker and telecommunications patent holder said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nokia-says-german-court-rules-its-favour-patent-dispute-with-amazon-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ6WA7YDARONJNRLDOFFYKFZMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 11:53:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Nifty 指数和 Sensex 指数表现优于全球大多数市场，仅次于华尔街]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度 NSE Nifty 50 指数和 S&amp;P BSE Sensex 指数是今年表现最好的指数，仅次于华尔街的纳斯达克指数和 S&amp;P 500 指数。【原文：India's NSE Nifty 50 and S&amp;P BSE Sensex are trailing only Wall Street's Nasdaq and S&amp;P 500 as top-performing indexes this year, with analysts expecting the rally to extend into 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/indias-nifty-sensex-outperform-most-global-markets-behind-only-wall-street-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVNWPPMDTVOMZJWC2WDEPE5ALM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 11:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三哩岛核电站可在微软人工智能电力协议基础上重启]]></title><description><![CDATA[Constellation Energy 和微软公司周五表示，两家公司已经签署了一项数据中心协议，帮助宾夕法尼亚州三里岛核电站的一个机组复活，这将是有史以来第一次重启此类机组。【原文：Constellation Energy and Microsoft have signed a data center deal to help resurrect a unit of the Three Mile Island nuclear plant in Pennsylvania in what would be the first-ever restart of its kind, the companies said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/constellation-inks-power-supply-deal-with-microsoft-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFJFFA4HDVO37MBJCWRLTGB56A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 11:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南电动汽车制造商 VinFast 报告连续亏损扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南电动汽车制造商 VinFast 周五公布的财报显示，尽管其收入仍呈上升趋势，但受其雄心勃勃的亚洲扩张所导致的成本上升影响，第二季度亏损加剧。【原文：Vietnamese electric-vehicle maker VinFast reported a deeper second-quarter loss on Friday, driven by rising costs linked to its ambitious Asia expansion, although its revenue remained on a rising trend, according to its exchange filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vietnamese-ev-maker-vinfast-reports-wider-sequential-gross-loss-2024-09-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QS67N7Z6MNLFLP2XWHVI4SM7IA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 11:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>