<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:04:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:04:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司因经济不确定性下调第一季度业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周一以宏观经济不确定性增加为由，下调了截至 3 月份的当季利润预期。【原文：Delta Air Lines on Monday slashed its profit estimates for the current quarter through March, citing increased macroeconomic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-airlines-cuts-first-quarter-profit-forecast-increased-macroeconomic-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYNPUMSVRNPJ5LPHB7IPDRKXZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称对冲基金两年来最大程度降低股票风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[据高盛周一发布的一份报告称，对冲基金周五减少了股票投资，减持幅度为两年多来最大。【原文：Hedge funds reduced their exposure to stocks on Friday at the largest amount in more than two years, according to a Goldman Sachs note released on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/hedge-funds-cut-risk-stocks-largest-amount-two-years-goldman-sachs-says-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QG5UMLTSSFJVPFI3VUH54L66YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受中国禁售令影响，Illumina下调业绩展望，将削减1亿美元成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国宣布禁止进口其基因测序仪器后，Illumina 周一下调了其年度预期，并表示计划削减 1 亿美元的支出。【原文：Illumina on Monday lowered its annual forecast and said it plans to cut $100 million in spending after China announced a ban on imports of its genetic sequencing instruments.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/illumina-lowers-outlook-due-china-sales-ban-cut-100-million-costs-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAHAEBZAOFP6VJR5QI6ZQUHX3Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文第三季度营收不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[甲骨文公司周一公布的第三季度营收不及华尔街预期，原因是企业在云基础设施服务上的支出疲软，以及来自大型企业的激烈竞争。【原文：Oracle missed Wall Street expectations for third-quarter revenue on Monday, weighed down by softer enterprise spending on its cloud infrastructure services, and strong competition from larger players.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/oracle-misses-third-quarter-revenue-estimates-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWCYYL4PSVOUNHZHBP76FQ4MPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:09:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国银行裁撤部分投资银行职位，包括在纽约的职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位不愿透露姓名的熟悉情况的消息人士透露，美国银行周一裁撤了一些投资银行业务的职位，包括纽约的职位。【原文：Bank of America eliminated some investment banking roles on Monday, including in New York, according to three sources familiar with the situation who declined to be identified discussing personnel matters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-eliminates-some-investment-banking-roles-including-new-york-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2C2IVGXEZ5OSXOB4XG6C4B7CHE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官芬克称民族主义政策将加剧通货膨胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）周一表示，包括驱逐工人在内的民族主义政策将加剧美国的通货膨胀。【原文：BlackRock Chief Executive Larry Fink said on Monday that inflation in the United States will be elevated by nationalistic policies including the deportation of workers.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackrock-ceo-fink-says-nationalistic-policies-will-stoke-inflation-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOZS6OQN6JJ43C7CHILNLI2A34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果准备对软件进行重大改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引熟知内情的人士的话报道，苹果公司正准备在今年晚些时候对其软件进行重大改革，这将改变操作系统的外观以及 iPhone、iPad 和 Mac 的界面。【原文：Apple is preparing a major overhaul of its software, due later this year, which will change the look of the operating systems and the interface of the iPhone, iPad and Mac, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the effort.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/apple-preparing-major-software-overhaul-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HX7JMO255PNZHUF3VZ6G64I3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:17:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 特朗普政府旨在取消石油储备销售，支持小型核能发电]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）周一表示，他正计划与国会合作，取消此前规定的战略石油储备销售，以此作为解决库存过低问题的一种方法。【原文：U.S. Energy Secretary Chris Wright said on Monday he was planning to work with Congress on cancelling previously mandated sales from the Strategic Petroleum Reserve as one way to address low stockpiles.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-trump-administration-aims-cancel-oil-reserve-sales-support-small-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGZGQLPJZJJ43NNV5NHX2MEAVE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官驳回 CFPB 中止对 Comerica 提起诉讼的动议]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一提交的一份法院命令，德克萨斯州的一名联邦法官驳回了美国消费者金融保护局暂停对科美嘉银行诉讼的动议。【原文：A federal judge in Texas denied the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau's motion to stay its lawsuit against Comerica Bank, according to a court order filed on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-denies-cfpbs-motion-stay-lawsuit-against-comerica-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X62I3ZCI4BJ7BPD7SMJATLLLCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:49:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 弗里波特公司认为，如果特朗普宣布铜为关键资源，每年将增加 5 亿美元的收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[Freeport-McMoRan 公司首席执行官凯瑟琳-奎克（Kathleen Quirk）周一表示，希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在宣布其促进美国采矿业发展的计划时，将铜宣布为关键矿产。【原文：Freeport-McMoRan hopes U.S. President Donald Trump declares copper to be a critical mineral when he announces his plan to boost American mining, CEO Kathleen Quirk said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ceraweek-freeport-sees-500-million-annual-boost-if-trump-declares-copper-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFTI7Q426NLVFKCGRGLEC4IWAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:27:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，CoreWeave 在上市前与 OpenAI 签订了价值 120 亿美元的合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周一告诉路透社，由英伟达（Nvidia）支持的人工智能初创公司 CoreWeave 已与 OpenAI 签订了一份为期五年、价值 119 亿美元的合同，将在其上市前提供云计算服务。【原文：CoreWeave, an artificial intelligence startup backed by Nvidia , has signed a five-year contract worth $11.9 billion with OpenAI to provide cloud computing services ahead of its hotly anticipated stock market launch, people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/coreweave-strikes-12-billion-contract-with-openai-ahead-ipo-sources-say-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWXNTLXF3RL33IRRHYUKOGFCEM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽油运输商与殖民地管道公司就条款修改建议发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[至少有四家美国汽油营销商正准备对殖民地管道公司提出法律和监管挑战，因为这些公司认为，拟议中的燃料运输条款变化将损害他们的利润，并推高加油站的燃料价格。【原文：At least four U.S. gasoline marketers are preparing legal and regulatory challenges to the Colonial Pipeline over proposed changes in fuel shipping terms which the companies say will hurt their margins and drive up fuel prices at the pump, sources familiar with the discussions said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/gasoline-shippers-clash-with-colonial-pipeline-proposed-changes-terms-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62IGF2YLFRKGPHYOZ43IHC34QM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 美国液化天然气出口商寻求重新谈判交易，以弥补不断上涨的成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的消息来源和公司声明称，由于建筑、劳动力和借贷成本上升，几家美国液化天然气生产商正试图与买家重新谈判更高的价格。【原文：Several U.S. LNG producers are trying to renegotiate higher prices with buyers as a result of rising construction, labor and borrowing costs, according to sources and company statements reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-us-lng-exporters-seek-renegotiate-deals-cover-rising-costs-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTKHKG27SZJ23L6Q7JCA73HQJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员押注美联储将在经济下滑时快速降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储不会在下周的政策会议上降低利率，但如果对贸易战引发经济衰退的担忧升温成真，美联储可能会在 6 月份快速降低借贷成本。【原文：The Federal Reserve won't lower interest rates at its policy meeting next week, but could deliver the first of a set of rapid-fire reductions in borrowing costs in June if rising fears of an economic downturn triggered by a trade war materialize.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/fed-deliver-rapid-fire-rate-cuts-if-economic-downturn-happens-traders-bet-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CK44HVPNYVILHNPW2KM6KOA2FE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会主席表示，美国证券交易委员会将不再要求加密货币公司注册为交易系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）代理主席周一表示，他已指示工作人员研究如何放弃一项计划，该计划将扩大另类交易系统的定义，把一些加密货币公司包括在内。【原文：The acting chief of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Monday he has directed staff to look at ways to abandon a plan that would have widened the definition of alternative trading systems to include some cryptocurrency firms.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/us-sec-move-away-requiring-crypto-firms-register-trading-systems-chief-says-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMCMOBRVPBM57AGEQLOTNUQKFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，欧盟可能对苹果和 Meta 违反 DMA 规定处以适度罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的人士周一表示，欧盟反垄断监管机构预计将对苹果公司和 Meta Platforms 公司处以适度罚款，因为这两家公司涉嫌违反了旨在约束其权力的具有里程碑意义的规定。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are expected to hand out modest fines to Apple and Meta Platforms for allegedly breaching landmark rules aimed at reining in their power, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/eu-likely-impose-modest-fines-apple-meta-over-dma-breaches-sources-say-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOPWLO57ZNOEBGXMPE5N5Z55KM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行就陷入困境的 4.81 亿美元房地产贷款起诉摩根大通]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）周一起诉摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase），要求为一笔 4.81 亿美元的商业房地产贷款的投资者追回损失。【原文：Wells Fargo sued JPMorgan Chase on Monday to recover losses for investors in a $481 million commercial real estate loan that was allegedly based on a fraudulently inflated financial metric.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/wells-fargo-sues-jpmorgan-over-troubled-481-million-real-estate-loan-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4GKTQO4O5O23PFPWJR4OPLYDQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:45:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦敦劳合社预计洛杉矶野火将造成 23 亿美元净损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦劳合社（Lloyd's of London）周一表示，预计近期的洛杉矶野火将造成 23 亿美元的净损失，该保险市场去年的承保利润也有所下降。【原文：Lloyd's of London said on Monday it expected $2.3 billion in net losses caused by the recent Los Angeles wildfires, as the insurance marketplace reported a dip in underwriting profit for last year.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/lloyds-london-expects-23-billion-net-losses-los-angeles-wildfires-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPMXQWI5HVM4HKJD4K4H2YS5NY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:43:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月份集装箱进口量接近历史最高水平，关税风险迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[供应链技术提供商笛卡尔周一表示，2月份美国集装箱进口量同比增长4.7%，但随着美国与中国和其他主要贸易伙伴的贸易战占据上风，未来几个月可能会降温。【原文：U.S. container import volumes increased 4.7% year-on-year in February, but could cool in coming months as the U.S. trade war with China and other key trading partners takes hold, supply chain technology provider Descartes said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-container-imports-near-record-level-february-tariff-risks-loom-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZTKZOVIXVPFHC4VA6NBQOYKDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普引发的不确定性引发经济担忧，投资者逃离股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[对贸易关税的不确定性将引发经济衰退的担忧正导致投资者逃离股市，这对曾因唐纳德-特朗普总统的议程前景而火热的华尔街来说是一个重大转变。【原文：Fears that uncertainty over trade tariffs will spark an economic downturn are causing investors to flee equities, in a major shift for Wall Street which had been fired-up by the prospect of President Donald Trump's agenda.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-flee-equities-trump-driven-uncertainty-sparks-economic-worry-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSTUGJEA2FIZJDORUN2GKYU4GU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的 DeepSeek 解决了短暂影响其人工智能推理模型的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的 DeepSeek 周一表示，影响其高级 R1 人工智能推理模型的一个问题在短暂中断后已得到解决。【原文：China's DeepSeek said on Monday an issue impacting its advanced R1 artificial intelligence reasoning model was resolved after a brief outage.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinas-deepseek-says-advanced-ai-reasoning-model-currently-unavailable-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMFDOAKKHFI65H5THHLJTLWTGU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metinvest 首席执行官：乌克兰钢铁产能重建取决于安全保障]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰钢铁巨头 Metinvest 的负责人告诉路透社记者，重建被战争严重破坏的业务将取决于美国和欧洲在与俄罗斯达成的任何停火协议中是否提供强有力的安全保障。【原文：The head of Ukrainian steel giant Metinvest told Reuters that rebuilding its heavily war-damaged operations will hinge on the robustness of U.S. and European security guarantees in any ceasefire deal with Russia.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/rebuilding-ukraine-steel-capacity-hinges-security-guarantees-metinvest-ceo-says-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUCR6GQ2ZNIQFESUMKD75BJEUE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咖啡豆价格飙升，美国咖啡盗窃案激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[据运输公司称，由于去年咖啡豆的价格升至历史最高点，世界上最大的咖啡豆进口国美国的卡车装载绿咖啡豆的盗窃案正在激增。【原文：Theft of truck loads of green coffee beans is surging in the United States, the world's largest importer of the commodity, as prices for the beans increased to all-time highs in the last year, according to transportation companies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/coffee-theft-surges-us-prices-beans-soar-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWDEAPPIFOOZGZJOIRXTCEYWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咖啡豆价格飙升，美国咖啡盗窃案激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[据运输公司称，由于去年咖啡豆的价格升至历史最高点，世界上最大的咖啡豆进口国美国的卡车装载绿咖啡豆的盗窃案正在激增。【原文：Theft of truck loads of green coffee beans is surging in the United States, the world's largest importer of the commodity, as prices for the beans increased to all-time highs in the last year, according to transportation companies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/coffee-theft-surges-us-prices-beans-soar-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWDEAPPIFOOZGZJOIRXTCEYWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱主席告诉 FCA Epstein-Staley 的关系不需要在 2019 年接受董事会审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据法庭文件显示，巴克莱银行董事长奈杰尔-希金斯（Nigel Higgins）认为，在英国金融监管机构对此事进行询问后，该行前首席执行官杰斯-斯塔利（Jes Staley）与已故失宠金融家杰弗里-爱泼斯坦（Jeffrey Epstein）的关系不值得在 2019 年夏天的董事会上讨论。【原文：Barclays chairman Nigel Higgins believed the bank's former CEO Jes Staley's ties with the late disgraced financier Jeffrey Epstein did not warrant a board discussion in the summer of 2019 after Britain's financial regulator inquired over the matter, according to court documents.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-chair-told-fca-epstein-staley-ties-did-not-need-board-review-2019-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNCOPNZRQROJTPI346BDPSDQ5A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：欧盟在特朗普首轮关税中面临哪些挑战？]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，欧盟正准备迎接美国的首轮关税，对铝和钢材进口征收25%的关税，受影响的欧盟进口商品价值超过美国总统唐纳德-特朗普2018年对欧盟金属进口征收的关税。【原文：The European Union is bracing for its first round of U.S. tariffs on Wednesday, 25% tariffs on aluminium and steel imports, affecting more EU imports in value than duties U.S. President Donald Trump imposed on EU metal imports in 2018.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/europe/what-challenges-face-eu-first-round-trump-tariffs-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWKJEOXGGNOSZGOK5P7XTVZ33M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普引发经济衰退担忧，华尔街抛售加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普拒绝预测其关税政策是否会导致经济衰退后，美国主要股指周一下挫，投资者情绪受到影响。【原文：Major U.S. stock indexes sank on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump declined to predict whether his tariff policies could lead to a recession, roiling investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/wall-street-selloff-deepens-trump-sparks-recession-concerns-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGEWS2GEGNKZLI6CIXQQJW4B7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:53:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安大略省对出口到美国的电力征收 25% 的附加费]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大安大略省省长道格-福特（Doug Ford）周一表示，该省将对出口到纽约州、密歇根州和明尼苏达州的电力征收25%的附加费，以抗议美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对加拿大征收关税。【原文：The Canadian province of Ontario is imposing a 25% surcharge on electricity exports to New York state, Michigan and Minnesota to protest against U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on Canada, Premier Doug Ford said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ontario-imposes-25-surcharge-electricity-exports-us-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDB7IR3QYBMLJJKOKMP7NIPBXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Northvolt 股东斯堪尼亚已获得更多电池芯供应商]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典卡车制造商斯堪尼亚（Scania）是陷入困境的电池制造商 Northvolt 的股东和客户，该公司周一告诉路透社，它已找到了另一家电池供应商。【原文：Swedish truckmaker Scania, a shareholder and customer of struggling battery maker Northvolt, told Reuters on Monday it had secured an additional supplier of battery cells.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/northvolt-shareholder-scania-has-secured-additional-supplier-battery-cells-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBBBXCJ3KNNHBKZDUMXT2WQDQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:13:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙首席执行官敦促美国采取持久的能源政策，而不是极端的波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙首席执行官迈克-沃思（Mike Wirth）周一表示，雪佛龙希望看到美国能源政策的持久性，而不是从一个极端摇摆到另一个极端。【原文：Chevron would like to see durability in U.S. energy policy rather than swings from one extreme to another, CEO Mike Wirth said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-chevron-ceo-says-extreme-energy-policy-swings-wrong-approach-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7EIZNDFNFJVZLIZDHR2WX734M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>