<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:38:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:38:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Zoox 启动首个机器人出租车生产设施，向特斯拉和 Waymo 发起挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊的Zoox公司周三表示，其首个机器人出租车批量生产工厂已经开业，这标志着该公司向推出商业机器人出租车服务迈出了关键一步，该服务将与Alphabet的Waymo和特斯拉展开竞争。
 Zoox正在美国多个城市用20多辆车进行测试，并计划今年在拉斯维加斯推出商业服务，随后在旧金山推出，并寻求扩大运营区域。【原文：Amazon's Zoox has opened its first robotaxi serial production facility, it said on Wednesday, marking a crucial step towards launching a commercial robotaxi service that will compete with Alphabet's Waymo and Tesla .
 Zoox is testing in various U.S. cities with more than 20 vehicles and plans to launch the commercial services in Las Vegas this year, followed by San Francisco, where it seeks to expand areas of operation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/zoox-launches-its-first-robotaxi-production-facility-taking-tesla-waymo-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQP5SOZHLJLWHCRBWQQKYK7ADE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称美国原油库存下滑，产品库存增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周三称，上周美国原油库存大幅下降，而汽油和馏分油库存上升。【原文：U.S. crude oil stockpiles fell sharply while gasoline and distillate inventories rose last week, the Energy Information Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-stockpiles-slump-products-build-eia-says-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GACTDG2UBNRBMUJ62X4NUELRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:52:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NHTSA 结束对 200 多万辆日产汽车的工程分析]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，已经结束了对203.8307万辆日产汽车后悬挂控制臂故障相关问题的工程分析。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday it had closed an engineering analysis on 2,038,307 Nissan Motor vehicles over issues related to rear suspension control arm failure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-closes-engineering-analysis-more-than-2-million-nissan-vehicles-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RG2KOFWWE5JX5GTFOOVPS5R6UA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院通过法案，稳定币市值飙升至历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据显示，稳定币的总市值在周三飙升至历史新高，因为美国参议院通过了一项监管稳定币行业的法案，这是使加密货币市场中曾经小众但现在快速增长的一角合法化的重要一步。【原文：The total market capitalization of stablecoins surged to a record high on Wednesday, data showed, as the U.S. Senate passed a bill to regulate the sector, a major step towards legitimising a once-niche but now fast-growing corner of the crypto market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stablecoins-market-cap-surges-record-high-us-senate-passes-bill-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2JUCKEIAZJM3EIIDYO2YQT6UM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 VinFast 在加利福尼亚州签下首家经销商]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南电动汽车制造商 VinFast 周三宣布其在加利福尼亚州的首家经销商将于本月开始运营。【原文：Vietnamese electric-vehicle maker VinFast on Wednesday announced its first dealership in California, and is set to begin operations this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-vinfast-signs-first-dealership-california-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBRCJK4LLBNVVIMBP2LOUX37TE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:15:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普税收和支出法案的参众两院版本之间的主要差异]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院共和党人公布了他们版本的唐纳德-特朗普总统的全面减税和支出法案，该法案与上个月以微弱优势通过的众议院立法大体相似。【原文：U.S. Senate Republicans have unveiled their version of President Donald Trump's sweeping tax-cut and spending bill that is broadly similar to the legislation that narrowly passed the House of Representatives last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/major-differences-between-house-senate-versions-trumps-tax-spending-bill-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3PXSZRJPBOZXCZSXAT3BDIXH4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:51:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔任命工程技术人员，作为首席执行官谭群钊扭亏战略的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司首席执行官陈立武在周三聘请了三位芯片业高管，负责工程和网络方面的工作，这也是陈立武对高层管理进行全面改革并扭转这家陷入困境的芯片制造商的计划的一部分。【原文：Intel hired three chip industry executives in engineering and networking roles on Wednesday, as part of CEO Lip-Bu Tan's plans to overhaul top management and turn around the embattled chipmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-appoints-engineering-hires-part-ceo-tans-turnaround-strategy-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WMVX52BWNOP5KSESZP5LJXKQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德州仪器计划在美国投资 600 多亿美元生产基础芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[德州仪器公司（Texas Instruments）周三表示，该公司将在美国七座半导体工厂投资 600 多亿美元，这是美国历史上对基础芯片制造的最大投资。【原文：Texas Instruments said on Wednesday it would invest more than $60 billion across seven U.S. semiconductor fabs, marking the largest investment in foundational chip manufacturing in American history.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/texas-instruments-plans-invest-over-60-billion-us-make-foundational-chips-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TMSI2SL6VIVJE2SMH47PWYYKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:13:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁完成对美国钢铁公司的收购，特朗普扮演重要角色]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新日铁公司（Nippon Steel）与美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）表示，新日铁公司以 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司的交易已于周三完成。【原文：Nippon Steel's $14.9 billion acquisition of U.S. Steel closed on Wednesday, the companies said, confirming an unusual degree of power for the Trump administration after the Japanese company's 18-month struggle to close the purchase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nippon-steels-acquisition-us-steel-closes-with-big-role-trump-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7IL4KKC2BOPVP7VVL22NHFQGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[视觉效果资深专家埃德-乌尔布里奇加盟人工智能公司 Moonvalley]]></title><description><![CDATA[曾参与《泰坦尼克号》、《本杰明-巴顿奇事》和《壮志凌云》等影片制作的视觉特效资深专家埃德-乌尔布里奇（Ed Ulbrich）已加入人工智能研究公司 Moonvalley，担任战略发展合作主管：他已加入人工智能研究公司 Moonvalley，担任战略发展与合作主管。【原文：Visual effects veteran Ed Ulbrich, who worked on such films as "Titanic" and "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button" and "Top Gun: Maverick," has joined artificial intelligence research company Moonvalley as head of strategic growth and partnerships.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/visual-effects-veteran-ed-ulbrich-joins-ai-company-moonvalley-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOTR5NCTLJLRRBUF7TQ7VTJMRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TP 的目标是到 2028 年向股东返还 15 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国呼叫中心和办公服务集团 TP（前身为 Teleperformance）周三宣布了新的中期目标，包括计划到 2028 年向股东返还 15 亿欧元。【原文：French call centre and office services group TP, formerly known as Teleperformance , on Wednesday announced new medium term targets including plans to return 1.5 billion euros to shareholders by 2028.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tp-aims-hand-back-15-billion-euros-shareholders-by-2028-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLM2WKKACRJHDM5KF7PZDUKDAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月独户住宅开工率上升；许可量下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份，美国独户住宅建设有所增加，但未来建设许可大幅下降，表明在关税和未售出住宅库存过剩的不利因素影响下，住房市场形势低迷。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding increased in May, but a sharp drop in permits for future construction pointed to subdued housing market conditions amid headwinds from tariffs and excess inventory of unsold homes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-single-family-housing-starts-rise-may-permits-slump-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALOLCOL4TJL7LMZBUQJNRNGJC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:48:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降，但仍处于高位]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数有所下降，但仍保持在6月份劳动力市场进一步失去动力的水平。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell last week, but stayed at levels consistent with a further loss of labor market momentum in June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-still-elevated-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHS7LGSNDNK5LP37IDAQZJ7DRE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融科技公司 Klarna 将在美国推出每月 40 美元的移动计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典金融科技公司 Klarna 周三表示，它将在美国推出无限量移动计划，加入其他金融公司进军电信业务的行列，其中包括英国竞争对手 Revolut。【原文：Swedish fintech Klarna on Wednesday said it would launch an unlimited mobile plan in the U.S., joining other finance companies moving into the telecoms business, including British rival Revolut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fintech-klarna-launch-40-per-month-mobile-plan-us-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKSG7AQV4NI2FD7LRQ4R25AFX4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:32:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环联称美国消费者对关税成本更加悲观]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用报告机构全美征信公司（TransUnion）称，由于关税加剧了人们对物价上涨的担忧，美国消费者对金钱的感觉更加糟糕。【原文：U.S. consumers are feeling worse about money as tariffs fuel concerns about rising prices, credit reporting agency TransUnion said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/us-consumers-more-pessimistic-tariff-costs-transunion-says-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDXUJ62AZ5J4FPHPSUMRPWCHDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希尔顿和万豪酒店集团宣布非洲扩张计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国连锁酒店希尔顿和万豪已宣布向非洲扩张，以利用非洲大陆快速增长的旅游业。【原文：U.S. hotel chains Hilton and Marriott have announced African expansion drives to tap into the continent's rapid tourism growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hotel-groups-hilton-marriot-announce-african-expansion-plans-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CJZKWMQ5VMQVEAABMULKAFAHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达支持的人工智能初创公司SandboxAQ创建新数据，加快药物研发速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[SandboxAQ 是一家从 Alphabet 旗下谷歌分离出来的人工智能初创公司，得到了 Nvidia 的支持，该公司周三发布了大量数据，希望通过帮助科学家了解药物是如何粘附在蛋白质上的，从而加快发现新的医疗方法。【原文：SandboxAQ, an artificial intelligence startup spun out of Alphabet's Google and backed by Nvidia , on Wednesday released a trove of data it hopes will speed up the discovery of new medical treatments by helping scientists understand how drugs stick to proteins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/nvidia-backed-ai-startup-sandboxaq-creates-new-data-speed-up-drug-discovery-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULYSE43GPRLCVMGENBYEKVUQ3A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:06:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国防务公司追逐欧洲军费浪潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防巨头在华盛顿强大的国会代表团的支持下，利用巴黎航展展示尖端技术，并向欧洲合作伙伴抛出橄榄枝，以寻求获得不断增长的地区军事开支。【原文：U.S. defence giants, backed by a strong Congressional delegation from Washington, used the Paris Airshow to showcase cutting-edge technologies and court European partners as they seek to tap into rising regional military spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-defence-firms-chase-european-military-spending-wave-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2IGXMDUC5JI3LCYJ22UTOYQHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司乐观，但可能需要等待亚航的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，经常在最后一刻上演交易大戏的廉价航空公司亚航（AirAsia）的老板淡化了与空客或巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）达成飞机交易的预期，这场全球最大的航展似乎将以平淡收场。【原文：The world's biggest air show looked set on Wednesday for a muted finale after the owner of budget carrier AirAsia, often a source of last-minute dealmaking drama, played down the prospect of expected plane deals with Airbus or Embraer .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-upbeat-may-have-wait-airasia-deal-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJEBO3AUBRPSVONSP75KTEW3CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美联储会议召开，油价再次下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2EZHP2ZONJLRJ46RXJVXVPRUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:55:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称马来西亚将增加 50%的天然气发电能力以满足数据中心需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位行业官员表示，马来西亚预计到 2030 年将增加 6-8 千兆瓦的燃气发电，以应对数据中心需求带动的电力消费增长。【原文：Malaysia is expected to add 6-8 gigawatts of gas-fired power by 2030 to address growing electricity consumption driven by demand from data centres, an industry official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/malaysia-build-50-more-gas-fired-power-capacity-meet-data-centre-demand-official-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6Z6FC6W4BRNILLSNE6WEDLOF4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:48:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[提前提名美联储主席可能令市场恐慌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他将很快提名杰罗姆-鲍威尔的继任者，距离美联储主席的任期结束还有近一年的时间。投资者表示，这可能会给市场带来风险。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has said that he would soon nominate Jerome Powell's successor, with nearly a year left before the Federal Reserve chair's term ends. Investors said that could present a risky proposition for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/early-fed-chair-nomination-could-rattle-markets-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTX5LRS3QVOM3AN7TVM6ACRYW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储利率决议前华尔街期货持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在美联储做出货币政策决定之前，美国股指期货走高，而以色列与伊朗的冲突已进入第六天，双方都发动了新的导弹袭击。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Wednesday ahead of the Federal Reserve's monetary policy decision, while the Israel-Iran conflict entered its sixth day, with new missile strikes launched from both sides.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-steady-ahead-feds-interest-rate-verdict-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUCKADWS3FMODCFE4XEU5WIWDU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储将维持利率稳定，中东危机和关税给前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计美联储将在周三维持利率不变，因为其决策者正在评估经济降温的迹象，以及美国进口关税和中东危机升级带来的通胀上升风险。【原文：The Federal Reserve is expected to keep interest rates unchanged on Wednesday as its policymakers assess signs of a cooling economy and the risk of higher inflation from U.S. import tariffs and the escalating crisis in the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-set-hold-rates-steady-middle-east-crisis-tariffs-cloud-outlook-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GY6545EFYVOAVPY5VGUE5ZEI3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:14:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[清洁能源在特朗普的美国拥有拥趸，使预算谈判复杂化]]></title><description><![CDATA[在犹他州盐湖城郊区克利菲尔德的一栋工业厂房里，美国制造的长条钢材被送入机器，经过穿刺、弯曲和切割，变成了不久将固定在屋顶上的太阳能电池板的棒材。【原文：In an industrial building in the Salt Lake City suburb of Clearfield, Utah, long strips of U.S.-made steel were fed through machines that punctured, bent and cut them into rods that will soon hold solar panels on rooftops.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/clean-energy-has-fans-trumps-america-complicating-budget-talks-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZIEH76WI5O6ZJG2Q6LSCRDH2Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡贷款机构星展银行的目标是在 5 年内将澳大利亚的贷款额翻一番]]></title><description><![CDATA[星展集团首席执行官陈苏山（Tan Su Shan）表示，星展集团的目标是在未来五年内将其在澳大利亚的贷款额翻一番，这家总部位于新加坡的银行正努力利用澳大利亚与东南亚之间的贸易联系。【原文：DBS Group aims to double its Australian lending book in the next five years, its CEO Tan Su Shan said, as the Singapore-headquartered bank seeks to take advantage of trade links between Australia and Southeast Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-lender-dbs-aims-double-australian-lending-book-5-years-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WV4LRSP5NMM5I7AQJPSFBCBOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员在长期通胀前景不明朗的情况下召开会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储官员在讨论如何正确制定货币政策时面临诸多不确定性，其中最棘手的问题之一就是如何预测通货膨胀的走向，尤其是长期走向。【原文：Among the uncertainties facing Federal Reserve officials as they debate the proper setting of monetary policy, one of the trickiest has been divining where inflation is going, especially over the longer run.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/officials-head-into-fed-meeting-with-uncertain-long-term-inflation-outlook-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7JANWNM6QVO65CRXTLRCSNNGSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:03:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚贸易部调查有关中国公司使用英伟达人工智能芯片的报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚贸易部周三表示，该部正在核实媒体关于该国一家中国公司使用配备英伟达（Nvidia）和人工智能芯片的服务器进行大型语言模型训练的报道。【原文：Malaysia's trade ministry is verifying media reports that a Chinese company in the country is using servers equipped with Nvidia and artificial intelligence chips for large language models training, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/malaysia-trade-ministry-probing-reports-chinese-firms-use-nvidia-ai-chips-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LWN277OGVMEJH4M2PWDGMGSTU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:29:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰任命亚洲资深人士 Christopher Chua 为全球并购主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的银行汇丰银行周三任命克里斯托弗-蔡（Christopher Chua）为并购业务主管，汇丰银行前全球主管上月离职后转投摩根大通。【原文：Europe's biggest bank HSBC appointed Christopher Chua head of mergers and acquisitions on Wednesday, after its former global head left for JPMorgan last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/hsbc-names-asia-veteran-christopher-chua-global-ma-head-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAT4USGD2BPBJDK4RKLVQF2FOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乘车服务公司 Careem 将暂停已有十年历史的巴基斯坦服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步（Uber）在中东的打车服务分支 Careem 将于 7 月 18 日暂停其在巴基斯坦的服务，理由是经济挑战、竞争加剧和资金紧张。【原文：Careem, Uber's ride-hailing arm in the Middle East, will suspend its Pakistan service on July 18, citing economic challenges, rising competition, and capital constraints, ending its core business in a country where it helped pioneer app-based transport nearly a decade ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/ride-hailer-careem-suspend-decade-old-pakistan-service-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXTO2EI4ZRPLHFKZ3HI2LD3DNM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>