<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:04:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:04:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联航首席执行官在会见新老板奥特伯格后表示对波音公司充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）首席执行官斯科特-柯比（Scott Kirby）周四在与波音公司新任最高负责人凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）会面后，预测波音公司的复苏将 "快于大多数人的预期"。【原文：United Airlines CEO Scott Kirby on Thursday predicted Boeing's recovery to be "faster than most expect" after meeting with the planemaker's new top boss, Kelly Ortberg.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-ceo-expresses-confidence-boeing-after-meeting-new-boss-ortberg-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4QDFW7XRVN3JBIG6C5TWJRWQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 19:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济数据向好，美国企业债券利差回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在近期强劲的经济数据增加了人们对降息的希望并平息了对经济衰退的担忧之后，美国公司债券利差（公司为债务支付的相对于国债的溢价）开始收复一些失地。【原文：U.S. corporate bond spreads, the premium over Treasuries that companies pay for debt, are starting to recoup some lost ground after recent strong economic data increased hopes for interest rate cuts and calmed recession fears.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-corporate-bond-spreads-recover-promising-economic-data-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXZ2E65A6RMSHFLJQIVWX6BWIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大驳回 CN Rail 就劳资纠纷提出的具有约束力的仲裁请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大劳工部长发言人周四表示，加拿大劳工部长史蒂文-麦金农（Steven MacKinnon）拒绝了 CN Rail 就与卡车司机工会的劳资纠纷提起具有约束力的仲裁的请求。【原文：Canadian Labour Minister Steven MacKinnon has rejected a request by CN Rail to initiate binding arbitration in a labor dispute with the Teamsters union, a spokesman for the minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-rejects-cn-rails-request-binding-arbitration-labor-dispute-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFKA5VZPAJNWDNPHTQP57CA2TM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[基于摇头丸的创伤后应激障碍药物在 FDA 遭到挫折后，Lykos 将裁员 75]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lykos Therapeutics 公司在美国食品药品管理局拒绝批准其基于亚甲二氧基甲基安非他明（MDMA）的创伤后应激障碍治疗方案几天后，于本周四表示将裁员 75%，并启动一些高管变动。【原文：Lykos Therapeutics said on Thursday it would reduce its workforce by 75% and initiate some executive changes, days after the U.S. Food and Drug Administration declined approval for its MDMA-based treatment for post-traumatic stress disorder.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lykos-cuts-workforce-by-75-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57EZYA2665O55OEVVEGPW26FT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德公司将斥资 4.5 亿美元收购卫星产品制造商 Terran 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司（Lockheed Martin）周四同意以 4.5 亿美元的价格收购卫星产品制造商 Terran Orbital 公司。【原文：Lockheed Martin on Thursday agreed to acquire satellite products maker Terran Orbital in a $450 million deal, months after the defense contractor withdrew it previous bid to take it private.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/lockheed-buy-satellite-products-maker-terran-450-mln-deal-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJBPLBKGIFIBNGZHI7QME2VNMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 因非法向中国实体运输零部件与美国达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球电子公司 TE Connectivity 已同意支付 580 万美元，与美国商务部达成和解，原因是该公司非法向与中国高超音速、无人机和军事电子项目有关的各方运送物品。【原文：Global electronics company TE Connectivity has agreed to pay $5.8 million to settle with the U.S. Department of Commerce for illegally shipping items to parties tied to Chinese hypersonics, drone and military electronics programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/te-connectivity-settles-with-us-illegally-shipping-components-chinese-entities-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VLB5M2HWZP3ZA3ASVFDQFDSZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，埃德加-布朗夫曼准备竞购派拉蒙母公司 National Amusements]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，前华纳音乐董事长小埃德加-布朗夫曼正准备竞购派拉蒙全球公司的家族企业 National Amusements。【原文：Former Warner Music Chairman Edgar Bronfman Jr. is preparing a bid for National Amusements, the family company that controls Paramount Global , the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/edgar-bronfman-prepares-bid-paramount-parent-national-amusements-wsj-reports-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSHSNXFSCZPKNEMVU4LE32IIPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:46:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 EIA 称中国 6 月柴油需求创三年来最大降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周四称，6月份中国柴油需求量同比下降11%，至每天390万桶，是2021年7月以来的最大降幅。【原文：China's diesel demand fell by 11% year over year to 3.9 million barrels per day in June, the biggest percentage drop since July 2021, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-diesel-demand-fell-june-by-most-three-years-us-eia-says-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5JAJUZCLBO2TMQRHHTQ7OXC5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓在智利的罢工进入第三天，推动全球铜价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[矿业巨头必和必拓（BHP）位于智利的埃斯孔迪达（Escondida）大型矿山的罢工周四进入第三天，推动了全球铜价的上涨，因为该公司与工人之间的持续对峙开始蔓延对红色金属供应的担忧。【原文：A strike at mining giant BHP's huge Escondida mine in Chile entered its third day on Thursday, bolstering global copper prices as an ongoing standoff between the company and workers starts to spread worries about supply of the red metal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/bhp-strike-chile-enters-third-day-buoying-global-copper-price-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YU4D7FOVBOMBBLE2N7L25Y5UE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:05:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官称可就佳得乐蛋白棒的健康声明起诉百事公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官裁定，百事可乐公司可以被起诉推销其佳得乐蛋白棒，称其对人体有益，尽管这些蛋白棒的含糖量超过了蛋白质，比一般的糖果棒含糖量还高。【原文：PepsiCo can be sued for marketing its Gatorade protein bars as good for you though they have more sugar than protein and more sugar than typical candy bars, a federal judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pepsico-can-be-sued-over-health-claims-gatorade-protein-bars-judge-says-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPBJI2GAUBM6JDNPJT4VAGOR34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月商业库存小幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于零售商库存的激增被批发商库存的温和增长所抵消，6 月份美国商业库存温和增长。【原文：U.S. business inventories increased moderately in June as a surge in stocks at retailers was offset by mild gains at wholesalers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-inventories-rise-marginally-june-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I3TDJL3XRPAFJL57GILOCWJWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车和飓风贝雷尔影响美国 7 月制造业产出]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于机动车产量下降和飓风贝里尔的影响，7 月份美国工厂的产量有所下降。【原文：Production at U.S. factories fell in July amid a decline in motor vehicle output and disruptions from Hurricane Beryl.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/autos-hurricane-beryl-weigh-us-manufacturing-output-july-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNABMB6PKVLDPNNB3X2LR5Z7OU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克股价大涨，阿克曼回归燃起扭亏希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克股价周四上涨近 4%，因为投资者希望亿万富翁威廉-阿克曼（William Ackman）重新成为耐克的股东后，这家一直在与战略失误和激烈竞争作斗争的运动服装巨头能迎来转机。【原文：Nike shares gained nearly 4% on Thursday as investors hoped the return of billionaire William Ackman as a stakeholder could spark a turnaround at the sportswear giant that has been battling with strategy missteps and tough competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-shares-jump-ackmans-return-sparks-turnaround-hopes-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCGM4D4ZTZI77COACYSLVZIG2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行与国际足联合作，首次成为 2026 年世界杯赞助商]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周四表示，美国银行将与国际足联（FIFA）合作，成为 2026 年世界杯足球赛的赞助商，此举将把这家金融巨头与世界上最受瞩目的体育赛事之一联系在一起。【原文：Bank of America is partnering with FIFA to become a sponsor for the 2026 World Cup, soccer's global governing body said on Thursday, in a move that will link the financial giant with one of the world's most-watched sporting events.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/bank-america-partners-with-fifa-first-time-sponsor-2026-world-cup-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H24UOGKGJ5O3XBP5DEOSXGWMNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员对 9 月降息持更开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，两位美联储官员支持美国央行在下个月的政策会议上降息的可能性，扭转了他们之前对过早降低借贷成本的怀疑态度。【原文：Two Federal Reserve officials on Thursday lined up behind the possibility of an interest rate cut at the U.S. central bank's policy meeting next month, reversing their previous skepticism about lowering borrowing costs too soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-officials-show-more-openness-september-rate-cut-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQ6ANQLABFPAZDLXLZW56YO7WI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:57:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第二位美国法官阻止美国联邦贸易委员会禁止工人签订 "非竞争 "协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[佛罗里达州的一名联邦法官暂时阻止了美国联邦贸易委员会的一项规定，该规定禁止工人签署不加入雇主的竞争对手或开展竞争性业务的协议，成为第二位裁定该禁令可能无效的法官。【原文：A federal judge in Florida has temporarily blocked a U.S. Federal Trade Commission rule that would ban agreements commonly signed by workers not to join their employers' rivals or launch competing businesses, becoming the second judge to rule that the ban is likely invalid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/second-us-judge-blocks-ftc-ban-worker-noncompete-agreements-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFWVLNHKQZNH5FLCIAYLK6NPYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[弗林集团在美国再买下 83 家温迪特许经营店]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗林集团自称是世界上最大的特许经营商，它在新泽西州和宾夕法尼亚州购买了 83 家 Wendy's 特许经营店，使其总数达到 277 家。【原文：Flynn Group, which says it is the world’s biggest franchise operator, bought 83 Wendy’s franchises in New Jersey and Pennsylvania, bringing its total to 277.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/flynn-group-buys-83-more-wendys-franchises-us-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEHS5HIYWRNKNA4XWQ664UYZNY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月进口价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份的进口价格几乎没有上涨，延续了通胀数据温和的势头，这增强了金融市场对下月降息的预期。【原文：U.S. import prices barely rose in July, extending the flow of tame inflation readings that have bolstered financial market expectations for an interest rate cut next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-import-prices-edge-up-july-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GEV26POWVRNQHBV5URJXJABRSI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:49:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量意外下降，表明劳动力市场仍在有序放缓，尽管下岗工人找到新工作有些困难。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits unexpectedly fell last week, suggesting an orderly labor market slowdown remained in place, though laid-off workers are finding it a bit difficult to land new jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-unexpectedly-fall-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWDLSV2F5JM2HLUXB5MTVH3R3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月零售销售增幅高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份零售额增幅超过预期，这可能有助于缓解金融市场因失业率飙升而对经济急剧放缓的担忧。【原文：U.S. retail sales rose more than expected in July, which could help to allay financial market fears of a sharp economic slowdown that were fanned by a jump in the unemployment rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-retail-sales-rise-more-than-expected-july-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6VSXHBY35J5BELMQU2LIB3YLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:38:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Ola Electric 上市几天后推出电动摩托车]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度电动汽车制造商 Ola Electric Mobility 在上市几天后的本周四推出了一系列新摩托车，进军全球最大两轮车市场中尚未开发的细分市场。【原文：Indian electric vehicle maker Ola Electric Mobility launched a new series of motorcycles on Thursday, days after it went public, expanding into an untapped segment in the world's largest two-wheeler market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/indias-ola-electric-launches-electric-motorcycles-days-after-going-public-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBISIER5KRIUTNF2CZT6IXPQNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:09:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司和夏威夷航空公司进一步延长拟议交易的审查期]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司（Alaska Air）周四表示，已同意进一步延长美国司法部（DOJ）对其拟斥资 19 亿美元收购同业夏威夷控股公司（Hawaiian Holdings）的审查期。【原文：Alaska Air said on Thursday it has agreed to further extend the review period of its proposed $1.9 billion acquisition of peer Hawaiian Holdings with the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/alaska-air-hawaiian-further-extend-review-period-proposed-deal-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZTYG72RHJJANIA5UPDY4NSVKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求稳定，沃尔玛上调年度利润预期，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国零售商沃尔玛周四今年第二次上调了年度利润预期，原因是美国人不断涌入沃尔玛商店购买物美价廉的日常必需品，而且沃尔玛向产品公司出售了更多利润率更高的广告。【原文：U.S. retailer Walmart raised its annual profit forecast on Thursday for the second time this year, as Americans kept flocking to its stores for inexpensive everyday essentials and as it sold more higher-margin ads to product companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-hikes-annual-profit-forecast-steady-demand-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QVK54UZBRVKLXJAU6B6PTKJDNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡 Grab 季度营收不及预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Grab Holdings第二季度营收未达预期，原因是其乘车共享和食品配送服务需求疲软，导致其在美国上市的股票在周四盘前交易中下跌7%。【原文：Grab Holdings missed second-quarter revenue estimates as demand faltered in its ride-share and food-delivery services, sending its U.S.-listed shares down 7% in premarket trading on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/singapores-grab-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCEIYMRRUFJUHCLSU57LFPHM3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tapestry 手袋需求稳定，季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[蔻驰母公司 Tapestry 第四季度收入超出华尔街预期，主要得益于其广受欢迎的 Tabby 手袋需求强劲。【原文：Coach parent Tapestry beat Wall Street expectations for fourth-quarter revenue, helped by robust demand for its popular Tabby handbags.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tapestry-beats-quarterly-revenue-expectations-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCS53VJBWFM6XAE2NWAYYCZJYA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:51:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蚂蚁金服集团季度利润下降 10.25% 至 120 亿元人民币]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社根据阿里巴巴集团控股公司周四发布的财报计算显示，截至3月31日的三个月里，中国蚂蚁金服集团实现净利润120亿元（16.8亿美元），同比下降10.25%。【原文：China's Ant Group posted a net profit of 12 billion yuan ($1.68 billion) for the three months to March 31, down 10.25% from a year earlier, Reuters calculations based on Alibaba Group Holdings' earnings released on Thursday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ant-group-quarterly-profit-falls-1025-12-bln-yuan-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5HNM3XB2IVLDFA6IQXWFM6PSL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，世界拉力锦标赛主办方正在探索 5.5 亿美元的出售方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟知内情的人士透露，世界拉力锦标赛商业部门的所有者正在探索各种方案，包括可能出售该业务，以在体育媒体版权估值较高的时候筹集现金。【原文：The owners of the World Rally Championship's commercial arm are exploring options including a possible sale of the business, seeking to bring in cash at a time of high valuations for sports media rights, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/world-rally-championship-promoter-explores-550-mln-sale-sources-say-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XU2LCOP53FODTHSMKU4HEUEXEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电子商务巨头阿里巴巴第一季度营收不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，阿里巴巴集团第一季度营收不及市场预期，原因是在经济不景气的情况下，中国消费者的谨慎消费给该公司的国内电子商务销售带来了压力。【原文：Alibaba Group Holding missed market expectations for first-quarter revenue on Thursday, as the company's domestic e-commerce sales came under pressure from cautious spending by Chinese consumers in a faltering economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinas-e-commerce-giant-alibaba-misses-first-quarter-revenue-estimates-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P4JRFLC6RNMQPPLIZEMO3IGK2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求低迷导致迪尔利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪尔公司（Deere &amp; Co）周四公布第三季度利润下降，原因是高借贷利率和农业收入大幅下降阻碍了对该公司拖拉机和其他农业设备的需求。【原文：Deere &amp; Co reported a lower third-quarter profit on Thursday, as high borrowing rates and plummeting farm incomes hampered demand for the company's tractors and other farm equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/deere-profit-falls-sluggish-demand-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3ZPHXG4CBPJ5KYPKY2CHFCQQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:19:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻低迷终现，美国零售业和中国房地产成关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5EVWUJDLFRO5TOCPFIPTYB4RZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>