<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:42:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:42:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中美官员在马来西亚就出口管制和特朗普关税威胁展开对峙]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国的高级经济官员将于周五抵达吉隆坡举行会谈，以防止贸易战升级，并使美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和中国国家主席习近平下周的会晤按计划进行。【原文：Top economic officials from the U.S. and China are due to arrive in Kuala Lumpur on Friday for talks to prevent a trade war escalation and keep next week's meeting between U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping on track.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-chinese-officials-face-off-export-controls-trump-tariff-threat-malaysia-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5NINWA3YJOLNK2SHCUGC6P3NQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称终止与加拿大的所有贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，在他所谓的前总统罗纳德-里根（Ronald Reagan）对关税发表负面言论的欺诈性广告之后，与加拿大的所有贸易谈判均已终止。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday that all trade talks with Canada were terminated following what he called a fraudulent advertisement in which former President Ronald Reagan spoke negatively about tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-all-trade-talks-with-canada-are-terminated-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HUABPHJVRKIZOJZ7VOGJ3MCYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:50:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市因中美贸易希望而上涨；石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于华尔街财报和中美关系解冻的迹象提振了投资者情绪，周五亚洲股市反弹，而油价则在美国对俄罗斯供应商实施新制裁后有所回落。【原文：Asian shares rallied on Friday as Wall Street earnings and signs of a thaw in U.S.-China relations boosted investor sentiment, while oil prices eased following fresh U.S. sanctions on Russian suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PO52PHGQINKOXBCU27DGRAUI4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:28:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）称，弱势美元的逆转可能考验亚洲抵御关税的能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织一位高级官员告诉路透社记者，如果美元反弹和低利率反弹导致金融条件收紧，亚洲抵御美国关税的能力可能会受到挑战。【原文：Asia may see its resilience to U.S. tariffs challenged if a rally in the dollar and a rebound in low interest rates lead to tighter financial conditions, a senior International Monetary Fund official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/reversal-weak-dollar-may-test-asias-resilience-tariffs-imf-says-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZIO3KRCXVJRZJCYL7YAF2J4J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织敦促亚洲削减贸易壁垒以抵御美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五敦促亚洲降低非关税壁垒，实现区域贸易一体化，以降低亚洲在美国关税和全球金融冲击面前的脆弱性。【原文：The International Monetary Fund on Friday urged Asia to lower non-tariff barriers and integrate regional trade to reduce its vulnerability to U.S. tariffs and global financial shocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/imf-urges-asia-cut-trade-barriers-beat-us-tariffs-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37IIW5W32JKL3ALHLJMXSGP7WE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员为美国通胀数据做准备，美元保持平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五持稳，兑主要对手的美元汇率有望在本周小幅上扬，因为投资者正在为延迟公布的通胀数据做准备，而这些数据不太可能阻止美联储下周降息。【原文：The U.S. dollar was steady on Friday, poised to eke out a small weekly gain against major rivals as investors braced for delayed inflation data that is unlikely to deter the Federal Reserve from lowering interest rates next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-calm-traders-brace-us-inflation-data-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APKARKYNRZKWRJ6L6FIB6WNPKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:38:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本百年企业藤仓借人工智能数据中心热潮成为日经一枝独秀]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本藤仓公司（Fujikura）在日经指数（Nikkei）红火的股价指数中一枝独秀，因为人们预期这家拥有百年历史的电线制造商将受益于使用其光纤的人工智能数据中心投资的增加。【原文：Japan's Fujikura has become a standout in the red-hot Nikkei share gauge on expectations the century-old wire maker will benefit from increased investment in artificial intelligence data centres that use its optical fibres.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-century-old-fujikura-rides-ai-data-centre-boom-become-nikkei-standout-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEE7AGHOIVNMZJCPEDLZ4ENE2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价大涨后回落，在供应担忧下仍有望实现周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国因乌克兰战争对俄罗斯最大的两家石油公司实施了新的制裁，加剧了市场对供应的担忧，周五早盘油价下跌，缩减了前一天的部分涨幅，但仍有望实现周线上涨。【原文：Oil prices dipped in early trade on Friday, trimming part of the previous day's surge but remaining on track for a weekly gain, as fresh U.S. sanctions on Russia's two biggest oil companies over the war in Ukraine fuelled supply concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-dip-after-surge-remain-track-weekly-gain-amid-supply-fears-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMVWJYMGOFIFNCMT3KUAVSANNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国第三季度经济温和增长，出口和消费保持弹性：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，在强劲的出口和家庭消费回升的支撑下，韩国经济在上个季度实现了小幅增长。【原文：South Korea's economy grew at a modest pace last quarter, supported by strong exports and a pickup in household consumption as government measures helped stimulate demand, a Reuters poll suggested.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-koreas-economy-grew-modestly-q3-exports-consumption-stay-resilient-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5AMATVQ5ZMLPLBNZO4NDYONDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 10 月份工厂活动创 19 个月新低（PMI]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五进行的一项私营部门调查显示，由于新订单大幅减少，日本制造业在10月份出现了19个月来最快的萎缩。【原文：Japan's manufacturing sector contracted in October at the fastest pace in 19 months due to a sharper decline in new orders, a private-sector survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-factory-activity-hits-19-month-low-october-pmi-shows-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U6VQ6BUW5MQ7PZ7U2P3KROAOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:34:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，作家协会计划反对派拉蒙与华纳兄弟合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引美国作家协会的一份电子邮件声明报道，代表编剧和新闻编辑的美国作家协会表示，将反对派拉蒙天舞公司与华纳兄弟发现公司的合并交易。【原文：The Writers Guild of America, which represents screenwriters and newsroom staffers, said it will oppose a deal combining Paramount Skydance and Warner Bros Discovery , Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing an emailed statement from the guild.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/writers-guild-plans-oppose-paramount-warner-bros-merger-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRUQDPLROVLMVIGE5QISGT3PIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司因燃料成本增加而下调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空集团（Alaska Air Group）周四下调了 2025 年的利润预期，原因是较高的燃料成本和包括恶劣天气在内的运营挑战影响了其利润率。【原文：Alaska Air Group lowered its 2025 profit forecast on Thursday as higher fuel costs and operational challenges, including adverse weather, weighed on its margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/alaska-air-cuts-annual-profit-forecast-higher-fuel-costs-2025-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANQTKRY7YFJMZATNCCUALJOUQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 9 月核心通胀加速，保持在日本央行目标之上]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的数据显示，日本9月份核心消费者物价同比上涨2.9%，继续高于央行2%的目标，并保持了市场对近期加息的预期。【原文：Japan's core consumer prices rose 2.9% year-on-year in September, data showed on Friday, staying above the central bank's 2% target and keeping alive market expectations of a near-term interest rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-core-inflation-accelerates-september-stays-above-boj-target-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQ2ZMK3S3ZNHVGSQIKT6SLWBJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:47:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚日出能源公司与洛克希德-马丁公司签署五年期钪期权，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚日出能源金属公司（Sunrise Energy Metals）周五表示，该公司已授予美国国防承包商洛克希德-马丁公司（Lockheed Martin）一项选择权，在五年内购买其陆上赛尔斯顿钪项目（Syerston Scandium Project）生产的最多 15 吨氧化钪。【原文：Australia's Sunrise Energy Metals said on Friday it has granted U.S. defence contractor Lockheed Martin an option to purchase up to 15 tonnes of scandium oxide produced over five years from its onshore Syerston Scandium Project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-sunrise-energy-signs-five-year-scandium-option-with-lockheed-martin-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAMK7WPFERND5HZTISEPG2VZWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局称阿拉斯加航空公司航班因技术问题停飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国联邦航空管理局的通知，阿拉斯加航空公司已要求周四晚间在所有机场停飞航班，原因是一个未说明的技术相关问题。【原文：Alaska Airlines has requested the grounding of its flights at all airports on Thursday evening due to an unspecified tech-related issue, according to a U.S. Federal Aviation Administration advisory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/alaska-airlines-flights-grounded-due-tech-issue-faa-says-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSZEKHCJ6NIU5O4UQ63IAYWBUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据加拿大广播公司（CBC）报道，加拿大对斯泰伦特公司和通用汽车公司免关税进口美国制造汽车的数量设置了上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[据加拿大广播公司（CBC News）周四报道，通用汽车公司（General Motors）和斯泰兰蒂斯公司（Stellantis）将不再像以前那样，可以免于支付加拿大对许多美国组装汽车征收的报复性关税。【原文：General Motors and Stellantis will no longer be exempt from paying Canada's retaliatory tariffs on as many U.S.-assembled vehicles as before, CBC News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-caps-how-many-us-made-vehicles-stellantis-gm-can-import-tariff-free-cbc-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5ZZYKC26BMBNII4HHEGUOLVHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济学家估计，美国每周申请失业救济人数增加，领取失业救济金的人数增多]]></title><description><![CDATA[据经济学家周四估计，上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量有所增加，在劳动力市场状况缓和的情况下，10月初领取失业救济金的人数也有所增加。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for jobless benefits increased last week, economists estimated on Thursday, and more people were collecting unemployment checks in early October amid easing labor market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-more-people-collecting-unemployment-checks-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M52BOX36I5JYXCAJCKRI7MBCKA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic 将开设韩国办事处，作为亚洲扩张的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Anthropic的一位高管周四表示，该公司将在韩国开设办事处，以加快其亚洲扩张步伐。【原文：Artificial intelligence startup Anthropic will open an office in South Korea, as it ramps up its Asia expansion, a top executive said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/anthropic-open-south-korea-office-part-asia-expansion-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWNPNUCU5ZN3LF5IER6GL7UYT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian 同意支付 2.5 亿美元解决 IPO 欺诈诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[据法院周四提交的一份文件显示，Rivian 公司已同意以 2.5 亿美元的价格与部分股东就 2022 年的集体诉讼达成和解。【原文：Rivian has agreed to settle a 2022 class-action lawsuit for $250 million with certain shareholders who had alleged that the electric vehicle maker defrauded investors over vehicle prices when it went public, according to a court filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/rivian-agrees-pay-250-million-settle-ipo-fraud-lawsuit-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHRJCJQC3ZJKRGEYQOCRHGXWPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:58:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果开始从休斯顿工厂出货人工智能服务器]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四表示，已开始出货在休斯顿一家工厂制造的人工智能服务器，这也是该公司未来几年在美国投资 6000 亿美元计划的一部分。【原文：Apple has started shipping artificial intelligence servers built in a factory in Houston, it said on Thursday, part of the company's plans to invest $600 billion in the U.S. in the next few years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-begins-shipping-ai-servers-houston-factory-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUSMBJL3B5JIZAOHLWZBMDZOYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音罢工工人将就合同进行投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表 3,200 多名装配战斗机和弹药的波音公司工人的工会周四表示，其成员将于 10 月 26 日就一份合同要约进行投票。【原文：A union representing over 3,200 Boeing workers who assemble fighter jets and munitions said on Thursday that its members will vote on a contract offer on October 26.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-striking-workers-vote-contract-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWY5RGZV7RO5HCV6JX6E5WL63U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Digital Realty 因数据中心服务需求而上调年度核心财务和利润预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字房地产信托公司（Digital Realty Trust）周四上调了对核心运营资金和收入的年度预测，因为该公司预计人工智能的蓬勃发展将增加对数据中心服务的需求。【原文：Digital Realty Trust raised its annual forecasts for core funds from operations and revenue on Thursday, as it expects an increase in demand for data center services due to the boom in artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/digital-realty-raises-annual-core-ffo-revenue-forecasts-data-center-services-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYNDDZOY6RNA7HXARG3VE5WNDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:11:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[域名需求强劲，VeriSign 季度收入增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[互联网服务公司威瑞信（VeriSign）周四公布的第三季度收入增长超过 7%，主要得益于企业建立网上业务时对域名注册的稳定需求。【原文：Internet services company VeriSign reported an over 7% rise in third-quarter revenue on Thursday, driven by steady demand for domain registrations as businesses build their online presence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/verisign-posts-increase-quarterly-revenue-robust-demand-domain-names-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G26B6M3DJFMVRM2LUQDEGOJI7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:08:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能数据中心初创企业克鲁索（Crusoe）在最新一轮融资中募集资金 13.8 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能数据中心初创公司克鲁索（Crusoe）周四表示，预计将在 E 轮融资中筹集 13.8 亿美元，估值约为 100 亿美元。【原文：AI data centre startup Crusoe is raising $1.38 billion at a valuation of about $10 billion from an anticipated Series E funding round, the Denver-based company said on Thursday】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ai-data-centre-startup-crusoe-raising-138-billion-latest-funding-round-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XNVIBQ4XVLODHMYASUNZO5EQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据中心公司 Equinix 拓展巴西市场，将其视为优先市场，总监如是说]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国数据中心运营商 Equinix 拉丁美洲常务董事 Eduardo Zago 周四表示，Equinix 正在扩大其在巴西的业务，该公司视巴西为优先市场。【原文：U.S. data center operator Equinix is expanding its operations in Brazil, which the firm sees as a priority market, its managing director for Latin America Eduardo Zago said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/data-center-firm-equinix-expands-brazil-sees-it-priority-market-director-says-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYR57CXYIRLRPH6LZ5IDG65CLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[应用材料公司将裁员 4% 以简化运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片设备制造商应用材料公司（Applied Materials）周四表示，由于美国收紧半导体出口管制，该公司将裁员约 4%，即大约 1400 个工作岗位，以精简业务。【原文：Applied Materials will cut about 4% of its workforce, or roughly 1,400 jobs, to streamline operations, the chip equipment maker said on Thursday as tighter U.S. export controls on semiconductors weigh on its business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/applied-materials-lay-off-4-workforce-simplify-operations-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3GFPQ5TCFMV5GUQM57Q3JCKME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：中美缓和，石油大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[受中美贸易紧张局势降温的提振，美国和全球股市周四上涨；而在华盛顿制裁两家俄罗斯石油巨头，引发对全球供应的担忧后，油价大涨5%。【原文：U.S. and world stocks rose on Thursday, boosted by a cooling in U.S.-China trade tensions, while oil prices rocketed 5% after Washington sanctioned two Russian oil giants, raising concern about global supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRUFKFHWUBI5ZISFC6UTD2UNEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯利润超预期，工业和能源技术部门表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[油田服务供应商贝克休斯周四公布的第三季度利润超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于其工业和能源技术部门的强劲表现。【原文：Oilfield services provider Baker Hughes surpassed Wall Street expectations for third-quarter profit on Thursday, helped by strength in its industrial and energy technology unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/baker-hughes-beats-third-quarter-profit-estimates-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJR6MQBLW5NTPHR5K4LYSXUGSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic 将使用 100 万个谷歌云 TPU 芯片训练其克劳德聊天机器人]]></title><description><![CDATA[Anthropic 公司周四表示，将使用价值数百亿美元的一百万个谷歌云张量处理单元对克劳德模型进行训练。【原文：Anthropic said on Thursday it Claude models would be trained using up to one million of Google Cloud's tensor processing units, worth tens of billions of dollars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/anthropic-expand-use-google-clouds-tpu-chips-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDXV5ZI6PROWPK7S3RH5TQ3GOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，塔吉特计划裁员 1800 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，作为扭转销售停滞战略的一部分，塔吉特计划裁员约 1800 人。【原文：Target plans to lay off around 1,800 employees as part of its strategy to reverse stagnant sales, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/target-plans-lay-off-1800-employees-wsj-reports-2025-10-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLRFV6LUYNJ5RJPWFD4LTJURIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:25:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>