<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 05:35:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 05:35:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[北京发布促进无人驾驶汽车在首都使用的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国首都北京周二通过了鼓励城市自动驾驶技术的新法规，当局计划最终允许公共汽车和出租车采用无人驾驶技术。【原文：China's capital Beijing passed new regulations on Tuesday to encourage autonomous driving technology in the city, with authorities planning to eventually allow driverless public buses and taxis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/beijing-unveils-plans-boost-driverless-vehicle-use-capital-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BZHS3EETJMAPLSNV2YQCKWPFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 05:19:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可可连续两年位居全球大宗商品涨幅榜首，钢铁配料因中国需求而举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球供应短缺，可可和咖啡将在 2024 年结束时连续第二年成为大宗商品中涨幅最大的品种，而炼钢用煤炭由于受到中国经济增长放缓的影响，将成为表现最差的品种。【原文：Cocoa and coffee are poised to close 2024 as the biggest gainers among commodities for a second year on a global supply deficit, while steel-making coal will end as the worst performer, hit by slow growth in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/cocoa-tops-global-commodities-rally-2nd-year-steel-ingredients-struggle-china-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IIGKYEOU5IJZPI5C3UAL4GUIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 05:19:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市和美元坚挺，2024 年强劲收官]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市在谨慎的年末交易中有所回落，投资者缩减了对美国在2025年大幅降息的押注，并为即将上任的特朗普政府做好准备，美元兑大多数其他货币保持高位。【原文：Asian stocks eased on Tuesday in cautious end-of-year trading that has seen investors scale back bets of deep U.S. rate cuts in 2025 and brace for the incoming Trump administration, with the dollar standing tall against most other currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WIU6I6U65O7LI4MAZOVYD72ZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 03:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金有望迎来十多年来最好的一年]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二是多事之秋的最后一个交易日，金价变化不大。【原文：Gold prices were little changed on Tuesday, the last trading day of an eventful year that saw the metal post its best annual performance in more than a decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-track-best-year-over-decade-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AB3ARFQWNM3NNZLVOYHPYNTDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易风险上升，中国 12 月工厂活动增速放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项官方工厂调查显示，12月份中国制造业活动连续第三个月实现增长，但增长乏力，这表明在新的贸易风险隐现之际，政策刺激的效果可能需要更多时间来提供支持。【原文：China's manufacturing activity grew for a third straight month in December but barely, an official factory survey showed on Tuesday, suggesting the effects of policy stimulus may take more time to lend support as fresh trade risks loom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-dec-factory-activity-expands-slower-pace-trade-risks-rise-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCTDYZS7XJKBFM6YAQE6FQVSWA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油因中国工厂活动扩大而上涨，但年底将走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，油价在数据显示中国12月制造业活动扩张后上涨，但由于主要消费国的需求担忧，油价将连续第二年收低。【原文：Oil prices rose in early trade on Tuesday after data showed China's manufacturing activity expanded in December, but for a second consecutive year oil was on track to end lower due to demand concerns in top consuming countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-expanding-chinese-factory-activity-set-end-year-lower-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUQT47URGVIHNKHC5A63RZHZX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 12 月制造业活动连续第三个月扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项官方工厂调查显示，中国的制造业活动在 12 月份连续第三个月扩张，但速度有所放缓，这表明新一轮刺激措施正在帮助支撑世界第二大经济体。【原文：China's manufacturing activity expanded for a third straight month in December but at a slower pace, an official factory survey showed on Tuesday, suggesting a blitz of fresh stimulus is helping to support the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-dec-manufacturing-activity-expands-third-month-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCSUBOGBKZIPRCKRL6NPL2JCCU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 01:41:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谨慎的美联储和特朗普贸易支撑美元在 2024 年屹立不倒]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元在今年的最后一个交易日表现坚挺，2024 年美元对大多数货币都将强劲上涨，因为投资者对美国降息次数减少和即将上任的特朗普政府的政策做好了准备。【原文：The dollar was firm on the last trading day of the year, poised to clock strong gains in 2024 against most currencies as investors prepared for fewer U.S. rate cuts and the incoming Trump administration's policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-stands-tall-2024-propped-up-by-cautious-fed-trump-trade-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5PYEYKQTVJGBKIMJU6VQYTLT4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 01:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州州长向监管机构投诉 PJM 电力市场规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州州长乔希-夏皮罗（Josh Shapiro）周一向联邦能源监管机构提交了一份针对 PJM Interconnection 的投诉，认为这家美国最大的电网运营商必须改变其市场规则，否则将面临电力成本飙升的风险。【原文：Pennsylvania Governor Josh Shapiro filed a complaint with a federal energy regulator against PJM Interconnection on Monday, arguing that the largest U.S. power grid operator must change its market rules or risk soaring electricity costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pennsylvania-governor-complains-regulator-about-pjms-power-market-rules-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5E2DLQWQVOUPOLNN3FEZKF2TE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 23:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行监管机构要求贝莱德在一月内解决银行股权问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国联邦存款保险公司已通知资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock）在 1 月 10 日之前接受一项协议，该协议将允许该机构加强对其在联邦存款保险公司监管下的银行机构投资的审查。【原文：The U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation has told asset manager BlackRock it has until Jan. 10 to accept an agreement that would allow the agency to step up scrutiny of its investments in FDIC-regulated banking institutions, according to a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-regulator-gives-blackrock-january-deadline-bank-stakes-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OF4WVW537RI2JIKTO4YUY5S2XU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 22:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[淡水河谷与巴西当局就铁路特许经营权达成 18 亿美元协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷在一份证券文件中称，该公司周一与地方当局达成协议，将支付高达 110 亿雷亚尔（约合 17.8 亿美元）的费用，以重新谈判两项铁路特许经营权的合同。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale said on Monday it reached an agreement with local authorities under which it would pay up to 11 billion reais ($1.78 billion) to renegotiate the contracts of two railway concessions, the firm said in a securities filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/vale-reaches-18-bln-agreement-with-brazil-authorities-over-railway-concessions-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2FDDBCHIFIAVN4A67AOFAGECA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对金融科技应用戴夫及其首席执行官提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周一对金融科技公司 Dave Inc 及其首席执行官 Jason Wilk 提起诉讼，并宣布对其采取民事强制措施，指控其违反联邦法律。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department filed a complaint and announced a civil enforcement action on Monday against financial technology company Dave Inc and its CEO Jason Wilk for alleged violations of federal law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-announces-civil-enforcement-action-against-fintech-app-dave-its-ceo-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZ4ORVPI3BN2NEHAHI2PC7XYGY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:32:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[刑事调查仍在继续，ADM 股东要求首席执行官辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[Archer-Daniels-Midland 公司的一名股东正在敦促该公司首席执行官辞职，因为他没有明确告诉投资者该公司内部会计做法存在问题，而路透社首先报道了这一问题引发的刑事调查。【原文：A shareholder of Archer-Daniels-Midland is pressing the company's CEO to resign for failing to clearly tell investors about problems with its internal accounting practices that have sparked a criminal investigation first reported by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/adm-shareholder-presses-ceo-resign-criminal-probe-continues-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5RML6BYUJNTBGZ2UYTSF7DF2U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:25:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citgo 股票拍卖案法官驳回阻止 Gramercy 基金诉讼的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法官在周一发布的一项命令中裁定，三家公司为增加在 Citgo 石油公司母公司股份拍卖中获得收益的机会而提起的诉讼可以继续进行。【原文：Lawsuits by three firms seeking to improve their chances of obtaining proceeds in an auction of shares in Citgo Petroleum's parent can go ahead, a U.S. judge ruled in an order issued on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-citgo-share-auction-rejects-bid-block-gramercy-fund-lawsuits-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OV2SRMWOZJPKNEN7VMPNCAXPDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[李-哈斯勒特-陈将辞去华纳兄弟探索公司董事会职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司周一在一份监管文件中披露，该公司董事会成员兼提名与公司治理委员会成员 Li Haslett Chen 将于 2025 年 1 月 31 日辞职。【原文：Li Haslett Chen, a member of the Warner Bros. Discovery board and a member of the company's Nominating and Corporate Governance Committee, will resign from her positions, effective Jan. 31, 2025, the company disclosed in a regulatory filing on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/li-haslett-chen-resign-warner-bros-discovery-board-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGD3MYBEDNJHDKM66VGMRYZCTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府基金完成对麦道夫的赔付，麦道夫受害者获赔 43 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府赔偿受麦道夫诈骗者的基金周一宣布了第十次也是最后一次分配，称将向已故庞氏骗局受害者中的 40,930 人支付 43 亿美元。【原文：A U.S. government fund to compensate people swindled by Bernard Madoff announced its tenth and final distribution on Monday, saying it will have paid out $4.3 billion to 40,930 of the late Ponzi schemer's victims.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bernard-madoffs-victims-collect-43-billion-us-government-fund-completes-payouts-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72JYWHSP6RNUBPDIE3ZOE5CFIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部称中国黑客在 "重大事件 "中窃取文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周一获得的一封致立法者的信称，中国国家支持的黑客本月早些时候入侵了美国财政部，并从其工作站中窃取了文件。【原文：Chinese state-sponsored hackers broke into the U.S. Treasury Department earlier this month and stole documents from its workstations, according to a letter to lawmakers that was provided to Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-treasurys-workstations-hacked-cyberattack-by-china-afp-reports-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGAS2OE6JBMDXP2KNXDIVSC4VY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比尔-阿克曼期待特朗普将房利美和房地美私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[这位亿万富翁投资者周一表示，比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）预计美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将解除对房利美（Fannie Mae）和房地美（Freddie Mac）的监管，使其有可能重新成为私营公司。【原文：Bill Ackman expects U.S. President-elect Donald Trump to remove Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac from conservatorship, potentially making them private companies again, the billionaire investor said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bill-ackman-expects-trump-privatize-fannie-mae-freddie-mac-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YHFZL4MABI2NHGNDCFKMSRQJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:14:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国新成立的空中出租车公司 Volocopter 申请破产]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中出租车初创公司 Volocopter GmbH 周一申请破产程序，理由是无力筹集新资金以维持正常运营。【原文：Air taxi start-up Volocopter GmbH filed for insolvency proceedings on Monday, citing its inability to raise new funds to maintain regular operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/german-air-taxi-start-up-volocopter-files-insolvency-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MTKEKD2SBMNVKIAFMWYF4L3YU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 19:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街将于 1 月 9 日闭市以纪念卡特总统]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易所将于 1 月 9 日（周四）闭市，以纪念周日去世的美国前总统吉米-卡特（Jimmy Carter），他享年 100 岁。【原文：U.S. stock exchanges will close on Thursday, January 9 in observation of a national day of mourning in honor of former U.S. President Jimmy Carter, who died on Sunday at the age of 100.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/wall-street-close-jan-9-honor-president-jimmy-carter-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUETVP2CNVMQRALG767R5NQF4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:54:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月成屋销售创 21 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管抵押贷款利率居高不下，但由于购房者集中利用库存改善的优势，11 月份美国旧房购买合同增幅超过预期，连续第四个月实现上涨。【原文：Contracts to buy U.S. previously owned homes rose more than expected in November, notching a fourth straight month of gains as buyers focused on taking advantage of improved inventory despite stubbornly high mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-pending-home-sales-hit-21-month-high-november-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIZ36JVSUZKBZO6AWM7G2PXV4I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 15:05:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[切尼尔公司在科珀斯克里斯蒂三期项目生产出首批液化天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[切尼尔能源公司（Cheniere Energy）周一表示，其科珀斯克里斯蒂第三阶段液化项目（Corpus Christi Stage 3 Liquefaction Project）的第一条生产线（1 号线）首次生产出液化天然气（LNG）。【原文：Cheniere Energy on Monday said that liquefied natural gas (LNG) was produced for the first time from the first train (Train 1) of its Corpus Christi Stage 3 Liquefaction Project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/cheniere-produces-first-lng-corpus-christi-stage-3-project-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWYJGYVYUFK2DET2E5N4S3XEYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达斥资 7 亿美元完成 Run:ai 收购案，但仍面临监管障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）周一表示，已完成对以色列人工智能公司Run:ai的收购，此前该收购案曾受到反垄断审查。【原文：Chipmaker Nvidia has completed its acquisition of Israeli AI firm Run:ai, the startup said on Monday, following antitrust scrutiny over the buyout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nvidia-closes-700-mln-runai-acquisition-after-regulatory-hurdles-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CM2KJSFKVKBBAWBEGD67KQGUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银集团老板警告说，在银行业全面改革前应避免过度监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥-埃尔莫蒂（Sergio Ermotti）被引述说，瑞士不应该为其银行业制定使其处于不利地位的规则，因为瑞士正准备在其银行收购瑞士信贷之后对监管进行全面改革。【原文：Switzerland should not set rules for its banking sector that put it at a disadvantage, UBS CEO Sergio Ermotti was quoted as saying on Monday, as the country prepares to overhaul regulation following his bank's takeover of Credit Suisse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-boss-warns-against-excessive-banking-regulation-ahead-overhaul-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YM7R5PUCUBKADG6ZTFMUFJEKBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 12:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国债收益率上升，华尔街期货下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货在清淡的交易量中下滑，因为国债收益率的上升有可能给股市历史上强劲的年末走势带来压力。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped in light trading volumes on Monday as elevated Treasury yields threatened to pressure a historically strong year-end period for equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-futures-slip-elevated-treasury-yields-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBCB2NDZYJKJNFGSPRGQKHRX7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 11:21:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢拉拥护巴西新任央行行长令市场警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[经过几个月的争吵，巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦和巴西央行之间的关系看起来将迎来一个甜蜜和光明的时代--这正是一些投资者所担心的。【原文：After months of rancor, ties between President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva and Brazil's central bank look poised for an era of sweetness and light - which is precisely what worries some investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/lulas-embrace-new-brazil-central-banker-has-markets-wary-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FH4YYXURJBPIBDP44UBGL3F3PQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 11:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经纪人称，1 月 1 日全球部分财产巨灾再保险费率将下降 5%至 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[再保险经纪公司盖伊-卡彭特（Guy Carpenter）周一表示，全球财产巨灾再保险费率将于 1 月 1 日下降 5%至 15%，这是因为在费率连年上涨之后，市场竞争变得更加激烈。【原文：Global property catastrophe reinsurance rates will fall 5% to 15% on Jan. 1 for books of businesses which have not suffered losses, reinsurance broker Guy Carpenter said on Monday, as the market becomes more competitive after years of rate rises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/some-global-property-catastrophe-reinsurance-rates-fall-5-15-jan-1-broker-says-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5DML5AYN5IGHA6I2EA6KCI3JY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 07:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 12 月制造业活动连续第三个月扩张：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的工厂活动可能在 12 月份连续第三个月实现增长，这给试图稳定世界第二大经济体的官员们带来了一丝乐观，因为他们正为特朗普第二任政府进一步征收美国贸易关税做准备。【原文：China's factory activity likely expanded for a third straight month in December, offering a glimmer of optimism to officials trying to steady the world's No. 2 economy as they brace for further U.S. trade tariffs under a second Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-dec-manufacturing-activity-seen-expanding-third-month-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCOAK5ZJPBIXBD4TYXOEPSKWUY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 04:56:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[举报人举报后，新加坡邮政任命新首席财务官，进行行政改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡邮政周日表示，任命现任澳大利亚业务首席财务官 Isaac Mah 为集团财务总监，此前一周，该公司因对举报人报告处理不当而解雇了包括首席财务官在内的三名高管。【原文：Singapore Post appointed Isaac Mah, the current CFO of its Australia business, as group finance chief, the company said on Sunday, a week after dismissing three senior executives, including its CFO, over mishandling a whistleblower report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-post-names-new-cfo-executive-overhaul-after-whistleblower-report-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVFFRWE3LZP6FDWP3V4IDZWQMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 03:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油在清淡交易中走低，投资者关注中国和美国数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，油价在年底前的清淡假日交易中走低，因为交易商在等待本周晚些时候来自中国和美国的更多经济数据，以评估世界上最大的两个石油消费国的经济增长情况。【原文：Oil prices slipped lower on Monday in thin holiday trade ahead of the year-end as traders awaited more economic data from China and the U.S. later this week to assess growth in the world's two largest oil consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-inches-lower-thin-trade-investors-eye-china-us-data-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBRAWD3QDJN3PP5XODK722QC7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 01:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>