<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:10:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:10:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[微软成立 "超级智能 "团队，以医疗诊断为起点]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软正在组建一个新的团队，希望从医疗诊断开始，在某些领域打造能力远超人类的人工智能。【原文：Microsoft is forming a new team that wants to build artificial intelligence that is vastly more capable than humans in certain domains, starting with medical diagnostics, the executive leading the effort told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-launches-superintelligence-team-targeting-medical-diagnosis-start-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLWWFHNQA5LUXIC72D34QKHWLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大型央行的宽松政策即将结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[大型经济体的央行已接近其降息周期的尾声，尽管有些央行，如美国联邦储备委员会和英格兰银行在今年早些时候较为谨慎，但仍有余地再宽松一些。【原文：Central banks in big economies are nearing the end of their rate-cutting cycles, though some, like the U.S. Federal Reserve and Bank of England - which were more cautious earlier in the year - have scope to ease a little more.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-cenbank-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TY42LP7Y7NPFVBTO5SDTVPPIZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[发电需求强劲，康明斯季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卡车发动机制造商康明斯（Cummins）周四公布的第三季度业绩高于华尔街预期，主要原因是发电系统和配电业务需求强劲，股价盘前上涨超过 7%。【原文：U.S. truck engine maker Cummins on Thursday reported third-quarter results above Wall Street estimates, driven by strong demand for its power generation systems and distribution segments, sending its shares up more than 7% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cummins-beats-quarterly-estimates-strong-power-generation-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVYHBZAJ5JLLBHZ7S62QT3ZIZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:54:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在价值 100 亿美元的肥胖症药物争夺战中，美塞拉权衡辉瑞和诺和诺德的竞标价]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）与美国竞争对手辉瑞公司（Pfizer）为争夺 Metsera 的肥胖症药物资产而展开了一场价值 100 亿美元的竞购战。【原文：A bidding war over U.S. biotech Metsera was coming to a head on Thursday, with Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk locked in a $10 billion battle with U.S. rival Pfizer to win Metsera's obesity drug assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/metsera-weighs-rival-bids-pfizer-novo-10-billion-obesity-drug-battle-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQJMF33MVFLNNJP4QWMAOJ7NJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室：如果最高法院驳回特朗普的关税要求，财政部将解决退款问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高贸易官员周四表示，如果美国最高法院裁定唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税无效，一些原告在某些情况下可以获得退款，但财政部必须制定付款时间表。【原文：Some plaintiffs could get a refund in certain situations if the U.S. Supreme Court rules against President Donald Trump's tariffs, but the Treasury would have to figure out any payment schedules, the nation's top trade official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ustr-treasury-would-sort-out-any-refunds-if-top-court-nixes-trumps-tariffs-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQH2EK4ZXNNZ3NLC5ZOZTOCMRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行的贝利如果市场对回报定价过高，人工智能将面临泡沫风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）周四表示，尽管人工智能技术可能会大幅提高生产率，但市场可能会出现人工智能引发的泡沫。【原文：Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey said on Thursday there could be an artificial intelligence-induced bubble in markets, notwithstanding the large productivity boost the technology would likely deliver.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/boes-bailey-risk-ai-bubble-if-markets-over-price-returns-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KILS7AJGJJM6LEVEUUGLS4YHN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥联储估计美国 10 月失业率回升至 4.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[据芝加哥联储周四公布的一项估计，由于失业工人的招聘率放缓，裁员和其他离职率上升，美国10月份的失业率可能升至四年来的最高点。【原文：The U.S. jobless rate likely edged up in October to the highest in four years as the hiring rate for unemployed workers slowed and the rate of layoffs and other job separations increased, according to an estimate by the Chicago Fed released Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-unemployment-rate-rounds-up-44-october-chicago-fed-estimates-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46ORHUP4INMFBBR3Z5FCSIYRNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受益于自动化需求，罗克韦尔第四季度利润和营收超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受成本削减和自动化需求持续增长的影响，罗克韦尔自动化公司周四公布的第四季度利润和收入均超过预期，股价在盘前交易中上涨约 5%。【原文：Rockwell Automation topped fourth-quarter estimates for profit and revenue on Thursday, helped by cost cuts and sustained demand for automation, sending its shares up about 5% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/rockwell-tops-fourth-quarter-profit-revenue-estimates-automation-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R55PWSEO7JNBXBXM3DIWB7AHFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:29:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Datadog 预测人工智能驱动的安全需求将带来强劲的第四季度收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[Datadog 周四预测第四季度盈利将高于华尔街预期，押注于采用人工智能技术的企业对其云安全产品的强劲需求。【原文：Datadog forecast fourth-quarter earnings above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, betting on strong demand for its cloud-security products from businesses adopting artificial intelligence technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/datadog-forecasts-strong-fourth-quarter-earnings-ai-driven-security-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSMGZAOGNZKOVD6TVENGCJQB4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:26:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton 因座椅安全风险召回约 83.3 万辆自行车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费品安全委员会周四表示，Peloton Interactive公司将召回约83.3万辆PL02型Original Bike+自行车，因为这种自行车的座管组件在使用过程中可能会断裂，有摔倒和受伤的危险。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission said on Thursday Peloton Interactive is recalling about 833,000 units of its Original Bike+ Model PL02 as the bike's seat post assembly could break during use, posing a risk of falls and injuries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/peloton-recalls-about-833000-bikes-over-seat-safety-risk-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFBPPFWVX5JAHNOGWPPAWBXR4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州寻求在泰诺诉讼中阻止 Kenvue 分红]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州总检察长肯-帕克斯顿（Ken Paxton）周四要求州法官阻止 Kenvue 在本月支付近 4 亿美元的股东分红，因为他起诉这家制药商涉嫌隐瞒孕妇使用泰诺对儿童造成的风险。【原文：Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton on Thursday asked a state judge to block Kenvue from paying a nearly $400 million shareholder dividend this month, after suing the drugmaker for allegedly concealing risks to children from the use of Tylenol by pregnant women.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/texas-seeks-block-kenvue-dividend-amid-tylenol-lawsuit-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I37QOAZM2VMNTCRT7Q34IBPCPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉尔夫-劳伦（Ralph Lauren）上调年度收入预期，原因是需求恢复强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉尔夫-劳伦（Ralph Lauren）周四上调了年度收入预期，押注在经济不确定性上升的情况下，对其高价位 Polo 衬衫和棉质电缆针织毛衣的需求将出现恢复性增长。【原文：Ralph Lauren raised its annual revenue forecast on Thursday, betting on resilient demand for its high-priced Polo shirts and cotton cable knit sweaters amid rising economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ralph-lauren-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-resilient-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWNC5V25HVI5FMGFUOPYW6J7XE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺维信凭借疫苗交易的优势上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺维信公司（Novavax）周四今年第三次上调了年度营收预期，主要得益于与日本武田制药公司（Takeda Pharmaceuticals）等达成的疫苗供应和许可协议所带来的里程碑付款。【原文：Novavax raised its annual revenue forecast for the third time this year on Thursday, banking on milestone payments from vaccine supply and licensing deals such as with Japan's Takeda Pharmaceuticals .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novavax-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-milestone-payment-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7K6FC3ARVMFPOTRWUXJ35NVYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Helios Towers 第三季度业绩超预期，推出 4 亿美元股东回报计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[电信塔运营商 Helios Towers 周四公布了强于预期的第三季度业绩，并启动了 7500 万美元的股票回购计划，作为新五年计划的一部分，该计划的目标是为投资者带来超过 4 亿美元的回报。【原文：Telecom towers operator Helios Towers on Thursday reported stronger-than-expected third‑quarter results and launched a $75 million share buyback as part of a new five‑year plan targeting more than $400 million in returns to investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/helios-towers-beats-q3-forecast-unveils-400-million-shareholder-returns-plan-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NDMRPTX5ZIMPMQ6D2JJTP4UDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EPAM 上调 2025 年预测，因 IT 服务支出强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[EPAM Systems今年第三次上调了年度盈利预期，原因是企业为实现人工智能系统的现代化投入了更多资金，这使得这家IT咨询公司的股价在周四的盘前交易中上涨了4%。【原文：EPAM Systems raised its annual earnings forecast for the third time this year as businesses spend more to modernize their systems for artificial intelligence, sending shares of the IT consultancy firm 4% higher in premarket trading on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/epam-raises-2025-forecasts-strong-it-services-spending-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQW3WIOO6RKQREPA2NLGIZ2ORU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各国在世贸组织寻求延长电子商务关税暂停期]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织周四的一份文件显示，一些国家正在寻求延长世界贸易组织关于不对数字传输征收关税的协议。【原文：A group of states is seeking to extend a World Trade Organization agreement to refrain from placing customs duties on digital transmissions, a World Trade Organization document showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/states-seek-extension-e-commerce-tariff-moratorium-wto-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECFB6GBM6NJMRJV2S637PEV5J4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ESPN 和 PENN Entertainment 将提前结束美国体育博彩合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国彭氏娱乐公司（PENN Entertainment）和沃尔特-迪斯尼公司（Walt Disney）旗下的 ESPN 周四表示，双方已同意终止其在美国的独家在线体育博彩合作关系，自 12 月 1 日起生效。【原文：PENN Entertainment and Walt Disney's ESPN have agreed to end their exclusive U.S. online sports betting partnership, effective December 1, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/espn-penn-entertainment-end-us-sports-betting-partnership-early-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEXITZJZXFL2ZD3BIDDHLA6NOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:33:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行在刀锋表决中维持利率不变，暗示将于 12 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行周四继续按兵不动，但投票结果以微弱优势胜出，而且有迹象表明，行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）可能很快会加入寻求降息的行列，这为本月晚些时候政府预算案出台后的降息行动敞开了大门。【原文：The Bank of England kept borrowing costs on hold on Thursday, but a narrow vote and signs that Governor Andrew Bailey might soon join those seeking a rate cut keeps the door open for a move following the government's budget later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/bank-england-keeps-rates-hold-knife-edge-vote-that-hints-december-cut-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CL6XIF5WZRPWXPS6Z7567UPSAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KFF民调显示，大多数美国人支持在政府停摆期间延长奥巴马医改税收抵免政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据研究公司 KFF 的一项最新民调显示，公众对延长奥巴马医改税收抵免政策的支持率仍然很高。【原文：Public support remains strong for extending the Obamacare tax credits, which have been central to the U.S. government shutdown due to disagreements over their inclusion in funding packages, according to a new poll from research firm KFF.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/most-americans-back-extending-obamacare-tax-credits-amid-government-shutdown-kff-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJA3CMD7JFJ3NNLLYY7MB6BC64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:27:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尔维对在支持力度更大的美国建设稀土工厂持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[化工集团索尔维公司首席执行官周四表示，该公司有意在美国建立一家稀土加工厂，因为美国的财政支持力度比欧洲大。【原文：Chemicals group Solvay would be interested in building a rare earths processing plant in the United States, where financial support is stronger than in Europe, its CEO said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/solvay-open-building-rare-earths-plant-us-where-support-is-stronger-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FW4Q777KXZNDVAYCRTOXAJJOQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银支持的 Metropolis 融资 16 亿美元，拓展人工智能停车场以外的业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家利用人工智能和计算机视觉识别车辆的停车场运营商 Metropolis Technologies 公司周四表示，该公司已筹集到 16 亿美元新资金，用于将其技术推广到零售、餐饮和加油站等行业。【原文：Metropolis Technologies, a U.S. operator of parking lots that uses artificial intelligence and computer vision to recognize vehicles, has raised $1.6 billion in fresh capital to extend its technology into sectors such as retail, restaurants and gas stations, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-backed-metropolis-raises-16-bln-expand-beyond-ai-powered-parking-lots-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I7TFMSZZBPGBIKRDCFC7MZZIA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司业绩未达预期，可能出售或分拆]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）周四公布的季度亏损超过预期，原因是其流媒体部门增长乏力，有线电视业务持续下滑，抵消了该媒体巨头电影制片厂部门的强劲表现。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery posted a bigger-than-expected quarterly loss on Thursday, as lackluster growth in its streaming unit and persistent declines in its cable TV business more than offset a strong showing from the media giant's studio division.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/warner-bros-discovery-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKUTV5B6NNIUZNCJ4HBPDW724U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:13:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[产量增加，康菲石油公司季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[康菲石油公司（ConocoPhillips）周四公布的第三季度利润超出华尔街预期，原因是石油和天然气产量增加以及成本削减措施帮助抵消了大宗商品价格下跌的影响。【原文：ConocoPhillips beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter profit on Thursday, as higher oil and gas production and cost-cutting efforts helped offset lower commodity prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/conocophillips-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-higher-production-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">352M3NT2EFIQRGLDQDJDLLP3KU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道英伟达支持的 Vast Data 与 CoreWeave 签订 11.7 亿美元的人工智能协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Vast Data告诉路透社，该公司已与云服务提供商CoreWeave签署了价值11.7亿美元的商业协议，随着对人工智能系统基础设施需求的增长，双方将扩大现有的合作关系。【原文：AI startup Vast Data has signed a $1.17 billion commercial agreement with cloud provider CoreWeave, extending their existing partnership as demand for infrastructure that powers artificial intelligence systems grows, the company told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-backed-vast-data-inks-117-billion-ai-deal-with-coreweave-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASLTY3K6GBNORHFDNNDZEPBFH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行在刀锋表决中维持利率不变，暗示不久将降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[作者：威廉-肖姆伯格、戴维-米利肯和苏班-阿卜杜拉【原文：By William Schomberg, David Milliken and Suban Abdulla】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/bank-england-keeps-rates-hold-knife-edge-vote-that-hints-cut-soon-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNOHFUTPNBOKBP6IBUUIOEMFMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:03:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大鹅季度销售额低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大奢侈服装制造商加拿大鹅周四公布的第二季度营收不及分析师预期，原因是尽管该公司努力加强营销和促销策略，但需求依然疲软。【原文：Canadian luxury apparel maker Canada Goose missed analysts' estimates for second-quarter revenue on Thursday, as demand remained soft despite its efforts to strengthen its marketing and promotional strategies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-goose-misses-quarterly-sales-estimates-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZIHZPUGCNPWFLKFDFXNVHUBWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通下挫，华尔街期货低迷，关注经济数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国股指期货走势低迷，高通公司股价下跌加剧了市场对科技股估值过高的担忧，而喜忧参半的经济数据则加剧了美国经济的不确定性。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were muted on Thursday, as a drop in Qualcomm's shares added to concerns about stretched valuations in technology stocks, while mixed economic data fueled uncertainty about the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-subdued-qualcomm-dips-focus-economic-data-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GNUCTVIINKM3LV6RDP25QNCUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:53:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[虎斑猫热推动手提包销售，挂毯提升年度目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tapestry 努力保护利润不受关税的影响，Kate Spade 产品线的精简，以及 Coach 的 Tabby 手袋在年轻一代中的强劲需求，帮助该公司在周四提高了年度利润和销售目标。【原文：Tapestry's efforts to protect margins against tariffs, a leaner Kate Spade product line and strong Gen-Z demand for Coach's Tabby handbags helped the company lift its annual profit and sales targets on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tapestry-lifts-annual-targets-tabby-craze-fuels-handbag-sales-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXOOAVIJPNKZVJWUS7XI2DYEHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:52:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府下令削减航班，美国航空公司争相调整时刻表]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府下令削减美国一些最繁忙机场的航班后，美国航空公司周四争先恐后地重新调整航班时刻表，并处理大量客户的询问，这是政府长期停摆造成的最新一次旅行中断。【原文：U.S. airlines were scrambling on Thursday to rejig schedules and fielding a flood of customer queries after the U.S. ordered flight cuts at some of the nation's busiest airports, the latest travel disruption from the prolonged government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-airlines-scramble-rejig-schedules-government-orders-flight-cuts-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQU5WH7W7RKNLMYD5DZAHSLHQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:52:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司的实验性药物在中期试验中显示出希望，体重减轻了 20.1%]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周四表示，其试验性肥胖症药物在一项中期试验中帮助患者减轻了多达20.1%的体重。【原文：Eli Lilly said on Thursday its experimental obesity drug helped patients lose as much as 20.1% of their weight in a mid-stage trial.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/lillys-experimental-drug-shows-promise-with-201-weight-loss-mid-stage-trial-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CW5FCKKMRIWNNSS55E3GYVS64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>