<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:05:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:05:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[芯片冷却初创公司 Corintis 募集 2400 万美元，英特尔首席执行官陈立武加入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士初创公司 Corintis 承诺提供更快速的液体芯片冷却技术，该公司已融资 2400 万美元，英特尔公司首席执行官陈立武也加入了公司董事会，因为人工智能推动了对更好的半导体热管理工具的需求。【原文：Corintis, a Swiss startup promising more rapid liquid chip-cooling technology, has raised $24 million and added Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan to its board as artificial intelligence fuels demand for better heat management tools for semiconductors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chip-cooling-startup-corintis-raises-24-million-adds-intel-ceo-lip-bu-tan-board-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNDVLBRDDNPIFNFV4BV6T2OMXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外长称美挪就财富基金退出卡特彼勒的争执正在平息]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威外交大臣埃斯彭-巴特-艾德（Espen Barth Eide）表示，美国和挪威之间因北欧国家财富基金从美国建筑设备制造商卡特彼勒撤资而引发的争执似乎即将结束。【原文：A spat between the United States and Norway over the Nordic country's wealth fund's divestment from U.S. construction equipment-maker Caterpillar appears to be coming to an end, Norwegian Foreign Minister Espen Barth Eide said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-norway-spat-over-wealth-funds-caterpillar-exit-is-settling-foreign-minister-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNSOFOZNQNOU7BKH6NDWKUAMA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:55:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金流动 美国、亚洲投资者转向欧洲和中东对冲基金，美国银行调查显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四看到的一份美国银行调查显示，美国和亚洲的富裕投资者取消了今年将资金投入美国对冲基金的计划，同时增加了对欧洲和中东的投资。【原文：Wealthy investors in the United States and Asia have cancelled plans to put money into U.S. hedge funds this year, while increasing their exposure to Europe and the Middle East, according to a Bank of America survey seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hedge-flow-us-asian-investors-turn-european-mideast-hedge-funds-bofa-survey-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6ER7TTDKZNYZFQA326YEB64WU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：更多美联储言论，更多问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VYRBRAXZZOVHJKDQTOVTNKVKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃森哲第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃森哲周四公布的第四季度营收略高于华尔街预期，原因是企业客户对其人工智能驱动的咨询和服务的需求保持强劲。【原文：Accenture on Thursday reported fourth-quarter revenue slightly above Wall Street estimates, driven by resilient demand from enterprise clients for its AI-driven consulting and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/accenture-posts-fourth-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T32PLCOOJJJV7I44DNJO3UDOJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国政府关门如何影响金融市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着国会民主党和共和党在如何继续为联邦政府提供资金的问题上陷入僵局，美国政府下周开始部分停摆的风险正在上升。【原文：The risk of a partial U.S. government shutdown beginning next week is rising as congressional Democrats and Republicans hit an impasse over how to continue to fund the federal government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/how-us-government-shutdown-could-affect-financial-markets-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSVA4HMMT5L5BHOCC4LXQT4F6Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货持平，通胀数据公布前谨慎情绪升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国股指期货变化不大，表明在本周创纪录的涨势之后，投资者在等待新的催化剂来保持市场在这个异常强劲的九月的势头。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were little changed on Thursday, pointing to a pause after a record-breaking rally this week as investors awaited fresh catalysts to keep up the momentum in what has been an unusually strong September for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-flat-caution-builds-ahead-inflation-data-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5M6ZWEUQJLAFKJZZ4AXXU5B24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，关税可能会削弱美元的储备地位，但尚未扭转这一地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在 4 月份的 "解放日 "提出的大规模关税措施使美元作为世界锚定货币的地位岌岌可危，而新的经济研究得出结论认为，美国政府最终向更温和的税率妥协很可能使美元的地位更加稳固。【原文：The massive tariffs proposed by President Donald Trump on "Liberation Day" in April put the U.S. dollar's role as the world's anchor currency at risk, while the administration's eventual climbdown to more modest rates has likely left it secure, new economic research has concluded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tariffs-could-weaken-not-yet-reverse-dollars-reserve-status-research-shows-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FBC2OAOXROHZPREKSYMC3D3RQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机场跑道险情刺激人们希望更广泛地采用驾驶舱警报技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[当一架波音 757 飞机准备降落时，驾驶舱里响起了警报声："跑道上有飞机！跑道上有飞机！"几秒钟后，导航显示屏上也出现了同样的警告。【原文：As a Boeing 757 aircraft prepared to land, an audio alert started blaring in the cockpit: "Traffic on runway! Traffic on runway!" Seconds later, the same warning popped up on the navigation display.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airport-runway-close-calls-spur-hopes-wider-adoption-cockpit-alert-technology-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMBMVRDRC5K3XCVQDXXJ2QYKDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[两家竞标者争当美国联邦航空局大规模空中交通改造项目经理]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局的高级官员告诉路透社记者，该局只有两名候选人竞争数十亿美元的美国空中交通管制大修项目经理的职位。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration has just two candidates vying to become the project manager of a multi-billion dollar effort to overhaul air traffic control in the United States, the agency's top official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/two-bidders-vie-be-project-manager-massive-faa-us-air-traffic-overhaul-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIMOOPBT3JPRZHST6P6J6ESXFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股持续反弹可能受制于通胀、盈利和估值风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[过去几个月来，美国股市在波动极小的情况下接连创下历史新高，但投资者表示，通胀率居高不下、盈利可能令人失望以及估值过高等因素可能会削弱美股的涨势。【原文：U.S. stocks have hit a string of record highs with minimal turbulence over the past few months, but investors say the rally could be undermined by persistently high inflation, possible earnings disappointments and elevated valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/relentless-us-stocks-rally-could-teeter-inflation-earnings-valuation-risks-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLAKZ6H2LRJQ5CXZI4KVS5RJSI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田在富士山附近启动 "梭织城市 "试验场进行技术测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司在日本富士山附近的 Woven City 测试基地的第一部分于本周四开放，这是在该项目推出五年多之后开放的，其目的是加速下一代技术的实际试验。【原文：Toyota Motor opened the first section of its Woven City testing site near Japan's Mt. Fuji on Thursday, more than five years after unveiling the project aimed at accelerating real-world trials of next-generation technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-launches-woven-city-test-site-near-mt-fuji-tech-testing-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHJN2W3ELNMURL7WPJTLECSHLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家 - 消息人士称，Blackstone 正在考虑 ancestry.com 的各种选择，包括可能的出售或首次公开募股]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/exclusive-blackstone-mulls-options-ancestrycom-including-possible-sale-or-ipo-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MICW3G2GVMZ7HKD4IKPEMY6WY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟对 SAP 可能的反竞争行为展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会对欧洲最大的软件制造商德国 SAP 公司可能采取的反竞争做法展开了调查，调查涉及该公司流行的商业管理软件。【原文：The European Commission has opened an investigation into possible anticompetitive practices by Germany's SAP , Europe's largest software maker, related to its popular business management software.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-opens-probe-into-possible-anticompetitive-practices-by-sap-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLWTQD3I2BKZDDSZ2O3I37OAPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Planet Labs 将向柏林卫星生产基地投资八位数的资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于加利福尼亚州的行星实验室（Planet Labs）计划在柏林建立其在美国以外的首个卫星生产基地，该公司首席执行官威尔-马歇尔（Will Marshall）表示，将为该企业投资八位数的资金，这将使该公司的高分辨率卫星生产能力翻一番。【原文：California-based Planet Labs plans to set up its first satellite production site outside the U.S. in Berlin, investing an eight-figure sum in the venture that will see the firm double its high-resolution satellite capacity, said CEO Will Marshall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/planet-labs-invest-eight-figure-sum-berlin-satellite-production-site-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNV6PPWQCZJODEAKO3S366M3OI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业协会称中国正在研究如何调控铜冶炼产能]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家国家新闻媒体周四称，由于加工费持续走低导致冶炼利润减少，中国正在研究如何加强对铜冶炼产能扩张的监管。【原文：China is studying ways to strengthen regulation on the expansion of copper smelting capacity, a state news outlet said on Thursday, as persistently low processing fees have reduced smelting profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-studies-how-regulate-copper-smelting-capacity-industry-association-says-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AC3AW6ROXFI2JBK2JW337FKI34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:31:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道称，在其他岗位裁员之际，美国立法者对科技公司使用 H-1B 签证的情况进行了严格审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国立法者正在审查包括亚马逊和苹果在内的大型科技公司使用 H-1B 签证的情况，即使这些公司正在裁员。【原文：U.S. lawmakers are scrutinizing large technology companies including Amazon and Apple over their use of H-1B visas even as they lay off other workers, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-lawmakers-scrutinize-tech-firms-over-h-1b-visa-use-amid-other-job-layoffs-wsj-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXDB3UM7EJMCZJWDG76VWHZUJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:22:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发出购买美国大豆取决于取消关税的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部发言人周四在被问及中国是否会购买美国大豆时表示，美国应取消中国所称的不合理关税，并为扩大双边贸易创造条件。【原文：The United States should remove what China described as unreasonable tariffs and create conditions to expand bilateral trade, a Chinese commerce ministry spokesperson said on Thursday when asked if China would purchase U.S. soybeans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-signals-that-purchases-us-soybeans-hinge-tariff-removal-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYTVZPARRFIQBFWWNEGIOV643Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:54:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飞利浦与美国就医疗技术进口调查进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[飞利浦公司周四表示，正在就美国进口医疗技术产品的调查问题与华盛顿的政策制定者积极接触，但预计调查不会产生直接影响。【原文：Philips is actively engaged with policymakers in Washington about investigations into U.S. imports of medical technology items but does not expect an immediate impact from the probes, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/philips-talks-with-us-over-probes-medical-technology-imports-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYBABD2TAZNMPFZKVOSJTLS2OI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:48:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司向中国苏帕尔纳航空公司交付一架 777 货机]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国飞机制造商波音公司周四通过其官方微信账号表示，波音于周三交付了中国苏鹏航空公司订购的两架777货机中的第一架。【原文：Boeing on Wednesday delivered the first of two 777 freighters ordered by China's Suparna Airlines, the U.S. planemaker said on Thursday via its official WeChat account.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-handed-777-freighter-chinas-suparna-airlines-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WKMWY66ONICDJUMIL2X5VJHQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nscale 从 Aker 和其他投资者处融资 11 亿美元，用于人工智能建设]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国人工智能集团Nscale周四表示，该公司已从包括挪威阿克尔公司（Aker ASA）和芬兰诺基亚公司在内的投资者处筹集到11亿美元资金，用于加快其数据中心基础设施的建设。【原文：British artificial intelligence group Nscale has raised $1.1 billion from investors, including Norway's Aker ASA and Finland's Nokia , to help accelerate its data centre infrastructure buildout, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nscale-raises-11-billion-aker-other-investors-ai-buildout-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G37SFVOK3ZL33FCEOFU33GEARQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:26:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，美国投资者 Stonepeak 寻求为第二支亚洲基础设施基金融资 40 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位直接了解该计划的消息人士称，随着寻求丰厚长期回报的投资者在该地区掀起新一轮投资热潮，总部位于美国的投资者Stonepeak正寻求为其第二支专注于亚洲的基础设施基金筹集多达40亿美元的资金。【原文：U.S.-based investor Stonepeak is seeking to raise as much as $4 billion for its second Asia-focused infrastructure fund, a source with direct knowledge of the plan said, as investors seeking lucrative long-term returns drive a wave of new investments in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-investor-stonepeak-seeks-raise-4-billion-second-asia-infrastructure-fund-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73NKS477NZPO3DYKYQ45LDQVSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:15:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将6家美国公司列入出口管制和不可靠实体名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周四表示，已将三家美国实体列入出口管制名单，并将另外三家美国公司列入 "不可靠实体名单"。【原文：China's Commerce Ministry said on Thursday it has added three U.S. entities to its export control list, and another three U.S. firms to its "unreliable entity list."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-adds-6-us-firms-export-control-unreliable-entity-lists-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DTDMZEXJZP3NBGFKFEJO5ZW2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国汽车游说团欢迎美国降低关税，但表示欧盟必须进一步推进]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车工业协会（VDA）周四对美国自8月1日起追溯性降低关税表示欢迎，但表示出口商仍面临着严峻的贸易壁垒。【原文：Germany's VDA car industry association on Thursday welcomed the United States lowering tariffs retroactively from August 1 but said exporters still faced challenging trade barriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/german-auto-lobby-welcomes-lower-us-tariffs-says-eu-must-push-further-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NO2TIWSFYFKHDHSP6A7A2VW424</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国因美国贸易谈判而摇摆不定，唤醒了韩元熊市]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，韩国与特朗普政府的贸易谈判越来越多地受到政治疑虑的困扰，这让投资者感到不安，他们担心首尔最终可能会得到一个生硬的协议，或者根本没有协议。【原文：South Korea's trade talks with the Trump administration have become increasingly dogged by political doubts this week, spooking investors who now worry Seoul may end up with a raw deal or perhaps no deal at all.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/koreas-wobbles-over-us-trade-talks-awaken-won-bears-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZX4566ACNRNSXHCRAFXDZASYMU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Nothing 公司拟出资 1 亿美元成立合资企业，扩大在印度的智能手机生产规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于伦敦的智能手机制造商 Nothing 公司周四表示，该公司已与 Optiemus Infracom 公司签署了一家合资企业，以扩大在印度的生产规模。【原文：London-based smartphone maker Nothing has signed a joint venture with Optiemus Infracom to expand manufacturing in India, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/uks-nothing-expand-smartphone-manufacturing-india-through-100-million-joint-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7K3QHJXZ4JJHDM5VBUCXUS2CVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 07:53:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星际娱乐公司黄金海岸赌场执照暂停执业延至 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚赌场运营商 Star Entertainment Group 周四表示，昆士兰州政府已将暂停其黄金海岸赌场执照的时间推迟至 2026 年 9 月 30 日。【原文：Australian casino operator Star Entertainment Group said on Thursday that the Queensland government had deferred the suspension of its Gold Coast casino licence to September 30, 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/star-entertainments-gold-coast-casino-licence-suspension-deferred-until-2026-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LM2R7BH5LFOJ3LXZN36RYNNAQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 07:42:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税，中国总理与欧盟首脑强调合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国务院总理李强和欧盟轮值主席国欧盟委员会主席乌尔苏拉-冯德莱恩在纽约会晤期间强调了合作，这两个世界第二和第三大经济体在受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税挤压之际，寻求化解贸易紧张局势。【原文：China's Premier Li Qiang and European Union chief Ursula von der Leyen stressed cooperation during their meeting in New York, as the world's No.2 and No.3 economies looked to defuse trade tensions while squeezed by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-premier-eu-chief-stress-cooperation-trump-tariffs-bite-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFYLAZNTOBJVRE4MZKN4ASAZXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 06:59:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[柏肯耐克上调 2025 财年收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国凉鞋制造商 Birkenstock 周四预计，由于对其木屐和鞋的需求强劲，2025 财年的收入将至少达到 20.9 亿欧元（24.5 亿美元），高于此前的预期。【原文：German sandal maker Birkenstock on Thursday forecast fiscal 2025 revenue of at least 2.09 billion euros ($2.45 billion) on strong demand for its clogs and shoes, ahead of its prior guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/birkenstock-raises-fiscal-2025-revenue-forecast-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEHAIQR33RJBDAEZLANB5CJG5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 06:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeTravel 融资 9,200 万美元，扩大人工智能功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[WeTravel公司的在线平台和人工智能工具简化了酒店预订、航班预订和支付处理等旅游组织流程，该公司表示已在新一轮融资中筹集了9200万美元，本轮融资由蓝宝石风投（Sapphire Ventures）领投。【原文：WeTravel, whose online platform and AI tools streamline travel organisation, such as hotel reservations, flight bookings and payment processing, said it had raised $92 million in a new funding round led by Sapphire Ventures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/wetravel-raises-92-million-funding-expand-ai-capabilities-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGE4JCMDONM6PBR5WX3LXX2CEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 06:55:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>