<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:03:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:03:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴菲特的伯克希尔公司因保险和投资实现创纪录利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周六公布了连续第三个创纪录的年度营业利润，这主要得益于其保险业务承保盈利和投资收益的大幅增长。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway on Saturday posted its third straight record annual operating profit, bolstered by large increases in underwriting earnings and investment income in its insurance businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/buffetts-berkshire-posts-record-profit-insurance-investments-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7SJL3QS65JV5IMNQSCRDGM4LQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 13:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，Stellantis公司因后视摄像头图像问题召回27354辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周六表示，由于后视摄像头图像无法显示，Stellantis公司将在美国召回27354辆玛莎拉蒂汽车。【原文：Stellantis is recalling 27,354 Maserati vehicles in the U.S over concerns of a rearview camera image that does not display, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-recalls-27354-us-vehicles-over-rearview-camera-image-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XTVSONUMJM7NNJ5J533ABP2PA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 10:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[媒体称 Seven & i Holdings 选择贝恩作为资产出售的首选买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体周六报道，7-Eleven 连锁便利店运营商日本 Seven &amp; i 控股公司已选择贝恩资本作为其非核心资产股份的首选买家。【原文：Japan's Seven &amp; i Holdings , operator of the 7-Eleven convenience store chain, has picked Bain Capital as its preferred buyer for a stake of its non-core assets, local media reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/seven-i-holdings-picks-bain-preferred-buyer-asset-sale-media-say-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVPJXX3CJZPBXKV5C3TI7BZ4RQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 10:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行维勒鲁瓦重申今年夏天存款利率可能达到 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国央行行长兼欧洲央行决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）在周六发表的一篇访谈中表示，欧洲央行可能在今年夏天之前将存款利率下调至 2%。【原文：The European Central Bank could cut its deposit rate down to 2% by this summer, said Bank of France head and ECB policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau in an interview published on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecbs-villeroy-reaffirms-deposit-rates-could-be-2-by-this-summer-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFVD57YAKRJEPORDWHOZWPQTZA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 07:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示波音首席航空安全官即将退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份备忘录，波音公司首席航空航天安全官迈克-德莱尼（Mike Delaney）将于今年晚些时候退休。【原文：Boeing's chief aerospace safety officer, Mike Delaney, will retire later this year, according to memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-chief-aerospace-safety-officer-retire-air-current-editor-says-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4GZQO6SFVOUDIPAFQEYYEKVZA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西法官在 "审查 "纠纷后暂停 Rumble 平台运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西最高法院周五以美国视频共享平台 Rumble 未遵守法院命令为由，下令暂停其在巴西的业务，这与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 公司去年面临的情况类似。【原文：Brazil's Supreme Court on Friday ordered the suspension of U.S. video-sharing platform Rumble in the country, citing its failure to comply with court orders, in a similar path to the one faced by Elon Musk's X last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-supreme-court-orders-rumble-suspension-country-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFNNQW7DRRJ4VP6OBICI3KCOVI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，特朗普征收 10%的石油关税可能导致外国生产商每年损失 100 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）周五表示，由于替代买家和加工能力有限，加拿大和拉丁美洲的重质原油仍然依赖于美国炼油厂，因此拟议中的 10%美国石油关税可能会使外国生产商每年损失 100 亿美元。【原文：Goldman Sachs said on Friday a proposed 10% U.S. oil tariff could cost foreign producers $10 billion per year, as Canadian and Latin American heavy crudes remain reliant on U.S. refiners due to limited alternative buyers and processing capabilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-10-oil-tariff-could-cost-foreign-producers-10-billion-annually-goldman-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKLHON545FPS5OYYRDRI3DUF7Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:28:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称美国可能因矿产问题切断乌克兰使用星链互联网服务的渠道]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，美国谈判代表向基辅施压，要求乌克兰获得关键矿产，并提出了切断该国使用埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）重要的星链（Starlink）卫星互联网系统的可能性。【原文：U.S. negotiators pressing Kyiv for access to Ukraine's critical minerals have raised the possibility of cutting the country's access to Elon Musk's vital Starlink satellite internet system, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-could-cut-ukraines-access-starlink-internet-services-over-minerals-say-2025-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEJUIMHFYJLUHIMET7UXML3QEA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年利润水平较低，CVS 削减奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 周五表示，由于去年利润水平较低，该公司已经削减了部分员工的奖金，因为这家医疗保健集团正在努力应对其医疗保险计划成本上升的问题。【原文：CVS Health said on Friday it has cut bonuses for some employees because of its low profit levels last year, as the healthcare conglomerate grapples with higher costs across its Medicare plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-cuts-bonuses-after-low-profit-levels-2024-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZSMOP3LQRM4VLQBBVBXRS6JQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普的领导下，消费者监督机构撤销了对在线贷款机构的起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）已着手废除美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau），该局周五向法院表示，将撤销对在线借贷平台 Solo Funds 的诉讼，该机构此前曾指控 Solo Funds 在贷款成本方面欺骗借款人。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, which President Donald Trump has moved to abolish, told a court on Friday it was dropping a lawsuit against the online lending platform Solo Funds, which the agency had earlier accused of deceiving borrowers about the cost of loans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/under-trump-consumer-watchdog-drops-case-against-online-lender-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSJUVARTARJNPGBWSUAMXC3WBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称考虑将美国邮政局与商务部合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周五表示，他正在考虑将美国邮政局与美国商务部合并，民主党人称此举将违反联邦法律。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday he was considering merging the U.S. Postal Service with the U.S. Commerce Department, a move Democrats said would violate federal law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-is-considering-merging-us-postal-service-with-commerce-department-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TL62IISZIFOPXKWPOZVVQ6OARM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普媒体提议在佛罗里达州重新注册公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的特朗普媒体&amp; 科技集团（Trump Media &amp; Technology Group）周五表示，将在 4 月底举行的年会上提议在佛罗里达州重新注册公司。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's Trump Media &amp; Technology Group said on Friday it will propose reincorporating the company in Florida at its annual meeting in late April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-media-propose-reincorporation-florida-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVMYNHJZYNILTKXTNF35GMEU4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将对数字税征收报复性关税，可能在周五实施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他将签署一份备忘录，对向美国科技公司征收数字服务税的国家征收关税。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday that he would sign a memorandum to impose tariffs on countries that levy digital service taxes on U.S. technology companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-impose-retaliatory-tariffs-digital-taxes-may-come-friday-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYXQTS6AHBO43HB32T5BWZFLGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街巨头摩根士丹利在年度报告中更加强调多元化]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）在周五发布的最新年度报告中淡化了对多元化的强调，这表明随着企业适应唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统政府领导下不断变化的现实，摩根士丹利正在进行重新调整。【原文：Morgan Stanley toned down its emphasis on diversity in its latest annual report published on Friday, signaling a recalibration as businesses adapt to a changing reality under President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-giant-morgan-stanley-eases-diversity-emphasis-annual-report-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCC6H5JPLBNJZF2SIUAKPKBOJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:21:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受经济和关税担忧影响，华尔街运输类股受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于投资者对疲软的经济数据做出反应并担心关税问题，运输类股票大幅反转，经济风向标道琼斯运输平均指数下跌超过2.6%，创下自12月18日以来的最大单日跌幅，也是连续第三次下跌。【原文：Transportation stocks went sharply in reverse on Friday with the economic bellwether Dow Jones Transport average index falling more than 2.6% in its steepest daily loss since December 18 and its third consecutive decline, as investors reacted to weak economic readings and worried about tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/transport-stocks-take-hit-wall-street-economic-tariff-fears-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTXFQIRE5JIV5FQXJXBGEIN5ZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富兰克林邓普顿申请 Solana ETF，加密货币的兴趣已超越比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[富兰克林邓普顿公司（Franklin Templeton）周五申请了一只交易所交易基金，该基金将跟踪索拉纳的现货价格，这反映出资产管理公司对从比特币以外的加密货币的受欢迎程度中获利的兴趣日益浓厚。【原文：Franklin Templeton filed for an exchange-traded fund on Friday that will track the spot price of Solana , reflecting the growing interest among asset managers to profit from the popularity of cryptocurrencies beyond bitcoin .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/franklin-templeton-files-solana-etf-crypto-interest-expands-beyond-bitcoin-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THA2ZAPXA5JBVGOXGNTTKOOE4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫官员称，特朗普将利用外国投资委员会限制中国在战略领域的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统将于周五签署一份备忘录，指示美国外国投资委员会限制中国在战略领域的投资。【原文：President Donald Trump will sign a memorandum on Friday that will direct the Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States to restrict Chinese investments in strategic areas, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-use-cfius-restrict-chinese-investments-strategic-areas-white-house-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR3VTWQIKNLCZOLWLFUDNK22KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储暂停量化宽松政策，财政部债务计划或为美债带来短暂宽松]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储缩减资产负债表的速度可能放缓，财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）也保证不会立即增加长期债务，这些都能在短期内缓解债券市场对财政问题的担忧。【原文：A potential slowdown of the Federal Reserve's balance sheet drawdown and Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent's assurance against imminent long-term debt hikes could offer relief in the near term to bond market jitters as fiscal concerns linger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-qt-pause-treasurys-debt-plans-may-offer-fleeting-relief-us-bonds-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6AF4A5INROG7FXG7M3RFDSMUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:12:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步首席执行官科斯罗萨西支持特朗普推动取消小费税]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步（Uber）首席执行官达拉-科斯罗萨希（Dara Khosrowshahi）周五表示，他和优步都支持美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提出的取消对优步司机收取小费征税的倡议。【原文：Uber's CEO Dara Khosrowshahi said on Friday that both he and the ride-hailing firm are supportive of U.S. President Donald Trump's initiative to eliminate taxes on tips received by its drivers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/uber-ceo-khosrowshahi-supports-trumps-push-eliminate-taxes-tips-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCJTJAHQNZO5VJUQDOWS3IUQYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 19:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waze 成为欧盟技术规则下的大型平台，色情网站将被除名]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的地图应用 Waze 在达到欧盟技术规则规定的关键用户数量后，需要采取更多措施来处理其平台上的非法网络内容，而三家成人内容网站在用户数量低于门槛后，可能会面临较宽松的要求。【原文：Alphabet's mapping app Waze needs to do more to tackle illegal online content on its platform after hitting a key user number under EU tech rules, while three adult content sites will likely face less stringent requirements after their user numbers fell below the threshold.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/waze-hits-large-platform-status-under-eu-tech-rules-porn-sites-set-drop-off-list-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLHW2UKC65K5LO3TDX76WBSJHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 19:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：禽流感如何导致美国鸡蛋价格飞涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于禽流感爆发导致数百万只母鸡死亡，造成鸡蛋短缺，美国食品杂货店的鸡蛋价格攀升至历史新高，几乎比一年前翻了一番。【原文：The price of eggs at U.S. grocery stores has climbed to a record high, nearly doubling from a year ago, as outbreaks of bird flu have led to shortages by wiping out millions of hens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-bird-flu-has-sent-us-eggs-prices-skyrocketing-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPHHIZST2JJNHB43XKO7RX3VHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院关注美联储的新工作组召开首次会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[由一个对美国中央银行制定货币政策的方法持批评态度的强大委员会的负责人成立的一个新的国会特别工作组已将其首次公开听证会安排在下月初举行。【原文：A new congressional task force focused on the Federal Reserve, set up by the head of a powerful committee who is critical of the U.S. central bank's approach to setting monetary policy, has penciled in its first public hearing for early next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/new-us-house-task-force-focused-fed-sets-first-meeting-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CI5SRLY6SBNU7K6PJCA2U6BTRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:23:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫希望乌克兰尽快签署重要的矿产协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫国家安全顾问迈克-华尔兹（Mike Waltz）周五表示，他期待乌克兰总统沃洛德梅尔-泽连斯基（Volodymyr Zelenskiy）与美国签署一项矿产协议，作为结束乌克兰战争努力的一部分。【原文：White House national security adviser Mike Waltz said on Friday he expects Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy to sign a minerals agreement with the United States as part of efforts to end the Ukraine war, while President Donald Trump said Kyiv has no cards to play with.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-expects-ukraine-sign-critical-minerals-deal-soon-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAYU7GD7D5OIFHI7XLYG7A4DFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:10:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国油气钻机数升至 6 月以来最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第四周增加石油和天然气钻机，达到自 6 月份以来的最高水平。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week added oil and natural gas rigs for a fourth week in a row to the highest level since June, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-gas-rig-count-rises-highest-since-june-says-baker-hughes-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHJXLUEXDFNZJJKBMZRPRYJGW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:10:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行行长希望审查维持 2% 的通胀目标不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[作者：Promit Mukherjee 和 David Ljunggren【原文：By Promit Mukherjee and David Ljunggren】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-head-wants-review-leave-2-inflation-target-unchanged-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CYFKIRBLVOLVIP55FIDV6YKPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康菲石油公司将以 7.35 亿美元的价格向壳牌出售在乌尔萨和欧罗巴油田的权益]]></title><description><![CDATA[康菲石油公司周五表示，将以 7.35 亿美元的价格向壳牌出售其在厄萨油田和欧罗巴油田的权益。【原文：ConocoPhillips said on Friday it would sell its interests in the Ursa and Europa Fields to Shell for $735 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/conocophillips-sell-interest-ursa-europa-fields-shell-735-million-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXQLRPOFDJLV7JX53OCY2LKEBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰斐逊称人工智能正加速投资者对央行官员信息的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储副主席菲利普-杰斐逊（Philip Jefferson）周五表示，人工智能正在加快投资者对央行行长讲话中的具体句子以及描述其政策行动的声明做出反应的速度，但目前还不清楚这种速度的加快是促进还是阻碍了货币政策的有效传导。【原文：Artificial intelligence is speeding the rate at which investors react to specific sentences in central bankers' speeches and in statements describing their policy actions, Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson said on Friday, but it's unclear whether that increased speed is boosting or hindering the effective transmission of monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-jefferson-says-ai-is-speeding-investors-reactions-central-bankers-messages-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URALGU5TVZLFRAEOOQ42UTV4I4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，特斯拉即将进入印度市场，印度将为电动汽车充电投资设置关税减免上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份政府文件显示，印度的电动汽车政策为在该国投资的外国汽车制造商提供进口税减免，但将限制他们将用于充电基础设施的资金用于减免，从而增加他们的汽车制造量。【原文：India's EV policy, which offers import tax cuts for foreign automakers investing in the country, will restrict them from using funds spent on charging infrastructure for such relief, increasing their car manufacturing, a government document shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-cap-investment-ev-charging-tariff-relief-tesla-entry-looms-document-shows-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD5JLHMMAZNBBEM6HT5UCS7SCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:59:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称股市可能面临调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）专家斯科特-鲁布纳（Scott Rubner）在周五路透社看到的一份周四报告中说，由于期权市场的混乱，华尔街股市可能面临调整。【原文：Wall Street stocks could be facing a correction because of ructions in the options market, Goldman Sachs specialist Scott Rubner said in a Thursday note seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/stock-markets-may-face-correction-says-goldman-sachs-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZMM4HVEX3BJN3MWSCEBRRWLQTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:55:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普京称俄罗斯应加快锂矿开采计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔-普京（Vladimir Putin）周五表示，俄罗斯应加快开采锂矿藏和稀土等其他重要矿产的计划，锂矿藏是生产高容量电动电池的关键金属。【原文：President Vladimir Putin said on Friday that Russia should speed up plans to mine its deposits of lithium, a metal crucial for the production of high-capacity electric batteries, and other critical minerals, including rare earths.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/putin-says-russia-should-speed-up-lithium-mining-plans-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUB3LLNHPRPG5L6BYIBDOSQFPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>