<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:39:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:39:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[高管称 Revolut 考虑收购美国银行以推进全球扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国 Revolut 公司周二表示，该公司正在探索收购一家美国银行，以加速全球扩张，并有意在本土市场推出信用卡，这家数字金融公司正试图进一步蚕食传统贷款机构的地盘。【原文：Britain's Revolut said on Tuesday it was exploring buying a U.S. bank to accelerate its global expansion and was eyeing launching credit cards in its home market, as the digital finance firm seeks to encroach further onto the turf of traditional lenders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/revolut-weighs-buying-us-bank-global-expansion-push-executive-says-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4VCEOPUWZP7FP3KXCRD2SQ5BM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第二季度经常账户大幅收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着大量进口的减少，美国第二季度经常账户赤字的缩减幅度创下历史之最。【原文：The U.S. current account deficit contracted by the most on record in the second quarter as a flood of imports subsided.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-current-account-narrows-sharply-second-quarter-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEFTGDNENJOHXEFLYXHI6B43QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼美联储需要果断抵御就业市场风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储负责监管事务的副主席米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周二表示，美联储在支持劳动力市场方面可能会迟到，如果需求状况减弱，企业开始裁员，美联储可能需要加快降息步伐。【原文：The Federal Reserve may be late in supporting the labor market and could need to speed the pace of rate cuts if demand conditions weaken and businesses begin to lay off workers, Fed Vice Chair for Supervision Michelle Bowman said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bowman-fed-needs-be-decisive-fending-off-job-market-risks-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIZEYBZKFJPGBMPTGAXQMBYA34</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:04:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，欧洲插电式混合动力汽车的蓬勃发展有助于中国汽车制造商在 8 月份的销量超过雷诺和奥迪]]></title><description><![CDATA[JATO Dynamics 周二提供的数据显示，受插电式混合动力汽车热销的助推，8 月份中国汽车制造商在欧洲的销量超过了雷诺和奥迪品牌，比亚迪、捷酷和名爵的车型跻身该类汽车销量前十名。【原文：Chinese automakers sold more cars in Europe than the Renault and Audi brands in August, helped by booming plug-in hybrid sales, with models from BYD, Jaecoo and MG in the category's top-ten sellers, data from JATO Dynamics showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/europes-plug-in-hybrid-boom-helps-chinese-carmakers-outsell-renault-audi-august-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34YLJIOL4BPGLFKMZS2PNRC3UI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:53:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行发出稳定利率 "新阶段 "信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行周二表示，该行已进入一个 "新阶段"，即决策者选择维持利率不变，同时评估当前的利率水平是否足以确保通胀率向 3% 的目标靠拢。【原文：Brazil's central bank said on Tuesday that it has entered a "new stage" in which policymakers opt to keep interest rates unchanged while evaluating whether the current level is enough to ensure inflation converges to its 3% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-central-bank-signals-new-stage-steady-interest-rates-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSRHOOYA6VOJZC37UIBXQGVJEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:52:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊公司将关闭其在英国的所有亚马逊生鲜店]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）表示，它计划关闭其在英国的 19 家 Amazon Fresh 便利杂货店，其中 5 家将转为其 Whole Foods Markets 品牌，这距离它进入英国市场还不到 5 年时间。【原文：Amazon.com said it planned to close all of its 19 Amazon Fresh UK convenience grocery stores, of which five would be converted to its Whole Foods Markets brand, less than five years after it entered the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazoncom-close-all-its-amazon-fresh-uk-stores-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHMO3XIJSRMYRGKRSI6SHOUB4Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:52:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会推动美国立法者通过《SHIPS 法案》以确保造船资金来源]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国五个工会呼吁立法者通过立法，帮助确保长期资金，以重振国内造船业，这项努力得到了唐纳德-特朗普总统的支持，并因对中国船只征收新的港口费而得到推动。【原文：Five U.S. unions are calling on lawmakers to pass legislation that would help secure long-term funding to revive domestic shipbuilding, an effort championed by President Donald Trump and boosted by new port fees on Chinese ships.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/unions-push-us-lawmakers-pass-ships-act-secure-shipbuilding-funding-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O46E6HLTLNMTRG4QAMHXVPYS64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥联储发布中期失业率预估，9 月份为 4.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储周二表示，它已将政府和私人数据合并为一个新的失业率估算值，这将为政策制定者提供更快、每月两次更新的统计数据，该数据对央行当前的利率辩论至关重要。【原文：The Chicago Federal Reserve said on Tuesday it had combined government and private data into a new estimate of the unemployment rate that would give policymakers faster-moving, twice monthly updates of a statistic central to the central bank's current interest rate debate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chicago-fed-releases-interim-unemployment-estimate-with-september-43-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FAXKRIMZJIDLDTVTGBJNXKT3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:35:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sempra 出售基础设施部门 100 亿美元的股份，为阿瑟港扩建工程开绿灯]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公用事业公司森普拉（Sempra）周二表示，将以 100 亿美元现金出售其基础设施部门的股份，并启动价值 140 亿美元的德克萨斯州亚瑟港液化天然气项目扩建工程。【原文：U.S. utility Sempra said on Tuesday it would sell a stake in its infrastructure unit for $10 billion in cash, as well as greenlit a $14 billion expansion of its Port Arthur LNG project in Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/utility-sempra-sell-stake-infrastructure-platforms-10-billion-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGB5WPJLL5NUBGVU5NXOKUNGXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:19:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 拒绝批准 Scholar Rock 的肌无力药物；股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[学岩药业周二表示，美国卫生监管机构以第三方生产设施存在问题为由，拒绝批准其治疗罕见神经肌肉疾病的药物，导致该公司股价在盘前交易中下跌了 12%。【原文：Scholar Rock said on Tuesday the U.S. health regulator has declined to approve its drug for a rare neuromuscular disease citing issues at a third-party manufacturing facility, sending the company's shares down 12% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-declines-approve-scholar-rocks-muscle-weakness-drug-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHGPETNGHZJBTJSZBHQTH7Y454</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 11:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国锑公司赢得五角大楼价值 2.45 亿美元的国防储备建设合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国锑业公司（United States Antimony Corporation）周二表示，该公司已从美国国防部后勤局（U.S. Defense Logistics Agency）获得一份为期五年、价值高达 2.45 亿美元的独家合同，为国防储备供应锑金属锭。【原文：United States Antimony Corporation said on Tuesday it has secured a sole-source, five-year contract worth up to $245 million from the U.S. Defense Logistics Agency to supply antimony metal ingots for the defense stockpile.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-antimony-corp-wins-245-million-pentagon-contract-build-defense-stockpile-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6UHDDLDSBJJPE45CJQPTPTOTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 11:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业投入数十亿美元推进人工智能基础设施建设]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）将向 OpenAI 投资高达 1000 亿美元，并为其提供数据中心芯片，这笔交易使这家芯片制造商获得了世界上最著名的人工智能公司的财务股份，而 OpenAI 已经是这家公司的重要客户。【原文：Nvidia is set to invest up to $100 billion in OpenAI and supply it with data center chips, in a deal that gives the chipmaker a financial stake in the world's most prominent AI company, which is already an important customer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/companies-pouring-billions-advance-ai-infrastructure-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHEEPBXQPJJARBM65WHZSHIUH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标疼痛阈值]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W62FZZJN3ZPIRMC7WNRP2NU5JU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音为争取欧盟批准 Spirit 交易提供补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据欧盟委员会网站的最新消息，波音公司已提出补救措施，以争取欧盟批准回购全球最大的独立航空结构公司 Spirit AeroSystems。【原文：Boeing has offered remedies in a bid to secure EU approval to buy back Spirit AeroSystems , the world's largest standalone aerostructures company, according to an update on the European Commission website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/boeing-offers-remedies-bid-eu-approval-spirit-deal-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TG337TL7LNJAZN3VPKXB5YNLLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，关税和法国动荡将导致欧洲经济放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的关键数据显示，欧元区经济增长继续保持稳定，因为德国的预算宽松支撑了市场情绪，并抵消了法国的动荡。【原文：Euro zone economic growth continues to hold up as Germany's budget largesse props up sentiment and offsets turmoil in France, but more weakness may be ahead as U.S. tariffs start to exert their full effect, key data showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/wrapup-europe-succumb-slowdown-driven-by-tariffs-french-turmoil-reports-show-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUPMY2YGZFPKDOXUS66ES56JYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:24:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道埃森哲拟在印度安得拉邦新建园区，计划增加 1.2 万个工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，技术咨询公司埃森哲（Accenture）已提议在印度南部的安得拉邦（Andhra Pradesh）建立一个新的园区，旨在最终为其在印度的员工队伍增加约 12,000 个工作岗位。【原文：Tech consultancy Accenture has proposed setting up a new campus in the southern Indian state of Andhra Pradesh, aiming to eventually add about 12,000 jobs to its workforce in India, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/accenture-proposes-new-campus-indias-andhra-pradesh-eyes-adding-12000-jobs-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6NTK7WBP5MSBDPX2IZ7UQ3KUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货在科技股推动的反弹后持稳；鲍威尔成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货基本持平，此前科技股大涨推动华尔街连续第三个交易日创下收盘纪录新高，而投资者则在等待美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）有关经济的讲话。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were largely unchanged on Tuesday after a tech-driven rally drove Wall Street to record closing highs for the third straight session, while investors awaited Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's remarks on the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-hold-steady-after-tech-fueled-rally-powell-focus-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATQXAGWZRFNAHJ4Y2SXSYNXSAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：百事公司部分投资者对艾略特分拆装瓶计划持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事公司的一些投资者支持激进股东埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）的建议，即全球食品饮料公司削减成本，放弃桂格（Quaker）等沉睡的品牌，但对对冲基金最大胆的想法--将这家苏打水生产商的装瓶网络一扫而空--则持谨慎态度。【原文：Some investors in PepsiCo support suggestions by activist shareholder Elliott Investment Management that the global food and beverage company cut costs and ditch sleepy brands like Quaker, but sound more cautious about the hedge fund's boldest idea - to hive off the soda maker's bottling network.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/some-pepsico-investors-cautious-elliotts-plan-spin-out-bottling-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIMZX5ZM4RPL7HKPCXMDW4PZFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊就联邦贸易委员会声称其欺骗 Prime 用户一案开庭审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（U.S. Federal Trade Commission）将于本周二在西雅图举行的庭审中试图证明，亚马逊在未经同意的情况下注册了数千万 Prime 客户，并用过于复杂的取消注册方法锁定了他们，从而欺骗了数千万 Prime 客户。【原文：Amazon duped tens of millions of Prime customers by signing them up without consent and locking them in with overly complex cancellation methods, the U.S. Federal Trade Commission will seek to show at a trial starting in Seattle on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/amazon-trial-begins-ftc-claims-it-duped-prime-subscribers-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2XMYU6EOJN23BBJEQCCWKFN74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:09:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车将于 2030 年在美国开始生产新型混合动力车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-begin-production-new-hybrid-model-united-states-by-2030-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2XJRGTYHFILZOM7QKTR7DE4I4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:07:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达 1000 亿美元 OpenAI 交易中的问题多于答案]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）向 OpenAI 投资高达 1000 亿美元，同时计划向 ChatGPT 创建者提供数百万个市场领先的人工智能芯片，这在科技行业几乎没有先例。【原文：Nvidia's move to invest up to $100 billion into OpenAI at the same time it plans to supply millions of its market-leading artificial intelligence chips to the ChatGPT creator has little precedent in the tech industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/more-questions-than-answers-nvidias-100-billion-openai-deal-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IVNH6AN2SROV7POGYFF2L3XWVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新的 H-1B 签证收费引发离岸外包讨论，硅谷招聘陷入混乱]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府对 H-1B 签证收取新的高额费用，促使硅谷及其他地区的公司内部就更多工作岗位转移到海外的可能性进行了高层会谈，而这恰恰是该政策想要阻止的结果。【原文：The Trump administration's hefty new visa fees for H-1B workers have prompted high-level talks inside companies in Silicon Valley and beyond on the possibility of moving more jobs overseas - precisely the outcome the policy was meant to stop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/silicon-valley-hiring-turmoil-after-new-h-1b-visa-fees-move-spurs-offshoring-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UK3XHUKT6NITPHVAAJL3O7MK7A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空破产威胁小镇航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）因一年内第二次破产而削减或取消阿诺德帕尔默地区机场的服务，宾夕法尼亚州拉特罗布（Latrobe）的居民可能很快就不得不驱车 65 英里前往匹兹堡，才能飞到任何地方。【原文：If Spirit Airlines slashes or eliminates service at Arnold Palmer Regional Airport due to the carrier's second bankruptcy in a year, residents of Latrobe, Pennsylvania, may soon have to drive 65 miles to Pittsburgh if they need to fly anywhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spirit-airlines-bankruptcy-threatens-small-towns-flights-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKFHNRWYKVLRFIF4ZCVB5VFLPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达斥资 1000 亿美元打造 OpenAI 引发重大反垄断问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家称，主导人工智能芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）与领先的人工智能公司 OpenAI 之间价值 1000 亿美元的合作关系，可能会使两家公司获得对竞争对手不公平的优势。【原文：The $100 billion partnership between dominant AI chipmaker Nvidia and leading artificial intelligence company OpenAI could give both companies an unfair advantage over their competitors, experts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/nvidias-100-billion-openai-play-raises-big-antitrust-issues-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5M6VPTG4OBPDDI5O74ZEX7X5NY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，J&J 将从非美国市场撤出胃酸倒流设备]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二援引强生公司发给医生的一封信报道，强生公司将从美国以外的市场撤回一种治疗胃酸倒流疾病的设备。【原文：Johnson & Johnson will withdraw a device to treat acid reflux disease from markets outside the U.S., Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a company letter sent to doctors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/jj-withdraw-acid-reflux-device-non-us-markets-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KV7KUHGVSFORRMZMF5NOMKKFSI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国监管机构就违规内容传唤字节跳动和阿里巴巴旗下平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国网络空间管理局周二表示，中国网络空间监管机构传唤了字节跳动旗下新闻平台头条号和阿里巴巴旗下互联网浏览器运营商 UCWeb，原因是内容违规。【原文：China's cyberspace regulator summoned ByteDance's news platform Toutiao and Alibaba's internet browser operator UCWeb over content violations, the Cyberspace Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-regulator-summons-bytedance-alibabas-platforms-over-content-violations-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LLKKN6CDRKG7FTJ4KGLD6MJ3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:27:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济合作与发展组织（OECD）称美国关税冲击尚未全面爆发，经济增长尚可维持]]></title><description><![CDATA[经合组织（OECD）周二表示，全球经济增长好于预期，但美国进口关税冲击的全部影响仍未显现，因为人工智能投资暂时支撑了美国的经济活动，财政支持也缓解了中国的经济放缓。【原文：Global growth is holding up better than expected, but the full brunt of the U.S. import tariff shock is still to be felt as AI investment props up U.S. activity for now and fiscal support cushions China's slowdown, the OECD said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/oecd-says-full-brunt-us-tariff-shock-yet-come-growth-holds-up-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UGMCQAWLRODRMOPJEAZANKOSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部对阿根廷的支持暂时为比索和米莱提供了友好的支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）承诺采取 "大规模、强有力 "的行动，利用有 91 年历史的美国危机基金来稳定阿根廷摇摆不定的货币，这可能会帮助比索站稳脚跟，至少暂时如此。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent's pledge of "large and forceful" actions to stabilize Argentina's wobbling currency by using a 91-year-old U.S. crisis fund could help the peso find its footing, at least for a while.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-treasurys-support-argentina-gives-peso-milei-friendly-leg-up-now-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RU6EDZQXDRKP5CWEJOTQI3HAKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:03:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 DHL 从周四起恢复飞往美国的商业包裹服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国敦豪快递公司（DHL）将从本周四起恢复向美国运送企业标准包裹的服务，这是该公司因美国即将对低价值包裹征收关税而暂停这项服务约四周后的又一举措。【原文：Germany's DHL will resume the shipment of standard parcels for businesses to the United States from Thursday, roughly four weeks after suspending the service over looming U.S. customs duties for low-value packages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/germanys-dhl-resume-us-bound-business-parcel-service-thursday-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HT6ETP23ZNWBPCEF7IUWRSD4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 08:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰诺制药商肯维股价反弹，特朗普的主张面临回击]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将泰诺（Tylenol）生产商肯维（Kenvue）的常用止痛药与怀孕期间的自闭症风险联系在一起，但肯维的股票在周二的欧洲交易中仍然上涨。【原文：Tylenol-maker Kenvue stock rose in European trading on Tuesday, even after U.S. President Donald Trump linked its popular pain medication to autism risk during pregnancy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/tylenol-maker-kenvue-shares-bounce-trump-claims-face-pushback-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3WRYX2OKNMWHBZKJUJJSMXQ7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 08:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>