<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 10:08:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 10:08:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Religare 公司称美国商人对其股份提出了竞争性收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度 Religare 企业称，一名美国商人已提出收购该公司 26% 股份的建议，这是该金融服务公司控制权争夺战的最新转折。【原文：India's Religare Enterprises said a U.S. businessman has made a proposal to acquire a 26% stake in it, the latest twist in the battle for control of the financial services company which has rejected another bid as being priced too low.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/indias-religare-says-us-businessman-makes-competing-offer-stake-2025-01-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKE7IRH7RFO3DEMYDGFA7RUOTU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道联邦贸易委员会主席称 COVID 早已结束，请回到办公室]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）主席周五承认，该机构约 80% 的员工每周大部分时间都在家工作，员工们对重返全职办公室感到焦虑，但他表示，COVID 大流行早已过去，员工们需要在办公桌前工作。【原文：The chairman of the Federal Trade Commission on Friday acknowledged staff anxiety over returning to full-time in the office at an agency where around 80% work from home most of the week, but said the COVID pandemic is long over and workers need to be at their desks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ftc-chairman-says-covid-is-long-over-get-back-office-2025-01-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DORY2L5ETRP4TGIB7S2GKOCM5E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 TechCrunch 报道，联合健康确认有 1.9 亿美国人受到技术部门黑客攻击的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 TechCrunch 周五报道，UnitedHealth 技术部门 Change 遭到的网络攻击影响了 1.9 亿美国人的个人信息。【原文：The cyberattack at UnitedHealth's tech unit Change affected the personal information of 190 million Americans, TechCrunch reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-confirms-190-million-americans-affected-by-hack-tech-unit-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNAQTFV5QRKHLKL4AIPTADGTCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞公司将为偏头痛药物回扣支付 5970 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五表示，辉瑞公司将支付 5970 万美元，以解决其收购的一家公司通过支付回扣让医生开具偏头痛药物 Nurtec ODT 来欺诈医疗保险和其他医疗项目的指控。【原文：Pfizer will pay $59.7 million to resolve charges that a company it acquired defrauded Medicare and other healthcare programs by paying kickbacks so doctors would prescribe the migraine drug Nurtec ODT, the U.S. Department of Justice said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/pfizer-pay-597-million-over-kickbacks-migraine-drug-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHQ7IT4FEVO43G7TFLKTUDFE7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 22:55:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ben & Jerry's指责联合利华因特朗普而对其封口]]></title><description><![CDATA[本-杰瑞（Ben &amp; Jerry's）周五加大了对联合利华（Unilever）的审查诉讼力度，指控其母公司压制了这家美国冰淇淋制造商想要发布的一份社会政策声明，因为该声明提到了唐纳德-特朗普总统。【原文：Ben &amp; Jerry's on Friday ratcheted up its censorship lawsuit against Unilever , accusing its parent company of suppressing a social policy statement the U.S. ice cream maker wanted to release because it mentioned President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ben-jerrys-accuses-unilever-muzzling-it-because-trump-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEBWKQWPXVPXTBBBLT4IOHXRXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 22:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[破产的普渡公司为推进价值 74 亿美元的阿片类药物交易赢得时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）周五表示，该公司需要更多的时间来为一项价值 74 亿美元的新和解方案争取支持，这项新和解方案可能会完成该公司多年来为解决数千起有关其成瘾性止痛药奥施康定（OxyContin）的诉讼所做的努力。【原文：Purdue Pharma said on Friday it needs more time to build support for a new $7.4 billion settlement that could complete the company's years-long effort to resolve thousands of lawsuits over its addictive pain medication OxyContin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bankrupt-purdue-buys-time-advance-74-billion-opioid-deal-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5HJDNRWZBNOLGT273YGLCRTBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博雅计划就去银行化问题与白宫和国会接触 - 发言人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行发言人周五表示，该行将与唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府和国会就可能导致该行退出与客户的银行业务关系的法规进行接触。【原文：Bank of America will be engaging with President Donald Trump's administration and Congress on regulations that the bank said can lead to it exiting banking relationships with a customer, a spokesperson said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bofa-plans-engage-with-white-house-congress-debanking-spokesperson-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X27E4JS26NK65BRJA52KS4S5PU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:35:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府要求最高法院在重新考虑政策时暂停审理案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周五要求美国最高法院搁置燃料生产商根据联邦空气污染法对加州汽车尾气排放和电动汽车标准提出质疑的辩论计划。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration asked the U.S. Supreme Court on Friday to put on hold planned arguments in a bid by fuel producers to challenge California's standards for vehicle emissions and electric cars under a federal air pollution law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/trump-administration-asks-supreme-court-pause-cases-it-reconsiders-policy-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDVG7JW675LNJNEOBYRRVNDHME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[服役、在建和开发中的美国海上风电场]]></title><description><![CDATA[1 月 20 日，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普重返椭圆形办公室的第一天就暂停了新的联邦海上风电租赁，以等待环境和经济审查。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump suspended new federal offshore wind leasing on his first day back in the Oval Office on Jan. 20, pending an environmental and economic review.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-offshore-wind-farms-service-construction-under-development-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WGJFAFI3FPBXE5I3ERMDFR3BQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 20:39:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：华尔街银行将出售数十亿美元 X 贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，华尔街银行正准备出售社交媒体平台 X 的大部分债务。【原文：Wall Street banks are preparing to sell a big portion of debt holdings in social media platform X, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/wall-street-banks-set-sell-billions-dollars-x-loans-wsj-reports-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">225BUSI2BFIJ5OVBTVYQV2U234</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 20:31:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国放弃对 UnitedHealth 医疗保险计划评级案的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国医疗保险与医疗补助服务中心周五表示，它不会对法院要求其重新计算对联合健康保险公司（UnitedHealth）私人管理的医疗保险计划的公开星级评定的命令提出上诉，该保险公司称，这将使其因失去客户而损失数百万美元。【原文：The U.S. Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services on Friday said it would not appeal a court order that it recalculate the public star ratings it gave to UnitedHealth's privately administered Medicare health insurance plans, which the insurer said would cost it millions of dollars from lost customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-drops-appeal-case-over-unitedhealth-medicare-plans-rating-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSS5VTC5GNJQZEEXK3JWGOI6RU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将在美国和日本测试 Threads 上的广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周五表示，随着其社交媒体平台 Threads 的月活跃用户超过 3 亿，该公司将开始与美国和日本的一些品牌合作，测试在 Threads 上投放广告。【原文：Meta Platforms will begin test launching ads on its social media platform Threads with a few brands in the U.S. and Japan, it said on Friday, as the app hits over 300 million monthly active users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-test-ads-threads-us-japan-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5WF2I4JRJNX7FW5IGQ7MHG7PU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（FTC）主席弗格森赢得对特朗普 "DEI大清洗 "的首次投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）主席安德鲁-弗格森（Andrew Ferguson）在委员会中仍占多数的民主党人下台后，获得了广泛的权力来清理该机构的多元化、公平和包容（DEI）政策。【原文：U.S. Federal Trade Commission Chair Andrew Ferguson gained broad authority to purge diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) policies at the agency after Democrats, who still have the majority on the commission, stood down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ftc-chair-ferguson-wins-first-vote-over-trumps-dei-purge-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKMHLNMETNP5RCL2XM4AQOLCTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官暂停太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）就反移民偏见案提出质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周五批准了美国司法部的请求，暂停埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）的诉讼，称司法部无权追究该太空技术公司拒绝雇用某些移民的指控。【原文：A federal judge on Friday granted the U.S. Department of Justice's request to pause a lawsuit by Elon Musk's SpaceX claiming the agency lacks the power to pursue claims that the space technology company refused to hire certain immigrants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-pauses-spacexs-challenge-case-over-anti-immigrant-bias-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBOTNVGEMRJLTA6JIXDHLGRMXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：亿万富翁卡尔塔吉隆如何影响意大利银行业并购浪潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利亿万富翁弗朗切斯科-加埃塔诺-卡尔塔吉罗内（Francesco Gaetano Caltagirone）已成为目前正在进行的意大利金融业重塑的领军人物。【原文：Italian billionaire Francesco Gaetano Caltagirone has emerged as a leading player in the reshaping of Italy's financial sector that is currently under way.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/how-billionaire-caltagirone-could-influence-italys-banking-ma-wave-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MR55SLA5JJ5NDTEM5FZLE4C5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kraken、Blockchain.com 与特朗普的游说者一起参加群众签名活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[记录显示，自11月大选以来，加密货币交易所Kraken和Blockchain.com背后的公司加入了数十家企业和富豪的行列，雇用了与特朗普总统结盟的游说公司巴拉德合伙人（Ballard Partners）。【原文：The companies behind the crypto exchanges Kraken and Blockchain.com have joined the dozens of corporations and wealthy individuals that have hired the President Trump-tied lobbying firm Ballard Partners since November's elections, records show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kraken-blockchaincom-join-crowd-signing-with-trump-tied-lobbyists-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAW3AS3QJRI2ZDULHG24CSAEJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰相关需求使美国 2024 年武器出口创纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院周五表示，2024年美国对外国政府的军事装备销售额将增长29%，达到创纪录的3187亿美元，因为各国都在寻求补充运往乌克兰的库存，并为重大冲突做好准备。【原文：Sales of U.S. military equipment to foreign governments in 2024 rose 29% to a record $318.7 billion, the U.S. State Department said on Friday, as countries sought to replenish stocks sent to Ukraine and prepare for major conflicts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ukraine-related-demand-sends-us-arms-exports-record-2024-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URYMBPXZ3BO5VAVDU63IVCIDTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:26:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国油气钻机数降至 2021 年 12 月以来最低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第三周削减石油和天然气钻井平台数量，创下自2021年12月以来的新低。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating for a third week in a row to the lowest since December 2021, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-gas-rig-count-falls-lowest-since-dec-2021-baker-hughes-says-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVSX565L2FPQZL5A67G7VOC3J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:17:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令实施多元化计划，目标公司终止 DEI 计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[塔吉特（Target）周五表示，它将终止其多元化、公平和包容计划以及其他公平举措，成为最新一家退出这些旨在提高工作场所种族和族裔代表性的政策的美国公司。【原文：Target said on Friday it was ending its diversity, equity and inclusion program along with other equity initiatives, becoming the latest U.S. firm to pull back on these policies, meant to boost racial and ethnic representation at workplaces.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/target-ends-its-3-year-diversity-equity-inclusion-initiatives-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VH6TQ4O3YRJMXONQWRD3UJ7SFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利 MPS 如何从濒临倒闭到竞购受人尊敬的商业银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[自 2022 年初来到锡耶纳以来，Monte dei Paschi（MPS）首席执行官路易吉-洛瓦格里奥（Luigi Lovaglio）已经熬了好几个通宵，当时意大利财政部挑选他来重振这家世界上历史最悠久银行的命运，而这已经是该银行被救助五年之后的事情了。【原文：Monte dei Paschi (MPS) CEO Luigi Lovaglio has pulled several all-nighters since arriving in Siena in early 2022, when Italy's Treasury picked him out to revive the fortunes of the world's oldest bank, five years after bailing it out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/how-italys-mps-went-near-collapse-bid-revered-merchant-bank-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W6IOGM62FRN4XCVWFSC2PFGFFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:57:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德州仪器第一季度盈利预期黯淡，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[德州仪器（Texas Instruments）周四预测第一季度利润低于分析师预期，因为这家模拟芯片制造商正努力应对其主要汽车和工业市场的库存积压问题。【原文：Texas Instruments forecast first-quarter profit below analysts' estimates on Thursday, as the analog chipmaker grapples with an inventory buildup in its key automotive and industrial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/texas-instruments-gives-dour-q1-profit-forecast-shares-fall-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BB64FCJG7FP6VKC3WTPEAZRVKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普改造美国电网的高难度动作并非易事]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周表示，美国电网越来越不可靠，他需要迅速采取行动进行监管，但电网最复杂、最麻烦的领域之一：长距离输电线路，却没有简单的解决办法。【原文：President Donald Trump's oversight of an increasingly unreliable U.S. power grid requires swift action, he said this week, but there is no easy fix for one of the grid's most complex and troubled areas: long-distance transmission lines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trumps-high-wire-act-transform-us-power-grid-wont-be-easy-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTTCB62TN5KPBOEVBFWDUZMO2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年对冲基金行业规模达 4.5 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司 HFR 周五表示，对冲基金行业在 2024 年底管理的资产规模为 4.51 万亿美元，比上年增长 9.75%。【原文：The hedge fund industry ended 2024 with $4.51 trillion in assets under management, a 9.75% increase from the previous year, research firm HFR said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hedge-fund-industry-reaches-45-trillion-2024-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SYQRANFMFIIHCSXE2L52GTCPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，亚马逊 Prime Video 将重点转向体育直播以提高利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周五报道，亚马逊的 Prime Video 已将战略重点转向体育直播，而不再关注原创电视节目和电影，以实现公司内部的利润目标。【原文：Amazon's Prime Video has shifted its strategic focus towards live sports and away from original television shows and movies, seeking to meet internal corporate profit targets, The Information reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/amazon-prime-video-shifts-focus-live-sports-boost-profits-information-reports-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2RCKY3ARVLFZD5LGNRA63DCVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金流动 博鳌亚洲银行调查显示，半数投资者希望在对冲基金上投入更多资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[在接受美国银行大宗交易经纪部门调查的全球投资者中，有一半人计划今年向对冲基金增拨资金，37%的人希望保持不变。【原文：Half of the global investors surveyed by Bank of America's prime brokerage department plan to allocate more money to hedge funds this year, while 37% wanted no change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/hedge-flow-half-investors-want-spend-more-hedge-funds-says-bofa-survey-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NLSNMR5SZPRLPQEEV2XPVOCW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路易斯安那州的 Argent 液化天然气公司与孟加拉国政府达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷液化天然气公司（Argent LNG）周五发表声明说，该公司正在路易斯安那州开发年产 2500 万公吨的液化天然气（LNG）设施，并已与孟加拉国政府签署了一项不具约束力的协议，每年将购买多达 500 万公吨的液化天然气（LNG）。【原文：Argent LNG, which is developing a 25 million metric tonnes per annum (MTPA) LNG facility in Louisiana, has signed a non-binding agreement with the government of Bangladesh to purchase up to 5 million metric tons of liquefied natural gas (LNG) annually, the company said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/louisianas-argent-lng-sets-deal-with-government-bangladesh-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZXHFTAUKBPMZEDWLCYK2OFIQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，IPO热情高涨，但要注意估值问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街分析师说，Venture Global 雄心勃勃的估值目标受到的冷遇表明，公司在上市时需要设定切合实际的预期，这也可能是一个信号，表明新股发行的复苏可能是谨慎的。【原文：The tepid reception to Venture Global's ambitious valuation target shows companies need to set realistic expectations when going public, Wall Street analysts said, and could be a signal that the recovery in new offerings may be a cautious one.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/appetite-ipos-is-strong-watch-those-valuations-analysts-say-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RB6V3B35JFPFTLBDAKUM2QURWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:57:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次呼吁欧佩克降低油价]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五再次呼吁欧佩克（OPEC）削减石油价格，以损害石油大国俄罗斯的财政，并帮助结束乌克兰战争。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday reiterated his call for OPEC to cut oil prices to hurt oil-rich Russia's finances and help bring an end to the war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-once-again-calls-opec-drop-oil-prices-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCD4TWLDBRKZPOH2OZKVC3QHGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:35:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Affirm 扩大与自由互惠投资公司的合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[现购现付贷款公司 Affirm Holdings 与投资公司 Liberty Mutual Investments (LMI) 周五表示，双方已扩大了资本合作关系。【原文：Buy now, pay later lender Affirm Holdings has expanded its capital partnership with investment firm Liberty Mutual Investments (LMI), the companies said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/affirm-expands-partnership-with-liberty-mutual-investments-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMDYZLDPYVNNPE5BRJW7UQO3P4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管有特朗普的命令，但放弃 DEI 可能会让公司陷入法律纠纷]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家表示，那些为避免特朗普政府审查而缩减工作场所多元化努力的美国公司，可能会使自己面临更多工人歧视诉讼。【原文：U.S. companies that scale back workplace diversity efforts to avoid scrutiny from the Trump administration may be exposing themselves to more discrimination lawsuits by workers, experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/despite-trump-order-abandoning-dei-could-land-companies-legal-trouble-2025-01-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7VQHKB7QZLYVOA2VCWMDW6WWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>