<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:37:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:37:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提议削减 1630 亿美元联邦预算]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府在一份声明中表示，建议明年削减1630亿美元的联邦支出，这将取消超过五分之一的非军事支出（不包括强制性项目）。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration proposed a $163 billion cut to federal spending next year, which would eliminate more than a fifth of the non-military spending excluding mandatory programs, it said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-unveils-federal-budget-blueprint-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WJWDOQSCJLNPNUMUGMPCOSNIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:21:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年利润预期下调后，布洛克公司股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Block 公司股价下跌 22%，创下自 2023 年 11 月以来的最低点，此前这家支付公司下调了今年的利润预期。【原文：Block's shares fell 22% on Friday, hitting their lowest since November 2023 after the payments firm cut its profit forecast for the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/block-shares-tumble-after-2025-profit-forecast-cut-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33IXXIJGSZOMHF5C5BXXT3ZISE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:18:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦政府就业人数再次下降，DOGE 裁员堆积如山]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于唐纳德-特朗普总统和顾问埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）致力于大幅削减联邦工作人员，4月份美国政府工作人员的数量连续第四个月下降，非邮政部门的就业人数减少了8500人。【原文：The ranks of U.S. government workers fell for a fourth straight month in April with non-postal employment falling by 8,500 as President Donald Trump and adviser Elon Musk aim for drastic cuts in the federal workforce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-federal-employment-drops-again-doge-cuts-stack-up-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SPSGOQUQZPHTAARAKTXUKO5YA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金连续第三周出现资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国贸易政策对经济增长和商业情绪的影响，截至4月30日，美国股票基金连续第三周出现资金外流。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed outflows for a third straight week through April 30, driven by worries over the impact of U.S. trade policies on economic growth and business sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-outflows-third-straight-week-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXXNN6HAWNNRLAGHFJ7EJT27F4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，DOGE 扩大了在华尔街监管机构的存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，总统顾问埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的政府效率部（DOGE）正在扩大其在美国证券交易委员会的存在，增加了第三名工作人员。【原文：Presidential adviser Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) is expanding its presence at the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission by adding a third staff member, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/doge-expands-presence-wall-st-regulator-sources-say-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VUJW3KO3NNXXEHQSRYOF3ZUL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师警告：旅游需求疲软，美国经济面临损失数十亿美元的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师警告说，随着特朗普政府的贸易政策对消费者情绪造成影响，与旅游相关的公司盈利预测黯淡，表明旅游需求减弱，今年美国经济可能因此损失数十亿美元。【原文：Weakening travel demand, signaled by grim earnings forecasts of travel-related companies, may erase billions of dollars from the U.S. economy this year as the Trump administration's trade policy takes a toll on consumer sentiment, analysts have warned.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-economy-risks-losing-billions-travel-demand-weakens-analysts-warn-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNN7FVEZEFOCZGNJOFD4WQQWQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:57:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构将于 6 月 10 日前就 SES 和 Intelsat 的交易做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据欧盟委员会网站上的一份文件，欧盟反垄断监管机构将在 6 月 10 日前决定是否批准欧洲卫星公司 SES 以 31 亿欧元收购 Intelsat 的交易。【原文：EU antitrust regulators will decide by June 10 whether to clear European satellite company SES's 3.1 billion euro acquisition of Intelsat, according to a filing on the European Commission website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-antitrust-regulators-decide-ses-intelsat-deal-by-june-10-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSR5USMSGRKDVMJJ2FDSPQ7OIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国经济处于 "转型期"，敦促美联储降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，美国经济正处于转型阶段，他列举了强劲的就业和他的关税计划，同时再次呼吁美国联邦储备委员会降低利率。【原文：President Donald Trump on Friday said the U.S. economy is in a transition stage, citing strong employment and his tariff plan while reiterating his call for the U.S. Federal Reserve to lower its interest rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-us-economy-transition-urges-fed-cut-rates-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XDKY35M75MRDFGX4TQC5X22TM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:45:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业市场依然稳定，美联储没有理由急于降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美联储政策制定者对劳动力市场可能出现的裂痕保持警惕，因为企业正在适应唐纳德-特朗普总统反复无常的贸易政策，他们得到了一些保证：到目前为止，劳动力市场几乎没有疲软，没有理由急于降息。【原文：Federal Reserve policymakers on the alert for possible cracks in the labor market as businesses adjust to President Donald Trump's erratic trade policy got some reassurance on Friday that so far there's little weakness, and no reason to rush on rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-gets-no-reason-rush-rate-cuts-still-stable-job-market-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XX4HQ5BOEBJOPM6RPTHI5RD5MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:40:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者抢购欧洲股票基金，但连续第三周逃离美国基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月30日的一周里，欧洲股票基金吸引了一年多来最大的单周资金流入，而美国基金则因关税对全球经济增长影响的持续不确定性而连续第三周出现资金流出。【原文：European equity funds attracted the largest weekly inflow in over a year in the week ending April 30, while U.S. funds saw outflows for a third straight week on continued uncertainty around the impact of tariffs on global economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5XK2H2R6FKV7BBQD6LUHE7IJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:30:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国将根据新制度禁止消费者借贷购买加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国监管机构周五表示，英国将限制消费者使用信用卡购买加密货币，并限制他们使用加密货币借贷产品，此举旨在加强对加密资产的保护，因为这是英国首次对加密资产进行监管。【原文：Britain is to restrict consumers' use of credit cards to buy crypto and their access to crypto lending products, the regulator said on Friday, a move aimed at improving protection as cryptoassets are regulated for the first time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/britain-bar-consumers-borrowing-buy-crypto-under-new-regime-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKV2HLYO3JLIDDRUTWQWRWOT2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:17:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在需求和贸易压力下，通用汽车将减少加拿大卡车组装厂的班次]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司和代表工人的工会周五表示，由于需求疲软和与贸易有关的挑战，通用汽车公司位于加拿大的奥沙瓦组装厂将从三班倒缩减为两班倒，该厂主要生产皮卡。【原文：General Motors' Oshawa Assembly plant in Canada, which builds pickup trucks, will cut back to a two-shift schedule from three due to softening demand and trade-related challenges, the company and the union representing workers said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-reduce-shifts-canadian-truck-assembly-plant-amid-demand-trade-pressures-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">466RKX5XTNOYRJVY6IWDNDQGPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，Nvidia 在美国出口禁令后再次开发中国定制芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《The Information》周五报道，英伟达（Nvidia）公司已告知其一些最大的中国客户，该公司正在调整其人工智能芯片的设计，以便在不违反美国出口规定的情况下将这些芯片出售给中国企业。【原文：Nvidia has told some of its biggest Chinese customers that it is tweaking the design of its AI chips so they can be sold to Chinese businesses without clashing with U.S. export rules, The Information reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-is-working-china-tailored-chips-again-after-us-export-ban-information-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SE7UFKXLNNGFA7VD6W6AJTKYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:14:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易所运营商 Cboe 因套期保值热潮实现创纪录利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[衍生品交易所 Cboe Global Markets 周五公布了创纪录的第一季度利润，并提高了全年收入增长预期，原因是市场波动加剧推动了期权交易的强劲增长。【原文：Derivatives exchange Cboe Global Markets reported a record first-quarter profit on Friday and boosted its annual revenue growth forecast as heightened market volatility fueled strong growth in options trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/exchange-operator-cboe-posts-record-profit-hedging-rush-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RD6XWDDSTBINBGF4BY65U4HCIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭裁决后，Spotify 的美国应用程序更新获得苹果批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify 周五表示，其美国应用程序更新已获得苹果批准，可以显示定价信息和外部支付链接，几天前，一名法官禁止 iPhone 制造商对非应用程序购买收取佣金。【原文：Spotify said on Friday its U.S. app update has secured Apple's approval to show pricing information and external payment links, days after a judge barred the iPhone maker from charging commission on off-app purchases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spotifys-us-app-update-gets-apple-approval-after-court-ruling-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5AKV6IG3ZKIRIPHQ5PJNN4YWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 4 月就业人数增长放缓，关税影响尚未完全显现]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 4 月份的就业增长略有放缓，但由于唐纳德-特朗普总统激进的关税政策加剧了经济的不确定性，劳动力市场的前景日益暗淡。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed marginally in April, but the outlook for the labor market is increasingly darkening as President Donald Trump's aggressive tariff policy heightens economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/view-april-us-payrolls-growth-slows-before-full-tariff-impact-felt-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNFMJ3DQWJJGFELHBELICS52BA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月就业增长小幅放缓；失业率稳定在 4.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 4 月份的就业增长略有放缓，但由于唐纳德-特朗普总统激进的关税政策加剧了经济的不确定性，劳动力市场的前景日益暗淡。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed marginally in April, but the outlook for the labor market is increasingly darkening as President Donald Trump's aggressive tariff policy heightens economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-job-growth-slows-marginally-april-unemployment-rate-steady-42-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YLKADMWGRPIVDHOIR4QRHFJDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:37:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，与竞购英国石油公司相比，壳牌首席执行官更倾向于股票回购]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，壳牌公司首席执行官周五表示，他宁愿回购更多公司股票，也不愿发起对竞争对手石油巨头英国石油公司（BP）的收购要约。【原文：Shell CEO said on Friday he would rather buy back more of his company's own shares than launch a takeover bid for rival oil major BP, the Financial Times reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-ceo-prefers-share-buybacks-over-bid-bp-ft-reports-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXRKZBB6UVIIJK2YKJS5FZHG54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大帝国石油公司因炼油利润率上升而实现季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，加拿大石油生产商帝国石油公司（Imperial Oil）公布第一季度利润增长，主要原因是其炼油和燃料销售业务的利润率上升，这使其在美国上市的股票在收盘前上涨了近 6%。【原文：Canadian oil producer Imperial Oil posted a rise in first-quarter profit on Friday, driven primarily by stronger margins in its refining and fuel sales business, sending its U.S.-listed shares up nearly 6% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/canadas-imperial-oil-posts-rise-first-quarter-profit-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72ALV7HPRNKA7FNFMXMUYIPSIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络攻击后，英国 M&S 进入销售中断的第二周]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，英国马莎百货公司（Marks & Spencer）在遭受重大网络攻击后，第二周无法接受网上服装和家居订单，这影响了新一季产品的销售，因为英国正沐浴在创纪录的气温中。【原文：Britain's Marks & Spencer entered a second week unable to take online clothing and home orders on Friday following a major cyberattack, hitting sales of new season ranges as the country basks in record temperatures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-ms-enters-second-week-sales-disruption-after-cyberattack-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKOZOAI5LNPLZBCL7GTJ525G6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take-Two Interactive 将《侠盗猎车手 6》的发行时间推迟至 2026 年 5 月 26 日]]></title><description><![CDATA[Take-Two Interactive 周五将《侠盗猎车手 6》的发行时间推迟到了 2026 年 5 月 26 日，延长了人们对视频游戏史上最炙手可热的游戏之一的等待时间，导致其股价在盘前交易中暴跌 9%。【原文：Take-Two Interactive on Friday pushed the release of "Grand Theft Auto VI" to May 26, 2026, extending the wait for one of the most hotly anticipated titles in video-gaming history and sending its shares tumbling 9% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/take-two-interactive-delays-grand-theft-auto-vi-release-may-26-2026-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U33RBLBO4NPJ3NCOVFFGEYEVVA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：五月买入？]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPHKNLCTINPWPPM2A7MG6CWRTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环保组织抨击 JBS 获准在美国上市，华尔街却对此大加赞赏]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国金融监管机构上个月批准了全球最大的肉类包装公司 JBS 在纽约证券交易所上市的提议，这招致了气候和动物权益组织的强烈批评，但却得到了华尔街的赞扬。【原文：The U.S. financial regulator's approval last month of a proposal by the world's largest meatpacker JBS to list on the New York Stock Exchange is drawing strong criticism from climate and animal rights groups but praise from Wall Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/environmental-groups-blast-jbss-us-listing-approval-wall-street-praises-it-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXAJN3AYHBOQ7HAPS3IVWQBYIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受欧盟碳排放规定和美国关税影响，大众汽车核心品牌集团利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车周五表示，受欧盟碳排放规定和与美国关税相关的库存减记的影响，其核心品牌集团（包括最畅销的大众品牌）的第一季度营业利润下降了 46.3%。【原文：Volkswagen on Friday said its first-quarter operating profit for the core brand group, which includes its best-selling VW brand, declined by 46.3%, impacted by EU carbon provisions and write-downs on inventory related to U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/volkswagen-core-brand-group-profit-falls-eu-carbon-provision-us-tariffs-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMWDXYP3HBOYNMV6YT3MXM6O6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:54:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利润低于预期，麦格纳计划采取成本削减措施以缓解关税冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大汽车零部件供应商麦格纳国际公司（Magna International）周五表示，该公司计划实施成本节约措施，以减轻美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收关税带来的冲击。【原文：Canadian auto parts supplier Magna International said on Friday that it plans to implement cost-saving measures to cushion the hit from U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/magna-plans-cost-cutting-measures-cushion-tariff-hit-after-profit-misses-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNLBWRG6GJKOTAFBSZ6KRJ2QFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易紧张局势出现缓和迹象，期货上涨，就业数据受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五上涨，原因是中美贸易战有望缓和，抵消了苹果和亚马逊令人失望的最新财报。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday as hopes of a de-escalation in a punishing U.S.-China trade war offset disappointing earnings updates from Apple and Amazon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/futures-rise-signs-easing-trade-tensions-jobs-data-focus-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B73XZZLEYBJKPNYJF2DCNYRAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:44:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司利润超出华尔街预期，受圭亚那和二叠纪生产提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚周五公布的第一季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，原因是圭亚那和二叠纪盆地的石油和天然气产量增加，帮助提高了收益。【原文：Exxon Mobil on Friday beat Wall Street's estimate for first-quarter profit as higher oil and gas production from Guyana and the Permian basin helped boost earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-beats-wall-street-profit-estimate-boosted-by-guyana-permian-production-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQH26LWPVJN5ZINELYM4PPHUDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[炼油业务较上一季度有所恢复，雪佛龙利润符合华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙（Chevron）周五公布的第一季度财报符合华尔街预期，该公司的炼油业务已从去年年底的亏损扭亏为盈。【原文：Chevron on Friday reported first-quarter earnings that met Wall Street estimates, as the company saw a turnaround in its refining business from a loss late last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-meets-wall-street-profit-estimates-refining-recovers-previous-quarter-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIIZDPFNGNIHLF7U2J2DV7RMJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:18:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，欧洲将把俄罗斯被冻结的数十亿美元现金交给西方投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社和熟悉内情的人士看到的文件显示，在莫斯科攫取俄罗斯投资者的现金后，欧洲清算公司计划扣押并重新分配比利时清算公司冻结的约 30 亿欧元（约合 34 亿美元）俄罗斯资金。【原文：Euroclear plans to seize and redistribute about 3 billion euros ($3.4 billion) of Russia's funds that are frozen at the Belgian clearing firm after Moscow grabbed investor cash in Russia, according to documents seen by Reuters and people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/europe-hand-billions-frozen-russian-cash-western-investors-sources-say-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLYHTCESV5JWFNZVCETLTIIDVA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜邦利润超预期，电子业务部门从人工智能芯片热潮中获益]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，杜邦公司第一季度利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于其电子行业部门销售额的增长。【原文：DuPont beat Wall Street expectations for first-quarter profit on Friday, helped by higher sales in its unit that caters to the electronics industry, and it warned of a hit to full-year earnings from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/dupont-beats-profit-estimates-electronics-unit-gains-ai-chip-boom-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5N7IP4SNUVOK5NW6GXDENGVPMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:14:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>