<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:36:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:36:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[印尼为苹果公司部分 iPhone 16 系列产品颁发电信许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚通信部网站称，该部已为苹果公司的部分 iPhone 16 系列产品颁发了电信许可证。【原文：Indonesia's communications ministry has issued a telecommunications permit for some of Apple's iPhone 16 series, according to the ministry's website.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/indonesia-issues-telco-permit-some-apples-iphone-16-series-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WV7CM7SCVPQFOSHQKX34WMHAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉董事长辞去澳大利亚最大风险投资公司运营合伙人职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士透露，特斯拉董事长罗宾-登霍姆（Robyn Denholm）已辞去澳大利亚最大风险投资基金黑鸟风险投资公司（Blackbird VC）运营合伙人的职务，但她仍是该公司的董事会成员和顾问。【原文：Tesla chair Robyn Denholm has moved out of her role as operating partner at Australia's biggest venture capital fund, Blackbird VC, people familiar with the situation said, while she remains a board member and adviser to the firm.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-chair-exits-operating-partner-role-australias-biggest-vc-firm-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7EXR7HG6RID3AHK3XTJLIUAOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:59:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场抛售，亚洲对冲基金表现优于美国同行]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲对冲基金比美国对冲基金更好地经受住了 3 月份市场大跌的考验，这得益于全球投资者纷纷涌入中国市场，中国股市表现相对优异。【原文：Asia hedge funds weathered the March selloff in markets better than their U.S. counterparts, helped by the relative outperformance of Chinese stocks as global investors rushed into that market.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/asia-hedge-funds-outperform-us-peers-markets-sell-off-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX74HMPTQZLQXGXP37WBCBIQME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特斯拉计划将Model Y的生产成本至少降低20%，以捍卫中国市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士透露，特斯拉将在上海生产其最畅销车型Y的低成本版本，旨在收复在其第二大市场价格战中失去的阵地。【原文：Tesla will make a lower-cost version of its best-selling Model Y in Shanghai, three people with knowledge of the matter said, aiming to regain ground lost during a price war in its second-largest market.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-plans-model-y-costing-least-20-less-produce-defend-china-share-sources-say-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7RDYJKSY5OYPM7H7J43QNGQ7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[条款表显示，新加坡星展银行通过美元债券融资 20 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份条款书显示，东南亚最大的银行星展集团已通过发行多期美元高级债券筹集了 20 亿美元资金，用于一般业务目的和财务活动。【原文：DBS Group , Southeast Asia's biggest bank, has raised $2 billion through a multi-tranche U.S. dollar senior bond issuance for general business purposes and to finance treasury activities, according to a term sheet seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/singapores-dbs-raises-2-billion-through-us-dollar-bonds-term-sheet-shows-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4W5RYZQDNFOYVD4Q7XX7VDZUHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，甲骨文将考虑在印度尼西亚巴淡岛建立数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，甲骨文公司正在与印度尼西亚政府商讨在该国巴淡岛建立云服务中心的事宜。【原文：Oracle Corp is in discussions with Indonesia's government to establish a cloud services center in the country's Batam Island, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/oracle-said-weigh-data-center-indonesias-batam-island-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YJFASTYVVNPDNCJW2ZOL2BI54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:42:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大对头号供应商征收 100%的关税后，中国将面临菜籽粕短缺问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中国政府对头号出口国加拿大的船运征收关税扰乱了贸易，而且替代来源不太可能弥补缺口，因此到今年第三季度，中国很可能面临菜籽粕供应短缺。【原文：China is likely to face a supply shortage of rapeseed meal by the third quarter of this year as Beijing's tariffs on shipments from top exporter Canada disrupt trade and as alternative sources are unlikely to make up the deficit.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-set-rapeseed-meal-shortage-after-100-duty-top-supplier-canada-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBITNSFSJ5KQ7KYNNZFMWFIS4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国就向美国利益集团出售港口一事发表批评性评论后，长江和记股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国港澳办在国家媒体上发表评论文章，批评香港企业集团长江和记最近出售港口是对中国的背叛，该公司股价周五下跌超过 6%。【原文：Shares of Hong Kong conglomerate CK Hutchison slid more than 6% on Friday after China's Hong Kong and Macau Affairs Office posted a commentary in state media criticising the company's recent port sale as a betrayal of China.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/ck-hutchisons-shares-drop-after-china-posts-critical-commentary-port-sale-us-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XER2DVJ55LULHCAWCGC5QMEUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰停火协议仍遥遥无期，石油价格反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五油价反弹，收复了上一交易日超过1%的部分跌幅，部分原因是乌克兰战争迅速结束的前景日益暗淡，这可能会带来更多的俄罗斯能源供应。【原文：Oil prices rebounded on Friday to recover some of their more than 1% losses in the previous session, partly due to diminishing prospects of a quick end to the Ukraine war that could bring back more Russian energy supplies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-bounces-ukraine-ceasefire-deal-remains-elusive-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F6MIOKA65LOPLXAX3VQCF3EGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 2 月通胀可能因恢复能源补贴而降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于能源补贴的恢复，日本 2 月份的核心通胀率可能比上月有所下降，但总体价格趋势可能会使决策者继续按计划在今年再次加息。【原文：Japan's core inflation likely decelerated in February from the previous month due to the resumption of energy subsidies, a Reuters poll showed, though the overall price trends will likely keep policymakers on track to raise rates again this year.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-inflation-likely-cooled-feb-energy-subsidy-resumption-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DR6D6SRB5N43FGRCYHKM2LZJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[已更新锂电池政策的航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲的几家航空公司已经更新了关于机上携带锂电池的指南。手机和电子烟等设备中都装有锂电池，一旦发生故障，就会产生烟雾、火灾或极度高温。【原文：Several airlines in Asia have updated their guidance on carrying lithium batteries onboard. The batteries are in devices such as cellphones and e-cigarettes, and can malfunction to produce smoke, fire or extreme heat.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airlines-that-have-updated-their-lithium-battery-policies-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQYAFVO4UFO4NFJTJFSTXY4MJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将讨论特朗普贸易战带来的经济风险，利率将保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行下周将维持利率稳定，并讨论不断升级的美国贸易战对依赖出口的日本经济构成了多大风险，这将是日本央行下一次加息时机的关键。【原文：The Bank of Japan is set to keep interest rates steady next week and discuss just how much of a risk the escalating U.S. trade war poses to the export-reliant economy, which will be key to the timing of its next rate hike.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-debate-economic-risks-trump-trade-war-rates-seen-steady-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGQNOPYRFVMHTKKOV2636NZVLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将讨论特朗普贸易战带来的经济风险，利率将保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行下周将维持利率稳定，并讨论不断升级的美国贸易战对依赖出口的日本经济构成了多大风险，这将是日本央行下一次加息时机的关键。【原文：The Bank of Japan is set to keep interest rates steady next week and discuss just how much of a risk the escalating U.S. trade war poses to the export-reliant economy, which will be key to the timing of its next rate hike.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-debate-economic-risks-trump-trade-war-rates-seen-steady-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGQNOPYRFVMHTKKOV2636NZVLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市持稳；贸易战升级，黄金创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球贸易紧张局势升级令投资者感到紧张，并引发了对避险资产的追捧，黄金创下了历史新高。【原文：Asia shares rose on Friday and global markets attempted a rebound after a brutal selloff, while gold reached a record as an escalation of global trade tensions left investors nervous and sparked a flight to safe-haven assets.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYYJ2JX4EZOVHLAZFTUYNPAC7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:12:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepSeek 之后，中国的基金经理们打败了 High-Flyer 的人工智能之路]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国对冲基金 "高飞"（High-Flyer）在市场交易中使用人工智能，引发了内地资产管理公司之间的人工智能军备竞赛，可能会撼动中国 10 万亿美元的基金管理行业。【原文：Chinese hedge fund High-Flyer's use of artificial intelligence in trading markets has spurred an AI arms race among mainland asset managers that could shake up the country's $10 trillion fund management industry.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/after-deepseek-chinese-fund-managers-beat-high-flyers-path-ai-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66WFKUGW3FI5VHXVVZYHMCQCG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球贸易紧张局势升级，美元坚挺，欧元漂移]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于市场正努力应对不断升级的全球贸易紧张局势和经济急剧下滑的风险，美元普遍走强，欧元则进一步远离五个月高点。【原文：The U.S. dollar was broadly firmer on Friday with the euro pulling further away from a five-month peak as markets grappled with escalating global trade tensions and risks of a sharp economic downturn.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-holds-firm-euro-drifts-global-trade-tensions-escalate-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3FEQUIDSZN35LNUDFWC4TASSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:26:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普让中国股市（在某种程度上）再度伟大]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发动的大范围贸易战引发了对经济衰退的担忧，全球投资者找到了一个不太可能的新避难所：中国股票。【原文：As U.S. President Donald Trump's wide-ranging trade war rouses fears of recession, global investors have found an unlikely new sanctuary: Chinese equities.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/donald-trump-makes-chinese-stocks-somewhat-great-again-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M33X4V4WA5KJDIIMIVAESVJL54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金再创新高，有望达到 3,000 美元峰值]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于美国关税的不确定性和对贸易紧张局势的担忧，以及对美联储放松货币政策的预期增强，黄金价格创下历史新高。【原文：Gold hit a record high on Friday, as uncertainty over U.S. tariffs and fears of trade tensions propelled prices, along with increased expectations of monetary policy easing by the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-mounts-record-summit-eyes-3000-peak-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z35ASMCMENI2PIW6OJQAS5OTCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 01:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，与硅谷相比，DeepSeek 将专注于研究而非收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，中国人工智能聊天机器人深鉴科技（DeepSeek）选择专注于研究而非营收，因为其亿万富翁创始人决定不效仿硅谷竞争对手，利用销售额突然飙升的机会。【原文：Chinese AI chatbot DeepSeek is choosing to focus on research over revenue, as its billionaire founder has decided not to follow Silicon Valley rivals by taking advantage of a sudden jump in sales, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/deepseek-focus-research-over-revenue-contrast-silicon-valley-ft-reports-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOXL2RIURRIERNA7X3ZTEPPX6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 01:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vietnam reviewing duties to boost import of US LNG, high-tech goods, PM says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vietnam is reviewing its duties on U.S. goods, including on liquefied natural gas, agriculture and high-tech products, Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh told the U.S. ambassador to the country, a report on the government's website said.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vietnam-reviewing-duties-us-lng-high-tech-products-pm-says-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXKO5DGO5ZIO3HBNM3Q6I3S2EY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Australian government to give ANZ $1.3 bln loan guarantee for Pacific operations]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Australian government will be giving ANZ Group a loan guarantee worth A$2 billion ($1.26 billion) to keep selling its services in the Pacific region, the lender said on Friday.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/australian-government-give-anz-13-bln-loan-guarantee-pacific-operations-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UO4LMK5S6JK5PGWH5EQ5YN6VEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Samsung SDI to issue new shares and invest in U.S. joint venture with GM]]></title><description><![CDATA[Samsung SDI said it would issue new shares worth 2 trillion won ($1.38 billion) in a regulatory filing on Friday and use the proceeds to invest in a U.S. joint venture with General Motors and expand its factory capacity in Hungary among others.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/samsung-sdi-issue-new-shares-invest-us-joint-venture-with-gm-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KJ6DU5RB5OO5MMDEPCAUNOBYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAweek: AI leading to faster, cheaper oil production, executives say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is speeding up oil and gas drilling and prompting companies to take a second look at places they had viewed as too difficult or expensive to develop, executives detailed during the CERAWeek conference in Houston.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-ai-leading-faster-cheaper-oil-production-executives-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PENN5ZILEFPYLGUSOYO6PWFQUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil's Eletrobras posts 25% rise in fourth-quarter net profit]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian power firm Eletrobras reported on Thursday a near 25% increase in its fourth-quarter net profit from a year earlier to 1.11 billion reais ($191.4 million).]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazils-eletrobras-posts-55-fall-fourth-quarter-net-profit-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YWBRQATPZJD5GVDPF3X55QOQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK, US hold private talks to resolve Apple encryption order, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[British officials held private talks with their U.S. counterparts to resolve concerns that UK is trying to force Apple to build a backdoor into Americans' encrypted data, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/uk-us-hold-private-talks-resolve-apple-encryption-order-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3S6ACJ3CJPCVHHX6RLDVGJJPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Foxconn to post higher Q4 profit on AI server demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker, is expected to report on Friday that fourth-quarter profit rose 2.35% on strong demand for artificial intelligence servers.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-post-higher-q4-profit-ai-server-demand-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3JZXXLPQNMOZBHEKKVYD25UOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US frees up almost $4.7 billion loan to TotalEnergies for Mozambique gas project, FT reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has released almost $5 billion in funding for a liquefied natural gas project by France's TotalEnergies in Mozambique, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-frees-up-almost-47-billion-loan-totalenergies-mozambique-gas-project-ft-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NABSASVBTZISRCNHGOTGBXKS4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Stock Exchange hires top ETF executives from Cboe, Nasdaq]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Texas Stock Exchange (TSXE), still months away from winning regulatory approval to begin operations, said it hired senior exchange-traded funds executives from Cboe Global Markets and Nasdaq to win a share of trading in the $11 trillion U.S. ETF market.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/texas-stock-exchange-hires-top-etf-executives-cboe-nasdaq-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWMOJTDJ4JO2RASNFNXC6TZBQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国大型玩具制造商加快将生产基地迁出中国的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与中国的贸易战愈演愈烈之际，沃尔玛和塔吉特的一家主要玩具供应商正在加快撤出中国的步伐，重新调整生产。【原文：A major supplier of toys to Walmart and Target is accelerating its shift out of China as it reshapes production amid President Donald Trump's intensifying trade war with the country.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/major-us-toymaker-speeds-up-plan-move-manufacturing-out-china-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32YHARYX7NPL7ONRYB54EPFT44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：贸易战担忧扼杀复苏希望，熊市开始发力]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKPR4AP6SZJMZL7DVVCXVOWXHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>