<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:35:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:35:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：欧盟高官预计特朗普将征收约 20% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，欧盟最高贸易谈判代表马罗什-谢夫乔维奇（Maroš Šefčovič）预计，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下周将对欧盟征收约20%的关税。【原文：The European Union's top trade negotiator Maroš Šefčovič expects U.S. President Donald Trump to hit the bloc with tariffs of about 20% next week, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/top-eu-official-expects-trump-tariffs-about-20-ft-reports-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIERJJXOLZP5BF2D3W52VIZKIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士政党计划遏制瑞银投资银行，以此作为资本规则的交换条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位资深立法者周三表示，作为旨在降低该行业风险的监管改革的一部分，瑞士的一个主要政党可能很快会提议对瑞银集团的投资银行活动设置上限。【原文：One of Switzerland's main political parties could soon propose capping UBS's investment banking activities as part of a regulatory overhaul aimed at making the sector less risky, a senior lawmaker said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swiss-party-plans-curb-ubs-investment-bank-trade-off-capital-rules-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7KLH2547RMTFIUKQ6SRDXYGTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储穆萨莱姆称关税可能引发更持久的通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周三表示，美国通胀率将停滞在美联储2%的目标之上，甚至在短期内进一步上升的风险已经增加，进口税的上升可能会引发更持久的物价压力。【原文：Risks have increased that U.S. inflation will stall above the Federal Reserve's 2% target or even rise further in the near term, with rising import taxes potentially triggering more persistent price pressures, St. Louis Fed president Alberto Musalem said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/st-louis-feds-musalem-says-tariffs-could-trigger-more-persistent-inflation-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAZPNFS2BJKFFFI5E4QVG6UJ3A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称可口可乐装瓶商遭到欧盟反垄断监管机构突袭]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位直接了解此事的人士说，可口可乐的装瓶商在本月早些时候遭到了欧盟反垄断监管机构的突袭。【原文：Coca Cola bottlers were raided by EU antitrust regulators earlier this month, a person with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coca-cola-bottlers-raided-by-eu-antitrust-regulators-source-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5J72XPYLZIIHPNZNYNT3Q5YHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 17:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普可能利用 2019 年的调查作为对汽车进口征收关税的理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业专家和前美国官员表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府很可能会利用他在第一个任期内完成的一项调查来为他所说的即将实施的汽车关税辩护。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is likely to use an investigation completed during his first term in office to justify auto tariffs that he says are imminent, industry experts and former U.S. officials said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-could-use-2019-investigation-justify-tariffs-auto-imports-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2QFBLPXE5KJDENYULU3W3WVAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:59:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称微软放弃在美国和欧洲租赁更多数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[道明证券（TD Cowen）分析师周三表示，由于供过于求，相对于当前的需求预测，微软在过去六个月中放弃了将在美国和欧洲使用 2 千兆瓦电力的数据中心项目。【原文：Microsoft has abandoned data center projects set to use 2 gigawatts of electricity in the U.S. and Europe in the last six months due to an oversupply relative to its current demand forecast, TD Cowen analysts said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-pulls-back-more-data-center-leases-us-europe-analysts-say-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3USLFKN45OTRKR4S3W3Y6QPIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于担心关税，意大利葡萄酒对美国的出口 "停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易集团Federvini周三表示，由于唐纳德-特朗普总统可能在未来几周内征收关税的不确定性，意大利葡萄酒和烈酒对美国的出口正在停滞。【原文：Italian wine and spirits exports to the United States are stalling due to the uncertainty over possible tariffs that President Donald Trump could impose in the coming weeks, trade group Federvini said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italian-wine-exports-us-at-standstill-due-tariff-fears-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5QJZ765NNK4BASIEL3YEGHK3M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普准备最快于周三宣布汽车关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）援引知情人士的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）准备最快于周三宣布有关汽车征税的消息。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is readying an announcement on auto levies as soon as Wednesday, Bloomberg News reported citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-is-preparing-auto-tariff-announcement-soon-wednesday-bloomberg-news-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5ZVMUR2LZMJPPKLNKHUZ63BGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表与中国副总理就贸易紧张局势表达 "坦率 "关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）准备进一步提高对中国进口商品的关税之际，美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）的办公室表示，格里尔在一次介绍性会晤中与中国国务院副总理何立峰就贸易问题进行了 "坦诚 "的会谈。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer held "candid" talks with Chinese Vice Premier He Lifeng on trade issues during an introductory meeting, Greer's office said as U.S. President Donald Trump prepares to raise tariffs on Chinese imports further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-trade-chief-chinese-vice-premier-express-candid-concerns-trade-tensions-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AF54MRMLDBMGRMYCA765NKJWSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:14:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席技术官就下一代喷气发动机的维护需求发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的航空公司之一的最高采购官员周三敦促通用电气航空航天公司和其他发动机制造商在设计下一代节油发动机时不要忽视耐用性。【原文：The top procurement official at one of Europe's largest airlines urged GE Aerospace and other engine makers on Wednesday not to overlook durability when it comes to designing the next generation of fuel-saving engines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lufthansa-cto-warns-over-maintenance-demand-next-jet-engines-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWHE2KTYDJPCTF4MW2KSF564GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:13:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：在具有里程碑意义的税务案件中，意大利要求 Meta、X 和 LinkedIn 缴税]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，四位直接了解此事的消息人士称，意大利已向 Meta、X 和 LinkedIn 提出税务要求，这是对美国科技巨头史无前例的增值税索赔的最后一个正式步骤，可能会对整个欧盟产生影响。【原文：Italy has handed tax demands to Meta , X and LinkedIn in the last formal step in an unprecedented VAT claim against the U.S. tech giants that could have repercussions across the European Union, four sources with direct knowledge of the matter said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italy-hands-vat-bill-meta-x-linkedin-landmark-tax-case-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZFAKC3S7VIUBKMZU3VZ22S2HI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡什卡利：美联储应在政策不确定的情况下长期按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周三表示，他对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税对美国经济的影响感到不确定，关税可能会推高物价，因此需要提高利率，而关税可能会减缓经济增长，因此需要降低借贷成本。【原文：Minneapolis Federal Reserve Bank President Neel Kashkari on Wednesday said he's uncertain about the effect of President Donald Trump's tariffs on the U.S. economy, with the possibility that they could push up prices arguing for higher interest rates, and the chance that they could slow economic growth calling for reducing borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-should-stay-put-extended-period-amid-policy-uncertainty-kashkari-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLDBREWBVVMLDACNSHYELEUNAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis的玛莎拉蒂在重新发布计划之前增加了定制选项]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利跑车制造商玛莎拉蒂是 Stellantis 集团旗下业绩最差的品牌之一，该公司周三表示，正在加强利润丰厚的定制服务，同时制定更广泛的扭亏为盈计划。【原文：Italian sports car maker Maserati, one of the worst performing brands within the Stellantis group, said on Wednesday it was boosting lucrative customisation services while working on wider turnaround plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-maserati-boosts-customisation-options-ahead-relaunch-plans-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VEXNTCC55O5ZHFCMYBAUX2SVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达拉斯联储称第一季度美国石油和天然气活动有所增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储周三的一项调查显示，2025 年第一季度美国石油和天然气行业的活动略有增加，但企业的不确定性和悲观情绪也有所上升。【原文：Activity in the U.S. oil and gas sector increased slightly in the first quarter of 2025, but uncertainty and pessimism among companies also rose, a Dallas Fed survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-gas-activity-edged-up-first-quarter-dallas-fed-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKQXBYQROBN6XO2GBKQEZGD7YU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:28:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富达投资公司测试与美元挂钩的稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国资产管理公司富达投资公司（Fidelity Investments）正在探讨是否推出自己的稳定币，这是主流投资者希望从加密货币兴趣复苏中套现的最新迹象。【原文：U.S. asset manager Fidelity Investments is exploring whether to launch its own stablecoin, in the latest sign of mainstream investors looking to cash in on a revival of interest in cryptocurrencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fidelity-investments-tests-dollar-pegged-stablecoin-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYPQVK4YIVNBLIZUQTSKHIT4PA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 15:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 月中旬纳斯达克指数短线兴趣上涨 2.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克交易所在周二晚些时候发布的一份声明中说，3 月中旬纳斯达克指数的空头利率上升了约 2.2%。【原文：Short interest on the Nasdaq rose about 2.2% in mid-March, the exchange said in a statement released late on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-short-interest-up-22-mid-march-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWHOOM3A5BLBVPJEQSJZZZBZKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:59:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部取消反洗钱法中对美国公司的报告要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三公布了一项临时最终规则，取消了美国公司、公民和其他实体根据反洗钱法报告受益所有权信息的要求，将范围缩小到外国实体。【原文：The U.S. Treasury on Wednesday published an interim final rule that removes a requirement for U.S. companies, citizens and other entities to report beneficial ownership information under an anti-money laundering law, narrowing the scope to foreign entities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasury-lifts-reporting-requirement-us-firms-anti-money-laundering-law-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IB5TMVTTQRKMDBH7YEK7QYROXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:49:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称美国原油、汽油和馏分油库存下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周三称，上周美国原油库存、汽油库存和馏分油库存均有所下降。【原文：U.S. crude stocks, gasoline and distillate inventories fell last week, the Energy Information Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-crude-stocks-gasoline-distillate-inventories-fall-eia-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VP6B72JDCVO4BANC4PQPZWOHPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:36:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国副总理在与美国贸易代表会谈时提出对关税的 "严正关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家媒体新华社报道，中国国务院副总理何立峰周三与美国最高贸易主管贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）进行视频通话时，对美国加征关税和计划中的 "对等 "关税表示了 "严正关切"。【原文：China's Vice Premier He Lifeng expressed "solemn concerns" over U.S. tariffs and planned "reciprocal" duties in a video call with U.S. top trade chief Jamieson Greer on Wednesday, Chinese state media Xinhua news agency reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/chinas-vice-premier-raises-solemn-concerns-over-tariffs-talks-with-us-trade-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2IVLQXJZJ5P4XAHLIAK7OGNCN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，随着特朗普关税计划的展开，首席财务官的乐观情绪有所下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两家美联储银行和杜克大学的调查显示，由于关税风险和不确定性开始给企业高管的前景蒙上阴影，公司首席财务官的乐观情绪在第一季度有所下降，而唐纳德-特朗普总统的大选胜利曾给他们的前景带来鼓舞。【原文：Optimism among company chief financial officers dropped in the first quarter as tariff risks and uncertainty began to cloud an outlook among business executives that had been buoyed by President Donald Trump's election victory, according to a survey by two Federal Reserve banks and Duke University.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/cfo-optimism-dropped-trump-tariff-plans-unfolded-survey-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJRUUDILN5KMBFRZJFCU7DS3GE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:33:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易争端加剧，加拿大皇家银行投资者权衡增长计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，加拿大皇家银行（Royal Bank of Canada）将举行七年来的首次投资者日活动，股东们将重点关注经济增长，因为与主要美国市场的贸易紧张局势正在恶化。【原文：When Royal Bank of Canada convenes its first investor day in seven years on Thursday, shareholders will focus on growth, as trade tensions worsen with its key U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rbc-investors-weigh-growth-plans-us-trade-feud-worsens-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7K6BJUK3RNVVGFWRLSPZIPDWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:12:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CBO 估计，如果不就债务上限采取行动，美国最快将在 8 月面临违约风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[据无党派的国会预算办公室周三预测，除非国会采取行动提高国家债务上限，否则美国政府最快将在8月份面临36.6万亿美元债务中部分债务违约的风险。【原文：The U.S. government will risk defaulting on some of its $36.6 trillion in debt as soon as August unless Congress acts to raise the nation's debt ceiling, the non-partisan Congressional Budget Office forecast on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-risks-default-soon-august-without-action-debt-ceiling-cbo-estimates-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3C2F4XONWNNRDLLYR2FX247OUM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:11:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司投资 1 亿美元建厂生产芯片工业用清洁酒精]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil）周三表示，将斥资 1 亿美元升级其位于路易斯安那州巴吞鲁日（Baton Rouge）的化工厂，以生产一种高纯度的异丙醇，这种异丙醇被科技行业用于清洁和处理微芯片。【原文：Exxon Mobil said on Wednesday it will spend $100 million to upgrade its Baton Rouge, Louisiana, chemical plant to produce a highly pure form of isopropyl alcohol that is used in the tech industry to clean and process microchips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-investing-100-million-facility-produce-cleaning-alcohol-chip-industry-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTOJM23RXZML5INS7BRGL47VD4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司投资 1 亿美元建厂生产芯片工业用清洁酒精]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil）周三表示，将斥资 1 亿美元升级其位于路易斯安那州巴吞鲁日（Baton Rouge）的化工厂，以生产一种高纯度的异丙醇，这种异丙醇被科技行业用于清洁和处理微芯片。【原文：Exxon Mobil said on Wednesday it will spend $100 million to upgrade its Baton Rouge, Louisiana, chemical plant to produce a highly pure form of isopropyl alcohol that is used in the tech industry to clean and process microchips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-investing-100-million-facility-produce-cleaning-alcohol-chip-industry-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTOJM23RXZML5INS7BRGL47VD4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储详述问题学生贷款借贷可能迫在眉睫的上升趋势]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备委员会的研究人员周三表示，各种大流行病时期的学生贷款支持计划的结束很可能预示着借款人的信贷问题会增加，尽管要了解问题的全部程度还需要时间。【原文：The end of various pandemic-era student loan support programs likely portends a rise in credit issues for borrowers, although it will take time to understand the full extent of the problem, New York Federal Reserve researchers said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ny-fed-details-likely-looming-rise-troubled-student-loan-borrowing-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWRF5I7IZZMCLFP6IPPJT6RO74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 14:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ninestar 向施乐出售利盟的价格远低于之前宣布的价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于中国的九星公司计划将打印机和打印软件制造商利盟国际二期出售给施乐公司，交易价格估计高达 1.5 亿美元，仅为施乐公司 12 月份披露价格的一小部分。【原文：China-based Ninestar Corp plans to sell printer and printing software maker Lexmark International II to Xerox in a deal estimated at up to $150 million, a fraction of the price Xerox disclosed in December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/ninestar-sell-lexmark-xerox-much-lower-price-than-previously-announced-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HYNKZA6GBN7JK6OVQUQR4RBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德推出新的示范投资组合，进一步推动私人市场发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德（BlackRock）周三表示，该公司已推出首个混合私人资产和公开交易资产的示范投资组合，以扩大其在利润丰厚的私人市场领域的业务范围。【原文：BlackRock has launched its first model portfolio blending private and publicly traded assets, it said on Wednesday, as it looks to expand its footprint in the lucrative private market landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-launches-new-model-portfolio-further-private-market-push-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJAOG2FFAZOHXH5US6BAZYVDOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:51:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行上调 2025 年和 2026 年金价预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（BofA）上调了今明两年的黄金期价平均预期，同时强调美国贸易政策带来的不确定性将在短期内继续为金价提供支撑。【原文：Bank of America (BofA) has raised its gold period average forecasts for this year and next, while highlighting that uncertainty arising from U.S. trade policies will continue to lend support to prices in the near-term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/bofa-raises-gold-price-forecasts-2025-2026-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67AXCHGG65MYHKYKIDAHC67BXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马里预计 2025 年黄金产量将因巴里克公司重新开业而增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三看到的一份文件显示，假定矿业巨头巴里克黄金公司（Barrick Gold）在与政府长达数月的对峙之后恢复运营，马里预测 2025 年工业黄金产量将略有回升。【原文：Mali is forecasting a slight recovery in industrial gold output in 2025 on the assumption that mining giant Barrick Gold will resume operations after a months-long standoff with the government, a document seen by Reuters on Wednesday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/mali-expects-rise-gold-output-2025-reopened-barrick-operations-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTMQQ4GLJ5MZBC34U54F72A2Q4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:30:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国皇家财务报告署（OBR）称，美国对等关税可能使英国经济增长下降 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国政府的独立财政监督机构称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁将于下周对世界各国征收新的互惠关税税率，这可能会使英国的经济增长最多下降 1%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's threats to impose new reciprocal tariff rates next week on countries around the world could cut British economic growth by up to 1%, according to the government's independent fiscal watchdog.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/us-reciprocal-tariffs-could-cut-british-economic-growth-by-1-obr-says-2025-03-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAWWJ54UJRJLRAW3P2U34GB62A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:28:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>