<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:47:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:47:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Figma 获得 "中性 "评级，华尔街认为估值过高、竞争加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街券商周一开始给予 Figma 中性评级，因为他们权衡了这家设计软件制造商在激烈竞争中的高估值和人工智能驱动的增长潜力。【原文：Wall Street brokerages on Monday started their coverage of Figma with neutral ratings, as they weighed the design software maker's lofty valuation amid stiff competition against its potential for artificial intelligence-driven growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/figma-draws-neutral-ratings-wall-street-flags-lofty-valuation-rising-competition-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZS6GL4QXWRMNLE4Z5S2VMV7F6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[信心增强刺激交易反弹，华尔街增聘高级银行家]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几个月，华尔街银行招聘了数十名高级管理人员，因为在今年早些时候由于担心美国关税的影响而陷入低迷之后，经济景气的改善刺激了兼并和首次公开募股。【原文：Wall Street banks have hired dozens of senior executives in recent months, as improved economic sentiment has spurred mergers and IPOs after a lull earlier in the year due to concerns over the effect of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/wall-street-hires-more-senior-bankers-growing-confidence-spurs-deal-rebound-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKINH3KGQRINRNKYPVER7K3ZZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特木公司所有者 PDD 季度收入超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子商务公司点点客控股公司（PDD Holdings）周一公布的季度收入超出市场预期，表明尽管全球贸易存在不确定性，但国内需求反弹，国际业务增长也有所改善。【原文：E-commerce firm PDD Holdings beat market estimates for quarterly revenue on Monday, signaling a rebound in domestic demand and improved growth in its international business despite global trade uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/temu-owner-pdd-tops-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCMSUH722FN7XFFOXRWHI6UQRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国立法者和工会反对铁路自动化轨道安全检查计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铁路行业计划更多地依靠技术而不是人力来进行日常轨道安全检查，这一计划引起了劳工团体和立法者的反弹，他们担心自动检查会导致更多事故。【原文：A U.S. railroad industry plan to rely more heavily on technology instead of humans to conduct routine track safety inspections has drawn a backlash from labor groups and lawmakers who voiced worry that automated inspections will result in more accidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-lawmakers-unions-oppose-railroad-plan-automate-track-safety-inspections-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OK7PGHASI5PTVKGY5OLSHPURDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:34:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Royalty Pharma 拟以高达 9.5 亿美元的价格收购安进公司肺癌药物的特许权使用费权益]]></title><description><![CDATA[Royalty Pharma 公司周一表示，它已与 BeOne Medicines 公司签署协议，将以最高 9.5 亿美元的价格收购安进公司治疗小细胞肺癌药物的特许权使用权。【原文：Royalty Pharma said on Monday it has signed a deal with BeOne Medicines to acquire a royalty interest in Amgen's drug for small cell lung cancer for up to $950 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/royalty-pharma-buy-royalty-interest-amgens-lung-cancer-drug-up-950-million-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SG7EHOYBB5I5VOOI5XK2UTCYUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔带动美国股市反弹，9 月减产预期升温，美股期货下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）暗示下个月的央行会议上可能会降息，美国股指期货周一下滑，在前一交易日强劲上涨后暂停。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Monday, pausing after strong gains in the previous session, when Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell hinted that an interest-rate cut could be on the table at the central bank's meeting next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-dip-after-powell-led-rally-september-cut-expectations-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXG7RQXHSFJTRFLIXMGOBRQCEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰退休金信托基金拟出售 3.46 亿美元日产汽车股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份条款书显示，梅赛德斯-奔驰的养老信托基金将出售其持有的陷入困境的日本汽车制造商日产汽车价值约 3.46 亿美元的股份。【原文：Mercedes-Benz's Pension Trust will sell around $346 million worth of shares it holds in beleaguered Japanese automaker Nissan Motor , a term sheet showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-benz-pension-trust-sell-346-million-stake-nissan-motor-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC4SCVXFMZIGHIXQ2Z4TV2IOEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:10:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大银行在最新财报中回避最糟糕的关税情景]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计加拿大大型银行第三季度的贷款损失准备金将比上一季度有所下降，因为美国关税对其贷款组合造成的损害可能比人们担心的要小。【原文：Canada's big banks are expected to have lowered loan-loss provisions in the third quarter from the prior quarter as U.S. tariffs have likely hurt their loan portfolios less than feared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadian-banks-dodge-worst-case-tariff-scenario-latest-earnings-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DXEVQBIONLTDMOGNKHD4DUPVM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:06:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：宝洁出售中国产豪华 "邦宝 "牌纸尿裤，市场份额岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝洁公司（Procter & Gamble）正在零售商塔吉特（Target）销售中国制造的添加芦荟的 "bumbum "牌豪华纸尿裤，因为其最畅销的帮宝适（Pampers）和Luvs品牌被越来越多标榜类似功能的进口竞争对手所击败。【原文：Procter & Gamble is selling luxury aloe-infused “bumbum” brand diapers made in China at retailer Target as its top-selling Pampers and Luvs brands lose ground to a growing number of imported rivals touting similar features.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pg-selling-china-made-luxury-bumbum-brand-diapers-market-share-falters-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VA6IUHHFDFPO7OKUSMV4T3RJOM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰消费者监督机构指控 Netflix 擅自提高收费标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰消费者监督机构竞争和消费者保护办公室（UOKiK）周一表示，该机构指控 Netflix 在未征得用户明确同意的情况下提高订阅费用。【原文：Poland's consumer watchdog the Office of Competition and Consumer Protection (UOKiK) has accused Netflix of raising subscription fees without securing explicit user consent, the regulator said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/polish-consumer-watchdog-accuses-netflix-unauthorised-fee-hikes-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOIF36NK75P5PJNDS3ZH5RWVAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[紧张的瑞士准备好接受特朗普的关税减免甜言蜜语]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟知内情的人士表示，瑞士希望尽快敲定一项新的商业提议，以减轻华盛顿的关税负担，其中可能包括增加国防开支和扩大美国能源利益的准入。【原文：Switzerland soon hopes to finalise a new business offer for Washington to ease its tariff burden, which will likely include more defence spending and greater access for U.S. energy interests, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/nervous-swiss-ready-trump-sweetened-offer-tariff-pain-relief-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2O2BK6XTHRP6VH3JVY3HI7NFCI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 09:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷取消 Cellforce 部门的电池生产计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商保时捷公司（Porsche AG）取消了其高性能电池部门 Cellforce 的生产计划，称由于电动汽车需求放缓以及中国和美国的情况发生变化，该公司将专注于研发。【原文：German carmaker Porsche AG scrapped production plans at its high-performance battery unit Cellforce, saying it would focus on development because of slow demand for electric vehicles and changed conditions in China and the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-scraps-battery-production-plans-cellforce-unit-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNUXACHC2RP3FF6NB6ZULE77BQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球负债最多的开发商恒大从违约到退市]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国恒大集团周一从香港证券交易所退市，这是近年来按市值和交易量计算的最大退市事件之一。【原文：China Evergrande Group was delisted from the Hong Kong stock exchange on Monday, in one of the largest removals by market value and volume in recent years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/default-delisting-evergrande-worlds-most-indebted-developer-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2KEXWII7ZLANO72JIZXID5HFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:48:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对 140 多万辆本田汽车发动机故障进行调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局正在对在美国销售的 140 多万辆本田汽车展开调查，因为人们担心本田汽车发动机连杆轴承故障可能导致发动机完全失效。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration is opening a probe into more than 1.4 million Honda vehicles sold in the United States over concerns that connecting rod bearing failures in their engines could lead to complete engine failure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-probes-into-more-than-14-million-honda-vehicles-over-engine-failure-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEWSGBQO2VLELDNUMJMJ5FQIY4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[证券交易所敦促监管机构打击 "代币化股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个代表全球最大证券交易所的组织正在敦促证券监管机构取缔所谓的代币化股票，认为基于区块链的代币给投资者带来了新的风险，并有可能破坏市场诚信。【原文：A group representing the world's biggest stock exchanges is urging securities regulators to clamp down on so-called tokenised stocks, arguing that the blockchain-based tokens create new risks for investors and risk damaging market integrity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/stock-exchanges-urge-regulators-crack-down-tokenised-stocks-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6ZVJE2NYVOZNBYKX5AY5Q53K4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国 7 月出口超预期，但受关税影响增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国商务部周一表示，泰国7月份的出口增长放缓，但好于预期，因为在美国加征关税之前出货量加速增长。【原文：Thailand's export growth slowed in July but beat forecasts as shipments accelerated ahead of U.S. tariffs, but growth is set to slow over the rest of the year after those tariffs took effect, the commerce ministry said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thai-exports-beat-forecast-july-growth-slow-due-tariffs-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIDSLSR66NP2BMEVC7FCJ4I534</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度将在通胀改革中直接利用亚马逊和 Flipkart 的数据，并推出服务指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度统计部负责人表示，印度将开始直接从亚马逊和沃尔玛旗下的 Flipkart 等电商巨头处获取价格数据，以全面调整其基准通胀率指标，旨在捕捉不断变化的消费习惯，并消除人们对当前数据已经过时的担忧。【原文：India will start sourcing price data directly from e-commerce giants including Amazon and Walmart-owned Flipkart to overhaul its benchmark inflation gauge, aiming to capture shifting consumption habits and address concerns that current data is outdated, the head of the statistics ministry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-tap-amazon-flipkart-data-directly-inflation-revamp-roll-out-services-index-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SX5R54RKHZMORN35Y5W4SFSGGA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰富瑞将标准普尔 500 指数年度目标上调至 6600 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰富瑞（Jefferies）在周日的一份报告中称，该公司将上证 500 指数的年底目标上调至 6,600 点，强调强劲的企业盈利是可能缓解对美国经济健康状况担忧的一个关键因素。【原文：Jefferies lifted its year-end target for the S&amp;P 500 index to 6,600, highlighting robust corporate earnings as a key factor likely to ease concerns about the health of the U.S. economy, it said in a note on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jefferies-lifts-sp-500-annual-target-6600-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWDKXBAXQBKBXGZH4ABIS3E5VY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰网上银行 Bunq 因洗钱控制不力被罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰中央银行 DNB 周一表示，荷兰在线银行 Bunq 因洗钱控制失误被罚款 260 万欧元（304 万美元）。【原文：Dutch online bank Bunq has received a fine of 2.6 million euros ($3.04 million) for failures in its money laundering controls, Dutch central bank DNB said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/dutch-online-bank-bunq-fined-sloppy-money-laundering-controls-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAYH5GC7UBPUVCXPEU54HY6PFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:16:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper 以超过 180 亿美元的价格收购荷兰咖啡公司 JDE Peet's]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper 周一表示，将以 157 亿欧元（183.8 亿美元）的价格收购荷兰咖啡公司 JDE Peet's。【原文：Keurig Dr Pepper on Monday said it will buy Dutch coffee company JDE Peet's for 15.7 billion euros ($18.38 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/keurig-dr-pepper-buys-dutch-coffee-company-jde-peets-over-18-billion-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSACHF7MKNIADP76V662AOTVE4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FACTBOX 相互竞争的电池技术塑造了电动汽车行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界各地的初创企业都在竞相开发使用钠和硫等材料或其他创新化学物质的新型电池技术，旨在降低成本，减少电动汽车（EV）供应对某些关键矿物的依赖。【原文：Startups worldwide are racing to develop new battery technologies using materials like sodium and sulfur or other innovative chemistries, aiming to cut costs and reduce reliance on some critical minerals to supply electric vehicles (EVs).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/factbox-competing-battery-technologies-shape-ev-industry-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLREDNFKGZJAHJN426NXDLKGIY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：电池初创企业莱腾尚未说服汽车制造商重振 Northvolt]]></title><description><![CDATA[硅谷初创公司Lyten需要说服汽车制造商相信它能在瑞典破产的电动汽车电池制造商Northvolt失败的地方取得成功--创造一个欧洲冠军，以减少该地区对中国的依赖。【原文：Silicon Valley startup Lyten will need to convince carmakers it can succeed where bankrupt Swedish EV battery maker Northvolt failed - creating a European champion to reduce the region's reliance on China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/battery-startup-lyten-yet-convince-carmakers-over-northvolt-revival-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4XVOHK3TNKOLMGECXTDXSO3T4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府阻止美国风电项目，Orsted 现金计划面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[风电场开发商 Orsted 筹集急需资金的计划面临风险，因为美国下令停止建设一个即将完工的项目，分析师称，该丹麦集团的股价周一可能会承压。【原文：Wind farm developer Orsted's plan to raise much-needed capital is at risk following a U.S. order to halt construction of a near-complete project, and the Danish group's share price could come under pressure on Monday, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/orsted-cash-plan-risk-trump-government-blocks-us-wind-project-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISX6WS23JVKTFGR3V2DS47FVQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：为什么 "对反弹和降息至关重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E34KWXE3X5LXLNEDV4ELFRPEYU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 04:33:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行、法国巴黎银行关注美联储 9 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）和法国巴黎银行（BNP Paribas）周五分别发表报告称，美国联邦储备委员会主席鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）发表讲话，释放出转向宽松政策的信号后，这两家券商预计美国联邦储备委员会将在9月份降息。【原文：Barclays and BNP Paribas expect the U.S. Federal Reserve to cut interest rates in September, after Chair Jerome Powell signaled a shift toward an easing bias in a speech at Jackson Hole, the brokerages said in separate notes on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/barclays-bnp-eye-september-fed-rate-cut-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HT7KS3RKSJMKTKP54XDIKGSYL4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 04:08:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球央行行长担心陷入美联储风暴]]></title><description><![CDATA[周末聚集在美国山区度假胜地的全球央行行长们开始担心，围绕美联储的政治风暴可能也会吞噬他们。【原文：Global central bankers gathered at a U.S. mountain resort over the weekend are starting to fear that the political storm surrounding the Federal Reserve may engulf them too.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/worlds-central-bankers-fear-being-caught-feds-storm-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6S34XKY6ZNO5DCAEO3QVRGGSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 04:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华侨银行启动 10 亿美元数字美国商业票据计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡第二大银行华侨银行（Oversea-Chinese Banking Corp）周一表示，该行已制定了一项价值 10 亿美元的数字美国商业票据计划，以增强其美元融资能力。【原文：Singapore's second-largest bank Oversea-Chinese Banking Corp said on Monday it has established a $1 billion digital U.S. commercial paper programme, bolstering its dollar funding capabilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ocbc-kicks-off-1-billion-digital-us-commercial-paper-programme-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2XGZNF2FJMCLEFEFOM5ZNTQME</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:44:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰袭击俄罗斯能源基地后油价攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰加强了对俄罗斯的攻击，加剧了人们对俄罗斯石油供应可能中断的担忧，而美国降息的预期则提振了全球经济增长和燃料需求的前景。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Monday after Ukraine stepped up attacks on Russia, fanning concerns Russian oil supply could be disrupted, while expectations of a cut in U.S. interest rates buoyed the outlook for global growth and fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-climb-after-ukraine-attacks-hit-russian-energy-sites-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAPW366DANNXLFS7WCEULASICY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:28:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州工厂让中国铜业公司在关税战中占得先机]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国铜扁线制造商 Wellascent 去年初决定在得克萨斯州建厂，是为了规避地缘政治风险。现在，随着美国征收进口关税促进了对其本地生产产品的需求，这项投资正在得到回报。【原文：Chinese copper flat wire manufacturer Wellascent's decision early last year to build a factory in Texas was a hedge against geopolitical risks. Now the investment is paying off as U.S. import tariffs boost demand for its locally produced goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/texas-factory-gives-chinese-copper-firm-an-edge-tariff-war-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2ZILYSLUBNFNO2FAW253IQDGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞穗和 MUFG 加入日本银行争夺海外基金经理交易的行列]]></title><description><![CDATA[他们告诉路透社，日本瑞穗银行和 MUFG 正在瞄准收购海外基金管理公司或与之合作，与其他日本金融公司一道，争取在全球投资市场上占有更大份额。【原文：Japanese banks Mizuho and MUFG are targeting buying or partnering with overseas money managers, they told Reuters, joining other Japanese financial companies aiming for a larger share of the global investing market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mizuho-mufg-join-race-by-japans-banks-money-manager-deals-overseas-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQJRCR2NHZIXDEMMBU62427LOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>