<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:11:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:11:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic任命微软资深高管伊琳娜·戈斯为印度董事总经理]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Anthropic周五宣布，任命前微软高管伊琳娜·戈斯（Irina Ghose）担任印度区董事总经理。【原文：Artificial intelligence startup Anthropic has appointed former Microsoft executive Irina Ghose as its managing director for India, the company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/anthropic-appoints-microsoft-veteran-irina-ghose-india-md-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCAUUKRYDNJBXCKIJ2FFH2JQAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:55:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚财长支持澳联储行长与美联储主席鲍威尔的团结姿态]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚财政部长周五公开支持该国央行行长与备受争议的美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔保持团结，称此举"恰当"。【原文：Australia's Treasurer on Friday threw his support behind the head of the country's central bank for standing in solidarity with embattled Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, saying the decision was "appropriate".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/australian-treasurer-backs-rba-chiefs-show-solidarity-with-feds-powell-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RVB3LP5OVZIN3I3HOACQA4APLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度印孚瑟斯公司上调2026财年业绩预期后，受人工智能发展势头推动股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[印孚瑟斯周五股价一度上涨4%，此前该公司意外上调了2026财年营收预期。分析师表示，该公司凭借更强劲的人工智能合作伙伴关系和更深入的客户互动，已做好充分准备赢得市场份额。【原文：Infosys rose as much as 4% on Friday after unexpectedly raising its fiscal 2026 revenue forecast, as analysts said it's well-positioned to win market share through stronger AI partnerships and deeper client engagement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-infosys-rises-ai-momentum-after-lifting-fy26-outlook-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QO5UZETXWROLFEKTNJLXSNYBUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司与前灵动航空系统公司员工达成初步劳资协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表约1600名机身供应商Spirit AeroSystems白领员工的工会周四表示，已与波音公司就新集体谈判协议达成初步协议。【原文：A union representing about 1,600 white-collar workers at fuselage supplier Spirit AeroSystems said on Thursday that it has reached a tentative agreement with Boeing on a new collective bargaining contract.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeing-secures-tentative-labor-deal-with-former-spirit-aerosystems-workers-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGL4O7ZAMNICXAUBYWV66HXX6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾在关税协议下力争成为美国战略性人工智能合作伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾副总理郑丽君周五表示，台湾正致力于成为美国在人工智能领域的紧密战略伙伴，双方达成协议将降低关税并促进台湾对美投资。【原文：Taiwan aims to become a close strategic artificial intelligence partner with the United States thanks to a deal to reduce tariffs and boost Taiwanese investment in the country, Taiwan Vice Premier Cheng Li-chiun said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-aims-be-strategic-ai-partner-with-us-under-tariff-deal-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5I3CK54P6BMDHPNZZHSAN7AXCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:44:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称日本央行内部部分人士认为加息时机可能早于市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉日本央行决策思路的消息人士称，部分政策制定者认为存在提前于市场预期加息的可能性，4月加息或成现实选项。因日元持续贬值可能加剧本已扩大的通胀压力。【原文：Some Bank of Japan policymakers see scope to raise interest rates sooner than markets expect with April a distinct possibility, as a sliding yen risks adding to already broadening inflationary pressure, four sources familiar with its thinking said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/some-boj-see-scope-raise-rates-sooner-than-markets-expect-sources-say-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XX4BI7LP2NJFTGSAXIL2ZN423U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:41:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价持平，因美国对伊朗发动袭击的可能性减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五油价持平，布伦特原油和美国西德克萨斯中质油较前一交易日收盘价仅波动几美分，因美国对伊朗发动军事打击的可能性有所降低。【原文：Oil prices were flat on Friday with both Brent and U.S. West Texas Intermediate moving only a few cents from their closing prices after the likelihood of a U.S. strike on Iran receded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-flat-chances-us-strike-iran-recedes-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46YD6CGM7BP5RAJI7AHXHQ5WN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:35:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市因人工智能乐观情绪逼近历史高点，美元因美联储降息预期减弱走强]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周五上涨，人工智能热潮再度升温；美元则维持在六周高位附近，因美国经济数据向好令交易员削减降息押注。【原文：Asian stocks advanced on Friday as the artificial intelligence boom regained momentum, while the dollar held near a six-week high after upbeat U.S. economic data left traders trimming bets on rate cuts there.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S32OVY4C45I4VDBMJECF7X56ZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:15:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元有望实现连续第三周上涨，强劲数据料将抑制美联储降息预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五有望实现连续第三周上涨，此前美国经济数据向好，降低了市场对美联储近期降息的预期。【原文：The dollar was poised for a third weekly gain on Friday after positive U.S. economic data lowered expectations for rate cuts by the Federal Reserve anytime soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-poised-third-weekly-gain-buoyant-data-seen-keeping-fed-cuts-bay-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAI3L5LNTFIVNNGGNJW64I3JUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，各州州长将于周五前往白宫，揭幕旨在抑制电价的标牌。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，美国多个数据中心建设快速扩张的州长将于周五访问白宫，与特朗普政府签署一项旨在遏制电力成本上涨的协议。【原文：Governors from U.S. states seeing a rapid expansion in data center construction will visit the White House on Friday to sign an agreement with the Trump administration intended to curb rising electricity costs, said two sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/governors-head-white-house-friday-unveil-sign-curb-power-prices-sources-say-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5EZYH4KMJNYHDPHFSJDBLEETU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称25%半导体关税是"第一阶段"行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周三宣布对部分高端半导体征收25%的国家安全关税，白宫官员周四表示，这是保护该行业的"第一阶段"行动，后续可能根据与其他国家及企业的谈判进展发布更多公告。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department's 25% national security tariff on certain high-end semiconductors announced on Wednesday is a "phase one" action to protect the sector and could be followed by other announcements pending negotiations with other countries and companies, a White House official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-says-25-semiconductor-tariffs-phase-one-action-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCJLDYXKVVPOPGZNURWMGDHRUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一量子支持巴拿马允许关闭铜矿进行库存加工的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大矿业公司第一量子矿业周四对巴拿马总统何塞·劳尔·穆利诺本月早些时候宣布的计划表示欢迎。该计划允许该公司对其关闭的科布雷巴拿马铜矿进行堆存矿石的移除和加工。【原文：Canadian miner First Quantum Minerals on Thursday welcomed Panama President Jose Raul Mulino's plan, announced early this month, to allow the removal and processing of stockpiled ore at its shuttered Cobre Panama copper mine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/first-quantum-backs-panamas-plan-allow-stockpile-processing-shut-copper-mine-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SV6SGKGIFJMXHIDVTWJZUTZLSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得州住宅开发商获SEC批准后将推出加密货币奖励计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州私营住宅建筑商Megatel Homes LLC周四宣布，将开始发行加密货币支付及奖励代币。【原文：Privately held Texas homebuilder Megatel Homes LLC said on Thursday it will start issuing a crypto payments and ​rewards token.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/texas-homebuilder-launch-crypto-rewards-after-sec-green-light-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4A6INYHNVOUFAXRS6EYIS55XM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，人工智能超大规模企业将推动2026年美国公司债券供应量上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师预测，2026年美国公司债券发行量预计将大幅增长，部分原因在于人工智能超大规模企业的扩建需求。【原文：U.S. corporate bond issuance is expected to increase ​substantially in 2026, driven in part by AI hyperscaler companies' build-out needs, analysts forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ai-hyperscalers-will-drive-higher-us-corporate-bond-supply-2026-analysts-say-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MGCKXSI4BKVVAHXORBNUXVA7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:53:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛国际业务主管凯瑟琳·麦克莱即将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛周四宣布，国际业务总裁兼首席执行官凯瑟琳·麦克莱将在任职约两年后于1月31日离职。【原文：Walmart on Thursday said Kathryn McLay, president and CEO of Walmart International, will leave the company on January 31 after about two years in the role.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/walmarts-international-chief-kathryn-mclay-step-down-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTOLZGJJC5IL5PAEUERP62YIOI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:51:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[散户投资者将创纪录资金涌入白银市场，形成拥挤交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Vanda Research周四发布的报告显示，散户投资者正以惊人速度抢购白银，使其成为市场上最拥挤的大宗商品交易。【原文：Individual investors have been snapping up silver at such a pace it has turned into the most crowded commodity trade in the market, according ​to a report published on Thursday by Vanda Research.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/retail-investors-steer-record-amount-cash-into-silver-creating-crowded-trade-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKNH3BUHZ5K6FHHQDSXTYJL4KM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：芯片股、银行股上涨；油价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行稳健的财报和科技股的反弹推动周四美股走高，特朗普总统对伊朗紧张局势态度的缓和也提振了全球风险偏好，但同时重创了油价。【原文：Solid U.S. bank earnings and a rebound in tech lifted U.S. stocks on Thursday, with global risk appetite also fueled by - and oil prices clobbered by - a more moderate tone from U.S. President Donald Trump on tensions with Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQZJOHYFHJNQDNAPVQHEPCQPUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望：政策噪音渐强，投资者押注美国企业盈利强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者将寄望于强劲的企业财报季，以维持美国股市的涨势，同时消化新年伊始涌现的一系列国内政策提案和加剧的地缘政治紧张局势。【原文：Investors will be counting on a strong corporate earnings season to keep the rally in U.S. stocks intact ​as they digest a wave of domestic policy proposals and heightened geopolitical tensions to start the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-bank-us-earnings-strength-policy-noise-grows-louder-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RC3HGNMQEFLLLH2MI5Q5IB722I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:38:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米·戴蒙表示，他希望至少再任职五年。]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米·戴蒙周四在美国商会主办的活动中表示，他希望至少再任职五年。【原文：JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon wants to stay at his job "at least" five more years, he told an event hosted by the U.S. Chamber of Commerce on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-says-he-wants-stay-job-least-5-more-years-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUQA7LWCOBPL5GJICF4DCIES3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[11月外国持有美国国债规模创历史新高，但中国减持]]></title><description><![CDATA[外国持有的美国国债在11月创下历史新高，此前连续两个月下跌后出现回升，因美国联邦政府结束史上最长的政府停摆后，市场情绪有所改善。【原文：Foreign holdings of U.S. Treasuries hit record ​highs in November, rising after two straight months of declines as market sentiment improved ‌after the U.S. federal government ended the longest-ever shutdown in history.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/foreign-holdings-us-treasuries-hit-all-time-high-november-data-shows-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54QCU7C25BKGRK4UMEAO4CS6EA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:12:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州即将批准威瑞森收购边疆公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[加州公共事业委员会将于周四批准威瑞森通信公司以200亿美元收购光纤互联网供应商边疆通信公司的交易，此前这家美国电信公司已同意满足一系列条件，委员会成员表示。【原文：The California Public Utilities Commission is set on Thursday to approve Verizon Communications's $20 billion deal to acquire fiber-optic internet providers Frontier Communications after a series of conditions agreed to by the U.S. telecom company, board members said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/california-set-approve-verizon-acquisition-frontier-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4JNXCBEIBOM5PVRDQK3IYV2WQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：国际货币基金组织总裁乔治耶娃称最新增长预测将显示经济对全球贸易冲击的韧性]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔利娜·格奥尔基耶娃周四向路透社表示，该组织下周将发布的最新经济预测将显示全球经济持续展现出对贸易冲击的韧性，并保持"相当强劲"的增长态势。【原文：The International Monetary Fund's latest economic forecasts due next week will show ​the global economy's continued resilience to ‌trade shocks and "fairly strong" growth, IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/imfs-georgieva-says-latest-growth-forecasts-show-resilience-global-trade-shocks-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2VVVD3QBBISJGLZQCOJESAHOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:43:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：国际货币基金组织总裁乔治耶娃称央行独立性至关重要，支持鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[她告诉路透社，有充分证据表明，中央银行的独立性符合企业和家庭的利益。【原文：She told Reuters there was ample evidence that central bank independence worked in the interest of businesses and households.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/imfs-georgieva-says-central-bank-independence-critical-backs-powell-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVOCUUZAIZIORLL7VBXZO5TOOI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《商报》报道，黑石集团可能斥资高达46.5亿美元在德国投资建设数据中心。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《商报》周四援引消息人士报道，黑石集团可能斥资高达40亿欧元（约合46.5亿美元）在德国利佩塔尔建设数据中心。【原文：Blackstone could invest up to 4 billion euros ($4.65 billion) for a data center in Lippetal, Germany, Handelsblatt reported on Thursday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackstone-invest-465-billion-data-center-germany-handelsblatt-reports-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKXZ23GDKJM3DNVNL3GWMPUD6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长卢特尼克表示，台湾芯片交易总价值达5000亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德·卢特尼克周四向CNBC透露，根据美国与台湾地区新签署的贸易协议条款，台湾企业将投资2500亿美元，台湾地区政府还将额外投资2500亿美元，用于在美国扩大半导体制造产能。【原文：Under the terms of a new U.S. trade deal with Taiwan, companies from Taiwan will invest $250 billion and the island's government will invest another $250 billion to expand semiconductor manufacturing in the United States, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick told CNBC on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-chip-deal-is-worth-total-500-billion-us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-says-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLTIRWUGTZOLXJJFMJOVYQMYUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部称美台达成以半导体为核心的贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国与台湾地区达成一项贸易协议，美国商务部周四表示，该协议将推动"美国半导体产业大规模回流"。【原文：The U.S. and Taiwan have a reached a trade deal that the U.S. Commerce Department said on Thursday would drive a "massive reshoring of America’s semiconductor sector."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-taiwan-reach-trade-deal-focused-semiconductors-commerce-department-says-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R542UIFK5NPA7AM7HGFMWWOSI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:24:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储达利：政策处于良好状态，调整应审慎行事]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽·戴利周四表示，尽管存在不确定性，且美联储的通胀和就业双重使命仍面临持续风险，但即将公布的美国经济数据前景可期。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve President Mary Daly said on Thursday ​that incoming U.S. economic data looks promising despite uncertainties and ‌continued risks to both the Fed's inflation and employment mandates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-policy-good-place-calibration-should-be-deliberate-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PG7ESVUGKBOGJGJTBI7PF267LQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出版商寻求加入针对谷歌的诉讼，指控其在人工智能训练中存在不当行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[出版商阿歇特图书集团和康恩杰集团周四向加州联邦法院申请介入针对谷歌的拟议集体诉讼，该诉讼指控谷歌滥用受版权保护的材料来训练其人工智能系统。【原文：Publishers Hachette Book Group and Cengage Group asked a California federal court on Thursday for permission to intervene in a proposed class action lawsuit against Google over the alleged misuse of copyrighted material used to train its artificial intelligence systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/publishers-seek-join-lawsuit-against-google-over-ai-training-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6Z6J55HU7FNGFPGGPMZCX2UKCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:32:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约州起诉前首席执行官内幕交易案，涉新冠疫苗污染事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长莱蒂西亚·詹姆斯周四指控Emergent BioSolutions公司前首席执行官涉嫌内幕交易，称其在知晓巴尔的摩工厂存在污染问题的情况下出售了这家合同制药公司的股票，而该工厂正是生产新冠疫苗的场所。【原文：A former chief executive of Emergent BioSolutions was charged on Thursday with insider trading by New York Attorney General Letitia James for allegedly selling the contract drug manufacturer's stock while knowing about contamination problems at a Baltimore plant that made COVID-19 vaccines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/ex-ceo-sued-by-new-york-insider-trading-tied-covid-19-vaccine-contamination-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AACI6N5TKFIEZG6LB4JBA5FBCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西因安全担忧关闭Sigma Lithium废料堆场]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社获得的文件显示，巴西劳工部已关闭西格玛锂业位于米纳斯吉拉斯州旗舰矿区的三处废料堆，称其对工人和当地社区构成"严重且迫在眉睫"的风险。【原文：Brazil's Labor Ministry has shut down three waste piles at Sigma Lithium's flagship mine in the state of Minas Gerais, citing a "grave and imminent" risk to workers and the local community, according to documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-shuts-down-sigma-lithium-waste-piles-over-safety-concerns-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQZYPGZK5JKGNJWEBLCGBKTUPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:06:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>