<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:06:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:06:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府警告：与伊朗有关的黑客可能会攻击美国公司和关键基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国政府官员周一发布的一份公告称，受伊朗庇护的黑客可能会将目标对准美国公司和关键基础设施运营商，特别是与以色列研究和国防公司有控股或合作关系的国防组织。【原文：Iranian-affilited hackers may target U.S. companies and critical infrastructure operators, particularly defense organizations with holdings or relationships with Israeli research and defense firms, according to an advisory from U.S. government officials Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/iran-linked-hackers-may-target-us-firms-critical-infrastructure-us-government-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHVPQKCDKZNG3ATRDZDVG4YNF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:39:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 数据显示，4 月份美国原油产量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署发布的《石油供应月报》系列数据显示，4 月份美国原油产量达到创纪录的 1,347 万桶/日，高于 3 月份的 1,345 万桶/日。【原文：U.S. crude oil production hit a record 13.47 million barrels-per-day in April, up from 13.45 million bpd in March, according to data released by the Energy Information Administration as part of its Petroleum Supply Monthly series.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-oil-output-hit-record-april-eia-data-shows-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFWOQUPKUFJXXHJAZULCZU2Q6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:30:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院法案削减清洁能源引起劳工和商界反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院在其版本的唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统税收和支出法案中提出的削减清洁能源补贴的建议自上周末公布以来，招致了商界和劳工团体的猛烈抨击，一些人认为此举将提高电价并扼杀就业机会。【原文：The U.S. Senate’s proposed cuts to clean energy subsidies in its version of President Donald Trump's tax and spending bill have drawn searing criticism from business and labor groups since they were unveiled over the weekend, with some arguing the moves will raise power prices and kill jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-senate-bills-clean-energy-cuts-draw-backlash-labor-business-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTW52QIYXJICTCP3576UP6L36Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:18:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood 推出代币，允许欧盟用户交易美股]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 周一表示，它已推出代币，允许欧盟客户交易 200 多只美国股票和交易所交易基金，包括英伟达、苹果和微软。【原文：Robinhood said on Monday it has launched tokens that will allow its customers in the European Union to trade more than 200 U.S. stocks and exchange-traded funds, including Nvidia , Apple and Microsoft .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/robinhood-launches-tokens-allowing-eu-users-trade-us-stocks-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JITJBP5T4FOVFJNQE4UIWEAUFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示美国将立即重启与加拿大的贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周一表示，在加拿大取消针对美国科技公司的数字服务税后，美国将立即重启与加拿大的贸易谈判。【原文：The United States will restart trade negotiations with Canada immediately after Canada scrapped its digital services tax targeting U.S. technology firms, White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-restart-trade-negotiations-with-canada-immediately-white-house-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RS6GYAONZFNNXEXCFGKJ7JHDMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:49:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长贝森特警告各国在 7 月 9 日最后期限后将面临更高的关税税率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一警告说，即使各国本着诚意进行谈判，它们仍有可能在7月9日面临大幅提高关税的局面，并补充说，任何可能的延期都将取决于唐纳德-特朗普总统。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said warned on Monday that countries could still face sharply higher tariffs on July 9 even if they are negotiating in good faith, adding that any potential extensions will be up to President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasurys-bessent-warns-countries-face-higher-tariff-rates-after-july-9-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXV2ZY5CBROHFOCPKBYG6XGSEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约市少年在 "地铁冲浪 "时遇害，其母可起诉 Meta、TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州法官裁定，Meta Platforms 和 TikTok 的所有者 ByteDance 必须面对曼哈顿一名 15 岁男孩的母亲提起的过失致死诉讼，这名男孩是在行驶的列车上 "地铁冲浪 "时死亡的。【原文：Meta Platforms and TikTok owner ByteDance must face a wrongful death lawsuit by the mother of a 15-year-old Manhattan boy who died while "subway surfing" on a moving train, a New York state judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/meta-tiktok-can-be-sued-by-mother-nyc-teen-killed-while-subway-surfing-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNIQ6X3MLBNVJEHNDVZW6Y4COE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉将波音公司的前景展望调整为稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构惠誉（Fitch）周一将飞机制造商波音公司的评级展望从 "负面 "调整为 "稳定"，理由是其财务灵活性和生产状况有所改善。【原文：Global ratings agency Fitch on Monday revised its outlook on planemaker Boeing to 'stable' from 'negative', citing improved financial flexibility and production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-revises-boeing-outlook-stable-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMI3K6WOYVNQNKUOVOEJUW5TLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟技术主管称，欧洲推动的人工智能千兆工厂吸引了 76 项投标]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟技术主管周一表示，已有76家公司竞标开发欧洲人工智能千亿国际娱乐，这对该集团为在这一关键技术上赶超美国和中国而做出的努力来说，是一个超出预期的回应。【原文：Seventy-six companies have bid to develop Europe's artificial intelligence gigafactories, the EU's tech chief said on Monday, hailing a bigger than expected response to the bloc's push to catch up with the U.S. and China in this key technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/europes-ai-gigafactory-push-attracts-76-bids-eu-tech-chief-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2GTEOV525PIZDM7ZZBQUOLD5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院在特朗普法案中保留部分税收抵免，可再生能源股涨跌不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国参议院推进总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全面税收和支出法案之后，美国可再生能源公司的股票在周一早盘交易中表现不一。【原文：Shares of U.S. renewable energy firms saw a mixed performance in early Monday trading after the U.S. Senate advanced President Donald Trump's sweeping tax-and-spending bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/renewable-energy-shares-mixed-us-senate-preserves-some-tax-credits-trump-bill-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWAMR6Z4VNO6FJCNUSV6IU3QRQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回美国航空公司对禁止捷蓝航空联盟裁决的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一驳回了美国航空公司要求推翻一项司法判决的请求，该判决认定该公司与捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）现已破裂的美国东北部地区合作关系违反了联邦反垄断法。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court rejected on Monday a request by American Airlines to overturn a judicial decision that found that the company's now-scrapped U.S. Northeast partnership with JetBlue Airways violated federal antitrust law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-rejects-american-airlines-appeal-ruling-barring-jetblue-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCJ4EVCF5BOWNFTMVSEXLCVFDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:56:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回埃克森公司对 1425 万美元空气污染罚款的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一驳回了埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil Corp）的诉讼请求，该公司要求推翻法官在德克萨斯州贝敦（Baytown）原油精炼厂空气污染的长期诉讼中判处的 1425 万美元民事罚款。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court turned away on Monday Exxon Mobil Corp's bid to overturn a $14.25 million civil penalty that a judge imposed in a long-running lawsuit over air pollution at its Baytown, Texas, crude oil refinery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-rejects-exxons-appeal-1425-million-air-pollution-penalty-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAGTWWMTCZPLLHQL6GIBOFZKMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:56:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将复审考克斯通信公司价值数十亿美元的版权案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一同意就考克斯通信公司 [RIC:RIC:COXC.UL] 与一些音乐唱片公司之间的版权纠纷做出裁决，此前的司法判决驳回了陪审团针对考克斯用户涉嫌盗版音乐而对这家互联网服务提供商做出的价值 10 亿美元的判决。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court agreed on Monday to decide a copyright dispute between Cox Communications [RIC:RIC:COXC.UL] and a group of music labels following a judicial decision that threw out a $1 billion jury verdict against the internet service provider over alleged piracy of music by Cox customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-review-billion-dollar-cox-communications-copyright-case-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAXJ5BMHSRJ7DK6BJ5MJZPDE3M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子从亚马逊招聘人工智能专家]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国技术公司西门子周一表示，已聘请亚马逊高管瓦西-菲洛明（Vasi Philomin）担任新的数据和人工智能主管一职。【原文：Siemens has recruited Amazon executive Vasi Philomin to its new position of head of data and artificial intelligence, the German technology company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/siemens-recruits-artificial-intelligence-expert-amazon-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSPB5QSUGNMUHDNEGTIIJRAPAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治紧张局势推高石油前景，但需求担忧依然存在：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周一的一项民意调查显示，中东紧张局势爆发后，分析师小幅上调了油价预期，但欧佩克+供应增加和需求前景缓和继续对原油构成压力。【原文：Analysts have marginally lifted their oil price forecasts after the flare-up of tensions in the Middle East, but rising OPEC+ supply and a tempered demand outlook continue to weigh on crude, a Reuters poll showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/geopolitical-tensions-nudge-oil-outlook-higher-demand-concerns-persist-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E74ANWXFUBNTLLATCQNHAXK4YM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年上半年或 2025 年的市场：美元下行，枪支上行]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普做出激进的竞选承诺后，投资者知道，随着他重返领导世界最大经济体的岗位，今年的市场将变得崎岖不平。但迄今为止，几乎没有人预测到结果，尤其是美元的大幅下跌。【原文：After U.S. President Donald Trump's radical campaign pledges, investors knew markets would get bumpy this year as he returned to lead the world's biggest economy. But almost nobody predicted the outcome so far, especially the dollar's dramatic fall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-h1-analysis-pix-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOQBRHJL3FOZJAFUWMN2ASI3UY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:10:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与麻省理工学院分拆出来的 Commonwealth 公司达成购买核聚变动力的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周一表示，它已达成一项协议，将从弗吉尼亚州的一个以核聚变为燃料的项目中购买电力。【原文：Alphabet's Google said on Monday it has struck a deal to buy power from a project in Virginia fueled by fusion, the reaction that powers the sun and the stars but is not yet commercial on Earth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/google-strikes-deal-buy-fusion-power-mit-spinoff-commonwealth-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HZZRQK6IBO5TFN65A5W5ZS5RU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特财富基金 2024 年净利润暴跌 60]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯主权财富基金周一报告称，受高利率和通货膨胀以及一些项目减值的影响，该基金 2024 年的净利润同比下滑 60%，降至 258 亿里亚尔（约合 69 亿美元）。【原文：Saudi Arabia's sovereign wealth fund's net profit slumped 60% from a year earlier to 25.8 billion riyals ($6.9 billion) in 2024, it reported on Monday, hurt by high interest rates and inflation as well as impairments on some projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-wealth-fund-net-profit-tumbles-60-2024-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVWCITQH5JI6BGZPKACSOG3LRI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 旗下 Cirsa 博彩公司寻求 29.5 亿美元的首次公开募股估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[账簿管理人之一周一表示，Blackstone 旗下的博彩公司 Cirsa 将于今年在西班牙证券交易所首次公开发行 4 亿欧元的股票，寻求获得 25.2 亿欧元（29.5 亿美元）的估值。【原文：Blackstone's gambling company Cirsa will seek a valuation of 2.52 billion euros ($2.95 billion) in an initial public offering of shares worth 400 million euros on the Spanish stock exchange this year, one of the bookrunners said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackstones-cirsa-gambling-company-seeks-295-bln-valuation-ipo-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4IOUY4CAJIBZFVU7BHSTW62ZY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:48:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称桑坦德银行提交了对萨瓦德尔旗下 TSB 的具有约束力的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士告诉路透社，桑坦德银行是向西班牙萨瓦德尔银行英国分行 TSB 提交有约束力收购要约的竞购者之一。【原文：Santander is among bidders that submitted a binding offer for Spanish lender Sabadell's British unit TSB, two sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/santander-bid-would-value-tsb-more-than-32-billion-source-says-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NU63DPXSDVLUTGP6E36GHVWGTA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾伯维将以不超过 21 亿美元的价格收购 Capstan Therapeutics]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯维周一表示，它将收购 Capstan Therapeutics，交易价值高达 21 亿美元，为其产品组合增添了治疗自身免疫性疾病的实验性疗法。【原文：AbbVie said on Monday it will acquire Capstan Therapeutics in a deal worth up to $2.1 billion, adding experimental treatments for autoimmune diseases to its portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/abbvie-buy-capstan-therapeutics-up-21-billion-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IR3SU7UJDJJSZF455PXZMOHH4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:42:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院共和党人试图让特朗普的减税计划顺利通过，抛开成本顾虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于该法案预计将对国家债务造成的 3.3 万亿美元的冲击，党内仍存在分歧。【原文：The party remains divided about the bill's expected $3.3 trillion hit to the nation's debt pile.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/senate-republicans-try-get-trumps-tax-cuts-over-line-setting-aside-cost-concerns-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAG4WSPX2JJFPBYFCJVR7K677I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得宝旗下的 SRS 将以约 43 亿美元的价格收购 GMS，竞争对手竞相出价]]></title><description><![CDATA[家得宝周一表示，SRS Distribution 部门已同意以约 43 亿美元的价格收购专业建筑产品分销商 GMS，而竞争对手 QXO .【原文：Home Depot said on Monday unit SRS Distribution has agreed to acquire specialty building products distributor GMS for about $4.3 billion, amid threats of a hostile takeover from rival QXO .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/home-depot-owned-srs-distribution-buy-gms-about-43-billion-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OZUYZ3S3BKILNWDV7DVLZJ2GU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递恢复以色列服务，对部分航线征收附加费]]></title><description><![CDATA[包裹巨头联邦快递（FedEx）周一表示，由于中东地区的飞行安全风险增加，该公司在此前停止了所有取件服务，并于6月27日恢复了往返以色列的服务。【原文：Parcel giant FedEx said on Monday that it reinstated its services to and from Israel on June 27 after previously halting all pickups amid heightened flight safety risks in the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/fedex-resumes-israel-services-imposes-surcharge-select-routes-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PXN6JERKVLWPCKLXD55K32W6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:15:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析显示，由于关税的影响，亚马逊上中国制造商品的价格上涨速度超过通胀率]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析显示，这些商品的价格从 5 月份开始加速上涨，这是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税开始向消费者渗透的一个信号。【原文：The analysis shows that price increases for those goods accelerated beginning in May, a signal U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs are starting to filter through to consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-prices-china-made-goods-amazon-rise-faster-than-inflation-analysis-shows-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5TJARLRXJMNFNUVYWJY4RTVTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街分析师看好 Circle 大手笔上市，但对过高估值提出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街券商周一开始对稳定币发行商Circle Internet Group进行评级，普遍看好该公司，但一些分析师对其估值过高表示担忧，因为该公司股价自上市以来已上涨了一倍多。【原文：Wall Street brokerages began coverage of stablecoin issuer Circle Internet Group on Monday with broadly bullish ratings, though some analysts voiced concerns about its elevated valuation after the stock more than doubled since its market debut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-analysts-bullish-circle-after-blockbuster-ipo-warn-sky-high-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q46BIRIPDROSPO2GKD4QNG3N4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅赛德斯称中国出口问题未造成供应链中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商梅赛德斯-奔驰（Mercedes-Benz）的一位高级主管周一表示，该公司的生产并未因中国原材料出口受限而中断。【原文：There has been no disruption to production due to limited raw material exports from China at German carmaker Mercedes-Benz , a senior executive said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-says-no-supply-chain-disruptions-after-china-export-concerns-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZ3HDXI3IBNCXMDQFH27AHASZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[INmune Bio 的阿尔茨海默氏症药物未达到中期研究目标，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[INmune 生物公司周一表示，在一项中期研究中，其阿尔茨海默氏症实验性药物未能改善这种夺人心智的疾病早期患者的认知功能，导致其股价在盘前交易中暴跌近 63%。【原文：INmune Bio said on Monday its experimental Alzheimer's drug failed to improve cognitive functions in patients with early stages of the mind-robbing disease in a mid-stage study, sending its shares plunging nearly 63% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/inmune-bios-alzheimers-drug-fails-meet-main-goal-mid-stage-study-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMXXXM57ORM7PAQYMFVHSKL4WQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:36:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安宏资本将收购数据中心设备制造商 LayerZero 的多数股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权投资公司 Advent International 周一表示，已同意收购 LayerZero Power Systems 公司的多数股权，该公司为数据中心生产电力基础设施设备。【原文：Private equity firm Advent International said on Monday it has agreed to acquire a majority stake in LayerZero Power Systems, which manufactures power infrastructure equipment for data centers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/advent-buy-majority-stake-data-center-equipment-maker-layerzero-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRIA3BASBJIFHG7H4TTBFBNRQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总部位于美国的 I Squared Capital 放弃单独收购香港宽频的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于美国的基础设施投资公司 I Squared Capital 周一表示，已撤销对香港宽带运营商香港宽频的收购计划，因为由一家国有实体支持的竞购占据了中心位置。【原文：U.S.-based infrastructure investment firm I Squared Capital has withdrawn plans to make a takeover offer for Hong Kong's HKBN , the broadband operator said on Monday, as a competing bid backed by a state-owned entity takes center stage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-based-i-squared-capital-dumps-plans-make-separate-offer-hong-kongs-hkbn-2025-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PE63XOOHLBNT7AKKAKZQHR32P4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>