<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:24:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:24:41 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银季度利润超预期，计划增持回购]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行瑞银周三公布第四季度净利润达12亿美元，同比增长56%，超出该公司提供的9.19亿美元市场预期。【原文：Swiss bank UBS posted on Wednesday a net profit of $1.2 billion for the fourth quarter, up 56% year-on-year and ahead of a company-provided consensus forecast of $919 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-quarterly-profit-beats-expectations-plans-more-buybacks-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBYBQPFRUJIJ5ERQAI4XRQBXMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国Uniper公司淡化对美国液化天然气的日益依赖，强调能源多元化]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国能源公司Uniper的一位高管淡化了欧洲对日益依赖美国液化天然气（LNG）的担忧，称企业签订的是与公司而非政府的合同，同时强调了多元化的必要性。【原文：A top executive at German utility Uniper has played down European concerns over increasing dependence on liquefied natural gas (LNG) from the United States, saying companies sign contracts with firms rather than governments, while stressing the need for diversification.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/germanys-uniper-downplays-increasing-reliance-us-lng-stresses-diversification-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DO22R3JXAZPFFMD5ZUG23KVALY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道称，在遭遇投资者反对后，Tether淡化了200亿美元融资规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周三报道，加密货币集团Tether首席执行官保罗·阿尔多伊诺在投资者对其5000亿美元估值目标提出质疑后，下调了新一轮融资目标金额。【原文：Crypto group Tether Chief Executive Paolo Ardoino has downplayed the amount of money it will raise in a new funding round following investor pushback over its $500-billion valuation goal, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tether-downplays-20-billion-funding-amount-after-investor-pushback-ft-reports-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5LKWGLU4BNCDDNJ6SIWGF75BQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道：雀巢新任掌门人谋划战略转型以提振增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周三援引知情人士报道，雀巢新任首席执行官正计划实施战略重组，将这家庞大的跨国公司业务聚焦于四大产品类别。【原文：The new chief executive of Nestle is planning a strategic overhaul to refocus the sprawling multinational around four product categories, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/new-nestle-boss-plots-strategic-overhaul-reignite-growth-ft-reports-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MBSPUF5NZOOXHJD7ER3SQPK5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：知情人士称福特与吉利正就制造与技术合作展开谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，福特汽车与中国的吉利汽车[RIC:RIC:GEELY.UL]正就潜在合作展开磋商。随着全球汽车制造商寻求分担日益沉重的技术研发与生产成本，此类合作正成为行业趋势。【原文：Ford and China’s Geely [RIC:RIC:GEELY.UL] are in discussions about a potential partnership, eight people with knowledge of the ongoing talks said, as the world's carmakers look to share heavier technology and manufacturing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-geely-talks-manufacturing-technology-partnership-sources-say-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4ZAZE37H5O5TEQJE2OFL7ZQEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:39:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度科技股暴跌，Anthropic人工智能工具引发全球用工担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，印度IT出口商股价暴跌6%，跟随全球软件股的跌势。此前人工智能开发商Anthropic推出新工具，加剧了业界对人工智能将颠覆数据及专业服务行业的担忧。【原文：Shares of Indian IT exporters slumped 6% on Wednesday, tracking losses in global software stocks, after AI developer Anthropic launched new tools that heightened concerns over AI-driven disruption in the data and professional services industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-tech-stocks-slump-anthropics-ai-tool-raises-global-staffing-concerns-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2ZTC7Q7T5JZJP75ZXFUPVGOOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司预计将在上半年开始交付改进型787梦想客机。]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司一位高管周三表示，该公司预计将于今年上半年开始向航空公司交付改进型787-9和787-10梦想客机，这些机型将具备更长的航程或更大的货运能力。【原文：Boeing expects to begin delivering improved 787-9 and 787-10 Dreamliners to airlines in the first half of this year, enabling longer flights or greater cargo capability, a senior executive said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-expects-start-delivering-improved-787-dreamliners-first-half-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I37G2PUPHVJKREJA3DM76PLPSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:56:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：韩国计划今年为养老基金发行美元债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国副福利部长表示，希望国家养老金服务局（NPS）能在年底前开始发行外币债券，此举将有助于在汇率波动加剧的背景下加强融资渠道多元化建设。【原文：South Korea's vice welfare minister said she hopes the National Pension Service (NPS) will start issuing foreign-currency bonds by the end of the year, a move that will strengthen efforts to diversify financing amid rising exchange-rate volatility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-eyes-dollar-bond-issuance-pension-fund-this-year-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VX64ROP7LZN5ZHBVEDZWIABRD4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道称，英伟达向中国销售AI芯片受阻于美国安全审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[《金融时报》周二援引知情人士消息报道称，尽管美国总统特朗普已批准出口许可，但英伟达H200人工智能芯片对华销售仍悬而未决，目前正等待美国国家安全审查。【原文：Nvidia's H200 AI chip sales to China remain in limbo nearly two months after U.S. President Donald Trump approved exports, pending a U.S. national security review, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-ai-chip-sales-china-stalled-by-us-security-review-ft-reports-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPWKGDBYONPNPGMTOE5LQTKBZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:24:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市震荡，油价攀升，黄金重拾涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周三走势震荡，此前因市场担忧人工智能的进步可能取代传统软件，美股和欧股大幅下挫。【原文：Asian stocks were on shaky ground on Wednesday, following steep losses in U.S. and European equities on fears that advancements in artificial intelligence could supplant traditional software.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRKU62T4ARNS7HMR6ZZOTYOEH4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[任天堂股价暴跌10%，市场担忧增长动能减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[任天堂股价周三下跌10%，投资者对其旗舰产品Switch 2游戏设备的销售势头感到担忧。【原文：Nintendo shares slid 10% on Wednesday as investors fretted about momentum for its flagship Switch 2 gaming device.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nintendo-shares-slide-10-momentum-fears-grow-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIH5LQ5BRZNG3B4NA7ZR2OCORY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:19:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场监管机构批准宁德时代与奇瑞汽车合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管总局周三表示，已无条件批准电池制造商宁德时代与国有汽车制造商奇瑞汽车成立合资企业。【原文：China's market regulator on Wednesday said it has unconditionally approved the establishment of a joint venture by battery manufacturer CATL and state-owned automaker Chery .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-market-regulator-approves-catl-chery-joint-venture-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEKJBAN4I5J2BMHZBQF2HWTHY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元持稳，日元在日本大选前波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三美元汇率持稳，因部分政府停摆迅速结束后投资者仍保持谨慎；而日元汇率则在两周低点附近徘徊，因本周末即将举行的全国大选前景难以预测。【原文：The U.S. dollar was steady on Wednesday as investors remained cautious after a partial government shutdown swiftly ended while the yen wobbled near a two-week low ahead of what is shaping up to be an unpredictable national election over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-steady-yen-wobbles-ahead-japan-election-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AITZQNZVBJOFRPZTKHLPRN3MCQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:01:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡ST工程公司展示货运无人机与船舶，拓展业务版图]]></title><description><![CDATA[新航工程在新加坡航展上展示了两个独特平台，标志着这家全球最大的飞机机身维护与维修服务供应商正大力拓展新一代航空技术领域。【原文：ST Engineering is showing off two distinct platforms at the Singapore Airshow that mark a significant expansion into next-generation aviation technologies for the world's largest airframe maintenance and repair services provider.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapores-st-engineering-showcases-cargo-drone-marine-craft-it-expands-reach-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXD4X3IA7NPEFNWXPGDPTCBFOQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:57:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价延续涨势，因担忧中东局势升级]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三油价上涨，延续了前一日的涨势。此前美国击落一架伊朗无人机，武装伊朗船只在霍尔木兹海峡逼近一艘悬挂美国国旗的船只，这重新点燃了华盛顿与德黑兰之间紧张局势升级的担忧。【原文：Oil prices rose on Wednesday, extending the previous day's gains, after the U.S. shot down an Iranian drone and armed Iranian boats approached a U.S.-flagged vessel in the Strait of Hormuz, rekindling fears of an escalation in tension between Washington and Tehran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-extend-gains-fears-escalating-tensions-mideast-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5ASOISX6JPWNDYAFLEQIQBMLE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示波音计划4月进行777X量产机首飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社获得的一份公司文件显示，波音计划于4月进行首架量产型777X客机的首飞。这对这家飞机制造商长期延迟的新型客机项目而言是一个重要进展信号，该机型计划于明年交付首架。【原文：Boeing plans the first flight of a production 777X in April, a company document seen by Reuters shows, an important signal of progress for the planemaker's long-delayed new jet, which is slated for first delivery next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-plans-first-flight-production-777x-april-document-shows-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWRCTIBERVOQHGVVEGPGE2J4SI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:38:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚Sunrise公司首席执行官表示，该公司有望为美国关键矿物储备提供供应。]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚钪矿项目首席执行官周二向路透社表示，该项目由矿业亿万富翁理查德·弗里德兰支持，预计将为美国120亿美元的关键矿物储备计划作出贡献。【原文：An Australian scandium project backed by mining billionaire Richard Friedland is expected to contribute to the $12 billion U.S. critical minerals stockpile, the company's CEO told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-sunrise-expects-supply-us-critical-minerals-stockpile-ceo-says-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFPUDZMFD5ORBLGYM3NKB67VZU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[和记黄埔旗下公司就港口裁决对巴拿马提起仲裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港和记黄埔周三表示，其旗下巴拿马港口公司已就巴拿马法院撤销其运营两座巴拿马运河港口的许可证一事，对巴拿马政府提起国际仲裁。【原文：Hong Kong's CK Hutchison said on Wednesday its Panama Ports Company unit has started international arbitration proceedings against Panama after a court there annulled its licences to operate two Panama Canal ports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/ck-hutchison-unit-launches-arbitration-against-panama-over-port-ruling-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPTMZ2J6RVKXPAEA44BFCPIEFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR与新电联财团将支付52亿美元全面收购STT GDC]]></title><description><![CDATA[KKR与新加坡电信联合财团将以66亿新元（约合52亿美元）现金收购ST Telemedia全球数据中心（STT GDC）剩余82%股权。双方周二宣布，此项收购使这家新加坡数据中心运营商的企业价值达到138亿新元。【原文：A KKR and Singapore Telecommunications consortium will pay S$6.6 billion ($5.2 billion) in cash to buy the remaining 82% stake in ST Telemedia Global Data Centres (STT GDC), valuing the Singapore-based data centre operator at an implied enterprise value of S$13.8 billion, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/kkr-singtel-consortium-pay-52-billion-take-full-control-stt-gdc-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STCKII6Q25OZTHBJPXDN6AH2DM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japan's services activity hits fastest growth in nearly a year, PMI shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's services activity expanded at its quickest pace in nearly a year while the overall private sector posted the fastest growth in 32 months, buoyed by robust demand, a private sector survey showed on Wednesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-services-activity-hits-fastest-growth-nearly-year-pmi-shows-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJC4XPGAV5OPHOKYN5H7RORM54</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:36:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Australia warns $3.2 trillion pension fund industry to lift systems investment]]></title><description><![CDATA[Australia's corporate regulator has warned the nation's A$4.5 trillion ($3.16 trillion) pension fund industry it needs to invest more in systems and technology to better prepare for the future and avoid becoming troubled like stock market operator ASX .]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-warns-32-trillion-pension-fund-industry-lift-systems-investment-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ME2O5OFQNRPL5AS2RDRG4YYRB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Former US agriculture officials, top Republican senator warn of farm country trouble]]></title><description><![CDATA[The chair of the U.S. Senate's agriculture committee warned on Tuesday that farmers were suffering heavy losses, while more than two dozen former industry leaders sounded the alarm about the risk of a "widespread collapse of American agriculture" ahead of a $12 billion government bailout expected to reach growers this month.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/former-us-agriculture-officials-top-republican-senator-warn-farm-country-trouble-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QO6GBUDSURIIRK2YAZQ2CKFRIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump signs extension of Africa duty-free trade program, USTR says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday signed a law extending a preferential trade program for Africa through December 31, effective retroactively from September 30, 2025, the chief U.S. trade negotiator said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/trump-signs-extension-africa-duty-free-trade-program-ustr-says-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2GFJVRHD5NW3DPPGP3K2TF754</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democratic senators seek delay in nomination proceedings of Warsh for Fed chair]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Democratic members of the Senate Banking committee on Tuesday asked Republican committee chair Senator Tim Scott to delay the nomination proceedings for former Federal Reserve governor Kevin Warsh, President Donald Trump's pick to be the next chair of the U.S. central bank.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-senators-seek-delay-nomination-proceedings-warsh-fed-chair-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMAAUGXNSZKFXGTCOGZJJF5SS4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia nears deal to invest $20 billion in OpenAI funding round, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia is nearing a deal to invest $20 billion in OpenAI as part of its latest funding round, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-nears-deal-invest-20-billion-openai-funding-round-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P25YNKYETNK5NDPZ7CMW7KFJAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:31:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Private markets for retail savers will not end well, private equity executive Josh Harris says]]></title><description><![CDATA[A recent rush to sell private markets investments to everyday savers is risky and could have negative consequences for other investors too, prominent private equity executive Josh Harris said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/private-markets-retail-savers-will-not-end-well-private-equity-executive-josh-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHJYWOOBC5JZXH3GQIL2GOZ2HQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:19:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed's Miran resigns from White House job]]></title><description><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran resigned on Tuesday from his position as chair of the White House's Council of Economic Advisers, a White House spokesman said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-miran-resigns-white-house-job-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VARZRKOQDZPMPCF7NOJZRCVKGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yuan expected to rise in 2026, but Beijing has its reasons for saying not so fast]]></title><description><![CDATA[Booming exports are pushing up China's currency and while analysts think authorities will resist further gains, risks are to the upside and could test the country's fragile economy.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/yuan-expected-rise-2026-beijing-has-its-reasons-saying-not-so-fast-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXBB4MIEDZM4XABOADMXMEBHM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon's AWS CEO calls orbital data centers 'pretty far' from reality]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amazon's top cloud computing executive said space-based data centers are "pretty far" from being a reality, even as a number of startups and the company's own founder, Jeff Bezos, have pursued the idea.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/amazons-aws-ceo-says-orbital-data-centers-pretty-far-reality-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DREMWG2UVK2VGP7SE3PTPRSQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prudential's fourth-quarter profit jumps on underwriting strength]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prudential Financial on Tuesday reported a rise in fourth-quarter profit, helped by strong underwriting and gains from its investment portfolio.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/prudentials-fourth-quarter-profit-jumps-underwriting-strength-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5DUYHO5YBNOFCK2XR3S6N44EM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:17:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>