<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:29:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:29:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者信心指数在2月份有所改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二公布的一项调查显示，随着家庭对劳动力市场的看法好转，美国消费者信心指数在2月份出现超预期反弹。【原文：U.S. consumer confidence rebounded more than expected in February amid an improvement in households' perceptions of the labor market, a survey showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-confidence-improves-february-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7N4SR3XLNOWVESDZR7IFJTZRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:22:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大交通部在特朗普争执后认证湾流G700和G800喷气机]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大交通部已认证通用动力湾流公司的G700和G800公务机，政府文件显示，此前数周美国总统特朗普曾指责加拿大监管机构审批该机型耗时过长。【原文：Transport Canada has certified General Dynamics Gulfstream's G700 and G800 business jets, according to a government document, weeks after U.S. President Donald Trump called out the Canadian regulator for taking too long to approve the aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/transport-canada-certifies-gulfstream-g700-g800-jets-after-trump-spat-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BM266K2MRVOF3EDTY4KQFO34VQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国无人机制造商大疆提起诉讼，挑战美国对新款机型的进口禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国无人机制造商大疆周二表示，已提起诉讼，对美国联邦通信委员会禁止进口其所有新型号及关键组件的决定提出质疑，该禁令涉及中国大疆和奥图尔等企业。【原文：Chinese dronemaker DJI said Tuesday it has filed suit challenging the Federal Communications Commission decision to bar imports of all of its new models and critical components including from China's DJI and Autel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/chinese-dronemaker-dji-files-lawsuit-challenge-us-import-ban-new-models-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGV6CT2SSZKJLMIWPSEHRDIZYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:59:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，欧盟预计美国将在数周内降低钢铁和铝制品关税。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周二报道，欧盟官员预计美国将在数周内降低对含钢铝产品的关税，这可能缓解跨大西洋贸易关系中的主要摩擦点。该报道援引知情人士消息称。【原文：European Union officials expect the U.S. to lower tariffs on goods containing steel and aluminum within weeks, potentially easing a major source of friction in transatlantic trade ties, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-expects-us-scale-back-steel-aluminum-tariffs-within-weeks-bloomberg-news-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUMEI5IY6RM2JOHZPBSYC3IQDI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安普瑞克在法律插件引发市场暴跌数周后推出新型人工智能工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能实验室Anthropic近日公布了10种新方案，帮助企业客户将其技术融入关键业务领域。此前数周，该公司的其他产品发布曾引发传统软件公司股价的剧烈抛售。【原文：Artificial intelligence lab Anthropic unveiled 10 new ways for business customers to plug in its technology to key areas of their work, weeks after other releases sparked an aggressive selloff in traditional software company shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/anthropic-touts-new-ai-tools-weeks-after-legal-plug-in-spurred-market-rout-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XN2OJDNXNRIDXOD62SJMVF55AE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员库克称人工智能正引发重大变革，预计短期失业率可能上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事丽莎·库克周二表示，人工智能已在美国劳动力市场引发代际转变，可能导致失业率上升，而美联储可能无法通过降息来应对。【原文：Artificial intelligence has triggered a generational shift in the U.S. labor market and could lead to a possible rise in the unemployment rate that the U.S. central bank may not be able to counter with lower interest rates, Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-cook-says-ai-triggering-big-changes-sees-possible-short-term-unemployment-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVURTU4OJFLSXFHKMWWZFFD5WQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:33:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW AMD成功拿下Meta作为下一家重要AI芯片客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[超微半导体公司周二宣布，已同意在五年内向Meta Platforms出售价值高达600亿美元的人工智能芯片。根据协议，这家Facebook母公司可收购该芯片公司最多10%的股权。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices said on Tuesday it has agreed to sell up to $60 billion worth of artificial intelligence chips to Meta Platforms over five years in a deal that allows the Facebook owner to purchase as much as 10% of the chip firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-amd-secures-meta-next-big-ai-chip-customer-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAZYF62ZFBP3DJ5I3IJ3TVLTIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Xcel能源公司将为谷歌在明尼苏达州的新数据中心供电]]></title><description><![CDATA[Xcel能源公司周二宣布，已与谷歌达成合作，为这家科技巨头位于明尼苏达州派恩岛的新数据中心供电，同时为电网新增1900兆瓦清洁能源。【原文：Xcel Energy said on Tuesday it has partnered with Google to power the tech giant's new data center in Pine Island, Minnesota, while contributing 1,900 megawatts of new clean energy to the grid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/xcel-energy-power-new-google-data-center-minnesota-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGZPJLT4FZLO7LCLEA45C753P4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:23:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储委员沃勒称央行正谨慎部署人工智能技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗·沃勒周二表示，美国央行正以系统性方式谨慎推进人工智能技术的采用。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Christopher Waller said Tuesday the U.S. central bank is carefully moving to adopt artificial intelligence technology in a system-wide approach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-waller-says-central-bank-deploying-ai-tech-cautiously-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XVUWIDXKFLJ5FQVJH5WSBDEGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:23:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦住房金融局称，12月美国独栋住宅价格涨幅放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国独栋住宅价格涨幅在12月放缓，但经济学家认为，库存紧张可能阻止全国房价出现全面下跌。【原文：U.S. single-family house price gains slowed in December, but economists believe tight inventory could prevent an outright decline in national home prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-single-family-home-price-growth-slows-december-fhfa-says-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZRVWGEPK5P4JN23QGOOSLOUDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[支付处理商FIS受益于银行解决方案部门的推动，利润实现增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融服务公司富达国家信息服务公司周二公布第四季度盈利增长，得益于其金融产品与服务的强劲需求，该公司股价在盘前交易中上涨3%。【原文：Banking and payments processing firm Fidelity National Information Services on Tuesday posted a higher profit for the fourth quarter on strong demand for its financial products and services, sending the company's shares up 3% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/payments-processor-fis-posts-higher-profit-boost-banking-solutions-unit-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDLOZNVCL5K5PKC7IRFAQ7542U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：激进投资者Irenic增持Ralliant股份，推动削减成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，艾瑞尼克资本管理公司已持有瑞利安特公司大量股份，并要求这家精密技术制造商削减成本、加快股票回购步伐，同时更专注于其国防和电子业务。【原文：Irenic Capital Management has built a sizable stake in Ralliant and wants the precision technology maker to cut costs, buy back more stock at a faster pace and focus more on its defense and electronics business, two sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/activist-irenic-builds-stake-ralliant-pushes-cost-cuts-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZK7MZVPR5MKBMJSMRAHSBX7QA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟正权衡派拉蒙修订后的报价，竞购战愈演愈烈]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司周二表示，正在考虑派拉蒙天空舞影业的新报价，但未披露交易金额。作为CBS母公司，华纳正竭力阻止奈飞收购这家备受追捧的好莱坞制片厂。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery said on Tuesday it was considering a new bid from Paramount Skydance without disclosing the value of the deal, as the CBS owner makes a last-ditch effort to thwart Netflix from buying the coveted Hollywood studio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/warner-bros-weighing-revised-bid-paramount-bidding-war-escalates-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6GW3ZHZQVKF7DOJSXQ3T47B2Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:22:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：特朗普瞄准五角大楼人工智能项目，为贸易集团矿产定价]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士向路透社透露，特朗普政府计划利用五角大楼开发的人工智能程序，为关键矿产设定基准价格，以推动建立全球金属贸易区。【原文：The Trump administration plans to use a Pentagon-created artificial intelligence program to help set reference prices for critical minerals as it works to build a global metals trading zone, three sources with direct knowledge of the effort told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-eyes-pentagon-ai-program-trade-blocks-minerals-pricing-sources-say-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPQ5B5YI2JOPTJSZ2I32W5ADFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:20:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最新要约收购中，Stripe估值跃升至1590亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stripe周二宣布，其面向员工和股东的要约收购将这家金融科技公司的估值定为1590亿美元，较一年前同类股权交易时的估值上涨逾70%。【原文：Stripe said on Tuesday a tender offer for employees and shareholders valued the fintech firm at $159 billion, marking a rise of more than 70% from its valuation in a comparable share sale a year ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stripe-valuation-jumps-159-billion-latest-share-sale-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFOLSX6QDNNPJM5IK6VVBAIUTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:13:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员古尔斯比：若通胀回落则降息合理，但押注生产率提升为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯坦·古尔斯比表示，若通胀开始回落，美联储可能重启降息；但若以预期生产率增长为由当前放松货币政策，则存在风险。此番言论标志着他介入了美联储内部日益凸显的核心争论。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve could resume cutting interest rates if inflation starts to fall, but it would be risky to use expected productivity growth as a reason to loosen monetary policy now, Chicago Fed president Austan Goolsbee said as he waded into what is emerging as a core debate at the U.S. central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-rate-cuts-appropriate-if-inflation-falls-too-soon-bet-productivity-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SI4E7I5VBKYTJC7TP4FGT76NM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper公司预测年度业绩强劲，因碳酸饮料需求表现坚挺]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周二公布的季度财报超出市场预期后，Keurig Dr Pepper公司预测全年业绩将表现强劲，其押注于新口味产品和营销举措将推动碳酸饮料及能量饮料的需求增长。【原文：Keurig Dr Pepper forecast strong annual results after beating quarterly earnings estimates on Tuesday, betting on its new flavors and marketing efforts to drive demand for its carbonated beverages and energy drinks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/keurig-dr-pepper-forecasts-strong-annual-results-resilient-demand-sodas-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XP2RUXFMEZPBBCO2NRIFS3MDRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国总理梅尔茨访华寻求突破口，全球压力持续增大]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希·梅尔茨本周访华，成为最新一位寻求重置中德关系的欧洲领导人。过去一年间，德美联盟的瓦解已暴露无遗，其供应链的脆弱性也浮出水面。【原文：German Chancellor Friedrich Merz visits China this week as the latest European leader seeking to reset relations with Beijing after a year that laid bare the crumbling of their alliance with the U.S. and exposed vulnerabilities in their supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/german-chancellor-merz-heads-china-seeking-openings-global-pressure-builds-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAVSWOYJFFKQ7CTITVFRNYU4G4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:44:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德将于2027年起将Wegovy在美国市场的定价削减一半]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦制药巨头诺和诺德周二宣布，从明年起将大幅下调其畅销糖尿病和减肥药物Ozempic与Wegovy在美国市场的定价，降幅最高可达50%。【原文：Novo Nordisk will slash U.S. list prices of its blockbuster diabetes and weight-loss drugs Ozempic and Wegovy by up to 50% starting next year, the Danish drugmaker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-slash-us-list-prices-ozempic-wegovy-wsj-reports-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTT5MKEXZVJOXAU67APZN3X5A4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:42:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铁塔公司受益于5G及数据中心业务增长，租赁活动强劲推动营收表现亮眼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铁塔公司周二公布的第四季度营收超出华尔街预期，得益于电信运营商租赁活动增强以及数据中心需求持续增长。【原文：American Tower on Tuesday posted fourth-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates, lifted by stronger leasing activity from telecom carriers and continued momentum in data-center demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/american-tower-posts-upbeat-revenue-strong-leasing-activity-amid-5g-data-center-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTTLPDZTYNJ77PWUDJASTENILI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:26:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惊惶不安的投资者因反乌托邦式人工智能前景的广泛传播而惊慌失措]]></title><description><![CDATA[由人工智能引发的大规模失业构想出的反乌托邦景象，在Citrini Research如今广为流传的报告中被重点提及，这已使全球市场动荡不安——近期对该技术的大规模押注正开始显露裂痕。【原文：An imagined dystopia of mass unemployment fuelled by artificial intelligence, highlighted in Citrini Research's now viral report, has unsettled global markets, where a recent huge bet on the technology is starting to show cracks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/skittish-investors-spooked-dystopian-ai-outlooks-go-viral-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72XQJ7C77NMJJGFDQ7GSFWNAJE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AES公司签署为谷歌得州数据中心供电的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[AES公司周二宣布，已与谷歌签署为期20年的协议，为其计划在德克萨斯州威尔巴格县建设的数据中心供电。【原文：AES Corp said on Tuesday it has signed a 20-year agreement with Google 
 to supply power to a data center planned in Wilbarger County, Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/aes-corp-signs-power-supply-agreements-google-data-center-texas-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLIZS647AJI43ME5FVD3ZCIZDU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:08:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团的对冲基金客户在最高法院关税裁决前后抛售美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国银行周一晚间向路透社提供的报告显示，花旗集团的对冲基金客户在周五美国最高法院就特朗普总统全面加征关税的裁决前后抛售美元。【原文：Citigroup's hedge fund clients sold the dollar around Friday's U.S. Supreme Court ruling on President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs, according to a note from the U.S. bank shared with Reuters late on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/citigroups-hedge-fund-clients-sold-dollar-around-supreme-court-tariff-ruling-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3762WIMFOZJJLFGTXNIBBHGZFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD再签巨额芯片供应协议，此次合作对象为Meta]]></title><description><![CDATA[超微半导体公司周二宣布，已同意在五年内向Meta Platforms出售价值高达600亿美元的人工智能芯片。根据协议，这家Facebook母公司可收购该芯片公司最多10%的股权。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices said on Tuesday it has agreed to sell up to $60 billion worth of artificial intelligence chips to Meta Platforms over five years in a deal that allows the Facebook owner to purchase as much as 10% of the chip firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/amd-clinches-second-mega-chip-supply-deal-this-time-with-meta-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5I32XBRFFPU5ODZPALMSHWKXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:01:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：人工智能的末日与关税阴霾]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJ6ZBHLCJBLJLEQNW73I6CYC6A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:56:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国隐私监管机构因儿童数据保护失职对Reddit处以2000万美元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国隐私监管机构周二宣布，因涉及儿童隐私保护的违规行为，对社交媒体平台Reddit处以1447万英镑（约合1952万美元）罚款。【原文：Britain's privacy watchdog on Tuesday said it had fined social media platform Reddit 14.47 million pounds ($19.52 million) for failures related to children's privacy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk-privacy-watchdog-fines-reddit-20-million-over-childrens-data-failures-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITQQXYWIYBOOBC2YBMGDZDC4EM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:44:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司因风暴持续扰乱航班取消逾2000架次]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国航空公司取消了逾2000个航班，较前日大幅减少。此前席卷东北部各机场的强劲冬季风暴预计将在傍晚减弱，但强风将持续至凌晨时分。【原文：U.S. airlines canceled over 2,000 flights on Tuesday, far fewer than a day earlier, as a powerful winter storm that disrupted airports across the Northeast was expected to ease by evening, with strong winds expected to continue into the early hours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-airlines-cancel-over-2000-flights-storm-disruption-continues-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIVTKFZZFJLURA4JUO5F2VF6DQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:31:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博廷将公布桑坦德银行数字化转型带来的成本节约，此前该行已完成多笔收购交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，桑坦德银行首席执行官安娜·博廷将于周三向投资者承诺，该行将通过数字化转型实现更精简的运营和更高的成本节约。她试图说服投资者相信，其在核心发达市场扩张的战略是最佳增长路径。【原文：Santander boss Ana Botin will promise a leaner lender with higher cost savings from the bank's digital drive as she seeks to convince investors on Wednesday that her bet on expanding in core developed markets is the best growth path, people familiar with the plans said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/botin-set-out-cost-savings-santander-digital-drive-after-deal-spree-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27LZ2TNKXFKEHGDSNWFVWMEQ7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:19:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货在周一重挫后企稳；关税与人工智能担忧主导市场情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周二小幅走高，在经历前一交易日全面抛售后略有回升。投资者正努力应对特朗普总统关税举措的不确定影响以及日益加剧的人工智能相关担忧。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged up on Tuesday, recovering slightly after a broad market selloff the previous session as investors grappled with the uncertain impact of President Donald Trump's tariff maneuvers and escalating AI-related concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-steady-after-mondays-battering-tariffs-ai-concerns-dominate-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZLHIOBQHNM3XPMD352J3L7PK4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得宝季度销售额超预期，得益于专业客户需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[家得宝周二公布的第四季度销售额超出华尔街预期，这家全球最大的家居建材连锁企业受益于专业承包商的强劲需求，以及预算紧张的消费者选择低成本维修方案。【原文：Home Depot beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter sales on Tuesday, as the world's largest home improvement chain benefited from resilient demand from professional contractors and lower‑cost repairs by budget-strapped customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/home-improvement-retailer-home-depot-edges-past-quarterly-sales-estimates-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D63OA4FIKZI7FIURPKJ2V3PIWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>