<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:16:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:16:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会已要求X公司将所有Grok文件保留至2026年底，发言人表示。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人周四表示，该机构已要求埃隆·马斯克旗下的社交媒体平台X保留其内置人工智能聊天机器人Grok的所有内部文件和数据，直至2026年底。【原文：The European Commission has ordered Elon Musk's social media site X to retain all internal documents and data relating to its built-in artificial intelligence chatbot, Grok, until the end of 2026, a commission spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eu-commission-has-ordered-x-retain-all-grok-documents-until-end-2026-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y75EA6GH7JOU7MUR2DTPKBXVBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，蒙太奇科技计划于明年1月在香港进行最高达10亿美元的股票发售。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，中国半导体设计公司蒙特吉科技计划最早于本月在香港进行二次上市，拟发行8亿至10亿美元股票，这将进一步加剧香港融资市场的火热态势。【原文：Chinese semiconductor designer Montage Technology plans a second listing in Hong Kong via a $800 million to $1 billion share offering as soon as this month, said two people with knowledge of the matter, adding to the hectic pace of fundraising in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/montage-technology-plans-up-1-billion-hong-kong-share-sale-january-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIZWW7T35NOWLJB4OKPKYEJQCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:01:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞标：特朗普的可见之手]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STBEBJ5FXRPC7GAJUQU7LKA3XU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[若特朗普在最高法院败诉，进口商将为1500亿美元关税退税之争做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[公司高管、报关行和贸易律师正紧盯最高法院对特朗普总统全球性关税合法性的裁决——若裁决结果不利，进口商可能发起争夺战，要求美国政府退还已缴纳的关税，金额或达1500亿美元。【原文：Company executives, customs brokers and trade lawyers are bracing for a Supreme Court ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump's sweeping global tariffs - and a potential fight over obtaining perhaps $150 billion in refunds from the U.S. government for duties already paid by importers if he loses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/importers-brace-150-billion-tariff-refund-fight-if-trump-loses-supreme-court-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBETWI5QB5LZBNHSBSVYKNHJTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院审议特朗普紧急关税权限之际，市场风险持续攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院即将就特朗普总统动用紧急关税权力的裁决可能引发金融市场剧烈波动，尤其当法官们推翻关税决定时。【原文：A forthcoming U.S. Supreme Court decision on President Donald Trump's use of emergency tariff powers could jolt financial markets, especially if the justices strike down the tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/market-risk-mounts-supreme-court-weighs-trumps-emergency-tariff-powers-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKINHB5OZRIE3NBHYRRM6Z2ULU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制药商为欧洲定价之争做准备，此前特朗普在美国达成降价协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球制药商在2026年将面临一场争夺战，试图在欧洲为其处方药争取更高售价。此前在特朗普总统的压力下，这些企业去年已同意降低美国药价。【原文：Global drugmakers face a battle in 2026 to secure higher prices for their prescription medicines in Europe after agreeing to cut U.S. pricing last year under pressure from President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/drugmakers-brace-europe-pricing-fight-after-trumps-us-price-cut-deals-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5NKIXIFPROYLO4NC4B3ZPAJ5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货下跌；国防企业因特朗普预算计划上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四美国股指期货走低，因投资者在周五关键的非农就业数据公布前转为谨慎；与此同时，在特朗普总统呼吁制定1.5万亿美元军事预算后，国防类股逆势上扬。【原文：U.S. stock index futures moved lower on Thursday, as investors turned cautious in the run up to Friday's crucial nonfarm payrolls, while defense companies advanced after President Donald Trump called for a $1.5 trillion military budget.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-dip-defense-firms-climb-up-trump-budget-plans-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDCXEANR6VO7ZGVX5XDMC43LZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:40:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰银行称，金价可能在2026年上半年触及每盎司5000美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行周四表示，受地缘政治风险和债务攀升影响，金价可能在2026年上半年升至每盎司5000美元。【原文：Gold prices could rise to $5,000 an ounce in the first half of 2026 on geopolitical risks and rising debt, HSBC said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gold-could-hit-5000-an-ounce-first-half-2026-says-hsbc-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQZYZDTSKFLWVOX5QASZ3CHSH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国西海岸喷气燃料对亚洲的溢价接近近两年来最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦金融交易所周四数据显示，美国西海岸即期喷气燃料对亚洲的溢价已升至近两年最高水平。炼油厂停产抑制了美国供应，而中国需求放缓则增加了该燃料在亚洲的供应量。【原文：The premium for prompt U.S. West Coast jet fuel to Asia has reached its widest in nearly two years, LSEG data showed on Thursday, as refinery outages curbed U.S. supply and slower Chinese demand increased the fuel's availability in Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-west-coast-jet-fuels-premium-asia-near-its-widest-nearly-two-years-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JK5AL6DFN5L4BOGCJU74EPRCJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:18:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构将于2月10日前就谷歌收购Wiz交易作出裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构将于2月10日前决定是否批准Alphabet以320亿美元收购网络安全公司Wiz的交易。这是该公司有史以来规模最大的并购案，欧盟委员会网站的文件显示。【原文：EU antitrust regulators will decide by February 10 whether to clear Alphabet's $32 billion acquisition of cybersecurity company Wiz, its largest deal ever, according to a filing on the European Commission website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/eu-antitrust-regulators-decide-googles-wiz-deal-by-february-10-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPYGPPD3AJOT3JPDC4AKMSDWUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:17:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车因倒车影像问题在美国召回逾41.3万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周四表示，瑞典汽车制造商沃尔沃汽车因后视摄像头存在问题，将在美国召回413,151辆汽车。【原文：Swedish automaker Volvo Cars is recalling 413,151 vehicles in the United States over an issue with the rearview camera, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/volvo-cars-recalls-over-413000-us-vehicles-due-rearview-camera-issue-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3G47EVONCBM3PFZV6CY5K4EPXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[笛卡尔公司称，受中国持续低迷影响，美国12月集装箱进口量下降5.9%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国集装箱进口量在12月下降5.9%，全年较2024年微降0.4%。供应链技术供应商笛卡尔系统集团周四表示，特朗普总统的关税政策导致中国货运量锐减，引发全球贸易动荡，并加剧了通胀担忧。【原文：U.S. container imports fell 5.9% in December to end the year down 0.4% from 2024 after President Donald Trump's tariff policies slashed shipments from China, shook up global trade and fueled inflation fears, supply chain technology provider Descartes Systems Group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-container-imports-dropped-59-december-continued-china-slump-descartes-says-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E42JKGIT3NLFNM6QHLJSODPSUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国奥维通集成电路公司香港上市定价触及上限，募资6.16亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国奥维通集成电路公司周四宣布，其香港上市每股H股发行价定为104.80港元，共筹集48亿港元（约合6.161亿美元）。【原文：China's OmniVision Integrated Circuits said on Thursday that it had set the offer price for its Hong Kong listing at HK$104.80 per H share, raising HK$4.80 billion ($616.1 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-omnivision-integrated-circuits-sets-hk-listing-price-top-end-raises-616-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NR26RZV6T5KORKV3B7BNBRMIB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:21:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度在苹果诉讼案中为反垄断处罚法辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度反垄断监管机构在法庭上表示，一项根据企业全球营业额计算罚款的法律将遏制跨国公司的违规行为。该机构此番表态旨在反对苹果公司对该措施的备受瞩目的挑战。【原文：A law used to calculate fines on the basis of a company's global turnover will discourage breaches by multinationals, India's antitrust watchdog told a court in opposing Apple's high-profile challenge to the measure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-defends-antitrust-penalty-law-apple-fight-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEQ23LYJSVP4XKFRWR3GPO3J7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 08:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索泰克任命英飞凌高管洛朗·雷蒙为首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国半导体晶圆制造商索泰克公司周四宣布，任命洛朗·雷蒙特接替皮埃尔·巴纳贝担任新任首席执行官，将于4月正式履新。【原文：Semiconductor wafer maker Soitec has appointed Laurent Remont as its new chief executive officer, to replace Pierre Barnabe from April, the French company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/soitec-appoints-infineon-executive-laurent-remont-ceo-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVY2GIEMGRJ5JFFOQ6QJFOCYMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 08:28:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian因转向拉杆组装不当在美国召回近2万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周四表示，Rivian汽车公司正在美国召回19,641辆已维修过的R1S和R1T电动汽车，原因是后轮外倾角连杆组装错误。【原文：Rivian Automotive is recalling 19,641 previously serviced R1S and R1T electric vehicles in the U.S., citing incorrectly assembled rear toe link, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-recalls-nearly-20000-us-vehicles-over-improperly-reassembled-toe-link-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEDY64TFORJ5FFSPRCWUUGWP64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 08:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车推出全新中型电动SUV，旨在解决续航焦虑问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司周四表示，其将于本月晚些时候推出的新款电动中型SUV，单次充电续航里程可达810公里（503英里），旨在赢得对电动汽车持怀疑态度的消费者。【原文：Volvo Cars' new electric mid-sized SUV, which launches later this month, will offer a driving range of up to 810 km (503 miles) on a single charge, the Swedish automaker said on Thursday, as it seeks to win over buyers sceptical of EVs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/volvo-cars-aims-tackle-range-anxiety-with-new-mid-size-electric-suv-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UEJGT6ZHNOVVNZ233WT2KU5MQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 08:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将评估、调查Meta收购人工智能初创公司Manus一事]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周四表示，将对Meta收购人工智能初创企业Manus一事进行评估和调查。【原文：China will assess and investigate Meta's acquisition of artificial intelligence startup Manus, the Chinese commerce ministry said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/china-assess-investigate-metas-acquisition-ai-startup-manus-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5AFTBEBXFIJ3JO2FMMZFI2N5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:45:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AB食品因Primark折扣促销及美国市场疲软下调盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[AB食品公司警告称，由于旗下Primark时尚业务大幅折扣促销，以及美国市场需求疲软——尤其是西班牙裔消费者需求减弱——导致食品原料销售受挫，公司年度利润将下滑，其股价因此一度下跌12%。【原文：AB Foods warned annual profit would fall as heavy discounting at its Primark fashion business and weaker U.S. demand - especially among Hispanic shoppers - hit food ingredient sales, driving its shares as much as 12% lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/primark-owner-ab-foods-warns-lower-annual-profit-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQII77NTDVOINLFBGYNIIXHNFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:11:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对委内瑞拉马杜罗采取行动后，投资者对拉丁美洲持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普在委内瑞拉和阿根廷采取强硬举措，加剧了拉丁美洲在关键选举年向右转的趋势。随着投资者预期该地区将推行市场友好型改革，外国资金流入该地区的可能性正不断增加。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's muscular moves in Venezuela and Argentina are adding to a rightward shift across Latin America in a pivotal election year, making foreign cash more likely to flow to the region as investors anticipate market-friendly reforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/investors-bullish-latin-america-after-us-move-venezuelas-maduro-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMPCCOWMUFOK7CU7YBDCP26BMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优衣库母公司迅销季度利润大幅增长，上调全年业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[优衣库服装品牌运营商迅销公司周四表示，得益于国内强劲销售以及在欧洲和北美市场的扩张，其第一季度营业利润较上年同期跃升34%。【原文：The Japanese operator of the Uniqlo clothing brand, Fast Retailing , on Thursday said its first-quarter operating profit jumped 34% from a year earlier as it benefited from strong sales at home and expansions in Europe and North America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/uniqlo-owner-fast-retailing-books-34-rise-q1-profit-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBKQLOTNORKJLORLAUIIKPBIK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示德国中小企业2025年将削减人工智能投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项研究显示，尽管企业整体在人工智能应用上的支出正在增加，但德国中小企业（统称为"中坚企业"）正放缓对人工智能的投资。【原文：Germany's small and medium-sized companies, collectively known as the Mittelstand, are putting the brakes on artificial intelligence investment, a study showed, even as overall corporate spending on AI applications rises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/germanys-mittelstand-cuts-ai-investments-2025-study-shows-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6QCAZU5ZJKZVE2IZ75Q72LUFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OVHcloud报告第一季度实现6%的有机增长，并确认全年业绩指引]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国云计算公司OVHcloud周四公布，受公有云业务强劲表现推动，其第一季度营收实现6%的有机增长，并重申了2026财年全年业绩指引。【原文：French cloud computing company OVHcloud on Thursday reported a 6% organic rise in its first-quarter revenue, driven by a strong performance in its Public Cloud business, and reiterated its full-year 2026 guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ovhcloud-reports-6-organic-growth-q1-confirms-annual-guidance-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIYGEZUMVRJWLCAVUCWCE4YEI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:06:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称英伟达要求中国客户全额预付H200芯片款项]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，英伟达要求中国客户全额预付购买其H200人工智能芯片的货款，以此规避北京方面是否批准这些芯片出货的不确定性。【原文：Nvidia is requiring full upfront payment from Chinese customers seeking its H200 artificial intelligence chips, hedging it against ongoing uncertainty over Beijing's approval of the shipments, said two people briefed on the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-requires-full-upfront-payment-h200-chips-china-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZICLAX5PFM3VK432UNCFGSY3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间要闻：特朗普豪言壮语遭投资者冷遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四欧洲及全球市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Thursday】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5EKAP5LWFMPXDRBT7OH3MA4NA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度顶级IT企业因美国需求疲软、客户支出减少，预计将迎来又一个业绩低迷的季度]]></title><description><![CDATA[九家券商在财报发布前表示，由于美国需求疲软以及假期期间客户停工，科技支出持续承压，印度信息技术公司预计将再次公布表现平淡的季度业绩。【原文：India's information technology firms are expected to report another muted quarter, as tepid demand in the U.S. and holiday-period client shutdowns continue to weigh on tech spending, nine brokerages said ahead of earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-top-it-firms-set-another-tepid-quarter-weak-us-demand-client-spending-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYOP522GUNPPZKEXUXLOIHXIHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:15:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普称人工智能将推动2040年前铜需求增长50%，但需增开矿山保障供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[咨询公司标普全球周四表示，人工智能和国防领域的发展将推动全球铜需求在2040年前增长50%，但若不加强回收和开采，预计每年供应缺口将超过1000万吨。【原文：Growth in the artificial intelligence and defense sectors will boost global copper demand 50% by 2040, but supplies are expected to fall short by more than 10 million metric tons annually without more recycling and mining, the consultancy S&amp;P Global said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ai-boost-copper-demand-50-by-2040-more-mines-needed-ensure-supply-sp-says-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUMS6Y7JK5KGRHHLQ77K45GZ24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价回升，股市震荡，投资者权衡地缘政治与美国数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在周四近期下跌后趋稳，而股市则开局震荡，因投资者正评估地缘政治紧张局势加剧及美国就业数据喜忧参半所带来的影响。【原文：Oil prices steadied on Thursday after their recent slide, while stocks were off to a rocky start as investors assessed the implications of deepening geopolitical tensions and mixed U.S. labour market data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPGLESYISRM2PETO5M7YVBAPT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:19:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以智浦人工智能为首的中国科技公司在香港上市首日股价攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[三家中国科技公司周四上市首日股价均报高开，此前它们合计募资93亿港元（11.9亿美元），为投资者期待的香港新股上市更活跃的一年定下基调。【原文：Three Chinese technology firms debuted higher on Thursday after raising a combined HK$9.3 billion ($1.19 billion), setting the tone for what investors hope will be a busier year for new listings in Hong Kong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinese-tech-companies-led-by-zhipu-ai-climb-hong-kong-debut-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SFW476BKJKVHE2HAGJD2A6PCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:13:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院裁定特朗普政府不得推进药品回扣试点计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦上诉法院周三叫停了特朗普政府的一项计划，该计划要求为低收入美国人提供服务的医院，在接受医保药品价格谈判的首批10种高价药品上预先支付全额费用，并等待后续返利。【原文：A federal appeals court on Wednesday blocked a Trump administration plan to require hospitals serving low-income Americans to pay full price upfront for the first 10 costly medications that are subject to Medicare drug price negotiations and wait for rebates later.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-cannot-proceed-with-pilot-drug-rebate-program-us-court-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFZQRQ3BBFIVHE7MBNJWYQH33Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>