<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:45:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:45:54 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[奢侈品破损的审计系统内幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，路威酩轩集团（LVMH）旗下迪奥在意大利的生产部门迪奥制造公司（Manufactures Dior）依靠正式检查来评估供应链内部的工作和安全标准。路透社对未公开的法庭文件进行审查后发现，在某些情况下，这些认证漏掉了明显的问题。【原文：LVMH-owned Dior's production arm in Italy, Manufactures Dior, relied on formal inspections to assess working and safety standards inside its supply chain last year. In some cases, such certifications missed glaring problems, a Reuters review of unpublished court documents has found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/inside-luxury-goods-broken-audit-system-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBX35A24ZBM5VEQE7PMKQHPZL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国家主席习近平承诺在 2025 年实施更加积极的经济政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家主席习近平周二在新年致辞中表示，中国2024年的国内生产总值（GDP）预计将超过130万亿元人民币（合17.8万亿美元），并表示中国将在2025年实施更加积极的政策来促进经济增长。【原文：China's 2024 gross domestic product (GDP) is expected to exceed 130 trillion yuan ($17.8 trillion), President Xi Jinping said on Tuesday in his New Year's address, adding that the country would implement more proactive policies to promote growth in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-xi-pledges-more-proactive-economic-policies-2025-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JRTR5FXGJI73GQICOWHSIDSS4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:11:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制药商将从 1 月 1 日起提高美国 250 多种药品的价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[据医疗保健研究公司3 Axis Advisors分析的数据显示，制药商计划在2025年初提高美国至少250种品牌药物的价格，其中包括辉瑞公司的COVID-19治疗药物Paxlovid、百时美施贵宝公司的癌细胞疗法和法国赛诺菲公司的疫苗。【原文：Drugmakers plan to raise U.S. prices on at least 250 branded medications including Pfizer COVID-19 treatment Paxlovid, Bristol Myers Squibb's cancer cell therapies and vaccines from France's Sanofi at the start of 2025, according to data analyzed by healthcare research firm 3 Axis Advisors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drugmakers-raise-us-prices-over-250-medicines-starting-jan-1-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNSNEBUYXBLMPJGH365NV2MBGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能蓬勃发展、美联储降息使美股在 2024 年创下新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货在 2024 年的最后一个交易日走高，延续了两年多前的牛市走势，原因是有迹象表明大流行后的经济具有韧性，借贷成本有望降低，人工智能得到提振。【原文：U.S. stocks index futures edged higher in the last trading session of 2024, continuing its bull run from more than two years ago on signs of post-pandemic economic resilience, hopes of lower borrowing costs and AI boost.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ai-boom-fed-rate-cuts-lift-us-stocks-new-highs-2024-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEU5RNO4XVOTHGQZMKOEAUICUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 11:38:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应充足、需求放缓将抑制 2025 年油价涨势：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二进行的一项月度民意调查显示，由于中国需求疲软和全球供应增加预计将给欧佩克+领导的支撑市场的努力蒙上阴影，2025年油价可能会被限制在每桶70美元附近。【原文：Oil prices are likely to be constrained near $70 a barrel in 2025 as weak demand from China and rising global supplies are expected to cast a shadow on OPEC+-led efforts to shore up the market, a Reuters monthly poll showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ample-supply-slow-demand-temper-oil-price-gains-2025-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JZL4YTRYJLR7EH5436GAQBY5A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 11:05:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场监管机构称特斯拉将修复 77650 辆中国制造汽车的软件问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周二表示，特斯拉将修复77650辆中国产Model 3和Model Y汽车存在安全隐患的软件。【原文：Tesla will fix software in 77,650 China-made Model 3 and Model Y cars over safety hazards, China's market regulator said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-fix-software-77650-china-made-vehicles-says-market-regulator-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7INS7AP35JAZIWCFDHJJRNAZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 09:32:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国股市自 2020 年以来首次实现年度上涨，香港股市结束四年颓势]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管在 2024 年的最后一个交易日出现了下跌，但中国股市在经历了前所未有的三年下跌后首次录得年度涨幅，而香港股市则在政策支持的乐观情绪支撑下在年底走高。【原文：Chinese stocks registered their first annual gain following an unprecedented three-year decline despite a dip on the final trading day of 2024, while Hong Kong shares ended the year higher, supported by optimism over policy support.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-stocks-post-first-annual-gain-since-2020-hk-ends-4-year-rout-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWMZP5J5YJLX5AA4HE4KBLQCHY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 08:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威兹航空公司称，由于发动机故障，40 架飞机将停飞至 2026 财年]]></title><description><![CDATA[威兹航空公司（Wizz Air）周二表示，在发动机出现问题的情况下，该公司已与国防和航空航天公司 RTX 旗下的普拉特-惠特尼公司（Pratt &amp; Whitney）签署了一项新的支持协议，并补充说，预计该公司的 40 架飞机将停飞至 2026 财年。【原文：Wizz Air on Tuesday said it had signed a new support agreement with defence and aerospace firm RTX's Pratt &amp; Whitney amid engine woes, adding that it expects 40 of its planes to stay grounded through fiscal year 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/wizz-air-says-40-planes-stay-grounded-through-fiscal-2026-amid-engine-woes-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNFYLK4QZVOZPL5WOF6VXHPY2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 08:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亨索特公司老板敦促德国将国内生产总值的 3% 用于国防开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，德国国防电子产品专业公司 Hensoldt 的首席执行官被引述说，德国应承诺将国防开支增加到相当于国内生产总值的 3%。【原文：Germany should commit to increasing its defence spending to a sum equivalent to 3% of gross domestic product, the chief executive officer of defence electronics specialist Hensoldt was quoted as saying on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/hensoldt-boss-urges-germany-spend-3-gdp-defence-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4SSK2KTXNLIBBPQOW3FGY4VX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 08:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴云计算部门宣布大语言机型大幅降价]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴云计算部门周二表示，将对其大型语言机型降价高达 85%。【原文：Alibaba's cloud unit said on Tuesday it was cutting prices by up to 85% on its large language models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alibabas-cloud-unit-announces-big-price-cuts-large-language-models-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KXQDGBS4NNH3PEHZXQ6FNJB6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 07:49:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国媒称中国习近平预计 2024 年国内生产总值增长 5%左右]]></title><description><![CDATA[据国家媒体报道，中国国家主席习近平周二表示，2024 年中国国内生产总值预计将增长 5%左右。【原文：China's gross domestic product is expected to grow by around 5% in 2024, President Xi Jinping said on Tuesday, state media reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-xi-expects-2024-gdp-growth-around-5-state-media-says-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64NKEFLAUBLXBOXU3XJKY6EMVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 06:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北京发布促进无人驾驶汽车在首都使用的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国首都北京周二通过了鼓励城市自动驾驶技术的新法规，当局计划最终允许公共汽车和出租车采用无人驾驶技术。【原文：China's capital Beijing passed new regulations on Tuesday to encourage autonomous driving technology in the city, with authorities planning to eventually allow driverless public buses and taxis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/beijing-unveils-plans-boost-driverless-vehicle-use-capital-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BZHS3EETJMAPLSNV2YQCKWPFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 05:19:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可可连续两年位居全球大宗商品涨幅榜首，钢铁配料因中国需求而举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球供应短缺，可可和咖啡将在 2024 年结束时连续第二年成为大宗商品中涨幅最大的品种，而炼钢用煤炭由于受到中国经济增长放缓的影响，将成为表现最差的品种。【原文：Cocoa and coffee are poised to close 2024 as the biggest gainers among commodities for a second year on a global supply deficit, while steel-making coal will end as the worst performer, hit by slow growth in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/cocoa-tops-global-commodities-rally-2nd-year-steel-ingredients-struggle-china-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IIGKYEOU5IJZPI5C3UAL4GUIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 05:19:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市和美元坚挺，2024 年强劲收官]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市在谨慎的年末交易中有所回落，投资者缩减了对美国在2025年大幅降息的押注，并为即将上任的特朗普政府做好准备，美元兑大多数其他货币保持高位。【原文：Asian stocks eased on Tuesday in cautious end-of-year trading that has seen investors scale back bets of deep U.S. rate cuts in 2025 and brace for the incoming Trump administration, with the dollar standing tall against most other currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WIU6I6U65O7LI4MAZOVYD72ZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 03:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金有望迎来十多年来最好的一年]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二是多事之秋的最后一个交易日，金价变化不大。【原文：Gold prices were little changed on Tuesday, the last trading day of an eventful year that saw the metal post its best annual performance in more than a decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-track-best-year-over-decade-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AB3ARFQWNM3NNZLVOYHPYNTDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易风险上升，中国 12 月工厂活动增速放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项官方工厂调查显示，12月份中国制造业活动连续第三个月实现增长，但增长乏力，这表明在新的贸易风险隐现之际，政策刺激的效果可能需要更多时间来提供支持。【原文：China's manufacturing activity grew for a third straight month in December but barely, an official factory survey showed on Tuesday, suggesting the effects of policy stimulus may take more time to lend support as fresh trade risks loom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-dec-factory-activity-expands-slower-pace-trade-risks-rise-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCTDYZS7XJKBFM6YAQE6FQVSWA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油因中国工厂活动扩大而上涨，但年底将走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，油价在数据显示中国12月制造业活动扩张后上涨，但由于主要消费国的需求担忧，油价将连续第二年收低。【原文：Oil prices rose in early trade on Tuesday after data showed China's manufacturing activity expanded in December, but for a second consecutive year oil was on track to end lower due to demand concerns in top consuming countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-expanding-chinese-factory-activity-set-end-year-lower-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUQT47URGVIHNKHC5A63RZHZX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 12 月制造业活动连续第三个月扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项官方工厂调查显示，中国的制造业活动在 12 月份连续第三个月扩张，但速度有所放缓，这表明新一轮刺激措施正在帮助支撑世界第二大经济体。【原文：China's manufacturing activity expanded for a third straight month in December but at a slower pace, an official factory survey showed on Tuesday, suggesting a blitz of fresh stimulus is helping to support the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-dec-manufacturing-activity-expands-third-month-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCSUBOGBKZIPRCKRL6NPL2JCCU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 01:41:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谨慎的美联储和特朗普贸易支撑美元在 2024 年屹立不倒]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元在今年的最后一个交易日表现坚挺，2024 年美元对大多数货币都将强劲上涨，因为投资者对美国降息次数减少和即将上任的特朗普政府的政策做好了准备。【原文：The dollar was firm on the last trading day of the year, poised to clock strong gains in 2024 against most currencies as investors prepared for fewer U.S. rate cuts and the incoming Trump administration's policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-stands-tall-2024-propped-up-by-cautious-fed-trump-trade-2024-12-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5PYEYKQTVJGBKIMJU6VQYTLT4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 01:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州州长向监管机构投诉 PJM 电力市场规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州州长乔希-夏皮罗（Josh Shapiro）周一向联邦能源监管机构提交了一份针对 PJM Interconnection 的投诉，认为这家美国最大的电网运营商必须改变其市场规则，否则将面临电力成本飙升的风险。【原文：Pennsylvania Governor Josh Shapiro filed a complaint with a federal energy regulator against PJM Interconnection on Monday, arguing that the largest U.S. power grid operator must change its market rules or risk soaring electricity costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pennsylvania-governor-complains-regulator-about-pjms-power-market-rules-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5E2DLQWQVOUPOLNN3FEZKF2TE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 23:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行监管机构要求贝莱德在一月内解决银行股权问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国联邦存款保险公司已通知资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock）在 1 月 10 日之前接受一项协议，该协议将允许该机构加强对其在联邦存款保险公司监管下的银行机构投资的审查。【原文：The U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation has told asset manager BlackRock it has until Jan. 10 to accept an agreement that would allow the agency to step up scrutiny of its investments in FDIC-regulated banking institutions, according to a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-regulator-gives-blackrock-january-deadline-bank-stakes-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OF4WVW537RI2JIKTO4YUY5S2XU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 22:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[淡水河谷与巴西当局就铁路特许经营权达成 18 亿美元协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷在一份证券文件中称，该公司周一与地方当局达成协议，将支付高达 110 亿雷亚尔（约合 17.8 亿美元）的费用，以重新谈判两项铁路特许经营权的合同。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale said on Monday it reached an agreement with local authorities under which it would pay up to 11 billion reais ($1.78 billion) to renegotiate the contracts of two railway concessions, the firm said in a securities filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/vale-reaches-18-bln-agreement-with-brazil-authorities-over-railway-concessions-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2FDDBCHIFIAVN4A67AOFAGECA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对金融科技应用戴夫及其首席执行官提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周一对金融科技公司 Dave Inc 及其首席执行官 Jason Wilk 提起诉讼，并宣布对其采取民事强制措施，指控其违反联邦法律。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department filed a complaint and announced a civil enforcement action on Monday against financial technology company Dave Inc and its CEO Jason Wilk for alleged violations of federal law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-announces-civil-enforcement-action-against-fintech-app-dave-its-ceo-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZ4ORVPI3BN2NEHAHI2PC7XYGY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:32:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[刑事调查仍在继续，ADM 股东要求首席执行官辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[Archer-Daniels-Midland 公司的一名股东正在敦促该公司首席执行官辞职，因为他没有明确告诉投资者该公司内部会计做法存在问题，而路透社首先报道了这一问题引发的刑事调查。【原文：A shareholder of Archer-Daniels-Midland is pressing the company's CEO to resign for failing to clearly tell investors about problems with its internal accounting practices that have sparked a criminal investigation first reported by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/adm-shareholder-presses-ceo-resign-criminal-probe-continues-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5RML6BYUJNTBGZ2UYTSF7DF2U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:25:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citgo 股票拍卖案法官驳回阻止 Gramercy 基金诉讼的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法官在周一发布的一项命令中裁定，三家公司为增加在 Citgo 石油公司母公司股份拍卖中获得收益的机会而提起的诉讼可以继续进行。【原文：Lawsuits by three firms seeking to improve their chances of obtaining proceeds in an auction of shares in Citgo Petroleum's parent can go ahead, a U.S. judge ruled in an order issued on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-citgo-share-auction-rejects-bid-block-gramercy-fund-lawsuits-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OV2SRMWOZJPKNEN7VMPNCAXPDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[李-哈斯勒特-陈将辞去华纳兄弟探索公司董事会职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司周一在一份监管文件中披露，该公司董事会成员兼提名与公司治理委员会成员 Li Haslett Chen 将于 2025 年 1 月 31 日辞职。【原文：Li Haslett Chen, a member of the Warner Bros. Discovery board and a member of the company's Nominating and Corporate Governance Committee, will resign from her positions, effective Jan. 31, 2025, the company disclosed in a regulatory filing on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/li-haslett-chen-resign-warner-bros-discovery-board-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGD3MYBEDNJHDKM66VGMRYZCTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府基金完成对麦道夫的赔付，麦道夫受害者获赔 43 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府赔偿受麦道夫诈骗者的基金周一宣布了第十次也是最后一次分配，称将向已故庞氏骗局受害者中的 40,930 人支付 43 亿美元。【原文：A U.S. government fund to compensate people swindled by Bernard Madoff announced its tenth and final distribution on Monday, saying it will have paid out $4.3 billion to 40,930 of the late Ponzi schemer's victims.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bernard-madoffs-victims-collect-43-billion-us-government-fund-completes-payouts-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72JYWHSP6RNUBPDIE3ZOE5CFIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部称中国黑客在 "重大事件 "中窃取文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周一获得的一封致立法者的信称，中国国家支持的黑客本月早些时候入侵了美国财政部，并从其工作站中窃取了文件。【原文：Chinese state-sponsored hackers broke into the U.S. Treasury Department earlier this month and stole documents from its workstations, according to a letter to lawmakers that was provided to Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-treasurys-workstations-hacked-cyberattack-by-china-afp-reports-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGAS2OE6JBMDXP2KNXDIVSC4VY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比尔-阿克曼期待特朗普将房利美和房地美私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[这位亿万富翁投资者周一表示，比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）预计美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将解除对房利美（Fannie Mae）和房地美（Freddie Mac）的监管，使其有可能重新成为私营公司。【原文：Bill Ackman expects U.S. President-elect Donald Trump to remove Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac from conservatorship, potentially making them private companies again, the billionaire investor said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bill-ackman-expects-trump-privatize-fannie-mae-freddie-mac-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YHFZL4MABI2NHGNDCFKMSRQJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:14:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国新成立的空中出租车公司 Volocopter 申请破产]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中出租车初创公司 Volocopter GmbH 周一申请破产程序，理由是无力筹集新资金以维持正常运营。【原文：Air taxi start-up Volocopter GmbH filed for insolvency proceedings on Monday, citing its inability to raise new funds to maintain regular operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/german-air-taxi-start-up-volocopter-files-insolvency-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MTKEKD2SBMNVKIAFMWYF4L3YU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 19:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>