<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 20:05:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 20:05:12 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[食品配送公司 Grubhub 将裁员 500 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[Grubhub 首席执行官周五表示，这家食品外卖公司已决定裁员约 500 人。【原文：Grubhub's CEO said on Friday that the food delivery firm has decided to lay off about 500 positions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/food-delivery-company-grubhub-lay-off-500-positions-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TT6PMH46NZP7PKTDEZG6ZVXXLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 19:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与泽伦斯基的冲突加剧市场紧张情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员说，乌克兰总统沃洛德梅尔-泽连斯基（Volodymyr Zelenskiy）在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）进行了有争议的椭圆形办公室会晤后，将于周五提前离开白宫。【原文：Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy is leaving the White House early on Friday after a contentious Oval Office meeting with President Donald Trump, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/view-trump-zelenskiy-clash-adds-market-nervousness-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7OEFF4DRVKVVG2NY756E4FWIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 19:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊的 Wondery 播客部门裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周五在给路透社的一份声明中说，亚马逊在其 Wondery 播客部门裁减了 "少量 "工作岗位，该部门以 "死亡博士 "和 "商战 "而闻名。【原文：Amazon cut "a small number" of jobs at its Wondery podcast unit, known for "Dr. Death" and "Business Wars," the company said in a statement to Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazons-wondery-podcast-unit-trims-jobs-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIMTN3FWOZK5DIVGBKUWERJNRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商连续第五周增加石油和天然气钻井平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第五周增加石油和天然气钻机，这是自2022年5月以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week added oil and natural gas rigs for a fifth week in a row for the first time since May 2022, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-add-oil-gas-rigs-fifth-week-row-baker-hughes-says-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5KQSDQLHFM25ESDWRKHRXSSXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:14:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国在首例未注册加密资产案中对个人判刑]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融监管机构周五表示，已对英国首例涉及未注册加密资产活动的案件做出四年监禁的判决。【原文：Britain's financial watchdog said on Friday a four-year prison sentence has been issued in the UK's first case involving unregistered cryptoasset activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-sentences-individual-first-unregistered-cryptoasset-case-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NS7RRYSNHZJARE4GBFWRDJ2WDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:28:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业组织敦促尽快采用有利于大科技公司的欧盟网络安全标签]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲 23 个行业组织敦促欧盟技术负责人亨娜-维尔库宁（Henna Virkkunnen）通过一项云服务网络安全认证计划（EUCS）草案，该草案去年经过调整，有利于亚马逊、Alphabet 旗下的谷歌和微软。【原文：Twenty-three industry groups across Europe have urged EU tech chief Henna Virkkunnen to adopt a draft cybersecurity certification scheme (EUCS) for cloud services that was tweaked last year in favour of Amazon , Alphabet's Google and Microsoft .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/industry-groups-urge-quick-adoption-eu-cybersecurity-label-that-favours-big-tech-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHJBWRUAORKD5CW6P4UEL4GV7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局批准 SpaceX 星际飞船 8 号在事故后发射]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周五表示，在对1月16日的星际飞船7号航班事故进行调查期间，已批准SpaceX公司的星际飞船返回飞行作业。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said Friday it has cleared the SpaceX Starship vehicle to return to flight operations while an investigation into the Jan. 16 Starship Flight 7 mishap remains open.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/faa-oks-spacex-starship-flight-8-launch-after-mishap-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBYDXQRETFPFDIUMZIGPZH2ZCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达飞海运称美国对中国船只征收港口费将影响所有航运公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部设在法国的达飞海运公司（CMA CGM）周五表示，美国向中国船只征收高额港口费的提议将对集装箱航运业的所有公司产生重大影响，因为该行业的大部分船只都是在中国建造的。【原文：U.S. proposals to hit Chinese vessels with high port fees would have a major impact on all firms in a container shipping industry in which most vessels are built in China, French-based shipping firm CMA CGM said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-port-fees-china-vessels-would-affect-all-shipping-firms-cma-cgm-says-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RQ4M3ZNW5LQRADWUHSUTQN3QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[硅谷银行前母公司可提起 19.3 亿美元的联邦存款保险公司诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官裁定，硅谷银行的前母公司可以提起诉讼，追回联邦存款保险公司在该银行 2023 年 3 月倒闭后扣押的 19.3 亿美元存款。【原文：Silicon Valley Bank's former parent may pursue a lawsuit to recover $1.93 billion of deposits that the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp seized following the bank's March 2023 collapse, a federal judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/silicon-valley-banks-former-parent-can-pursue-193-billion-fdic-lawsuit-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQXVOK6QYZOCZDKV2WU746L5JU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:56:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即使在特朗普达成协议之后，乌克兰仍将面临漫长的不确定采矿业繁荣之路]]></title><description><![CDATA[在乌克兰中部白雪皑皑的田野上，一小队生态顾问将传感器放入地洞，测量水位。【原文：On snow-covered fields in central Ukraine, where some of the country's biggest proven lithium deposits are located, a small team of ecological consultants drop sensors into holes in the earth to measure water levels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/even-after-trump-deal-ukraine-faces-long-uncertain-road-mining-boom-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LW46ZFFEO5MSROBCC44HANMUGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:39:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大大型银行在渥太华推动改革以应对关税风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大的大型银行首席执行官们正在敦促联邦政府消除内部贸易壁垒、评估税收政策和其他监管措施，因为加拿大的顶级贷款机构警告说，关税和贸易风险正在给经济前景蒙上阴影。【原文：Canada's big bank CEOs are urging the federal government to remove internal trade barriers, evaluate tax policies and other regulation as the country's top lenders cautioned that tariff and trade risks are clouding the economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadas-big-banks-push-reforms-ottawa-confront-tariff-risks-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4FHR3KZTBOUVFXGYMPLEIXMQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:24:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，英特尔将耗资 280 亿美元的俄亥俄州芯片工厂推迟至 2030 年建成]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体 The Columbus Dispatch 周五报道，英特尔承诺在俄亥俄州投资 280 亿美元建设的芯片制造厂正面临进一步的延期，位于新奥尔巴尼的第一座工厂预计要到 2030 年才能完工。【原文：Intel's promised $28 billion chip fabrication plants in Ohio are facing further delays, with the first factory in New Albany expected to not be completed until 2030, local media outlet The Columbus Dispatch reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-delays-28-billion-ohio-chip-factory-2030-local-media-reports-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B32DZ2SJTJP3JMZUQHJJTXYLD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普拟征收汽车关税影响铂族金属需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，如果唐纳德-特朗普总统对美国进口汽车征收关税的提议抑制了汽车销售，那么工业贵金属铂金和钯金的需求可能会下降。【原文：Demand for industrial precious metals platinum and palladium will likely fall if tariffs proposed by President Donald Trump on U.S. auto imports dampen vehicle sales, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-proposed-auto-tariffs-seen-hitting-demand-platinum-group-metals-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5SDVZQZKBKHNMONAUPCKWKMTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CME 集团计划于 3 月 17 日推出索拉纳期货]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥商品交易所集团（CME Group）周五表示，该公司计划于 3 月 17 日推出加密货币索拉纳的期货合约，但还需等待监管部门的审查。【原文：CME Group said on Friday that it plans to roll out futures contracts on cryptocurrency Solana on March 17, pending regulatory review.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cme-group-plans-launch-solana-futures-march-17-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBT33AOW6FIONF2YTUHU2MPH7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将提议推动提高电动汽车需求，要求增加本地电池数量]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份提案草案，欧盟委员会将于下周提出旨在促进欧盟电动汽车（EV）需求的措施，并设想了汽车电池生产的本地含量要求。【原文：The European Commission will present measures next week meant to boost demand for electric vehicles (EVs) in the European Union, and envisages local content requirements for car battery production, according to a draft of the proposals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-propose-push-boost-ev-demand-require-more-local-batteries-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRZD6W44WFMNZP2PNPVCOWEXXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道在美国政府财政不确定的情况下，美联储哈马克着眼于稳步削减资产负债表]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）认为，在政府财政状况不明朗的时期，美国央行可以继续稳步缩减资产负债表，同时她还指出，即使通胀压力没有迅速消退，她也不倾向于支持加息。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack reckons the U.S. central bank can keep steadily shrinking its balance sheet through a period of uncertain government finances, while noting she is disinclined to support an interest rate hike even if inflation pressures do not retreat quickly enough.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-hammack-eyes-steady-balance-sheet-cuts-amid-us-government-financial-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OI55SXZWENIDJKGHZUJIAW2I5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软优先考虑团队，Skype 最后一次通话将于五月举行]]></title><description><![CDATA[Skype 将于 5 月 5 日最后一次响铃，因为其所有者微软公司将退出这项拥有二十年历史的互联网通话服务。【原文：Skype will ring for the last time on May 5 as owner Microsoft retires the two-decade-old internet calling service that redefined how people connect across borders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/skypes-final-call-set-may-microsoft-prioritizes-teams-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMCHB4LHMVJJ7K7NYVMCVSE7B4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 1 月 PCE 通胀不意外，同比降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五公布的数据显示，美国1月份个人消费支出（PCE）价格指数增长0.3%，而12月份的增幅为0.3%，未作修正。经济学家此前预计PCE物价指数将上升0.3%。在截至1月份的一年中，物价上涨了2.5%，而12月份则上涨了2.6%。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department's Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) price index increased 0.3% in January after advancing by an unrevised 0.3% in December, data showed on Friday. Economists had expected the PCE price index to climb 0.3%. In the year through January, prices rose 2.5% after increasing 2.6% in December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-january-pce-inflation-no-surprise-cools-year-year-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57EVNLHEHBIBPDODSTR6ML3X74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月份商品贸易逆差大幅扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 1 月份的货物贸易逆差急剧扩大，这很可能是因为企业在加征关税之前提前进口货物，从而可能使贸易拖累第一季度的经济增长。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit in goods widened sharply in January, most likely as businesses front-loaded imports ahead of tariffs, potentially positioning trade to be a drag on economic growth in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-goods-trade-deficit-widens-sharply-january-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YC3XKPMQSVJIVJLNZ7XHC27BHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀数据公布后，交易员继续押注美联储 6 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，按美联储政策利率结算的期货合约交易商继续押注美国央行将在6月重启短期借贷利率下调，因为数据显示1月份通胀率升幅符合预期。【原文：Traders of futures contracts that settle to the Federal Reserve's policy rate maintained bets on Friday that the U.S. central bank will restart cuts to short-term borrowing rates in June after data showed inflation rose in line with expectations in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-keep-bets-fed-rate-cut-june-after-inflation-data-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7VGWJ3KYZIPPKDXD7DZHH5FA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:49:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月消费者支出下降；月通胀率上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 1 月份的消费支出意外下降，但通胀回升可能会为美联储推迟一段时间降息提供掩护。【原文：U.S. consumer spending unexpectedly fell in January, but a pick up in inflation could provide cover for the Federal Reserve to delay cutting interest rates for some time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-spending-falls-january-monthly-inflation-rises-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZOIJNZTYVNMNB6VC3MRFQFA7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:47:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大经济第四季度按年率计算意外增长 2.6]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，加拿大第四季度国内生产总值按年率计算增长了2.6%，超出了人们的普遍预期，原因是消费者支出、企业投资和出口的大幅增长拉动了经济增长。【原文：Canada's gross domestic product in the fourth quarter expanded by 2.6% on an annualized basis, surpassing widespread expectations, as a jump in consumer spending, business investments and exports lifted growth, data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadas-economy-posts-surprise-annualized-fourth-quarter-growth-26-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLEPZBETHROPROGRBEEDCZQGDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯谢韦尔钢铁公司警告：该地区禁止外来劳工，建筑业面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯钢铁制造商谢韦尔钢铁公司（Severstal）周五抨击了一位州长禁止农民工从事建筑业的决定，并称此举可能对工业项目造成严重损害。【原文：Russian steelmaker Severstal on Friday slammed a decision by a regional governor to ban migrant workers in the construction industry and said the move could cause serious harm to industrial projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russias-severstal-warns-construction-risks-region-bans-migrant-labour-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A65LOB4MNNI73AFJAEW2FDP4FY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚 Capital A 公司因外汇损失转为年度亏损，预计 2025 年实现盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚廉价航空公司亚航（AirAsia）的所有者 Capital A Berhad 公司周五出现年度亏损，主要原因是外汇损失，但该公司表示今年将恢复盈利。【原文：Malaysia's Capital A Berhad , owner of budget airline AirAsia, swung to an annual loss on Friday due mainly to foreign exchange losses, but the company said it would return to profitability this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/malaysias-capital-swings-annual-loss-forex-losses-expects-profitability-2025-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKHH5KUA6RK2ZF2GYRTIYVCQPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管存在关税担忧，美国股票基金仍获得大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至2月26日的一周内，投资者增持了美国股票基金，原因是他们对经济的韧性充满信心，并预期美联储将在今年晚些时候降息以刺激经济增长。【原文：Investors increased their holdings in U.S. equity funds over the week to February 26, buoyed by confidence in the economy's resilience and expectations of a Federal Reserve rate cut later this year to stimulate growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-gain-sharp-inflows-despite-tariff-concerns-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TMCFULJJZLPPONVBHJJ3HSONA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 获得 4.5 亿美元贷款，推迟发布季度财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 周五表示，该公司已获得一笔为期 12 个月的贷款，金额高达 4.5 亿美元，并将把第四季度业绩推迟到四月份，同时提交 2024 财年的年度文件。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Polestar has secured a 12-month loan facility of up to $450 million, it said on Friday, and would delay its fourth-quarter results to April along with its annual filing for fiscal 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestar-secures-450-million-loan-facility-delays-quarterly-results-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADZQKJPLPVMKXO5AHOOWNFR2ME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利法院解除对 LVMH 旗下迪奥意大利分公司涉嫌劳工行为的管制]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，意大利一家法院宣布提前结束对法国奢侈品巨头路威酩轩集团（LVMH）旗下一家意大利子公司的特别管理制度，该子公司被指控在生产迪奥（Dior）品牌手袋的过程中存在剥削劳工的行为。【原文：An Italian court on Friday announced the early end of a special administration regime placed on an Italian subsidiary of French luxury giant LVMH over allegations of labour exploitation in the manufacturing of Dior-branded handbags.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/italy-court-lifts-controls-lvmhs-dior-italian-unit-over-alleged-labour-practices-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWXL4VMOHBK67AHNDYGEV4ACSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:53:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[今年美国住房的可负担性将有所提高，但主要原因是利率降低：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对房地产市场专家进行的调查显示，未来一年美国房地产市场的可负担性将略有改善，这主要是基于对再次降息的预期，而非可购买房屋数量的增加。【原文：Affordability in the U.S. housing market will improve modestly in the coming year, according to property market experts polled by Reuters, based on expectations for a few more interest rate cuts, not an increase in homes available to purchase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-housing-get-bit-more-affordable-this-year-mainly-due-lower-rates-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFFSTEBQ3NJ3NKXGRJ4EQBZCGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:42:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战担忧加剧，美国标普500指数2025年收红]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7N6UMDM22RJI3KVI5ZXLDJOXBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大牧场主因担心特朗普征收关税而缩减牛群，牛肉价格可能上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普当选后，加拿大农民乔恩-瓦格斯（Jon Vaags）于 11 月放弃购买肉牛，因为对加拿大出口产品征收关税似乎是一个严重的风险。【原文：Canadian farmer Jon Vaags quit buying beef cattle in November after the election of U.S. President Donald Trump made tariffs on Canadian exports seem like a serious risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/beef-prices-may-rise-canadian-ranchers-shrink-cattle-herds-fearing-trump-tariffs-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3WH3NSDFBIXFJ5UMFKLIDFSTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>