<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:39:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:39:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[先锋集团新任首席执行官关注固定收益产品的拓展]]></title><description><![CDATA[先锋集团（Vanguard）新任总裁萨利姆-拉姆吉（Salim Ramji）周三表示，考虑到市场规模和机遇，他计划扩大这家美国顶级资产管理公司的固定收益产品。【原文：Vanguard's new chief, Salim Ramji, said on Wednesday that he plans to expand the fixed income offering of the U.S. top asset manager given the market's size and opportunities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/vanguards-new-ceo-eyes-fixed-income-offering-expansion-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALQE6NZDB5OLFBRYR5XZGNJ454</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 15:54:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司称仲裁委员会裁定新日铁 149 亿美元收购交易胜诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）周三表示，该公司与美国钢铁工人工会（United Steelworkers union）为解决双方争议而共同选定的仲裁委员会已作出裁决，支持新日铁 149 亿美元的收购交易。【原文：U.S. Steel said on Wednesday the board of arbitration, jointly selected by the steelmaker and the United Steelworkers union to settle disputes between them, has ruled in favor of Nippon Steel's $14.9 billion buyout deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-says-arbitration-board-rules-favor-nippon-steels-149-bln-buyout-deal-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVDOSX4U3FNAHHPNQOJYWSZ45M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 15:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会宣布打击欺骗性人工智能声明和计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）周三表示，它将对五家公司采取行动，称这些公司以欺骗性和不公平的方式使用人工智能。【原文：The Federal Trade Commission said on Wednesday it was taking action against five companies that it said used artificial intelligence in deceptive and unfair ways.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ftc-announces-crackdown-deceptive-ai-claims-schemes-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4SOOELCIZOYNESPDVZOGYS7QA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:48:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示美国大选风险打击企业投资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[近三分之一的公司财务总监表示，围绕11月5日美国总统大选的风险已导致他们推迟或缩减投资计划，这至少在短期内对经济增长是一个潜在的打击。【原文：Nearly a third of company financial officers say that risks around the Nov. 5 U.S. presidential election have caused them to delay or scale back investment plans, a potential blow at least in the short-term to economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-election-risk-hitting-corporate-investment-plans-survey-says-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSKZN6TSXROAPHULRIYD2IJOFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:37:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行业贸易组织称，全球债务达到创纪录的 312 万亿美元，气候融资是一项挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家银行业贸易集团的数据显示，受美国和中国借贷的推动，全球债务在第二季度末达到 312 万亿美元，创历史新高，而新兴市场的一个关键债务比率也达到了新的峰值。【原文：Global debt hit a record high of $312 trillion at the end of the second quarter, driven by borrowing in the United States and China, while a key debt ratio in emerging markets also scaled a fresh peak, data from a banking trade group showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-debt-hits-record-312-trillion-climate-finance-challenge-banking-trade-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOLAXFLC45MA5J3GSBIT6BLE5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美林证券、嘉实波动率管理公司将支付 930 万美元以了结美国证券交易委员会的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner &amp; Smith Inc. 和 Harvest Volatility Management LLC 已同意支付合计 930 万美元，以了结美国证券交易委员会有关投资限制和费用的指控。【原文：Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner &amp; Smith Inc. and Harvest Volatility Management LLC have agreed to pay a combined $9.3 million to settle U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charges related to investment limits and fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/merrill-lynch-harvest-volatility-management-pay-93-mln-settle-sec-charges-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4VTF55E4JKHXPL4ED6D53QTAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月新屋销售下降；房价中位数下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份美国新建独户住宅的销售量有所下降，但抵押贷款利率和房价的下降可能会刺激未来几个月的需求。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell in August, but declining mortgage rates and house prices could stimulate demand in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-august-median-house-price-drops-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DCAKJAGONNSNF427W5PC3IUGE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解释：加州称埃克森公司的回收索赔造成了 "公害"。这是什么意思？]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州周一提起诉讼，指控埃克森公司误导公众回收塑料垃圾的局限性，助长了全球塑料垃圾污染，这是最近一系列基于具有数百年历史的 "公害 "法律理论的案件中的最新一起。下面将介绍公害索赔的运作方式、此类索赔的结果以及它对加利福尼亚州的努力可能意味着什么。【原文：California's lawsuit on Monday accusing Exxon of fueling global plastic waste pollution by misleading the public about the limitations of recycling is the latest in a line of recent cases based on a centuries-old legal theory known as public nuisance. Here is a look at how public nuisance claims work, how such claims have fared and what it might mean for California's effort.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/california-says-exxons-recycling-claims-created-public-nuisance-what-does-that-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KU4AEDRHLBPPPDYYXZRYJJ2DQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国立法者寻求向畜牧业者支付费用，让他们采用更有利于气候的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据众议院和参议院周三提出的议案，美国大型工业化养殖牲畜的农民可以从乔-拜登总统签署的气候法中获得资金，以过渡到更环保的做法。【原文：Farmers in the United States who raise livestock in large industrial operations could get funding from President Joe Biden's signature climate law to transition to more environmentally friendly practices under bills introduced in the House and Senate on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/us-lawmakers-seek-pay-livestock-farmers-use-climate-friendlier-practices-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LBDPLKSHBKA5BCIBDAD5UDABU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:36:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，西南航空计划减少亚特兰大航线，裁员 300 多人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周三报道，西南航空公司计划明年减少往返亚特兰大的服务，并裁减 300 多个飞行员和空乘人员职位。【原文：Southwest Airlines plans to reduce service to and from Atlanta next year and cut more than 300 pilot and flight attendant positions, CNBC reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-plans-reduce-atlanta-service-cut-over-300-jobs-cnbc-reports-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWCUVPTO2VJ2HNMNDSPO4YQLUQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌就微软云计算做法向欧盟投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下公司谷歌（Google）周三向欧盟委员会（European Commission）提交了一份诉状，控诉微软将客户锁定在微软云平台 Azure 上的反竞争做法。【原文：Alphabet unit Google filed a complaint to the European Commission on Wednesday against what it said were Microsoft's anti-competitive practices to lock customers into Microsoft's cloud platform Azure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-files-complaint-eu-over-microsoft-cloud-practices-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AES3464ZARLMZATGUPFEAH46WQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于购物者债台高筑，美国 "先买后付 "的假日消费将创纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据数据公司 Adobe Analytics 周三发布的预测，今年最后一个季度，美国购物者使用第三方 "先买后付 "服务进行假日购物的花费预计将达到创纪录的 185 亿美元。【原文：U.S. shoppers are expected to spend a record $18.5 billion using third-party buy now, pay later services for holiday purchases in the last quarter of the year, according to projections by data firm Adobe Analytics released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-holiday-spending-buy-now-pay-later-hit-record-due-debt-laden-shoppers-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2SILX5UUJPWDFJBOPUK6O3K7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合信贷银行的姿态让德国中小型企业无所畏惧]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行（Commerzbank）表示，作为推动欧洲经济发展的中型企业 "Mittelstand "的主要贷款机构，该行有理由抵制联合信贷银行（UniCredit）的姿态。但 "中型企业 "的领导者们自己却不这么认为。【原文：Germany's Commerzbank says its role as a key lender to the swathe of "Mittelstand" midsize companies that drive Europe's top economy is grounds to resist UniCredit's overtures. But Mittelstand leaders themselves are less convinced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-overtures-hold-few-fears-germanys-mittelstand-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDYITK2BSVP6FAETYANE4TQ6SQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士称，印度要求泰米尔纳德邦介入三星工人罢工事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士周三称，印度联邦劳工部长要求南部泰米尔纳德邦解决三星电子工人长达数周的罢工问题。【原文：India's federal labour minister asked the southern state of Tamil Nadu to resolve a weeks-long strike by workers at Samsung Electronics , a government source said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-asks-tamil-nadu-state-find-resolution-samsung-workers-strike-govt-source-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHTBXLOHCJKCNKB6LM4O7TDW7U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:15:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国处于守势，联合信贷银行谈判获得一定支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国周三强烈反对意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）对德国商业银行（Commerzbank）的收购，与此同时，这家德国银行的一位大投资者也呼吁进行谈判，而这家意大利银行的首席执行官安德烈亚-奥塞尔（Andrea Orcel）正在寻求谈判。【原文：Germany cranked up its opposition on Wednesday to UniCredit's raid on Commerzbank at the same time as a big investor in the German lender called for talks, which are being sought by the Italian bank's CEO Andrea Orcel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/germany-turns-up-heat-while-unicredits-orcel-calls-commerzbank-talks-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQLYS2EU7JMPFAYCNVFULUPTOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:12:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期抵押贷款利率降至 6.13%，再融资跃升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国抵押贷款银行家协会（Mortgage Bankers Association）周三公布的数据显示，上周美国最受欢迎的住房贷款利率降至6.13%，创下约两年来的最低水平，再融资活动也大幅增加。【原文：The interest rate for the most popular U.S. home loan ticked down to 6.13% last week, the lowest in about two years, and refinancing activity jumped, data from the Mortgage Bankers Association showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-mortgage-rate-slips-613-refinancing-jumps-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBIKH6OMTRMFJDQKWOUJO25FRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克公司的结直肠癌疗法晚期试验失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司（Merck）周三表示，该公司的疗法没有达到在一种结直肠癌患者中进行评估的后期试验的主要目标。【原文：Merck said on Wednesday its therapy did not meet the main goal of a late-stage trial evaluating it in patients with a type of colorectal cancer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/mercks-colorectal-cancer-therapy-fails-late-stage-trial-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTAOLECUVFKKDMTGWOPKNUMFAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，8月份中国外资智能手机销量下降12.7]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家政府下属研究公司周三公布的数据显示，包括苹果公司 iPhone 在内的外国品牌智能手机 8 月份在中国的销量同比下降了 12.7%。【原文：Sales of foreign-branded smartphones, including Apple Inc's iPhone, in China fell 12.7% in August year-on-year, according to data released on Wednesday from a government-affiliated research firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/foreign-smartphone-sales-china-drop-127-august-data-show-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQOMLOPNSNNM5EALGP3WO3OKOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔出售更多美国银行股票，自 7 月以来净赚 90 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周二提交的最新文件显示，该公司抛售了更多的美国银行股票，自 7 月份以来共抛售了约 90 亿美元的股票。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway has offloaded more shares in Bank of America , its latest filing showed on Tuesday, raking in about $9 billion since July.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/berkshire-sells-more-bofa-shares-netting-9-bln-since-july-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WOIMU3PPVMLXPI3KJRM7GYHU4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:46:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司称南非正在洽谈购买 C-390 飞机事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周三表示，在第二次在非洲国家展示 C-390 千禧型军用货机之后，南非在可能购买该飞机的谈判中取得了进展。【原文：South Africa has advanced in talks for a potential purchase of Embraer's C-390 Millennium, the Brazilian planemaker said on Wednesday, after showcasing the military cargo aircraft in the African nation for the second time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/embraer-says-south-africa-talks-purchase-c-390-aircraft-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADHL7ABBNNI2HE5KJBKL5KVULA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待经济数据和美联储利率线索，期指下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周三下滑，投资者在等待有关经济健康状况和美联储一周前启动宽松政策周期后降息前景的更多线索时，避免了大举押注。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Wednesday, with investors avoiding big bets as they awaited more clues on the health of the economy and the outlook for interest rate cuts after the Federal Reserve kicked off its policy easing cycle a week ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-slip-investors-await-economic-data-fed-rate-clues-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EV4QITQ5ZJNZZMOP4SZK5GDBFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:32:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行首席财务官称美联储似乎正在赢得通胀之战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行首席财务官阿拉斯泰尔-博思威克（Alastair Borthwick）在周三的一次会议上表示，美联储似乎正在赢得美国的通胀之战。【原文：The Federal Reserve seems to be winning the inflation battle in the United States, Bank of America CFO Alastair Borthwick said at a conference on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bank-america-cfo-says-fed-seems-be-winning-inflation-battle-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBSYFQ73WFKKVPVGURLY3APA2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国信心动荡，中国受到鼓舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VNOWWG55NOHJMKJJB24OOE2J4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，Stellantis公司在美国召回15,000多辆菲亚特汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，由于软件错误可能导致前安全气囊在碰撞中过度展开，Stellantis公司将召回15,835辆菲亚特汽车。【原文：Stellantis is recalling 15,835 Fiat vehicles due to a software error that may cause the front airbags to deploy with excessive force in a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-recalls-over-15000-fiat-vehicles-us-nhtsa-says-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQNEL6ZIHRIWDPUZUETRXEPJTA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:10:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香蕉、汽车和服装：美国港口劳资纠纷威胁一系列产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月 1 日，美国东海岸和海湾地区的海港将有约 45,000 名工会工人失业，这将在美国总统大选前几周切断重要的贸易通道。【原文：Some 45,000 union workers could walk off the job at seaports on the U.S. East and Gulf Coasts on Oct 1, cutting off vital trade arteries just weeks ahead of the nation's presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bananas-cars-clothes-us-port-labor-dispute-threatens-range-products-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45BQBSRE6FIPJASLEFO5HQQ4KI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步与中国自动驾驶技术初创公司宣布合作在阿联酋推出机器人出租车]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步科技公司（Uber Technologies）和WeRide周三宣布建立合作关系，从阿联酋开始将中国自动驾驶技术公司的车辆引入优步的共享出行平台。【原文：Uber Technologies and WeRide announced a partnership on Wednesday to bring the Chinese self-driving technology firm's vehicles to the rideshare platform, starting in the United Arab Emirates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-chinese-self-driving-tech-startup-announce-partnership-launch-robotaxis-uae-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IO7MFLBIWZPYJAMMZQZYGY3RIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:08:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储大幅降息令美国债券市场重现 "通货再膨胀幽灵]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储积极启动宽松周期，重新点燃了美国债券市场对通胀的担忧，因为一些投资者担心宽松的金融条件可能会重新引发价格压力。【原文：The Federal Reserve's aggressive start of the easing cycle has rekindled inflation worries in the U.S. bond market, as some investors fear looser financial conditions could re-ignite price pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bumper-rate-cut-revives-reflation-specter-us-bond-market-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXCJSU5OQNODFP4P3GY2FCFD6E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：托运人在美国港口罢工威胁前争相寻求变通办法]]></title><description><![CDATA[依赖东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸海港的美国公司已经提前进口，将货物转移到西海岸，甚至将货物放在价格昂贵的航班上，以规避 10 月 1 日罢工的威胁，因为罢工可能会在美国总统大选前堵塞供应链并重燃通胀。【原文：U.S. companies that rely on East and Gulf Coast seaports have been importing early, shifting goods to the West Coast, and even putting cargo on pricey flights to hedge against a threatened Oct. 1 strike that could jam supply chains and reignite inflation ahead of the U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/shippers-scramble-workarounds-ahead-threatened-us-port-strike-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NV2XOY2W5ZPWDBDNA6S4Y6JO3Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 准备在 Connect 活动上展示 AR 眼镜]]></title><description><![CDATA[Facebook 的所有者 Meta 公司周三准备在其加利福尼亚总部召开年度 Connect 大会，预计将在会上预览其首款增强现实眼镜，并宣布对现有虚拟现实和人工智能产品进行更新。【原文：Facebook owner Meta prepared on Wednesday to kick off its annual Connect conference at its California headquarters, where it is expected to preview its first augmented reality glasses and announce updates to its existing virtual reality and artificial intelligence products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-readies-ar-glasses-reveal-connect-event-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBFUFO62M5KKVNSNHPS3CMJ2LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:03:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空盈利乏力加剧业务模式改革压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，西南航空公司（Southwest Airlines）这家低成本航空公司的先驱正面临着一位激进投资者要求彻底改革其认为过时的商业模式的运动，这给首席执行官罗伯特-乔丹（Robert Jordan）带来了压力，并使该航空公司不得不努力实现现代化。【原文：Southwest Airlines , the pioneering low-cost carrier, is facing a campaign by an activist investor to overhaul a business model it says is outdated, putting pressure on CEO Robert Jordan and leaving the airline scrambling to modernize, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-airs-lackluster-profit-fuels-pressure-revamp-business-model-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TC7PHELA3NIFXHSGRTHJ4X4RDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>