<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 23:05:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 23:05:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[石油涨幅扩大，因有报道称伊朗准备打击以色列]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚市早盘，油价延续涨势，此前有报道称伊朗正准备在未来几天内从伊拉克境内对以色列实施报复性打击。【原文：Oil prices extended gains in early Asian trade on Friday, following reports that Iran was preparing a retaliatory strike on Israel from Iraqi territory in the coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-extends-gains-reports-iran-preparing-strike-israel-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUIEFSCJRZOSPKYBVQC6J2GV54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 22:39:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道工会称波音向罢工工人提出加薪 38% 的改进方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位工会发言人告诉路透社，波音公司周四向美国西海岸的罢工工人提出了一份改进后的合同，其中包括在四年内加薪 38%。【原文：Boeing made an improved contract offer to striking workers on the U.S. West Coast on Thursday, including a 38% pay increase over four years, a union spokesperson told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-makes-improved-38-pay-raise-offer-striking-workers-union-says-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OP4KB3KAJVKLLHHCC7TO53GHVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 22:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称波音公司将提高工资以结束罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉此事的消息人士告诉路透社记者，波音公司预计将于周四向代表该飞机制造商美国西海岸工厂33000多名罢工工人的工会提出一份改进后的工资方案。【原文：Boeing is expected to make an improved wage offer on Thursday to the union representing over 33,000 of the planemaker's striking U.S. West Coast factory workers, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-due-make-improved-wage-offer-bid-end-strike-sources-say-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YVU3GZAOVJB5ORWJDGGS6L5D4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 22:12:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲 邦德义警大显身手，科技滋补品依然炙手可热]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-pix-graphic-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPKE7FQNEJI3PAKP5JELEBHYYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，波音公司解散多元化部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四援引知情人士的话报道，波音公司已经解散了其全球多元化、公平和包容部门。【原文：Boeing has dismantled its global diversity, equity and inclusion department, Bloomberg news reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-dismantles-diversity-department-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENBIIKIPOJNDLMEZWVEK2BVGQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉加密货币公司 Gotbit 创始人涉嫌电信诈骗]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，加密货币做市商 Gotbit 的创始人因涉嫌代表客户加密货币公司操纵加密货币市场而被起诉。【原文：The founder of cryptocurrency market maker Gotbit was indicted for his alleged role in a wide-ranging conspiracy to manipulate cryptocurrency markets on behalf of client cryptocurrency companies, the U.S. Justice Department said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-indicts-founder-crypto-firm-gotbit-alleged-market-manipulation-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TN7FCMU3ZZNEHFXKZI7VTDXAME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环保人士就美国批准 ioneer 内华达州锂矿提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，环保和原住民团体提起诉讼，质疑美国内政部批准离子公司在内华达州 Rhyolite Ridge 开采锂矿，这是民主党总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）政府批准的首个国内电池金属矿。【原文：Environmental and Indigenous groups on Thursday filed a lawsuit challenging the U.S. Interior Department's approval of ioneer's Rhyolite Ridge lithium mine in Nevada, the first domestic source of the battery metal to be permitted by Democratic President Joe Biden's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/environmentalists-sue-over-us-approval-ioneers-nevada-lithium-mine-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">II6DKTLO2FK6ZP7542WXPA6Y3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:28:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瞻博网络季度业绩超预期，网络设备需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[瞻博网络公司（Juniper Networks）正在被惠普企业公司（Hewlett Packard Enterprise）收购，受网络设备需求的推动，该公司周四公布的第三季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Juniper Networks , which is being bought by Hewlett Packard Enterprise , beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue and profit on Thursday, aided by demand for its networking equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/juniper-beats-quarterly-estimates-networking-gear-demand-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEGADPQQHJNXRGXYWGPWJ7DKCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通就信息披露问题与美国证券交易委员会达成 1 亿美元和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的银行摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）将支付 1 亿美元，以了结美国证券交易委员会对其披露信息误导客户投资 "导管 "产品的指控。【原文：JPMorgan Chase , the largest U.S. bank, will pay $100 million to settle U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charges its disclosures misled customers who invested in "conduit" products, which pooled customer money to invest in private equity or hedge funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-chase-reaches-100-million-settlement-with-sec-over-disclosures-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3VQMG7QYVOSZJC6GGBXX5TH6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:54:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受 iPhone 销售支撑，苹果业绩超出华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四公布的第四财季销售额和利润超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于 iPhone 16 的强劲提前销售。【原文：Apple beat Wall Street sales and profit expectations on Thursday for its fiscal fourth quarter, bolstered by strong early sales of iPhone 16, a set of phones designed for new AI features that was released near the end of the quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-beats-wall-street-estimates-supported-by-iphone-sales-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDC6I42ZRNJ2RAHI3LQUNT76MY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:30:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科特拉能源公司季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[受天然气价格疲软的影响，美国石油和天然气生产商科特拉能源公司（Coterra Energy）周四公布的第三季度利润下降了 22%。【原文：U.S. oil and gas producer Coterra Energy posted a 22% decline in third-quarter profit on Thursday, hurt by weak prices of natural gas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/coterra-energy-posts-lower-quarterly-profit-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVZXZMXKXNLNFPTWYKCMZEOZIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:11:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊公司季度利润、营收均超华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周四公布的第三季度利润和销售额均超出华尔街预期，股价在常规交易时段下跌后，收盘后上涨达 6%。【原文：Amazon.com on Thursday posted third quarter profit and sales that beat Wall Street estimates, sending shares up as much as 6% after the closing bell after they fell during the regular trading session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazoncom-beats-estimates-quarterly-revenue-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPO2JKXHGRO7XHOSGP4CND7LAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔公布第三季度亏损，但预计第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受减值和重组费用的影响，英特尔周四公布了巨额净亏损，但预计第四季度营收高于预期。【原文：Intel reported a massive net loss on Thursday, weighed down by impairment and restructuring charges, but forecast fourth-quarter revenue above estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-reports-third-quarter-loss-forecasts-q4-revenue-above-estimates-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNV54RQ6MJKYPMT23WNPCOYLBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德成为寻求批准 ETF 股份类别的最新、最大公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德公司（BlackRock Inc.【原文：BlackRock Inc. on Wednesday filed an application with the U.S. Securities &amp; Exchange Commission seeking approval to create exchange-traded fund classes for its mutual funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-becomes-latest-largest-firm-seek-approval-etf-share-class-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLB5Z4QTARPOVG3R47BOUIOLTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 19:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州男子被控与 CVS 收购案有关的内幕交易罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦检察官周四指控一名宾夕法尼亚州男子涉嫌内幕交易，他利用其家庭伴侣提供的线索，在 CVS Health 去年以 95 亿美元收购初级保健提供商 Oak Street Health 之前进行非法交易。【原文：Federal prosecutors charged a Pennsylvania man on Thursday with insider trading for using tips from his domestic partner to trade illegally ahead of CVS Health's $9.5 billion purchase last year of primary care provider Oak Street Health.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/pennsylvania-man-charged-with-insider-trading-related-cvs-takeover-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJX4WG23NJMXTDEBMIZ4EBGQHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[L3Harris 火箭发动机部门的投资提高了产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高管告诉路透社记者，L3Harris 技术公司对其 Aerojet Rocketdyne 火箭发动机部门的投资有助于改善设施和流程，而此前该部门多年来一直投资不足，向客户交付火箭发动机的时间也较晚。【原文：Investments by L3Harris Technologies into its Aerojet Rocketdyne rocket motor unit have helped improve facilities and processes after years of underinvestment and late deliveries to customers, an executive told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/l3harris-rocket-motor-unit-investments-boosting-output-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Z4WNY6QPZIZDF5HLMOICBWP4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:23:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国海上风电企业高管私下担心特朗普可能赢得大选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国海上风电开发商在本周举行的一次会议上表现得很勇敢，吹嘘他们有能力与两党领导人合作，但与会者私下担心，如果共和党人唐纳德-特朗普赢得 11 月 5 日的总统大选，他们的日子可能会不好过。【原文：U.S. offshore wind developers put on a brave face at a conference this week, touting their ability to work with leaders from both political parties, although privately attendees fretted that things could get rough for them if Republican Donald Trump wins the Nov. 5 presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-offshore-wind-execs-fret-privately-over-possible-trump-election-win-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMUPLBSJIBPLDL36UYPICR3IT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 为 ChatGPT 添加新的搜索功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周四为其流行的大型语言模型 ChatGPT 添加了一套新的搜索功能，选择将该功能集成到聊天机器人中，而不是推出一个单独的产品。【原文：OpenAI on Thursday added a set of new search functions to its popular large language model ChatGPT, opting to integrate the feature into the chatbot instead of launching a separate product.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-adds-new-search-function-chatgpt-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQMTRFBK7ZO5TPR4XJ4RLWZGUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 17:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储理事违反交易规则剥离配偶购买的股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里亚娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）是美国中央银行七名董事会成员中最新的一位，今年夏天，她的配偶在她不知情的情况下购买了苹果公司和另一家公司的股票，她因此触犯了有关官员及其家人如何进行交易和投资的道德新规。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler, the newest of the U.S. central bank's seven board members, has run afoul of new ethics rules governing how officials and their families can trade and invest after her spouse bought stock in Apple and another company without her knowledge this summer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-governor-divesting-stock-bought-by-spouse-violation-trading-rules-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7BYABNSH5PKNLUMJI4USUOUWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 17:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tradeweb 将在美国大选次日延长交易时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[债券交易平台 Tradeweb 计划延长 11 月 6 日美国总统大选次日的交易时间，并在大选日提供隔夜支持。【原文：Bond trading platform Tradeweb plans to extend trading hours on Nov. 6, the day after the U.S. presidential election, and offer overnight support on Election Day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tradeweb-extend-trading-hours-day-after-us-election-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQACAQJOOFPB7KBL7OBQKBR3MA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 17:13:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯雷向首席执行官出售在突尼斯马扎里能源公司（Mazarine Energy）的控股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mazarine 能源公司周四表示，私募股权巨头凯雷集团已将其在突尼斯石油和天然气生产商 Mazarine Energy 公司的多数股权出售给该公司首席执行官 Edward van Kersbergen。【原文：Private equity giant Carlyle Group has sold its majority holdings in Tunisia-focused oil and gas producer Mazarine Energy to the company's CEO Edward van Kersbergen, Mazarine said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/carlyle-sells-holding-tunisia-focused-mazarine-energy-ceo-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HS3NGH6Y2BJVBHQ4APSBOKFPEE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 17:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称美国 8 月石油产量创单月历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（EIA）在其月度石油和天然气产量报告中称，8月份美国石油产量增长了1.5%，达到1340万桶/日，创下月度历史新高。【原文：U.S. oil production rose 1.5% in August to a monthly record high of 13.4 million barrels per day (bpd), the U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) said in its monthly oil and natural gas production report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-oil-output-hits-monthly-record-high-august-eia-says-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFDNS23UNZJ3FMZ2QGPMMQIGFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 17:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调解员称普渡制药接近与萨克雷达成新的破产协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）的一名法庭指定调解人周四表示，该公司即将与其所有者、富豪萨克勒家族成员以及州政府和地方政府达成新的破产和解协议，这些人提起诉讼，指控普渡制药的止痛药奥施康定（OxyContin）在美国引发了致命的阿片类药物成瘾危机。【原文：Purdue Pharma is close to a new bankruptcy settlement with its owners, members of the wealthy Sackler family, and state and local governments that have filed lawsuits alleging that its painkiller OxyContin spurred a deadly opioid addiction crisis in the U.S., a court-appointed mediator said Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/purdue-pharma-nears-new-bankruptcy-deal-with-sacklers-mediator-says-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZSZQZM32KVLCHC5TOBRKOOU7BU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:59:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伍德赛德公司与东京燃气公司商讨美国液化天然气项目股份事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟知内情的人士透露，东京燃气公司正在与伍德赛德能源公司（Woodside Energy）就入股路易斯安那州价值数十亿美元的液化天然气（LNG）出口项目进行谈判。【原文：Tokyo Gas is in talks with Woodside Energy over taking a stake in a multi-billion-dollar Louisiana liquefied natural gas (LNG) export project, according to two people familiar with the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/woodside-tokyo-gas-discussions-over-stake-us-lng-project-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BF7BB2UOCNNE3DH3VLGYO7FWLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:57:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，由于公司业绩下滑，福特将下调经理人奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉内情的人士透露，福特汽车首席执行官吉姆-法利（Jim Farley）已告诉员工，该汽车制造商需要加快提高质量和降低成本的步伐，而与这些指标挂钩的经理奖金将被削减至总额的 65%。【原文：Ford Motor CEO Jim Farley has told employees that the automaker needs to speed efforts to improve quality and lower costs, and that manager bonuses, which are tied to those metrics, would be slashed to 65% of their total, according to three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-lower-managers-bonuses-company-performance-slips-sources-say-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYDLHJ5KP5LDTHFMXE4ONYT7SI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:55:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛杉矶县就塑料污染问题起诉百事公司和可口可乐公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶县起诉饮料生产商百事可乐公司和可口可乐公司，指控它们用塑料瓶污染了这个美国人口最多的县，并在塑料容器的环境影响和可回收性方面误导公众。【原文：Los Angeles County has sued beverage makers PepsiCo and Coca-Cola , accusing them of polluting the most populous U.S. county with plastic bottles and misleading the public about the environmental impact and recyclability of their containers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/los-angeles-county-sues-pepsico-coca-cola-over-plastic-pollution-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EI2C4WMWUFMRHAV7DZMMTQCWSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:22:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通聘请德意志银行的 Rajendram 担任欧洲、中东和非洲地区消费者交易主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四发布的一份员工备忘录显示，摩根大通已从竞争对手德意志银行聘请 Rumesh Rajendram 担任欧洲、中东和非洲地区消费者与零售并购业务主管。【原文：JPMorgan has hired Rumesh Rajendram from rival Deutsche Bank as head of consumer and retail M&amp;A for EMEA, according to a staff memo distributed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-hires-rajendram-deutsche-bank-head-emea-consumer-deals-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">65RKIMRMERKCLCRW2BGLB5GKDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:04:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国金融公司被要求加强缓冲，防范类似 CrowdStrike 的事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国市场监管机构周四表示，英国的金融公司必须做好准备，确保能够在 "严重但可信 "的情况下提供业务服务，如全球技术中断，以最大限度地减少对消费者和市场的影响。【原文：Financial companies in Britain must prepare to ensure they can deliver business services in "severe but plausible" scenarios, such as a global tech outage, to minimise any impact on consumers and markets, the markets regulator said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/uk-finance-firms-told-beef-up-buffers-against-crowdstrike-like-events-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALRM4KQKZVI47AESTYTJE6DUZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:25:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商尼古拉季度亏损超预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼古拉公司周四公布的季度亏损超过预期，该公司仍在努力应对与燃料电池电动卡车增产相关的高成本，导致这家电动汽车制造商的股价下跌超过 5%。【原文：Nikola reported a bigger-than-expected quarterly loss on Thursday as the company continues to grapple with high costs related to the production ramp up of its fuel-cell electric truck, sending the EV maker's shares down more than 5%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-nikola-posts-bigger-than-expected-quarterly-loss-shares-fall-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULLF7VB6BNKPJK7FW46QKRG5FM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:21:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌为地图应用带来人工智能答案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司（Google）周四宣布了一系列功能，将其人工智能聊天机器人 "双子座"（Gemini）纳入其地图应用程序套件。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Thursday announced a set of features that incorporated Gemini, its artificial intelligence chatbot, into its suite of mapping applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/google-brings-ai-answers-map-applications-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYGV6BOJGRLVNDQDOJ27PCDKAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>