<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:09:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:09:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[说明：什么是气候融资？]]></title><description><![CDATA[各国在努力向清洁能源转变的同时，也在为气候变暖带来的极端天气和其他影响做准备，这就需要钱--大量的钱。随着全球变暖的成本和风险不断攀升，气候融资的话题也变得更加紧张。以下是您需要了解的内容：【原文：Countries trying to shift to clean energy while also preparing for extreme weather and other impacts in a warmer world will need money - a lot of it. As the costs and risks of global warming escalate, the topic of climate finance has become more tense. Here's what you need to know:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/what-is-climate-finance-why-does-it-matter-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ELCVKNWYZLNFGVYBVC3TO66ZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于关税影响降低，索尼将利润预期上调 8]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼周二将截至 2026 年 3 月的年度营业利润预期上调 8%，至 1.43 万亿日元（合 94.8 亿美元），理由是美国关税的影响较小，以及音乐和芯片业务的强劲表现。【原文：Sony on Tuesday raised its operating profit forecast for the year ending March 2026 by 8% to 1.43 trillion yen ($9.48 billion) citing a smaller impact from U.S. tariffs and the strength of its music and chips businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/sony-raises-profit-forecast-by-8-lower-tariff-impact-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQZFNRES2BJRNIRCFB7P5DHL7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者监督机构称其无法合法获取资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高消费者监督机构周一表示，法律禁止该机构从美联储提取现金以支持持续运营，但其目前的资金 "至少 "应持续到今年年底。【原文：The top U.S. consumer watchdog said on Monday it was legally prohibited from drawing cash from the Federal Reserve to support continuing operations, but that its current funding should last through the end of this year "at least."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-consumer-watchdog-says-it-is-legally-blocked-accessing-funds-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASFMZ63ZCVON7ODS26CBBEVLKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓将为澳大利亚煤炭工人的圣诞轮班提供补偿]]></title><description><![CDATA[矿业与能源工会周二表示，澳大利亚联邦法院已下令必和必拓向其在昆士兰州的劳务雇佣部门雇佣的 85 名煤矿工人提供赔偿，因为必和必拓非法要求他们在圣诞节和节礼日假期工作，且未提供合理的拒绝权。【原文：BHP has been ordered by Australia's Federal Court to compensate 85 coal mine workers employed by its labour hire arm in Queensland for unlawfully requiring them to work Christmas and Boxing Day holidays without providing a reasonable right of refusal, the Mining and Energy Union said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/bhp-compensate-australian-coal-workers-christmas-shifts-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUIJWHDNGZJHHLUPGYVT3DOGLI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:25:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：中国制定计划阻止美军获得稀土磁铁]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周一援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，中国计划通过一个系统放宽稀土和其他受限制材料对美国的流通，该系统将排除与美国军方有关系的公司，同时快速审批其他公司的出口。【原文：China plans to ease the flow of rare earths and other restricted materials to the U.S. via a system that will exclude companies with ties to the U.S. military while fast-tracking export approvals for other firms, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-devises-plan-keep-us-military-getting-its-rare-earth-magnets-wsj-reports-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6DGUD4B6JNN5EWPFRRG4KI4TE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国部委称推迟就谷歌地图数据传输请求作出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国周二表示，已推迟就谷歌出口地图数据的申请做出决定，并称将在该公司提交补充文件后做出最终裁决。【原文：South Korea said on Tuesday it has delayed a decision on Google's request for permission to export map data, saying it will make a final ruling once the company submits additional documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-delays-decision-googles-request-map-data-transfer-says-ministry-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KS26CQGPMRK3DAQREZ56NR2SCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:10:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称东南亚数字经济的私人资金投入落后于全球水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份行业报告周二称，在截至2025年6月的12个月里，东南亚互联网经济的私人资金同比增长15%，达到77亿美元，落后于全球私募股权和风险投资25%的增长率。【原文：Private funding for Southeast Asia's internet economy grew 15% from a year earlier to $7.7 billion in the 12 months to June 2025, lagging the global growth rate of 25% for private equity and venture capital investments, an industry report said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/private-funding-southeast-asia-digital-economy-lags-global-level-report-says-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHFJ7CV4P5KD3A7IOBBOULERAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与韩国的协议因潜艇细节问题陷入僵局]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和韩国总统李在镕会晤并宣布他们已经解决了数月来有关关税和安全问题的谈判两周后，双方仍未达成任何书面协议。【原文：Two weeks after U.S. President Donald Trump and South Korea's Lee Jae Myung met and announced they had resolved months of negotiations over tariffs and security issues, the two sides have yet to release any agreement on paper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trumps-deal-with-south-korea-bogged-down-details-over-submarine-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMWKQ7FVSZJQZIEXKNMO77OBLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计美国将达成停摆协议，黄金和股市上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市上涨，黄金和纳斯达克指数创下几个月来的最大涨幅，这得益于有迹象表明，结束美国政府关门的协议即将达成。【原文：Asian stocks rose on Tuesday while gold and the Nasdaq were basking in their sharpest gains for months thanks to signs a deal to end the U.S. government shutdown was in the offing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZPDMD4UYBKO3LH2WL6M5TY4GE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 02:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应过剩忧虑令石油价格回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二亚市早盘，油价下跌，缩减了上一交易日的涨幅，原因是对供应过剩的担忧超过了对美国政府可能解决停摆问题的乐观情绪。【原文：Oil prices dipped in early Asian trade on Tuesday, trimming gains from the previous session as oversupply concerns outweighed optimism over a potential resolution to the U.S. government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-retreats-oversupply-worries-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQG6UGBG4NLNXB4NCTCUGUGT64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 01:46:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《时事航空》报道，波音公司获准推进 777X 的认证工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《航空周刊》周一援引熟悉该项目进展的人士的话报道，波音公司上周获得了美国联邦航空管理局的批准，开始对其777-9进行五个主要阶段中的第三阶段认证飞行测试。【原文：Boeing received approval last week from the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration to begin the third of five major phases of certification flight tests for its 777-9, the Air Current reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the program's progress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-gets-nod-moving-777x-forward-certification-air-current-reports-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSWLP4U5FFL5NEDGECEW6QELYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 01:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员关注美国停摆结束，避险日元承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，避险货币日元接近几个月来的最弱水平，而风险货币兑美元则表现坚挺，交易商在等待美国立法者是否能在未来几天内结束政府关门。【原文：The safe-haven yen was pinned near its weakest levels for months on Tuesday while riskier currencies were firm against the dollar, as traders waited to see whether U.S. lawmakers could secure an end to the government shutdown in coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/safe-haven-yen-under-pressure-traders-eye-end-us-shutdown-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6YMGGBAEBNP5G3ELZXK7KVBLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[舒默因政府拨款协议再次陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[周末达成的结束美国政府史上最长停摆的协议使参议院民主党人产生分歧，并激怒了该党声势浩大的自由派支持者，他们今年第二次将矛头转向参议院少数党领袖查克-舒默（Chuck Schumer）。【原文：A weekend deal to end the longest U.S. government shutdown in history divided Senate Democrats and angered the party's vocal liberal base, who turned their vitriol on Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer for the second time this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/schumer-hotseat-again-over-deal-fund-government-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EVSQ6TBRJLJHIPM6R6UQDPFTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师上调目标股价，软银的 OpenAI 赌注成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，科技投资商软银集团（SoftBank Group）公布了第二季度财报，该公司在人工智能领域的投资热潮使其股价一路飙升。【原文：Technology investor SoftBank Group reports second quarter earnings results on Tuesday in the midst of feverish investment in artificial intelligence that has sent its share price soaring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbanks-openai-wager-focus-analysts-upgrade-share-price-target-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C42YTQHO5FKJVCXV6DT2KM4KNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国航空旅行何时恢复正常？本周不会]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管联邦政府关门有望在本周结束，但美国的航空旅客仍将经历几天的艰难旅程，在天空飞行恢复正常之前，全国范围内的航班都将取消或延误。【原文：Despite hopes the federal government shutdown could end this week, air travelers in the United States are still in for a rough few days of cancellations and delays nationwide before taking to the skies gets back to normal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/when-will-us-air-travel-be-back-normal-not-this-week-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCBD5K2YBJNH7JE46JFQGQ2RNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI高管离职后，英特尔首席执行官将监管公司的人工智能工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔在一份声明中表示，在公司首席技术官离职加入 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 之后，英特尔首席执行官陈立武将负责监管芯片制造商的人工智能工作。【原文：Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan will oversee the chipmakers artificial intelligence efforts after the firm's chief technology officer departed for ChatGPT maker OpenAI, Intel said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-ceo-oversee-companys-ai-efforts-after-departure-exec-openai-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Z23R5IQLVJ7NHQ2TT63EXRP5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Natura 公司第三季度出现亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西化妆品生产商 Natura 周一公布，第三季度经常性净亏损为 1.19 亿雷亚尔（2202 万美元），扭转了去年同期 3.01 亿雷亚尔的净利润。【原文：Brazilian cosmetic maker Natura posted on Monday a third-quarter recurring net loss of 119 million reais ($22.02 million), reversing a 301 million real net profit recorded in the same period a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-natura-swings-loss-third-quarter-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4TDTYIFOFPILMA4UK244R4SGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:43:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[成本增加、需求下滑导致 Beyond Meat 第三季度亏损扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，Beyond Meat 公布了第三季度的更大亏损，因为这家植物肉生产商正努力应对产品需求持续低迷和成本增加的问题。【原文：Beyond Meat posted a bigger loss for the third quarter on Monday, as the plant-based meat maker grappled with persistent sluggish demand for its products and mounting costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/beyond-meat-third-quarter-loss-widens-costs-mount-demand-slumps-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PISYKUFQCBPHHECN77GB5S4ANU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：停产隧道尽头的曙光]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和全球股市周一大涨，原因是对美国政府关门可能很快结束的希望引发了科技股的救市反弹，而日元则在日本首相高市真奈表示倾向于采取宽松的财政政策和不那么鹰派的货币政策后下跌。【原文：U.S. and world stocks leaped on Monday as hopes that the U.S. government shutdown could soon end sparked a tech-fueled relief rally, while the yen slumped after Japan's Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi indicated her preference for looser fiscal and less hawkish monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ROYXX7NIRNWVHRGFMBQVE36Y4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IPG 第三季度业绩超出预期，原因是媒体和医疗支出强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[广告公司 Interpublic Group 周一公布的第三季度营收和利润均超出预期，主要得益于媒体和医疗保健客户支出的恢复性增长。【原文：Advertising firm Interpublic Group beat third-quarter revenue and profit estimates on Monday, helped by resilient spending from media and health care clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ipg-beats-third-quarter-estimates-strong-media-health-spending-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A75UIGQR3ZM75LBDQDE5VYJDOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官驳回联邦贸易委员会阻止私募股权医疗公司交易的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司 GTCR 可以继续推进对医疗器械涂层制造商 Surmodics 的收购，芝加哥的一名联邦法官周一作出裁决，驳回了美国联邦贸易委员会阻止该交易的要求。【原文：Private equity firm GTCR can move forward with its acquisition of medical device coatings maker Surmodics' , a federal judge in Chicago ruled on Monday, rejecting the U.S. Federal Trade Commission's bid to block the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-judge-rejects-ftcs-bid-block-private-equity-medical-company-deal-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJMBM5M5UBIUPHWRZIZ5GSNOPM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:49:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[激进投资者 Biglari 称 ISS 和其他机构支持 Cracker Barrel 的变革举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[Biglari Capital 周一表示，代理咨询公司已敦促股东投票反对一些现任董事会提名人，Cracker Barrel Old Country Store 在年度会议前面临新的压力。【原文：Cracker Barrel Old Country Store faced fresh pressure ahead of its annual meeting after Biglari Capital said on Monday that proxy advisory firms have urged shareholders to vote against some incumbent board nominees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/activist-investor-biglari-says-iss-others-back-move-changes-cracker-barrel-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBOB324SHJIMJF6BLCAYRYAZZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称若最高法院裁定关税无效，美国将面临 "经济灾难]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，如果最高法院裁决反对他使用紧急权力法对几乎所有国家征收全面关税，美国将面临经济和国家安全灾难。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday the United States faced an economic and national security disaster if the Supreme Court ruled against his use of an emergency powers law to impose sweeping tariffs against nearly every country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-us-faces-economic-disaster-if-supreme-court-rules-against-tariffs-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSK76R5IWJPMZANSXRDO65CID4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西方石油公司季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[西方石油公司（Occidental Petroleum）周一公布的第三季度利润超出华尔街预期，原因是这家美国页岩油生产商受益于产量增加。【原文：Occidental Petroleum beat Wall Street expectations for third quarter profit on Monday, as the U.S. shale producer benefited from higher production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shale-producer-occidental-petroleum-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YCA7TPLGNOFDIIQAQYUIKR7HU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能计算蓬勃发展，CoreWeave 第三季度营收超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能云服务提供商 CoreWeave 周一公布的第三季度营收超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于市场对其支持人工智能工作负载的计算基础设施的需求激增。【原文：AI cloud provider CoreWeave beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue on Monday, benefiting from surging demand for its computing infrastructure that powers artificial intelligence workloads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coreweave-beats-third-quarter-revenue-estimates-ai-computing-boom-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRRTQVUFLBJ5LA3D6HUAYX2H5U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙天空舞蹈公司在合并后的首份报告中预测季度收入将有所增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙天舞公司（Paramount Skydance）表示，明年将在节目制作方面投资 15 亿美元，预计第四季度收入将高于华尔街预期，这是自 84 亿美元的合并完成以来，合并后的公司首次发布季度财报。【原文：Paramount Skydance said it will make $1.5 billion in programming investments next year, as it forecast fourth-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates, in its first quarterly results for the combined company since the completion of the $8.4 billion merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-skydance-misses-revenue-estimates-first-earnings-report-since-merger-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQJGRMJOFFOFZNAZFG3SFTAOBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，创始人兼首席执行官西贝尔离职后，C3 AI 正在权衡出售事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉内情的人士透露，企业人工智能软件提供商 C3 AI 创始人托马斯-西贝尔（Thomas Siebel）最近因健康问题辞去首席执行官一职，公司正在探索潜在的出售方案。【原文：Enterprise artificial intelligence software provider C3 AI is exploring a potential sale, among other options, after founder Thomas Siebel recently stepped down as CEO over health concerns, according to three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/c3-ai-weighs-sale-after-founder-ceo-siebel-steps-aside-sources-say-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUJAVZU7KBIPNIPW4DCHJB7Q2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 CBA 第一季度利润小幅增长，销量增长抵消了利润率的紧缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚联邦银行（Commonwealth Bank of Australia）周二报告称，第一季度现金利润略有增长，贷款和存款量的恢复性增长无法完全抵消竞争压力和低利率环境对利润率的压缩。【原文：Commonwealth Bank of Australia reported a marginal rise in first-quarter cash profit on Tuesday, with resilient lending and deposit volumes unable to fully counter margin compression from competitive pressures and a lower rate environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-top-bank-cba-reports-marginal-rise-first-quarter-profit-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RX6BMY345RLGFDLR4GTKSDSO7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国可能结束停摆为投资者带来宽慰，新数据成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国政府停摆可能即将结束，担心经济受到更多影响的投资者放松了警惕，转而期待大量延迟发布的数据来揭示经济增长和可能的利率走势。【原文：With an end to the U.S. government shutdown potentially on the horizon, investors who feared more economic fallout breathed easier and turned to an expected flood of delayed data to shed more light on growth and the likely path for interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/possible-us-shutdown-end-brings-investor-relief-fresh-data-focus-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOMHPLKCMZLCLC3EG7EFWW2AMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[红利还是品牌？帝亚吉欧新任首席执行官在解决债务问题时面临削减成本的两难选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[帝亚吉欧即将上任的首席执行官戴夫-刘易斯（Dave Lewis）在金融界以其大刀阔斧的企业扭亏为盈而被称为 "Drastic Dave"，当他 1 月份加入这家全球最大的烈酒制造商时，他将面临降低债务和重振销售的挑战，这将是对他削减成本声誉的一次考验。【原文：Diageo's incoming CEO Dave Lewis, known in financial circles as “Drastic Dave” for his sweeping turnaround of businesses, will put his reputation as a cost-cutter to the test when he joins the world’s largest spirits maker in January with the challenge of lowering its debt and reigniting sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dividends-or-brands-new-diageo-ceo-faces-cost-cutting-dilemma-tackling-debt-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X454P2RP2FOUNELDQX2RMJGNHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>