<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 19:34:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 19:34:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[立法者称欧洲应启动针对特朗普关税的反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位欧洲资深立法者周六表示，布鲁塞尔应立即采取反制措施，应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普 "蛮横无理 "地威胁对从欧盟进口的商品加征关税的行为。【原文：A senior European lawmaker said on Saturday Brussels should react immediately with countermeasures against U.S. President Donald Trump's "outrageous" threat to hike tariffs on imports from the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/europe-should-activate-countermeasures-against-trump-tariffs-lawmaker-says-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SOMYHJJZFRK4XCAFQN373JNZRE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 19:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示仍希望与美国达成贸易协议，并将捍卫自身利益]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）周六表示，如果美国继续威胁从8月1日起对欧洲商品征收30%的关税，欧盟准备采取报复行动以维护自身利益。【原文：The EU is ready to retaliate to safeguard its interests if the U.S. proceeds with imposing a threatened 30% tariff on European goods starting on August 1, European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-says-it-still-wants-us-trade-deal-will-defend-interests-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSY7DHRJ5FKKZEMUAWAMOETP2Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 16:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对特朗普对欧盟和墨西哥征收 30% 关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六宣布，从8月1日起对从欧盟和墨西哥进口的商品征收30%的关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump announced on Saturday a 30% tariff rate for goods imported from the European Union and Mexico, starting on August 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-investors-react-trumps-30-tariffs-eu-mexico-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2FQJU23CDZKX7PRPST7ZYT3XU4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 14:22:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布对欧盟和墨西哥征收 30% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六在其社交媒体平台上发布信件称，从8月1日起，从欧盟和墨西哥进口的商品将面临美国30%的关税税率。【原文：Goods imported from both the European Union and Mexico will face a 30% U.S. tariff rate starting August 1, U.S. President Donald Trump said in letters posted to his social media platform on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-announces-30-tariffs-eu-mexico-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTDETVBTWZONLJDKZO2PZBJ5TE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 13:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe 称，大幅折扣促进销售，美国在线支出激增 241 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在被称为 "夏季黑色星期五 "的 7 月 8 日至 11 日期间，美国零售商的在线消费额猛增 241 亿美元，超过了 Adobe Analytics 之前的预测，因为热心的购物者急于抢购返校必需品的超低折扣。【原文：Online spending soared $24.1 billion across U.S. retailers during the stretch from July 8 to 11 – dubbed "Black Friday in Summer", outpacing Adobe Analytics' prior forecast, as eager shoppers rushed to snap up deep discounts on back-to-school essentials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-online-spending-surges-241-billion-steep-discounts-boost-sales-adobe-says-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JOLIMHIFLJK6LAXKIQVDBOUKQ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普强化贸易战，对欧盟和墨西哥征收 30% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统是在与主要贸易盟国进行了数周的谈判，但未能达成一项更全面的协议后宣布这一消息的。【原文：President Trump's announcement came after weeks of negotiations with the key trading allies failed to reach a more comprehensive deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-announces-30-tariffs-eu-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J3LXQLO2KFKGVBYPXP3M5S5S5I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 12:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[捷豹路虎北美公司因乘客安全气囊破损召回约 21,000 辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周六表示，捷豹路虎北美公司将在美国召回20999辆汽车，原因是乘客安全气囊破损，在发生碰撞时可能无法充分保护乘员，增加受伤风险。【原文：Jaguar Land Rover North America is recalling 20,999 vehicles in the United States due to torn passenger airbags that may not adequately protect an occupant in a crash, increasing the risk of injury, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jaguar-land-rover-north-america-recalls-about-21000-us-vehicles-over-torn-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQGYZTNBKZJG5O3USLTGSINJTU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 07:33:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司与在 737 MAX 坠机事故中丧生的加拿大男子达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司与一名加拿大男子达成和解，该男子的律师周五表示，他的家人在 2019 年 3 月埃塞俄比亚航空公司一架波音 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故中丧生。【原文：Boeing reached a settlement with a Canadian man whose family died in the March 2019 crash of an Ethiopian Airlines Boeing 737 MAX, the man's lawyer said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-settles-with-canadian-man-whose-family-died-737-max-crash-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXM7Z6ABC5JY5FC5G334LDHCMQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，谷歌将支付 24 亿美元，获得 Windsurf 的技术许可。]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，谷歌同意支付约 24 亿美元，获得人工智能辅助编码工具 Windsurf 的技术许可。【原文：Google has agreed to pay about $2.4 billion in a deal to license the technology of artificial intelligence-assisted coding tool Windsurf, The Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-pay-24-billion-deal-license-tech-windsurf-wsj-reports-2025-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66JOIAKDKVONRNH5KKWHBDBTNQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，特朗普征收 50%的铜进口关税据说将包括精炼金属]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周五援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺的50%铜关税据说将包括所有精炼金属。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's promised 50% copper tariffs are said to include all refined metal, Bloomberg reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-50-copper-import-tariff-said-include-refined-metal-bloomberg-reports-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOBQRTSOTZMB7IH7URUGXD5WEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:26:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼 GoTo 公司称尊重正在进行的法律程序，此前有报道称当局突袭了 GoTo 公司的办公室]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚科技公司 GoTo Gojek Tokopedia 周五晚些时候发表声明称，该公司尊重正在进行的法律程序，并将支持任何维护法律的努力。【原文：Indonesian tech firm GoTo Gojek Tokopedia said in a statement late on Friday that it respects the ongoing legal process and will be supportive of any efforts to uphold the law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/indonesias-goto-says-it-respects-ongoing-legal-process-after-reports-authorities-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBNYS5VIABIJBA4FJTFSNOVRYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌聘请 Windsurf 首席执行官和研究人员推进人工智能雄心]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌发言人周五表示，谷歌已聘请Windsurf首席执行官瓦伦-莫汉（Varun Mohan）、联合创始人道格拉斯-陈（Douglas Chen）以及该编码工具研发团队的部分成员加入其DeepMind部门，此举旨在加强自身在人工智能领导力竞争中的实力。【原文：Google has hired Windsurf CEO Varun Mohan, co-founder Douglas Chen, and select members of the coding tool's research and development team to join its DeepMind division, a Google spokesperson said on Friday, in a move to strengthen itself in the race for AI leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-hires-windsurf-ceo-researchers-advance-ai-ambitions-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJSXK2RKTVIUNB6MMDOVXUFWSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 22:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道通用汽车墨西哥皮卡工厂停产数周]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉情况的人士告诉路透社，通用汽车公司正在暂停墨西哥一家皮卡工厂的生产，为期数周，以压低其最畅销车型的产量。【原文：General Motors is pausing production at a pickup-truck plant in Mexico for several weeks, crimping output of its top-selling vehicles, people familiar with the situation told Reuters, and the company confirmed the information when asked.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-pickup-truck-plant-mexico-pauses-output-several-weeks-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BF235GHDKRMR7CJNM2V3RLRLDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 22:20:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者焦急等待美欧贸易的下一步行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周重燃全球贸易战战火，投资者正等待周五美国和欧盟之间的关税消息。【原文：Investors awaited tariff news between the U.S. and European Union on Friday that could add a potentially volatile development to the end of a week in which President Donald Trump reignited his global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-anxiously-await-next-steps-trade-between-us-eu-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPQWGDCEXBJC3KIVJOKMNWIFWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:54:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度航空公司坠机事件调查的主要事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[上个月造成 260 人死亡的印度航空公司坠机事件的初步报告显示，飞机起飞几秒钟后，发动机燃料切断开关几乎同时从运行状态切换到切断状态，导致发动机燃料匮乏。【原文：A preliminary report into the Air India crash that killed 260 people last month showed that seconds after taking off, the plane's engines fuel cutoff switches almost simultaneously flipped from run to cutoff, starving the engines of fuel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/key-events-air-india-crash-investigation-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEYCC7QETZJSHPWT2DHPUM4B44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 CFPB 与 FirstCash 就涉嫌违反《军事借贷法》达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protections Bureau）周五表示，该消费者监督机构已就当铺连锁店主 FirstCash Inc 及其子公司涉嫌违反《军事借贷法》（Military Lending Act）达成和解。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protections Bureau has reached a settlement with pawn shop chain owner FirstCash Inc and its subsidiaries for alleged violations of the Military Lending Act, the consumer watchdog agency said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-cfpb-reaches-settlement-with-firstcash-alleged-military-lending-act-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7GGQCMGANJERHO5GIFFXJEANA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Cerberus 和 Dean Metropoulos 也曾竞购 WK Kellogg]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉内情的消息人士称，私募股权公司 Cerberus Capital Management 和亿万富翁投资者 Dean Metropoulos 联手竞购麦片生产商 WK Kellogg，但未获成功，Cerberus Capital Management 拥有杂货商 Albertsons 的股份。【原文：Private equity firm Cerberus Capital Management, which owns a stake in grocer Albertsons , and billionaire investor Dean Metropoulos teamed up in an unsuccessful bid for cereal maker WK Kellogg , according to three sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/cerberus-dean-metropoulos-also-made-bid-wk-kellogg-sources-say-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RVLTUEUGVJLUJH2PBVNYCPLCF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在无线运营商放弃 DEI 计划后，FCC 批准了 T-Mobile 的两项交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦通信委员会周五的一份声明显示，该委员会本周批准了两项涉及 T-Mobile 的交易，此前这家无线运营商表示将终止其多元化、公平和包容计划。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission has approved two transactions involving T-Mobile this week, a statement by the commission showed on Friday, after the wireless carrier said it was ending its diversity, equity and inclusion programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/fcc-approves-two-t-mobile-deals-after-wireless-carrier-drops-dei-programs-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHPNBYADNZPYBIW76JFL3AJPWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[太空与国防公司 Firefly Aerospace 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[太空与国防技术公司 Firefly Aerospace 周五提交了在美国首次公开募股的申请。【原文：Space and defense technology company Firefly Aerospace on Friday filed for an initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/space-firm-firefly-aerospace-files-us-ipo-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDCUMEIJLFJ6JO3XQ2SEJNCLHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:48:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟计划对大企业征收新税以增加预算 -FT]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，布鲁塞尔将提议对净营业额超过 5000 万欧元（5844 万美元）的公司征收新税，作为为欧盟共同预算创造新资金流的努力的一部分。【原文：Brussels will propose a new tax on companies with a net turnover exceeding 50 million euros ($58.44 million) as part of an effort to generate new financing streams for the European Union’s common budget, the Financial Times report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-plans-new-tax-big-corporates-boost-budget-ft-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7OI2HCBSRJ4FBCQVQQ3UYQAHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:38:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度发现印航致命空难中的发动机开关动作，波音或通用电气未立即采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[上个月造成 260 人死亡的印度航空公司坠机事件的初步报告显示，飞机起飞三秒钟后，发动机燃料切断开关几乎同时从运行状态切换到切断状态，导致发动机燃料匮乏。【原文：A preliminary report into the Air India crash that killed 260 people last month showed three seconds after taking off, the plane's engines fuel cutoff switches almost simultaneously flipped from run to cutoff, starving the engines of fuel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/india-finds-engine-switch-movement-fatal-air-india-crash-no-immediate-action-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2OBH4IDP5LL7ALXTR5JSVAZ64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》报道，苹果出价至少每年 1.5 亿美元购买一级方程式赛车流媒体播放权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Business Insider 周五报道，苹果公司已经提交了一份从 2026 年开始每年至少价值 1.5 亿美元的一级方程式赛事流媒体竞标书。【原文：Apple has submitted a bid worth at least $150 million a year to stream Formula 1 races starting in 2026, Business Insider reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-bids-least-150-million-year-formula-1-streaming-rights-business-insider-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFX7HDFXRJI7TGHORHKFGB6WX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普阻止香港公司收购设备供应商 Jupiter Systems]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五发表声明称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发布命令，阻止香港公司穗瑞国际收购视听设备供应商 Jupiter Systems。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump issued an order blocking the acquisition of audiovisual equipment supplier Jupiter Systems by Hong Kong company Suirui International, the U.S. Treasury Department said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-blocks-acquisition-equipment-supplier-jupiter-systems-by-hong-kong-firm-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXAXOW5V3BLUXJEXAZQXU4GXHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会建议俄罗斯石油价格上限比全球价格低 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟外交官说，欧盟委员会周五提议对俄罗斯石油实行浮动价格上限，即低于前三个月原油平均市场价格的 15%。【原文：The European Commission proposed on Friday a floating price cap on Russian oil of 15% below the average market price of crude in the previous three months, EU diplomats said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/european-commission-proposes-russian-oil-price-cap-15-below-global-price-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5532BBOZHVLTHOXKXMYIGPHHK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，马斯克的 xAI 在下一次融资中寻求高达 2000 亿美元的估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引接近谈判的人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克的xAI公司正准备从投资者那里筹集更多资金，这笔交易可能使这家人工智能公司的估值高达2000亿美元。【原文：Elon Musk's xAI is preparing to raise more money from investors in a deal that could value the artificial-intelligence company as high as $200 billion, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people close to the talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-xai-seeks-up-200-billion-valuation-next-fundraising-ft-reports-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFWV352LAVPKFITKGOJAUXS3UI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，摩根大通计划向金融科技公司收取客户数据费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，摩根大通正计划向金融科技公司征收获取其客户银行账户数据的费用。【原文：JPMorgan Chase is planning to impose fees on fintech companies for access to its customer bank account data, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-plans-charge-fintechs-customer-data-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SJ5RZGFYZO2FGYHC32QYGMPWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:42:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储古尔斯比：需要等到焦虑消退才能对前景感到放心]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普新宣布的关税措施使得对经济状况的解读变得 "一团糟"，他还补充说，他从商业联系人那里听到了很多对即将到来的通货膨胀的焦虑，而这种焦虑在数据中还不明显。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's fresh tariff announcements make it "messy" to interpret the state of the economy, Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee said, adding that he is hearing a lot of anxiety from business contacts about coming inflation that is not yet obvious in the data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-need-wait-until-anxiety-recedes-feel-comfortable-about-outlook-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PK4ZJT2SFLHXJQMKFSK4DRTOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部称明年生物燃料需求将占美国豆油产量的一半以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部周五表示，由于近期一系列联邦政策措施改变了美国生物燃料行业，包括提高掺混规定以及限制外国生物燃料进口和原料，明年美国生物燃料制造商将消耗美国生产的全部豆油的一半以上。【原文：U.S. biofuel makers will consume more than half of all soybean oil produced in the United States next year as a recent flurry of federal policy moves has transformed the sector, including higher blending mandates and curbs on foreign biofuel imports and feedstocks, the U.S. Department of Agriculture said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/biofuel-demand-soak-up-more-than-half-us-soyoil-production-next-year-usda-says-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QE6B6C5LROJ3GPAS2PWXYSGL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员就即将到来的中国之行警告英伟达首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国两党参议员周五就英伟达（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋即将进行的中国之行致信黄仁勋，警告他不要与涉嫌破坏美国芯片出口管制的公司会面。【原文：A bipartisan pair of U.S. senators sent a letter to Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang on Friday about an upcoming trip to China, warning the CEO to refrain from meeting with companies that are suspected of undermining U.S. chip export controls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-senators-warn-nvidia-ceo-about-upcoming-china-trip-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGWG2ESMI5MFTO2R5LLIAGONRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:03:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[厄瓜多尔和 Codelco 声称在 Llurimagua 采矿仲裁案中获胜]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一家国际仲裁法院下令厄瓜多尔支付一个大型铜矿项目 5.68 亿美元索赔中的约 2500 万美元后，厄瓜多尔总检察长办公室和智利国有矿业公司 Codelco 周五均宣称取得了胜利。【原文：The Ecuador attorney general's office and Chilean state miner Codelco both claimed victory on Friday after an international arbitration court ordered Ecuador to pay some $25 million of a $568 million claim regarding a major copper project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/ecuador-wins-llurimagua-arbitration-case-against-chiles-codelco-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLR5GVDOTNKETJWYQF4HKC7W4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>