<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:07:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:07:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚澳新银行称市场主管 Sidher 将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚澳新银行集团（ANZ Group）周三表示，其市场董事总经理安舒尔-西德（Anshul Sidher）将离职，这是新任首席执行官努诺-马托斯（Nuno Matos）领导下的又一重要人事变动。【原文：Australian lender ANZ Group said on Wednesday its markets managing director, Anshul Sidher, will leave, in another key executive change under new Chief Executive Nuno Matos.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australias-anz-says-markets-chief-sidher-leave-bank-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23WHTVUIOFPYRP5W2RGFRCVVMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:16:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韦格威生产商诺和诺德将在重组中裁员 9000 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）周三表示，该公司将在重组中裁员 9000 人，旨在每年节省 80 亿丹麦克朗（约合 12.6 亿美元），以应对来自美国主要竞争对手礼来公司（Eli Lilly）不断上升的压力。【原文：Wegovy-maker Novo Nordisk will cut 9,000 jobs in a restructuring, aiming to save 8 billion Danish crowns ($1.26 billion) annually, the company said on Wednesday, as it battles rising pressure from main U.S. rival Eli Lilly .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wegovy-maker-novo-nordisk-cut-9000-jobs-restructuring-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHZRUOQVFNOIFGCTSQ3UXUDZUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌取消欧盟和英国部分云数据传输费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌周三表示，在《欧盟数据法案》于周五生效之前，谷歌已经取消了欧盟和英国机构在两个或多个云平台上 "并行 "处理工作负载的数据传输费用。【原文：Google said on Wednesday it had scrapped data transfer fees for organisations processing workloads "in parallel" across two or more cloud platforms in the European Union and Britain ahead of the EU Data Act coming into effect on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/google-scraps-some-cloud-data-transfer-fees-eu-uk-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P35SY5LKQRLPRCMR64L4I65NU4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，埃克森预计欧盟将签署美国天然气长期协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，埃克森美孚预计，欧盟将根据其购买数十亿美元美国能源的承诺，签署长达数十年的美国天然气合同。【原文：ExxonMobil expects the European Union to sign multi-decade U.S. gas contracts under its pledge to buy billions of dollars of American energy, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-expects-eu-sign-long-term-us-gas-deals-ft-reports-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPKJCJVRGZJB7G3PJN6G44UOVY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在旺季中错过了数十亿美元的中国大豆销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商和分析师表示，由于贸易谈判陷入僵局，出口停止，竞争对手南美供应商介入填补空缺，美国农民在黄金销售季节过半时错过了数十亿美元的对华大豆销售。【原文：U.S. farmers are missing out on billions of dollars of soybean sales to China halfway through their prime marketing season, as stalled trade talks halt exports and rival South American suppliers step in to fill the gap, traders and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-misses-out-billions-china-soybean-sales-midway-through-peak-season-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYUZBTFFF5PSBOXZMSGPVQO6XU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 04:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 滞胀阴影笼罩美联储减息乐观情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQU5ZHTZBZJEZPSD5LO765AW24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 04:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德勤报告预测，美国假日销售额将出现自大流行病以来最缓慢的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德勤（Deloitte）在周三发布的一份预测报告中称，由于宏观经济的不确定性拖累了消费者支出，预计美国假日销售额将以自大流行病以来最慢的速度增长。【原文：U.S. holiday sales are projected to grow at their slowest pace since the pandemic, Deloitte said in a forecast released on Wednesday, as macroeconomic uncertainties weigh on consumer spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-holiday-sales-set-slowest-growth-since-pandemic-deloitte-report-forecasts-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7RMOMO6QJKAJL3NSUNYQHZ5D4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 04:13:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[留在欧洲"：中国汽车制造商借鉴大众汽车的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商正在欧洲大举进军，其高管表示，他们将继续留在欧洲，这凸显了一个关键的逆转，因为从比亚迪到上汽集团，这些品牌正在欧洲大陆抢占市场份额，而在欧洲大陆，这些品牌曾经在销售方面举步维艰。【原文：Chinese car makers are making inroads in Europe and executives say they are in the region to stay, underscoring a key reversal as brands from BYD to SAIC take market share on a continent where they once struggled to make sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/in-europe-stay-chinese-carmakers-steal-leaf-vws-playbook-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E53NOVQV3ZJ2BMILRZDWLNKUIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 04:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市上涨，债券下跌，交易商判断美联储加大减息力度的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，亚洲股市追随华尔街走高，债券下跌，原因是交易商加强了对美国劳动力市场疲软将促使美联储下周至少降息四分之一点的押注。【原文：Asian stocks tracked Wall Street higher on Wednesday and bonds fell as traders firmed up bets that U.S. labour market softness would spur the Federal Reserve to cut rates by at least a quarter point next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG2FFOMGBVK4XIYYLOYSLHYXOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 03:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚斥资 11 亿澳元打造 Anduril 水下无人机舰队]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚说，它将斥资 17 亿澳元（11 亿美元）购买一支 "幽灵鲨 "自主潜水器舰队，该舰队由澳大利亚国防军和美国初创公司 Anduril Industries 共同开发，用于监视和打击。【原文：Australia said it will spend A$1.7 billion ($1.1 billion) on a fleet of "Ghost Shark" autonomous undersea vehicles, developed by its defence force and U.S. startup Anduril Industries, for surveillance and strikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australia-spend-11-billion-anduril-undersea-drone-fleet-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVRUAKYHSFMSPKDH4JBT3UTEHM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 02:52:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arm 推出面向人工智能的新一代移动芯片设计]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arm控股公司周二表示，它将推出一套名为Lumex的下一代芯片设计，该设计已针对人工智能进行了优化，无需访问互联网即可在智能手机和手表等移动设备上运行。【原文：Arm Holdings said on Tuesday it was launching its next-generation set of chip designs called Lumex that it has optimized for artificial intelligence to run on mobile devices such as smartphones and watches without accessing the internet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/arm-launches-new-generation-mobile-chip-designs-geared-ai-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADKMIFCEZBLRZP7RQAFUEKQV3E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 02:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴地图应用涉足本地企业排名，竞争加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴旗下的地图应用Amap正在摆脱其传统的导航业务，通过推出自己的餐厅、酒店和旅游目的地排名，进一步蚕食竞争对手美团的本地生活方式领域。【原文：Alibaba's mapping app Amap is moving away from its traditional focus on navigation and is encroaching further into rival Meituan's local-lifestyle territory by launching its own ranking of restaurants, hotels and tourist destinations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/alibaba-mapping-app-steps-into-local-business-rankings-intensifying-competition-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZQHDPZVEBN3XIHR2X5N67KPLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 02:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官暂时阻止特朗普解除美联储理事库克的职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一名联邦法官暂时阻止了唐纳德-特朗普总统解除美联储理事丽莎-库克的职务，这是白宫在一场史无前例的法律战中遭遇的早期挫折，这场法律战可能会颠覆中央银行长期以来坚持的独立性。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday temporarily blocked President Donald Trump from removing Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook, an early setback for the White House in an unprecedented legal battle that could upend the central bank's long-held independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-blocks-trump-removing-fed-governor-cook-now-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5FP4Z5XS5PMXIYNC5CHGYUHHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 02:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国居民消费价格以 6 个月来最快速度下降，生产者通货紧缩有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份，中国居民消费价格以六个月来最快的速度下降，但生产者通货紧缩有所缓解，这表明决策者抑制过度竞争和关键工业部门降价的努力已初见成效。【原文：China's consumer prices fell at the fastest pace in six months in August but producer deflation eased, suggesting policymakers' efforts to rein in excessive competition and price cuts in key industrial sectors were starting to bear fruit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-consumer-prices-drop-fastest-pace-6-months-producer-deflation-eases-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5AD2Y7BDJOHZGGV77E64RL7IY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行裁员 410 人，将在印度和越南招聘员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行（National Australia Bank）发言人表示，该行将在澳大利亚的技术和企业业务部门裁员 410 人，并在印度和越南设立 127 个职位，这证实了澳大利亚金融服务联盟首次披露的裁员消息。【原文：National Australia Bank is cutting 410 jobs in its technology and enterprise operations in Australia and creating 127 roles in India and Vietnam, a spokesperson said, confirming cuts first revealed by the country's financial services union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/national-australia-bank-cuts-410-jobs-hire-india-vietnam-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">523ELOXQWJKVPFWR6PD3NXQXKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀报告公布前美元走势平稳；美国降息押注未变]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周三持稳，守住了隔夜的涨幅，因为交易商正在为本周的重要通胀报告做准备，这些报告可能有助于确定美联储下周及以后的降息规模和范围。【原文：The U.S. dollar was steady on Wednesday, holding onto overnight gains as traders braced for crucial inflation reports this week that could help define the size and scope of interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve for next week and beyond.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-treads-water-ahead-inflation-reports-us-rate-cut-bets-intact-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UP4JVWDQRNOTXBHLKDK2YGW6QQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:39:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列袭击卡塔尔、特朗普推动对俄征收关税后油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在以色列袭击了哈马斯在卡塔尔的领导层以及美国总统唐纳德-特朗普要求欧洲对俄罗斯石油买家征收关税之后，周三油价上涨，但疲软的市场前景限制了涨幅。【原文：Oil prices rose on Wednesday after Israel attacked Hamas leadership in Qatar and U.S. President Donald Trump asked Europe to impose tariffs on buyers of Russian oil, but a weak market outlook capped gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-after-israeli-attack-qatar-trumps-russia-tariff-push-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBM2WTZJM5NWLI4CJYR3B5R47U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，超薄 iPhone Air 可能是苹果公司在设计上的一次胜利]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，苹果公司首席执行官蒂姆-库克（Tim Cook）在发布 iPhone Air 时，似乎在向他的前任、设计天才史蒂夫-乔布斯（Steve Jobs）学习，这是苹果公司迄今为止最薄的手机，也是八年来苹果产品线的最大变化。【原文：Apple CEO Tim Cook appeared to be channeling his predecessor and design genius Steve Jobs on Tuesday when he unveiled the iPhone Air, the company's slimmest handset yet and the biggest change in eight years to a lineup that fans and analysts complained was stagnating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/slim-iphone-air-could-be-design-win-apple-analysts-say-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27CR6TYDZBP73HB25NFXJE43RY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:39:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查称中美紧张局势使企业信心降至新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项调查显示，政治紧张局势、激烈的国内竞争和中国经济增长放缓正在削弱美国企业对中国的信心，他们对五年前景的乐观情绪降至历史最低点。【原文：Political tensions, fierce domestic competition and China's slowing economic growth are sapping the confidence of U.S. businesses in the country, with optimism about their five-year outlook falling to a record low, a survey showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-tensions-drive-business-confidence-new-lows-survey-says-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CM3QMIZXSNKEDMJZNDXXJF2WWA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:27:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚房价将因降息而上涨，但对经济承受能力的担忧依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对房地产分析师进行的一项民意调查显示，随着借贷成本的降低刺激了房屋销售，澳大利亚的房价在未来两年内将上涨约5%-6%，尽管承受能力的压力可能会限制房价的涨幅。【原文：Australia's home prices will rise around 5-6% over the next two years as lower borrowing costs provide a fillip to home sales, although affordability pressures may cap gains, according to a Reuters poll of property analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/aussie-home-prices-rise-interest-rate-cuts-affordability-worries-persist-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQ46HQ6OEJJ7VEW7RZL7FXEVJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音防务罢工进入第六周，双方仍僵持不下]]></title><description><![CDATA[在圣路易斯地区约3200名组装军用飞机的工人举行的罢工进入第六周之际，波音防务公司和机械工人工会周二举行了会议，试图恢复合同谈判，但双方仍处于僵持状态。【原文：Boeing Defense and the machinists' union remained at loggerheads after meeting on Tuesday in an effort to resume contract negotiations as a strike by about 3,200 St. Louis-area workers that assemble military aircraft enters its sixth week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeing-defense-strike-enters-sixth-week-with-sides-still-loggerheads-2025-09-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHSC6QYE35KT5FI7BWDFMA3DJM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Synopsys 公布季度收入低于预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片设计软件供应商 Synopsys 周二公布的第三季度营收不及华尔街预期，受设计 IP 业务疲软影响，股价盘后下跌近 18.5%。【原文：Chip design software provider Synopsys missed Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue on Tuesday, hurt by weakness in its Design IP business, sending shares down nearly 18.5% after the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/synopsys-reports-quarterly-revenue-below-estimates-shares-fall-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7DJKPQCYJPIJGGBX3G3B6CF6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Klarna 在美国的 IPO 定价为每股 40 美元，估值达 151 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周二告诉路透社，瑞典金融科技公司 Klarna 及其部分股东将其美国 IPO 定价为每股 40 美元，公司估值为 151 亿美元。【原文：Swedish fintech Klarna and some of its shareholders priced its U.S. IPO at $40 per share, valuing the company at $15.1 billion, a source told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/klarna-prices-us-ipo-40-per-share-valuing-it-151-billion-source-says-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BZJZIQAOVJYVGEP3F2GGYZOZA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布洛克挫败股东对 2021 现金应用程序数据泄露的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，由推特联合创始人杰克-多西（Jack Dorsey）领导的技术和金融服务公司布洛克（Block）赢得了对其诉讼的驳回，该诉讼声称布洛克在其 Cash App 移动支付服务的大规模数据泄露事件中误导了股东。【原文：Block , the technology and financial services company led by Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey, won the dismissal on Tuesday of litigation claiming it misled shareholders in connection with a large data breach at its Cash App mobile payment service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/block-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-2021-cash-app-data-breach-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BK5OKRSGFZJIPOHNC2LJY7IBB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储提名人米兰被参议员沃伦问及道德申报不一致的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统选中填补美联储空缺席位的人选提出了新的质疑，周二要求斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）解释向美国政府道德办公室提交的文件中披露其配偶收入的差异。【原文：U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren raised fresh questions about President Donald Trump's pick to fill an open seat at the Federal Reserve, demanding on Tuesday that Stephen Miran explain a discrepancy in filings to the U.S. Office of Government Ethics disclosing income that his spouse received.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-nominee-miran-queried-by-senator-warren-about-discrepancy-ethics-filings-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2Y3FJCEIFIQVMMC2S7SYHQFRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 将加强对制药广告的执法力度，并发出执法信函]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府高级官员周二表示，美国食品和药物管理局将发出约 100 份停止执行通知和数千封信函，警告制药公司直接面向消费者的广告必须遵守已颁布的法规。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration will send out around 100 cease-and-desist enforcement notices and thousands of letters warning pharmaceutical companies that direct-to-consumer ads must comply with regulations that are already on the books, senior administration officials said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-fda-step-up-enforcement-pharma-ads-sends-enforcement-letters-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHNDXLTU6NNT3DCPSYI7UCS7W4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米-戴蒙警告美国经济前景阴云密布]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米-戴蒙（Jamie Dimon）对美国经济前景持谨慎态度，认为关税和其他地缘政治阻力的全面影响尚未完全显现。【原文：JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon is cautious about the U.S. economic outlook, believing that the full effects of tariffs and other geopolitical headwinds have yet to fully unfold.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-warns-cloudy-us-economic-outlook-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OU77CKEBNNM7LH2G5S3GKW5WE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[举报者告诉美国国会，Meta 公司将虚拟现实技术的利润置于儿童安全之上]]></title><description><![CDATA[Facebook 母公司 Meta Platforms 的两名前研究人员周二在参议院的一个小组会议上说，他们把虚拟现实平台的利润看得比安全更重要。【原文：Facebook parent Meta Platforms put profit from its virtual-reality platform over safety, two former researchers told a Senate panel on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-put-virtual-reality-profit-over-kids-safety-whistleblowers-tell-us-congress-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLGHIRAYEVNXHLWG7F2BPQRGFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:47:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 Neuralink 公司称已有 12 人接受了其植入物]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的大脑植入公司 Neuralink 周二表示，全球已有 12 人收到了它的芯片。【原文：Elon Musk's brain implant company Neuralink said on Tuesday that 12 people worldwide have received its chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/musks-neuralink-says-12-people-have-received-its-implants-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J44J62PJHZI2ZNXBXP5GFHOQVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国要求餐饮公司向儿童推广更健康的食品]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 "让美国再次健康 "委员会周二发布的第二份报告，美国联邦政府将要求餐馆通过推广健康饮食和限制不健康食品广告来自律其对儿童的营销行为。【原文：The U.S. federal government will ask restaurants to self-regulate their marketing to children by promoting healthy meals and limiting advertisements for unhealthy foods, according to the "Make America Healthy Again" Commission’s second report released Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-asks-restaurant-companies-promote-healthier-foods-children-2025-09-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2QSXCQNBZPOTKB75D6IJB6CTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>