<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:05:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:05:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通称，散户购买股票的规模为过去十年来最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）在周五的一份报告中说，散户投资者周四买入了 47 亿美元的股票，创下了过去十年来的最高水平。【原文：Retail investors bought $4.7 billion in stocks on Thursday, the highest level over the past decade, JPMorgan said in a note on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/retail-bought-stocks-largest-level-over-past-decade-jpmorgan-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWTDH4C46VNQJHTDKDY6DTYUGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:58:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场担忧工业需求，白银创逾八周新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，白银价格跌至逾八周低点，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的一系列关税措施引发了经济衰退的担忧，从而主导了市场对工业贵金属需求的担忧情绪。【原文：Prices of silver dropped to over eight-week lows on Friday as concerns about demand for the industrial precious metal dominated sentiment due to recession fears stemming from U.S. President Donald Trump's slew of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/silver-hits-over-eight-week-low-market-frets-about-industrial-demand-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4SLONYXLBMFVCJM7DWMZJFPJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中国对美国的关税报复 "玩错了]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五表示，在中国政府对美国的新关税进行报复，公布了包括对美国商品征收34%的额外关税在内的反制措施之后，中国 "玩错了"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday said China "played it wrong" after Beijing retaliated against new U.S. tariffs, unveiling countermeasures that included additional duties of 34% on U.S. goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-china-played-it-wrong-retaliation-against-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FRSMSLM6JL6PAXYM2TOHIHBJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:49:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发经济衰退担忧，纳斯达克指数将确认进入熊市]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收的关税可能引发贸易战，并使全球经济陷入衰退，投资者纷纷逃离风险较高的资产，科技股重镇纳斯达克综合指数周五将确认进入熊市，从近期的历史高点下跌超过20%。【原文：The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was set to confirm it was in a bear market on Friday, down more than 20% from a recent record high, as investors fled riskier assets on fears that tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump could spark a trade war and tip the global economy into recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-set-confirm-bear-market-trump-tariffs-trigger-recession-fears-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LP4NNQPKHJLMPKB5UA2KU4625Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国反击美国关税，道指走上修正之路]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普政府宣布对贸易伙伴全面征收关税一天后，中国采取了新的关税报复措施，道指从 12 月份创纪录的收盘高点下跌了 10%，有望在周五确认回调。【原文：The Dow fell 10% from its record closing high in December, putting it on track to confirm a correction on Friday, after China retaliated with fresh tariffs a day after the Trump administration announced sweeping levies on trade partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/dow-correction-path-china-strikes-back-against-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBHLN7CBSNKT3EBPO4ZNPRH5NQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:43:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[接下来的市场：美元信心危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[在市场恐慌的时候，投资者倾向于涌向安全的美元，但当本周股市因美国关税而暴跌时，他们却逃离了美元。投资者说，这是一个迹象，表明美元的全球地位可能正在削弱。【原文：In times of market panic investors tend to rush to the safety of the dollar, but when stocks swooned in response to U.S. tariffs this week, they ran away from it. Investors say it's a sign that the greenback’s global standing may be eroding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/next-up-markets-crisis-confidence-dollar-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXD6O6JQCJK2LHWG6OHGKYWUDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 的内容审核承包商在巴塞罗那裁员 2000 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[当地工会 CCOO 和 UGT 表示，在 Facebook 所有者 Meta Platforms 解除合同后，总部位于加拿大的科技公司 Telus 将从其位于巴塞罗那的内容审核中心解雇多达 2000 人。【原文：Canadian-based tech company Telus is dismissing as many as 2,000 people from its content moderation centre in Barcelona after Facebook owner Meta Platforms severed its contract, local unions CCOO and UGT said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/metas-content-moderation-contractor-cuts-2000-jobs-barcelona-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5OIGGYDNBNQBBXHN25CYNMCTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:40:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可可、咖啡、糖价格下滑，市场仍受特朗普关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场仍然受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普 "解放日 "全面关税的影响，特别是在中国对美国进口商品征收关税进行报复之后，世界可可、咖啡和糖的价格周五再次下滑。【原文：World cocoa, coffee and sugar prices slid again on Friday as markets remained rattled by U.S. president Donald Trump's sweeping 'Liberation Day' tariffs, especially after China retaliated with its own tariffs on U.S. imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/cocoa-coffee-sugar-prices-slide-markets-remain-rattled-by-trump-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDDVJ4OQU5L7HDJIFXFCVATMFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:16:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对美国农产品的报复打击了大豆，支持了巴西]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五对美国新关税的报复行动将加速中国政府向包括巴西在内的其他农产品供应商的转变，这一转变始于唐纳德-特朗普总统第一任期内的贸易战。【原文：China's retaliation on Friday against new U.S. tariffs is poised to accelerate Beijing's move towards alternative suppliers for agriculture goods including Brazil, a shift that began during the trade war of President Donald Trump's first term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-retaliation-us-farm-goods-hits-soybeans-bolstering-brazil-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NVSXREWUFOZFAJEJNUFVTLD4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 强劲的就业报告使美联储在关税困扰下陷入宽松窘境]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份美国经济新增就业岗位远超预期，但在商业信心下滑和股市大跌的背景下，唐纳德-特朗普总统全面征收进口关税可能会在未来数月考验劳动力市场的韧性。【原文：The U.S. economy added far more jobs than expected in March, but President Donald Trump's sweeping import tariffs could test the labor market's resilience in the months ahead amid sagging business confidence and a stock market selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-strong-jobs-report-creates-fed-easing-quandary-amid-tariff-distress-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRKPQKJ5TNKVBGJASZQCRO7JM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在上月就业大幅增长之后，美联储被认为要等到 6 月才会开始降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对全球进口商品征收全面关税之际，一份政府报告显示上月就业增长强于预期，缓解了人们对劳动力市场状况的担忧。【原文：The Federal Reserve is seen waiting until June to start cutting interest rates after a government report showed stronger than expected jobs growth last month that eased concern about the state of the labor market as President Donald Trump moves to put sweeping tariffs on imports from around the globe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-go-big-with-june-start-interest-rate-cuts-traders-bet-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZXT67D3I5ITJI75WR5CKEZGVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国就美国新关税向世贸组织提出申诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国表示已于周五向世界贸易组织正式投诉美国的新关税措施，称这些措施违反了世贸组织规则，并要求进行磋商。【原文：China said it had opened a formal complaint against the new U.S. tariffs with the World Trade Organization on Friday, saying the measures violate WTO rules and requesting consultations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-files-complaint-with-wto-over-new-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUQXQVFWKVP4BLTDBYH7V5MGOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 中国在全球贸易战中采取报复行动后，石油暴跌 8]]></title><description><![CDATA[继美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周早些时候全面征收关税之后，中国周五又对美国商品征收 34% 的额外关税，从而使全球贸易冲突升级。【原文：China escalated the global trade conflict on Friday by imposing an additional 34% tariff on U.S. goods, following President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/view-oil-tumbles-8-after-china-retaliates-global-trade-war-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKI3AEPUDFMHFI67XBXO62N5ZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月份就业增长超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份美国经济新增就业岗位远超预期，但在商业信心下滑和股市大跌的背景下，唐纳德-特朗普总统全面征收进口关税可能会在未来数月考验劳动力市场的韧性。【原文：The U.S. economy added far more jobs than expected in March, but President Donald Trump's sweeping import tariffs could test the labor market's resilience in the months ahead amid sagging business confidence and a stock market selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-growth-beats-expectations-march-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RMQBBFGV5RPGZLHS6MIKCBWIWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:38:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，汽车制造商 INEOS 调整定价]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于伦敦的英力士汽车公司周五表示，由于新的25%汽车进口关税，该公司正在提高其高档汽车的价格。【原文：London-based INEOS Automotive is increasing prices on its premium vehicles as a result of the new 25% tariff on auto imports, the company said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/automaker-ineos-adjusts-pricing-result-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J3MM4W3HLFINJOQBY2ZDKWEQS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:38:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年，Spotify 向尼日利亚和南非艺术家支付的版税激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[音频流媒体巨头 Spotify 去年向尼日利亚和南非（其最大的两个非洲市场）艺人支付的版税飙升至约 5900 万美元，因为艺人对非洲大陆音乐的兴趣与日俱增。【原文：Audio streaming giant Spotify's royalty payments to artists from Nigeria and South Africa - its two biggest African markets - spiked to around $59 million last year as performers rode a wave of growing interest in music from the continent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/spotify-royalty-payouts-nigerian-south-african-artists-boom-2024-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GL6TQPHN6RIH5LEDCUG2T5OAKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国报复特朗普关税，科技股和银行股首当其冲]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国政府对美国商品征收34%的额外关税进行报复之后，美国科技重镇、银行和石油巨头周五扩大了跌幅，这加剧了投资者对全球贸易战升级的担忧，而贸易战升级又加剧了对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. tech heavyweights, banks and oil majors extended losses on Friday after Beijing retaliated with additional duties of 34% on U.S. goods, amplifying investor concerns over an escalating global trade war that has stoked fears of a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tech-bank-stocks-bear-brunt-china-retaliates-trump-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMP5O5K4WZJYJGWSL7PPOCVCAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司 SandboxAQ 新增英伟达和谷歌为支持者，再融资 1.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[利用量子计算技术为企业开发定量人工智能模型的初创公司 SandboxAQ 表示，该公司已从包括谷歌、英伟达（Nvidia）和法国巴黎银行（BNP Paribas）在内的新投资者那里筹集了 1.5 亿美元。【原文：SandboxAQ, a startup drawing on quantum computing techniques to develop quantitative artificial intelligence models for enterprises, said it has raised $150 million from new investors including Google, Nvidia and BNP Paribas .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-startup-sandboxaq-adds-nvidia-google-backers-raises-additional-150-million-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGAYSYO5V5KDVATPYBNVDJVZNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:08:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税担忧升级，投资者逃离美国股票基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月2日的一周里，美国股票基金出现资金外流，原因是投资者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收贸易关税可能会推高成本、给企业利润带来压力并加剧经济衰退风险的担忧与日俱增，因而抛售风险资产。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw outflows in the week ending April 2 as investors shed risky assets on growing concerns that President Donald Trump's sweeping trade tariffs could drive up costs, pressure corporate profits and heighten recession risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/investors-flee-us-equity-funds-escalating-tariff-concerns-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4HEO4SUSZL2ZPQX4WLDF2RCTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:58:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国以稀土出口管制回击美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为对唐纳德-特朗普总统一揽子关税计划的回应，中国周五对一些稀土元素实施了出口限制，这可能会切断美国与从智能手机到电动汽车电池等各种产品所需的重要矿产的联系。【原文：China placed some rare earth elements under export restrictions on Friday as part of its response to President Donald Trump's tariff package, potentially cutting the U.S. off from critical minerals vital to everything from smartphones to electric car batteries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-hits-back-us-tariffs-with-rare-earth-export-controls-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5MBLZPRMROYRMDMRW5Y27UJGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:53:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发美国经济衰退担忧，印度 IT 企业做好应对准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，印度价值 2830 亿美元的 IT 行业未来一年将面临严峻考验，因为关税可能会刺激其主要美国市场的通货膨胀，并迫使客户削减支出。【原文：India's $283-billion IT sector should brace for a rough year ahead as tariffs are likely to stoke inflation in its key U.S. market and force clients to cut spending, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indian-it-firms-brace-impact-tariffs-fan-us-recession-fears-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CZYMEEGC5NKZOMYTPC6HUZ4AE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道德国为欧洲通信卫星公司在乌克兰的互联网提供资金，马斯克紧张局势加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[柏林一直在为乌克兰接入法国欧洲通信卫星公司（Eutelsat）运营的卫星互联网网络支付费用，因为欧洲正在寻求埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 "星际链路"（Starlink）的替代方案。【原文：Berlin has been paying for Ukraine's access to a satellite-internet network operated by France's Eutelsat , as Europe seeks alternatives to Elon Musk’s Starlink.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/germany-funds-eutelsat-internet-ukraine-musk-tensions-rise-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKPZB7SYSJK4TOY7GMOATZ62GI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:37:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北约代表吕特表示，美国关税并未违反北约条约]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，北约秘书长马克-吕特（Mark Rutte）在布鲁塞尔与北约外长会晤后表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统宣布的美国全面新关税并未违反北约条约。【原文：The sweeping new U.S. tariffs announced by President Donald Trump do not violate NATO treaties, the military alliance's Secretary-General Mark Rutte said on Friday after meeting NATO foreign ministers in Brussels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-tariffs-dont-violate-nato-treaty-says-natos-rutte-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5SPBWZYXVKHRIZQRHPBTKNYOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易关税引发经济放缓担忧，全球货币市场资金流入激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月2日的一周里，全球货币市场基金出现大量资金流入，原因是投资者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的激进贸易政策越来越谨慎，这些政策加剧了对全球经济放缓的担忧，并促使一些经济学家上调了对经济衰退的预测。【原文：Global money market funds saw massive inflows in the week ending April 2 as investors grew cautious over U.S. President Donald Trump's aggressive trade policies, which are heightening fears of a global slowdown and prompting some economists to revise their recession projections upward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMGBRPKSQRPGBPK6BWNCXVHZLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税冲击后，评级机构标普将审查所有全球预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评级巨头S&amp;P Global表示，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周大规模征收世界贸易关税之后，该公司正在审查其所有宏观经济预测，此举可能会加剧人们对信用评级再次下调的担忧。【原文：Credit ratings giant S&amp;P Global has said it is reviewing all its macro economic forecasts in the wake of Donald Trump's sweeping world trade tariffs this week, a move likely to fuel concerns of a renewed wave of credit score downgrades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/ratings-agency-sp-review-all-global-forecasts-after-us-tariff-shock-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3G7EUVU4KRKDZBODFYDSZYGJ3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start Campus 计划投资 93.5 亿美元建设葡萄牙数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国投资基金 Davidson Kempner 和英国的 Pioneer Point Partners 计划到 2030 年投资 85 亿欧元（93.5 亿美元）在葡萄牙建设一个数据中心枢纽，以满足大型科技和人工智能公司日益增长的需求。【原文：U.S. investment fund Davidson Kempner and Britain's Pioneer Point Partners plan to invest 8.5 billion euros ($9.35 billion) by 2030 in a data centre hub in Portugal to serve a growing demand from major tech and artificial intelligence companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/start-campus-plans-invest-935-billion-portugal-data-hub-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5R6SG2DIPVOU3K5IHLLFUNHYUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:10:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储经济衰退警报之一发出 2008 年式信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储首选的经济衰退指标之一本周的恶化速度与 2008 年一样快，这是一个最新迹象，表明债券投资者正在为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税政策导致经济急剧放缓做好准备。【原文：One of the Federal Reserve's preferred recession indicators has this week deteriorated as fast as it did in 2008, the latest sign that bond investors are bracing for a sharp economic slowdown as a result of U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/one-feds-top-recession-alarms-sends-2008-style-signal-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IK3A6MPHCZKPDOEQKMSWCAAWXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 投资者对中国对美国商品征收报复性关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五宣布对美国商品征收 34% 的额外关税，以报复美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周实施的全面关税措施，这些措施加剧了市场对经济衰退的担忧，并引发了全球股市暴跌。【原文：China announced additional tariffs of 34% on U.S. goods on Friday, retaliating to President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs this week that have fed fears of a recession and triggered a global stock market rout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/view-investors-react-chinas-retaliatory-tariffs-us-goods-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4FFV6UWYJN73HQTWPIJRO7V3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税将削弱印度钻石业，损害就业和出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国的高额关税可能会破坏印度的宝石和珠宝出口，危及成千上万工人的生计，一股焦虑情绪笼罩着印度的钻石抛光中心苏拉特。【原文：A wave of anxiety has gripped India's diamond polishing hub of Surat, as hefty U.S. tariffs threaten to undermine the country's gem and jewellery exports, putting at risk the livelihoods of thousands of workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-tariffs-set-cripple-indias-diamond-industry-hurting-jobs-exports-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UE7Q74QKTVI3FINU2PND6I56PY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:56:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国垃圾债券利差因贸易战担忧飙升至 17 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至周四晚些时候，美国高收益公司债券利差飙升至401个基点，创下2023年11月以来的新高，原因是全球市场担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的进口关税计划将引发贸易战。【原文：U.S. high yield corporate bond spreads surged to 401 basis points as of late Thursday, their highest since November 2023, as global markets swooned over fears that U.S. President Donald Trump's plan for import tariffs would kick off a trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-junk-bond-spreads-surge-17-month-high-trade-war-fears-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJICXFQYRZNURMV5MNZ3O7DHNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:48:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>