<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 12:08:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 12:08:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟 2 月份对美出口激增 22.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟统计局（Eurostat）周三的数据显示，2月份欧盟对美国的出口同比增长22.4%，创下13个月以来的最高出口增长率，出口总额达518亿欧元。【原文：European Union exports to the United States increased by 22.4% in February compared to the previous year, Eurostat data showed on Wednesday, marking the highest exports growth rate in 13 months and totalling 51.8 billion euros.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-exports-us-surge-by-224-february-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BOW24TFXRKU5HJJIKQQYWWHRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:57:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用电气弗诺瓦公司因电力和电气化业务强劲而实现季度收入增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用电气弗诺瓦公司（GE Vernova）周三公布的第一季度营收超过华尔街预期，主要得益于其电力和电气化部门的强劲表现，该公司股价在盘前交易中上涨超过 8%。【原文：GE Vernova reported first-quarter revenue on Wednesday that beat Wall Street estimates on the back of strong performance at its power and electrification units, sending its shares up more than 8% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/ge-vernovas-quarterly-revenue-beats-strength-power-electrification-units-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRSRUDB6GZJW7JYOOIMLGE566Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:45:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于费率上调和强劲的电力需求，NextEra 盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受电力公司上调费率和电力需求增长的提振，NextEra Energy 公司周三公布的第一季度利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：NextEra Energy beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter profit on Wednesday, boosted by rate hikes at its electric utility and increased power demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/nextera-beats-profit-expectations-rate-hikes-robust-power-demand-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJA5CGAGYBJINIJQN6FBFFX32E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:39:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司因喷气机交付量增加而减少季度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周三公布的季度亏损小于预期，因为这家美国飞机制造商生产并交付了更多的喷气式飞机，而在此之前，一场质量危机和瘫痪性罢工导致其大部分飞机的生产在2024年底停产。【原文：Boeing reported a smaller-than-expected quarterly loss on Wednesday, as the U.S. planemaker produced and delivered more jets, after a quality crisis and crippling strike shuttered production of most of its aircraft in late 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-posts-smaller-quarterly-loss-higher-jet-deliveries-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKTR6VPFGVPPPLDSDVGLNKXOXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因国防产品需求持续增长，Teledyne 季度业绩居首]]></title><description><![CDATA[受航空航天和国防领域对目标探测传感器和电子元件持续需求的推动，美国国防公司 Teledyne Technologies 周三公布的第一季度利润和收入均超出预期。【原文：U.S. defense firm Teledyne Technologies topped expectations for first-quarter profit and revenue on Wednesday, aided by sustained demand for its target detection sensors and electronic components used in aerospace and defense.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/teledyne-tops-quarterly-results-sustained-demand-defense-products-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUDMV5UNKRKG7NAUCRKRFFM5YE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[临床研究工具和服务需求稳定，赛默飞业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[赛默飞世尔科技公司（Thermo Fisher Scientific）周三公布的第一季度利润和收入均好于预期，这主要得益于市场对其用于开发疗法的产品和服务的强劲需求。【原文：Thermo Fisher Scientific reported better-than-expected profit and revenue for the first quarter on Wednesday, helped by resilient demand for its products and services used for developing therapies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/thermo-fisher-beats-estimates-steady-demand-tools-services-used-clinical-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBTHIIMVYBPKDMUF6XIZCYOFZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:19:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 因利润率提高，第二季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 周三公布的第二季度利润好于预期，并预测由于其工业解决方案部门的营业利润率提高，本季度的收入将有所增长。【原文：TE Connectivity reported better-than-expected profit in the second quarter on Wednesday and forecast upbeat revenue for the current quarter, on the back of improved operating margin at its industrial solutions unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/te-connectivity-tops-second-quarter-profit-estimates-improved-margins-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AC3QWQTEOFNZVHTMKXLK5P3RFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用动力公司利润因国防需求持续增长而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用动力公司（General Dynamics）周三公布第一季度利润增长 27%，主要得益于地缘政治不确定性下对军用弹药和车辆的持续需求，国防部门业绩强劲。【原文：General Dynamics reported a 27% rise in first-quarter profit on Wednesday, driven by strength in its defense units owing to sustained demand for military munitions and vehicles amid geopolitical uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/general-dynamics-profit-rises-sustained-defense-demand-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDKETJ6EAJMXNNACMRFGSXAR7Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易量创历史新高，CME 季度利润大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，衍生品交易所 CME 集团公布第一季度利润增长近 12%，主要得益于各产品线创纪录的交易量，交易员们在瞬息万变的经济环境中游刃有余。【原文：Derivatives exchange CME Group posted a nearly 12% jump in its first-quarter profit on Wednesday, buoyed by record trading volumes across product lines as traders navigated a rapidly changing economic environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cmes-quarterly-profit-jumps-strong-trading-activity-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6XGOMKDIZIAXIYXMGQQENIRKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:07:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特航空公司确认订购 10 架空客 A330neo 喷射机]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特廉价航空公司 flyadeal 周三确认了一项订购 10 架空客 A330neo 宽体客机的协议，以拓展东南亚快速增长的长途市场。【原文：Saudi budget carrier flyadeal on Wednesday confirmed a deal to order 10 Airbus A330neo wide-body passenger jets as it expands into fast-growing long-haul markets in Southeast Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/saudi-flyadeal-confirms-order-10-airbus-a330neo-jets-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMEFLPTOUBMLPMM55QJSUXDY24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士莲暂缓加拿大供应转移，提振当地库存]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士巧克力制造商瑞士莲（Lindt & Spruengli）表示，该公司仍在研究如何应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发起的不断升级的贸易战，并暂时增加了在加拿大的库存，以缓解关税带来的影响。【原文：Swiss chocolate maker Lindt & Spruengli said it is still working out how to deal with the escalating trade war launched by U.S. President Donald Trump and has temporarily increased stocks in Canada to cushion the impact of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/lindt-holds-back-canada-supply-shift-boosts-local-stocks-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IML2QPIFQVKTFIVDED57LLC4WA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本立法者敦促养老基金投资国内私募股权基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群日本执政党议员周三呼吁日本顶级公共养老基金 GPIF 扩大对国内私募股权和风险投资基金的投资，以加强国内私人资产投资链。【原文：A group of Japan's ruling party lawmakers on Wednesday called on the country's top public pension fund GPIF to expand investment in domestic private equity and venture capital funds to strengthen the domestic private asset investment chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-lawmakers-urge-pension-fund-invest-domestic-private-equity-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LHS7ABHQRIN7L42LQ2C2F4LRE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:40:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲对科技监管保持强硬态度，谷歌和 X 成为下一个目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位直接知情人士透露，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌和埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 可能是下一个面临欧洲监管机构罚款的公司，因为尽管担心美国会征收报复性关税，欧洲监管机构仍会对大型科技公司采取强硬措施。【原文：Alphabet's Google and Elon Musk's X may be the next to face fines from European regulators, as they stay tough on Big Tech despite concerns of retaliatory U.S. tariffs, according to three sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-x-next-targets-europe-stays-tough-tech-regulation-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U3YINXL5ZL6NGXFQB333XDC2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AT&T 依靠捆绑计划新增用户数超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，AT&amp;T 第一季度无线新增用户数超出华尔街预期，主要原因是市场对其捆绑高速光纤服务和 5G 移动产品的计划需求稳定。【原文：AT&amp;T beat Wall Street estimates for wireless subscriber additions in the first quarter on Wednesday, driven by steady demand for its plans that bundled high-speed fiber services and 5G mobile offerings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/att-leans-bundled-plans-beat-estimates-subscriber-additions-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYEHUDLNTZN6JFMOJ2BZMDKERY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能繁荣受到关税和全球经济动荡的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国企业的人工智能投资热潮摆脱了对回报缓慢的担忧，也摆脱了对中国 DeepSeek 廉价制造的人工智能模型的怀疑。但是，特朗普政府挑起的全球贸易战有可能阻碍从能源到软件等各行各业的繁荣。【原文：Corporate America's artificial intelligence investment frenzy has shrugged off fears of slow returns and doubts fueled by AI models built cheaply by China's DeepSeek. But a global trade war started by the Trump administration threatens to stall the boom across industries from energy to software.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-boom-under-threat-tariffs-global-economic-turmoil-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMHT3WBDMRPEHPTDYP6PZ4EEOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:34:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 美好的一天？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天美国和全球市场的重要事件。金融市场》欧洲、中东和非洲地区编辑 Dhara Ranasinghe 对美国和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today. A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by Dhara Ranasinghe, Editor, Financial Markets EMEA.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3AXSAVJLVPPNPSQPRL53DP7F4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:28:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席财务官称，Temenos 正在追赶因特朗普关税不确定性而推迟的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行软件公司Temenos的财务总监周三表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）4月2日宣布加征关税，该公司上个月推迟了一些交易，但现在这些交易正在进行中，而且该集团在美国的发展计划也已步入正轨。【原文：Swiss banking software company Temenos had some deals delayed last month because of U.S. President Donald Trump's April 2 tariff announcement, but they were coming through now and the group's U.S. growth plans were on track, its finance chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/temenos-catching-up-deals-delayed-by-trump-tariffs-uncertainty-cfo-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USGUFXO3BFIT3NQOXEZU6ND5AI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:25:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赫伯罗特称 30% 运往美国的中国货物被取消]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国集装箱航运集团赫伯罗特的一位发言人周三告诉路透社，受两个超级经济大国之间贸易冲突的影响，该集团的客户已经取消了30%从中国运往美国的货物。【原文：Customers of Hapag-Lloyd have cancelled 30% of shipments to the United States from China, spooked by the trade conflict between the two economic super powers, a spokesperson for the German container shipping group told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hapag-lloyd-says-30-chinas-us-bound-shipments-have-been-cancelled-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5M7RVXWRK5PWPO7HZFKB77TU6E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者支出不确定，宝洁盈利预测受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝洁公司（Procter & Gamble）将于本周四公布第三季度业绩报告，届时该公司的年度目标将成为关注焦点，一些分析师预计，由于全球贸易紧张局势导致的支出不确定性，该公司的业绩预期将被下调。【原文：Procter & Gamble's annual targets will be in focus when the consumer goods bellwether reports third-quarter results on Thursday, with some analysts expecting a forecast cut due to uncertainty around spending amid global trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pgs-earnings-forecast-spotlight-uncertainty-plagues-consumer-spending-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJRDR7FTZZIS7D3TPLYXLO2QDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税可能意味着更多的美国钢铁岗位。会有工人来填补吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿肯色州密西西比县因钢铁行业的就业机会而繁荣，但却因劳动力短缺而苦苦挣扎。尽管工资不错，但工人们仍要长途跋涉或住在房车里。当地经济持续面临挑战，但仍努力通过住房激励措施和培训计划吸引人才。【原文：Mississippi County, Arkansas, thrives with steel industry jobs, but struggles with a labor shortage. Workers commute long distances or live in RVs, despite good wages. Local economic challenges persist, with efforts to attract talent through housing incentives and training programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tariffs-may-mean-more-us-steel-jobs-will-there-be-workers-fill-them-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUJFCXAGX5OYXMWWGHLW6RJZKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Benchmark Minerals 与 ICE 合作开发电池材料期货]]></title><description><![CDATA[BMI告诉路透社，洲际交易所（ICE）将在6月份推出的合约中采用咨询公司Benchmark Minerals Intelligence（BMI）评估的电池材料锂和钴的价格。【原文：Prices of battery materials lithium and cobalt assessed by consultancy Benchmark Minerals Intelligence (BMI) will be used for contracts launched by Intercontinental Exchange (ICE) in June, BMI told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/benchmark-minerals-ice-team-up-battery-material-futures-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LF5UM5WORNHFEKQHVSLYZBTTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普收回解雇美联储主席的威胁，美股期货跳涨；特斯拉跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普总统放弃解雇美联储主席的威胁并提高了与中国达成贸易协议的希望之后，美国股指期货周三大幅飙升。【原文：U.S. stock index futures leapt on Wednesday, after President Donald Trump backed off from his threats to fire the head of the Federal Reserve and raised hopes for a trade deal with China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-jump-trump-backtracks-threats-fire-fed-head-tesla-jumps-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23GHZ6W7D5NZPCIM7KTMM7C3YM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:49:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司因违反欧盟法律被罚款 5.7 亿美元，梅塔公司被罚款 2.28 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，苹果公司被罚款 5 亿欧元（约合 5.7 亿美元），梅塔公司被罚款 2 亿欧元，这是欧盟反垄断监管机构根据旨在遏制大型科技公司势力的里程碑式立法做出的首批处罚。【原文：Apple was fined 500 million euros ($570 million) on Wednesday and Meta 200 million euros, as European Union antitrust regulators handed out the first sanctions under landmark legislation aimed at curbing the power of Big Tech.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apple-fined-570-million-meta-228-million-breaching-eu-law-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZRRCR2UOZIELIPJ43GDZUJEHE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税动荡令欧洲银行 2025 年盈利能力蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着国际贸易关系的破灭和全球经济信心的跌落，欧洲主要银行正面临着这样一种可能性：2025 年最强劲的一个季度可能已经过去。【原文：With international trade ties in tatters and confidence in the global economy plumbing fresh depths, Europe's leading banks are confronting a possibility that their strongest quarter of 2025 may already be behind them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tariff-turmoil-casts-pall-over-european-banks-2025-earnings-power-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YR5JYPQCMNPVFMT5JMQHW3NLJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾芯片制造商联电表示目前没有正在进行的合并 "活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾芯片制造商联华电子公司（UMC）周三表示，目前没有正在进行的并购 "活动"。【原文：Taiwanese chipmaker United Microelectronics Corp (UMC) said on Wednesday that there was currently no ongoing merger "activity".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-chipmaker-umc-says-no-ongoing-merger-activity-right-now-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XN35ANEAEFIDRJWVKVHVVOPERY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Check Point 软件公司第一季度利润和收入均高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Check Point 软件技术公司第一季度利润超出预期，主要得益于其人工智能驱动的保护企业网络免受网络威胁产品的销售增长。【原文：Check Point Software Technologies beat first-quarter profit expectations, boosted by sales gains in its AI-driven products to protect corporate networks from cyber threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/check-point-software-q1-profit-revenue-top-estimates-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKPZXWBDQNJ47MO7SC7S2CNL24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:22:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行预计今年工资增长将大幅放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行周三公布的数据显示，欧元区今年的工资增长预计将大幅放缓。【原文：Wage growth in the euro zone is expected to ease considerably this year, according to data from the European Central Bank released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/ecb-expects-wage-growth-ease-considerably-this-year-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBJZCNFDZ5JD7FMOOYQHQEQQNE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:21:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来起诉四家复配商仿制减肥药]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周三表示，在美国法官上月禁止药店仿制其减肥药和糖尿病药后，该公司已起诉四家复方制剂生产商销售未经批准的含有替扎帕肽的产品。【原文：Eli Lilly said on Wednesday it had sued four compounders for selling unapproved products containing tirzepatide, after a U.S. judge last month blocked pharmacies from making copies of its weight-loss and diabetes medicines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/lilly-sues-four-compounders-over-copies-weight-loss-drugs-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q26YUZ4XTFONLADD2SB5RXTOUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国长城汽车董事长表示正寻求在巴西生产汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商长城汽车董事长周三在上海表示，长城汽车正在寻找机会将巴西作为汽车生产基地，并向附近地区扩张。【原文：Great Wall Motor is looking for opportunities to use Brazil as a base for vehicle production and expand to nearby regions, the Chinese carmaker's chairman said in Shanghai on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-great-wall-motor-is-seeking-produce-vehicles-brazil-chairman-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6MADR42DNKLXAZPHNUGAAAXAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:55:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车首席执行官表示，大众汽车在中国将经历 "适当规模 "的过程]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商大众汽车集团首席执行官周三表示，随着过去几年电动汽车销售的蓬勃发展，中国这一全球最大汽车市场的竞争日趋激烈，大众汽车将需要在中国经历一个 "适当规模 "的过程。【原文：German carmaker Volkswagen will need to go through a 'right-sizing' process in China, its group CEO said on Wednesday, as competition intensifies in the world's biggest auto market following a boom in electric vehicle sales in the past several years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/volkswagen-will-go-through-right-size-process-china-ceo-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2X4PR3XTR5JM3GS2YOS4OEU2QM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>