<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:39:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[薪资平台 Deel 在最新一轮融资中估值达 173 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[薪酬初创公司 Deel 周四表示，该公司在新一轮融资中筹集了 3 亿美元，由新投资者 Ribbit Capital 与现有支持者 Andreessen Horowitz 和 Coatue Management 共同领投，公司估值达 173 亿美元。【原文：Payroll startup Deel said on Thursday it raised $300 million in a funding round, led by new investor Ribbit Capital alongside existing backers Andreessen Horowitz and Coatue Management, valuing the company at $17.3 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/payroll-platform-deel-valued-173-billion-latest-funding-round-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZKRYCLMAVLOVEBCVAJAT5HEPU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约银行因手续费增长而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约银行周四报告称，由于股市飙升提升了客户资产价值，帮助这家全球最大的托管银行赚取了更多的费用，该行第三季度利润大幅增长了 21%。【原文：BNY reported a 21% jump in third-quarter profit on Thursday, as soaring equity markets boosted the value of its client assets, helping the world's largest custodian bank earn more in fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bnys-profit-jumps-fee-growth-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I23RBSVBZBJ33AILRMT5ELXGXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Wipro 公司第二季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度 Wipro 公司周四公布的第二季度财报显示，该公司第二季度营收超过预期，主要得益于其美洲一号市场的强劲增长，该市场包括美国和拉丁美洲的通信业务等部门。【原文：India's Wipro reported a bigger-than-expected revenue for the second quarter on Thursday, supported by strong growth in its Americas One market, which includes units such as the communications business of U.S. and Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-wipro-beats-second-quarter-revenue-view-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3XEJBGB65OZPLFYPWIZK5RKSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国扩大投资，关键矿产公司加强华盛顿游说活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对公共记录的审查以及对高管和官员的采访显示，关键矿产公司正在加大在华盛顿的游说力度，希望分享美国总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺向被认为对国家安全至关重要的公司提供的雄心勃勃的投资。【原文：Critical mineral companies are boosting lobbying efforts in Washington, hoping to share in the ambitious investments that U.S. President Donald Trump has pledged to firms deemed essential to national security, a Reuters review of public records and interviews with executives and officials showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/critical-mineral-firms-boost-washington-lobbying-us-expands-investments-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4XJCRR2WFMQRN4UFZS7JF6F5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电业绩支撑人工智能乐观情绪再起，华尔街期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周四上涨，受台积电（TSMC）强劲的季度业绩更新提振，投资者对人工智能的乐观情绪增强，芯片股延续了前几个交易日的涨势。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Thursday, boosted by strong quarterly update from TSMC that reinforced investor optimism around AI, extending a rally in chip stocks in the previous sessions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-gain-after-tsmcs-results-support-renewed-ai-optimism-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4A35EW3TBOY3CSXDSYVAFBR7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[绘制陷入困境的 First Brands 债务规模及其债权人分布图]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周，汽车零部件制造商 First Brands 的破产在信贷市场激起了涟漪，使一些世界顶级金融机构的风险暴露成为焦点。【原文：Auto parts maker First Brands' bankruptcy has sent ripples through credit markets in recent weeks, casting a spotlight on the exposure of some of the world's top financial institutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mapping-scale-beleaguered-first-brands-debts-its-creditors-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RL4MJNNFNO57NX6SH2JCCMATA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，削减成本与维持现状：竞标者对 Citgo 未来的设想截然不同]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位消息人士告诉路透社，埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）的一家附属公司希望削减委内瑞拉所有的 Citgo 石油公司的成本，而 Gold Reserve 公司的一个部门则主要致力于维持现状。【原文：An affiliate of Elliott Investment Management wants to cut costs at Venezuela-owned Citgo Petroleum while a unit of Gold Reserve would largely focus on maintaining the status quo, five sources told Reuters, as a lengthy auction that will determine the refiner's future nears an end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/cost-cutting-vs-status-quo-bidders-envision-starkly-different-futures-citgo-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7UVEVIMNRMILJWU6NHFGJAWL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kraken 与 Small Exchange 签订价值 1 亿美元的交易，以扩大美国衍生品业务规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币重量级公司 Kraken 周四表示，它已以 1 亿美元的价格从 IG 集团收购了期货交易所 Small Exchange，为推出完全基于美国的衍生品套件铺平了道路。【原文：Crypto heavyweight Kraken said on Thursday it has acquired futures exchange Small Exchange from IG Group for $100 million, paving the way to launch a fully U.S.-based derivatives suite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/kraken-signs-100-million-deal-small-exchange-bulk-up-us-derivatives-business-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGEAB6Z5TVIYJMAPAKLHUWRWSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马称供应商网络受芯片制造商 Nexperia 风波影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商宝马公司的一位发言人周四告诉路透社，宝马公司的部分供应商网络受到了美国和中国对芯片制造商Nexperia实施的出口限制的影响，因为双方在知识产权问题上的争执日益加剧。【原文：Parts of BMW's supplier network are affected by U.S. and Chinese export restrictions that have been imposed on chipmaker Nexperia amid a growing row over intellectual property, a spokesperson for the German carmaker told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bmw-says-supplier-network-impacted-by-developments-chip-maker-nexperia-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GQ237RDIZKQBBV2QADXA2UFUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，阿玛尼高管马索奇将出任时装公司首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周四透露，乔治-阿玛尼（Giorgio Armani）副总经理朱塞佩-马索奇（Giuseppe Marsocci）将被任命为这家意大利时装公司的首席执行官，这证实了当地媒体的报道。【原文：Giorgio Armani's deputy managing director, Giuseppe Marsocci, is set to be appointed chief executive of the Italian fashion house, a source said on Thursday, confirming a local media report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/armani-exec-marsocci-set-be-named-new-ceo-source-local-media-say-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNXCTHVHVNITZCKNQLFYOZXX5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:03:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[G20 风险监督机构警告全球加密货币规则存在 "重大漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[二十国集团（G20）风险监督机构周四警告说，各国在试图监管快速增长的加密货币市场方面存在 "重大差距"，这可能会损害金融稳定。【原文：There are "significant gaps" in countries' attempts to regulate fast-growing crypto markets, which could potentially harm financial stability, the G20's risk watchdog warned on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/g20-risk-watchdog-warns-significant-gaps-global-crypto-rules-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIUWFRQIPJOQVCS6FM6IB3OLQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[400 亿美元出售 Aligned 后，麦格理对人工智能和数据中心的未来充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚麦格理资产管理公司（Macquarie Asset Management，MAM）以价值 400 亿美元的交易出售了其 Aligned 数据中心业务，该公司负责人周四表示，此次出售并不表明全球数据中心的繁荣已经达到顶峰。【原文：The head of Australia's Macquarie Asset Management (MAM), which sold its Aligned Data Centers business in a deal worth $40 billion, said on Thursday the sale was not a sign the global data centre boom had peaked.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/macquarie-confident-ai-data-centre-future-after-40-billion-aligned-sale-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JW5RXZRNYJLYJPSEKIMO5YPRYA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:56:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国无人机制造商 Quantum 接近完成一轮融资，估值可能翻三番]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《经理人杂志》周四援引未具名消息人士的话报道，德国无人机制造商量子系统公司（Quantum Systems）即将完成一轮1.5亿欧元（1.75亿美元）的融资，其估值可能增至30亿欧元的三倍。【原文：German drone maker Quantum Systems is close to completing a 150 million euro ($175 million) funding round that could triple its valuation to 3 billion euros, Manager Magazin reported on Thursday, citing unnamed sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/german-drone-maker-quantum-nears-funding-round-that-could-triple-valuation-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G43PR5YWXVMYDG3RKWCRBSTNQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:36:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者呼吁丰田收购集团公司时披露更多信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球投资者呼吁丰田汽车公司就其收购集团公司丰田自动织机（Toyota Industries）的计划提供更多信息披露，批评丰田的估值 "不透明"，未能保障小股东的利益。【原文：Global investors have called on Toyota Motor to provide more disclosure about its planned buyout of group firm Toyota Industries , criticising what they said was "opaque" valuation and a failure to safeguard the interests of minority shareholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/investors-call-greater-disclosure-toyotas-buyout-group-company-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E424YVSTZRPZ3GEZMRJDYOUHGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:15:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，福特将因发动机缸体加热器问题召回超过 5.9 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周四表示，福特将在美国召回59,006辆汽车，原因是发动机缸体加热器可能出现裂缝和冷却液泄漏，导致在插入缸体加热器时发生短路。【原文：Ford is recalling 59,006 vehicles in the U.S. as the engine block heater may crack and develop a coolant leak, causing it to short circuit when the block heater is plugged in, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-over-59000-us-vehicles-over-engine-block-heater-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DWW2FJW4JOYNPMSYJINDOFWFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易摩擦加剧稀土紧张局势]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国营媒体周四对美国要求中国政府逐步减少稀土控制措施的呼吁发表了七点反驳意见，双方都在努力摆脱一连串的抨击和指责，以避免误伤对方。【原文：Chinese state media on Thursday issued a seven-point rebuttal to U.S. calls for Beijing to wind back its rare earth controls, as both sides struggle to move beyond a volley of barbs and accusations of blindsiding the other.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/rare-earths-tensions-rise-us-china-trade-barbs-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWAIUEKYGRKYZAWB2HFWZJIIFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士军刀制造商尝试新工具以应对特朗普关税打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士军刀制造商维多利诺（Victorinox）正在努力压低其在美国的售价，同时开拓新的市场，因为它正在尝试新的工具，以应对唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易关税。【原文：Swiss Army Knife maker Victorinox is trying to hold down its U.S. prices, while exploring new markets, as it experiments with new tools to navigate President Donald Trump's trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/swiss-army-knife-maker-tries-new-tools-blunt-trump-tariff-blow-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMTJYUZOMZMQZD7TKYUEUPVJHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:20:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第三季度利润增长 39.1%，创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于受益于人工智能应用领域对半导体的需求激增，全球最大的合约芯片制造商台积电周四公布的第三季度净利润大幅增长 39.1%，超过市场预期，创下历史新高。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest contract chipmaker, posted a 39.1% jump in third-quarter net profit on Thursday, beating market forecasts and hitting a record as it benefited from surging demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsmc-q3-profit-jumps-391-record-beats-expectations-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KVYG4XGABL57L4NXH535BGK74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国和美国市场疲软拖累保乐力加第一季度销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国烈酒制造商保乐力加（Pernod Ricard）表示，由于消费需求疲软以及中国和美国的去库存化，该公司第一季度销售额下降了7.6%，但仍预计2026财年的销售额将有所改善。【原文：French spirits maker Pernod Ricard said it still expected sales to improve in fiscal year 2026 after reporting a well-flagged 7.6% fall in first quarter sales, due to weak consumer demand and destocking in China and the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/weak-chinese-us-markets-weigh-pernod-ricard-q1-sales-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">245OY6ESHBPF5ILVGKSLVUC6JE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢新任首席执行官上任后销售增长超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司周四公布的销售增长和销量均好于预期，并维持了对 2025 年的展望，这是这家全球最大的包装食品公司自任命 Philipp Navratil 担任首席执行官以来首次公布业绩。【原文：Nestle reported better-than-expected sales growth and volumes on Thursday and maintained its outlook for 2025 as the world's largest packaged food company reported results for the first time since appointing Philipp Navratil as CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nestle-reports-better-than-expected-sales-growth-with-new-ceo-helm-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRK2QOUCWFLIVC6GC7UDXLRIEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:12:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马力雷诺-吉利发动机装置加速，电动汽车换挡停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国汽车制造商雷诺和中国吉利汽车公司（GEELY.UL）在 2022 年分拆内燃机业务时，这家合资企业看起来就像是过时技术的注脚。现在，Horse Powertrain 获得了新生。【原文：When French carmaker Renault and China's Geely (GEELY.UL) carved out their combustion-engine operations in 2022, the venture looked like a footnote to an outdated technology. Now, Horse Powertrain has a new lease of life.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/horse-power-renault-geely-engine-unit-speeds-up-ev-shift-stutters-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XP22QETFCFPDJIO2BQ7PJIDDNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABB 认为 "强劲的市场 "迄今未受美国关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士工程公司 ABB 周四在公布第三季度业绩时表示，目前形势 "稳健"，美国关税带来的不确定性对客户需求的影响甚微。【原文：ABB is seeing a "robust" situation with so far little impact on customer demand from the uncertainties caused by U.S. tariffs, the Swiss engineering company said on Thursday, as it reported its third quarter results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/abb-sees-robust-market-q3-profit-rises-12-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCSB6ITLTRLNXACMCGBZ254UXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 04:56:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCCGLU54F5JI7BBSHRPMUYKBLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 04:33:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国库葡萄酒公司董事长受到股东质疑，但轻松连任]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管如此，在周四举行的年度股东大会上，约翰-马伦还是以较大优势再次当选。【原文：Treasury Wine Estates shareholders grilled Chairman John Mullen over the Australian winemaker's poor performance, stock slump as well as his heavy workload, but he was re-elected by a wide margin at its annual general meeting on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australias-treasury-wine-chair-grilled-by-shareholders-comfortably-re-elected-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7G346SWOOBPTTHCO5PSKWVKNSI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 04:17:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市加入华尔街涨势，黄金因贸易忧虑创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲大部分地区股市上涨，芯片板块在隔夜美国股市强劲反弹后表现活跃。【原文：Stocks rose across most of Asia on Thursday, with the chip sector buoyant following a strong rally among U.S. peers overnight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T72S7SDU2JJ5DERUDJQN6GGXO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 03:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国总统府政策室长称对美国关税谈判 "持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国首席总统政策顾问周四表示，他对目前正在进行的与美国敲定贸易协议的谈判持 "乐观 "态度，这是官员们发表的最新言论，表明停滞数月的谈判取得了进展。【原文：South Korea's chief presidential policy adviser said on Thursday he was "optimistic" about ongoing talks to finalise a trade deal with the U.S., in the latest remarks by officials suggesting progress in negotiations that had stalled for months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korean-presidential-policy-chief-says-optimistic-about-us-tariff-talks-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQU4SWJWHZIXZKVCIL3TF5A7JQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:50:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美国网络安全服务提供商 F5 遭到入侵的责任归咎于中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三援引熟知内情的人士的话报道称，美国一家大型网络安全供应商 F5 遭到入侵的责任被归咎于来自中国的国家支持的黑客。【原文：A breach of a major U.S.-based cybersecurity provider F5 has been blamed on state-backed hackers from China, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/breach-us-based-cybersecurity-provider-f5-blamed-china-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O327YC37ORM2ZCTCCAOGVPLFZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易关系紧张，美元走软]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周四下滑，原因是中美贸易战削弱了投资者的情绪，同时美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）今年下调政策利率的信心增强也对美元构成了压力。【原文：The U.S. dollar slipped on Thursday as the Sino-U.S. trade war sapped investor sentiment, while growing confidence of the U.S. Federal Reserve cutting its policy interest rate this year also weighed on the greenback.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-soft-sino-us-trade-tension-weighs-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IVFL3GPGJK7THUOZFGFZR6HY4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 01:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 9 月失业率跃升至四年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 9 月份的失业率意外飙升至近四年来的新高，原因是有更多的人开始找工作，而就业率仅略有反弹。【原文：Australia's unemployment rate spiked unexpectedly to a near four-year high in September as more people went looking for work, while employment bounced only modestly, a weak reading that adds to the case for further cuts in interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-unemployment-rate-jumps-four-year-high-september-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBHEZ7O2HBLZRMHLIB7MPINPWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:44:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子股价创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者对半导体行业持乐观态度，韩国芯片制造商三星电子的股价周四最多上涨了 2%，创下历史新高。【原文：Shares of South Korean chipmaker Samsung Electronics rose as much as 2% on Thursday to an all-time high on investor optimism surrounding the semiconductor industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-electronics-shares-hit-record-high-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVOJIDCV4ZIA5DV4MRUVYEUWAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>