<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:39:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:39:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[南非汽车业受失业和公司倒闭打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非贸易部长周三表示，本地制造汽车的国内销量低迷、进口汽车的大量涌入以及本地含量低，已导致南非汽车行业两年内有 12 家公司倒闭，4000 多人失业。【原文：Low domestic sales of locally made cars, an influx of imports and low levels of local content have led to 12 company closures and over 4,000 job losses in the South African motor industry over two years, the trade minister said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/south-africas-auto-sector-hit-by-job-losses-company-closures-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSU2NB7PPRKOXN325RUUW6CMKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:22:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受 9 月降息预期影响，标普 500 指数和纳斯达克指数期货创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场对美联储可能在下个月重启货币政策宽松周期的信心不断增强，周三跟踪标普 500 指数和纳斯达克指数的期货价格创下历史新高。【原文：Futures tracking the S&amp;P 500 and the Nasdaq indexes were pinned at record highs on Wednesday, buoyed by increasing confidence that the Federal Reserve could restart its monetary policy easing cycle next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/sp-500-nasdaq-futures-record-highs-september-rate-cut-expectations-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHLKZUPX5FLCPODVQBUBZCMZTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:16:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制造商借助人工智能抵御关税风暴]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国割草机制造商托罗公司（The Toro Company）等制造商并未因美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收全球贸易关税的前景而感到恐慌。【原文：Manufacturers like U.S. lawnmower maker The Toro Company are not panicking at the prospect of U.S. President Donald Trump's global trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/just-time-manufacturers-turn-ai-weather-tariff-storm-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGYES4IQ2NPI7I2LBG4VHNYGHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:08:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察：五角大楼两个项目的解体可能导致代价高昂的重来]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）领导的海军和空军准备取消两个几乎已经完成的软件项目，这两个项目的开发耗时长达 12 年，总投资超过 8 亿美元，最初的目的是彻底改造陈旧的人力资源系统。【原文：Donald Trump's Navy and Air Force are poised to cancel two nearly complete software projects that took 12 years and well over $800 million combined to develop, work initially aimed at overhauling antiquated human resources systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-unraveling-two-pentagon-projects-may-result-costly-do-over-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEFUGZP5R5KRBMBBTGKYZNCFYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:05:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[渣打银行将年底以太币预测值上调至 7,500 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周三将以太坊的年终目标从 4,000 美元上调至 7,500 美元，理由是最近几个月行业参与度有所提高，而且出现了以太坊财务公司。【原文：Standard Chartered raised its year-end target for ether to $7,500 from $4,000 on Wednesday, citing improvement in industry engagement in recent months and emergence of Ethereum treasury companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/standard-chartered-lifts-year-end-ether-forecast-7500-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4JRJ3ATVZMHPJB7UP3JTR45BE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 09:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于人工智能需求激增，亏损不断扩大，CoreWeave 股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[CoreWeave 的股价在周三的盘前交易中下挫了 10%，原因是这家由英伟达（Nvidia）支持的公司公布的亏损超过了预期，令人怀疑它在人工智能需求强劲的情况下控制成本的能力。【原文：CoreWeave shares sank 10% in premarket trading on Wednesday after the Nvidia-backed company posted a bigger-than-expected loss, raising doubts about its ability to keep costs under check amid robust AI demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coreweave-shares-drop-growing-losses-eclipse-ai-demand-surge-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIPTGSB6K5KZBH26XVPIE6UMGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 09:06:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国腾讯第二季度收入增长 15%，游戏表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[腾讯周三公布第二季度收入增长 15%，主要得益于强劲的游戏表现和人工智能驱动的业务扩张。【原文：Tencent reported second-quarter revenue growth of 15% on Wednesday, driven by robust gaming performance and AI-powered business expansion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-tencent-revenue-grows-15-q2-strong-gaming-performance-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRJLASHFVVKJFKKL4CXOBCGXXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北欧半导体股价创两年新高，因强劲的业绩和第三季度业绩指引]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威芯片制造商北欧半导体公司（Nordic Semiconductor）周三公布的第二季度业绩超出了市场的一致预期，并给出了高于市场预期的第三季度收入指导，理由是主要客户的需求更加强劲，以及新的nRF54产品平台的发展势头良好。【原文：Norwegian chipmaker Nordic Semiconductor on Wednesday reported consensus-beating second-quarter results and gave a revenue guidance above market expectations for the third quarter, citing stronger demand from major customers and momentum in its new nRF54 product platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nordic-semiconductor-shares-hit-two-year-high-strong-results-q3-guidance-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2J5NJXDZQVMRRIGY5V65BBDLDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:30:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+做出增产决定后，国际能源署上调 2025 年石油供应预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在欧佩克+产油国集团决定增产之后，国际能源机构周三上调了今年的石油供应增长预测，并因主要经济体需求低迷而下调了需求预测。【原文：The International Energy Agency on Wednesday raised its forecast for oil supply growth this year following a decision by the OPEC+ producer group to hike production and lowered its demand forecast due to lacklustre demand across the major economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/iea-raises-2025-oil-supply-forecast-after-opec-output-hike-decision-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUSDVOI3R5JYDC434QJF242MQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:22:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国在人工智能芯片运输中植入追踪器，以抓捕向中国转移的芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当局在他们认为极有可能被非法转运到中国的先进芯片目标货物中秘密安装了定位跟踪装置。【原文：U.S. authorities have secretly placed location tracking devices in targeted shipments of advanced chips they see as being at high risk of illegal diversion to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-embeds-trackers-ai-chip-shipments-catch-diversions-china-sources-say-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67XL4RLEUBJWZLFKSZJHZJRCEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:14:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[价格改革后中国下半年太阳能发电量增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师称，由于取消保底定价的改革给新项目带来了不确定性，2025 年下半年中国新增太阳能发电能力将放缓，但由于前期投入，全年新增太阳能发电能力仍有可能创下历史新高。【原文：China's new solar power capacity will slow in the second half of 2025 as reforms removing guaranteed pricing create uncertainty for new projects, though full-year additions will still likely reach a record high because of frontloading, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/chinas-solar-power-capacity-growth-slow-h2-after-pricing-reforms-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GY2QW4FQ2BMQ3M32J4AV2G2RFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:54:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CoinDesk 所有者 Bullish 首次公开募股价格高于区间，募集资金超过 11 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁彼得-蒂尔（Peter Thiel）支持的加密货币交易所运营商 Bullish 表示，其美国首次公开募股的定价高于预期范围，为每股 37 美元。【原文：Bullish, a cryptocurrency exchange operator that counts billionaire Peter Thiel amongst its backers, said its U.S. initial public offering was priced above its indicated range at $37 per share.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/coindesk-owner-bullish-prices-ipo-above-range-raise-over-11-billion-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJZ4MJBZKJK57GMHZA34SL456Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金回流日本股市，摩根士丹利增持韩国股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）的一份报告显示，在日经指数（Nikkei）飙升至历史新高之前，由于关税担忧有所缓解，全球对冲基金提高了风险偏好，增加了对日本股市的风险敞口，同时加强了对韩国股市的空头头寸。【原文：Global hedge funds ramped up risk appetite and added exposure to Japanese equities ahead of the Nikkei's surge to an all-time high as tariff worries eased, while stepping up short positions in South Korea, a Morgan Stanley note showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-pile-back-into-japan-stocks-add-shorts-south-korea-morgan-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWRYL56PHJJNLNILLSFKV6HTBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来在印度推出 Mounjaro 笔，售价 160 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司（Eli Lilly）周三在印度推出了起始剂量为 2.5 毫克的减肥药 Mounjaro 的预灌封注射笔，售价为 14,000 卢比（近 160 美元），从而加强了与竞争对手诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）的竞争。【原文：Eli Lilly launched the pre-filled injector pen of its blockbuster weight-loss drug Mounjaro for 14,000 rupees (nearly $160) for its starting dose of 2.5 mg in India on Wednesday, stepping up competition with rival Novo Nordisk .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-launches-mounjaro-pen-india-priced-160-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GHMR3GQO2BIFFM4Y44CYKBRL6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，因悬挂转向节问题，捷豹路虎将在美国召回超过 12.15 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，塔塔汽车公司（Tata Motors）旗下的捷豹路虎汽车公司（Jaguar Land Rover）将在美国召回超过12.15万辆汽车，原因是这些汽车的前悬挂节出现裂纹。【原文：Tata Motors-owned Jaguar Land Rover is recalling more than 121,500 vehicles in the United States due to cracked suspension knuckles in the front, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jaguar-land-rover-recall-over-121500-us-vehicles-due-suspension-knuckle-issue-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQSINYR4I5JRFMZXTCYHEGEI2E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西填补关键供应期，美国失去对华大豆销售机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据贸易商称，由于贸易谈判迟迟未决，美国头号油籽进口国的买家锁定了在美国关键销售季节从巴西装运的货物，美国大豆出口商今年有可能错失价值数十亿美元的对华销售。【原文：U.S. soybean exporters risk missing out on billions of dollars worth of sales to China this year as trade talks drag on and buyers in the top oilseed importer lock in cargoes from Brazil for shipment during the key U.S. marketing season, according to traders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-losing-out-china-soybean-sales-brazil-fills-key-supply-period-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWQOM7A3SRPMTIGC5FNNBJMNPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求激增，迪拜开发商将建筑工程搬到公司内部]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这座以将沙漠变为天际线而闻名的城市，开发商们正在将建设过程掌握在自己手中，以求推动房地产繁荣，最大限度地增加现金流。【原文：In a city famed for transforming desert into skyline, developers are taking the building process into their own hands as they seek to turbo-charge a property boom and maximise cash flow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dubai-developers-bring-construction-in-house-demand-surges-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGRECBFOTNNLPBHFHMEXQY4TAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行面临放弃模糊通胀指标、明确收紧政策路径的压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行内部正面临越来越大的压力，要求其放弃定义模糊的通胀指标，因为对第二轮价格效应的担忧促使一些董事会成员呼吁对政策进行更鹰派的沟通，并为未来的加息制定更清晰的路径。【原文：Pressure is mounting within the Bank of Japan to ditch a vaguely defined gauge of inflation as worries about second-round price effects prompt some board members to call for a more hawkish communication of policy and a clearer path to future rate hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-faces-pressure-ditch-obscure-inflation-gauge-clear-path-tighter-policy-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WX5QJ3LOS5MQLCIBMVIU3TUKDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 06:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星展银行发现中国出口商对人民币结算的需求不断增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[东南亚资产规模最大的贷款机构星展集团的一位高管表示，中国出口商对以人民币结算的兴趣日益浓厚，尤其是与拉美和中东地区的同行。【原文：DBS Group , Southeast Asia's largest lender by assets, is seeing growing interest from Chinese exporters to settle trades in renminbi (RMB), or yuan, particularly with counterparts in Latin America and the Middle East, a senior executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dbs-sees-rising-demand-yuan-settlements-chinese-exporters-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMCQ3HVQYFMJ5FO5WQQAQIWP4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 06:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软件公司 Sapiens 将被 Advent 以 25 亿美元收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列软件公司 Sapiens International 周三表示，私募股权公司 Advent 将以 25 亿美元现金收购该公司。【原文：Israeli software company Sapiens International said on Wednesday that it will be acquired by private equity firm Advent for $2.5 billion in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/software-firm-sapiens-be-acquired-by-advent-25-billion-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4AR6XO2JCVMI3NSMZK27D73UAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着通胀降温，野村认为美联储将于 9 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[野村预计美国联邦储备委员会将在 9 月份降息 25 个基点，从而将其宽松预期提前，因为有迹象表明美国 7 月份的通胀较为温和，而且劳动力市场出现了早期裂痕。【原文：Nomura expects the U.S. Federal Reserve to cut interest rates by 25 basis points in September, bringing forward its easing forecast, amid signs of milder U.S. inflation in July and early cracks in the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nomura-sees-fed-rate-cut-september-inflation-cools-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44V4CNBSNVMZXEI74B7KMM5VQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价股市庆祝温和的通胀数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LRPXH7P5WFP6LGIRTXALYKJQDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 04:42:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球投资者涌向美国以外市场，以寻求更好的增长和估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[Global ex-U.S. equity funds received their biggest inflows in more than four-and-a-half years in July, as investors redirected capital away from the United States on concerns over the economy, stretched stock values, and a weakening dollar.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-funds-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7K2ZUSPIRRJQRM4QK3NFHP5PSQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 04:11:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀数据温和，亚洲股市上涨，美元处于守势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，亚洲股市攀升，美元受抑，原因是数据显示主要经济体的韧性和中央银行保持宽松的必要性。【原文：Stocks in Asia climbed and the U.S. dollar was subdued on Wednesday, as data showed both resilience in major economies and the need for central banks to remain accommodative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXNGW6DBSBNYDH7OCPTHAJOOPY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 02:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约银行被任命为 OpenEden 代币化美国国债基金的投资经理]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于新加坡的金融科技公司 OpenEden 周三表示，它已任命美国金融公司纽约银行（BNY）为其代币化美国国债基金的投资管理人和主要资产托管人。【原文：Singapore-based fintech firm OpenEden said on Wednesday it has appointed U.S. financial firm BNY as the investment manager and primary custodian for assets backing its tokenised U.S. Treasury fund.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bny-appointed-investment-manager-openedens-tokenised-us-treasury-fund-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUOY5QKDKVINBJUC6Y2LZQPLIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 01:57:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业报告指出美国需求放缓，油价变化不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份行业报告显示，上周美国原油库存攀升，说明夏季季节性需求期即将结束。【原文：Oil prices were little changed on Wednesday after falling in the previous session after an industry report showed U.S. crude stockpiles climbed last week illustrating the end of the seasonal summer demand period is nearing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-little-changed-industry-report-points-slowing-us-demand-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLEXKVNH7NODNIALIM27RUKOXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 01:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者关注美联储 9 月减息，美元下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[The dollar weakened on Wednesday after a tame reading on U.S. inflation bolstered expectations of a Federal Reserve rate cut next month, with President Donald Trump's attempts to extend his grip over U.S. institutions also undermining the currency.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-slips-investors-eye-september-fed-cut-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDAG6D6V4JLR5CQRDTJZ327ZMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:48:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司和墨西哥航空公司要求延期完成反垄断协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司和墨西哥航空公司周二表示反对美国交通部提出的终止反垄断协议的建议，同时要求在必要时延长协议期限。【原文：Carriers Delta and Aeromexico on Tuesday argued against winding down their antitrust agreement, as proposed by the U.S. Department of Transportation, while asking for an extension to do so if needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/delta-aeromexico-request-extension-wrap-up-antitrust-agreement-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ECYAZ5LNNLLZAY4C4U2EGZO4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:18:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Tyro Payments 公司确认来自不同方面的收购意向]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tyro Payments 公司周三表示，近几个月来已收到来自多方的收购邀约，此举是为了澄清上一交易日该公司股票在澳大利亚交易所停牌后的猜测。【原文：Tyro Payments said on Wednesday it has received takeover approaches from multiple parties in recent months, moving to clarify speculation after its shares were halted on the Australian exchange in the prior session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-tyro-payments-confirms-takeover-interest-separate-parties-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4ZMZVBXZFMDHLF5VSTOWP53MU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:12:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 7 月份批发通胀率连续第 4 个月放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的数据显示，日本 7 月份的年度批发通胀率连续第四个月放缓，这凸显了日本央行的观点，即原材料成本带来的价格上涨压力将逐渐消散。【原文：Japan's annual wholesale inflation slowed for the fourth straight month in July, data showed on Wednesday, underscoring the central bank's view that upward price pressure from raw material costs will dissipate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-wholesale-inflation-slows-4th-month-july-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFQWSUVYEJJMBGSMFJ6R5N6VBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>