<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 08:05:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟法院基本确认对高通公司的欧盟反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲二审法院周三基本确认了欧盟对美国芯片制造商高通公司（Qualcomm）的反垄断罚款，从最初的2.42亿欧元略微下调至2.387亿欧元（2.655亿美元）。【原文：Europe's second-top court largely confirmed on Wednesday an EU antitrust fine imposed on U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm , revising it down slightly to 238.7 million euros ($265.5 million) from an initial 242 million euros.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-court-largely-confirms-qualcomms-eu-antitrust-fine-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSPL77WRN5MIFJOCFCCT6GZDPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 07:53:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟法院支持谷歌挑战 14.9 亿欧元的欧盟反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲二审法院周三支持 Alphabet 旗下公司谷歌（Google）对五年前因在网络搜索广告中妨碍竞争对手而被处以 14.9 亿欧元（16.6 亿美元）反垄断罚款的质疑。【原文：Europe's second-top court on Wednesday backed Alphabet unit Google's challenge against a 1.49 billion euros ($1.66 billion) antitrust fine imposed five years ago for hindering rivals in online search advertising.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-court-backs-googles-challenge-against-149-bln-euro-eu-antitrust-fine-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIWIUHNOH5M5VEF43CBPQGNO7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 07:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼央行意外降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼央行周三宣布三年多来的首次降息，令市场大吃一惊。在美国预期的宽松周期开始之前，印尼央行采取行动支持这个东南亚最大经济体的增长。【原文：Indonesia's central bank surprised markets by delivering its first rate cut in more than three years on Wednesday, moving to bolster growth in Southeast Asia's largest economy ahead of the start of an expected easing cycle in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/indonesias-central-bank-delivers-surprise-rate-cut-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCRHJAHP4ZIBJM5YFDGCWNJUZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 07:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大工会与通用汽车达成临时协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大工会 Unifor 周三表示，它已与通用汽车公司就汽车制造商位于安大略省英格索尔工厂的工人问题达成临时协议。【原文：Canadian labor union Unifor said on Wednesday it has reached a tentative agreement with General Motors for workers at automakers' plant in Ingersoll, Ontario.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canadian-union-gm-reach-tentative-agreement-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPQSQVT3QJNFZMOM7LKOJ5IXIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 07:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国就对台武器销售对9家美国公司采取反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国外交部周三宣布就美国向台湾出售武器一事对九家与美国军方有关联的公司采取反制措施。【原文：China's foreign ministry announced countermeasures on Wednesday against nine U.S. military-linked firms over U.S. weapons sales to Taiwan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/china-sets-countermeasures-against-9-us-firms-over-weapons-sales-taiwan-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F6CT7WMKN5K7XAGSVRPCCRPXFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 07:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 8 月通胀率维持在 2.2%，英国央行考虑加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国官方数据周三显示，8月份英国通胀年率为2.2%，与7月份持平，但英国央行密切关注的服务业价格增长有所加快。【原文：British inflation stood at an annual rate of 2.2% in August, unchanged from July, but price growth in the services sector - closely watched by the Bank of England - picked up, official figures showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-inflation-unchanged-22-august-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWYH4WOXIZKQ7JLBKL5PSNRYY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 06:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Harvey Norman 因保修问题遭到集体诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[律师事务所 Echo Law 周三表示，澳大利亚最大的家电零售商 Harvey Norman 及其旗下的一个单位已代表被指销售不良保修服务的消费者向法院提起集体诉讼。【原文：Australia's biggest appliance retailer Harvey Norman and one of its units have been served with a class action lawsuit on behalf of consumers who were allegedly sold bad warranties, law firm Echo Law said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/australias-harvey-norman-served-with-class-action-over-warranties-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YGRM577UFMT7FRUNDOPHOEMPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:46:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北上广房价超跌的阴影笼罩南方强国]]></title><description><![CDATA[长期以来，预算紧张的中国购房者一直在寻找鹤岗这个位于俄罗斯边境的前煤炭繁荣城市。现在，随着中国房地产危机的蔓延，鹤岗的地下室价格正在富裕地区显现，对经济构成了新的威胁。【原文：Chinese homebuyers on a tight budget have long sought out Hegang, an ex-coal boomtown on the Russian border. Now, as China's property crisis spreads, Hegang's basement prices are showing up in wealthier regions in a new threat to the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ultra-weak-home-prices-northern-china-arrive-southern-powerhouses-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LX7QKJQYLNOYJHTMR4LRKZVYUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊任命从业 25 年的资深人士库马尔为新任印度主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司周三任命在印度工作了 25 年的资深人士萨米尔-库马尔（Samir Kumar）为新任印度区负责人，接替上个月卸任的马尼什-蒂瓦里（Manish Tiwary）。【原文：Amazon.com named 25-year veteran Samir Kumar as its new India head on Wednesday, replacing Manish Tiwary who stepped down after an eight-year stint last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-names-25-year-veteran-kumar-new-india-head-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FO5ILU2NWNJS5FOJIPSWKLX7CM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，越南最高领导人拉姆将于下周在美国与谷歌和 Meta 公司会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南国家主席兼执政党共产党总书记杜林在下周访问美国期间将会见包括谷歌和 Meta 在内的几家美国公司的代表，两位了解该计划的人士告诉路透社记者。【原文：Vietnam's president and ruling Communist Party chief To Lam is set to meet representatives from several U.S. corporations, including Google and Meta, during a visit to the United States next week, two people briefed about the plans told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/vietnams-top-leader-lam-meet-google-meta-us-next-week-sources-say-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z76BTECAX5JWRJOMRJMOOJQGAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员为多年来最不可预测的美联储会议做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球金融市场的交易员们正面临着极大的不确定性，他们正等待着美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）周三的降息预期，这为市场带来了一阵波动。【原文：Traders in global financial markets are facing extraordinary uncertainty as they await the U.S. Federal Reserve's expected rate cut on Wednesday, setting up markets for a burst of volatility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-brace-least-predictable-fed-meeting-years-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DRTJMPOUBPHDHSUCTCITX4ML4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息在即，关于降息幅度有多大的争论不绝于耳]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国央行开始扭转为抑制通胀而施加的限制性条件，美联储周三几乎肯定会在四年多来首次降低利率，但决策者是选择降息半个百分点还是更小的幅度，仍是未知数。【原文：The Federal Reserve on Wednesday almost certainly will lower interest rates for the first time in more than four years as the U.S. central bank starts to reverse the restrictive conditions it imposed to beat back inflation, but whether policymakers opt for a half-percentage-point cut or smaller move remains up in the air.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/with-feds-rate-cut-hand-debate-swirls-over-how-big-move-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAMCO7CP4VLCNOR32JJGR5NAJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[桥水的达里奥和新加坡政府投资公司（GIC）总裁对全球前景持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大对冲基金的创始人雷-达里奥（Ray Dalio）和新加坡主权财富基金 GIC 的老板林周吉（Lim Chow Kiat）由于政治风险和不确定的全球经济增长前景，对未来一年越来越谨慎。【原文：Ray Dalio, founder of the world's largest hedge fund, and Lim Chow Kiat, the boss of Singapore's sovereign wealth fund GIC are increasingly cautious on the year ahead due to political risk and uncertain global growth prospects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/bridgewaters-dalio-singapores-gic-chief-cautious-global-outlook-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJKFQIFP5FLS7BX2AEFYVCJLXQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美联储最后倒计时，交易员仍在猜测]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPFRVH25GBMLPFIIVOIXQKLO6E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 04:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大工会与通用汽车延长合同谈判期限，避免安大略工厂罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大工会 Unifor 周二延长了与通用汽车公司进行合同谈判的最后期限，从而避免了安大略省英格索尔生产电动汽车和电池的工厂发生罢工。【原文：Canadian labor union Unifor extended its deadline for contract negotiations with General Motors on Tuesday, averting a strike at the plant in Ingersoll, Ontario that makes electric vehicles and batteries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canadian-union-gm-extend-contract-talks-deadline-averting-strike-ontario-plant-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MT2OPCLTHJJKFCJFF56H4K4WCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 04:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，Meta 因分类广告行为面临巨额欧盟反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周三援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，Meta Platforms Inc 因涉嫌垄断分类广告市场而面临欧盟巨额罚款。【原文：Meta Platforms Inc is facing a hefty fine in the EU over its alleged efforts to dominate the classified advertising market, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-faces-hefty-eu-antitrust-fine-over-classified-ads-practices-ft-reports-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJW4NQZKHJLKXDMSKHAJ3OJT6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 04:21:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[为打造 "意大利制造 "这一奢侈品标签，移民工人如何受尽折磨]]></title><description><![CDATA["意大利制造：意大利耻辱"，上周，在日内瓦，来自意大利著名皮革制品产区托斯卡纳的几名移民劳工在奢侈饰品制造商万宝龙的旗舰店外高呼这句口号，他们举着写有这句口号的标语牌。【原文："Made in Italy: shame in Italy," a handful of migrant labourers who had travelled from Italy's famed leatherware region Tuscany chanted last week in Geneva outside the flagship store of luxury accessory maker Montblanc, holding placards with the slogan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/how-migrant-workers-suffered-craft-made-italy-luxury-label-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIUNLSI6EFPKDEF4MCZB5PJI3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 04:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司与工会谈判代表将于周三恢复合同谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际机械师和航空航天工人协会（IAM）表示，在周二未能就工资和养老金等关键问题达成一致后，波音公司与其最大的工会将于周三在联邦调解员在场的情况下恢复合同谈判。【原文：Boeing and its largest union will resume contract talks on Wednesday, in the presence of federal mediators, after failing to agree on key issues of wages and pensions on Tuesday, the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM) said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-union-negotiators-set-resume-talks-wednesday-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ERENS6XFVMXJP2PMKSYRBPK3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 03:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元回落，亚洲股市涨跌不一，美联储阴影笼罩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元回吐了隔夜的部分涨幅，而亚洲股市则表现不一，因为交易员们在权衡美联储当天晚些时候超大规模降息的可能性。【原文：The dollar ceded some of its overnight gains on Wednesday while Asian stocks put in a mixed display as traders weighed the odds of a super-sized Federal Reserve interest rate cut later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWVJD6FL7VNUXIVEVZE4AAWZQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 02:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：日本执政党竞选如何影响日本央行加息时机？]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本执政党领导人竞选将决定谁将成为下一任首相，这可能会使央行将超宽松货币政策正常化的计划复杂化。【原文：Japan's ruling party leadership race, which will determine who becomes next prime minister, could complicate the central bank's plan to normalise ultra-loose monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/how-would-japans-ruling-party-race-affect-boj-rate-hike-timing-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAUVLTXRLVLQDPJVMYWHP3SWLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 02:13:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价持稳，投资者关注美联储决议]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在等待美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）的降息预期，加上中东可能发生更多暴力事件，油价在前两个交易日上涨后，周三趋于稳定。【原文：Oil prices steadied on Wednesday, after rising in the previous two sessions, as investors await the U.S. Federal Reserve's anticipated interest rate cut, with the potential for more violence in the Middle East supporting the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-steady-with-investors-focusing-fed-decision-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJ6Y5GKUCJJFNI3JNVN56Q6MCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 01:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本出口大幅放缓，机械订单萎缩，经济复苏受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本 8 月份的出口增长大幅放缓，原因是对美国的发货量三年来首次出现下降，而 7 月份的机械订单出人意料地出现萎缩，这对正在努力实现稳健复苏的日本经济来说是一个令人担忧的迹象。【原文：Japan's export growth slowed sharply in August as shipments to the U.S. dropped for the first time in three years, while machinery orders unexpectedly shrank in July in a worrying sign for an economy struggling to mount a solid recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-exports-rise-slower-pace-pressuring-fragile-economic-recovery-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQXLTTU4GZIAXN3DFDYWNTSO3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:19:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元在美联储会议前站稳脚跟]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国零售销售强于预期，交易商略微降低了对美国宽松周期将以大幅降息开始的押注，美元周三企稳。【原文：The dollar steadied on Wednesday as stronger-than-expected U.S. retail sales had traders slightly trimming bets that the U.S. easing cycle will begin with an outsized interest rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-catches-footing-ahead-fed-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NQHIKA2FFNDJFGF647GVW7PBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司的决定推迟至大选之后]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士周二表示，负责审查新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司的国家安全委员会批准了两家公司重新提交交易申请的请求，这使得拜登政府可以在美国总统大选之后再决定是否阻止该交易。【原文：A national security committee reviewing Nippon Steel's bid for U.S. Steel granted a request by the companies to refile their bid for approval of the deal, a person familiar with the matter said on Tuesday, giving the Biden administration until after the U.S. presidential election to make a decision about whether to block the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-decision-nippons-bid-us-steel-pushed-back-until-after-election-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GB4ZIZ7OSJOKXJS5EMUJI5V6GI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会主席表示，UAW 将在 Stellantis 工厂举行罢工投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合汽车工人工会主席肖恩-费恩（Shawn Fain）周二表示，该工会计划在未来几天内在一个或多个斯泰兰特地区举行罢工授权投票，这可能会导致针对吉普车制造商的破坏性罢工。【原文：The United Auto Workers union plans to hold strike authorization votes at one or more of its Stellantis locals in the coming days, union president Shawn Fain said on Tuesday, which could lead to a disruptive walkout against the Jeep maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uaw-union-prepares-hold-strike-authorization-votes-stellantis-locals-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXADA7VKLRI43LY4QJXD67235Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:31:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，诺和诺德称 Ozempic "极有可能 "进入 2027 年医疗保险谈判名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二援引一位公司高管的话报道，丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司预计，其糖尿病药物Ozempic "极有可能 "进入美国政府2027年的价格谈判名单。【原文：Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk expects its diabetes drug Ozempic will "very likely" be on the U.S. government's 2027 list of price negotiations, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday citing a company executive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-says-ozempic-very-likely-be-2027-medicare-negotiation-list-bloomberg-news-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YXKYVZ7LVOEJBPLMLC7T3MHLA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:17:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：美国推动越南海底电缆计划远离中国的内幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[会谈知情人士透露，美国正敦促越南在其到2030年建设10条新海底电缆的计划中避免中国电缆铺设公司HMN Technologies和其他中国公司参与。【原文：The United States is urging Vietnam to avoid Chinese cable-laying firm HMN Technologies and other Chinese companies in its plans to build 10 new undersea cables by 2030, sources with knowledge of the talks said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/inside-us-push-steer-vietnams-subsea-cable-plans-away-china-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYAL5F56CBKCVOWAEEZKLFVRQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标美联储千钧一发--等待即将结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X37ODNU3KFIR7NQNE2BMLTPF74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:51:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[23andMe独立董事因首席执行官的收购计划不尽如人意而退出董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[基因检测公司 23andMe 的独立董事周二表示，由于没有收到首席执行官安妮-沃西基（Anne Wojcicki）令人满意的私有化要约，他们已辞去公司董事会职务。【原文：The independent directors of genetic testing firm 23andMe said on Tuesday they have resigned from the company's board after not receiving a satisfactory take-private offer from CEO Anne Wojcicki.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/23andme-independent-directors-quit-board-over-unsatisfactory-buyout-plan-ceo-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITRKURGW6VLXFJ3LGWONWWDQDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长表示，哥伦比亚政府不会改变 2025 年拟议预算值]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚财政部长里卡多-博尼利亚（Ricardo Bonilla）周二在接受采访时表示，哥伦比亚政府将不会修改其 2025 年拟议预算中的 523 万亿比索（约合 1239 亿美元）。【原文：Colombia's government will not modify the value of 523 trillion pesos ($123.9 billion) for its proposed 2025 budget, Finance Minister Ricardo Bonilla said in an interview on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-government-will-not-change-proposed-2025-budget-value-finance-minister-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VLHVVJN2JL5ZEIIQEYQ2V4KWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:27:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>