<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:04:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:04:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[福耀玻璃称俄亥俄州分部不是国土安全局突袭调查的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车玻璃制造商福耀玻璃工业集团称，美国政府机构于 7 月 26 日在俄亥俄州搜查了其子公司，这是对一家第三方劳务公司正在进行的调查的一部分。【原文：Chinese automotive glass maker Fuyao Glass Industry Group said the United States government agencies searched its subsidiary on July 26 in Ohio as part of an ongoing investigation into a third-party labour services company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fuyao-glass-says-ohio-unit-not-target-investigation-after-homeland-security-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJCUB5DIUNMBLLTAZWOILJ5Z5A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 08:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，三菱汽车将加入本田-日产联盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周日报道，日本三菱汽车公司（Mitsubishi Motors）将加入本田汽车公司（Honda Motor）和日产汽车公司（Nissan Motor）之间的联盟，创建一个汽车总销量超过 800 万辆的汽车集团。【原文：Japan's Mitsubishi Motors is set to join an alliance between Honda Motor and Nissan Motor , creating an auto group with combined sales of more than 8 million vehicles, the Nikkei business daily said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mitsubishi-motors-join-honda-nissan-alliance-nikkei-reports-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNEYPKQNBFOOXFCIX4E3GJMTCY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 02:36:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普以中国竞争为由誓言建立比特币 "储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周六在比特币会议上表示，美国必须主导这一行业，否则中国就会这样做，这是他讨好加密货币拥护者的最新举动。【原文：Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump told a bitcoin conference on Saturday that the U.S. must dominate the sector or China would, his latest move to court advocates of cryptocurrency, which Beijing has restricted and which he once dismissed as a "scam."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-cites-china-competition-vowing-create-bitcoin-stockpile-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EPKZUE4I35NKRNLXBDK4SL7NAI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 23:45:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴黎奥运会开幕式吸引 2860 万美国观众，为 2012 年以来最多]]></title><description><![CDATA[据康卡斯特旗下的 NBC 环球公司周六提供的初步数据显示，巴黎奥运会开幕式吸引了 2860 万美国观众，该公司称这是自 2012 年伦敦奥运会以来，夏季奥运会开幕式收视率最高的一次。【原文：The opening ceremony for the Paris Olympics drew 28.6 million U.S. viewers, according to preliminary data from Comcast's NBCUniversal on Saturday, which the company said was the most-watched start to a summer Games since London in 2012.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/olympics/paris-olympics-opening-ceremony-draws-286-million-us-viewers-most-since-2012-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TD2BPUVN5BMIPM4WTENJVX34BU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普向加密货币听众发表讲话，比特币价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六，美国共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普对一群加密货币爱好者说，比特币将登上月球，他希望美国能引领比特币的发展，比特币价格因此有所回落。【原文：The price of bitcoin eased on Saturday as U.S. Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump told an audience of cryptocurrency enthusiasts that bitcoin was going to the moon and he wanted the U.S. to lead the way.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bitcoin-price-dips-trump-addresses-crypto-audience-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOWIXP34F5OLFAGTVWZRB6RCRI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 20:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称每年需要 3 万亿美元气候融资，远高于当前水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周六表示，全球向低碳经济转型需要在2050年前每年新增3万亿美元的资金，远远高于目前每年的融资额，但填补这一缺口是21世纪最大的经济机遇。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Saturday that the global transition to a low-carbon economy requires $3 trillion in new capital each year through 2050, far above current annual financing, but that filling the gap is the biggest economic opportunity of the 21st century.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/yellen-says-3-trillion-needed-annually-climate-financing-far-more-than-current-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A2WHFZLJRJJIPBGWDD7KFMSP3Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 19:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚签署 14 亿美元协议升级海军潜艇]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚周六表示，已与国有潜艇建造商 ASC 公司签署了一份价值 22 亿澳元（14 亿美元）的四年期合同，以升级澳大利亚海军的柯林斯级潜艇。【原文：Australia said on Saturday it had signed a A$2.2 billion ($1.4 billion) four-year contract with state-owned submarine builder ASC to upgrade the navy's Collins class submarines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australia-signs-14-bln-deal-upgrade-navy-submarines-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2OBPQ5GPRK4VKBDBLSGZROV64</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士央行行长乔丹："无趣 "是央行成功的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[即将离任的瑞士国家银行行长托马斯-乔丹（Thomas Jordan）上周六表示，中央银行业务并不枯燥，尽管准备好贴上这个标签也许是成功的关键。【原文：Central banking is not boring, although being prepared to carry the label is perhaps the key to success, departing Swiss National Bank Chairman Thomas Jordan said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/being-boring-key-central-bank-success-says-snbs-jordan-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDN75ATPDJJ6FMGLSBYLBRDAUM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部要求法院驳回 TikTok 对打击法的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五晚些时候要求美国上诉法院驳回对要求中国字节跳动公司（ByteDance）在 1 月 19 日前剥离 TikTok 美国资产，否则将面临禁令的法律挑战。【原文：The Department of Justice late on Friday asked a U.S. appeals court to reject legal challenges to a law requiring China-based ByteDance to divest TikTok's U.S. assets by Jan. 19 or face a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/usdoj-tells-court-reject-tiktok-challenge-crackdown-law-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBL7SN4T7BPFVIAAB6EWEDXUWU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管经济不景气，中国 6 月工业利润仍实现较快增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六的官方数据显示，中国 6 月份的工业利润增速加快，尽管在经济复苏不稳的情况下，企业仍在努力应对消费者情绪的下滑。【原文：China's industrial profits grew at a faster clip in June, official data showed on Saturday, even as businesses were grappling with a downshift in consumers' sentiment amid a shaky economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-industrial-profits-post-faster-gains-june-despite-faltering-economy-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIE63BWGGBLV3DNAY52Z3FTHMM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:11:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国工会与苹果公司达成临时劳资协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际机械师和航空航天工人协会（IAM）零售员工组织联盟（IAM CORE）周五与科技巨头苹果公司就改善工作与生活的平衡、加薪和工作保障等问题达成了临时协议。【原文：The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM) Coalition of Organized Retail Employees (IAM CORE) reached a tentative agreement with tech giant Apple on Friday over improvement in work-life balance, pay raises and job security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-union-apple-reach-tentative-labor-agreement-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7DE3F7ENJJZZPZDPYFMOF5IWY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:49:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小肯尼迪质疑特朗普最近支持加密货币的论调，两人正在争夺选票]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国独立总统候选人小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr）周五质疑共和党提名人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最近支持加密货币的立场，两人正在比特币2024大会上争夺11月选举中加密货币持有者的选票。【原文：Independent U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr on Friday questioned Republican nominee Donald Trump's recent pro-cryptocurrency stance, as the two vie for votes in November's election from crypto-holders at the Bitcoin 2024 conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/rfk-jr-questions-trumps-recent-pro-crypto-tone-two-vie-votes-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNXAFPSJDVPCBB2UJNO75MWCBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:49:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》报道，耶伦称日本解释了 2022 年的外汇干预措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》（Nikkei Business daily）周六报道，美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）表示，日本已就其在2022年干预货币市场做出了解释。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said Japan had explained its intervention into the currency market in 2022, the Nikkei Business daily reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/yellen-says-japan-explained-2022-fx-intervention-nikkei-reports-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEI6TK5K25K3PJYYIXEGGJGFXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金关于美国国债发行的研究引发争论]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金的一份研究报告称，美国财政部去年通过放缓长期债券销售有效地刺激了经济，该报告在债券市场引发了一场争论，美国财政部也否认了这一说法，称其目的并非如此。【原文：A hedge fund study that said the U.S. Treasury last year effectively provided economic stimulus by moderating long-dated bond sales has sparked a debate in the bond market and a denial from the U.S. Treasury that said it was not aiming for such an effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-fund-study-us-treasury-issuance-fuels-debate-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFUETR5EXJOD3OLDWQRRCS5MQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:35:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦：新兴市场共同关注中国工厂产能过剩问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周五表示，包括一些二十国集团（G20）国家在内的新兴市场与她一样对中国工业产能过剩感到担忧，并应敦促中国政府改变其经济模式。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Friday that emerging markets, including some G20 countries, share her concerns about China's excess industrial capacity and should press Beijing to change its economic model.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/yellen-emerging-markets-share-concerns-chinas-excess-factory-capacity-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WT4OUV3KM5LKRHJ4NQDH46F3FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[20 国集团同意解决超级富豪的税收问题，但论坛尚未做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[二十国集团（G20）财政领导人周五首次发表联合声明，誓言在对全球最大的财富进行有效征税方面开展合作，但这一声明掩盖了关于推进这一议程的合适论坛的更深分歧。【原文：The first-ever joint declaration by G20 finance leaders vowing to cooperate on effectively taxing the world's largest fortunes on Friday papered over deeper disagreement about the right forum to advance the agenda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/g20-agrees-tackle-taxation-super-rich-forum-not-yet-decided-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6HZNDPJUFJQXGD34OIEOMPFSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:26:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[六家银行在纽约就欧洲债券价格操纵诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括美国银行和花旗集团在内的六家银行同意支付 8000 万美元，以了结纽约的反垄断诉讼，该诉讼指控它们合谋操纵欧洲政府债券的价格。【原文：Six banks including Bank of America and Citigroup agreed to pay $80 million to settle antitrust litigation in New York accusing them of conspiring to rig prices of European government bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/six-banks-settle-european-bond-price-fixing-litigation-new-york-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7E2MBI5SUZIGJENVVX4WLA4U3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:25:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，星巴克前首席执行官舒尔茨反对与埃利奥特达成潜在和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，星巴克前首席执行官霍华德-舒尔茨（Howard Schultz）反对该咖啡连锁店与激进投资者埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）之间可能达成的和解。【原文：Former Starbucks chief executive, Howard Schultz, is opposing a potential settlement between the coffee chain and activist investor Elliott Investment Management, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-ex-ceo-schultz-opposes-potential-settlement-with-elliott-ft-reports-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7U4I5VF35M3RKRKFI3LHFWH6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克称第一大股东 Thoma Bravo 将出售价值 28 亿美元的股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克周五表示，私募股权公司 Thoma Bravo 将通过二次公开募股出售该交易所运营商的 4160 万股股票。【原文：Nasdaq said on Friday private equity firm Thoma Bravo will sell 41.6 million shares in the exchange operator through a secondary public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nasdaq-says-top-shareholder-thoma-bravo-sell-shares-worth-28-bln-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NKWNM3DHROS7NVZ7KOYNZICNQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:50:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约证券交易所网站显示，阿克曼的美国潘兴广场公司推迟 IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约证券交易所网站周五发布公告称，亿万富翁比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）管理的基金美国潘兴广场公司（Pershing Square USA）已推迟首次公开募股。【原文：Pershing Square USA, a fund managed by billionaire Bill Ackman, has postponed its initial public offering, according to a notice on the New York Stock Exchange's website on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ackmans-pershing-square-usa-postpones-ipo-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZJ6CGH3L55JAXCW5HJGWNQWNSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:36:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[密歇根州养老基金进行 660 万美元的比特币 ETF 投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[密歇根州退休系统（State Michigan Retirement System）为州政府雇员监管着约 1.439 亿美元的养老基金资产，该系统在周五的一份监管文件中披露，已向 ARK 21Shares 比特币 ETF 投资了 660 万美元。【原文：The State of Michigan Retirement System, which oversees some $143.9 million in pension fund assets for state employees, has invested $6.6 million in the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF , it disclosed in a regulatory filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/michigan-state-pension-fund-makes-66-million-bitcoin-etf-investment-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVY63MQTHFMELB2EF3R4YNS3OY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈里斯的两位亿万富翁捐款人希望她解雇联邦贸易委员会主席莉娜-汗]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁、民主党捐助者巴里-迪勒（Barry Diller）和里德-霍夫曼（Reid Hoffman）本周在接受采访时表示，他们希望卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）如果成为美国总统，将取代联邦贸易委员会主席莉娜-汗（Lina Khan），公开拒绝乔-拜登（Joe Biden）总统的反垄断政策支柱。【原文：Billionaire Democratic donors Barry Diller and Reid Hoffman said in interviews this week they hope Kamala Harris will replace Federal Trade Commission Chair Lina Khan if she becomes U.S. president, openly rejecting a pillar of President Joe Biden's antitrust policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/two-billionaire-harris-donors-hope-she-will-fire-ftc-chair-lina-khan-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNAWBVOQHFNKBMQIURCIOIJR4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:40:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[破产的 Steward Health 将关闭两家马萨诸塞州医院]]></title><description><![CDATA[破产医院所有者 Steward Health Care 周五表示，由于未能找到买家，该公司将关闭马萨诸塞州的两家医院。【原文：Bankrupt hospital owner Steward Health Care will close two locations in Massachusetts after failing to find a buyer for them, the company said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bankrupt-steward-health-close-two-massachusetts-hospitals-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXAOYIVNENLB3IPOQ4TRQFVA54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:15:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦表示，全球税务谈判应留在经合组织，而非联合国]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周五表示，她反对将全球税收协议的谈判从经济合作与发展组织（Organisation for Economic Cooperation and Development）转移到联合国，以回击一些发展中国家和非营利组织的愿望。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Friday that she opposes shifting the negotiations for a global tax deal to the United Nations from the Organisation for Economic Cooperation and Development, pushing back against the desires of some developing countries and non-profit groups.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/keep-global-tax-negotiations-oecd-not-un-yellen-says-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNHY454UJJMSHJHLNIQUSQ3HI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:51:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉债券持有人希望大选前的招募活动能取得成效]]></title><description><![CDATA[在委内瑞拉即将于周末举行关键性选举之际，其债券持有人正在进行招募活动，希望这次投票能为世界上最大的债务重组开辟某种途径。【原文：As Venezuela heads for pivotal elections at the weekend, its bondholders are on a recruitment drive in the hope the vote will open up some sort of path to the world's biggest debt restructuring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/venezuelas-bondholders-hope-pre-election-recruitment-drive-will-pay-off-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKGZU66ZXBM3RBVSV5C2I6SM3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道波音公司要求供应商提供长达十年之久的钛金属文件线索，以扩大对赝品的检查范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封信，波音公司正在要求供应商披露自 2014 年以来有关中国钛的记录，因为这家美国飞机制造商正在扩大对用于验证商用喷气机所用金属的虚假文件的检查。【原文：Boeing is asking suppliers to disclose records on Chinese titanium since 2014, according to a letter seen by Reuters, as the U.S. planemaker widens checks for false paperwork used to authenticate the metal used in commercial jets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-asks-suppliers-decade-long-titanium-paper-trail-check-forgeries-widens-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQ3CGEVGARLG7BDYEMKFF6EZFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:13:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴黎奥运会转播商在人工智能方法上存在分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴黎奥运会将向美国观众展示生成式人工智能，但欧洲观众不会看到类似的方式，这种反差反映了全球媒体公司正在如何斟酌这项技术的使用。【原文：The Paris Olympics will be a showcase of generative AI for American viewers but European audiences won't see a similar approach, a contrast that reflects how global media companies are deliberating over the use of the technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paris-olympics-broadcasters-diverge-ai-approach-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOHBOFJKZ5MXHAEBILH3VPWLIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 前电影主管斯图伯与亚马逊米高梅结盟，重振联艺集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊米高梅影业公司（Amazon MGM Studios）周五表示，该公司已与 Netflix 前电影部门长期主管斯科特-斯图伯（Scott Stuber）建立了多年的电影合作关系，为他的新制片公司提供资金并发行电影。【原文：Amazon MGM Studios has entered a multi-year film partnership with Scott Stuber, the former longtime head of films at Netflix , to finance and release movies from his new production company, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflixs-ex-film-head-stuber-ties-with-amazon-mgm-revive-united-artists-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EX2AOFU4GZOBPAHWWB7WPQTKMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:15:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司起诉 NBA 竞购转播权]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司及其体育部门特纳广播系统周五在纽约对美国国家篮球协会提起诉讼，原因是联盟拒绝了该公司对媒体转播权的匹配竞标。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery and its sports division, Turner Broadcasting System, filed a lawsuit on Friday against the National Basketball Association in New York over the league's rejection of its matching bid for media rights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-discovery-sues-nba-over-bid-broadcast-rights-court-filing-shows-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V37L42XKHBOOROAYTADK4HB3TE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止劳工部最新版信托规则的实施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官阻止了劳工部一项本可扩大被视为受托人的退休顾问类型的规定生效，认为该规定武断且与管理退休计划的法律相冲突。【原文：A U.S. judge has blocked a Department of Labor rule from taking effect that would have expanded the types of retirement advisers who are considered fiduciaries, finding the rule was arbitrary and conflicted with a law that governs retirement plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-latest-version-labor-departments-fiduciary-rule-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VM7TSWRX5NKPJQTKGE2OHHG5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>