<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 11:05:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 11:05:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[林德集团第四季度盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，全球最大的工业气体公司林德公布的第四季度财报高于市场预期。【原文：Linde , the world's largest industrial gases company, reported fourth quarter earnings above market expectations on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/linde-beats-q4-earnings-expectations-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJITLYQ6QZOOVHB6QHDTJQRCPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:59:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，石油和天然气贸易商将寻求中国政府对美国进口石油和天然气产品减免关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易消息人士周四称，中国政府计划从2月10日起对美国进口的原油和液化天然气（LNG）征收关税，石油和天然气贸易商可能会寻求中国政府的豁免。【原文：Oil and gas traders are likely to seek waivers from Beijing over tariffs that the Chinese government plans to impose on U.S. crude and liquefied natural gas (LNG) imports from February 10, trade sources said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-gas-traders-seek-tariff-waivers-beijing-us-imports-sources-say-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DDVEQJJVJIAPLLCD5FEWBXYSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行降息前欧洲股市攀升至历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲股市创下历史新高，黄金接近自己的历史峰值之一，债券市场再次承压，因为交易员们在经历了数日的贸易战焦虑之后，又将目光转向了全球利率的走向。【原文：European shares hit a record high, gold was near one of its own all-time peaks and bond markets were back under pressure on Thursday as traders turned their focus back to where global interest rates are heading after days of trade war angst.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-3-pix-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5N4XB5BVIFJW7PYZXRIZIBAN3M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:46:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大型企业业绩公布前，期货走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[与华尔街主要股指挂钩的期货周四在一波企业财报公布前上扬，而美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关税升级似乎有所缓和，这给市场带来了一些喘息的机会。【原文：Futures tied to Wall Street's main indexes edged up on Thursday ahead of a wave of corporate earnings, while a seeming lull in the escalation of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs gave markets some reprieve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-tick-higher-run-up-big-corporate-results-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKZWQBW57BKMVJDPUY3KQCCDAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:34:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepSeek 暂时停止 API 服务充值]]></title><description><![CDATA[DeepSeek 网站周四显示，由于服务器资源紧张，DeepSeek 暂时中止了 API 服务充值，这是一个允许其他模型开发者集成其人工智能模型的平台。【原文：DeepSeek has temporarily suspended API service top-ups, a platform that allows developers of other models to integrate its AI models, due to server resource constraints, its website showed Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/deepseek-temporarily-suspends-api-service-top-ups-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETOZWPTRFNMUXM3REKK773DPAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：霍尼韦尔将从自动化业务中分离航空航天部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，霍尼韦尔国际公司（Honeywell International）预计将透露其将航空航天业务从自动化部门分离出来的计划。【原文：Honeywell International is expected to reveal its plans to separate its aerospace business from its automation division, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/honeywell-separate-its-aerospace-unit-automation-business-wsj-reports-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGWTUFLXRJJBFAQF7HKKQIDRPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:28:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：立法者推动禁止美国政府设备使用 DeepSeek]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国立法者计划在周四提出一项法案，禁止 DeepSeek 的聊天机器人应用在政府设备上使用。【原文：U.S lawmakers plan to introduce a bill on Thursday that would ban DeepSeek's chatbot application from government-owned devices, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/lawmakers-push-ban-deepseek-us-government-devices-wsj-reports-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABPZK45UJRIENHFJNDOVUKEI4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:10:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普美国贸易代表人选贾米森-格里尔呼吁制定务实的贸易政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）将在周四举行的参议院确认听证会上主张采取务实的美国贸易政策，重点是重建美国制造业和巩固供应链。【原文：Jamieson Greer, President Donald Trump's nominee for U.S. trade representative, will argue for a pragmatic U.S. trade policy focused on rebuilding U.S. manufacturing and shoring up supply chains in his Senate confirmation hearing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-ustr-pick-jamieson-greer-calls-pragmatic-trade-policy-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDVJMBK6YFJMBE3EAHY6ZD2IJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:03:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[风电开发商 Orsted 预计 2025 年核心利润与 2024 年持平或高于 2024 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的海上风电开发商 Orsted 周四表示，预计今年的核心利润将等于或高于 2024 年的水平。【原文：Orsted , the world's biggest offshore wind power developer, said on Thursday it expected core profit this year to be equal to, or above 2024, a day after cutting investment plans for coming years, sending its shares higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/wind-power-developer-orsted-sees-2025-core-profit-line-with-or-higher-than-2024-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMZ2MJMKVJPYXDGMPD3Z4TXHRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 09:30:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉吉将完全控股巴西 SJC 生物能源公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份声明称，嘉吉公司已就 SJC Bioenergia 50%的股份签署了一份买卖协议，从而获得了对这家巴西制糖和可再生能源公司的完全控制权。【原文：Cargill has signed a purchase and sale agreement for a 50% stake in SJC Bioenergia, giving it full control of the Brazilian sugar and renewable energy firm, according to a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/cargill-take-full-control-brazils-sjc-bioenergia-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7RXSAQO4ZIH7PFFQ3XF3RYQ4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 09:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼国家媒体称，印尼命令开发商 MNC Land 停止与特朗普有关的项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[据印尼国家通讯社安塔拉（Antara）周四报道，由于水管理问题，印尼环境部已下令地产公司PT MNC Land停止开发与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普有关的丽都旅游项目。【原文：Indonesia's environment ministry has ordered property firm PT MNC Land to halt development of a Lido tourism project affiliated with President Donald Trump over a water management issue, state news agency Antara reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-orders-developer-mnc-land-halt-project-linked-trump-state-media-says-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2O4A2NHXVPWRPESZ7QB3O2SEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 08:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，中国电动车巨头比亚迪第一季度将在郑州招聘 2 万名员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[据河南日报周四报道，中国电动汽车制造商比亚迪计划第一季度在郑州招聘20,000名员工，涉及领域包括研发和制造。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle maker BYD plans to hire 20,000 employees in Zhengzhou in the first quarter, in areas including R&amp;D and manufacturing, government-run Henan Daily reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-ev-giant-byd-hire-20000-zhengzhou-q1-local-media-reports-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UBZ2KUG4NKX5NDZEJVDUAO7L4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 08:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着 DeepSeek 的飞跃发展，俄罗斯储蓄银行计划与中国联合开展人工智能研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯最大银行的一位高管告诉路透社，俄罗斯储蓄银行计划与中国研究人员合作开展人工智能联合项目，因为中国的 DeepSeek 公司以比美国竞争对手更低廉的成本创建了一个人工智能模型，从而颠覆了科技界的格局。【原文：Sberbank plans to collaborate with Chinese researchers on joint AI projects, a top executive at Russia's biggest bank told Reuters, as China's DeepSeek has upended the tech landscape by creating an AI model much more cheaply than U.S. rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/russias-sberbank-plans-joint-ai-research-with-china-deepseek-leaps-forward-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X47UEFHJ5FN35CSOLESPKQ4FKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 08:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的 "微量 "取消对特穆来说是个坏消息，但对谢因来说更糟]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府阻止低成本进口商品免关税进入美国的举措，对快时尚零售商Shein的打击可能比在线一元店Temu更大，因为Temu的产品种类更多，而且正在改变其运输策略。【原文：The Trump administration move to stop low-cost imports entering the U.S. tariff-free is likely to hit fast fashion retailer Shein harder than online dollar-store Temu, thanks to Temu's wider product range and moves to change its shipping strategy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trumps-de-minimis-cancellation-is-bad-news-temu-worse-shein-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IUFYUAEKVKYHHTNAJBE2VHF7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 08:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepSeek 热助长了对中国人工智能股票的爱国押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国投资者正在抢购与人工智能相关的股票，押注本土初创公司 DeepSeek 在人工智能方面的进步将带动该行业的繁荣，并使中国在愈演愈烈的中美技术战中占据主动。【原文：Chinese investors are rushing into AI-related stocks, betting the artificial intelligence advance of home-grown startup DeepSeek will lead to a boom in the sector and give the initiative to China in an intensifying Sino-U.S. technology war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/deepseek-fever-fuels-patriotic-bets-chinese-ai-stocks-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5FACGVHNKFMB7KMPXDNWQ7FL54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 08:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉诺威再保险公司预计洛杉矶火灾索赔额为 5-7 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[汉诺威再保险公司（Hannover Re）首席执行官让-雅克-亨乔兹（Jean-Jacques Henchoz）周四表示，洛杉矶地区的火灾可能会给该公司带来 5 亿欧元（5.1895 亿美元）至 7 亿欧元的索赔。【原文：Fires in the Los Angeles area may result in claims of between 500 million euros ($518.95 million) and 700 million euros for the reinsurer Hannover Re , the company's chief executive Jean-Jacques Henchoz said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hannover-re-sees-los-angeles-fires-claims-500-700-mln-euros-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6VZRSSJBZNVZMSCBFIAKFLXNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 08:13:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔将在美国新建钢铁厂以满足汽车行业需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔公司（ArcelorMittal）周四表示，该公司将在阿拉巴马州卡尔弗特（Calvert）建造一座先进的钢铁制造厂，以提高生产能力，满足美国汽车行业的需求。【原文：ArcelorMittal said on Thursday that it would build an advanced steel manufacturing facility in Calvert, Alabama, as it seeks to increase its production capacity to meet demand from the U.S. automotive sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/arcelormittal-build-new-steel-plant-us-meet-auto-sector-demand-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Q4TQAW5HJJZ3CICSMCW4GVI6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:49:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：为降低成本，2025 年中国的美国乙烷进口量将激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管华盛顿和中国政府之间的贸易战愈演愈烈，但今年中国从美国进口的乙烷量仍将激增，因为大型石化生产商正在与利润缩水作斗争，转而使用美国页岩气繁荣带来的廉价原料。【原文：Despite a growing trade war between Washington and Beijing, China's ethane imports from the U.S. are set to surge this year as big petrochemical producers battling shrinking profits switch to the cheaper feedstock flowing from the U.S. shale gas boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-us-ethane-imports-surge-2025-drive-cut-costs-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARI7NZASQBMAPE2EVTIFJMHJE4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司预计未来 20 年印度和南亚航空公司将增加超过 2,800 架喷气机]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周四表示，随着中产阶级的崛起和健康的经济增长刺激了旅行需求，预计印度和南亚航空公司在未来 20 年内将增加 2835 架商用飞机，比目前的水平增加四倍。【原文：Boeing said on Thursday it expects Indian and South Asian airlines will add 2,835 commercial aircraft to their fleet over the next 20 years, a four-fold increase over current levels, as a rising middle class and healthy economic growth spur travel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-sees-delivery-over-2800-commercial-jets-indian-south-asian-airlines-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BB23TPI5NJJ3PIZLDGS3NOMXN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:31:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司股价下跌，原因是许可业务预期令人失望]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，高通公司股价在法兰克福下跌超过 3%，原因是其专利授权业务不增长的预期令人失望，给高于预期的销售和利润前景蒙上了阴影。【原文：Shares in Qualcomm fell more than 3% in Frankfurt on Thursday as a disappointing forecast for no growth in its patent licensing business overshadowed a higher-than-expected outlook for sales and profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qualcomm-shares-fall-licensing-business-forecasts-disappoints-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTQDDKIJXFMQXJVDR7TFHZOA6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:27:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基第四季度利润超预期，预计 2025 年盈利将放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[马士基周四公布的第四季度利润高于预期，并表示在宏观经济不确定性较大、可能影响全球贸易的情况下，预计今年的盈利将低于去年水平。【原文：Maersk on Thursday reported fourth-quarter profits above expectations and said it expects earnings this year to trail last year's level amid considerable macroeconomic uncertainties which could impact global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/maersk-q4-profit-beats-forecast-expects-softer-2025-earnings-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UT6T57DEZNYBK37J3GHPIVFVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:22:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市 1 月份外资大幅流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国国债收益率上升，以及对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府征收额外关税可能导致亚洲出口受损的担忧加剧，外国投资者在 1 月份大量撤出亚洲股市。【原文：Foreign investors pulled heavily out of Asian stocks in January, deterred by higher U.S. Treasury yields and rising concerns that regional exports could suffer under additional tariffs from President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asian-equities-see-sharp-foreign-outflows-january-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3C3Q4PFSE5OTXBLQBLBVT4BM3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:17:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[啤酒生产商嘉士伯报告利润增长达到指导区间上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦啤酒酿造商嘉士伯（Carlsberg）表示，其年度有机营业利润增长了 6%，达到了指导范围的上限，并预测本年度将进一步增长 1%至 5%。【原文：Danish brewer Carlsberg said its annual organic operating profit grew by 6%, at the top end of its guidance range, and forecast further growth of between 1% and 5% for the current year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/beer-maker-carlsbergs-annual-profit-misses-forecasts-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JQCWBS2R5IULKUYZC2IYTSYBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 07:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[饮料集团 Pernod 下调 2025 年销售展望，原因是美国和中国市场面临挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国饮料公司保乐力加（Pernod Ricard）周四以美国和中国市场形势严峻为由，下调了 2025 年及更长期的业绩展望，并提前发布了上半年财报。【原文：French drinks company Pernod Ricard cut its 2025 and longer-term outlook on Thursday and brought forward issuing of its first half results, citing challenging market conditions in the United States and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/drinks-group-pernod-cuts-2025-sales-outlook-challenges-us-china-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSMWWN4M4VMGHKHIGTHKFD7RDU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:52:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁表示，美国钢铁公司的出价符合特朗普的目标，但不能确定交易一定会完成]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大的钢铁制造商新日本制铁公司周四表示，在两个盟国领导人准备会晤之际，该公司收购美国钢铁公司的提议符合唐纳德-特朗普总统加强美国的目标。【原文：Nippon Steel , Japan's biggest steelmaker, said on Thursday its proposed acquisition of U.S. Steel fits with President Donald Trump's goal of a stronger United States as the leaders of the two allies prepared to meet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/nippon-steels-9-month-net-profit-down-18-24-billion-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLDQO5CIEJNXRKCDTU7C2FIOME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:44:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲第一大卫星公司：欢迎 SpaceX 在特朗普 2.0 时代崛起]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于亚洲最大的卫星公司 SKY Perfect JSAT 而言，其总裁周四表示，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）第二次担任美国总统期间，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的火箭和卫星互联网巨头 SpaceX 的崛起并非逆风。【原文：For Asia's biggest satellite company, SKY Perfect JSAT , the rise of Elon Musk's rocket and satellite internet giant SpaceX under the second Donald Trump U.S. presidency is not a headwind, its president said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/spacexs-rise-under-trump-20-is-welcome-asias-no1-satellite-company-says-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWBCTPX75JLE5KOOKFSFLXO5HE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车第四季度利润下滑，为动荡的 2025 年做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于瑞典的沃尔沃汽车公司周四公布第四季度营业利润下降，并预测 2025 年市场环境将充满挑战。【原文：Sweden-based Volvo Cars reported a fall in fourth-quarter operating profit on Thursday and predicted a turbulent 2025 with challenging market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-operating-profit-falls-q4-automaker-braces-turbulent-2025-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSW4BSNUZFJOVPKOCM27XPTXCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:13:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行警告：欧洲可能成为中美贸易战的最大输家]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行董事会成员皮埃罗-西波隆（Piero Cipollone）表示，随着通胀放缓，欧洲央行的利率还有进一步下降的空间，他同时警告说，美国政府与中国的贸易战可能会对拥有 20 个成员国的欧元区造成不利影响。【原文：European Central Bank interest rates have room to fall further as inflation moderates, ECB board member Piero Cipollone said, warning that the U.S. administration's trade war with China could have a detrimental impact on the 20-member euro zone.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/europe-could-be-big-loser-us-china-trade-war-ecb-warns-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQJY4PQZLRPQ3NYOHR4UQWBVLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元飙升刺激企业外汇套期保值激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业财务主管们正在加大力度保护公司盈利，以防美元进一步走强，一些分析师表示，此举表明，他们更加相信唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税计划将有助于美元在更长时间内保持高位。【原文：Corporate treasurers are ramping up efforts to guard company earnings against more dollar strength, a move that some analysts said points to increased conviction that President Donald Trump's tariff plans will help keep the U.S. currency higher for longer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/surging-dollar-spurs-jump-corporate-fx-hedging-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAD2VK3GRNNRHB3JBTDGS62PX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行希望特朗普的加密货币计划能加速数字欧元的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行董事会成员皮埃罗-西波隆（Piero Cipollone）告诉路透社，欧洲央行希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普支持与美元挂钩的加密货币的计划能加快数字欧元的立法支持。【原文：The European Central Bank hopes U.S. President Donald Trump's plan to support cryptocurrencies pegged to the U.S. dollar will speed up legislative backing for the digital euro, ECB board member Piero Cipollone told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ecb-hopes-trumps-crypto-plan-will-speed-up-digital-euro-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SB2TZJ4QVOX7LW3OPU7MKN66Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>