<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:15:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:15:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰成功测试星链（Starlink）的直达蜂窝技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰最大的移动运营商 Kyivstar 周二表示，该公司已在东欧成功进行了埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 Starlink 直对蜂窝卫星技术的首次现场测试。【原文：Ukraine's largest mobile operator Kyivstar has successfully conducted the first field test of Elon Musk's Starlink direct-to-cell satellite technology in Eastern Europe, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ukraine-successfully-tests-starlinks-direct-to-cell-technology-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNYNCENTXVN45MTIAJKMTHHOXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[注重隐私的智能手机制造商 Unplugged 将开始在美国内华达州组装手机]]></title><description><![CDATA[智能手机初创公司Unplugged周二表示，将于今年秋天开始在内华达州组装其注重隐私的 "UP Phone "手机，这标志着在特朗普政府推动扩大国内制造业的背景下，该公司将战略重点转向陆上生产。【原文：Smartphone startup Unplugged said on Tuesday it will start assembling its privacy-focused "UP Phone" in Nevada this fall, marking a strategic pivot toward onshore production as the Trump administration pushes to expand domestic manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/privacy-focused-smartphone-maker-unplugged-start-us-assembly-nevada-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUWSXJZH2FL6NHFPNW6XRIVWYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:04:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic 以 1 美元的价格向美国政府提供人工智能聊天机器人 Claude]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）支持的 Anthropic 公司周二表示，它将以 1 美元的价格向美国政府提供其 Claude 人工智能模型，加入了越来越多的人工智能初创公司的行列，这些公司为赢得联邦合同提出了利润丰厚的交易。【原文：Amazon.com-backed Anthropic said on Tuesday it will offer its Claude AI model to the U.S. government for $1, joining a growing list of artificial intelligence startups proposing lucrative deals to win federal contracts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/anthropic-offers-ai-chatbot-claude-us-government-1-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A25VFFAVG5NR7AOHCG7DEIH5DA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 7 月通胀率上升，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份美国消费者价格温和上涨，基本符合预期，但由于进口关税导致商品成本上升，衡量基本通胀率的指标出现了六个月来的最大涨幅。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased moderately in July, largely in line with expectations, though rising costs for goods because of import tariffs led to a measure of underlying inflation posting its largest gain in six months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-us-inflation-rises-july-line-with-expectations-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPCIJ24EEBIJBL7YCTF6G4MVUQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲软件股因担心人工智能陷阱而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，欧洲软件类股大幅下跌，权重股思爱普（SAP）下滑超过6%，原因是人们担心人工智能可能给这部分技术行业带来风险。【原文：Software stocks in Europe fell sharply on Tuesday, with heavyweight SAP sliding more than 6% amid concerns over the risks that artificial intelligence could pose to this part of the technology sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/software-stocks-europe-fall-concerns-over-ai-pitfalls-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRU6D5UYKVNBBNSRGXNZQ47NOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:53:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月消费者物价温和增长；数据质量问题日益突出]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管进口关税导致商品成本上升，导致衡量基本通胀率的指标出现六个月来的最大涨幅，但 7 月份美国消费者物价温和上涨。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased moderately in July, though rising costs for goods because of import tariffs led to a measure of underlying inflation posting its largest gain in six months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-prices-increase-moderately-july-data-quality-concerns-rising-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7NBPXULE5PG5JE2VNKDNCDLEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:40:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电气元件制造商 Hubbell 将以 8.25 亿美元收购同行 DMC Power]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hubbell 周二表示，它将以 8.25 亿美元现金收购规模较小的同行 DMC Power，这家电气设备制造商将加强其关键元件组合，以满足预期的电力需求增长。【原文：Hubbell said on Tuesday it will acquire smaller peer DMC Power for $825 million in cash, as the electrical equipment maker bolsters its critical components portfolio to meet an expected boom in power demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/electrical-component-maker-hubbell-buy-peer-dmc-power-825-million-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QFVQHURGHBMRDBKXFJWX34H47I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟等待美国就贸易协议承诺采取后续行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟发言人周二表示，欧盟无法透露与美国的关税联合声明何时准备就绪，也无法透露白宫何时会就欧洲汽车进口关税发布行政命令。【原文：The European Union could not say when a joint statement on tariffs with the United States would be ready, nor when the White House would issue an executive order on European car import duties, a spokesperson said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-union-awaits-us-follow-up-trade-deal-promises-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNO5W62INJJUXMNS5HQPSB2U4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:10:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国大麻重新分类如何帮助大麻公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府正寻求将大麻重新归类为危险性较低的毒品，这一转变可能会减轻刑事处罚，并通过降低税收负担和使企业更容易获得资金来重塑大麻产业。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is looking to reclassify marijuana as a less dangerous drug, a shift that could ease criminal penalties and reshape the pot industry by lowering tax burdens and making it easier for firms to secure funding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-us-marijuana-reclassification-could-help-cannabis-companies-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ5TVVOTIFKJJOBT56CE4NJSR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:59:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易平台 eToro 盈利超预期，零售投资蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[股票和加密货币交易平台eToro周二公布的第二季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，原因是尽管新关税带来了更广泛的宏观经济不确定性，但散户投资者仍保持了坚定的风险偏好。【原文：Stock and crypto trading platform eToro beat Wall Street views for profit in the second quarter on Tuesday, as retail investors maintained a firm risk appetite despite broader macroeconomic uncertainty due to new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trading-platform-etoro-beats-profit-estimates-retail-investing-boom-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNQSTANUYNKB7HSEQANOP5FEH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲第二季度企业利润前景进一步改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，最新的盈利预测显示，欧洲企业的健康前景已大大改善，在中美关税休战和欧盟-美国贸易协议延期后，欧洲企业的盈利持续上升。【原文：The outlook for European corporate health has considerably improved, the latest earnings forecasts showed on Tuesday, showing a continued rise after the extension of the U.S.-China tariff truce and the EU-U.S. trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-q2-corporate-profit-outlook-improves-further-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5XEOO44265PQBFU7M27FBW5H3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:14:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[稳定币发行商 Circle 自首次公开募股（IPO）以来的首份业绩报告显示，公司收入大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，Circle 发布了自 6 月份上市以来的首份季度财报，收入和储备收入均有所增长，这主要得益于其 USDC 稳定币发行量的增加和订阅服务的加强。【原文：Circle posted higher revenue and reserve income on Tuesday in its maiden quarterly results since going public in June, driven by increased circulation of its USDC stablecoin and stronger subscription services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stablecoin-issuer-circles-revenue-jumps-first-results-since-blockbuster-ipo-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDT6HJLSDVPUBJANGCSC3K2RIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游说团体：瑞士希望特朗普对黄金关税做出有约束力的承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士贵金属协会（ASFCMP）负责人周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于不对黄金征收关税的声明为贸易稳定发出了一个令人鼓舞的信号，但只有正式决定才能提供确定性。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's statement on not putting tariffs on gold has sent an encouraging signal for trade stability but only a formal decision will provide certainty, the head of the Swiss precious metals association ASFCMP said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/switzerland-wants-binding-trump-commitment-gold-tariffs-lobby-group-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHIUPVO7ZJJ7DIDTLHRFDTA4YU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：中美贸易摩擦后，CPI成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVZMMYTTPJJFHKAAAIYGDPKIGY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因押注美国关税回落，Comex 8 月以后的铝溢价下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于有人猜测美国对进口金属征收的关税可能减半，或头号供应国加拿大可能获得豁免，Comex 交易所 8 月以后的铝溢价合约价格下跌。【原文：Prices of aluminium premium contracts on Comex exchange beyond August have fallen due to some speculation that tariffs on U.S. imports of the metal could be halved or that top supplier Canada could get an exemption.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/comex-aluminium-premiums-beyond-august-dip-us-tariff-rollback-bets-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTDJDCXXCRI4BGFXN73AVL4C44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:37:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shopee 所有者 Sea 季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，受电子商务业务强劲增长的推动，Shopee 所有者 Sea Ltd 的季度营收超过了市场预期，这使得该公司在美国上市的股票在盘前交易中上涨了 9% 以上。【原文：Shopee-owner Sea Ltd topped market estimates for quarterly revenue on Tuesday, powered by strong growth at its e-commerce business, sending the company's U.S.-listed shares up more than 9% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/shopee-owner-sea-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMLUEVT2B5PXZJKSPZ7Z662VG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车托运人称美国关税阴霾仍在影响汽车贸易往来]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的汽车运输车队之一的运营商Wallenius Wilhelmsen周二告诉路透社，尽管上个月达成了贸易协议，但欧洲的汽车出口商仍在美国关税的不确定性中挣扎。【原文：Europe's car exporters are still struggling with uncertainty over U.S. tariffs despite last month's trade deal, Wallenius Wilhelmsen , the operator of one of the world's largest car-carrier fleets, told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/car-shipper-says-us-tariff-haze-still-affecting-auto-trade-flows-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOPFOE7NKZOP3GO7APEIJOX3AE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:29:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业数据引发特朗普不满，但美联储官员认为这不是操纵，而是削减开支的理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[正是这些数据导致唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇了劳工统计局局长，因为他不喜欢 7 月份的就业报告，称其 "被操纵"，而美联储官员却将其视为经济放缓的重要证据，并将其作为特朗普希望降息的理由。【原文：The very data that caused President Donald Trump to fire the head of the Bureau of Labor Statistics because he did not like the July employment report, calling it "rigged," is being taken as serious evidence by Federal Reserve officials of a slowing economy and as a justification for the interest rate cuts Trump wants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jobs-data-triggered-trump-fed-officials-saw-it-not-rigged-reason-cut-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DL45EF2CIJLNLLVJCRIN66JAUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:14:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国小型企业乐观情绪上升，但不确定性给前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管企业主对经济前景越来越不确定，许多人还担心劳动力的质量，但 7 月份美国小型企业的景气度仍有所上升。【原文：U.S. small-business sentiment rose in July, though owners were becoming increasingly uncertain about the economic outlook and many worried about the quality of labor available.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-small-business-optimism-up-uncertainty-clouds-outlook-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEYK3ZUPDJMNRHKNFBZZQDJ4LM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:07:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公司计划根据新法律发行稳定币，但专家称仍存在障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行和 Fiserv 等金融公司正准备推出自己的美元支持加密代币，因为美国的一项新法律首次为稳定币制定了规则，但专家警告说，未来的道路可能并不简单。【原文：Financial companies from Bank of America to Fiserv are preparing to launch their own dollar-backed crypto tokens now that a new U.S. law has established the first-ever rules for stablecoins, but experts warn the path forward could be anything but simple.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/companies-plan-stablecoins-under-new-law-experts-say-hurdles-remain-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTXEGLVYHNPM7FDRUJBOHHJA3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:07:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为关键通胀数据做好准备，华尔街期货持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货交易平淡，因为在一份可能左右美联储下一步货币政策举措预期的关键通胀报告公布前，市场普遍谨慎。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were trading flat on Tuesday, as caution prevailed ahead of a key inflation report that could sway expectations over the Federal Reserve's next monetary policy move.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-steady-investors-brace-crucial-inflation-data-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLZ7MHG7KFI3PBPIDL3PVVXORE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）在退出破产程序数月后引发持续经营质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）在摆脱破产困境仅数月后，就因国内需求疲软和现金储备减少而陷入经营困境，并发出了破产疑云的警告。【原文：Spirit Airlines has warned of going-concern doubts, just months after emerging from bankruptcy as weak domestic demand and dwindling cash reserves strain its operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spirit-airlines-raises-going-concern-doubts-months-after-exiting-bankruptcy-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBREFEW2ANKWBJGIP6TV25R3AU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 09:47:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[腾讯音乐季度收入超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[腾讯音乐娱乐（Tencent Music Entertainment）周二公布的第二季度营收超出预期，主要得益于用户增长强劲，以及播客和有声读物等长篇音频内容的参与度不断提高。【原文：Tencent Music Entertainment , surpassed second-quarter revenue expectations on Tuesday, driven by stronger subscriber growth and rising engagement with long-form audio content such as podcasts and audiobooks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/tencent-music-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUO7XTZOE5I4ZF2KW5RVP5XX7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 09:09:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[猪肉加工商史密斯菲尔德食品公司（Smithfield Foods）因需求强劲而实现销售额和利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[史密斯菲尔德食品公司（Smithfield Foods）周二公布，由于包括培根在内的包装肉类和新鲜猪肉业务需求强劲，该公司第二季度销售额和利润均有所增长。【原文：Smithfield Foods posted a rise in second-quarter sales and profit on Tuesday, helped by resilient demand for its packaged meats, including bacon, and fresh pork business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pork-processor-smithfield-foods-posts-higher-sales-profit-strong-demand-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JV2QY5GPFKVJJBMTKCBCHLHZ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:47:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚法院在 Epic Games 诉讼案中裁定苹果和谷歌部分败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体周二报道，澳大利亚一家法院认定，苹果和谷歌旗下安卓系统的智能手机应用商店不具备竞争力，《堡垒之夜》游戏开发商 Epic Games 在与科技巨头的较量中取得了部分胜利。【原文：An Australian court found the smartphone app stores of Apple and Google-owned Android were uncompetitive, local media reported on Tuesday, in a partial victory for Fortnite game developer Epic Games against the tech giants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/australia-court-rules-partly-against-apple-google-epic-games-lawsuit-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">462ADSGL7VLKXGVRF4WCCJMRBM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:39:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾仁宝电子投资 3 亿美元加强美国业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾仁宝电子公司（Compal Electronics）周二表示，其董事会已批准一项在美国投资 3 亿美元的计划，以加强其在北美的运营和竞争力，重点是扩大其服务器业务。【原文：Taiwan’s Compal Electronics said on Tuesday its board has approved a $300 million investment plan in the United States to strengthen its operations and competitiveness in North America, with a focus on expanding its server business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwans-compal-electronics-boosts-us-operations-with-300-million-investment-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEKG2POMZ5M4FNL56Z63C4UCAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在西藏部署机器人羚羊以监视真正的羚羊群]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于西藏的狼群来说，中国的第一只 "机器羚羊 "可能看起来就像在崎岖冻土带上漫步的真正羚羊一样令人食欲大增，但这种 "生物 "是中国政府不断加强监控的一部分，现在甚至已经深入到最偏远的地方。【原文：To the wolves of Tibet, China's first 'robot antelope' may look as appetising as the real herds that roam the rugged tundra, but the "creature" is part of Beijing's growing surveillance that now even reaches into its most remote places.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/china-deploys-robot-antelope-tibet-surveil-real-herds-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HD6ZTV6AQBJXPK2KUZZVZAY7FQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:27:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，福特将因车轴螺栓损坏召回超过 103,000 辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周二表示，福特将在美国召回超过10.3万辆F-150皮卡车，原因是车轴螺栓可能断裂，导致车辆侧翻或失去驱动力。【原文：Ford is recalling over 103,000 F-150 pickup trucks in the U.S. over axle bolts that may break and result in vehicle rollaway or loss of drive power, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-over-103000-us-vehicles-over-damaged-axle-bolts-nhtsa-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMH7M4GV3NLF3F2IQXTXETLFUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国艾兰得健康正以超过 15 亿美元的估值寻求买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，总部位于中国的全球营养补充剂生产商爱兰德健康控股公司（aland Health Holding）的所有者正在寻求出售其合计控股权，目标估值超过 15 亿美元。【原文：The owners of aland Health Holding, a China-based global nutritional supplement maker, are seeking to sell their combined controlling stake, targeting a valuation of more than $1.5 billion, two sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/chinas-aland-health-seeking-buyers-over-15-billion-valuation-sources-say-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLURDW5JKFK7PAU7NXHLQP2DNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，中国工厂减班减薪]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Chai 的目标是将其厨柜工厂的工资成本降低约 30%，以保持与其他中国公司的竞争力。【原文：Mike Chai aims to cut wage costs at his kitchen cabinet factory by about 30% to remain competitive against other Chinese firms, which have stopped selling to the U.S. due to steep tariffs and are now coming after his long-time customers in Australia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/china-factories-cut-shifts-workers-pay-us-tariffs-bite-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLNBUI5JXBMSFCWPUKN6J5ZLOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>