<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:03:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:03:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国 6 月份工厂活动连续第二个月萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日，一项官方工厂调查显示，中国制造业在 6 月份连续第二个月萎缩，在近期一系列指标显示中国经济难以恢复元气之后，进一步刺激经济的呼声依然不绝于耳。【原文：China's manufacturing contracted for a second month in June, an official factory survey showed on Sunday, keeping alive calls for further stimulus after a string of recent indicators showed the economy struggling to get back on its feet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-june-factory-activity-contracts-second-month-2024-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XT7M7ZDPTVMT3N2SR5WHFEF2T4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 02:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国检察官与波音公司和坠机受害者会面，刑事指控决定迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司曾因 2018-2019 年 737 MAX 飞机发生致命坠机事故，被联邦航空管理局指控共谋欺诈而有望逃脱起诉。【原文：Boeing had been poised to escape prosecution over a criminal charge of conspiracy to defraud the Federal Aviation Administration, arising from the 2018-2019 fatal crashes of 737 MAX airplanes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-prosecutors-meeting-with-boeing-crash-victims-criminal-charging-decision-2024-06-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWYMZA3WVNPHXEK6XRGOKD3SJY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:52:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发布稀土法规进一步保护国内供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国公布了一份旨在以国家安全的名义保护稀土供应的法规清单，对用于制造从电动汽车磁铁到消费电子产品等产品的关键材料的开采、冶炼和贸易制定了规则。【原文：China has unveiled a list of rare earth regulations aimed at protecting supplies in the name of national security, laying out rules on the mining, smelting and trade in the critical materials used to make products from magnets in electric vehicles to consumer electronics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-issues-rare-earth-regulations-further-protect-domestic-supply-2024-06-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APXSNQQKYZMCNN6Z5KCJFWAQUE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定，Binance 必须面对美国证券交易委员会的大部分加密货币诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周五晚些时候裁定，美国证券交易委员会（SEC）对全球最大加密货币交易所 Binance 提起的诉讼的大部分可以继续进行。【原文：A federal judge ruled late Friday that the majority of a lawsuit filed by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, can proceed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/binance-must-face-bulk-us-sec-crypto-lawsuit-judge-rules-2024-06-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43BIDVQF3FOK5BUKKBQKSLCFZA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[天空新闻》记者称，在沃尔格林出售计划陷入僵局后，博姿首席执行官詹姆斯辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[天空新闻》（Sky News）记者马克-克莱因曼（Mark Kleinman）周六在 X 网站上发文称，在所有者沃尔格林博姿联盟（Walgreens Boots Alliance）计划以 50 亿英镑（63.2 亿美元）出售或在股市上市该公司后，博姿连锁店首席执行官塞巴斯蒂安-詹姆斯（Sebastian James）辞去了首席执行官一职。【原文：Boots chain CEO Sebastian James quit as CEO after owner Walgreens Boots Alliance's plans for a 5 billion pound ($6.32 billion) sale or stock market listing of the company stalled, Sky News reporter Mark Kleinman said in a post on X on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/boots-ceo-james-quits-after-walgreens-plans-sale-stalls-sky-news-reporter-says-2024-06-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZNZUCQXFVLHZBL4HXQ6IBOAQY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 10:46:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度反对派要求莫迪政府质疑富士康的招聘行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社报道称，苹果公司的供应商富士康拒绝已婚妇女在印度从事 iPhone 组装工作，印度反对党国会周六敦促总理纳伦德拉-莫迪（Narendra Modi）领导的政府质询富士康的招聘行为。【原文：India's opposition Congress urged Prime Minister Narendra Modi's government on Saturday to question Foxconn about its hiring practices after Reuters reported that the Apple supplier rejects married women from iPhone assembly jobs in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-opposition-asks-modi-government-question-foxconn-hiring-practices-2024-06-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXCJCHYWAVL2VLBJUGY4JUDFHA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 09:41:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢公司首席执行官告诉本报，第二季度销售额将保持稳定增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士食品巨头雀巢公司首席执行官周六告诉瑞士周末报《Schweiz am Wochenende》，随着成本通胀的缓解，雀巢公司的目标是从第二季度开始，在今年剩余时间内实现销售量的稳定增长。【原文：Swiss food giant Nestle is targeting stable growth in sales volumes from the second quarter throughout the remainder of the year as cost inflation eases, its CEO told Swiss weekend paper "Schweiz am Wochenende" on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nestle-sees-stable-sales-growth-q2-ceo-tells-paper-2024-06-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F23ID73QVBK25NAAQBRXBSQSLU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南第二季度 GDP 增长加速；通胀压力上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南政府周六公布的数据显示，由于出口强劲，越南第二季度经济增长加速，但通胀上升仍是这个东南亚国家面临的挑战。【原文：Vietnam's economic growth accelerated in the second quarter on robust exports, government data showed on Saturday, but rising inflation remained a challenge for the Southeast Asian country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/vietnam-q2-gdp-growth-accelerates-inflation-pressure-rises-2024-06-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZBN7OOWLBIRZKTGG3JHGQBNCA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州赢得法院对拜登加班工资规定的阻挠]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州的一名联邦法官周五暂时阻止了拜登政府的一项规定生效，该规定将把强制性加班工资的适用范围扩大到 400 万美国受薪工人。【原文：A federal judge in Texas on Friday temporarily blocked a Biden administration rule from taking effect that would extend mandatory overtime pay to 4 million salaried U.S. workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/texas-wins-court-block-biden-overtime-pay-rule-2024-06-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JP6OCSTNVJQ5BOREZEDDS4AMI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司正式将 1282 航班 737 MAX 9 退还波音公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿拉斯加航空公司（Alaska Airlines）周五表示，该公司已向波音公司归还了一架 737 MAX 9 飞机，这架飞机今年 1 月曾在空中发生门板炸裂事故。【原文：Alaska Airlines said on Friday that it has returned to Boeing the 737 MAX 9 plane that was involved in a mid-air door panel blowout in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/alaska-air-formally-returns-flight-1282-737-max-9-boeing-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVVXPIV7JRPUJLZSCYUXVPCEJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官称威士卡和万事达卡有可能达成远高于 300 亿美元的和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位联邦法官说，威士公司和万事达公司与商家达成的和解协议可能比她本周否决的 300 亿美元协议 "大得多"。【原文：A federal judge said Visa and Mastercard can likely withstand a "substantially greater" settlement with merchants who said they overpaid on swipe fees than the $30 billion accord she rejected this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/visa-mastercard-can-likely-handle-settlement-much-bigger-than-30-billion-judge-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WAHHPUIHRO7PMLA4GZN7KDXXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:43:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着最后期限的临近，美国和印度将数字税收休战延长至周日]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五表示，美国和印度已将美国对印度征收数字服务税的报复协议延期至周日，使其与重新分配全球最大、最赚钱公司征税权的全球协议的最后期限迅速一致。【原文：The United States and India have extended a standstill agreement on U.S. retaliation over India's digital-services tax until Sunday, aligning it with a fast-approaching deadline for a global deal to reallocate taxing rights on the world's biggest and most profitable companies, the U.S. Treasury said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-india-extend-digital-tax-truce-sunday-deadline-approaches-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3RWEOST3JP6NMHTBPBYTWZJJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:07:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美军授予洛克希德-马丁公司价值 45 亿美元的多年期 "爱国者 "导弹合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[五角大楼周五表示，美国陆军授予洛克希德-马丁公司一份价值 45 亿美元的多年期合同，用于生产防空导弹系统 "爱国者"。【原文：The U.S. Army awarded Lockheed Martin a multi-year contract worth $4.5 billion for its air defense Patriot Missiles system, the Pentagon said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-army-awards-lockheed-martin-45-bln-contract-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWRUZABEWZP6XP33H54H7VFWOI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院或将推迟至 9 月审理花旗银行竞购案]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周五提交给美国法院的一份动议，美国法院被要求将委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份拍卖的高价竞标听证会推迟至 9 月 19 日。【原文：A U.S. court has been asked to postpone to Sept. 19 a hearing to present the high bid in an auction of shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum, according to a motion filed with the court on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-court-may-put-off-hearing-citgo-bids-september-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QJHNHF6MJOHFENLP7ZAR3QMYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:54:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技热潮引领全球市场至 2024 年上半年]]></title><description><![CDATA[超级大盘股势不可挡的前进、央行怠慢般的中枢调整、政治悸动层出不穷以及 M&amp;A 又回来了--2024 年上半年，世界市场又刮起了一阵旋风。【原文：The unstoppable march of the mega caps, sloth-like central bank pivots, political palpitations aplenty and M&amp;A is back - the first half of 2024 has been another whirlwind in world markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-h1-graphics-pix-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UY7S6P2GLRP4HEN4XMCFE2PNOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，福特预计在两年半内盈利 3 万美元的电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[据CNBC周五报道，福特汽车公司预计将推出一款售价3万美元的电动车，该车可在两年半左右的时间内实现盈利，但福特并未提供该车的更多细节。【原文：Ford Motor Co expects to launch a $30,000 EV that could be profitable in about two and a half years but did not provide any further details on the vehicle, CNBC reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-expects-profitable-30000-ev-two-half-years-cnbc-reports-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Q7HZH7J2VLEJPEGWLH5QMRQ3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:25:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊聘请人工智能初创公司Adept的联合创始人加入其人工智能组织]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周五在一篇博客文章中说，亚马逊已经聘用了旧金山人工智能初创公司Adept的联合创始人及其部分团队成员。【原文：Amazon has hired San Francisco-based artificial intelligence startup Adept's co-founders and some of its team, Adept said in a blogpost on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-hires-ai-startup-adepts-cofounders-join-its-ai-org-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UF6KAWO3LFL5FGY5SSE7DRSREA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:22:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国顶级银行通过美联储压力测试后上调股息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行业巨头周五宣布，计划提高第三季度股息，因为它们在美联储的年度健康检查中证明，它们有足够的资本抵御严重的经济和市场动荡。【原文：U.S. banking giants announced plans to raise their third-quarter dividends on Friday after proving that they have enough capital to withstand severe economic and market turmoil in the Federal Reserve's annual health check.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/top-us-banks-hike-dividends-after-sailing-through-feds-stress-test-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NREWBWQBCRPZZP4NACFVKP7Q5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部敲定新的加密货币报税规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五敲定了一项规定，要求加密货币经纪商（包括交易所和支付处理商）向国内税收署报告用户销售和交换数字资产的新信息。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department finalized a rule on Friday requiring cryptocurrency brokers, including exchanges and payment processors, to report new information on users' sales and exchanges of digital assets to the Internal Revenue Service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-treasury-finalizes-new-crypto-tax-reporting-rules-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LUYXO2OIBJFBHRHEYBO2V3J5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：NFL 输掉 47 亿美元的 "周日门票 "审判后的下一步行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国就全国橄榄球联盟（National Football League）"周日门票 "转播套餐的成本做出了 47 亿美元的判决，如果该判决成立的话，可能会重塑比赛的传播方式。【原文：A $4.7 billion U.S. verdict against the National Football League over the cost of its "Sunday Ticket" broadcast package could reshape how games are distributed — if it holds up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/whats-next-after-nfl-loses-47-billion-sunday-ticket-trial-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJGTYWNS65JCVPRDIQMMZRK6NM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:35:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院裁决后，华尔街最高监管机构面临的斗争日益加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[法律专家在周五具有里程碑意义的裁决后表示，最高法院限制联邦机构权力的举措可能会削弱美国证券交易委员会制定新规则以监管华尔街的努力，并招致更多诉讼。【原文：The Supreme Court's move to curb federal agency powers could curtail efforts by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to establish new rules to police Wall Street and invite more litigation, legal experts said in the wake of Friday's landmark ruling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/wall-streets-top-regulator-faces-worsening-battle-wake-supreme-court-ruling-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FL5S4ZCQWZOWTDFEOOYYLXLWPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德股东投票决定在与萨巴公司的斗争中保留公司董事职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的最新数据显示，贝莱德本周赢得了与对冲基金经理 Boaz Weinstein 的斗争，其四只封闭式基金的股东投票决定保留该资产管理公司的董事职位，并继续由其担任基金经理。【原文：BlackRock won a fight with hedge fund manager Boaz Weinstein this week when shareholders voted at four of its closed-end funds to keep the asset manager's directors in place and retain it as the manager, new data released on Friday show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-shareholders-vote-keep-company-directors-place-fight-with-saba-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GXAOD3YYFMBDAXIXFNX4L3RXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莫迪政党的妇女派别呼吁调查富士康印度公司的招聘行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，苹果公司供应商富士康拒绝已婚妇女在印度从事 iPhone 组装工作，印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪领导的执政党妇女部周五敦促全国妇女委员会展开调查。【原文：The women's wing of Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi's ruling party on Friday urged the National Commission for Women to launch an investigation after Reuters reported that Apple supplier Foxconn rejects married women from iPhone assembly jobs in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/womens-wing-modis-party-calls-probe-into-foxconn-india-hiring-practices-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFRHHME4NVMAXHASFIKGSOEU3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:31:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rite Aid 破产计划获批，削减 20 亿美元债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名破产法官周五批准了 Rite Aid 的重组计划，允许这家连锁药店削减 20 亿美元的债务，并将公司控制权移交给一组贷款人。【原文：A U.S. bankruptcy judge on Friday approved Rite Aid's restructuring plan, allowing the pharmacy chain to cut $2 billion in debt and turn over control of the company to a group of its lenders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/rite-aid-bankruptcy-plan-approved-cutting-2-bln-debt-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBA7ABZJJFMMZIPRKAKTL4YDGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:19:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会起诉区块链软件技术公司 Consensys]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周五起诉加密货币公司 Consensys，称其未能通过 MetaMask 掉期服务注册为经纪人。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday sued cryptocurrency firm Consensys, alleging it has failed to register as a broker through its MetaMask swaps service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sec-sues-blockchain-software-technology-company-consensys-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQEVFUSTJBJ5DCTPDA57M2HIFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CDK 让部分经销商重新使用经销商管理系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[软件生产商 CDK 周五表示，在网络攻击造成系统中断后，该公司的经销商管理系统已使两家小型经销商集团和一家大型上市经销商集团上线运行。【原文：Software maker CDK said on Friday it brought two small groups of dealers and one large publicly traded dealer group live on its dealer management system, following an outage caused by a cyber attack.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/cdk-brings-some-dealers-back-dealer-management-system-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMRMOQWMANNOPNCX2GVTT6YB24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:56:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克计划推出售价低于 100 美元的运动鞋，以吸引注重价格的购物者]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司首席财务官周四表示，耐克将在全球各国推出 100 美元及以下的新款运动鞋，这家运动服装巨头正在调整其产品阵容，旨在使销售重回正轨。【原文：Nike will roll out new $100-and-under sneakers in countries around the world, its chief financial officer said Thursday, as the sportswear giant tweaks its product lineup in a plan aimed at getting sales back on track.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-plots-100-and-less-sneakers-lure-price-conscious-shoppers-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BN3OL3RDAFK6HMQ7OLLSWSRCGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:46:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 就业、通胀数据或将打破美国国债市场窄幅震荡的局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[即将发布的一系列经济报告和美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的国会证词可能会使美国政府债券摆脱窄幅交易区间。【原文：A series of upcoming economic reports and Congressional testimony from Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell could jolt U.S. government bonds out of a narrow trading range.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-jobs-inflation-data-may-break-us-treasury-market-out-narrow-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L33MSAFM3VL45BIY2LVZLLJNDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:42:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储称逆回购资金流入创年初以来最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[本季度末，纽约联邦储备银行的逆回购机制在周五出现了大量资金流入。【原文：The quarter end saw substantial inflows into the Federal Reserve Bank of New York's reverse repo facility on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/new-york-fed-says-reverse-repo-inflows-hit-highest-level-since-start-year-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBIEIN2UDNIJ3IVHZDAB6VUYRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，申银万国保留香港 IPO 备选方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，尽管在线快速时尚集团Shein本月早些时候向英国金融监管机构提交了机密文件，但该公司仍保留了在香港上市的后备方案。【原文：Online fast-fashion group Shein is keeping alive a fallback option to list in Hong Kong despite filing confidential paperwork earlier this month with the UK's financial regulator, Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shein-keeps-option-hong-kong-ipo-backup-plan-ft-reports-2024-06-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMHSMH755ZMANN4FCBC6JNAABU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:45:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>