<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:08:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:08:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商 12 周来首次增加石油/天然气钻井平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周增加了石油和天然气钻机，这是 12 周以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week added oil and natural gas rigs for the first time in 12 weeks, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-add-oilgas-rigs-first-time-12-weeks-baker-hughes-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOZJJDJGRNN57IBCKZZYQ3XY6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:51:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称加拿大钢铁进口关税违反世贸组织规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国驻渥太华大使馆周五批评加拿大本周对中国进口钢铁征收关税，称这违反了世界贸易组织（WTO）规则，扰乱了全球贸易秩序。【原文：The Chinese embassy in Ottawa criticized duties slapped by Canada this week on Chinese imported steel, saying on Friday they violated World Trade Organization (WTO) rules and disrupted the global trade order.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/canadas-steel-import-duties-violate-wto-rules-says-china-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LOH3ZIVSRK5JNSXDHAYXY2A54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税迫使希腊橄榄油生产商寻求新市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[当美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在春季发出征收关税的威胁时，希腊橄榄油生产商康斯坦丁诺斯-帕帕佐普洛斯几乎没有浪费时间。他立即开始在全球寻找替代买家。【原文：Greek olive oil producer Konstantinos Papadopoulos wasted little time when the threat of U.S. tariffs was floated by President Donald Trump in the spring. He immediately started looking for alternative buyers around the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-tariffs-force-greek-olive-oil-producers-seek-new-markets-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMLL7ZMYEZOXNIRGWBXL73RYM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙进入圭亚那油田解决了公司面临的最大挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙即将进入圭亚那丰富的近海油田，这解决了困扰这家美国大型企业的最大问题之一：未来几年的增长将来自哪里。【原文：Chevron’s imminent entry into Guyana’s rich offshore oilfields solves one of the biggest problems dogging the U.S. major: where its growth will come from beyond the next few years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-entry-guyana-oilfields-solves-companys-top-challenge-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR244FUOW5IWRHV53NBIPTB75I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）修订全球预测，但警告贸易紧张局势仍给前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五警告说，与贸易紧张局势有关的风险继续给全球经济前景蒙上阴影，尽管贸易有所增长，金融状况有所改善，但不确定性仍然很高。【原文：The International Monetary Fund warned on Friday that risks related to trade tensions continue to cloud the global economic outlook and uncertainty remains high despite some increased trade and improved financial conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imf-eyes-revised-global-forecast-warns-trade-tensions-still-cloud-outlook-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDTJVYFAUBNQDFXEINMVAKRQKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，摩根大通着眼于新的研究领域，覆盖私营企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士周五告诉路透社记者，摩根大通已开始发布关于著名私营企业转型行业的研究报告。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has begun publishing research notes on prominent private companies transforming industries, a person familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-eyes-new-research-frontier-with-coverage-private-firms-source-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KE4PCCHKVRKRRPDK3BSA7NQDMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：特朗普解除制裁后，美国公司将制定叙利亚能源总体规划]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷液化天然气公司（Argent LNG）首席执行官乔纳森-巴斯（Jonathan Bass）周五表示，美国贝克休斯公司（Baker Hughes）、亨特能源公司（Hunt Energy）和阿根廷液化天然气公司（Argent LNG）将为叙利亚的石油、天然气和电力部门制定一项总体规划。【原文：U.S.-based firms Baker Hughes , Hunt Energy and Argent LNG will develop a masterplan for Syria's oil, gas and power sector, Argent LNG CEO Jonathan Bass said on Friday, in a partnership aimed at rebuilding energy infrastructure shattered by 14 years of civil war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-firms-develop-syria-energy-masterplan-after-trump-lifts-sanctions-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOGNDA2N3ZIA7CE4672KRM72NQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:44:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：特朗普推动对所有欧盟商品征收 15-20% 的最低关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）正在推动在与欧盟达成的任何协议中将最低关税设定为15%至20%，并补充说，即使达成协议，美国政府目前也在考虑将对等关税税率设定为超过10%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is pushing for a minimum tariff of 15% to 20% in any deal with the European Union, the Financial Times reported on Friday, adding that the administration is now looking at a reciprocal tariff rate that exceeds 10%, even if a deal is reached.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-pushes-15-20-minimum-tariff-all-eu-goods-ft-reports-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PY4AZA6GM5IWHFI3ZK4YQEYRFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3M 工厂收到肯塔基州监管机构发出的 PFAS 传票]]></title><description><![CDATA[3M 公司周五发布的季度报告显示，该公司的辛西安娜工厂在 5 月份收到了一份传票，要求提供有关该工厂使用或释放的全氟辛烷磺酸（PFAS）和所谓有害物质的信息。【原文：3M's Cynthiana facility received a subpoena in May seeking information about PFAS and alleged hazardous substances used or released at the site, the company's quarterly report on Friday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/3m-plant-receives-pfas-subpoena-kentucky-regulator-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTLHJDS6ZJKG5CGPSVRAOVCPQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:40:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡称网络间谍组织以关键基础设施为目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡周五表示，它正在应对一个被安全专家称为与中国有关的间谍组织对其关键基础设施的网络攻击。【原文：Singapore said on Friday that it was responding to cyberattacks on its critical infrastructure by an espionage group alleged by security experts to be linked to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/singapore-says-cyber-espionage-group-targeting-critical-infrastructure-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UL5WKZSWNIYFLKMUGKL54DMRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟监管机构接受手机制造商让步，康宁免于反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构周五接受了玻璃制造商康宁的提议，即放弃与手机制造商和玻璃加工公司的排他性协议，废除采购条款，以结束长达八个月的调查，避免可能的罚款。【原文：EU antitrust regulators on Friday accepted glass maker Corning's offer to waive exclusive deals with mobile phone makers and glass processing companies and scrap purchasing clauses to end an eight-month long investigation and stave off a possible fine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/corning-staves-off-antitrust-fine-eu-regulators-accept-concessions-mobile-phone-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUDCDNZKIVI33LVKNYAELLOJOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:58:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[G20 公报的要点和遗漏]]></title><description><![CDATA[二十国集团（G20）财政首脑周五达成公报，强调了中央银行独立性的重要性以及世界贸易组织在推进贸易问题方面的作用。【原文：G20 finance chiefs agreed a communique on Friday that underscored the importance of central bank independence and the role of the World Trade Organisation in advancing trade issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/main-points-omissions-g20-communique-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5NIL6XSWNJI5J7RH5JUIJOOXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国官员：中国汽车制造商应在电动汽车行业追求 "理性竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国工业部周五发表声明称，中国一位高级官员周四表示，主要汽车制造商应推动电动汽车行业的 "理性竞争"。【原文：Major automakers should push for "rational competition" in the electric vehicle industry, a senior Chinese official said on Thursday, according to a statement from the industry ministry published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-automakers-should-pursue-rational-competition-ev-industry-official-says-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAYEMBFRIRN4XH3KMNP3SKK3Q4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:43:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 股价下跌，原因是营收预期未给投资者留下深刻印象]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 股价在周五早盘交易中下跌超过 5%，原因是投资者对这家流媒体巨头因美元走软而非客户需求强劲而上调营收预期感到失望。【原文：Netflix shares declined more than 5% in early trading on Friday, as investors were disappointed by the streaming giant's revenue forecast raise being driven by a weaker dollar instead of strong customer demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/netflix-shares-drop-revenue-forecast-leaves-investors-unimpressed-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VRMZUOG5AVKDJK6QWCBATQXMW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国小组共和党高层反对恢复英伟达 H20 芯片出货]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会众议院中国问题特别委员会主席约翰-穆莱纳尔（John Moolenaar）周五在给美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）的信中反对恢复向中国销售 Nvidia H20 等效图形处理器。【原文：John Moolenaar, chairman of the House Select Committee on China, on Friday objected to the resumption of Nvidia H20 equivalent graphics processing unit sales to China in a letter to U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-republican-china-panel-objects-resumption-nvidia-h20-chip-shipments-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMOCPCVC6ZMKTIE4K4XHSZEDJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月消费者信心指数上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份，美国消费者情绪有所改善，虽然通胀预期继续下降，但家庭仍认为未来价格压力会有大幅上升的风险。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment improved in July, and while inflation expectations continued to decline, households still saw substantial risk of price pressures increasing in the future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-improves-july-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEWFX3TYGFKXXIDEMDZR2BVDFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷首席执行官布卢姆就另一项节约计划展开会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一封信称，保时捷首席执行官奥利弗-布卢姆（Oliver Blume）已开始就新一轮成本削减措施进行谈判，以帮助这家德国汽车制造商应对中国市场的挑战和美国的关税争端。【原文：Porsche CEO Oliver Blume has initiated negotiations on another round of cost-cutting measures to help the German carmaker cope with challenges in China and the U.S. tariff dispute, according to a letter seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-ceo-blume-initiates-talks-another-savings-programme-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QD26QXJDIFO53ENY5RAQ7TYYQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管关税导致价格飙升，美国钢铁企业第二季度业绩喜忧参半]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税的不确定性影响下，钢材价格的上涨和需求的不平衡将使美国顶级钢铁制造商的第二季度业绩喜忧参半。【原文：Top U.S. steelmakers' second-quarter fortunes are likely to be a mixed bag, caught between a fillip from higher steel prices and uneven demand amid uncertainty over U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-steelmakers-eye-mixed-second-quarter-despite-tariff-led-price-spikes-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBDO2IE7DRMYVNJPY62ZYB3ORA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 分析师：雪佛龙在赫斯交易仲裁中胜过埃克森]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司将继续以 530 亿美元收购赫斯公司，在此之前，雪佛龙在一场具有里程碑意义的法律战中战胜了更大的竞争对手埃克森美孚，获得了圭亚那海岸数十年来最大的石油发现。【原文：Chevron will proceed with its $53 billion acquisition of Hess after it prevailed in a landmark legal battle against larger rival Exxon Mobil to gain access to the largest oil discovery in decades off the coast of Guyana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/view-analysts-chevron-winning-arbitration-over-exxon-hess-deal-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7IGJ4AJKQ5I5ZDQTFUFO2WPM4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，美国医疗保险公司寻求实现自 2018 年以来奥巴马医改保费的最大跃升]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据健康研究公司 KFF 的分析，受保费税收抵免即将到期和医疗商品可能被征收关税的影响，美国保险公司要求对奥巴马医保计划的保费进行自 2018 年以来最大的一次上调。【原文：U.S. insurers are requesting the biggest premium increases for Obamacare plans since 2018, according to an analysis by health-research firm KFF, prompted by the looming expiry of premium tax credits and potential tariffs on medical goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-health-insurers-seek-largest-jump-obamacare-premiums-since-2018-study-shows-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGHEK2YBANLALKYCI7WVJFMOJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:16:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉信理财因交易繁荣和资产增长而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经纪公司嘉信理财（Charles Schwab）周五表示，受强劲的交易活动和资产管理费增加的推动，该公司第二季度利润增长了近 60%。【原文：U.S. brokerage firm Charles Schwab said on Friday its profit rose nearly 60% in the second quarter, driven by robust trading activity and increased asset management fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/charles-schwab-profit-surges-trading-boom-asset-growth-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEHGBM6XXFP3PLJ7SU2XU2DYWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月独户住宅开工量和许可量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于高抵押贷款利率和经济不确定性阻碍了购房，6 月份美国单户住宅建设和未来建设许可大幅下降，这表明住宅投资在第二季度再次萎缩。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding and permits for future construction fell sharply in June as high mortgage rates and economic uncertainty hampered home purchases, suggesting residential investment contracted again in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-single-family-housing-starts-permits-decline-june-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KNEUAVVFZKBRJI7LL247M6Q7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税忧虑和通胀压力导致美国股票基金每周资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至7月16日的一周内，美国股票基金再次面临抛售压力，原因是人们担心唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税言论和通胀压力的增加，可能会使美联储对过早降息保持谨慎。【原文：U.S. equity funds again came under selling pressure through the week to July 16, dampened by worries over President Donald Trump's tariff rhetoric and the buildup in inflationary pressure, potentially keeping the Federal Reserve cautious about a premature rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-weekly-outflows-tariff-worries-inflation-pressure-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSRZWVGGCZPHFMO3XJGS6RJAWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威兹航空公司将恢复波兰莫德林机场的航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[运营官罗兰-蒂施纳（Roland Tischner）周五表示，在伦敦上市的低成本航空公司威兹航空（Wizz Air）将在停飞 13 年后恢复波兰中部华沙莫德林机场的航班，并计划从 12 月起在该机场部署两架飞机。【原文：London-listed low-cost carrier Wizz Air will resume flights from Warsaw Modlin Airport in central Poland after a 13-year hiatus, with plans to deploy two aircraft there from December, operations officer Roland Tischner said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/wizz-air-resume-flights-polands-modlin-airport-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLCCCEN7N5OBTOSTMEL2QE2JCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:16:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《卫报》报道，英国 JLR 公司推迟推出路虎揽胜和捷豹电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《卫报》周五援引两位知情人士的话报道称，英国豪华汽车制造商捷豹路虎已推迟推出电动路虎揽胜和捷豹车型，以便有时间进行更多测试，并等待需求回升。【原文：British luxury carmaker Jaguar Land Rover has delayed the launch of its electric Range Rover and Jaguar models to allow time for more testing and for demand to pick up, The Guardian reported on Friday citing two people with knowledge of the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/britains-jlr-delays-launch-range-rover-jaguar-evs-guardian-reports-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIJQ66DDJZIIVBY2I6E75KFUJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国财长告诉七国集团伙伴，关税战必须尽快结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国财政部长拉尔斯-克林拜尔周五在与来自七大经济体集团的同行会晤时明确表示，必须尽快结束全球贸易冲突。【原文：German Finance Minister Lars Klingbeil made clear in a meeting with his counterparts from the Group of Seven major economies on Friday that the global trade conflict must be ended quickly, he told reporters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tariff-war-must-end-quickly-german-finance-minister-tells-g7-partners-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2EKK2BULROGLAN3ZDHGAQ3N2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行在华业务，高管面临离职禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士称，在一名银行家被禁止离开中国后，富国银行已暂停了所有前往中国的旅行，这使这家美国银行在世界第二大经济体的业务成为焦点。【原文：Wells Fargo has suspended all travel to China after a banker was blocked from leaving the country, a source said, bringing the U.S. bank's operations in the world's second-largest economy into focus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargos-business-china-where-senior-executive-faces-an-exit-ban-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUFEES4DANLEHDUAYN3D6BMLBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街券商撤回 9 月英国央行降息呼声，因通胀形势胶着]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街主要券商已经撤销了对英国央行 9 月份降息的预期，因为通胀依然坚挺，劳动力市场具有活力。【原文：Major Wall Street brokerages have withdrawn their expectations for a September interest rate cut by the Bank of England, as inflation remains sticky and the labour market resilient.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-brokerages-pull-september-boe-rate-cut-calls-inflation-proves-sticky-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KQRQJP3P5IJ7M3YIAFGAUNAPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税担忧导致全球股票基金资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至7月16日的一周内，全球投资者纷纷从股票基金中撤资，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税威胁和一份显示美国消费者价格上涨的通胀报告抑制了风险情绪。【原文：Global investors pulled money out of equity funds in the week through July 16 as U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats and an inflation report indicating an increase in U.S. consumer prices, dampened risk sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFOLIZLSLNLTDLL2EZFI5KK5BE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[具有系统性风险的人工智能模型就如何遵守欧盟人工智能规则给出了指导意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五制定了指导方针，以帮助其认定存在系统性风险并面临更严格义务以减轻潜在威胁的人工智能模型遵守欧盟人工智能法规（AI Act）。【原文：The European Commission set out guidelines on Friday to help AI models it has determined have systemic risks and face tougher obligations to mitigate potential threats comply with European Union artificial intelligence regulation (AI Act).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ai-models-with-systemic-risks-given-pointers-how-comply-with-eu-ai-rules-2025-07-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJ7KLDVLDNIKROVVABTUSAFESA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>