<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:35:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:35:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[切尼尔公司在科珀斯克里斯蒂三期项目生产出首批液化天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[切尼尔能源公司（Cheniere Energy）周一表示，其科珀斯克里斯蒂第三阶段液化项目（Corpus Christi Stage 3 Liquefaction Project）的第一条生产线（1 号线）首次生产出液化天然气（LNG）。【原文：Cheniere Energy on Monday said that liquefied natural gas (LNG) was produced for the first time from the first train (Train 1) of its Corpus Christi Stage 3 Liquefaction Project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/cheniere-produces-first-lng-corpus-christi-stage-3-project-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWYJGYVYUFK2DET2E5N4S3XEYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达斥资 7 亿美元完成 Run:ai 收购案，但仍面临监管障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）周一表示，已完成对以色列人工智能公司Run:ai的收购，此前该收购案曾受到反垄断审查。【原文：Chipmaker Nvidia has completed its acquisition of Israeli AI firm Run:ai, the startup said on Monday, following antitrust scrutiny over the buyout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nvidia-closes-700-mln-runai-acquisition-after-regulatory-hurdles-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CM2KJSFKVKBBAWBEGD67KQGUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银集团老板警告说，在银行业全面改革前应避免过度监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥-埃尔莫蒂（Sergio Ermotti）被引述说，瑞士不应该为其银行业制定使其处于不利地位的规则，因为瑞士正准备在其银行收购瑞士信贷之后对监管进行全面改革。【原文：Switzerland should not set rules for its banking sector that put it at a disadvantage, UBS CEO Sergio Ermotti was quoted as saying on Monday, as the country prepares to overhaul regulation following his bank's takeover of Credit Suisse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-boss-warns-against-excessive-banking-regulation-ahead-overhaul-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YM7R5PUCUBKADG6ZTFMUFJEKBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 12:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国债收益率上升，华尔街期货下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货在清淡的交易量中下滑，因为国债收益率的上升有可能给股市历史上强劲的年末走势带来压力。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped in light trading volumes on Monday as elevated Treasury yields threatened to pressure a historically strong year-end period for equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-futures-slip-elevated-treasury-yields-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBCB2NDZYJKJNFGSPRGQKHRX7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 11:21:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢拉拥护巴西新任央行行长令市场警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[经过几个月的争吵，巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦和巴西央行之间的关系看起来将迎来一个甜蜜和光明的时代--这正是一些投资者所担心的。【原文：After months of rancor, ties between President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva and Brazil's central bank look poised for an era of sweetness and light - which is precisely what worries some investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/lulas-embrace-new-brazil-central-banker-has-markets-wary-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FH4YYXURJBPIBDP44UBGL3F3PQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 11:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经纪人称，1 月 1 日全球部分财产巨灾再保险费率将下降 5%至 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[再保险经纪公司盖伊-卡彭特（Guy Carpenter）周一表示，全球财产巨灾再保险费率将于 1 月 1 日下降 5%至 15%，这是因为在费率连年上涨之后，市场竞争变得更加激烈。【原文：Global property catastrophe reinsurance rates will fall 5% to 15% on Jan. 1 for books of businesses which have not suffered losses, reinsurance broker Guy Carpenter said on Monday, as the market becomes more competitive after years of rate rises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/some-global-property-catastrophe-reinsurance-rates-fall-5-15-jan-1-broker-says-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5DML5AYN5IGHA6I2EA6KCI3JY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 07:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 12 月制造业活动连续第三个月扩张：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的工厂活动可能在 12 月份连续第三个月实现增长，这给试图稳定世界第二大经济体的官员们带来了一丝乐观，因为他们正为特朗普第二任政府进一步征收美国贸易关税做准备。【原文：China's factory activity likely expanded for a third straight month in December, offering a glimmer of optimism to officials trying to steady the world's No. 2 economy as they brace for further U.S. trade tariffs under a second Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-dec-manufacturing-activity-seen-expanding-third-month-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCOAK5ZJPBIXBD4TYXOEPSKWUY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 04:56:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[举报人举报后，新加坡邮政任命新首席财务官，进行行政改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡邮政周日表示，任命现任澳大利亚业务首席财务官 Isaac Mah 为集团财务总监，此前一周，该公司因对举报人报告处理不当而解雇了包括首席财务官在内的三名高管。【原文：Singapore Post appointed Isaac Mah, the current CFO of its Australia business, as group finance chief, the company said on Sunday, a week after dismissing three senior executives, including its CFO, over mishandling a whistleblower report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-post-names-new-cfo-executive-overhaul-after-whistleblower-report-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVFFRWE3LZP6FDWP3V4IDZWQMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 03:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油在清淡交易中走低，投资者关注中国和美国数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，油价在年底前的清淡假日交易中走低，因为交易商在等待本周晚些时候来自中国和美国的更多经济数据，以评估世界上最大的两个石油消费国的经济增长情况。【原文：Oil prices slipped lower on Monday in thin holiday trade ahead of the year-end as traders awaited more economic data from China and the U.S. later this week to assess growth in the world's two largest oil consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-inches-lower-thin-trade-investors-eye-china-us-data-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBRAWD3QDJN3PP5XODK722QC7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 01:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元在收益率走高的支持下叱咤风云]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，日元兑美元汇率在五个月低点附近波动，受美国收益率上升的支撑，年末流动性稀缺使大多数货币保持在狭窄区间。【原文：The Japanese yen traded around five-month lows on Monday against a dollar underpinned by rising U.S. yields as thin year-end liquidity kept most currencies in tight ranges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-reigns-with-support-higher-yields-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VFEEW5TYNIQBCXXZXFU7V5QEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 01:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为下调多款高端设备价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[华为公司（HWT.UL）周日在其官方微博社交媒体账户上发文称，上周末，包括手机在内的多款高端设备在中国一家领先的电子商务平台上降价，最高降幅达3000元人民币（合411美元）。【原文：Huawei (HWT.UL) cut the prices of a variety of high-end devices, including mobile phones, by up to 3,000 yuan ($411) over the weekend on one of China's leading e-commerce platforms, it said in a post on its official Weibo social media account on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/huawei-cuts-prices-variety-high-end-devices-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPCVXKTZLVLLRIWRWY4I3ABWXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:53:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PMI 显示，日本工厂活动萎缩速度放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项私营部门调查显示，由于生产和新订单的降幅放缓，12 月份日本工厂活动的萎缩速度有所放缓，在经历了近期的下滑之后，日本工厂活动正逐步趋于稳定。【原文：Japan's factory activity shrank at a slower pace in December as declines in production and new orders eased, a private-sector survey showed on Monday, edging closer to stabilisation after recent falls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-factory-activity-shrinks-slower-pace-pmi-shows-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUJRE5MPYJL3HBOJMVSAGXE7FU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:35:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[致命空难后济州航空股价跌至历史新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，韩国廉价航空公司济州航空（Jeju Air）发生致命空难，造成 179 人死亡，其股价跌至历史最低点。【原文：Shares of South Korean budget carrier Jeju Air hit their lowest level on record on Monday, after a deadly plane crash that killed 179 people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/jeju-air-shares-plunge-record-low-after-deadly-plane-crash-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRHN66RDMRPWDGW7MOOBPAPCZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市下跌，高收益率考验估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市走低，原因是国债收益率高企挑战了华尔街股票的高估值，同时支撑美元接近数月高位。【原文：Asian shares edged lower on Monday as high Treasury yields challenged lofty Wall Street equity valuations while underpinning the U.S. dollar near multi-month peaks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6U6MZAG3G5KUPBRYXCKDNZZOQ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国年轻人涌向公务员队伍，但经济放缓使 "铁饭碗 "岗位面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[在经济放缓冲击私营部门、青年失业率居高不下的情况下，终身工作保障和包括住房补贴在内的福利前景吸引了340万中国青年参加公务员考试，创下了今年的新高。【原文：A record 3.4 million young Chinese flocked to the civil service exam this year, lured by the prospect of lifetime job security and perks including subsidised housing as an economic slowdown batters the private sector and youth unemployment remains high.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-youth-flock-civil-service-slow-economy-puts-iron-rice-bowl-jobs-risk-2024-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYNBGFGBXZKIPF2YJOQSDYSBSU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉民集团因推动数据中心建设而在澳大利亚房地产公司中脱颖而出]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年以来，随着人工智能热潮推动了对数据中心的疯狂需求，嘉民集团的股价一路走高，在澳大利亚房地产同行中大放异彩。【原文：Goodman Group's stock has been on a hot streak this year, shining bright among its Australian real-estate peers as the artificial intelligence boom has driven a frenzied demand for data centres.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/goodman-group-shines-among-australian-property-firms-data-centre-push-2024-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZKPRDZB3JNGDJB6SGSDAWSPW4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 23:26:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国 11 月工厂产出降幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国政府周一公布的数据显示，在出口放缓和商业信心减弱的情况下，韩国 11 月份的工厂产出降幅超过预期。【原文：South Korea's factory output fell more sharply than expected in November, government data showed on Monday, amid slowing exports and weakening business confidence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/south-korea-november-factory-output-falls-more-sharply-than-expected-2024-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JANRYDIF2BMLZFQNBBRGAM2LBQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子首席财务官告诉《德国商报》，西门子正在审查 Healthineers 的多数股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国技术集团首席财务官拉尔夫-托马斯（Ralf Thomas）告诉《德国商报》，西门子公司正在审查其在医疗技术子公司西门子医疗集团（Siemens Healthineers）的多数股权。【原文：Siemens AG is reviewing its majority stake in medical technology subsidiary Siemens Healthineers, , the German technology group's Chief Financial Officer Ralf Thomas told the Handelsblatt newspaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/siemens-reviewing-healthineers-majority-stake-cfo-tells-handelsblatt-2024-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNHIXBZUQVJ2ROJESSDNQDTC54</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 22:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗氏首席执行官表示，罗氏没有裁员计划，业务健康发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士一家报纸周日援引瑞士制药公司罗氏首席执行官托马斯-希内克尔的话说，罗氏没有裁员计划，业务也很健康。【原文：Swiss pharmaceutical company Roche is not planning job cuts and its business is healthy, CEO Thomas Schinecker was quoted as saying by a Swiss newspaper on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/roche-has-no-plans-job-cuts-business-is-healthy-ceo-says-2024-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICOJUFNNWRP33HWT3B27CMQPXQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 17:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电话电报公司（AT&T）成为 "盐台风 "网络攻击行动的目标，但网络安全无虞]]></title><description><![CDATA[与中国有关的 Salt Typhoon 网络间谍行动以 AT&amp;T 公司的系统为目标，但该公司周六首次承认受到攻击，并表示公司正与执法部门和政府官员合作，确保美国无线运营商网络的安全。【原文：The Chinese-linked Salt Typhoon cyberespionage operation targeted AT&amp;T's systems, but the wireless carrier's U.S. networks are now secure as it works with law enforcement and government officials, the company said on Saturday in its first acknowledgment of the attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/chinese-salt-typhoon-cyberespionage-targets-att-networks-secure-carrier-says-2024-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJRJ5AIH3VK7FFS5APG57E43AI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 01:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将削减部分再生铜和铝原材料的进口关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国政府周六表示，中国将从明年开始降低乙烷和某些再生铜铝原材料的进口关税。【原文：China will reduce import tariffs on ethane and certain recycled copper and aluminium raw materials from next year, the government said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-cut-import-tariffs-some-recycled-copper-aluminium-raw-materials-2024-12-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDOO6UHF2NJYZJTRTQSDKUQDUE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 03:39:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称美国最早可能在 1 月 14 日达到新的债务限额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周五在一封信中告诉立法者，美国财政部最早可能需要在1月14日之前采取 "非常措施"，以防止美国出现债务违约。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department may need to take "extraordinary measures" by as early as Jan. 14 to prevent the United States from defaulting on its debt, Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen told lawmakers in a letter on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-may-hit-new-debt-limit-early-jan-14-yellen-says-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSM2NL55I5OJ7JRJU2BQTKTCPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 23:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求最高法院暂停执行可能禁止 TikTok 的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）敦促美国最高法院暂停联邦TikTok法律，该法律将禁止这一流行的社交媒体应用程序或迫使其出售，这位共和党美国当选总统认为，他在上任后应该有时间寻求 "政治解决 "这一问题。【原文：Donald Trump has urged the U.S. Supreme Court to pause a federal TikTok law that would ban the popular social media app or force its sale, with the Republican U.S. President-elect arguing that he should have time after taking office to pursue a "political resolution" to the issue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trump-asks-supreme-court-pause-law-that-could-ban-tiktok-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSOV4EENKVJ2ZPGH4XWJNBNRXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 22:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝索斯的蓝色起源公司首次发射新格伦火箭获得联邦航空局许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周五表示，已为杰夫-贝索斯（Jeff Bezos）的火箭公司蓝色起源（Blue Origin）的 "新格伦"（New Glenn）发射项目颁发了商业航天发射许可证。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said on Friday that it has issued a commercial space launch license for Blue Origin's — Jeff Bezos' rocket company — New Glenn launch.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/bezos-blue-origin-gets-faa-license-its-first-new-glenn-rocket-launch-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSV3TT732JPHTDPQTXCG7K57YY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 21:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦存款保险公司与 Vanguard 达成被动协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦存款保险公司周五表示，它已与 Vanguard 达成了被动协议。【原文：The Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation said on Friday it has struck a passivity agreement with Vanguard.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fdic-strikes-passivity-deal-with-vanguard-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFRL27BIRVJP5JIUOMPPQGZHHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 21:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解释器：为什么 OpenAI 计划转型为公益公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周五制定了一项计划，将其营利性部门转型为特拉华州公益公司（PBC），以帮助其筹集资金，并在与谷歌等公司的高成本人工智能竞赛中保持领先地位。【原文：OpenAI on Friday laid out a plan to transition its for-profit arm into a Delaware public benefit corporation (PBC) to help it raise capital and stay ahead in the costly AI race against companies such as Google.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/why-openai-plans-transition-public-benefit-corporation-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTPTF6IVPBNVBFCHENC5SWF2YU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 21:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在遭中国支持的 "台风盐 "网络攻击的公司名单中增加第 9 家电信公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫一位高级官员周五表示，在与中国有关的被称为 "盐台风"（Salt Typhoon）的大规模网络间谍行动中受到攻击的实体名单中，美国官员又增加了第九家电信公司。【原文：U.S. officials have added a ninth telecommunications company to the list of entities compromised by a sweeping Chinese-linked cyberespionage operation known as Salt Typhoon, a top White House official said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-adds-9th-telcom-list-companies-hacked-by-chinese-backed-salt-typhoon-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCQC4K2R2BMD7BDNV5KDJQ2BII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜克能源公司申请追回 11 亿美元飓风成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于美国的公用事业公司杜克能源周五表示，它已向佛罗里达州公共服务委员会提交了一份计划，以收回与公司紧急启动和应对飓风黛比、海伦和米尔顿有关的约 11 亿美元的直接费用。【原文：U.S.-based utility Duke Energy said on Friday it had filed a plan with the Florida Public Service Commission to recover about $1.1 billion in direct costs associated with the company's emergency activation and response to hurricanes Debby, Helene and Milton.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/duke-energy-files-recover-11-bln-hurricane-costs-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4M4UGNZ2CZMXDN2ZCKJKT5QL6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[言论自由倡导者告诉最高法院，美国的 TikTok 法律让人联想到独裁统治]]></title><description><![CDATA[言论自由倡导者周五告诉最高法院，美国针对中国拥有的 TikTok 的法律让人联想到美国专制敌人建立的审查制度。【原文：A U.S. law against Chinese-owned TikTok evokes the censorship regimes put in place by the United States' authoritarian enemies, free-speech advocates told the Supreme Court on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/free-speech-advocates-tell-supreme-court-us-tiktok-law-reminiscent-dictatorships-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLDLO5L3OJJZ7O6YYS6HOS6GDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国劳资关系委员会的案件中，星巴克就咖啡师被解雇一案提出的上诉基本败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦上诉法院周五基本驳回了星巴克对全国劳工关系委员会认定该咖啡连锁店非法解雇两名费城咖啡师的上诉，因为这两名咖啡师想组织工会。【原文：A federal appeals court on Friday largely rejected Starbucks' appeal of a National Labor Relations Board finding the coffee chain illegally fired two Philadelphia baristas because they wanted to organize a union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/starbucks-largely-loses-appeal-over-baristas-firing-nlrb-case-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JOWJJI4NRNXRLP2WWGRXGKWXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>