<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:11:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:11:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国第一季度GDP萎缩，进口激增导致关税前置]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经济在第一季度出现萎缩，原因是企业为避免成本上升而大量进口商品，这凸显了唐纳德-特朗普总统经常混乱的关税政策的破坏性。【原文：The U.S. economy contracted in the first quarter, weighed down by a deluge of goods imported by businesses eager to avoid higher costs, underscoring the disruptive nature of President Donald Trump's often chaotic tariff policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-q1-us-gdp-shrinks-amid-import-surge-front-run-tariffs-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2D7MG5L4HJLXVM3P44VD5RNNHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卫星公司 SES 与欧盟就补充星链的长期选择权进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲卫星公司 SES 首席执行官告诉路透社记者，该公司正在与欧盟和其他国家的政府商谈，以补充埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 "星链"（Starlink）所提供的服务。【原文：European satellite company SES is in talks with EU and other governments about complementing services provided by Elon Musk's Starlink, its CEO told Reuters, as the region looks for home-grown options for its space-based communications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/satellite-firm-ses-talks-with-eu-over-long-term-option-complement-starlink-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62CDA54BZBKJPIN634366ZZUHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:58:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员减少对美联储 2025 年降息的押注，但仍认为会在 6 月开始降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份政府报告显示，由于美国企业在关税预期出台前抢购进口商品，上一季度美国经济按年率计算萎缩了0.3%，交易员对美联储今年将降息整整一个百分点的押注略有回落。【原文：Traders pulled back slightly from bets the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates by a full percentage point this year after a government report showed the economy contracted by an annualized 0.3% last quarter as American businesses rushed to buy imported goods ahead of expected tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/traders-pare-bets-fed-rate-cuts-2025-still-see-june-start-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3KASNOXSROMTO4PDPWQGQLBNM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 WEG 公司因第一季度盈利不及预期而警告全球不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西电机制造商 WEG 周三公布，其第一季度净利润同比增长 16.4%，但低于市场预期，因为该公司对全球不确定性发出了警告。【原文：Brazilian motor maker WEG reported a 16.4% year-on-year rise in its first-quarter net profit on Wednesday, but fell short of market expectations as it warned about global uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-weg-warns-global-uncertainty-q1-earnings-miss-estimates-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RE2HICTJ6BLPHNDSL3W5MNYTCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:54:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第一季度劳动力成本温和上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于关税导致的经济不确定性降低了对劳动力的需求，美国第一季度的劳动力成本略有上升。【原文：U.S. labor costs increased moderately in the first quarter as economic uncertainty caused by tariffs cools demand for labor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-labor-costs-rise-moderately-first-quarter-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJLMOUH36FIMTPTCEMOYVXCABY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:48:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税鞭打迫使更多汽车制造商取消利润指引]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于无法预测美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）不断变化的贸易战的影响，斯太尔和梅赛德斯-奔驰成为本周三最新一批以关税带来的市场不确定性为由下调利润指导的汽车制造商。【原文：Unable to predict the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's ever-changing trade war, Stellantis and Mercedes-Benz became the latest automakers on Wednesday to yank their profit guidance citing market uncertainty wrought by tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-tariff-whiplash-forces-more-automakers-scrap-profit-guidance-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVU2XQZP3VNX3FIKQCAP5LRAQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月私营部门就业人数不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三发布的《ADP全国就业报告》显示，4月份美国私营企业薪资增长放缓幅度超过预期。【原文：U.S. private payrolls growth slowed more than expected in April, the ADP National Employment Report showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-private-payrolls-miss-expectations-april-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO5UHMTOOVLH7KS2OY73CYKJIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:25:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究发现：如果受到关税打击，欧元区消费者乐于放弃美国产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行的一项调查显示，如果在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府针锋相对的贸易战中受到关税打击，欧元区消费者乐于放弃美国产品。【原文：Euro zone consumers are happy to ditch U.S. products if they are hit by tariffs in the course of a tit-for-tat trade war with U.S. President Donald Trump's administration, a European Central Bank survey showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/euro-zone-consumers-happy-ditch-us-products-if-hit-by-tariffs-study-finds-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2JUYUGH2JKD7PZPMLOG3PESBI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cast AI 获得 1.08 亿美元融资，以扩大云计算自动化规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cast AI 是一家总部位于迈阿密的初创公司，致力于帮助企业实现云基础设施管理自动化，该公司周三表示，在由 G2 Venture Partners 和软银愿景基金二期（SoftBank Vision Fund 2）领投的一轮后期融资中，已筹集到 1.08 亿美元。【原文：Cast AI, a Miami-based startup that helps businesses automate cloud infrastructure management, said on Wednesday it has raised $108 million in a late-stage funding round led by G2 Venture Partners and SoftBank Vision Fund 2.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cast-ai-secures-108-million-funding-expand-cloud-automation-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVVLT32OCFIIZNXODVWIDM2E4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税不确定，电动汽车制造商 Polestar 暂停年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[Polestar周三暂停了对2025年的预测，因为这家电动汽车制造商正准备应对美国全面关税可能带来的冲击，这些关税有可能扰乱供应链并推高汽车价格。【原文：Polestar paused its 2025 forecast on Wednesday as the electric-vehicle maker braces for a potential hit from sweeping U.S. tariffs that threaten to roil supply chains and push up car prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestar-pauses-annual-forecast-amid-tariff-uncertainty-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTSGWBWJMNOSZD6CMKCGOSEBPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[服装和礼品需求稳定，Etsy 季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线市场 Etsy 周三公布的第一季度营收超出华尔街预期，表明市场对礼品和手工艺品以及其转售服装平台 Depop 的需求稳定。【原文：Online marketplace Etsy beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter revenue on Wednesday, signaling steady demand for gifts and handcrafted goods as well as its resale apparel platform, Depop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/etsy-tops-quarterly-revenue-estimates-steady-demand-apparel-gifts-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWSPFYC44JLVJHHOPNKWDWNIPU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[薪资需求强劲，ADP 季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动数据处理公司（Automatic Data Processing）周三公布的第三季度营收超出华尔街预期，得益于企业在劳动力市场稳定的情况下保持支出，对其薪资和人力资本管理服务的强劲需求。【原文：Automatic Data Processing beat Wall Street expectations for third-quarter revenue on Wednesday, benefiting from strong demand for its payroll and human capital management services as businesses maintain spending amid a steady labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/adp-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimate-strong-payroll-demand-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UU7F4NGG6FPTJPLG6QFZXUIRIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银第二季度开局 "尚可"，但不确定性可能影响客户活动--首席财务官称]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行瑞银集团（UBS）首席财务官托德-塔克纳（Todd Tuckner）周三告诉记者，第二季度的开局 "尚可"，部分原因是美国关税引发了市场波动，但如果不确定性持续增加，"将对我们的客户活动水平产生影响"。【原文：Swiss bank UBS had an "okay-ish" start to the second quarter due partly to market volatility induced by U.S. tariffs, but if increased uncertainty persists it "will have an impact on our activity levels with our clients," UBS Chief Financial Officer Todd Tuckner told reporters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-had-okay-ish-start-q2-uncertainty-could-impact-client-activity-cfo-says-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7XWOPFWWZI3PFQESKI5S2NWIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:46:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Miu Miu 的发展势头推动 Prada 销售额增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品集团普拉达（Prada）第一季度的净收入按固定汇率计算增长了 12.5%，略高于分析师的预期，这主要得益于其较小品牌 Miu Miu 的零售额猛增了 60%。【原文：Net revenues at Italian luxury group Prada rose 12.5% at constant exchange rates in the first quarter, slightly above analysts expectations, thanks to a 60% jump in retail sales at its smaller brand Miu Miu.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/prada-posts-125-increase-first-quarter-revenues-thanks-miu-mius-growth-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2ILLFTFTRJIBJHL7Y2PLOXEJU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:42:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院共和党人将取消 20 美元的车辆注册费，并将拟议的电动汽车注册费提高至 250 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院共和党人将放弃从 2031 年起对所有车辆征收 20 美元联邦年度注册费的提议，以资助道路维修，现在将提议对电动汽车征收新的 250 美元年费，作为正在审议的税制改革法案的一部分。【原文：U.S. House Republicans will drop a proposed $20 federal annual registration fee on all vehicles starting in 2031 to fund road repairs and will now propose a new $250 annual fee on electric cars as part of a tax reform bill under consideration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-republicans-drop-20-vehicle-registration-fee-boost-proposed-ev-fee-250-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZ77WL6JN5JCXIGN7YOOMMH46U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，关税风险为伦敦首次公开募股蒙上阴影，申银万国权衡美国重组事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对中国进口商品征收的关税有可能危及其在伦敦的首次公开募股（IPO），快速时尚零售商Shein正在权衡重组其在美国的业务。【原文：Fast fashion retailer Shein is weighing a restructuring of its U.S. operations as U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on Chinese imports threaten to jeopardize its London IPO, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shein-weighs-us-restructuring-tariff-risks-cloud-london-ipo-ft-reports-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RFAIXMPRFJQ5LF4FX7KFRGZIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Loblaw 季度业绩超出预期，得益于杂货和药房需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大零售商 Loblaw 周三公布的第一季度收入和利润超出了分析师的预期，这主要得益于其药店和日常必需品折扣店 Maxi 和 No Frills 的强劲需求。【原文：Canadian retailer Loblaw exceeded analysts' expectations for first-quarter revenue and profit on Wednesday, driven by robust demand at its pharmacy stores and discount banners, Maxi and No Frills, for everyday essentials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loblaws-quarterly-results-beat-estimates-grocery-pharmacy-demand-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UKRPIBQWNN6JH377AZSHN7MHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:25:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标即使在关税之前，美国经济也在吱吱作响]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XZEYIRZ3ZN3RBMAD4ZRS6QBVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因塔可钟需求坚挺，肯德基母公司百胜餐饮集团销售额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[百胜餐饮集团（Yum Brands）周三公布的第一季度可比销售额超出华尔街预期，主要得益于美国塔可钟（Taco Bell）分店和国际市场肯德基分店的强劲需求。【原文：Yum Brands beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter comparable sales on Wednesday, helped by robust demand at its Taco Bell locations in the U.S. and KFC outlets in international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kfc-parent-yum-brands-tops-sales-estimates-taco-bell-demand-holds-firm-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NOBT5XW3ZKDFKYPSKFFKZX4GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾日月光评估如何支持英伟达 5000 亿美元的美国计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾日月光科技股份有限公司（ASE Technology Holding Co.【原文：Taiwan's ASE Technology Holding Co. has yet to decide how it will support a plan by Nvidia to build artificial intelligence servers worth as much as $500 billion in the U.S. over the next four years, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwans-ase-evaluates-how-it-will-support-nvidias-500-bln-us-plan-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAOPZGEMNRJWRJXYZUDVXWHKJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威邮轮公司季度盈利不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威邮轮公司（Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings）周三公布的第一季度营收和利润均未达到预期，原因是对关税不确定性的担忧不断升温，对该邮轮运营商的高端海上航程的需求造成了压力。【原文：Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings missed first-quarter revenue and profit estimates on Wednesday, as rising concerns about tariff uncertainty have pressured demand for the cruise operator's premium sea voyages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/norwegian-cruise-line-misses-quarterly-earnings-estimates-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5VY5BBN7CVPOVGFWPPFH2FEQEI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:54:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[超微因预期下调而下滑，分析师淡化对更广泛人工智能需求的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[超级微电脑（Super Micro Computer）股价在周三收盘前暴跌 15%，原因是这家服务器制造商下调了收入预期，这是这家昔日的人工智能宠儿在逾期提交文件和卖空者攻击之后试图重拾投资者信心所遭受的最新打击。【原文：Super Micro Computer shares tumbled 15% before the bell on Wednesday after the server maker slashed its revenue forecast, the latest blow to the former AI darling trying to regain investor confidence following late filings and short-seller attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/super-micro-slumps-forecast-cut-analysts-downplay-broader-ai-demand-concerns-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N33AWNEHBZJRVDEYIBEVE3N6D4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡特彼勒因需求疲软利润下降，警告关税将冲击全年销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡特彼勒周三公布，受经济不确定性导致建筑设备需求疲软的影响，第一季度利润下降。【原文：Caterpillar on Wednesday posted a drop in first-quarter profit, hurt by weak demand for its construction equipment due to economic uncertainty and said annual sales would be slightly lower from a year ago if it accounts for tariff impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/caterpillars-first-quarter-profit-falls-softer-demand-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZANOD5V2VJBZIUVQS4XSGANCY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 CSL 公司评估中国对其美国产药品的关税豁免政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 CSL 有限公司表示，该公司正在评估其用于外科手术的药物是否可以免于中国对美国制造的商品征收 125% 的关税，以尽量减少北京和华盛顿之间贸易战的影响。【原文：Australia's CSL Ltd said it's evaluating whether its drugs used in surgery would be exempted from 125% tariffs China imposed on U.S.-made goods, as it seeks to minimise impact of a trade war between Beijing and Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/australias-csl-evaluates-china-tariff-exemptions-its-us-made-drugs-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E65YZBK3KNIS7PLFFWBCDCDGNQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，阿达尼暂停与以色列塔塔公司就 100 亿美元印度芯片业务的谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）的集团已暂停与以色列塔牌半导体公司（Tower Semiconductor）就价值 100 亿美元的芯片项目进行讨论，因为这对该集团没有战略和商业意义，两位熟悉此事的人士告诉路透社记者。【原文：Indian billionaire Gautam Adani's group has paused discussions with Israel's Tower Semiconductor for a $10 billion chip project as it did not make strategic and commercial sense for the group, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/adani-pauses-talks-with-israels-tower-10-billion-india-chip-foray-sources-say-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IUPP2AAMNJ4HGM4UYYOU2L4AI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:14:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股期货在数据风暴和巨头财报前不温不火]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国股指期货持平或小幅下跌，投资者正准备迎接一系列经济数据和企业业绩，为金融市场动荡的一个月画上句号。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were flat to slightly lower on Wednesday as investors braced for a spate of economic data and corporate results to close a turbulent month for financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-tepid-ahead-data-storm-megacap-earnings-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MHPCT3OONM45LEEFDHDTWEI6E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院小组将权衡削减对消费者和审计的监督]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会一个小组将于周三审议一项立法，该立法希望大幅削减政府在监管消费金融市场和审查上市公司会计方面的现有努力。【原文：A U.S. congressional panel is set to consider legislation Wednesday that looks to drastically curtail existing government efforts to police consumer financial markets and scrutinize public company accounting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-house-panel-weigh-cuts-consumer-audit-oversight-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYP3Z7G5ANNC5B4C6AWXH5CQII</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:09:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被玷污的 "华丽 7 "股票反弹面临盈利考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[被称为 "壮丽七雄 "的美国科技股和成长股在经历了急剧下滑后，已在某种程度上重新站稳了脚跟，但几周来估值的不断上升和盈利优势的减弱，可能会使它们更难推动华尔街走高。【原文：The U.S. technology and growth stocks known as the "Magnificent Seven" have regained their footing somewhat after a steep slide, but a few weeks of growing valuations and a dimming earnings edge could make it harder for them to push Wall Street higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tarnished-magnificent-7-stocks-rebound-faces-test-with-earnings-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RA2M23OTFVNHFBKZZPOFUGMNUQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌首席执行官桑达尔-皮查伊将在搜索反垄断审判中出庭作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌首席执行官桑达尔-皮查伊（Sundar Pichai）预计将于周三上午在华盛顿的一次庭审中出庭作证，反垄断执法人员将寻求一项命令，迫使谷歌出售其 Chrome 浏览器，并采取其他措施促进在线搜索提供商之间的竞争。【原文：Google CEO Sundar Pichai is expected to take the stand on Wednesday morning at a trial in Washington where antitrust enforcers seek an order forcing the company to sell its Chrome web browser and take other measures to boost competition among online search providers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-take-stand-search-antitrust-trial-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7F7RS6FTVNTJMFGBNSD3ENL64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[除非美元进一步下滑，否则外国对美国资产的需求将减弱：高盛集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）首席经济学家表示，除非美元进一步贬值，否则外国投资者对美元资产的兴趣可能会减弱。【原文：Foreign investor appetite for U.S. dollar assets may wane unless the currency depreciates further, said Goldman Sachs' chief economist, cautioning that a downward trajectory is expected even in the absence of a meaningful economic slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/foreign-demand-us-assets-seen-waning-unless-usd-slides-more-says-goldman-sachs-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2TV6SME2ZO7DPOFARFSX26IHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>