<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:33:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:33:36 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空烧掉更多现金，737 产量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空系统公司（Spirit AeroSystems）周一报告称，由于其最大客户波音公司的 737 机身出货量下降，该公司最畅销的窄体喷气式飞机的生产速度也在下降，因此季度现金消耗增加。【原文：Spirit AeroSystems on Monday reported a higher quarterly cash burn on lower 737 fuselage shipments to its biggest customer Boeing , which is producing its best-selling narrowbody jets at a lower rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-aero-burns-more-cash-737-output-drops-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HAFYYA4U6VORNLZ543LWVHPTHE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国掉期利差收窄，显示压力增大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国利率掉期与国债的利差收窄或变得更加负面，因为长期投资者在掉期市场对冲风险，为利率下降做准备，这表明了对股市大幅抛售的担忧。【原文：Spreads on U.S. interest rate swaps over Treasuries tightened or turned more negative on Monday as long-term investors hedged their exposure in the swaps market to position for lower interest rates in a sign of concern over the sharp sell-off in stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-swap-spreads-tighten-sign-stress-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMUV5DHT7ZNWDC43EUGG4RUUXI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid 获沙特股东注资 15 亿美元，营收超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lucid 集团周一表示，其最大股东沙特阿拉伯公共投资基金将注资 15 亿美元现金，因为这家电动汽车制造商希望为其产品线增加新车型。【原文：Lucid Group said on Monday its largest shareholder, Saudi Arabia's Public Investment Fund, will inject $1.5 billion in cash, as the electric vehicle maker looks to add new models to its product line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lucid-gets-15-billion-cash-infusion-saudi-shareholder-quarterly-revenue-beats-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NLVL5ZTYVLY5IOTFMHQU7AR3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir 凭借人工智能优势上调年度收入预期，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，Palantir Technologies 公司今年第二次上调了年度收入预期，这是生成式人工智能热潮推动其软件服务需求的最新迹象。【原文：Palantir Technologies raised its annual revenue forecast for the second time this year on Monday, the latest sign that the generative AI boom is driving demand for its software services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/palantir-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-ai-strength-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFW5CO4BNZKZTADDGLUG7I3LHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 称法院应驳回美国司法部在资产剥离诉讼中秘密提交的文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 和母公司 ByteDance 周一请求美国上诉法院驳回美国司法部秘密提交部分法律文件的请求，该文件旨在为一项法律辩护，该法律要求在 1 月 19 日前强制剥离 TikTok 的美国资产，否则将实施禁令。【原文：TikTok and parent company ByteDance asked a U.S. appeals court on Monday to reject the Justice Department's bid to file part of its legal case in secret that defends a law seeking to force the divestiture of TikTok's U.S. assets by Jan. 19 or impose a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tiktok-says-court-should-reject-us-justice-secret-filings-divestiture-suit-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVRTH7OR5FKUPLXFELF3VZFQV4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:30:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车安全机构称正寻求有关特斯拉 Cybertruck 致命车祸的信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周一表示，它正在向特斯拉电动汽车制造商寻求有关特斯拉 Cybertruck 事故的更多信息。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Monday it was seeking more information about an accident involving Tesla's Cybertruck from the electric vehicle maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-auto-safety-agency-says-it-is-seeking-information-fatal-tesla-cybertruck-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3V6BFA2BY5I5FPUG2Z5NL2USXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官裁定谷歌在搜索案中违反反垄断法]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周一裁定，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司为巩固其在网络搜索和相关广告领域的主导地位而触犯了法律，这是美国司法部 20 多年来在打击垄断方面取得的首次胜利。【原文：Alphabet's Google broke the law to cement its dominance over online searches and related ads, a federal judge ruled on Monday in the U.S. Justice Department's first victory against a monopoly in more than 20 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-rules-google-broke-antitrust-law-search-case-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6P64DIXXRNV7AVAA2BVOS45LU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着对经济增长的担忧骤增，2024 年获胜交易的回落打击了全球市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[从规模庞大的美国科技股到比特币，一连串的经济忧虑正迫使今年最热门的交易平仓，让投资者不得不判断未来还有多少下跌空间。【原文：From massive U.S. tech stocks to bitcoin, a spasm of economic worries is forcing an unwind of the year’s most popular trades, leaving investors to determine how much more downside could lay ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/unwind-2024s-winning-trades-batters-global-markets-growth-fears-spike-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBZHDFRZVBP7HIGCGYCCROX6YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储调查显示，第二季度美国银行对工商业贷款的需求并未减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美联储周一公布的一项对高级贷款官员的调查显示，最近一个季度美国银行对商业和工业贷款的需求没有变化，这是两年来该指标表现最强劲的一次。
上周，美联储官员在决定将政策利率维持在 5.25%-5.50% 的范围内，但表示可能会降息时，已经掌握了这一调查结果。【原文：U.S. banks reported no change in demand for commercial and industrial loans in the most recent quarter, the strongest showing on that measure in two years, according to a Federal Reserve survey of senior loan officers published on Monday.
Fed officials had the survey results in hand last week when they decided to leave the policy rate in the 5.25%-5.50% range but to flag a possible interest-rate c】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-banks-report-demand-ci-loans-did-not-weaken-2nd-quarter-fed-survey-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYUG5KYPLJLLVA2TWIVMYSVRZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，房利美和房地美将收紧房地产贷款规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周一报道，房利美（Fannie Mae）和房地美（Freddie Mac）两家抵押贷款融资公司将对商业地产贷款机构和经纪人实施更严格的规定，此前监管部门已开始打击这一价值数万亿美元市场中的欺诈行为。【原文：Mortgage financing firms Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac are set to impose stricter rules for commercial property lenders and brokers, following a budding regulatory crackdown on fraud in the multi-trillion dollar market, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fannie-mae-freddie-mac-set-tighten-real-estate-lending-rules-wsj-reports-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSAFBT2E7VNJTLZDFWE44HA73I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[接触孟加拉国主要供应商的全球服装公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[孟加拉国当前的政治动荡预计将扰乱该国的服装业，可能影响到从 H&amp;M 到 Zara 等全球服装零售商进入关键的假日销售旺季。【原文：The current political unrest in Bangladesh is expected to disrupt the country's clothing industry, potentially affecting global apparel retailers from H&amp;M to Zara as they head into the key holiday season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-apparel-companies-with-exposure-key-supplier-bangladesh-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOIUNZAVY5LWFABI3ZRTQDUNQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音和 Spirit AeroSystems 高层将在 NTSB 听证会上就 MAX 9 紧急事件作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会表示，波音公司和 Spirit AeroSystems 公司的多位高管将在周二开始的为期两天的听证会上就阿拉斯加航空公司波音 737 MAX 9 型客机一月份发生的机舱门堵塞紧急事件作证。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board said a number of Boeing and Spirit AeroSystems executives will testify at a two-day hearing starting Tuesday on the January Alaska Airlines Boeing 737 MAX 9 in-flight door plug emergency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-spirit-aerosystems-execs-testify-ntsb-hearing-max-9-emergency-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XTG3CLNJVMS7F4RKHALCZDB3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:15:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 投资者对全球股市下跌的评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，全球股市暴跌，债券反弹，原因是人们担心美国可能会走向衰退，投资者纷纷逃离风险资产，同时打赌利率必须迅速下降才能挽救经济增长。【原文：Share markets around the world tumbled and bonds rallied on Monday as fears the United States could be heading for recession sent investors rushing from risk assets while wagering interest rates will have to fall rapidly to rescue growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-selloff-quotes-6-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5EHK3WWH5LIVIYTHBTWXMR26Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:12:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济数据疲软引发衰退担忧，美国银行股暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心经济衰退，投资者纷纷逃离这个与经济健康状况密切相关的行业，转向避险资产，美国银行股周一大幅下挫。【原文：U.S. bank stocks slumped on Monday as fears of a recession sent investors fleeing from a sector closely tied to the health of the economy and toward safe-haven assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-banks-tumble-weak-economic-data-sparks-recession-fears-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCP7MLUM2RKXLCLPCDDAFIBH7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国五州推动马斯克修复人工智能聊天机器人的选举误报问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国五个州的州务卿周一敦促亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克修复社交媒体平台 X 的人工智能聊天机器人，称其传播了与 11 月 5 日大选有关的错误信息。【原文：Secretaries of state from five U.S. states urged billionaire Elon Musk on Monday to fix social media platform X's AI chatbot, saying it had spread misinformation related to the Nov. 5 election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/five-us-states-push-musk-fix-ai-chatbot-over-election-misinformation-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSRAQO25SNPWFO56CMJJLIQBDQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场散发 "黑色星期一 "气氛，股市下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周伊始，全球市场进入全面下挫模式，波动率创下单日最高纪录，股票期货和加密货币暴跌，唤起了人们对过去危机的回忆。【原文：Global markets have kicked off the week in full selloff mode, with measures of volatility shooting up by the most on record in a single day, while equity futures and cryptocurrencies plummet, reviving memories of past crises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-milestones-graphic-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKYO7YNP4VLF5EKDLK7FVMQGZM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与美国经济相比，全球市场崩溃更多与廉价资金结束有关]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，最近几天全球股市的崩盘更多反映的是投资者为增加赌注而进行的套利交易的清盘，而不是美国经济前景的急剧变化。【原文：A meltdown in world equity markets in recent days is more reflective of a wind-down of carry trades used by investors to juice their bets than a hard and fast shift in the U.S. economic outlook, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-rout-positioning-analysis-pix-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYFPEVIZRBKELIWHT6TA3VCGLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源数据大幅修正令交易员和分析师一头雾水]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国官方石油消费数据的一连串大幅修正令依赖这些数据进行交易的市场参与者感到不安。【原文：A string of dramatic revisions to official U.S. oil consumption data have unnerved market participants who rely on the figures to trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/large-revisions-us-energy-data-leave-traders-analysts-befuddled-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LC3KCTMPVJWFHB6P7CRNWZZ6M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔首席执行官表示，英特尔正在采用 ASML 的另一款高 NA 工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司首席执行官 Pat Gelsinger 在 8 月 1 日的财报电话会议上表示，英特尔正在接收 ASML 价值 3.5 亿欧元（3.83 亿美元）的第二台新 "High NA "EUV 工具。【原文：Intel is in the process of receiving the second of ASML's new 350 million euro ($383 million) "High NA" EUV tools, CEO Pat Gelsinger said, according to a transcript of the company's Aug. 1 earnings call.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-is-taking-another-asmls-high-na-tools-says-ceo-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOTZTETDMJPIPI42BNIJAI4HCY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:15:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月服务业反弹，就业率也有所回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于订单和就业人数增加，7 月份美国服务业活动从四年低点反弹，这可能有助于消除上个月失业率飙升引发的对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. services sector activity rebounded from a four-year low in July amid a rise in orders and employment, which could help to quash fears of a recession that were sparked by a surge in the unemployment rate last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-service-sector-rebounds-july-employment-also-recovers-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5L346JESPZPS5DE4UUYIAKDVDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示数千用户的在线交易平台瘫痪]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线交易平台 Charles Schwab、Fidelity Investments 和 TD Ameritrade 周一有数千名用户出现故障，根据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 的数据。【原文：Online trading platforms Charles Schwab , Fidelity Investments and TD Ameritrade were down for thousands of users on Monday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/online-trading-platforms-down-thousands-users-downdetector-shows-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TH23V2FG4BPH5LUGEEBSREOUXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:58:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济担忧令收益率跌至一年低点，2/10 曲线转为正值]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国国债收益率跌至一年多低点，国债收益率曲线中受到密切关注的部分两年来首次转为正值，原因是人们越来越担心美国可能会步入衰退。【原文：U.S. Treasury yields dropped to more than one-year lows on Monday and a closely watched part of the Treasury yield curve turned positive for the first time in two years on increasing concerns that the United States may be heading into a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/economic-fears-send-yields-one-year-lows-210-curve-turns-positive-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TV2JMXAVSBMTTEFKUBPTHPH74I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市下滑，华尔街 "恐惧指数 "盘中创纪录大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街最受关注的投资者焦虑指数周一创下了有史以来最大的盘中跳水幅度，美国股指期货因市场对美国可能陷入衰退的担忧加剧而暴跌。【原文：Wall Street's most watched gauge of investor anxiety logged its largest ever intraday jump on Monday, as U.S. stock futures tumbled on rising fears the United States could be tipping into recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-fear-gauge-posts-record-intraday-jump-stocks-slide-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3YILSMYXNOVFCHWW6QQZVXVFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比告诉CNBC，美国看起来并未陷入衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周一表示，虽然上周五的美国就业数据弱于预期，但看起来并不像经济衰退，但美联储官员需要认识到环境的变化，以避免在利率方面限制过多。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee on Monday said while the U.S. employment data on Friday was weaker than expected, it does not look like a recession, but that Fed officials need to be cognizant of changes in the environment to avoid being too restrictive with interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-doesnt-look-like-its-recession-feds-goolsbee-tells-cnbc-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IW6NITQ4KNL4RHL655DSVJTWIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品公司肉类销售反弹，季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）第三季度收入和利润超出华尔街预期，原因是肉类产品销售反弹，同时谷物价格下跌降低了动物饲料成本。【原文：Tyson Foods surpassed Wall Street expectations for third-quarter revenue and profit on Monday as sales of meat products rebounded while lower grain prices reduced costs for animal feed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tyson-foods-tops-quarterly-estimates-meat-sales-rebound-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACYF5XEP5JM4XDSXH3JDWDAG2I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果、英伟达领衔的 "华丽七巨头 "价值将缩水 1 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，苹果和英伟达（Nvidia）引领了科技股的抛售潮，原因是对美国经济衰退的担忧以及伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）减持 iPhone 制造商股份的决定刺破了该行业长达数月的涨势。【原文：Apple and Nvidia led a sell-off in technology stocks on Monday as U.S. recession fears and Berkshire Hathaway's decision to cut its stake in the iPhone maker punctured a months-long rally in the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/magnificent-seven-set-shed-1-trillion-value-led-by-apple-nvidia-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VE5PDZDAXBMTJEWGZHKTXS6GWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与通用电气和波音公司达成抵消协议后，波兰更接近购买阿帕奇直升机]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰国防部周一与波音公司和通用电气公司签署了价值近 10 亿兹罗提（约合 2.55 亿美元）的抵消协议，使其更接近于敲定一项价值 120 亿美元的购买 96 架 AH-64E 阿帕奇直升机的协议。【原文：Poland's defence ministry signed offset deals with Boeing and General Electric worth nearly 1 billion zlotys ($255 million) on Monday, bringing it closer to finalising a $12 billion agreement to buy 96 AH-64E Apache helicopters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/poland-closer-buying-apache-helicopters-after-offset-deals-with-ge-boeing-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGLWS5SDLBOBHELBS2LT373BQ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元回升让高歌猛进的日本公司重回人间]]></title><description><![CDATA[日元升值导致日本股市在周一跌回谷底，使投资者急于判断盈利前景可能恶化，并扼杀了东京市场长达数月的大幅上涨。【原文：A resurgent yen helped bring Japanese stocks crashing back to earth on Monday, leaving investors scrambling to gauge the potentially diminished outlook for earnings, and snuffing out a months-long dramatic run by the Tokyo market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/resurgent-yen-brings-high-flying-japan-inc-back-earth-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4KJFY54GVMDFH2VRNFUT3B3TQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:01:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，埃隆-马斯克重启对 Sam Altman 和 OpenAI 的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周一报道，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）重启了对 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 及其首席执行官山姆-阿尔特曼（Sam Altman）的诉讼，指控该公司将利润和商业利益置于公共利益之上。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk has revived a lawsuit against ChatGPT-maker OpenAI and its CEO Sam Altman, alleging that the firm put profits and commercial interests ahead of the public good, the New York Times reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/elon-musk-revives-lawsuit-against-sam-altman-openai-nyt-reports-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L75H2IMR4NODBOLOO6NGFJEU7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品公司因需求反弹、成本开始下降，季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）周一公布的第三季度收入和利润超出华尔街预期，表明市场对其肉类产品的需求正在回升，同时谷物价格下降也降低了动物饲料的成本。【原文：Tyson Foods surpassed Wall Street expectations for third-quarter revenue and profit on Monday, indicating that demand was rebounding for its meat products, while lower grain prices reduced costs for animal feed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tyson-foods-tops-quarterly-estimates-demand-rebounds-costs-begin-fall-2024-08-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUBPU66ILFIC7EMSEZRO6ETQQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>