<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:21:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:21:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，SpaceX正考虑在首次公开募股中采用双重股权结构]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周五援引知情人士消息报道称，埃隆·马斯克旗下的SpaceX公司正考虑在今年计划中的首次公开募股（IPO）中采用双层股权结构。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX is considering a dual-class share structure in its planned IPO this year, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/spacex-considering-dual-class-shares-ipo-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3TWSA4DFJLWDBNSBN5U4L5G6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行监管机构正逐步推进针对大型银行的新版《巴塞尔协议》规则提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据本周公布的监管文件显示，美国银行监管机构似乎正逐步推进所谓"巴塞尔终局"规则的新版本提案，该规则将规定大型银行必须如何衡量其风险。【原文：U.S. bank regulators appear to be moving closer to proposing a new version of the so-called "Basel endgame" rules dictating how large banks must measure their risk, according to regulatory filings posted this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-bank-regulators-move-closer-proposing-new-basel-rules-large-banks-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNIWWXNP75PPZHM6TAFE675OHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司寻求运营美国至委内瑞拉航班的批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司周五向美国交通部提交文件称，该公司正寻求批准，计划通过其全资拥有的地区性航空公司Envoy，开通从迈阿密飞往委内瑞拉首都加拉加斯和马拉开波的美国境内航班。【原文：American Airlines said Friday it was seeking approval to operate U.S. flights to Caracas and Maracaibo in Venezuela from Miami through its wholly owned regional carrier Envoy, according to a filing with the U.S. Transportation Department.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/american-airlines-seeks-approval-operate-us-flights-venezeula-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMLHAKCV3FMPJBGVFQEU7OSUBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普环保署取消美国车企排放限值；各州法规及诉讼或将接踵而至]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统废除联邦气候监管基础的举措，将立即使汽车制造商摆脱昂贵的尾气排放标准束缚。但此举可能引发诉讼，并迫使企业面对各州及地区规则纷繁复杂的不确定未来。【原文：President Donald Trump's repeal of the foundation for federal climate regulation will immediately free automakers from costly tailpipe emissions standards, but the move could spark lawsuits and force businesses to navigate an uncertain future of multiple state and regional rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-epa-ends-emissions-limits-us-automakers-state-rules-lawsuits-could-follow-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWTZ47IHHNL77FWCBVZ75XLP2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:07:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航空公司和旅游集团警告称，政府部分停摆将影响机场安检人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[主要航空公司和旅游集团周五敦促国会避免政府部分停摆，否则在繁忙的美国春假旅行季来临前，约5万名机场安检人员将无法获得薪资。【原文：Major airlines and travel groups on Friday urged Congress to avoid a partial government shutdown, which would result in about 50,000 airport security officers not getting paid ahead of the busy U.S. spring break travel period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/airlines-travel-groups-warn-impact-partial-government-shutdown-airport-screeners-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYR23G6H6JLO5PA5VAUR2L4AHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软、爱立信牵头组建全球科技联盟，共筑数字信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[由微软和爱立信牵头的15家公司于周五联合发起"可信技术联盟"，该联盟围绕五大原则构建，旨在确保技术无论在何处开发都能安全使用。【原文：A group of 15 companies, led by Microsoft and Ericsson , launched on Friday the “Trusted Tech Alliance,” built around five principles to safely use technology regardless of where it is developed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-ericsson-lead-global-tech-alliance-digital-trust-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNR2IMGO7NNYRK3CM4UA26RTPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称委内瑞拉国家石油公司仅向获得单独许可的企业出售石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[委内瑞拉国有石油公司PDVSA过去两周拒绝向未获得美国单独许可的企业出售石油，四家寻求购买货物的公司消息人士向路透社透露。此举限制了该国石油出口，阻碍了其加快清空满溢储油罐的进程。【原文：Venezuela's state-run oil company PDVSA has refused to sell oil to companies without individual U.S. licenses in the past two weeks, four sources from companies seeking to buy cargoes told Reuters, limiting exports and preventing the country from draining brimming storage tanks faster.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuelas-pdvsa-selling-oil-only-individually-licensed-companies-sources-say-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKHTCWFKZVNUPDJC4DWMKCKNOI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026年企业缩减规模、推迟IPO，市场波动考验估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[2026年，多家公司缩减或推迟了在美国市场的首次公开募股计划，市场波动、估值审查以及同行表现疲软等因素共同影响了新股上市进程。【原文：Several companies have downsized or postponed their U.S. initial public offerings in 2026, as market volatility, valuation scrutiny and weak peer performance weighed on the new listings pipeline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/companies-trim-delay-ipos-2026-volatility-tests-valuations-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26B4LCOPJBJLVP3ZF57LXU3T3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:58:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，美国联邦贸易委员会正加强对微软人工智能和云计算业务的审查，并向竞争对手展开问询。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周五报道，美国联邦贸易委员会正加强对微软的审查力度，并已向该科技巨头的竞争对手征询有关其许可协议及其他商业行为的意见。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is escalating scrutiny of Microsoft and has sought answers from the company's rivals on the tech giant's licensing and other business practices, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-ftc-ramps-up-scrutiny-microsoft-over-ai-cloud-practices-questions-rivals-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SCFO4SIL5JYFATPAJMUSCG2ZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行称，该行客户对美元风险敞口的对冲规模创2023年以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大托管机构之一纽约梅隆银行的客户正以逾两年最高幅度对冲美元风险敞口，该行高级策略师周五向路透社透露，这反映出投资者今年对美元的谨慎态度有所增强。【原文：Clients of BNY, one of the world's biggest custodians, are hedging their exposure to the dollar by the most in over two years, a senior strategist told Reuters on Friday, reflecting an increase in investor caution towards the U.S. currency this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-clients-hedge-dollar-exposure-by-most-since-2023-bank-says-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRRL2JZXDBPQZGOUG5RRDMYBDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:22:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官裁定摩根大通客户可就现金清算利率过低提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通必须面对部分拟议集体诉讼，联邦法官裁定，该诉讼指控这家美国最大银行向经纪账户和退休账户持有人支付接近零利率的闲置现金利息，而非市场利率。【原文：JPMorgan Chase must face part of a proposed class action lawsuit accusing the largest U.S. bank of paying brokerage and retirement account holders near-zero interest rates instead of market rates on their idle cash, a federal judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/jpmorgan-customers-can-sue-over-low-rates-cash-sweeps-us-judge-rules-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NY2PFBW3RIH3LKATLOPFTBWE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instacart股价飙升，乐观预测缓解市场对竞争的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线杂货配送公司Instacart周五股价一度飙升19%，这家数百万美国人的首选购物平台发布了乐观的一季度业绩预期，缓解了市场对其面临日益激烈竞争的担忧。【原文：Instacart's shares surged as much as 19% on Friday after the online grocery delivery company, a go-to for millions of Americans, issued an upbeat first-quarter forecast that eased worries about growing competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/instacart-shares-soar-upbeat-forecast-tempers-competition-fears-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3RRSAONTVIUJC7ALD26AP4YB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅首席执行官称，在开云集团与科蒂公司推进交易之际，欧莱雅倾向于优先获得古驰美妆授权。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅首席执行官尼古拉·希罗尼穆斯周五表示，公司希望能在2028年前获得古驰美妆品牌授权，并补充称该问题正在古驰母公司开云集团与现任授权方科蒂公司之间进行磋商。【原文：L'Oreal would welcome gaining access to the Gucci beauty licence earlier than 2028, CEO Nicolas Hieronimus said on Friday, adding that the issue was being discussed between Gucci-owner Kering and current licence holder Coty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/loreal-favours-early-access-gucci-beauty-licence-kering-coty-work-towards-deal-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXGTW73RHBOHHHSCC3PSKZ7GBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从软件到房地产，美国各行业正深陷人工智能恐慌交易的漩涡]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街正深陷人工智能引发的颠覆性担忧。最初投资者抛售软件公司股票，但很快蔓延至被视为易受自动化冲击的行业，导致本周美股大幅下挫。【原文：Wall Street is in the grip of disruption worries from AI. It first started with investors dumping shares of software companies but soon spread to sectors seen as vulnerable to automation, driving sharp losses in U.S. stocks this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/software-real-estate-us-sectors-under-grip-ai-scare-trade-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCYK3EJPNJIHPJMABWDL253RVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:44:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟考虑采取双轨制打破经济改革僵局]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟各国政府长期以来宣扬团结是应对中美经济压力的最佳对策，但如今发现亟需提升欧洲竞争力，而等待全部27个成员国达成共识可能耗时过久。【原文：EU governments have long preached unity as the best response to U.S. and Chinese economic pressure, but are discovering they need urgently to boost Europe's competitiveness and that waiting for all 27 member states to agree may take too long.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-weighs-two-track-approach-break-economic-reform-deadlock-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2HGWNECBNMYXKVYZP4BKEIGSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:29:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利国家铜业公司（Codelco）在调查后更换了埃尔滕尼恩特矿的高管团队]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利国有企业科德尔科公司——全球最大的铜生产商——周五宣布，在对埃尔特尼恩特矿山致命坍塌事故的调查结果公布后，将更换部分高管。【原文：Chile's state-run Codelco, the world's largest copper producer, announced on Friday it was replacing some executives following the results of an investigation into a deadly mine collapse at its El Teniente mine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chiles-codelco-replaces-top-executives-el-teniente-mine-after-investigation-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCTAUBV525ODDFDFADUWZVYEFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:26:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国允许石油巨头重启委内瑞拉业务，基本批准新能源投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周五放宽了对委内瑞拉能源领域的制裁，颁布两项通用许可证，允许全球能源公司在该欧佩克成员国恢复油气业务，并允许其他公司就新能源业务投资合同进行谈判。【原文：The U.S. eased sanctions on Venezuela's energy sector on Friday, issuing two general licenses that allow global energy companies to resume oil and gas operations in the OPEC member and for other companies to negotiate contracts on investments in new energy operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-allows-oil-majors-resume-venezuela-operations-broadly-okays-new-energy-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WYJEWMLHNNIJFNS6WEBIWPMTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，Vista Equity正寻求以10亿美元以上价格出售AlertMedia。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，Vista Equity Partners正考虑以10亿美元以上的价格出售其旗下紧急通讯软件供应商AlertMedia。【原文：Vista Equity Partners is exploring a $1 billion-plus sale of its emergency communications software provider AlertMedia, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/vista-equity-explores-1-billion-plus-sale-alertmedia-sources-say-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CC6SRUFMIJKDFNJVAOXKN32SDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部初步支持西班尼-斯蒂尔沃特公司对俄罗斯钯征收关税的呼吁]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班尼-斯蒂尔沃特公司周五表示，其呼吁美国对俄罗斯钯进口征收关税的提议已获得美国商务部的初步支持，但最终决定预计要到2026年年中才会作出。【原文：Sibanye-Stillwater's call for U.S. tariff on Russian palladium imports has received preliminary support from the U.S. Commerce Department, although a final decision is not expected until mid-2026, the miner said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/us-commerce-dept-gives-initial-backing-sibanye-stillwaters-call-tariffs-russian-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QD7756O2WJNLBLJN7JA3M3K75M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称美联储拟任命前华尔街律师盖恩担任银行监管要职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，美国联邦储备委员会预计将任命兰德尔·盖恩担任新的监管总监，这位与华尔街渊源深厚、在银行业关系广泛的资深人士将执掌监管行业的重要职位。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve is expected to name Randall Guynn as its new director of supervision and regulation, said two people familiar with the matter, putting a Wall Street veteran with deep banking ties in a powerful position policing the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-fed-tap-former-wall-street-lawyer-guynn-top-bank-oversight-role-say-sources-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXVRMES7F5N55DOGS57BVCVOFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:23:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛首席执行官向CNBC表示，他"不情愿地接受了"律师鲁姆勒的辞职。]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团首席执行官大卫·所罗门周五向CNBC表示，他虽不情愿但已接受首席法律官凯西·鲁姆勒的辞职，并强调尊重她的离职决定。【原文：Goldman Sachs CEO David Solomon said he had reluctantly accepted Chief Legal Officer Kathy Ruemmler's resignation, he told CNBC on Friday and stressed that he respected her decision to leave.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-sachs-ceo-says-he-reluctantly-accepted-lawyer-ruemmlers-resignation-cnbc-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXWI53PS4ZLAZGNXNATQJZZLXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:21:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司表示，随着美加贸易紧张局势加剧，海外商务旅行需求激增。]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司一位高管周五表示，随着该国寻求摆脱对美国的贸易依赖，企业海外出行量激增近30%，这推动了国际旅行需求。【原文：Air Canada sees a near 30% surge in corporate traffic flowing overseas as the country seeks to diversify trade away from the United States, fueling demand for international travel, a company executive said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/air-canada-sees-surging-overseas-corporate-travel-following-us-trade-tensions-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42Z2CGY3IVOKJJ3UCBTVNYXM6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国1月消费者价格涨幅低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据显示，美国1月份消费者价格涨幅低于预期，这使得美联储今年降息的计划得以推进。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased less than expected in January, data showed, keeping the Federal Reserve on track to cut interest rates this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-us-consumer-prices-rise-less-than-expected-january-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUKCJHVHL5KO3BMGHBHTATK4RU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国利率期货显示，在通胀数据公布后，美联储六月放松政策的可能性上升。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国利率期货小幅上调了美联储6月降息的可能性，此前数据显示1月份通胀涨幅低于预期。【原文：U.S. interest rate futures slightly raised odds of rate cuts by the Federal Reserve in June after a report that showed inflation rose less than expected in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-rate-futures-raise-odds-fed-eaasing-june-after-inflation-data-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUYVNLGPSFIZLJPHH6MUZUZIDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称PJM计划或将加速数据中心电力交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，美国最大电网运营商PJM互联公司为应对数据中心激增的电力需求而制定的计划，可能加速数据中心所有者与独立电力生产商之间的交易达成。【原文：A plan from PJM Interconnection, the largest power grid operator in the U.S., to manage burgeoning power demand from data centers could accelerate deal-making between data-center owners and independent power producers, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pjm-plan-could-accelerate-data-center-power-deals-analysts-say-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSHXAA6ULVNA5NKTOJPTCWQYGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pinterest股价暴跌，因关税拖累大客户广告支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五盘前交易中，图片分享平台Pinterest股价暴跌逾20%，此前该公司表示，由于关税引发的不确定性导致美国大型零售商削减广告支出，其季度营收预期受到冲击。【原文：Pinterest shares plummeted over 20% in premarket trading on Friday after the image-sharing platform said its quarterly revenue forecast was hit by large U.S. retailers scaling back ad spending due to tariff-induced uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/pinterest-plunges-tariffs-weigh-large-customers-ad-spending-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5T6RIZ23EZOPHNJH5WPODFUSMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:53:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian股价飙升，即将上市的平价SUV推动电动汽车交付预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian预计其低价车型今年将吸引更多买家，推动该公司股价周五飙升24%，这再次表明电动汽车制造商正押注平价车型以重振销量——此前一项关键联邦补贴政策已到期。【原文：Rivian's projection that its cheaper models would attract more buyers this year powered a 24% stock jump on Friday, the latest sign of electric vehicle makers betting on affordable cars to revive sales after a key federal subsidy expired.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-surges-upcoming-affordable-suv-powers-ev-delivery-forecast-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FH3ZZUAYGROPDL43NKJRGFE32I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[施罗德出售案使更多欧洲基金管理公司成为收购目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国历史悠久的基金管理公司施罗德本周决定向美国资产管理公司纽文出售资产，这凸显了欧洲竞争对手在快速整合的全球行业中面临的严峻抉择：要么扩大规模，要么出售资产。【原文：Historic British fund manager Schroders' decision this week to sell up to U.S. asset manager Nuveen highlights the stark choice facing European rivals struggling to compete in a rapidly consolidating global industry: bulk up or sell out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/schroders-sale-puts-more-european-money-managers-play-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADEBFV2IXJMTTLIYSEUKSOV5T4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者价格涨幅低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国1月份消费者价格涨幅低于预期，但随着企业年初提价，潜在通胀有所增强。加之劳动力市场趋于稳定，美联储可能在一段时间内维持利率不变。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased less than expected in January, but underlying inflation firmed as businesses raised prices at the start of the year, which together with a stabilizing labor market could allow the Federal Reserve to keep interest rates unchanged for a while.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-prices-rise-less-than-expected-january-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35TTTA6P2VMKRLZNAI5L7KOR24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:38:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金在Wegovy对决前大举押注Hims & Hers Health，Hazeltree数据显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金做空Hims & Hers Health的仓位在1月份达到至少一年来的最高水平，就在这家在线远程医疗公司与诺和诺德就其低价减肥药发生冲突之前。Hazeltree向路透社提供的数据显示。【原文：Hedge fund bets against Hims & Hers Health hit their highest in at least a year in January, just before the online telehealth firm clashed with Novo Nordisk over its cut-price weight-loss pill, according to data shared with Reuters by Hazeltree.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hedge-funds-bet-big-against-hims-hers-health-before-wegovy-showdown-hazeltree-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDF7VEUFLBJDXEMXXQUKOQCSU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>