<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 08:07:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 08:07:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[EssilorLuxottica 的 Nuance 音频眼镜获得 FDA 认证]]></title><description><![CDATA[依视路（EssilorLuxottica）周一表示，美国食品和药物管理局（FDA）为其非处方 Nuance 音频眼镜开了绿灯。【原文：EssilorLuxottica said on Monday it received a green light from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for its over-the-counter Nuance audio glasses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/essilorluxottica-receives-fda-clearance-its-nuance-audio-glasses-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLDRU62DJFOG5JVDMM43Q6KAKI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 07:47:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 采用新的内部组织结构，继续物色新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 周一宣布了一项旨在简化结构和加快流程的内部改革，这家汽车制造商在前首席执行官卡洛斯-塔瓦雷斯（Carlos Tavares）于 12 月离职后开始推进重组。【原文：Stellantis announced on Monday an internal overhaul aimed at simplifying its structure and speeding up processes, as the carmaker presses ahead with a reorganisation it started after former CEO Carlos Tavares left in December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-adopts-new-internal-organisation-new-ceo-search-continues-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPWNQ4N7NNKBTI3KAKQ7HCW3TU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 07:12:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：DeepSeek 让欧洲科技公司有机会在全球人工智能竞赛中迎头赶上]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国初创公司 Novo AI 的老板 Hemanth Mandapati 是 DeepSeek 聊天机器人的早期采用者，两周前他从 OpenAI 的 ChatGPT 改用了中国的人工智能模型。【原文：Hemanth Mandapati, boss of German startup Novo AI, was an early adopter of DeepSeek chatbots when he switched to the Chinese AI model from OpenAI's ChatGPT two weeks ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/deepseek-gives-europes-tech-firms-chance-catch-up-global-ai-race-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFEC3WG2NFONXLJPLCJKODM3IE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 06:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：中国将提议恢复 2020 年与美国的 "第一阶段 "贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》援引消息人士的话报道，中国对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府加征关税的初步建议将以恢复特朗普第一任期内于2020年签署的第一阶段贸易协议为中心。【原文：China's initial proposal to tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump's administration will centre on restoring the Phase 1 trade deal signed in 2020 during Trump's first term, the Wall Street Journal reported, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/china-propose-restoring-2020-phase-1-trade-deal-with-us-wsj-reports-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3RML7A6AZK4NHUXSKQR7WROAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:56:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价特朗普关税现实令市场不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHJ6VP33HROFHGKVXUD6OSO5KE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:36:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银与 OpenAI 同意成立日本人工智能合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[软银集团首席执行官孙正义（Masayoshi Son）周一表示，他已与 OpenAI 首席执行官山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）达成协议，将在日本成立一家合资企业，为企业客户提供人工智能服务。【原文：SoftBank Group CEO Masayoshi Son said on Monday he has agreed with OpenAI CEO Sam Altman to set up a joint venture in Japan to offer artificial intelligence services to corporate customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/softbank-openai-set-up-ai-japan-joint-venture-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIKAYOB6P5MV7JOHD3QAC6H5H4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国人可能在与墨西哥、加拿大和中国的贸易战中感受到 "痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收的全面关税可能会给美国人带来 "短期 "痛苦，因为全球市场担心这些征税可能会破坏经济增长并重新引发通货膨胀。【原文：President Donald Trump said the sweeping tariffs that he has imposed on Mexico, Canada and China may cause "short term" pain for Americans as global markets reflected concerns the levies could undermine growth and reignite inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-americans-may-feel-pain-trade-war-with-mexico-canada-china-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V75HBLEQQFKW5FRTLJTJ6QVTLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:17:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：尽管澳大利亚严格禁止未成年人使用社交媒体，但对 YouTube 的豁免仍存在风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚政府在通过禁止 16 岁以下儿童访问社交媒体的法律时，为 YouTube 规定了一项豁免，但一些心理健康和极端主义专家说，视频共享网站会让他们接触到令人上瘾的有害内容。【原文：Australia's government carved out an exemption for YouTube when it passed laws banning social media access for children under 16, but some mental health and extremism experts say the video-sharing website exposes them to addictive and harmful content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/despite-australias-strict-social-media-ban-minors-youtube-exemption-poses-risks-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VWDLOQ4SFMLTF6EZITIVEHCXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普征收关税后，台湾将帮助企业迁往美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾经济部周一表示，台湾将支持有意迁往美国的企业，包括帮助它们在当地寻找合作伙伴，并概述了在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收新关税后台湾将提供的援助。【原文：Taiwan will support firms that intend to relocate to the United States including helping them find partners on the ground, the economy ministry said on Monday, outlining assistance it will offer following U.S. President Donald Trump's new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/taiwan-help-companies-relocate-us-following-trump-tariffs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X43WW7772JOYLP5JHTJMDOKIPY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:10:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称特朗普关税对石油和天然气价格影响有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）在周日的一份报告中表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对从加拿大、墨西哥和中国进口的商品征收的新关税可能会对全球石油和天然气价格产生有限的短期影响。【原文：The new tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump on imports from Canada, Mexico, and China are likely to have a limited near-term impact on global oil and gas prices, Goldman Sachs said in a note on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trumps-tariffs-have-limited-impact-oil-gas-prices-goldman-sachs-says-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAFI5CFPB5ICBAYTYU5G6HBC34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的贸易战炮火震撼市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对美国主要贸易伙伴征收关税后，投资者周一买入美元、抛售股票并担心通货膨胀，争相评估贸易战风险。【原文：Investors bought dollars, sold stocks and fretted about inflation on Monday in a scramble to assess the risk of trade war after Donald Trump put tariffs on top U.S. trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-trade-war-salvo-jolts-markets-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CT6NXQ2HOJMH5J35AZR7PYIUZY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普关税影响，亚洲汽车制造商跌幅居前]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，日本和韩国汽车制造商及其供应商的股票领跌亚洲股市，因为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对墨西哥、加拿大和中国全面征收关税，使整个地区的出口商遭受重创。【原文：Shares of Japanese and South Korean car makers and their suppliers led declines in Asia on Monday, as exporters across the region were walloped by U.S. President Donald Trump's introduction of sweeping tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/asia-automakers-lead-decline-region-takes-beating-trump-tariffs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDPEVJS3HVOJZCXNWANGDUXK64</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度誓言避免发出贸易保护主义信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）采取关税举措之际，印度财政部最高官员在削减高端摩托车进口关税后表示，印度不想发出任何保护主义的信号。【原文：India does not want to give any signal that it is protectionist, the top bureaucrat in the finance ministry said, after slashing import duties on high-end motorcycles, amid U.S. President Donald Trump's moves on tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-vows-avoid-protectionist-signals-trade-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DS46QCSSJLWJPYFH6SMIRLOW4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:59:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税可能对大宗商品和能源行业产生哪些影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六对加拿大和墨西哥征收25%的关税，对中国征收10%的关税，并称这些措施是打击非法移民和毒品贸易所必需的。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump slapped Canada and Mexico with duties of 25% and China with a 10% levy on Saturday, calling the measures necessary to combat illegal immigration and the drug trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/how-trumps-tariffs-might-affect-commodity-energy-sectors-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQELWI7T4RIPXAAHGCBJ3MAG7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本经济产业省称，尚难预测 DeepSeek 对电力需求的潜在影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本产业省通过电子邮件表示，它知道有一种观点认为，数据中心的扩张可能会增加电力需求，但目前还很难预测随着 DeepSeek 等一项技术的出现，电力需求会发生怎样的变化。【原文：Japan's industry ministry is aware of a view that expansion of data centres may increase demand for electricity, however, it is difficult yet to predict how demand may change with the appearance of one technology such as DeepSeek, it said by email.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/difficult-yet-predict-deepseeks-potential-impact-power-demand-japans-meti-says-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCXHMK3WZFO6TKDL4TJLWEAIKE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 02:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球经济 特朗普关税引发情绪波动，亚洲工厂活动疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的民间调查显示，由于中国需求疲软以及美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁提高关税，影响了商业情绪，亚洲的工厂活动在1月份有所减弱，从而使该地区的经济前景变得暗淡。【原文：Asia's factory activity weakened in January as soft Chinese demand and threats of higher tariffs by U.S. President Donald Trump weighed on business sentiment, private surveys showed on Monday, darkening the outlook for the region's economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-economy-asias-factory-activity-weakens-trump-tariffs-jolt-sentiment-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GQRDBLX6ZPLDCDCSOQPCN2QJE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 02:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新制造业采购经理人指数显示 1 月份中国工厂活动增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一进行的一项私营企业调查显示，由于贸易不确定性增加，1 月份中国工厂活动增速放缓，员工人数创下近五年来最快降幅。【原文：China's factory activity grew at a slower pace in January, while staffing levels fell at the quickest pace in nearly five years as trade uncertainties increased, a private-sector business survey showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-factory-activity-growth-slows-january-caixin-pmi-shows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRZCW3DTURJJJMYJL545F2LF3Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚购物者受折扣诱惑，支撑第四季度经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 12 月份的零售额有所下滑，这是对上个月 "黑色星期五 "大肆挥霍的回报，但打折活动帮助购物者在整个第四季度为经济增长做出了急需的贡献。【原文：Australian retail sales dipped in December as pay back for a Black Friday splurge the month before, but discounting helped shoppers make a desperately-needed contribution to economic growth over the whole fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-shoppers-lured-by-discounts-shore-up-economy-4q-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXJIWE4GPJLHZLQMJTIVIZQS7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发贸易战，股市暴跌，美元飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元和比特币暴跌，油价上涨。【原文：The euro and bitcoin plunged while oil prices rose.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1pixtv-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76NVLAILPRLGHH5Z5AB3AC5DMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本工厂活动延续下滑态势，乐观情绪减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一项私营部门调查显示，由于需求低迷，日本工厂活动以 10 个月来最快的速度下滑，商业信心创下两年多来的新低，这表明制造业正承受着沉重的压力。【原文：Japan's factory activity fell at the fastest pace in 10 months on sluggish demand, a private-sector survey showed on Monday, with business confidence hitting a more than two-year low in a sign that the manufacturing sector is under heavy pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-factory-activity-extends-decline-optimism-weakens-pmi-shows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORHB3U73QZPW7EQTLC5L7QMNTM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摘要显示，日本央行董事会在 1 月会议上讨论了更多加息的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行 1 月份会议的意见摘要周一显示，日本央行决策者讨论了进一步加息的可能性，一些决策者警告通胀上行风险和日元疲软可能对经济造成的损害。【原文：Bank of Japan policymakers discussed the likelihood of raising interest rates further with some warning of upside inflation risks and the damage a weak yen could inflict on the economy, a summary of opinions at their January meeting showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/boj-board-discussed-january-meeting-likelihood-more-rate-hikes-summary-shows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRUWEJYONFLNNMV5HKZ6SPQBK4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:22:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 推出新的人工智能工具，为研究任务提供便利]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周日推出了一款名为 "深度研究 "的新型人工智能（AI）工具，并称该工具可在互联网上针对复杂任务开展多步骤研究。【原文：OpenAI launched a new artificial intelligence (AI) tool on Sunday called "deep research", which it said conducts multi-step research on the internet for complex tasks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-launches-new-ai-tool-facilitate-research-tasks-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SYWNWOZYBILHF62CK3TSLEZCE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:19:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星首席执行官就有争议的合并案面临裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子（Samsung Electronics）董事长李在镕（Jay Y. Lee）周一将面临首尔一家上诉法院对其 2015 年并购案的裁决。【原文：Samsung Electronics Chair Jay Y. Lee faces a ruling by a Seoul appeals court on Monday over a 2015 merger that prosecutors said was designed to cement his control of the tech giant at the expense of minority shareholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/samsung-chief-faces-ruling-controversial-merger-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A76NF7FEBVMIPBHIZKTGHJJKCU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人民币创历史新低，墨西哥比索和加元因特朗普关税而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人民币周一在离岸交易中跌至历史新低，墨西哥比索和加拿大元跌至多年低点，此前美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对这些国家征收关税，引发了对贸易战升级的担忧。【原文：China's yuan slumped to a record low in offshore trading on Monday, while Mexico's peso and Canada's dollar tumbled to multi-year troughs after U.S. President Donald Trump slapped the countries with tariffs, triggering fears of an escalating trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yuan-hits-record-low-mexican-peso-canadian-dollar-tumble-trump-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SOQTDIM6RNLJO3KURP5V2EBMI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:42:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收关税后油价跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收关税，引发了市场对贸易战和美国最大的两个原油供应国原油供应中断的担忧，油价在周一开盘时跳涨。【原文：Oil prices jumped at the market open on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump imposes tariffs on Canada, Mexico and China, raising fears of a trade war and disruption in crude supply from two of the United States' biggest suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-jump-after-trump-imposes-tariffs-canada-mexico-china-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GFFP63AP7FJFNLF7XBPLWY7VZE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:29:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税震荡市场，比特币跌破 10 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球贸易战的阴影让投资者惶惶不安，并将他们挤出风险资产，加密货币价格下滑。【原文：Cryptocurrency prices slid as the spectre of a global trade war put investors on edge and pushed them out of risky assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/bitcoin-slides-below-100000-tariffs-rattle-markets-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQVEMCRP25LR7HKJMI7RDORTPI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:41:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大将对美国关税采取法律行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府一位高级官员周日表示，加拿大将根据相关国际机构采取法律行动，挑战美国对大多数加拿大商品征收25%关税的做法，并称美国的关税是非法和不合理的。【原文：Canada will take legal action under the relevant international bodies to challenge the 25% tariffs imposed by the United States on most Canadian goods, a senior government official said on Sunday, calling the tariffs illegal and unjustified.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-take-legal-action-against-us-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5RBDJ2ZPBPG3IQOU5IHMB3YMY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税引发贸易战，墨西哥谢因鲍姆誓言顽强抵抗]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）在墨西哥政府与美国宣布相互征收关税一天后的周日表示，理智应该占上风。【原文：Mexico's President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Sunday that reason should prevail a day after her government and the U.S. announced tariffs against one another, raising her fist in the air as she said she does not lack courage to respond.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-sheinbaum-vows-resilience-us-tariffs-trigger-trade-war-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VP2WVJINGZOEHCJMBMDSQLMN5M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标特朗普发动贸易战，各方纷纷躲避]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE54RORANPSFN2FO2EP223BOY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 21:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大将推出减轻企业关税负担的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大官员周日宣布，他们将为加拿大企业提供一种机制，使其免受未来几天生效的针对美国的报复性关税的影响。【原文：Canadian officials announced Sunday they will provide a mechanism for Canadian businesses to obtain relief from retaliatory tariffs set to take effect against the United States in the coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canada-launch-program-relieve-businesses-tariff-hit-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RK3JYJP6C5PFPNMCORBFCT2UN4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 19:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>