<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:34:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:34:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片需求激增，Lam Research 季度收入超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受先进人工智能芯片需求强劲的推动，芯片制造设备供应商Lam Research周三公布的第三季度营收超出华尔街预期，公司股价在盘后交易中上涨4.5%。【原文：Chip-making equipment supplier Lam Research beat Wall Street expectations for third-quarter revenue on Wednesday, fueled by robust demand for advanced AI chips, sending the company's shares up 4.5% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/lam-research-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-surging-ai-chip-demand-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPIJ7PPXDNKBFKAFFH4MAYURMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[损失准备金减少，利息收入增加，Discover Financial 利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国信用卡发行商发现金融公司（Discover Financial）周三报告称，受信贷损失准备金下降和利息收入增加的影响，该公司第一季度利润增长了 30%。【原文：U.S. credit card issuer Discover Financial reported a 30% rise in first-quarter profit on Wednesday, helped by a drop in the company's provision for credit losses and higher interest income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/discover-financial-profit-jumps-lower-loss-provision-higher-interest-income-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLMIQO3CHNMDFAHWB6FMZDFQ2E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 贸易战担忧减弱，华尔街延续反弹势头]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OUUDCB4A5K3NHTHLKGKP3B2ZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡业务强劲，拉斯维加斯金沙季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于新加坡业务的强劲需求抵消了澳门市场增长的停滞，赌场运营商拉斯维加斯金沙周三公布的第一季度利润超过了分析师的预期。【原文：Casino operator Las Vegas Sands surpassed analysts' expectations for first-quarter profit on Wednesday, as strong demand from its Singapore business offsets stalling market growth in Macao.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/las-vegas-sands-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-strong-singapore-business-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7E2V4U45NNMJAXZJVGET32OFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:54:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》：特朗普将豁免汽车制造商部分美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周三援引几位熟知内情的人士的话报道称，在汽车行业高管最近几周的大力游说下，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正计划免除汽车制造商的部分关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is planning to spare carmakers from some tariffs following intense lobbying by industry executives over recent weeks, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday, citing a couple of people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-exempt-carmakers-some-us-tariffs-ft-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFMITRSOTVOLFM7GXDBZOBLKWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府对进口商用卡车展开国家安全调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周三表示，正在对进口到美国的中型和重型卡车及相关零部件对国家安全的影响展开调查。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Wednesday it is opening a probe into national security impacts of imports of medium-duty and heavy-duty trucks and related parts into the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-opens-national-security-probe-into-imported-commercial-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFGBMVQVSFKGJA3VTAWNDTUPYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:45:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空公司下调 2025 年和 2026 年利润展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国西南航空公司周三以当前宏观经济的不确定性为由，下调了 2025 年和 2026 年的利润预期。【原文：Southwest Airlines on Wednesday pulled its profit outlook for 2025 and 2026, citing the current macroeconomic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/southwest-airlines-pulls-it-profit-outlook-2025-2026-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOT45ULLDBJXJOFC2SHBFM4QNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，狮门股东批准分拆制片厂和 Starz 业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉此事的人士周三告诉路透社，《约翰-威克》系列电影的幕后工作室狮门娱乐公司（Lions Gate Entertainment）的股东已经批准了一项将其电影和电视工作室从 Starz 业务中分离出来的计划。【原文：Shareholders of Lions Gate Entertainment , the studio behind the "John Wick" movie franchise, have approved a plan to split its film and TV studio from the Starz business, a person familiar with the matter told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/lions-gate-shareholders-approve-split-studio-starz-business-source-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CW3CEREGWVITHF6PL7P4EZJ4UM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长莱恩表示，美元配置正从超重转向更自然的权重]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行执行董事会成员菲利普-莱恩（Philip Lane）周三表示，最近资产组合配置从美元向外转移，可能代表着从超配美元资产转向更自然地在美元和包括欧元在内的其他货币之间加权。【原文：The recent shifts in asset portfolio allocations away from the dollar may represent a move from overweighting dollar assets to a more natural weighting between dollars and other currencies, including the euro, European Central Bank executive board member Philip Lane said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-allocations-moving-overweight-more-natural-weighting-ecbs-lane-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASB6G4FVQVI35I4ZVOKJ47KOEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道通用汽车将增加俄亥俄州变速器工厂的产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司周三证实，该公司将增加俄亥俄州托莱多工厂的变速器产量，从电动汽车驱动装置生产转向汽油车零部件生产。【原文：General Motors is increasing production of transmissions at its Toledo, Ohio facility, shifting away from EV drive unit manufacturing toward parts for gasoline vehicles, the company confirmed Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-increase-production-ohio-transmission-facility-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUBH36Q3G5IV3NFBZ7UXDULU7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:34:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，特朗普计划豁免汽车制造商的部分关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周三援引两位知情人士的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正计划免除汽车制造商的部分关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is planning to spare carmakers from some tariffs, The Financial Times reported on Wednesday, citing two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-plans-exempt-carmakers-some-tariffs-ft-reports-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XR6DKRY72BI7DG3E47AKXKJYTU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州州长为陷入困境的炼油厂寻求帮助]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州州长加文-纽森（Gavin Newsom）已指示州政府官员加大力度，确保为全美最大的汽车市场提供可靠的燃料供应，这促使石油公司将经营困难和高油价归咎于州政府的政策。【原文：California Governor Gavin Newsom has directed state officials to step up efforts to guarantee reliable fuel supplies for the nation's biggest auto market, prompting oil companies to blame state policies for difficult business conditions and high pump prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/california-governor-seeks-help-struggling-oil-refiners-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOHN6D23PVOGPE3AI4IIJFT65I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[著名做空者安德鲁-莱福特（Andrew Left）未能终结美国证交会欺诈案]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官驳回了安德鲁-莱福特（Andrew Left）要求驳回美国证券交易委员会民事诉讼的请求，该民事诉讼指控这位著名的做空者欺诈性地操纵股价，并从与其公开声明相矛盾的交易中获利。【原文：A federal judge rejected Andrew Left's bid to dismiss a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission civil lawsuit accusing the prominent short seller of fraudulently manipulating stock prices, and profiting from trades that contradicted his public statements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/prominent-short-seller-andrew-left-fails-end-us-sec-fraud-case-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3WOSPSZKVPPNO5X7WIYTBGVDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费疲软，Chipotle 下调年度销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于通胀压力和经济不确定性迫使消费者控制外出就餐的开支，Chipotle Mexican Grill 公司周三调低了年度可比销售额增长预期。【原文：Chipotle Mexican Grill on Wednesday tempered its annual comparable sales growth forecast as sticky inflation and economic uncertainty force consumers to rein in spending on dining out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chipotle-mexican-grill-tempers-annual-comparable-sales-growth-forecast-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELWVXMOQRBJHZIKMKMTU5EB5UQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ServiceNow因人工智能驱动的软件需求复苏而实现乐观的季度盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，ServiceNow 的第一季度利润超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于市场对其人工智能驱动的 IT 服务管理软件的强劲需求，该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨了 7%。【原文：ServiceNow beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter profit on Wednesday, helped by resilient demand for its artificial intelligence-powered software for managing IT services, sending the company's shares up 7% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/servicenow-posts-upbeat-quarterly-profit-resilient-ai-powered-software-demand-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7REGGN4J5JEHKA6XC2EX2R2FY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:14:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBM预测第二季度营收高于预期，舒缓关税忧虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际商业机器公司（IBM）周三表示，预计第二季度营收将高于华尔街预期，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策带来经济不确定性的情况下，该公司押注于其软件服务需求的弹性。【原文：IBM said on Wednesday it expects second-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates, betting on resilient demand for its software services amid economic uncertainty brought on by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ibm-forecasts-second-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-soothing-tariff-worries-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERV7TQAYLROM7PYLPMBSFLGOPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于关税拉动，德州仪器预计第二季度收入将高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[德州仪器（Texas Instruments）周三预计第二季度营收将高于华尔街预期，尽管美国关税引发了广泛的经济不确定性，但该公司仍寄希望于模拟芯片的强劲需求。【原文：Texas Instruments forecast second-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, betting on robust demand for its analog chips despite widespread economic uncertainty stemming from U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/texas-instruments-forecasts-second-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCFH2GR4PNNW5PCWEGVCAD356A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:11:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普有望签署推动技工培训的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份白宫摘要显示，唐纳德-特朗普总统可能最快于周三签署一项改善技术行业就业培训的命令，这项举措与关税并行，是他重振美国制造业的赌注。【原文：President Donald Trump could sign as soon as Wednesday an order to improve job training for skilled trades, an initiative twinned with tariffs in his gambit to revive U.S. manufacturing, a White House summary seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-expected-sign-order-pushing-training-skilled-trades-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQQOMKB4XNJOTAXQBVMAOSISEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EQT 计划减少开支，同时在 2025 年生产更多美国天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国第二大天然气生产商、美国能源公司 EQT 计划减少资本支出，但在 2025 年生产更多能源；而竞争对手 Range Resources 则表示，将从 2024 年起保持支出和产量相对稳定。【原文：U.S. energy company EQT , the country's second-biggest natural gas producer, plans to reduce capital spending but produce more energy in 2025, while rival Range Resources said it would hold expenditures and output relatively steady from 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eqt-plans-spend-less-while-producing-more-us-natgas-2025-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQDDFBTQX5JDZKYSM2P3625R64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球圆桌会议认为，随着不确定性增加，低收入国家的债务风险也在上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球债务圆桌会议主席周三表示，需要做更多的工作来改进主权债务重组进程，并帮助面临日益严峻的偿债挑战的国家，他们同时还发布了一本新的手册来帮助这些努力。【原文：More work is needed to improve the sovereign debt restructuring process and help countries facing mounting debt service challenges, the chairs of a global debt roundtable said on Wednesday, as they released a new playbook to aid those efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-roundtable-sees-rising-debt-risks-low-income-countries-uncertainty-mounts-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QWJ6GZGCNNUTEUNNJRDLYUDNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国央行行长称美国可能因贸易战陷入衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国央行行长弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周三表示，美国可能会因全球贸易战的影响而陷入衰退，但包括欧元区在内的所有人都会受到影响，即使影响较小。【原文：The United States could dip into recession on the fallout from a global trade war but everyone will suffer, including the euro zone, even if to a lesser effect, French central bank chief Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-could-dip-into-recession-trade-war-french-central-banker-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5DWGTKG4VJ2ZNY23YSGPBZSYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:50:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国财政部长表示迫切需要降低关税的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国财政部长约尔格-库基斯（Joerg Kukies）周三在谈到与美国的贸易关税谈判时说，减少不确定性对经济和企业来说都是当务之急。【原文：Reducing uncertainty is urgent for economies and businesses, German Finance Minister Joerg Kukies said on Wednesday, talking about negotiations on trade tariffs with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/german-finance-minister-says-it-is-urgent-reduce-tariffs-uncertainty-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQIX7RU7TZIJTOPGX5D2HUBPY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电展示拼接更大、更快芯片的新技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾积体电路制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co on Wednesday unveiled technology for making faster chips and putting them together in dinner-plate sized packages that will boost performance needed for artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tsmc-shows-off-new-tech-stitching-together-bigger-faster-chips-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4WPK27TSVMLLJTDPI7NOH2FMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国和美国试图在联合国将对方描绘成恶霸]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国和美国周三在联合国安理会非正式会议上相互指责对方的不公平贸易做法，试图将对方描绘成贸易战升级中的全球恶霸。【原文：China and the United States accused each other of unfair trade practices at an informal United Nations Security Council on Wednesday, seeking to portray each other as global bullies amid their escalating trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-seek-portray-each-other-bullies-un-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3Z3IW564LZOQNOW2S6ANVIRLI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国排除在与日本贸易谈判中设定货币目标的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）在本周预计与日本财务大臣加藤胜信（Katsunobu Kato）举行会谈之前于周三表示，美国在与日本的双边贸易谈判中没有特定的货币目标。【原文：The U.S. does not have specific currency targets in mind as part of bilateral trade talks with Japan, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday, ahead of an expected meeting with Japanese Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-rules-out-setting-currency-targets-trade-talks-with-japan-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPWZHJ5PKRPCVEZDYIJSWN6XF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储称最近几周美国经济活动稳定，但不确定性普遍存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三在一份报告中称，自3月份以来，美国大部分地区的物价上涨，经济活动和就业情况变化不大，这份报告反映了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普反复无常地推出旨在重塑全球贸易的全面关税措施所带来的一些早期影响。【原文：U.S. prices are up and economic activity and employment have changed little since March across most of the nation, the Federal Reserve said on Wednesday in a report that captures some of the early fallout from U.S. President Donald Trump's erratic rollout of sweeping tariffs aimed at reshaping global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economic-activity-steady-recent-weeks-uncertainty-pervasive-fed-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W67OLFFURFNETBL7TM3BGE5XZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥 Banorte 公司再次权衡收购 Banamex 公司事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥银行 Banorte 的首席执行官周三告诉分析师，Banorte 将再次考虑收购 Banamex。【原文：Mexican lender Banorte will again consider a potential purchase of Banamex, Citi's one-time retail unit in the country which it split off last year, Banorte's CEO told analysts on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mexicos-banorte-once-again-weighs-banamex-purchase-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BORY7SG3WVIFXIXFEJEUZN6MYE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:55:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，马斯克的 Neuralink 公司估值可达 85 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克的大脑植入公司 Neuralink 计划以 85 亿美元的投前估值融资约 5 亿美元。【原文：Elon Musk's brain implant company Neuralink is planning to raise about $500 million at a pre-money valuation of $8.5 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-neuralink-could-fetch-85-billion-valuation-bloomberg-reports-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MAQFINEMJPCBCIXRXDEGJ4IDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢旺达称正与美国就可能的矿产交易进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[卢旺达周三表示，它正在与美国就潜在的矿产交易进行谈判，这是继华盛顿与卢旺达的邻国刚果民主共和国正在进行类似谈判之后的又一进展。【原文：Rwanda said on Wednesday it was in talks with the U.S. over a potential minerals deal, a development that follows similar ongoing talks between Washington and Rwanda's neighbour Democratic Republic of Congo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/rwanda-says-it-talks-with-us-possible-minerals-deal-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7UKFTHHDBMV7H7PWH2VCEH7TI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:50:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称中国关税不可持续，美国释放缓和信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，美国和中国之间的高关税是不可持续的，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府对缓和世界两大经济体之间的贸易战持开放态度，这场贸易战已引发了对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that high tariffs between the United States and China are not sustainable, as President Donald Trump's administration signaled openness to de-escalating a trade war between the world's two largest economies that has raised fears of recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-china-tariffs-are-not-sustainable-us-signals-willingness-de-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNOS264ZPVITVEIUKLUCQTJI6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:39:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>