<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:46:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:46:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[油价下跌，因特朗普缓解伊朗担忧；亚洲科技股走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，油价从数月高点回落，避险资产黄金也从历史峰值回落，此前美国总统特朗普缓解了市场对美国可能对伊朗采取军事行动的担忧。【原文：Oil prices retreated from multi-month highs on Thursday and safe-haven gold ​eased back from a record peak after U.S. President Donald Trump calmed market anxiety about potential U.S. military ‌action against Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOL77U4YEVJYNC7K6M4MPWKGLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴升级Qwen应用，支持订餐与旅行预订]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴周四对其Qwen人工智能应用进行了重大升级，称该应用现可执行订餐、预订旅行等任务，标志着其正更积极地进军面向消费者的AI领域。【原文：Alibaba on Thursday launched significant upgrades to its Qwen artificial intelligence app, saying it could now execute tasks such as order food delivery and make travel bookings as it more aggressively pushes into consumer-facing AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/alibaba-upgrades-qwen-app-order-food-book-travel-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VE3VDWQZFVMLPHYFPQYJFGE4GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元汇率持稳，交易员为大选做准备，干预担忧隐现]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四日元维持隔夜涨幅，但仍徘徊在18个月低点附近。因日本大选前强硬警告可能引发更多财政刺激，令交易员对干预保持警惕，日元汇率持续承压。【原文：The yen held onto overnight gains on Thursday but was pinned near 18-month lows as traders remained wary of intervention after strong warnings ahead of an election in Japan that could usher in more fiscal stimulus and keep the currency constrained.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-steadies-traders-gird-election-intervention-fears-lurk-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AINA2ET2CBLEXHCBCJ4ALGVRCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:38:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普总统接受路透社采访的精彩片段]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三在椭圆形办公室接受了路透社的专访。以下是部分关键引语：【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump sat for an interview with Reuters in the Oval Office on Wednesday. Here are some key quotes:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/key-quotes-president-trumps-interview-with-reuters-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7E3OEBAEVML7GKYDLRY3VI4DI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普支持委内瑞拉留在欧佩克]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，他认为委内瑞拉留在石油输出国组织（OPEC）会更好，但补充说他不确定这对美国是否更有利。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Wednesday that he believes it would be better for Venezuela to remain in the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries, or OPEC, but added he was unsure if that would be a better situation for the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-backs-venezuela-staying-opec-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KBZS3ZBBRJH7CUEHHBTF7TZ4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase首席执行官阿姆斯特朗表示，公司无法支持当前形式的加密货币法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase首席执行官兼联合创始人布莱恩·阿姆斯特朗周三表示，该公司无法支持美国参议员本周早些时候提出的一项立法草案，该草案旨在为加密货币建立监管框架。【原文：Coinbase CEO and co-founder Brian Armstrong said on Wednesday the company cannot support a draft legislation U.S. senators introduced earlier this week aimed at creating a regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/coinbase-cannot-support-crypto-bill-current-form-ceo-armstrong-says-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R57CSD5KA5JVNNHUK6D2KKGATA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称无意解雇美联储主席鲍威尔，尽管存在调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，尽管司法部对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔展开刑事调查，但他目前没有解雇鲍威尔的计划，但称现在说他最终会采取什么行动还"为时过早"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Wednesday he has no plans to fire Jerome Powell despite a Justice Department criminal investigation into the Federal Reserve chair, but it was "too early" to say what he would ultimately do.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-has-no-plan-fire-feds-powell-despite-investigation-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEFJSJRD4ZIZ5G5SFSELAIXBUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚银称全球贸易紧张局势加剧，贸易融资缺口达2.5万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲开发银行最新调查显示，全球金融机构去年未能满足企业贸易所需的2.5万亿美元融资需求，拖累了全球经济增长。【原文：Financial institutions globally failed to meet $2.5 trillion in financing that companies needed for trade last year, holding back the global economy, according to a new survey by the Asian Development Bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/global-trade-finance-gap-25-trillion-global-trade-tensions-rise-adb-says-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLMWIEASLNMZRHJU6KYHU5ARAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音就737 MAX坠机相关诉讼达成初步和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司已与一名加拿大男子达成初步和解协议，该男子在2019年埃塞俄比亚航空737 MAX客机起飞后不久的坠机事故中失去了六位亲人。【原文：Boeing has reached tentative settlements with a Canadian man who lost six relatives in the 2019 crash of an Ethiopian Air 737 MAX jet shortly after takeoff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-reaches-tentative-settlements-related-737-max-crash-lawsuits-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HYDUBHWARPHTH7JIIOCINXRMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特敦促日本央行采取"稳健"政策以应对过度外汇波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三发表声明称，财政部长斯科特·贝森特周一与日本财务大臣片山萨茨基会晤时，"强调了审慎制定和沟通货币政策的必要性"。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent met Japanese Finance Minister Satsuki Katayama on Monday and "emphasized the need for sound formulation and communication of monetary policy," the U.S. Treasury Department said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bessent-urges-sound-boj-policy-address-excess-fx-volatility-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTUFTV7PRJM7RDMOXUHBJVKLVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:44:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌表示，美国输电系统是连接数据中心面临的最大挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌一名能源高管周三表示，接入美国输电系统已成为该公司在电网中为数据中心供电面临的最大难题，因为在某些地区，接入等待时间已激增至十多年。【原文：Connecting to the U.S. electrical transmission system has become the biggest problem for powering up Google data centers on the grid, as the wait times to connect surge to more than a decade in some parts of the country, an energy executive with Google said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-says-us-transmission-system-is-biggest-challenge-connecting-data-centers-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZOH3YBHCVO45BMPSOLCQT2NJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:40:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国油价下跌逾1美元，特朗普言论缓解对伊朗的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四亚洲早盘交易时段，美国油价下跌逾1美元。此前美国总统特朗普表示，伊朗镇压全国抗议活动中的杀戮行为正在减少，这缓解了市场对供应中断及可能对伊朗采取军事行动的担忧。【原文：U.S. oil prices fell more than $1 in early Asian trade on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said killings in Iran's crackdown on nationwide protests were subsiding, easing fears of supply disruptions and possible military action against Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-prices-dip-more-than-1-trump-remarks-reduce-fears-about-iran-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7NSJ3NXXRPEJKCG3BRHX2YCI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称暂不征收关键矿产关税，将寻求海外供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，他目前决定暂不对稀土、锂等关键矿产征收关税，转而要求政府寻求从国际贸易伙伴处获取供应。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Wednesday he had opted for now against imposing tariffs on rare earths, lithium and other critical minerals, and instead ordered his administration to seek supplies from international trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-no-critical-minerals-tariffs-now-will-seek-overseas-supplies-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SO5XTWPYRIWBPELI4OIZDYV4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:25:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻报道称，Temporal正就将估值翻倍至50亿美元进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[软件初创企业Temporal Technologies正就新一轮融资进行深入谈判，估值达50亿美元，较三个月前融资时的估值翻倍。彭博社周三援引知情人士消息报道称。【原文：Software startup Temporal Technologies is in advanced talks ​to raise fresh capital ‌at a $5 billion valuation, double of what it was valued at in a financing three ‌months ago, Bloomberg News reported ​on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/temporal-talks-double-valuation-5-billion-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ESOMAHVC7BKOXGJ4MQU4DEMTBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第四季度利润有望大幅增长，得益于人工智能热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的人工智能芯片制造商台积电预计，受人工智能基础设施需求持续强劲推动，其第四季度净利润将跃升28%，创下历史新高。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest manufacturer of advanced artificial intelligence chips, is expected to post a 28% jump in fourth-quarter net profit to a record high on Thursday driven by ongoing strong demand for AI infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-profit-leap-driven-by-ai-boom-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W76TAPLVWVMBTBL2VAXVUZJ7VQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：SK海力士加速新芯片厂投产以满足内存需求，高管称]]></title><description><![CDATA[SK海力士高管表示，由于内存需求激增导致全球供应紧张，该公司计划将新工厂的投产时间提前三个月，并将于2月启动另一座新工厂的运营。【原文：SK Hynix plans to accelerate the opening of a new factory by three months and will also begin operating another new plant in February, a senior executive said, as surging memory demand pressures global supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/sk-hynix-speeds-up-new-chip-fab-opening-meet-memory-demand-executive-says-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DB6P7N6VYFJGDPKCFGEGN5EWMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：实物资产创下新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，围绕伊朗与美国的地缘政治紧张局势持续升温，笼罩全球市场。尽管美国零售销售数据表现强劲，但该局势仍令华尔街股市下挫，推高油价，并使黄金及其他金属价格创下新高。【原文：Rising geopolitical tensions centering on Iran and the U.S. loomed large over world markets on Wednesday, overshadowing strong U.S. retail sales figures to push Wall Street lower, lift oil prices and send gold and other metals prices to new highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQENDR444ZISXPLHMPE2W7OBAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜克能源旗下公司将提前一个月取消客户账单中的风暴恢复费]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公用事业公司杜克能源旗下佛罗里达分公司周三表示，风暴损失回收费将比原计划提前一个月从客户账单中移除。【原文：U.S.-based utility Duke Energy's Florida unit said on Wednesday that the storm cost recovery charge would be removed from customer bills a month earlier than originally scheduled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/duke-energy-unit-drop-storm-recovery-charge-customer-bills-month-early-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2BWXAYYVJPUBKXMIFB7TZC6I4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:59:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对部分先进计算芯片进口征收25%关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据白宫发布的简报显示，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三对某些先进计算芯片征收25%的关税，包括英伟达H200人工智能处理器以及AMD公司名为MI325X的类似半导体产品。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday imposed a 25% tariff on certain advanced computing chips, such as the Nvidia H200 AI processor and a similar semiconductor from AMD called the MI325X, according to a fact sheet released by the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-imposes-25-tariff-imports-some-advanced-computing-chips-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5FWJKAEDVKQBIS7ZHZMCLKBC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:40:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院共和党人推进法案限制议员股票交易，民主党人则寻求更严格管控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院共和党人周三推进立法，对议员股票交易行为实施新限制。此前他们否决了民主党人提出的全面禁令提案——批评者指责这种普遍存在的交易行为利用了内幕信息。【原文：Republicans in the ​U.S. House of Representatives on Wednesday advanced legislation placing new restrictions on lawmakers' ‌stock-trading practices, after they squashed Democrats' push for an outright ban on the widespread practice that critics say takes advantage of insider information.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-house-republicans-advance-bill-curtail-lawmaker-stock-trades-democrats-seek-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEEMNHMLZZMZDOCJ57AGGIOJJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼任命阿萨德·阿亚兹为首席营销官，负责管理新成立的集团级营销部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼公司周三任命阿萨德·阿亚兹为首席营销官，他将负责管理新设立的跨公司营销组织。【原文：Walt Disney Wednesday named Asad Ayaz chief marketing officer, where he will oversee a newly created company-wide marketing organization.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/disney-names-asad-ayaz-chief-marketing-officer-overseeing-new-company-wide-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BACGZD2FJLP3HCKBS5SMXWY2M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国允许就卢克石油海外资产问题进行谈判，截止日期为2月28日]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三将相关许可延长了一个多月——直至2月28日——允许企业与俄罗斯能源公司卢克石油就收购其海外资产进行洽谈。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department on Wednesday extended a license by more than a month - until February 28 - for companies to talk with Russian energy company Lukoil about buying its foreign assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-allows-talks-over-lukoils-foreign-assets-until-february-28-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATC5VOWUYNIWNESRXRTJI562LI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:17:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙任命丹尼斯·西内利为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙天空舞影业周三宣布任命丹尼斯·西内利为首席财务官，自1月15日起生效，接替临时首席财务官安德鲁·沃伦。【原文：Paramount Skydance on Wednesday named Dennis Cinelli as its chief financial officer, effective January 15, replacing interim CFO Andrew Warren.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-names-dennis-cinelli-cfo-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4P5QFLXHWFJHBIDNHCTJU2LMQ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:14:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024年美国医疗支出飙升至逾5万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国医疗保健支出在2024年增长7.2%，从2023年的4.9万亿美元增至5.3万亿美元。美国联邦医疗保险和医疗补助服务中心周三表示，这一增长主要源于医疗保险参保人数增加以及医疗服务使用量激增，尤其体现在私人医疗保险计划中。【原文：U.S. healthcare spending rose by 7.2% to $5.3 trillion in 2024 from $4.9 trillion in 2023, driven by increased health insurance enrollment and a jump in use of medical services, particularly in private health insurance plans, the U.S. Centers for Medicare & Medicaid Services said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-healthcare-spending-soars-over-5-trillion-2024-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5EEBLIK3J5MW5A2X4CWHZYP64A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员称，美国完成首批价值5亿美元的委内瑞拉石油销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国官员周三向路透社透露，美国已完成首批委内瑞拉石油销售，这是本月早些时候加拉加斯与华盛顿达成的20亿美元协议的一部分。【原文：The U.S. has completed the first sales of Venezuelan oil that are part of a $2 billion deal reached earlier this month between Caracas and Washington, a U.S. official told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-completes-first-venezuelan-oil-sales-valued-500-million-us-official-says-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VEJN3CLCNIGDP7VLELTBP553M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储交易台计划下月进行逾550亿美元的购债操作]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周三发布的操作日程显示，其操作台计划于1月15日至2月12日期间实施约154亿美元的再投资购买操作，并额外进行约400亿美元的储备金管理购买操作。【原文：The New ​York Federal ‌Reserve's operations desk plans ‌to conduct about $15.4 ​billion in reinvestment ‍purchases and an additional ⁠approximately $40 ‍billion in reserve ‌management ‌purchases between January 15 ⁠and ⁠February ​12, it said in ‍a schedule released on ​Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/new-york-fed-desk-plans-conduct-purchases-worth-over-55-billion-over-next-month-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJUKVCQ37JIZBPKHKMBKKDAMFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:18:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球主要央行加速推进备受关注的跨境支付测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球多家顶尖央行及逾40家主要商业银行将加速推进一项备受瞩目的数字支付项目测试工作。随着各国竞相升级并争夺国际金融体系主导权的竞争日趋激烈，该项目正成为焦点。【原文：A group of the world's leading central banks and over 40 major commercial banks are to step up testing of one of world's most closely watched digital payments projects, as the race to upgrade - and dominate - the international financial architecture heats up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/top-central-banks-forge-ahead-with-closely-watched-cross-border-payments-testing-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQ2KRMZDP5LT7O3HPALWCTSXGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金表现强劲，推动华尔街主要经纪业务引擎大幅盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街大型银行去年见证了其主经纪业务部门的强劲增长，这些银行通过向全球最大的多策略对冲基金提供贷款赚取了丰厚手续费——这些基金在金融市场波动中稳健运作，创造了可观回报。【原文：Wall Street's largest banks witnessed healthy ​growth last year from their prime brokerage units, as they earned handsome fees from lending to the world's largest multi-strategy hedge funds ‌which navigated volatility in financial markets to produce robust returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/strong-year-hedge-funds-drives-big-gains-wall-streets-prime-brokerage-engine-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2IU6MC2PRP4FILYJZ3TSWVRUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:09:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，OpenAI将斥资约100亿美元向初创公司Cerebras购买计算能力。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，OpenAI已同意在三年内向Cerebras购买高达750兆瓦的计算能力，这笔交易价值超过100亿美元。【原文：OpenAI has agreed to purchase up to 750 megawatts of computing power over three years from Cerebras in a deal worth more than $10 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-buy-compute-capacity-startup-cerebras-around-10-billion-wsj-reports-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHSIBTKFKNLBXICSDMHAYMTGIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会称，波音公司于2011年针对MD-11飞机部件发布了服务通告。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会周三表示，去年11月在肯塔基州坠毁的UPS UPS.NMD-11货运飞机上发现裂纹的关键部件，正是2011年波音公司服务通告中提及的对象。该事故造成15人遇难。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board said on Wednesday that a key part of a UPS UPS.NMD-11 cargo jet that crashed in November in Kentucky, killing 15 people, that was found to have cracks was the subject of a 2011 Boeing service letter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ntsb-says-boeing-issued-service-advisory-2011-md-11-part-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3SFRP7TFRPBLOROLYP2GB5PEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>