<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:20:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:20:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙将在得克萨斯州裁员近 800 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙周三向德克萨斯州劳动力委员会（Texas Workforce Commission）发出通知，称将在德克萨斯州裁员近 800 人，这也是这家美国石油生产商计划在 2026 年底前裁减全球 20% 员工的一部分。【原文：Chevron will lay off nearly 800 employees in Texas, according to a notice on Wednesday to the Texas Workforce Commission, part of the U.S. oil producer's plan to cut up to 20% of its global workforce by the end of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/chevron-cut-nearly-800-jobs-texas-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BF2EKDQQFOMXF6VZHRPBIER5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院阻止特朗普征收 "解放日 "关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家联邦法院周三阻止了唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "解放日 "关税生效，裁定总统越权对来自向美国销售多于购买的国家的进口商品征收全面关税。【原文：A U.S. federal court on Wednesday blocked President Donald Trump's "Liberation Day" tariffs from going into effect, ruling that the president overstepped his authority by imposing across-the-board duties on imports from nations that sell more to the United States than they buy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-court-blocks-trumps-liberation-day-tariffs-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBDTXDVX4ZLBTCHVJUUBDOMHLE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，派拉蒙出价 1500 万美元和解哥伦比亚广播公司诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，派拉蒙全球公司与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普就解决他对哥伦比亚广播公司新闻（CBS News）的诉讼进行了一个月的谈判，但双方在条件上仍有很大分歧。【原文：A month into negotiations between Paramount Global and U.S. President Donald Trump to settle his lawsuit against CBS News, the parties remain far apart on terms, The Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/paramount-has-offered-15-million-settle-cbs-lawsuit-wsj-reports-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VM4JO3WEW5OCPCW34R7PJUARL4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kaiser Permanente 表示其网络正面临间歇性中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[医疗保健集团凯撒医疗集团（Kaiser Permanente）周三表示，该公司正面临间歇性网络中断，影响到其多个系统，包括电子健康记录和病人服务。【原文：Healthcare conglomerate Kaiser Permanente said on Wednesday it is facing intermittent network disruptions affecting several of its systems, including electronic health records and patient services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kaiser-permanente-says-it-is-facing-intermittent-network-disruptions-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXN4DHKVLFLN7HOCH6BL3XO5OA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国机器人出租车制造商进军热情洋溢的海湾地区，海外雄心日益壮大]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你是一家中国的机器人出租车公司，海湾地区已经成为你的首选之地，因为这里的监管环境正在接受这种技术，而且对乘车服务的需求也很旺盛。【原文：If you're a Chinese robotaxi company, the Gulf has become the place to be, attractive for a regulatory environment that is embracing the technology and robust demand for ride-hailing services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/chinese-robotaxi-makers-head-welcoming-gulf-overseas-ambitions-grow-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXPW4F4ZZNN23PQCHUXHVDNRG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会将要求 Synopsys 和 Ansys 剥离部分资产以解决合并问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周三表示，将要求两家软件公司（Synopsys 和 Ansys）剥离某些资产，以解决围绕其 350 亿美元合并案的反垄断问题。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Wednesday it will require two software companies —Synopsys and Ansys — to divest certain assets to resolve antitrust concerns surrounding their $35 billion merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-ftc-will-require-synopsys-ansys-divest-certain-assets-resolve-merger-concerns-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAW3R6WLGFPO7KVB6GF5QFXLMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[维多利亚的秘密因安全事件关闭网站]]></title><description><![CDATA[服装和内衣零售商维多利亚的秘密周三在其网站上发布声明称，为 "处理一起安全事件"，公司暂停了网站的大部分功能和部分店内服务。【原文：Clothing and lingerie retailer Victoria’s Secret suspended most of the functionality of its website and some in-store services to “address a security incident,” according to a statement posted to the company’s website on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/victorias-secret-pulls-down-website-amid-security-incident-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5OU2V7HQVN3JAQLWYDI7ZVCQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:16:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国取消对 Moderna 禽流感疫苗超过 7 亿美元的资助]]></title><description><![CDATA[该制药商周三宣布，特朗普政府已取消了授予 Moderna 公司用于人类禽流感疫苗后期开发的合同以及购买疫苗的权利。【原文：The Trump administration has canceled a contract awarded to Moderna for the late-stage development of its bird flu vaccine for humans, as well as the right to purchase shots, the drugmaker announced on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-cancels-more-700-million-funding-moderna-bird-flu-vaccine-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTY2M7LXKVNCXOU3Y4GIRC3AHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[象征日产崛起的工厂可能成为日产衰落的牺牲品]]></title><description><![CDATA[1961 年，日产汽车的 Oppama 工厂开业，它是日本最早的大型汽车工厂之一，也是该公司全球雄心的象征。64 年过去了，数以百万计的汽车从这里驶出，但随着日产汽车陷入更深的危机，这家充满传奇色彩的工厂现在面临着关闭的可能。【原文：When Nissan's Oppama plant opened in 1961, it was one of Japan's first large-scale auto factories and a symbol of the company's global ambitions. Sixty-four years and millions of cars later, the storied plant now faces possible closure as Nissan sinks deeper into crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/factory-that-symbolised-nissans-rise-may-become-victim-its-decline-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLZ2VMAO5ZNWLNEMTEHPWW6FCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[REX Financial 在财报发布前数小时推出备兑英伟达 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三上午，在 Nvidia 财报发布前几个小时，REX Financial 推出了与 Nvidia 相关的单一股票交易所交易基金，Nvidia 是一家强大的芯片制造商，在过去两年中主导了股市回报率。【原文：REX Financial launched a single-stock exchange-traded fund tied to Nvidia , the powerhouse chipmaker that has dominated stock market returns over the last two years, on Wednesday morning, hours ahead of the release of Nvidia's earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rex-financial-launches-covered-call-nvidia-etf-hours-before-earnings-release-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QKI5CGQXFMZRJYYXZOL2GMJG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：特朗普政府取消新诺华能源公司 30 亿美元贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周三援引住宅太阳能电池板安装商 Sunnova Energy 的消息报道称，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府已经取消了向该公司提供的高达 30 亿美元的贷款担保。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration has canceled an up to $3 billion loan guarantee that was awarded to residential solar panel installer Sunnova Energy, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-administration-cancels-sunnova-energy-3-billion-loan-bloomberg-news-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Z5IHT53DVNPHMHRW4HXBYLHAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:41:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党人沃伦对美国关税协议将有利于大科技公司而不利于工人表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）周三对特朗普政府的关税谈判将有利于大型科技公司而牺牲消费者和工人利益表示担忧。【原文：Democratic U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren on Wednesday expressed concern the Trump administration's tariff negotiations would favor big technology firms at the expense of consumers and workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/democrat-warren-raises-concerns-that-us-tariff-deals-will-favor-big-tech-over-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5XCJYTOIVVPG3HLF3Q7HEIY7UI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:23:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：投资者摆脱对英伟达的谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NCJA5S4LJKOHDFP5Y2BSAWKSU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[生命科学公司安捷伦因仪器需求超出季度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[安捷伦科技公司（Agilent Technologies）周三公布的第二季度利润和收入超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于市场对药物开发工具和设备的强劲需求，该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨了 5.1%。【原文：Agilent Technologies beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit and revenue on Wednesday, helped by strong demand for its tools and equipment used in drug development, sending its shares up 5.1% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/life-sciences-firm-agilent-beats-quarterly-estimates-instrument-demand-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PB7LWNWBU5K6VEP7W557QVMF34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特斯拉计划于 6 月 12 日在奥斯汀推出机器人出租车服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引一位知情人士的话报道，特斯拉准备于 6 月 12 日在奥斯汀开始提供期待已久的机器人出租车服务。【原文：Tesla is poised to begin its long-awaited robotaxi service in Austin on June 12, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-targets-june-12-launch-robotaxi-service-austin-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKC7PS4MFZNXJMLS32RP4FLWOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SentinelOne 下调年度收入预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[SentinelOne 周三下调了年度营收预期，表明企业在经济不确定的情况下支出谨慎，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌近 14%。【原文：SentinelOne trimmed its annual revenue forecast on Wednesday, signaling cautious spending by businesses amid economic uncertainty, sending its shares down nearly 14% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sentinelone-cuts-annual-revenue-forecast-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z73IMRBNK5MEVFHJV4TN5B3EFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达预测第二季度营收低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周三预测第二季度营收低于市场预期，预计美国收紧对主要半导体市场中国的人工智能芯片出口限制将对销售造成重大打击。【原文：Nvidia forecast second-quarter revenue below market estimates on Wednesday, expecting a major hit to sales from tighter U.S. curbs on exports of its AI chips to key semiconductor market China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-forecasts-second-quarter-revenue-below-estimates-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7F4GTFKL5JRHLGYLH5RCAHVXY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:24:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠普下调年度利润预期，因关税拖累需求，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠普公司周三下调了年度利润预期，原因是该公司预计在全球经济环境持续动荡的情况下，个人电脑市场的增长速度将有所放缓，从而导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌了 14%。【原文：HP Inc cut its annual profit forecast on Wednesday as it expects a moderation in PC market growth at a time when the global economic environment remains volatile, sending its shares down 14% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hp-cuts-annual-profit-forecast-tariffs-weigh-demand-shares-fall-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2SV27TCLVI6NKBNVWDQMWUZIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:21:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Synopsys 预测季度收入大幅高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[新思科技（Synopsys）周三预测，随着企业加大对人工智能芯片的投入，对其半导体设计软件的需求强劲，第三季度营收将大幅高于华尔街预期。【原文：Synopsys forecast third-quarter revenue largely above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, driven by strong demand for its semiconductor design software, as companies ramp up spending on AI chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/synopsys-forecasts-quarterly-revenue-largely-above-estimates-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKNZ3V7Z7BKYNOWD3FNOZNDP5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海莉-比伯（Hailey Bieber）以 10 亿美元的价格将彩妆品牌 Rhode 出售给 Elf Beauty]]></title><description><![CDATA[名模海莉-比伯（Hailey Bieber）的彩妆和护肤品牌 Rhode 将以约 10 亿美元的价格被 Elf Beauty 收购，从而使这家经济型化妆品零售商获得在 Z 世代和千禧一代中大受欢迎的明星代言产品系列。【原文：Model Hailey Bieber's makeup and skincare brand, Rhode, is being snapped up by Elf Beauty for about $1 billion, giving the budget cosmetic retailer access to a celebrity-endorsed product line that has become hugely popular among Gen Z and millennials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hailey-bieber-sells-makeup-brand-rhode-elf-beauty-1-billion-deal-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFIQ4WQF7ZPVVECL2MRDS5GM4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[云计算支出强劲，Salesforce上调年度业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Salesforce 周三上调了 2026 财年的营收和调整后利润预期，原因是这家企业软件供应商受益于强劲的云计算支出，同时加大了人工智能代理的货币化力度。【原文：Salesforce raised its revenue and adjusted profit forecast for fiscal 2026 on Wednesday, as the enterprise software provider benefits from strong cloud spending while ramping up monetization of its artificial intelligence agents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/salesforce-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRISSKKK2FOFNDWPAUX6XFZA7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:08:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，网络安全提供商 Netskope 选择摩根士丹利进行美国 IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，网络安全公司 Netskope 已聘请摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）牵头筹备在美国的首次公开募股，募集资金可能超过 5 亿美元。【原文：Cybersecurity firm Netskope has hired Morgan Stanley to lead preparations for a U.S. initial public offering that could raise more than $500 million, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cybersecurity-provider-netskope-taps-morgan-stanley-us-ipo-sources-say-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUWATU2JBVPATDEF4N5XRN5JKA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:06:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，特朗普要求美国芯片设计商停止向中国出售芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周三援引几位熟悉此举的人士的话报道称，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府已下令提供半导体设计软件的美国公司停止向中国集团出售服务。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration has ordered U.S. firms that offer software used to design semiconductors to stop selling their services to Chinese groups, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday, citing several people familiar with the move.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-tells-us-chip-designers-stop-selling-china-ft-reports-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIHLRIZFP5LX7H5CYDOP5B4T2I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 19:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利称将对荷兰股息逃税调查提出抗辩]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）周三表示，将就荷兰检察官对荷兰股票股息逃税的调查提出抗辩。【原文：Morgan Stanley said on Wednesday it will contest a Dutch public prosecutor's investigation into tax evasion related to dividends on Dutch shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/morgan-stanley-says-it-will-contest-dutch-dividend-tax-evasion-probe-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3FWLFONZNNVZIELKF5FZIZE5E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 经销商将美国扭亏为盈的希望寄托在新任首席执行官身上]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉普 SUV 和公羊皮卡的美国经销商寄希望于斯泰兰特新任首席执行官安东尼奥-费罗萨（Antonio Filosa）扭转数月来令人失望的销售业绩和信任度下降的局面。【原文：U.S. dealers of Jeep SUVs and Ram pickup trucks are pinning their hopes on new Stellantis CEO Antonio Filosa to turn around months of disappointing sales and weakening trust.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/stellantis-dealers-pin-us-turnaround-hopes-new-ceo-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5PUPF3M4ZIR5EN4KHLIIUBFYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[万斯称美国应利用比特币作为与中国竞争的优势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国副总统万斯（JD Vance）周三表示，中国对比特币的警惕应鼓励美国拥抱这种世界上最大的加密货币，并巩固其在数字资产领域的战略优势。【原文：China's wariness of bitcoin should encourage the U.S. to embrace the world's largest cryptocurrency and build on its strategic advantage in the digital asset, U.S. Vice President JD Vance said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/vance-says-us-should-use-bitcoin-an-advantage-rivalry-with-china-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRRXSPFH35IQJEGGWYCG3DLZF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:15:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD 收购 Enosemi 以提升共同封装光学产品的性能]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商先进微器件公司（Advanced Micro Devices）周三表示，它已收购了光子集成电路制造商伊诺塞米公司（Enosemi），以扩大其在人工智能系统中的联合封装光学产品。【原文：Chipmaker Advanced Micro Devices said on Wednesday it has acquired Enosemi, a builder of photonic integrated circuits, to expand its co-packaged optics offerings across AI systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/amd-buys-enosemi-boost-co-packaged-optics-offerings-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUGBTPERPZPB7MVECFQ3VYL4SM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称纽瓦克空中交通运营在削减航班后有所改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）周三表示，纽瓦克机场是服务纽约市的主要机场之一，在联邦政府实施航班削减之后，该机场的运营情况已得到明显改善。【原文：Operations at Newark, one of the main airports serving New York City, have improved significantly after the federal government imposed flight cuts following a series of major disruptions, U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/newark-air-traffic-operations-improving-with-flight-cuts-us-says-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRL35RK4YJKSFNRS2Y27ZT6UMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储会议纪要认为 5 月会议后通胀和失业风险上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据最新公布的 5 月 6-7 日会议纪要，美国联邦储备委员会官员在上次会议上承认，他们在未来几个月可能面临 "艰难的权衡"，即通胀上升与失业率上升并存。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve officials at their last meeting acknowledged they could face "difficult tradeoffs" in coming months in the form of rising inflation alongside rising unemployment, an outlook buttressed by Fed staff projections of increased risks of a recession, according to newly released minutes of the May 6-7 session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-minutes-saw-rising-inflation-jobless-risks-may-meeting-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">422LEF2VAFMVBBO5JEDFEFHVCA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，雪佛龙公司终止合同，但将保留在委内瑞拉的员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司已经终止了在委内瑞拉的石油生产、服务和采购合同，将合资企业的管理权下放给其合作伙伴--国营公司 PDVSA，但该公司计划保留在委内瑞拉的直属员工，四位接近该决定的消息人士说。【原文：Chevron has terminated the oil production, service and procurement contracts it had to operate in Venezuela, delegating its joint-venture governance to its partner, state company PDVSA, but it plans to retain its direct staff in the country, four sources close to the decisions said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/chevron-terminates-contracts-will-keep-staff-venezuela-sources-say-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTVW5HLQLZKIPL6MPAXQ7FGJVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>