<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:06:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:05:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特出任美国财政部部长的提名获得参议院财政委员会通过]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院财政委员会周二投票决定将亿万富翁、对冲基金经理斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）担任唐纳德-特朗普总统财政部长的提名提交参议院全会批准。【原文：The U.S. Senate Finance Committee on Tuesday voted to send the nomination of billionaire hedge fund manager Scott Bessent as President Donald Trump's Treasury secretary on to the full Senate for approval.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-nomination-us-treasury-clears-senate-finance-committee-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J3QYI7O5JRLD7PKN72DMOJG6WI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济学家将巴西利率预测上调至 15%以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家对巴西今年的利率预测进行了新一轮的上调，理由是通胀预期恶化、货币疲软以及对拉美最大经济体财政前景的担忧挥之不去。【原文：Economists have launched a fresh wave of upward revisions to projections for Brazil's interest rate this year, citing deteriorating inflation expectations, a weaker currency and lingering concerns over the fiscal outlook of Latin America's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/economists-ramp-up-projections-brazils-interest-rates-above-15-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6HB7TVGAFL7PG7MJ572KFU74M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[仓库需求改善，Prologis 核心财务和利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产投资信托公司（REIT）Prologis 第四季度核心运营资金（FFO）超出华尔街预期，主要得益于仓储空间需求的增长和一个数据中心的出售。【原文：Real estate investment trust (REIT) Prologis beat Wall Street expectations for fourth-quarter core funds from operations (FFO), helped by improving demand for its warehousing spaces and sale of a data center.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/prologis-beats-core-ffo-estimates-improving-warehouse-demand-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7E7GDRKMROPXI3FWRWSPCMOQQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：特朗普对欧盟贸易逆差的抱怨以及接下来可能发生的事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普
 他承诺要解决与欧盟长期存在的贸易逆差问题，并表示将通过征收关税或让欧盟购买更多美国石油和天然气来扭转这一局面。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump
 has promised to address a longstanding trade deficit with the European Union, saying he will reverse that by imposing tariffs or making the EU buy more U.S. oil and gas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-complaints-about-trade-deficit-with-eu-what-may-come-next-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EN3PZEX5CFPZXK4L45GQZCRWII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威银行在空气产品公司董事会之争中投票支持激进分子的四名候选人]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威主权财富基金是空气化工产品公司的 10 大投资者之一，该基金表示将投票支持激进投资者 Mantle Ridge 的所有四名董事候选人加入这家工业气体公司的董事会。【原文：Norway's sovereign wealth fund, one of Air Products and Chemicals' 10 biggest investors, said it will vote for all four of activist investor Mantle Ridge's director candidates to join the industrial gases company's board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/norges-bank-votes-activists-four-candidates-air-products-board-fight-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R33CWGXTKVMEJFJATOBYQOP5TE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金大举押注为特朗普第二任期拉开序幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行研究和行业数据显示，对冲基金为唐纳德-特朗普就任美国总统进行了自 2010 年以来最高水平的借贷，同时押注美元将继续上涨。【原文：Hedge funds positioned for Donald Trump's U.S. presidency with their highest levels of borrowing since 2010, while betting the dollar would continue to rise, according to bank research and industry data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-funds-ante-up-big-bets-kick-off-trumps-second-term-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRU4JCTG4RJ2BFWJQ2QPWOIMA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:17:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管特朗普推迟禁令，TikTok 应用程序在美国的苹果和谷歌商店仍无法使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普签署行政命令，将对中国流行短视频应用的禁令执行时间推迟 75 天之后，美国的苹果和谷歌应用商店仍然无法下载 TikTok。【原文：TikTok remained unavailable on Apple and Google app stores in the U.S. on Tuesday, a day after President Donald Trump signed an executive order delaying the enforcement of a ban on the popular Chinese-owned short-video app by 75 days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-app-unavailable-apple-google-stores-us-despite-trump-delaying-ban-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXJZVAAGA5OT3F3JINPXEQOFD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度尼西亚对谷歌不公平商业行为罚款 1200 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚反垄断机构周二勒令谷歌支付约2,020亿印尼盾（合1,237万美元）的罚款，原因是谷歌为其软件分发平台Google Play Store提供的支付系统服务存在不公平商业行为。【原文：Indonesia's antitrust agency on Tuesday ordered Google to pay fines about 202 billion rupiah ($12.37 million) for unfair business practices related to its payment system services for Google Play Store, its software distribution platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indonesia-fines-google-12-million-unfair-business-practices-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6RWNNVKRZPSTGLPFQX3P2ZLSQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISS 的 Guerra 将离开代理咨询公司，加入战略治理顾问公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，克里斯蒂亚诺-格拉（Cristiano Guerra）作为机构股东服务公司（Institutional Shareholder Services）的特殊情况研究主管，在决定美国一些竞争最激烈的董事会斗争的结果方面发挥了重要作用。【原文：Cristiano Guerra, who has been instrumental in determining the outcome of some of the America's most hotly contested board battles as head of special situations research at Institutional Shareholder Services, is leaving the proxy advisory firm, sources familiar with the move told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/iss-guerra-leave-proxy-advisory-firm-join-strategic-governance-advisors-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HAH6RLMK5BJQFAIQQEVRRDRD2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，欧盟将批准国际纸业以 71 亿美元收购 DS Smith 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据直接知情人士周二透露，总部位于美国的国际纸业公司（International Paper）在同意出售资产以解决竞争问题后，将获得欧盟批准，以 58 亿英镑（71.2 亿美元）收购英国竞争对手 DS Smith。【原文：U.S.-based International Paper is set to receive EU approval for its 5.8 billion pound ($7.12 billion) acquisition of UK rival DS Smith after agreeing to sell assets to address competition concerns, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/eu-approve-international-papers-71-billion-ds-smith-deal-sources-say-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2AI24O2DVJTFGH5JLOP4G62WQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:18:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Enverus 表示，随着交易规模缩小，2025 年美国能源并购可能放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[据能源分析公司 Enverus 周二发布的一份报告称，2025 年美国上游公有企业对公有企业的兼并速度可能会从最近的平均每年五起放缓，同时交易规模也会下降。【原文：The pace of U.S. upstream public-to-public mergers could slow in 2025 from their recent average of five per year along with a fall in deal sizes, according to a report from energy analytics firm Enverus that was released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-energy-mergers-may-slow-2025-deal-sizes-shrink-says-enverus-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K63I33HIRFOBVKQY3J7SGBVSGQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lonestar 的登月计划：公司计划在月球表面建立数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[隆斯塔数据控股公司（Lonestar Data Holdings）正在向月球进发，试图在月球上建立第一个物理数据中心。【原文：Lonestar Data Holdings is reaching for the moon in its quest to place the first physical data center on the lunar landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/lonestars-moonshot-firm-aims-place-data-center-lunar-surface-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CF6DPOUV4VPJBF7S7FZ74VE7KE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛调整管理层以加强华尔街业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）周二表示，将选拔一批高管领导其最重要的华尔街业务。【原文：Goldman Sachs is tapping a slew of executives to lead its most important Wall Street businesses, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-shuffles-management-strengthen-wall-street-business-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJXZUEJFU5LLHLSS7CCQ5SVVHU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官表示，气候转变将帮助 StanChart 增加近 10 亿美元的收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行首席执行官比尔-温特斯（Bill Winters）在达沃斯世界经济论坛上对高管们说，渣打银行将在 2025 年从帮助客户实现可持续发展目标的业务中获得近 10 亿美元的收入，同时他将加倍支持净零议程。【原文：Standard Chartered is set to book almost $1 billion in income in 2025 from business geared towards helping clients meet sustainability goals, CEO Bill Winters told executives at the World Economic Forum in Davos, as he doubled down on supporting the net-zero agenda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/climate-shift-help-boost-stanchart-income-by-almost-1-billion-ceo-says-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCGJM6NZJFI4LDYQ3HRXOUHOJA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉信理财第四季度利润因资产管理费增加而飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[经纪公司嘉信理财（Charles Schwab）周二表示，受资产管理费飙升的推动，该公司第四季度利润增长了 44%，股价在盘前交易中上涨超过 6%。【原文：Brokerage firm Charles Schwab said on Tuesday that its profit rose 44% in the fourth quarter driven by a jump in asset management fees, sending its shares up more than 6% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/charles-schwabs-fourth-quarter-profit-soars-higher-asset-management-fees-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SECW7TMRNKCHDORMAX6EM6ABI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:45:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌将 SandboxAQ 的定量人工智能模型添加到云产品中]]></title><description><![CDATA[量子初创公司SandboxAQ周二告诉路透社记者，该公司的大型定量模型（LQMs）将在谷歌云上提供，因为云提供商希望通过人工智能技术来促进增长。【原文：Quantum startup SandboxAQ said its large quantitative models (LQMs) will be available on Google Cloud, the company told Reuters on Tuesday, as cloud providers look to AI tech to fuel growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/google-adds-sandboxaqs-quantitative-ai-models-cloud-offerings-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DH4ZQJT5MVLEZCB3RXGLWMCVFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:37:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：工会能否阻止特朗普解雇数千名联邦雇员？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统在周一上任后数小时内就签署了一项命令，使解雇数千名联邦机构雇员并用政治忠诚者取而代之变得更加容易。这项命令与特朗普在第一任期末发布的命令基本相同，目前已面临一个主要工会的诉讼，并可能引发更多的法律挑战。【原文：President Donald Trump signed an order within hours of taking office on Monday to make it easier to fire thousands of federal agency employees and replace them with political loyalists. The order, which is largely identical to one Trump issued late in his first term, is already facing a lawsuit by a major union and is likely to trigger more legal challenges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/can-unions-stop-trump-firing-thousands-federal-employees-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJSZAVI7SJMSBAPT62C63W3AJE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金行业要求 "第一天 "暂停执行美国证券交易委员会规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金行业的游说者向美国证券交易委员会（SEC）递交了一份愿望清单，要求撤销或推迟监管机构关于行业透明度的严厉议程。【原文：Hedge fund industry lobbyists have sent a wish list to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) asking for repeals and delays to much of the regulator's hard-hitting agenda on industry transparency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-fund-industry-asks-day-one-reprieve-sec-rules-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXYLVWP76ROFXD5I5VISIMFBSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:32:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因手续费收入增加，第五第三银行集团季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，第五第三银行公司（Fifth Third Bancorp）报告称，受整个行业交易复苏以及财富和资产管理费用增加的推动，第四季度利润有所增长。【原文：Fifth Third Bancorp reported a rise in fourth-quarter profit on Tuesday, driven by a recovery in dealmaking across the industry and higher wealth and asset management fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fifth-third-bancorps-quarterly-profit-rises-fee-income-boost-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYQ5GOM6DZM23JHPRKEYEYK4QQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行首席执行官欢迎特朗普的经济政策，认为这对企业是 "好事]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行首席执行官布莱恩-莫伊尼汉（Brian Moynihan）周二对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普就职以来宣布的经济政策表示欢迎，认为这对企业来说是件 "好事"。【原文：Bank of America Chief Executive Brian Moynihan on Tuesday welcomed economic policies announced by U.S. President Donald Trump since his inauguration as a "good thing" for business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bofa-ceo-welcomes-trumps-economic-policies-good-thing-business-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEJZ5QNKBFNYPAT4SURTS74EQE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:49:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄牙 TAP 航空公司 2024 年客运量增长，美洲领衔增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[葡萄牙 TAP 航空公司周二表示，该公司计划进行私有化，去年在北美和巴西航线的带动下运送了 1610 万乘客，比 2023 年增长了 1.6%。【原文：Portugal's airline TAP, which is slated for privatisation, carried 16.1 million passengers last year, a 1.6% rise from 2023, led by North American and Brazilian routes, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/portuguese-airline-taps-passenger-traffic-up-2024-americas-lead-growth-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44VNC2SZJJN2DMORV6RNBZRJCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:45:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 首席执行官在达沃斯表示，特朗普对加密货币的影响不可否认，将吸引投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase 首席执行官在达沃斯世界经济论坛的一次小组讨论会上表示，唐纳德-特朗普连任美国总统后，将吸引大量投资进入加密货币领域。【原文：Donald Trump's second term as U.S. president will draw a lot of investment into crypto, the CEO of Coinbase told a panel discussion at the World Economic Forum in Davos.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-effect-crypto-undeniable-will-lure-investment-coinbase-ceo-says-davos-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3A456JE6VO4PAHZ5YBPHZ56YY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:32:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[D.R. Horton 第一季度业绩超出预期，原因是低住房供应量促进了新房需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，D.R. Horton 公司第一季度营收和利润均超出华尔街预期，原因是尽管抵押贷款利率上升，但美国住房市场上现房持续短缺，这有助于促进新房销售。【原文：D.R. Horton beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter revenue and profit on Tuesday as a persistent shortage of existing homes in the U.S. housing market helped boost new home sales despite higher mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dr-horton-beats-q1-estimates-low-housing-supply-boosts-new-home-demand-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFWHH5GTXJKBBAGQXW5IKO7HAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:31:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年中国非金融类对外直接投资同比增长 10.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周二表示，按美元计算，2024 年中国非金融类对外直接投资同比增长 10.5%，达到 1,439 亿美元。【原文：China's non-financial outbound direct investment rose 10.5% year-on-year in dollar terms in 2024 to $143.9 billion, the country's commerce ministry said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-2024-non-financial-outbound-direct-investment-rose-105-year-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VEIP5LHK5ITVPYRKTZHDQUUTE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:25:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普重返白宫：市场赢家和输家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫后，全球市场既感到欣慰，也感到失望，因为投资者正试图了解未来四年会带来什么。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's return to the White House has been met with both relief and disappointment across world markets as investors try to work out what the next four years will bring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trump-graphic-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPGVKMY7C5IUTDQL2CNGVFSS44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:20:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银首席执行官称考虑收购为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥-埃尔莫蒂（Sergio Ermotti）周二表示，该瑞士银行目前考虑收购的时机尚不成熟，因为它仍在专注于整合其于 2023 年收购的瑞士信贷。【原文：UBS Chief Executive Sergio Ermotti on Tuesday said it was currently premature for the Swiss bank to consider acquisitions as it continues to focus on the integration of Credit Suisse, which it bought in 2023.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-ceo-says-premature-consider-acquisitions-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIHWKLFBCVJ3TMQKHY3J6TWW7Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:19:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Birkenstock 首席财务官 Erik Massmann 将卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国鞋商 Birkenstock 周二表示，其首席财务官 Erik Massmann 将在任职近两年后卸任，由 Ivica Krolo 接替。【原文：German shoemaker Birkenstock said on Tuesday its Chief Financial Officer Erik Massmann will step down after nearly two years in the role, and will be succeeded by Ivica Krolo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/birkenstock-cfo-erik-massmann-step-down-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZU225ZKUZIARGW7Z4GEXFOWSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:15:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商称特朗普关税将损害美国消费者和汽车产业]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国强大的汽车行业周二警告说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税计划将意味着美国消费者的汽车价格上涨，并打击全球汽车制造商，汽车股也因美国提高进口关税的前景而下跌。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff plans would mean higher car prices for U.S. consumers and hit global automakers, Germany's powerful car industry warned on Tuesday, as auto stocks fell on the prospect of higher U.S. import duties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/german-carmakers-say-trump-tariffs-would-hurt-us-consumers-industry-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGNV2RCKCVJHPKNABP3JGE4PHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美敦力任命雷诺高管 Thierry Piéton 为财务总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[美敦力公司周二表示，将任命雷诺公司财务总监 Thierry Piéton 为公司首席财务官，3 月 3 日起生效。【原文：Medtronic said on Tuesday it will appoint Renault's finance chief Thierry Piéton as its chief financial officer, effective March 3.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/medtronic-appoints-renaults-exec-thierry-piton-finance-chief-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCML5HTNKJL3NNXN4ZXQEWB6LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:58:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[史密斯菲尔德食品公司美国首次公开募股目标估值高达 107 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[史密斯菲尔德食品公司（Smithfield Foods）周二表示，其美国首次公开募股的目标估值将高达 107.3 亿美元。【原文：Smithfield Foods is targeting a valuation of up to $10.73 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, the Farmland bacon maker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/smithfield-foods-targets-up-107-bln-valuation-us-ipo-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J46UZYQ6MFJMNPONA4I2VIVFPE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:46:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>