<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 19:04:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 19:04:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席戴利：现在是缓慢、谨慎地制定政策的时候了]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周二表示，在经济强劲、特朗普政府的新政策效果尚不明朗的情况下，央行不应急于调整利率。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly on Tuesday said with the economy strong and a lot still unclear on the effect of new policies of the Trump administration, the central bank should not rush to adjust interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-daly-theres-time-tread-slowly-carefully-policy-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGA2TCKPFZLZTGIAIN6ZMAWHLA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西监管机构授权星链公司为其本地运营增加 7,500 颗卫星]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西电信监管机构 Anatel 周二在一份声明中说，该监管机构授权埃隆-马斯克的 Starlink 公司增加 7500 颗新卫星，以便在这个拉美国家运营。【原文：Brazil's telecommunications regulator Anatel authorized Elon Musk's Starlink to add 7,500 new satellites to operate in the Latin American nation, the watchdog said in a statement on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/brazil-regulator-authorizes-starlink-add-7500-satellites-its-local-operation-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXW2QDS665JPTB35H6S3IX2BA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大称将从 4 月 9 日起对部分美国产汽车征收反关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大联邦财政部周二表示，加拿大上周表示将对部分美国制造的汽车征收25%的反关税，该反关税将于4月9日生效。【原文：The 25% counter-tariffsCanada said last week it would impose on some U.S.-made vehicles will go into effect on April 9, the federal finance ministry said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/canada-says-counter-tariffs-against-some-us-made-autos-will-start-april-9-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45JXKXTVIRKKLI76E5HT7ZALTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NRF 称，美国复活节消费将增长，因为节日的欢乐气氛与经济阴霾背道而驰]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国全国零售联合会周二发布的一份报告显示，尽管人们对高通胀和经济不确定性感到担忧，但由于美国人抢购糖果和礼物来庆祝复活节，预计今年美国复活节的消费支出将增长约5%。【原文：U.S. consumer spending for Easter is expected to rise about 5% this year as Americans snap up candy and gifts to celebrate despite concerns around high inflation and economic uncertainty, a National Retail Federation report showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-easter-spending-rise-holiday-cheer-defies-economic-gloom-nrf-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIQOS2TGIROOLEZYQWPHXMH6VY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员加大对美联储将于五月开始降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，交易员们加大了对美联储最快将于下月开始下调政策利率的押注，因为白宫表示，对从中国进口的商品征收的额外关税将于周三生效，贸易敌对行动进一步升级，可能会拖累经济。【原文：Traders boosted bets on Tuesday the Federal Reserve will start cutting its policy rate as soon as next month, as the White House said additional tariffs on imports from China will go into effect on Wednesday in a further escalation of trade hostilities that could slow the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-boost-bets-fed-will-start-cutting-rates-may-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4IX4BJMFRJTBCSSP5LLOWFSIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:59:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，在遭到反对后，美国考虑调整针对中国船只的港口费计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据六位消息人士透露，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑软化其对访问美国港口的与中国有联系的船只征收费用的提议，因为来自各行业的大量负面反馈称这一提议可能会造成经济破坏。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering softening its proposed fee on China-linked ships visiting U.S. ports after a flood of negative feedback from industries that said the idea could be economically devastating, according to six sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-considers-adjusting-port-fee-plan-chinese-vessels-after-pushback-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNO23GFFWZKA5NG64QMZWCIRDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表格里尔称，并非所有中国船舶收费都将实施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周二向立法者表示，美国贸易代表办公室提出的向停靠美国港口的中国船只征收数百万美元费用的建议并不会全部实施，而且这些费用可能不会累积。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer told lawmakers on Tuesday that not all of the agency's proposed multimillion-dollar fees for Chinese-built ships to dock at U.S. ports will be implemented, and they may not be cumulative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/not-all-chinese-ship-fees-will-be-implemented-ustr-greer-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGDDCXFWMNI4XHTH65ES3VEG6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社/益普索民意调查显示，73%的美国人预计特朗普关税将导致物价飞涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社/益普索（Reuters/Ipsos）的一项最新民意调查显示，在唐纳德-特朗普总统对来自世界大多数国家的进口商品征收全面新关税之后，大多数美国人都在为各种消费品的价格上涨做准备。【原文：Most Americans are bracing for higher prices on a wide range of consumer goods following President Donald Trump's move to impose sweeping new tariffs on imports from most of the world, a new Reuters/Ipsos poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/73-americans-expect-price-surge-under-trump-tariffs-reutersipsos-poll-finds-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGVG6ICNTBOSVOGWHCENQAMWZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司称美国新关税将增加喷气机的复杂性和成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）推出的关税措施将增加这家巴西喷气机制造商在美国的业务和客户的复杂性和成本。【原文：Embraer said on Tuesday that tariffs introduced by U.S. President Donald Trump would add complexity and costs for the Brazilian jet maker’s business and customers in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-says-new-us-tariffs-will-add-complexity-costs-jets-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24PUKUKOWRKKHH6JL7I7PIW2DU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表在关税范围和期限问题上面临两党质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周二告诉美国参议员们，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的政府没有计划在短期内改变全球关税计划的策略。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer told U.S. senators on Tuesday that President Donald Trump's administration has no plans to change tactics on the global tariff program in the near term, prompting some light push back from Republican lawmakers as Democrats excoriated the approach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-trade-rep-faces-bipartisan-questions-scope-duration-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2V7B2FR6FNKTBH3TFROKGF4FDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比："远超预期 "的关税构成通胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布的关税 "远远大于 "预期，目前尚不清楚这些较高的成本将如何迅速或全面地转嫁给消费者，也不清楚企业和消费者可能会在多大程度上做出缩手缩脚的反应，从而导致经济放缓。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee said on Tuesday that U.S. President Donald Trump's announced tariffs are "way bigger" than had been modeled, and it's unclear how quickly or fully those higher costs will be passed on to consumers and to what degree businesses and consumers may react by hunkering down, slowing the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-way-bigger-than-expected-tariffs-pose-inflation-risks-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKQWEC74NVJAZNRA5HMM7EBU3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟市场监督机构警告与加密货币相关的金融稳定风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟证券监管机构周二警告说，随着加密货币行业的发展以及该行业与传统金融市场之间联系的加强，加密货币行业的问题可能会在未来给更广泛的金融稳定带来风险。【原文：The European Union's securities watchdog warned on Tuesday that problems in the cryptocurrency industry could pose risks to broader financial stability in future, as the sector grows and as ties between it and traditional financial markets increase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-markets-watchdog-warns-crypto-related-financial-stability-risks-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDYARV3UT5M2VEQZEQWJ6T76TE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:24:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司下达后门命令后，两名美国议员敦促白宫终止英国数据条约]]></title><description><![CDATA[有报道称，英国命令苹果公司建立一个后门来访问加密的用户数据，两名美国议员周二致信唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府，敦促终止与英国的数据协议，并重新谈判一项新协议。【原文：Two U.S. lawmakers on Tuesday sent a letter to President Donald Trump's administration urging an end to a data agreement with the U.K. and to renegotiate a new one in the wake of reports that the U.K. ordered Apple to build a backdoor to access encrypted user data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/two-us-lawmakers-urge-white-house-end-uk-data-treaty-after-apple-backdoor-order-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VC2Y52YOK5LEFG5J2AARSIQNH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官称，Codelco 的目标是铜产量范围的上限，并计划重返债券市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利 Codelco 公司首席执行官鲁本-阿尔瓦拉多（Ruben Alvarado）周二表示，这家国营铜生产商的目标是使今年的产量达到预计范围的上限，预计将达到 139 万公吨。【原文：The CEO of Chile's Codelco, Ruben Alvarado, said on Tuesday that the state-run copper producer aims to bring output to the upper end of its estimated range this year, expecting to reach 1.39 million metric tons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/codelco-aims-upper-end-copper-output-range-plans-return-bond-market-ceo-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SIZPSGOADBOLDLTIUKYSTTPMHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立陶宛表示，作为贸易谈判的一部分，欧盟可汇总对美国天然气的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[立陶宛能源部长周二告诉路透社，作为与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）试图避免贸易战的谈判的一部分，欧盟可能会考虑汇总其成员国购买美国液化天然气的需求。【原文：The European Union could consider aggregating its member countries' demand to buy U.S. liquefied natural gas, as part of negotiations with President Donald Trump to try to avert a trade war, Lithuania's energy minister told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-could-aggregate-demand-us-gas-part-trade-talks-lithuania-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVDHO25KAZMYFBQVATVSTK5JQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的政策风险如何体现在国债上]]></title><description><![CDATA[自唐纳德-特朗普总统 1 月份上任以来，基准美国国债收益率大幅下降。但这一数字中蕴含的一个风险指标却一直保持正值，显示出投资者的紧张情绪。【原文：The yield on the benchmark U.S. Treasury bond has fallen dramatically since President Donald Trump took office in January. But one measure of risk embedded in that number has remained positive, in a sign of investor nervousness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/how-trumps-policy-risk-is-showing-treasury-bonds-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNTX7EPGKVIHTI5DPKSWQEP3ZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，台积电可能因美国调查面临 10 亿美元或更多罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，台湾中芯国际集成电路制造有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing）可能面临 10 亿美元或更多的罚款，以了结美国对其生产的一款芯片的出口管制调查。【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing could face a penalty of $1 billion or more to settle a U.S. export control investigation over a chip it made that ended up inside a Huawei AI processor, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-could-face-1-billion-or-more-fine-us-probe-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4USWWB5H5JYDBYBR53XPAXFEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街下滑为卖空者带来 1 270 亿美元收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据和分析公司 Ortex Technologies 的数据显示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税计划引发股市大幅下挫之后，从 4 月 2 日到本周一，针对美国公司的做空者已经获得了 1,270 亿美元的纸面收益。【原文：Short sellers targeting U.S. companies have gained $127 billion on paper from April 2 through Monday after President Donald Trump's plans for sweeping tariffs sparked a sharp selloff in stocks, according to data and analytics company Ortex Technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-slide-nets-short-sellers-127-billion-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ITBX3KVAZLGNCAOUK5GEJW4X4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总统表示，大多数汽车制造商将留在墨西哥]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆周二表示，大多数在墨西哥设厂的汽车企业高管都表示，到目前为止，他们还没有搬迁工厂的计划。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Tuesday that the majority of automobile executives with plants in Mexico have said that, as of now, they have no plans to move their factories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/most-automakers-stay-put-mexico-president-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYXQXGVVVFMDLOXAUM7ZD4G4RU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Boaz Weinstein 的 Saba Capital 出售英国信托公司 Keystone Positive Change 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一份监管文件显示，美国激进投资者 Boaz Weinstein 的 Saba Capital 已出售其在英国投资信托公司 Keystone Positive Change (KPC) 近 30% 的股份。【原文：U.S. activist investor Boaz Weinstein's Saba Capital has sold its nearly 30% stake in British investment trust Keystone Positive Change (KPC) , a regulatory filing showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/boaz-weinsteins-saba-capital-sells-stake-uk-trust-keystone-positive-change-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BH5NYBSBINJYNEBXPHVUTH5PMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰美洲证券融资主管在银行重组中离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士告诉路透社，汇丰银行美洲证券融资主管格雷戈里-布恩（Gregory Bunn）将在任职两年后离职，因为该银行将该部门并入另外两个部门。【原文：HSBC's head of securities financing for the Americas, Gregory Bunn, is leaving after two years in the post as the lender merges the unit into two others, a person with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-americas-head-securities-finance-leaves-amid-bank-restructuring-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VM2RBSSQRBLHRAYEJM2DDJMLUY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:26:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大油气公司首席执行官避免在价格下跌期间做出 "草率 "决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大两家石油和天然气生产商的首席执行官周二表示，在全球油价徘徊在四年低点、经济衰退担忧加剧之际，他们正努力避免做出草率的决定。【原文：The CEOs of two Canadian oil and gas producers said on Tuesday they are seeking to avoid making rash decisions, as global oil prices hover around four-year lows and recession fears grow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/canadian-oil-gas-ceos-avoiding-rash-decisions-during-price-rout-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNUNO5YYFFJ4LEDIPTTOAK4MKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:17:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司三月份交付量同比增长 41]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二宣布，3月份交付了41架喷气式飞机，高于去年同期的29架，但这一数字略低于1月份的45架和2月份的44架。【原文：Boeing delivered 41 jets in March, up from 29 during the same month a year ago, the company announced Tuesday, though the figure was slightly lower than the 45 handed over in January and 44 in February.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-deliveries-march-jump-by-41-compared-year-earlier-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57W62QCIEBNIDD6PH6FX5H6RMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 CFPB 要求撤销拜登时代针对速汇金的案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，美国消费者金融最高监管机构已要求联邦法院退出该机构自己对速汇金公司提起的 2022 年诉讼案，让纽约总检察长成为唯一的原告。【原文：The top U.S. watchdog for consumer finance has asked a federal court to withdraw from the agency's own 2022 case against MoneyGram, leaving the New York attorney general as the sole plaintiff, according to court papers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-cfpb-asks-exit-biden-era-case-against-moneygram-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBL6HLXR4VLOHAG46NTFKOXUII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲希望减轻初创企业的人工智能合规负担]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份欧盟委员会文件显示，欧盟委员会计划征求反馈意见，以帮助努力遵守欧盟人工智能使用规则的初创企业减轻监管负担。【原文：The European Commission plans to seek feedback to help lighten the regulatory burden for startups struggling to comply with European Union rules on the use of artificial intelligence, according to a Commission document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/europe-wants-lighten-ai-compliance-burden-startups-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4OLXVYUBVIZXNO3UWNRWDQOKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界黄金协会称第一季度黄金 ETF 流入量为三年来最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界黄金协会（WGC）周二公布的数据显示，2025年1月至3月，实物黄金交易所交易基金（ETF）创下三年来最大季度流入量。【原文：Physically backed gold exchange-traded funds (ETFs) registered the largest quarterly inflow in three years in January-March, 2025, data from the World Gold Council (WGC) showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-etfs-drew-largest-inflow-three-years-q1-says-wgc-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRES4R57WFIFHGAAQQXDXTQHFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）寻求募集 200 亿美元巨型基金，因为全球都在关注美国的人工智能初创企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，风险投资公司安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）正寻求筹集约200亿美元，这将是该公司历史上规模最大的基金，以利用全球投资者对支持美国人工智能公司的兴趣。【原文：Venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz is seeking to raise about $20 billion in what will be the largest fund in its history, to capitalize on global investors' interest in backing U.S. artificial intelligence companies, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/andreessen-horowitz-seeks-raise-20-billion-megafund-amid-global-interest-us-ai-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GCXGDBPARLL3P265AZGWBYYAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:33:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国主要贸易伙伴对特朗普关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对美国进口产品全面征收新关税，将矛头指向世界各国，这是对全球贸易体系几十年来最严重的打击。【原文：Donald Trump's sweeping new tariffs on U.S. imports have targeted countries across the world in the most serious blow to the global trading system in decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/how-top-us-trading-partners-have-reacted-trump-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLK6L66IZJNXDASAUCCFYKAYOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比尔-阿克曼呼吁暂停实施特朗普的关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[支持唐纳德-特朗普竞选总统的亿万富翁投资者比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）周二在社交媒体上发文称，美国应在贸易谈判期间推迟实施新的关税措施长达90天。【原文：The U.S. should delay implementing its new tariffs for up to 90 days while trade negotiations take place, billionaire investor Bill Ackman, who endorsed Donald Trump's run for president, said in a social media post on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/bill-ackman-calls-pause-implementing-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPQ4354C75MM3MBA6D25ZKJXMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，德国经济研究所将 2025 年的经济增长预测下调至 0.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士周二告诉路透社，德国经济机构已将今年的经济增长预期从9月份的0.8%下调至0.1%，并补充说这一调整尚未包括美国最新宣布的关税。【原文：German economic institutes have cut their forecast for this year to 0.1% growth from the 0.8% growth expected in September, two sources told Reuters on Tuesday, adding that the revision does not include yet the latest tariffs announced by the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-economic-institutes-cut-forecast-2025-01-growth-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IA33KY3DB5MAFN6XFISYGVNCNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>