<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:05:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:05:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贸易、关税、能源--市场对特朗普就职演说的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，他将对各国征收关税和税收，以让美国人致富，并将全面改革贸易体系和宣布国家能源紧急状态，此后美元延续跌势，而原油价格则收敛跌幅。【原文：The dollar extended its slide while crude prices curtailed their losses after U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he would tariff and tax countries to enrich Americans, overhaul the trade system and declare a national energy emergency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trump-quotes-instant-view-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H43MKM4UY5MZLAIRTWX7L3EZTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 19:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会代理主席范大为承诺 "与所有利益相关者合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党人卡罗琳-范周一被新上任的总统唐纳德-特朗普任命为美国商品期货交易委员会代理主席，她承诺将与所有利益相关者开展建设性的合作。【原文：Republican Caroline Pham, named acting chair on Monday of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission by newly installed President Donald Trump, pledged to work constructively with all stakeholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/acting-us-cftc-chair-pham-pledges-work-with-all-stakeholders-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOTRSDIQXFN6HNHKQQ2AASNV5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 18:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣誓就职，马克龙警告欧洲不能只依赖美国武器]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙（Emmanuel Macron）周一警告说，纳税人用于欧洲军事预算的数十亿欧元不应只用于购买美国武器，他还推动对本土国防工业进行更多投资。【原文：French President Emmanuel Macron warned on Monday that the billions of euros of taxpayer money spent on Europe's military budgets should not be used to buy only American weapons, pushing for more investment in home-grown defence industries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-is-sworn-macron-warns-europe-it-cant-depend-only-us-weapons-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M54VASOCFJNJJMNA4XIQRUC2RM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道努班克首席执行官考虑将注册地迁至英国，并在美国扩展业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nu Holdings Ltd 是一家金融科技公司，它创建了拉丁美洲最有价值的 Nubank 贷款公司，其创始人兼首席执行官大卫-维莱斯（David Velez）告诉路透社，该公司正在考虑在全球扩张（可能包括美国）之前，将其合法注册地迁往英国。【原文：Nu Holdings Ltd , the fintech that created Latin America's most valuable lender in Nubank, is considering moving its legal domicile to Britain ahead of a global expansion that may include the United States, its founder and CEO David Velez told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nubank-ceo-considers-moving-domicile-britain-expanding-us-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XF7446D2BISJODGP2YMGCVPEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示：首席执行官对全球经济增长持乐观态度，但风险依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球调查显示，生成式人工智能的进步并未导致就业机会的减少。【原文：The global survey showed advancements in generative AI had not led to a reduction in employment opportunities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/ceos-optimistic-about-global-growth-risks-remain-survey-shows-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O53FDYEWLNNKJPGPQ5PCNDG2DM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比利时任命调查法官调查刚果冲突矿产案]]></title><description><![CDATA[刚果（金）的一名律师周一表示，刚果（金）于 12 月提起刑事诉讼，指控苹果公司的子公司在供应链中使用所谓的冲突矿产，比利时已任命一名调查法官。【原文：An investigating magistrate has been appointed in Belgium after Democratic Republic of the Congo in December filed criminal complaints accusing Apple subsidiaries of using so-called conflict minerals in their supply chain, a lawyer for Congo said Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/investigating-magistrate-appointed-belgium-congo-conflict-minerals-case-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROJNB2IBFJO4FGQEC7X6QCAIXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:43:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将立即宣布全国能源紧急状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，他将立即宣布国家能源紧急状态，承诺充实战略储备并向全世界出口美国能源。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he would immediately declare a national energy emergency, promising to fill up strategic reserves and export American energy all over the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-says-he-will-immediately-declare-national-energy-emergency-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5RSOHTVVBBNIBICZ2IRMDJBNWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普就职典礼上的亿万富翁和首席执行官们：安巴尼、扎克伯格和贝索斯出席教堂和典礼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，科技界亿万富翁、外国外交官和首席执行官们与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普如影随形，其中几位出席了华盛顿的圣约翰教堂（St.【原文：Tech billionaires, foreign diplomats and CEOs shadowed U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday, with several attending St. John's Church in Washington and seated prominently on the dais in the U.S. Capitol ahead of his speech.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-inauguration-billionaires-ceos-ambani-zuckerberg-bezos-attend-church-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVLLSCKMQFK7HNDTR5CZ42GCOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普指示美国政府削减消费者成本，但未透露细节]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据白宫周一公布的一份文件，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一呼吁联邦政府机构采取行动，降低美国消费者的成本，但没有透露其他细节。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday called on federal government agencies to take action aimed at lowering American consumer costs, but gave no other details, according to a White House document released on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-directs-us-government-cut-consumer-costs-gives-no-details-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFNCNYPAPVMINPAIB7T7HZA57E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[古根海姆预计 2025 年美联储大约每季度降息一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[古根海姆合伙公司（Guggenheim Partners）首席投资官周一预测，美国联邦储备委员会可能在 2025 年大致每个季度都会降息一次，从而使今年的降息幅度达到 75 个基点左右，甚至整整一个百分点。【原文：Guggenheim Partners' chief investment officer forecast on Monday that the U.S. Federal Reserve is likely to cut interest rates roughly every quarter in 2025, bringing the reduction to around 75 basis points or even a full percentage point this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/guggenheim-expects-fed-cut-rates-about-every-quarter-2025-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQPHKF32ZJNRFNJ427FOXJJBNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国表示愿意达成协议，TikTok 等待特朗普的缓兵之计]]></title><description><![CDATA[该应用程序和网站已于周一开始运行，但 TikTok 仍无法在苹果和谷歌应用程序商店下载，这表明两家公司正在等待更明确的法律保证。【原文：The app and website were operational on Monday, but TikTok was still not available for download in the Apple and Google app stores, suggesting the two companies were waiting for clearer legal assurances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-awaits-trump-reprieve-china-signals-open-deal-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZ67WSR3K5J6TEPI5GOC3Q5UAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:48:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[央行调查：加拿大企业销售好转，担忧美国可能采取的措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[作者：Promit Mukherjee 和 David Ljunggren【原文：By Promit Mukherjee and David Ljunggren】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-firms-see-better-sales-fret-about-possible-us-measures-central-bank-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4RWX3VVSJLBZKN2L6CBMURLJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIE 美元暴跌，特朗普团队发出不会立即征收关税的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一位即将上任的美国政府官员表示，当选总统唐纳德-特朗普不会在上任第一天就征收新的贸易关税，这减轻了一些人对美国会立即采取强力措施的担忧，美元因此大幅下挫。【原文：The dollar tumbled broadly on Monday after an official for incoming U.S. administration said President-elect Donald Trump would not impose new trade tariffs on his first day in office, alleviating some fears of an immediate blitz.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/global-markets-trump-instant-view-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLTZ7E5CIFJMNADIFLOCV7EGOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:29:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储退出，央行推动绿色发展遭遇障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）决定退出一个专门负责监管金融业环境风险的俱乐部，各国央行参与应对气候变化的全球努力遇到了重大障碍。【原文：A global effort by central banks to join the fight against climate change has hit a major hurdle with the U.S. Federal Reserve's decision to leave a club devoted to policing environmental risk in finance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/central-banks-green-push-hits-hurdle-fed-drops-out-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64N6D5HAHZL3XJCEMFJ4WNAEDA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者期待更多矿业并购，嘉能可对交易持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[矿产商和大宗商品交易商嘉能可表示，它愿意接受能为股东创造价值的并购交易，充分利用其作为全球前三大铜生产商的地位。【原文：Miner and commodity trader Glencore said it is open to M&amp;A transactions that create value for its shareholders, leveraging its position as a top three global copper producer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/glencore-open-deals-investors-brace-more-mining-ma-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYYMC3CFEVK2PADEAZXZVZ23SE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将提出贸易愿景，但官员称暂不会征收新关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位即将上任的特朗普政府官员表示，唐纳德-特朗普将于周一发布一份内容广泛的贸易备忘录，但不会在上任第一天就征收新的关税，而是指示联邦机构评估美国与中国、加拿大和墨西哥的贸易关系。【原文：Donald Trump will issue a broad trade memo on Monday that stops short of imposing new tariffs on his first day in office, but rather directs federal agencies to evaluate U.S. trade relationships with China, Canada and Mexico, an incoming Trump administration official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-lay-out-trade-vision-wont-impose-new-tariffs-yet-wsj-reports-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDPAJARWPBKWPIOWOPA4AZI43U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥央行行长希思认为 1 月份通胀率将降至 4% 以下]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥央行副行长乔纳森-希思（Jonathan Heath）在周一发表的一篇报道中告诉《Excelsior》报，墨西哥1月份的总体和核心通胀率可能会低于4%，并补充说央行没有必要夸大限制性姿态。【原文：Mexico's headline and core inflation rates will likely land below 4% in January, deputy central bank governor Jonathan Heath told newspaper Excelsior in a story published on Monday, adding that the bank does not need to exaggerate a restrictive posture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-central-banker-heath-sees-inflation-dipping-below-4-january-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HAJ23ZZUNBIYBKSVCE5JW32Z5U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:29:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：特朗普当选总统对俄罗斯卢布的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着唐纳德-特朗普承诺迅速结束乌克兰与俄罗斯之间的战争，市场参与者开始关注这对卢布可能产生的影响。【原文：With Donald Trump's pledge to quickly end the war between Ukraine and Russia, market players are starting to look at what impact that could have on the rouble, which became an outcast following sanctions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/what-trumps-presidency-could-mean-russias-rouble-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPI4OFB2Z5K4HH6GR7DWTXO45Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 13:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示，Facebook、X、YouTube 应进一步打击网络仇恨言论]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周一表示，Meta 的 Facebook、埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 公司、谷歌的 YouTube 和其他科技公司已同意根据更新后的行为准则，采取更多措施应对网络仇恨言论。【原文：Meta's Facebook, Elon Musk's X, Google's YouTube and other tech companies have agreed to do more to tackle online hate speech under an updated code of conduct that will now be integrated into EU tech rules, the European Commission said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/facebook-x-youtube-do-more-against-online-hate-speech-eu-says-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDRWNRRUQBKAJNCJWBNR3KVPWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 12:44:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[朗盛第四季度核心利润将因美国采购而超出预期 20% 以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国特种化学品制造商朗盛周一表示，预计其第四季度核心利润将超出市场预期 20% 以上，这主要归功于美国客户的预购。【原文：German specialty chemicals maker Lanxess said on Monday it expected its fourth-quarter core profit to exceed market expectations by more than 20%, largely due to pre-buying by U.S. customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/lanxess-expects-q4-core-profit-above-expectations-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWXA7WK2TBI2TBVJLQ2OG6JE4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 12:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Circle 首席执行官预计美国即将颁布的行政命令将扩大加密货币的范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[Circle 首席执行官杰里米-阿莱尔（Jeremy Allaire）预计，美国即将上任的总统唐纳德-特朗普将 "很快 "颁布行政命令，他说，这可能会允许银行进行加密货币交易，向富裕客户提供加密货币投资，并在投资组合中持有加密货币。【原文：Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire expects U.S. executive orders "imminently" from incoming President Donald Trump, which he said could allow banks to trade crypto, offer crypto investments to wealthy clients and hold it in portfolios.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/circle-ceo-expects-imminent-us-executive-orders-widen-crypto-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGHTG6KWDBLABLRCMJLGBWZZQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 11:35:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普媒体的忠实信徒押注总统任期开始后股票大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月下旬的一天晚上，惠特尼-帕特森在 YouTube 上看到一段视频，内容是人们购买美国当选总统的社交媒体和流媒体公司特朗普媒体与科技集团的股票。【原文：One night in late October, Whitney Patterson spotted a YouTube video about people buying shares in Trump Media &amp; Technology Group , the U.S. president-elect's social media and streaming company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-medias-true-believers-bet-stock-surge-presidency-begins-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7E3YJTGPBNP5BFAFBZ5PQBGBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 11:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普重返白宫，市场表现乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者准备迎接唐纳德-特朗普的第二次就职，预期他的亲商议程将带来好处，同时对他的贸易保护主义政策，特别是他的关税立场保持警惕。【原文：Investors prepared to welcome Donald Trump's second inauguration, anticipating benefits from his pro-business agenda, while remaining wary of his protectionist trade policies, particularly his stance on tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/markets-optimistic-trump-returns-white-house-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7E5C5FGZ55PYPK5T74YTL3IJSU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 11:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对约 295,00 辆本田汽车不慎自动紧急制动展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周一表示，已对约 295,125 辆美国本田汽车展开调查，原因是有报告称自动紧急制动系统无意中启动，导致车辆急剧减速，增加了碰撞风险。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Monday it has opened a probe into about 295,125 American Honda vehicles over reports of inadvertent activation of the automatic emergency braking system, resulting in rapid vehicle deceleration that increases the risk of a collision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-opens-probe-into-about-29500-honda-vehicles-over-inadvertent-automatic-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHOHMSEZUBJWXHIW5H5ABH6FQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 10:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对超过12.9万辆福特汽车的免提技术展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周一表示，已开始对 129,222 辆福特汽车的免提驾驶技术 BlueCruise 碰撞事故进行调查。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Monday it has opened a probe into 129,222 Ford Motor vehicles over reports of collisions involving the company's hands-free driving technology, BlueCruise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-opens-probe-into-over-129000-ford-vehicles-over-hands-free-tech-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYYFF3G6XNNTPLEKBWJVFMH7EQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 10:49:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称三菱化学选择贝恩作为子公司的首选竞购者]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周一报道，三菱化学集团选择美国投资基金贝恩资本（Bain Capital）作为其制药子公司田边三菱制药（Tanabe Mitsubishi Pharma）的首选竞购者。【原文：Mitsubishi Chemical Group picked U.S. investment fund Bain Capital as the preferred bidder for its pharmaceutical subsidiary, Tanabe Mitsubishi Pharma, the Nikkei reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/mitsubishi-chemical-has-given-bain-first-refusal-right-negotiate-purchase-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QONBOXRU5FILRMX6LQMTZRVJPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 10:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宜家顶级零售商警告关税可能推高消费价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的宜家特许经营商英卡集团（Ingka Group）首席执行官周一告诉路透社记者，对于经济型家具零售商宜家来说，贸易关税越少越好，因为企业都在为唐纳德-特朗普总统提高美国关税做准备。【原文：For budget furniture retailer IKEA, the fewer trade tariffs there are the better, the CEO of Ingka Group, the biggest global IKEA franchisee, told Reuters on Monday as businesses brace for higher U.S. tariffs under President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/top-ikea-retailer-warns-tariffs-could-drive-up-consumer-prices-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LE5J57K2XJLAVEHOYJZQSPSQHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 09:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共同社称，新日铁就美国钢铁公司竞购案提起诉讼的听证会将于 2 月至 3 月举行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据共同社周一报道，新日铁和美国钢铁公司对美国总统拜登政府提起诉讼的听证会定于 2 月和 3 月举行，但未引述消息来源。【原文：The hearing for a lawsuit that Nippon Steel and U.S. Steel brought against U.S. President Joe Biden's administration is scheduled for February and March, Kyodo news agency reported on Monday, without citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/hearing-nippon-steels-lawsuit-over-us-steel-bid-set-feb-march-kyodo-says-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWVEKXRVCFKZFJSNP6MXTETFWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 09:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希腊能源部表示雪佛龙公司有意在希腊勘探碳氢化合物]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊能源部周一发表声明称，美国石油生产商雪佛龙公司表示有意在希腊伯罗奔尼撒半岛西南部勘探碳氢化合物。【原文：U.S. oil producer Chevron has expressed insterest in exploring for hydrocarbons southwest of the Peloponnese peninsula in Greece, the Greek energy ministry said in a statement on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-expresses-interest-hydorcarbons-exploration-greece-energy-ministry-says-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBWF6ECPPBJZDHRT2WJSPIISAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 09:25:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国节俭的青壮年加速储蓄，引发经济风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着 Z 世代避开政府的 "消费、消费、消费 "号召，加倍努力节省开支，节俭风潮在中国大流行病造成的经济混乱中开始兴起，并在房地产市场危机中愈演愈烈。【原文：The frugal trend that began in China during the economic disruption of the pandemic and deepened amid the crisis in the property market is intensifying as Gen Z shuns government calls to spend, spend, spend and doubles down on saving.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-frugal-young-adults-accelerate-saving-raising-economic-risks-2025-01-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITOKUWLATJLZPIOSIRUVTT22CM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 09:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>