<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 02:46:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 02:46:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市小幅回落，美元走强，就业报告与关税裁决前夕]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周五小幅走低，美元坚挺，市场正等待关键就业报告出炉。与此同时，投资者正为最高法院对特朗普总统去年引发市场震荡的全球性关税合法性裁决做准备。【原文：Asian stocks drifted lower and the dollar stood tall on Friday ahead of a crucial jobs report, while investors girded for a Supreme Court ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump's sweeping global tariff that jolted markets last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYXA43YGBRKTFPF74LOKVV6MF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 02:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aktis Oncology将美国IPO发行价定为每股18美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[抗癌药物开发商Aktis Oncology周四宣布，其扩大的美国首次公开募股定价为每股18美元，筹集资金约3.18亿美元。【原文：Cancer drug developer Aktis Oncology said on Thursday it priced its upsized U.S. initial public offering at $18 per share, raising about $318 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/aktis-oncology-prices-upsized-us-ipo-18-per-share-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3QC2EQB2NLVNLSXZGLRKVVZ24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 02:20:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价上涨，因市场对委内瑞拉和伊朗供应中断的担忧加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五油价连续第二日上涨，有望实现连续第三周上涨，这源于委内瑞拉未来供应前景的不确定性，以及伊朗局势动荡加剧了市场对其产量的担忧。【原文：Oil prices rose for a second day on Friday, set for their third weekly gain, on uncertainty about the future of supply from Venezuela and as Iranian unrest increases concerns about output there.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-concerns-about-supply-disruptions-venezuela-iran-increase-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2SPYNXGDJOB7GWZERCRMG23CE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 02:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司与美国政府达成协议以降低药品价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司周四表示，已与美国总统特朗普政府达成协议，将为美国民众降低药品价格，以换取美国关税豁免。【原文：Johnson & Johnson said on Thursday that it has reached an agreement with U.S. President Donald Trump's administration to cut drug prices for Americans in exchange for exemptions from U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/johnson-johnson-reaches-deal-with-us-government-lower-drug-prices-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RO72BISLN5KZZAP2XNQSAPLERY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:43:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国消费者物价涨幅逼近三年高位，生产者物价通缩压力缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国12月消费者价格年同比涨幅升至34个月高点，主要受食品价格上涨推动，但全年涨幅跌至16年来最低水平，同时生产者价格持续通缩，表明需求疲软态势仍在延续。【原文：China's annual consumer price inflation accelerated to a 34-month high in December, driven by rising food prices, but the full-year rate slumped to the lowest in 16 years while producer deflation persisted, indicating persistent softness in demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-consumer-inflation-hits-near-3-year-high-factory-gate-deflation-eases-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWFSDFISLZJSLOGYRGBPE66QMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国人工智能公司MiniMax香港上市首日股价有望大幅上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能模型开发商MiniMax集团将于周五在香港市场首次公开募股，此前该公司已筹集48.2亿港元（约合6.186亿美元），延续了香港科技股上市热潮。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence model developer MiniMax Group is set to jump on its Hong Kong market debut on Friday after raising HK$4.82 billion ($618.6 million), extending a flurry of tech listings in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-ai-firm-minimax-set-surge-hong-kong-debut-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FFEYNR3CRPAPO53CKAFHKWQ34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蓝星钢铁最大股东支持拒绝90亿美元收购案]]></title><description><![CDATA[蓝星钢铁最大股东澳大利亚超级基金周五表示，支持这家澳大利亚钢铁制造商拒绝SGH和美国钢铁动力公司提出的90亿澳元收购要约。【原文：BlueScope Steel's largest investor, AustralianSuper, said on Friday it supported the Australian steelmaker's decision to reject a $9 billion takeover offer from SGH and U.S-based Steel Dynamics .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bluescopes-largest-investor-backs-9-billion-takeover-rejection-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXQPM4FOWVN7RI23SRR5TF6NX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道，和记黄埔聘请高盛和瑞银为屈臣氏集团首次公开募股提供服务。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，知情人士透露，香港和记黄埔有限公司已选定高盛集团和瑞银集团，为旗下屈臣氏集团计划中的首次公开募股（IPO）提供服务。【原文：Hong Kong-based CK Hutchison has picked Goldman Sachs and UBS Group AG to work on the planned initial public offering of its unit A.S. Watson Group, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ck-hutchison-taps-goldman-sachs-ubs-watson-ipo-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7PRRVGIT5N65FQOE3M66UHEXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:07:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因美国就业数据走强，最高法院裁决在即]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲时段开盘，美元汇率走高。交易员们正等待最新美国就业报告的发布，同时为即将到来的美国最高法院裁决做准备——该裁决将涉及特朗普总统动用紧急关税权力的行为。【原文：The U.S. dollar advanced at the start of the Asian session on Friday, as traders awaited the release of the latest U.S. jobs report and braced for a forthcoming U.S. Supreme Court decision on President Donald Trump's use of emergency tariff powers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-advances-with-us-jobs-data-supreme-court-ruling-view-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGUU2TIA4VMHZABONAICHTSZBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，马斯克旗下xAI公司季度净亏损达14.6亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四援引内部文件报道，埃隆·马斯克的人工智能初创公司xAI在9月季度报告净亏损14.6亿美元，较第一季度的10亿美元亏损有所扩大。【原文：Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence startup xAI reported a net loss of $1.46 billion for the September quarter, up from $1 billion in the first quarter, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing internal documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/musks-xai-posts-net-quarterly-loss-146-billion-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJZMKSSAHBJQ3ECW3LCQRERGLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:31:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普基于《国际紧急经济权力法》征收关税影响最大的国家和行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院将于周五就多起案件作出裁决，这些案件涉及特朗普总统依据《国际紧急经济权力法》征收关税的合法性问题。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court is set to issue rulings on Friday on cases related to the legality of tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/countries-industries-most-exposed-trumps-ieepa-based-tariffs-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76ESY6C2QBJJHKQAYEDQW2MH4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡纳斯达克联动计划引发关注，但准入门槛与流动性或限制参与度]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Singaporean initiative to boost the IPO market with a fast-track route to a Nasdaq dual listing has garnered a warm response from potential issuers, though bankers caution thin liquidity and a high valuation requirement could limit take-up.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/singapores-nasdaq-link-draws-interest-threshold-liquidity-may-limit-take-up-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M33JH2QJBJLVZBYPCDQHYHGPZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[健身追踪应用Strava秘密提交IPO申请，据消息人士透露]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fitness tracking app Strava has confidentially filed for an initial public offering in recent weeks, the Information reported on Thursday, citing people with direct knowledge of the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fitness-tracking-app-strava-confidentially-files-ipo-information-reports-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K3IVAXZMMVNTHO2LCU77MHMMKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:52:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：防御性板块胜过科技股，下看就业数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四全球股市普遍下跌，油价和美国国债收益率则出现上涨。投资者对美国总统特朗普呼吁大幅增加国防开支的言论反应紧张，同时等待周五公布的美国关键就业数据。【原文：Global stocks mostly fell, while oil and Treasury yields rose on Thursday, as investors reacted nervously to U.S. President Donald Trump's call for a huge increase in defense spending and awaited key U.S. employment figures on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXBLX4I4SNJ77FXSGY2DXLEGJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪分析师称特朗普1.5万亿美元国防预算计划可能扩大赤字]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪评级公司分析师表示，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普提出的2027年国防开支增加计划，不太可能通过节省开支或增加收入来抵消，并将对美国本已庞大的财政赤字产生负面影响。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's proposed increase in defense spending for 2027 is unlikely to be offset by savings or revenues and would have a negative impact on already large U.S. fiscal deficits, said an analyst at Moody's Ratings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/moodys-analyst-says-15-trillion-trump-defense-budget-plan-could-widen-deficits-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSNRRPUY7VKN5DRICPDBUKCRMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump orders his representatives to buy $200 billion dollars in mortgage bonds]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周四表示，他已下令其代表购买2000亿美元抵押贷款债券，并称此举旨在降低住房成本。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday he is ordering his representatives to buy $200 billion dollars in mortgage bonds, adding that the step aimed to bring down housing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-orders-his-representatives-buy-200-billion-dollars-mortgage-bonds-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LU5F4RYQ3JICZDGOH37E3XRVKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:41:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长要求Instacart提交价格测试相关信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长莱蒂西亚·詹姆斯周四要求Instacart提供信息，称该公司可能违反了该州法律——该法律要求在线零售商在利用消费者信息定价时必须予以披露。【原文：New York Attorney General Letitia James demanded information from Instacart on Thursday, saying it may have violated the state's law requiring online retailers to disclose when they use consumers' information to set prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/new-york-ag-demands-instacart-hand-over-information-about-price-tests-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYHQ42X6CJKFVEVSHSZM3ZYKAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:38:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车因电动汽车业务收缩将计提60亿美元减值损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车周四表示，将计提60亿美元费用以撤回部分电动汽车投资。这是最新一家因特朗普政府政策及需求疲软而缩减电动汽车业务的汽车公司。【原文：General Motors said on Thursday it would take a $6 billion charge to unwind some electric-vehicle investments, the latest car company to pull back from EVs in response to the Trump administration's policies and fading demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-take-6-billion-writedown-ev-pullback-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDAO2WGWLJKPFBME54IIG2TOJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克正洽谈收购生物技术公司Revolution Medicines，英国《金融时报》报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[《金融时报》周四援引知情人士消息报道称，默克公司正就收购抗癌药物开发商Revolution Medicines展开谈判。【原文：Merck is in talks to buy cancer drug developer Revolution Medicines , the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-talks-buy-biotech-revolution-medicines-ft-reports-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVRBWOVHXVLWLAWH5BNYZCCEFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:56:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，雪佛龙正与竞争对手争夺委内瑞拉石油销售权]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业消息人士周四透露，美国石油巨头雪佛龙、全球贸易商维托尔及其他石油贸易商、生产商和炼油商正竞相争取委内瑞拉原油出口合同，作为其与美国官员谈判获取与该国开展业务许可的一部分。【原文：U.S. oil major Chevron , global trading house Vitol and other oil traders, producers and refiners are competing to win deals for exports of Venezuelan crude as part of their talks with U.S. officials for licenses to do business with the country, industry sources said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-competes-with-rivals-venezuelan-oil-sales-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULCKEC5YCJKYBHK6EJUULHURDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称特朗普支持者、石油大亨哈里·萨金特正就委内瑞拉问题向美国提供建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位知情人士透露，亿万富翁能源企业家、共和党捐助者哈里·萨金特三世及其团队正就美国如何推动部分美国石油公司重返委内瑞拉向特朗普政府提供建议。【原文：Billionaire energy entrepreneur and Republican donor Harry Sargeant III and his team are advising the Trump administration on how the U.S. can engineer a return of some American oil companies to Venezuela, according to four sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-supporter-oil-magnate-harry-sargeant-advising-us-venezuela-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOBS6VIGZRJGHB5SW5T3R6MOTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英美资源集团与泰克资源公司合并案即将获得欧盟反垄断批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[据欧盟委员会文件显示，伦敦上市矿业公司英美资源集团与加拿大泰克资源公司的拟议合并案，在欧盟监管机构表示不存在竞争担忧后，正朝着获得欧洲反垄断批准的方向推进。【原文：The proposed merger of London-listed miner Anglo American and Canada's Teck Resources is heading for antitrust clearance in Europe after EU regulators signalled the absence of competition concerns, according to a European Commission filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/anglo-american-teck-merger-heading-eu-antitrust-approval-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXZI3C475VMEHJHUP7GTZWE6DA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:00:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉能可表示正就被力拓收购事宜进行初步谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[Glencore said on Thursday it was in early talks to be acquried by Rio Tinto , , in a combination that would potentially create the world's largest mining company.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/glencore-rio-tinto-resume-talks-mining-mega-deal-ft-reports-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSJFK2N2WFJ2HA45YM3CHW7T6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:50:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部官员贝森特表示，里德尚未接受美联储最高职位的面试，任命决定可能在本月作出。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周四表示，贝莱德首席债券投资经理里克·里德尚未接受美国总统唐纳德·特朗普的面试，以竞聘美联储主席一职。他补充称，预计提名结果将于本月晚些时候公布。【原文：BlackRock's chief bond investment manager, Rick Rieder, has not been interviewed yet by U.S. President Donald Trump for the Federal Reserve top job, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday, adding that he expects the nominee to be announced later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasurys-bessent-says-rieder-not-yet-interviewed-top-fed-job-decision-likely-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFGD6JOWWJND7ET5PVELCKTNFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:44:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，欧盟数字法规改革中科技巨头免于严格监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周四透露，尽管电信公司呼吁加强监管，但谷歌母公司Alphabet、Meta Platforms、奈飞、微软和亚马逊在欧洲数字法规改革中不会面临严厉监管。【原文：Alphabet's Google , Meta Platforms , Netflix , Microsoft and Amazon will not face heavy-handed regulations in Europe's digital rule overhaul despite calls from telecoms companies, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/big-tech-spared-strict-rules-eu-digital-rule-overhaul-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POP3KJ2XPNLC7AEWWPK3U72LPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国会预算办公室预测美联储今年将小幅降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[国会预算办公室周四预测，美联储今年可能进一步小幅降息以"应对劳动力市场的下行风险"。由于关税提高以及特朗普政府减税政策带来的需求增长，通胀率预计将持续远高于美联储2%的目标水平。【原文：The Federal Reserve will likely cut rates a little more this year to "address downside risks to the labor market," the Congressional Budget Office forecast on Thursday, with higher tariffs and increased demand from the Trump administration's tax cuts expected to keep inflation well above the Fed's 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-cut-rates-slightly-this-year-cbo-forecasts-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJIL7MDVE5MC7K6NOAHVJNMAUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:26:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CrowdStrike以7.4亿美元收购身份安全初创公司SGNL，以应对人工智能威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[CrowdStrike周四宣布将以7.4亿美元收购身份安全初创公司SGNL，旨在增强其网络安全工具，帮助客户应对人工智能驱动的威胁。【原文：CrowdStrike said on Thursday it would buy identity security startup SGNL in a deal valued at $740 million aiming to enhance its cybersecurity tools to help customers counter artificial intelligence-powered threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/crowdstrike-buy-identity-security-startup-sgnl-740-million-tackle-ai-threats-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NVDJE73UBKMRAOXRE5BP4QUNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:09:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：从奢侈品巨头到濒临崩溃：萨克斯百货重大并购赌局如何失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[萨克斯百货与内曼·马库斯以27亿美元完成合并，旨在打造奢侈品百货领域的行业巨头，以应对来自线上零售商及布鲁明戴尔、诺德斯特龙等竞争对手的挑战。【原文：The $2.7-billion marriage of Saks and Neiman Marcus was meant to create a powerhouse in the world of luxury department stores, helping it fight competition from online players and rivals such as Bloomingdale's and Nordstrom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/luxury-powerhouse-brink-how-saks-big-merger-bet-failed-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELXQC7E445KPXD26WGQAGUEDY4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:55:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西2025年鸡蛋出口量激增，得益于美国强劲需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西动物蛋白协会（ABPA）周四发布的数据显示，得益于美国强劲需求，2025年巴西鸡蛋出口量（含鲜蛋和加工蛋）创下40,894公吨的历史新高。【原文：Brazilian egg exports, including fresh and processed, hit a record 40,894 metric tons in 2025 on strong U.S. demand, according to data compiled by the Brazilian Association of Animal Protein (ABPA) on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-2025-eggs-exports-soar-strong-us-demand-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IINJG5334NITZMFAHXS4QUN3VU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:38:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利隐私监管机构就深度伪造AI内容对Grok发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利数据保护机构周四警告人工智能工具用户及提供商——包括埃隆·马斯克的聊天机器人Grok——在未经被拍摄者同意的情况下，利用真实内容生成深度伪造图像存在风险。【原文：Italy's data protection authority on Thursday warned users and providers of artificial intelligence tools, including Elon Musk’s chatbot Grok, over the risk of generating deepfake images from real content without the consent of featured individuals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/italys-privacy-watchdog-warns-grok-over-deepfake-ai-content-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQID2N2EZ5ORZG73VAYCL4RC5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>