<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:35:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:35:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[在加拿大央行 9 月 17 日利率决议之前，委员们预计他们可能会在 10 月货币政策报告中提出对经济增长和通货膨胀的基线预测 - 讨论纪要]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/ahead-bank-canadas-sept-17-rate-decision-members-expected-they-could-present-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNUN5EUS2FKCNCM6AQCOVN5G2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:33:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[First Brands 获得破产法官批准 5 亿美元救援融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[破产汽车供应商 First Brands 周三获得了美国法官的许可，可以进行 11 亿美元破产贷款的第一阶段工作，在该公司努力重组长期债务的同时，可立即获得 5 亿美元的资金注入。【原文：Bankrupt auto supplier First Brands on Wednesday received a U.S. judge's permission to proceed with the first phase of a $1.1 billion bankruptcy loan, giving the company an immediate infusion of $500 million as it tries to reorganize its longer-term debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/first-brands-obtains-bankruptcy-judge-approval-500-million-rescue-financing-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLHQGZLI6BLOZE6XCHUBBVL2CM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，人工智能数据分析初创公司 Dataiku 已选定在美国上市的银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，人工智能数据分析初创公司 Dataiku 已聘请投资银行推进首次公开募股。【原文：Dataiku, an artificial intelligence data analytics startup, has hired investment banks to push ahead with an initial public offering, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ai-data-analytics-startup-dataiku-picked-banks-us-ipo-sources-say-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIRZ4G57CJOJFCZUS7EAX6JW5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:08:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲炼油厂押宝绿色项目以确保长远未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[炼油行业高管周三表示，由于亚洲、中东和非洲的竞争对手更加现代化和复杂化，欧洲炼油厂不得不投资能源转型项目，从而导致欧洲工厂关闭。【原文：European oil refineries are having to invest in energy transition projects as modern and more complex competitors in Asia, the Middle East and Africa have prompted plant closures in Europe, refining industry executives said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/european-oil-refineries-bet-green-projects-secure-long-term-future-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYQKQ5REDNPJNMMKNYWQQRS62M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车企业高管担心美国税收补贴消失导致电动汽车销售崩溃]]></title><description><![CDATA[在为电动汽车购买者提供的 7500 美元关键税收减免政策消失后，汽车业高管正为美国电动汽车销售的自由落体做好准备。【原文：Automotive executives are bracing for a freefall in U.S. electric-vehicle sales following the disappearance of a critical $7,500 tax break for buyers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/car-executives-fear-collapse-ev-sales-us-tax-subsidy-vanishes-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VU3IPYI2WZJQJDYVWEB46XMWDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自动驾驶卡车公司 Einride 融资 1 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典自动驾驶卡车初创公司 Einride 在最新一轮融资中筹集了约 1 亿美元，投资方包括资产管理公司 EQT Ventures 和量子计算公司 IonQ，估值未公开。【原文：Swedish self-driving truck startup Einride has raised around $100 million in the latest funding round from investors, including asset management firm EQT Ventures and quantum computing company IonQ , at an undisclosed valuation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/self-driving-truck-company-einride-raises-100-million-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2BZKTYUPZLUVLMQ5LEWWGP7NI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:46:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软任命首席执行官负责商业业务，纳德拉将专注于技术领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软首席商务官贾德森-阿尔索夫（Judson Althoff）将担任商业业务首席执行官一职，这将使公司首席执行官萨蒂亚-纳德拉（Satya Nadella）腾出手来，更加专注于技术方面的业务，从而使这家科技巨头在人工智能竞赛中占据主导地位。【原文：Microsoft Chief Commercial Officer Judson Althoff will take on an expanded role as CEO of commercial business, freeing up company chief Satya Nadella to focus more on the technical side of the business in the tech giant's quest to dominate the AI race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-names-ceo-run-commercial-business-nadella-focus-tech-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GILSE3XPGRJVJLBWACZFXOEPCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:44:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[5000 亿美元 "星际之门 "人工智能项目的主要利益攸关方]]></title><description><![CDATA[星际之门是一项耗资 5000 亿美元的人工智能基础设施计划，是华盛顿推动在该领域占据主导地位的核心，自今年 1 月启动以来，已吸引了众多投资者和供应商。【原文：Stargate, a $500 billion AI infrastructure initiative that is central to Washington's push for dominance in the field, has drawn a slew of investors and suppliers since its launch in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/key-stakeholders-500-billion-stargate-ai-project-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQNSQYGKLFLWVFYNU3WV4BO5OY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府信用违约掉期利差走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府信用违约掉期的利差（以市场为基础衡量主权违约风险的指标）在市场对美国政府停摆的担忧中走高。【原文：Spreads on U.S. government credit default swaps, market-based gauges of the risk of a sovereign default, have ticked higher amid market concerns over the U.S. government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-government-credit-default-swap-spreads-edge-higher-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56MUIWWI2BLJ5O6YOE73FHGHVM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:41:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软推出人工智能驱动的 365 Premium 捆绑包，每月 19.99 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周三发布了面向个人的 365 Premium 订阅计划，每月 19.99 美元，并配备了由人工智能驱动的 Copilot 助手。【原文：Microsoft on Wednesday unveiled a 365 Premium subscription plan for individuals at $19.99 a month with its Copilot artificial intelligence powered assistant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-launches-ai-powered-365-premium-bundle-1999-per-month-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CV7PFGM4XZORFB4QNL7XXGJWOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:21:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 9 月份在意大利的新车销量下降 25.6]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利交通部周三公布的数据显示，9月份特斯拉在意大利的新车注册量连续第五个月下降，同比降幅达25.6%。【原文：Tesla's new car registrations in Italy fell for a fifth month in a row in September, posting a 25.6% year-on-year drop, data from the Italian transport ministry showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/teslas-new-car-sales-italy-down-256-september-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGLRRBU6OFKVVIDF3JHOOKNXDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cucinelli 重申其在俄罗斯的运营符合欧盟规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品公司布鲁内罗-库奇内利（Brunello Cucinelli）周三重申，该公司在俄罗斯的运营完全符合欧盟规定，第三季度收入增长了 12%，达到 3.36 亿欧元（约合 3.94 亿美元）。【原文：Italian luxury company Brunello Cucinelli reaffirmed on Wednesday that it operated in Russia in full compliance with EU regulations, as it posted a 12% increase in revenues in the third quarter, to 336 million euros ($394 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cucinelli-reaffirms-that-it-operates-russia-line-with-eu-rules-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3KF5UVISRN4VBL5I7HFDKT6DQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海王星保险公司估值超过 30 亿美元，股价在纽交所首次亮相时大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[海王保险股价周三在纽约证券交易所首次亮相时大涨 12.5%，公司估值近 31.1 亿美元，成为最新一家利用繁荣上市市场的保险公司。【原文：Neptune Insurance shares jumped 12.5% in their New York Stock Exchange debut on Wednesday, valuing the company at nearly $3.11 billion and making it the latest insurer to capitalize on a buoyant listings market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/neptune-insurance-valued-over-31-billion-shares-jump-nyse-debut-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UGSS7Q3CRNWZJSZMYVCTHLE34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:59:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将 Xbox Game Pass 最高订阅费用提高 50]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司的 Xbox 已将 Game Pass 最高级别的价格提高了 50%，并扩大了电子游戏订阅服务的产品范围，包括更多游戏、增强型云流媒体和经过改进的奖励系统。【原文：Microsoft's Xbox has raised the price of the highest tier of Game Pass by 50% and expanded its offerings under the videogame subscription service to include more games, enhanced cloud streaming and a revamped rewards system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-raises-top-xbox-game-pass-subscription-by-50-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RQMBBXQHBM2LP6I3SYVUANXYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道无人机袭击后俄罗斯西部港口石油出口增长 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位贸易消息人士称，由于乌克兰无人机袭击导致炼油厂停工，释放了更多原油，俄罗斯 9 月份通过其西部港口的石油出口量比 8 月份增加了 25%。【原文：Russia boosted oil exports via its western ports by 25% in September versus August, according to three trading sources, as refinery outages caused by Ukrainian drone attacks freed up more crude.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russias-western-port-oil-exports-up-25-after-drone-attacks-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOD624IKXNOWHDZHBQ4VTMRHKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国大陆集团预计下半年关税将达到 "两位数百万欧元"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国大陆集团（Continental AG）周三表示，预计 2025 年下半年将受到美国关税 "高达两位数百万欧元 "的冲击，并补充说这已经考虑到了自 8 月份起追溯到 15%的关税削减。【原文：Continental AG expects a "high double-digit million-euro" hit from U.S. tariffs in the second half of 2025, it said on Wednesday, adding this already factored in a retroactive cut to 15% as of August.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/continental-ag-expects-high-double-digit-million-euro-tariff-hit-second-half-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLUYHHJHOZKBDHBWXVUJAZ4GKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:47:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金刚石公司首席执行官认为美国原油产量增长将因每桶 60 美元的油价而停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国顶级石油生产商之一钻石能源公司（Diamondback Energy）的首席执行官周三表示，如果油价维持在每桶 60 美元附近，美国石油产量的增长将停滞不前，因为在这一水平上有利可图的钻井地点越来越少。【原文：U.S. oil production growth will stall if prices stay near $60 per barrel, as fewer drilling sites are profitable at that level, the CEO of Diamondback Energy , one of the country's top oil producers, said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/diamondback-ceo-sees-us-crude-output-growth-stalling-with-60bbl-oil-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPGFVSUKB5LRLBH35VE3FEN37M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车第三季度美国汽车销量增长约 8]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）周三公布，受电动汽车和 SUV 需求强劲的推动，其第三季度美国汽车销量增长了 7.7%。【原文：General Motors reported a 7.7% rise in its U.S. auto sales during the third-quarter on Wednesday, aided by strong demand for electric vehicles and SUVs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-third-quarter-us-auto-sales-up-about-8-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGR3OEHENNNETJCQIKME5XYZKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:32:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田汽车第三季度美国销量增长近 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车北美分公司周三公布的汽车销量增长近 16%，主要得益于皮卡和轿车的销售。【原文：Toyota Motor's North American unit reported a near 16% rise in auto sales on Wednesday, helped by sales of its pickup trucks and cars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyotas-third-quarter-us-sales-up-nearly-16-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QRZELTORVPPXOR6SSYA5EESJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁支持的比特币公司 OranjeBTC 将在巴西交易所开始交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西加密货币公司 OranjeBTC 计划下周开始在当地证券交易所 B3 上市交易，试图挑战金融科技公司 Meliuz 的主导地位，后者是巴西首家拥有比特币财务战略的上市公司。【原文：Brazilian cryptocurrency firm OranjeBTC is scheduled to begin trading on the local stock exchange B3 next week as it tries to challenge the dominance of fintech Meliuz , the first listed firm to have a bitcoin treasury strategy in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/billionaire-backed-bitcoin-firm-oranjebtc-begin-trading-brazilian-exchange-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EVQKCPILZKJRH46MBU3N6Z6LI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦资金耗尽，美国金融监管机构开始关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国国会未能延长拨款，联邦政府于周三关闭，美国市场监管机构开始裁员，从而削弱了关键的监督职能，阻碍了首次公开募股，并限制了一些市场和经济数据。
根据美国证券交易委员会（Securities and Exchange Commission）的应急计划，从午夜开始的停摆将迫使该机构90%以上的员工休假，仅保留约393名员工处理紧急执法行动和市场监管工作。
据路透社报道，负责监管数千家上市公司、交易所、经纪商和基金的该机构于周二晚间通知员工为停摆做好准备。
美国商品期货交易委员会（CFTC）在周二晚间公布的一份计划中称，负责监管衍生品市场的CFTC计划仅以543人中的5.7%开展工作，他们将继续确保市场监督，防止欺诈和滥用。
虽然市场普遍对之前的短暂停摆不以为然，但长期停摆将推迟或取消投资者用来评估宏观经济趋势的关键经济数据发布，从而可能造成资产价格波动。周三，华尔街期货和美元跌跌不休，黄金则创下历史新高。
美国证券交易委员会（SEC）的常规公司备案工作将继续进行，但该机构将无法处理首次公开募股（IPO），这可能会抑制近期IPO市场的复苏。
"Mergermarket股票资本市场主管塞缪尔-克尔（Samuel Kerr）说："在政治不确定性加剧之际，停摆让投资者有理由三思是否购买新交易。【原文：U.S. market regulators began the process of furloughing workers on Wednesday as the federal government shut down after Congress failed to extend funding, curtailing key oversight functions, stymieing initial public offerings, and limiting some market and economic data.
The shutdown, which began at midnight, will force the Securities and Exchange Commission to furlough more than 90% of its workforce, retaining only about 393 employees to handle emergency enforcement actions and market surveillance, according to its contingency plan.
The agency, which regulates thousands of listed companies, exchanges, broker-dealers, and funds notified staff on Tuesday evening to prepare for the shutdown, Reuters reported.
The CFTC, which oversees derivatives markets, plans to operate with just 5.7% of its 543 people, who will continue to ensure market oversight and prevent fraud and abuse, the CFTC said in a plan published Tuesday evening.
While markets have generally shrugged off previous short-lived shutdowns, a prolonged one would delay or cancel key economic data releases investors use to assess macroeconomic trends, potentially creating asset price volatility. Wall Street futures and the dollar stumbled on Wednesday, while gold struck a record high.
Routine company SEC filings will continue, but the agency will not be able to process IPOs, potentially dampening a recent IPO market revival.
"A shutdown gives investors a reason to think twice on whether to buy into new deals at a time of heightened political uncertainty," said Samuel Kerr, head of equity capital markets at Mergermarket.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-financial-regulators-start-shuttering-federal-funding-runs-out-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDQ6FUUZ6FPILEZOLWQNG2HYPY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:06:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会称，美国消费者不能在美国联邦贸易委员会关门期间向其报告欺诈行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（U.S. Federal Trade Commission）周三表示，在政府关门期间，该机构将不会受理消费者的欺诈投诉或帮助他们阻止垃圾邮件电话，也不会提前批准合并。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission will not take consumers' fraud complaints or help them block spam calls, and it will not grant early clearance to mergers during the government shutdown, the agency said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-consumers-cannot-report-fraud-ftc-during-shutdown-agency-says-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWTWJ6ZB3RLAXOQ2U6QJ5WUSTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:57:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲范围警告：美国政府停摆对信用评级不利]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲评级机构 Scope 表示，美国政府的关门对美国面临降级威胁的信用评分来说是另一个负面因素。【原文：European rating agency Scope has said that the shutdown of the U.S. government is another negative for the country's downgrade-threatened credit score.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-government-shutdown-negative-credit-rating-europes-scope-warns-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ED4WBBDIQZKPBC6NFGB4YCGXJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[激进投资者在本季度开展了 61 项活动，是有史以来最繁忙的一个季度]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）的最新数据显示，在第三季度，推动公司进行运营变革和管理层调整的激进投资者对全球企业发起的攻击次数创下新高，并赢得了更多的董事会席位和和解协议。【原文：Activist investors who push companies for operational changes and management shake-ups launched a record number of attacks on global corporations in the third quarter and won more board seats and settlements, new data from Barclays show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/activist-investors-had-busiest-quarter-ever-launching-61-campaigns-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S52GKL3ZLNKGLGCKSZX7353AAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:46:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 将面临范围缩小的股东诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官表示，Coinbase 股东可以提起范围缩小的诉讼，指控这家美国最大的加密货币交易所运营商隐瞒业务风险，包括是否会被美国证券交易委员会起诉。【原文：A federal judge said Coinbase shareholders may pursue a narrowed lawsuit accusing the largest U.S. cryptocurrency exchange operator of concealing business risks, including whether it would be sued by the Securities and Exchange Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/coinbase-face-narrowed-shareholder-lawsuit-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5GYK5MO4BKL3HRDW7O5G2UL6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息，美元面临长期疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对外汇策略师进行的一项调查显示，自今年年初以来一直承压的美元在未来12个月内可能难以找到其相对于大多数主要货币的立足点。【原文：The U.S. dollar, under pressure since the start of the year, may struggle to find its footing against most major currencies over the coming 12 months, according to a Reuters poll of FX strategists who said the already crowded short U.S. dollar trade will remain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-faces-prolonged-weakness-amid-fed-rate-cuts-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4P24FHAERODREYDKGMDVA6O2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，比亚迪季度汽车销量自2020年以来首次下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社根据比亚迪周三发布的公司文件计算得出，比亚迪第三季度销量同比下降 2.1%，这是这家中国电动汽车和混合动力汽车制造商五年多来首次出现季度下滑。【原文：BYD's third-quarter sales fell 2.1% from a year earlier, according to Reuters' calculations based on a company filing released on Wednesday, the first quarterly decline for the Chinese EV and hybrid car maker in more than five years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byds-quarterly-car-sales-fall-first-time-since-2020-data-shows-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUZTOIJVVJNBZHLO7TI24XOMWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卫星初创公司 Spacecoin 通过太空发送数据，欲与 Starlink 竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国初创公司 Spacecoin 周三表示，它已成功地通过太空发送了安全信息，这在业内尚属首次。【原文：U.S. startup Spacecoin said on Wednesday it had successfully sent secured information through space in what it said was a first for the industry as the firm tries to show it can offer an alternative to Starlink's satellite internet service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/satellite-startup-spacecoin-sends-data-through-space-bid-rival-starlink-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJGZTOWZU5IOZBZRA66PTYJYC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:18:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[9 月美国制造业有望复苏，订单减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国制造业在 9 月份开始复苏，但新订单和就业情况不佳，因为工厂仍在努力应对进口关税带来的影响。【原文：U.S. manufacturing edged toward recovery in September, though new orders and employment were subdued as factories continued to grapple with the fallout from tariffs on imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-manufacturing-eyes-recovery-september-orders-contract-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHJTP7ZWDBLDLPURTKHRQIWZFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+"小组强调必须全面遵守石油产量限制规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克在会后发表的一份声明中说，欧佩克+小组在周三的在线会议上强调了全面遵守石油产出协议的必要性。【原文：An OPEC+ panel stressed the need for achieving full compliance with oil output agreements at its online meeting on Wednesday, OPEC said in a statement after the meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-panel-stresses-need-full-compliance-with-oil-output-limits-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJ7UJFWSA5NMZO2GCHHI3MPAVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>