<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:37:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:37:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在冬季风暴后取消 1,300 多个航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一场冬季风暴给美国广大地区带来了冰雪和严寒，美国航空公司取消了 1300 多个航班。【原文：Airlines in the United States canceled more than 1,300 flights on Monday after a winter storm brought snow, ice and freezing temperatures to a broad swath of the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-cancel-over-1300-flights-after-winter-storm-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2HEWCAEYNJU5NV4BMCUL7GYEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国交易所要求大型基金经理限制股票抛售]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士称，中国的主要证券交易所要求一些大型共同基金在今年年初限制股票抛售，因为中国政府正试图在世界第二大经济体进入困难时期之际安抚市场。【原文：China's main stock exchanges asked some large mutual funds to restrict stock selling at the start of the year, three sources familiar with the matter said, as authorities sought to calm markets heading into a tricky period for the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-exchanges-ask-big-fund-managers-restrict-stock-selling-sources-say-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYANKZA3OBM5BHXFJ6JOH5YLYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 08:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：加元平静，特鲁多走向出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LC6QE32U4JOGTOT4O4OBCKGHOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国争相支撑下滑的人民币和股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，中国的证券交易所和中央银行慌忙为暴跌的人民币和下跌的股市辩护，试图安抚对唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫和中国政府重振经济的能力感到担忧的投资者。【原文：China's stock exchanges and central bank scurried to defend a tumbling yuan and falling stock markets on Monday, trying to soothe investors concerned about Donald Trump's return to the White House and Beijing's ability to revive the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-scrambles-shore-up-sliding-yuan-stock-markets-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2IKPHPMUZMGLAL2Q4TUYNICPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街银行退出气候组织令倡导者担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周，美国的贷款机构急于退出全球银行业顶级气候联盟之一，这招致了运动人士的嘲讽，他们担心该行业正在失去对化石燃料采取行动的决心。【原文：U.S. lenders have been rushing in recent weeks to leave one of the world's top banking sector climate coalitions, drawing scorn from campaigners who worry the industry is losing resolve to take action on fossil fuels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/exodus-by-wall-street-banks-climate-group-worries-advocates-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6ICLM4U6BIT7IRTSBU7CLIHJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 05:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 要求富士软对贝恩 "违反 NDA "申请禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权基金 KKR 周一表示，已致函富士软公司，要求其向法院提起诉讼，以制止贝恩资本在贝恩和 KKR 争夺这家软件制造商的过程中违反保密协议的行为。【原文：U.S. private equity fund KKR said on Monday it sent a letter to Fuji Soft asking it to make a court filing to stop what it said was Bain Capital's violation of a non-disclosure agreement amid Bain and KKR's acquisition battle for the software maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-asks-fuji-soft-file-injunction-against-bains-breach-nda-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5JFS2Y5ZVKHTMUYCQHCWBLGXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:46:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡数据中心公司 Digital Edge 融资逾 16 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于新加坡的数据中心公司 Digital Edge 周一表示，该公司已通过股权和债务融资相结合的方式筹集了超过 16 亿美元的新资金，为下一阶段的发展提供资金。【原文：Singapore-headquartered data centre company Digital Edge said on Monday it had raised over $1.6 billion in new capital via a combination of equity and debt financing to fund its next phase of growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/singaporean-data-centre-company-digital-edge-raises-over-16-billion-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56X3RJUAJVKRFD67NIAXH7DRTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国吉利控股公司的目标是到 2027 年年销量超过 500 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国吉利控股集团（GEELY.UL）周日表示，该公司的目标是到2027年汽车年销量超过500万辆，比2023年有大幅提升。【原文：China's Geely Holding Group (GEELY.UL) on Sunday said it aims to sell more than 5 million vehicles annually by 2027, a big jump from 2023, which it hopes to achieve by accelerating consolidation of its sprawling brands and improving efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-geely-holding-targets-over-5-million-units-annual-sales-by-2027-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZXJEP7LBFOOBNQ6FCVO3HT5DM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新服务业采购经理人指数显示，中国服务业活动创 7 个月新高，但美国贸易担忧削弱了乐观情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项私营部门调查显示，受国内需求激增的推动，中国服务业活动在12月份以七个月来最快的速度扩张，但来自国外的订单却出现下降，这反映出经济面临的贸易风险正在增加。【原文：China's services activity expanded at the fastest pace in seven months in December, driven by a surge in domestic demand, but orders from abroad declined, reflecting growing trade risks to the economy, a private sector survey showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-services-activity-hits-7-month-high-us-trade-fears-dent-optimism-caixin-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F56KNVEFVZPVBFAZSJUO6RTJ54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:54:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受寒冷天气和中国刺激政策影响，石油价格徘徊于 10 月以来最高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者关注北半球寒冷天气和中国政府经济刺激措施对全球燃料需求的影响，周一油价徘徊在10月份以来的最高点。【原文：Oil prices hovered at their highest since October on Monday as investors eyed the impact on global fuel demand from colder weather in the Northern Hemisphere and Beijing's economic stimulus measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-hovers-highest-since-oct-cold-weather-china-stimulus-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I36AHCC2Q5PQVKC3YTPKP6NT3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国 LG CNS 启动首次公开募股（IPO），募集资金高达 8.17 亿美元，条款表显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的一份条款书显示，韩国 IT 服务提供商 LG CNS 周一开始簿记建档，计划在首次公开募股（IPO）中融资最多 8.17 亿美元。【原文：South Korean IT services provider LG CNS started bookbuilding on Monday to raise up to $817 million in an initial public offering (IPO), according to a term sheet reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/south-koreas-lg-cns-launches-ipo-up-817-mln-term-sheet-says-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FO63AMISGBI7ZOJJF47F3L64R4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元维持在两年高点附近；人民币受到威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美元离两年高点不远，交易员们在等待本周发布的一系列美国经济数据，其中最重要的是 12 月份的非农就业报告，以寻找有关美联储利率前景的进一步线索。【原文：The dollar strayed not too far from a two-year peak on Monday as traders awaited a raft of U.S. economic data releases this week, headlined by December's nonfarm payrolls report, for further clues on the Federal Reserve's rate outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-holds-near-two-year-high-yuan-under-threat-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USFEPR25DVOZJPNWWMQP7GFYHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本服务业活动因需求稳健而扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项私营部门调查显示，受需求稳健和业务扩张的推动，日本服务业活动在 12 月份连续第二个月出现扩张。【原文：Japan's service activity expanded for a second straight month in December, buoyed by solid demand and business expansion, a private-sector survey showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-service-activity-expands-solid-demand-pmi-shows-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYMF22MPUJKRTG6AOOBLDSD6PA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市谨慎，美元在大量数据公布前上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市开局谨慎，因为本周将有大量经济新闻发布，这些新闻应会凸显美国股市的相对优异表现，并支持美元继续走牛。【原文：Asian share markets got off to a wary start on Monday ahead of a week brimming with economic news that should underline the relative outperformance of the United States and support the dollar's ongoing bull run.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNQIWSKVDJITJDHM6NHBMYVUI4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 NTV 报道，新日铁总裁称起诉美国政府是一种选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[据日本电视台周一报道，在美国总统拜登（Joe Biden）阻止新日铁收购美国钢铁公司的提议后，新日铁总裁今井忠志（Tadashi Imai）表示，对美国政府提起诉讼是 "重要选择之一"。【原文：Nippon Steel President Tadashi Imai said filing a lawsuit against the U.S. government is one of the "important options", Nippon Television reported on Monday, after President Joe Biden blocked its proposed purchase of U.S. Steel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steel-president-says-suing-us-government-is-an-option-ntv-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAGMKGLSZBOW5KTF4LP66MG5AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标中国两年期收益率有望跌破 1.00]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HI7LQXM47ZKMLDOK3ZPNXQKYPQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Insignia 公司获得 CC Capital 18 亿美元的出价，超过贝恩的出价]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，Insignia Financial 公布了美国投资管理公司 CC Capital Partners 提出的 28.7 亿澳元（17.8 亿美元）收购要约，超过了贝恩资本提出的 26.7 亿澳元收购要约，股价创下三年新高。【原文：Insignia Financial shares shot to a three-year high on Monday after it revealed a A$2.87 billion ($1.78 billion) takeover bid from U.S.-based investment manager CC Capital Partners, eclipsing a A$2.67 billion offer from Bain Capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/australias-insignia-financial-receives-18-billion-takeover-offer-cc-capital-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3C4ZVFGC6JMMZINEIWNBV4K5QY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:46:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，意大利正在就价值 15 亿美元的 SpaceX 安全服务交易进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周日报道，意大利正与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX 公司就该公司向政府提供安全电信服务的 15 亿欧元（15.5 亿美元）交易进行深入谈判。【原文：Italy is in advanced talks with Elon Musk's SpaceX over a 1.5 billion euro ($1.55 billion) deal for the company to provide secure telecommunications to the government, Bloomberg News reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italy-plans-15-bln-spacex-telecom-security-services-deal-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUWV44HQJBLOPKXUAPS3U6E7MM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 19:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件指控：竞争对手首席执行官向华尔街散布对新日铁交易前景的疑虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在新日铁公司面临拜登政府对其 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司这一注定失败的出价的怀疑时，它还面临着来自一个不可能的来源的阻力：该公司竞争对手的首席执行官一再向投资者对该交易的前景表示怀疑。【原文：Even as Nippon Steel faced skepticism of its doomed $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel from the Biden administration, it was also contending with headwinds from an unlikely source: the CEO of a rival bidder for the firm who repeatedly cast doubt on the deal's prospects to investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/rival-ceo-spread-doubt-about-nippon-steel-deal-prospects-wall-street-documents-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHOR4NXNIBJVXOSL7RK7RKVWWY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 19:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》称，中国黑客入侵美国电信公司的数量超出此前已知范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周六晚间援引知情人士的话报道称，中国黑客入侵的美国电信公司比之前已知的还要多，其中包括 Charter Communications、Consolidated Communications (CCII.UL) 和 Windstream。【原文：A Chinese hack compromised even more U.S. telecoms than previously known, including Charter Communications , Consolidated Communications (CCII.UL) and Windstream, the Wall Street Journal reported late on Saturday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinese-hack-us-telecoms-compromised-more-firms-than-previously-known-wsj-says-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5FPBYWXLJK7PKYSDUQXABGIUU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 14:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司将于春季在航班上使用马斯克的 "星链 "技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周日表示，预计将于今年 2 月开始测试埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的星链（Starlink）机上互联网服务，并将于今年春季首次在巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）E-175 飞机运营的商业航班上提供这种连接。【原文：United Airlines said on Sunday it expects to begin testing Elon Musk's Starlink in February for in-flight internet services, and to first offer the connectivity on a commercial flight operated by Embraer E-175 aircraft this spring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-bring-musks-starlink-flights-by-spring-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6URIQHT3ORNNTFFL37NPXNNL3E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康第四季度营收增长 15.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约电子制造商、苹果公司最大的 iPhone 组装商台湾富士康周日发布报告称，其第四季度收入增长 15.2%，创下该季度历史新高。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker and Apple's biggest iPhone assembler, reported on Sunday that its fourth-quarter revenue jumped 15.2%, reaching a record high for the quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-fourth-quarter-revenue-up-152-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJFLDNQVUJJG7P6N45SS53RGCM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 07:48:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国寻求加强西部地区港口和航空枢纽建设]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周日表示，将推出 15 项措施，通过建设港口和航空枢纽等物流基础设施来促进西部省份的发展。【原文：China said on Sunday it would launch 15 measures to bolster the development of its western provinces with the construction of logistical infrastructure such as ports and aviation hubs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-seeks-bolster-ports-aviation-hubs-western-regions-2025-01-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPBOY5WSRBP35HG4LOKXCD6D6Y</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 05:42:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒和戴利称抑制通胀的工作尚未完成]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周六表示，美国经济在2024年结束时形势良好，通胀率从峰值回落，劳动力市场接近充分就业，但美国央行在抑制通胀方面的工作尚未完成。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler on Saturday said the U.S. economy ended 2024 in a good place, with inflation down from its peak and the labor market near full employment, but the U.S. central bank's job on taming inflation is not yet done.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-kugler-daly-say-job-not-done-taming-inflation-2025-01-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5S2H4IIPZJMCVIQRCBLWXV2RNY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 23:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机构援引俄罗斯工业部消息，2024 年俄罗斯新车销量将增长 47]]></title><description><![CDATA[据俄罗斯通讯社周六援引工业和贸易部数据报道，2024 年俄罗斯新乘用车销量同比增长 47%，达到 155 万辆。【原文：Sales of new passenger cars in Russia increased by 47% year on year to 1.55 million units in 2024, Russian news agencies reported on Saturday, citing industry and trade ministry data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/russias-new-car-sales-up-47-2024-agencies-cite-industry-ministry-2025-01-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YR27E2YRNNZXN2IBM2VNEPIRA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 08:56:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部敦促最高法院驳回特朗普推迟 TikTok 禁令的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五晚些时候请求最高法院驳回当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）关于推迟实施一项法律的请求，该法律将在 1 月 19 日前禁止流行社交媒体应用 TikTok 或强制其出售。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice asked the Supreme Court late on Friday to reject President-elect Donald Trump's request to delay implementation of a law that would ban popular social media app TikTok or force its sale by Jan. 19.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/doj-urges-supreme-court-reject-trump-request-delay-tiktok-ban-law-2025-01-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7E7MH6VJNZM4VMVVLUN5GOT6L4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒称数据将推动美联储在不确定性中做出政策选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周五表示，美国央行对2025年的经济表现并不确定，将让即将公布的经济数据来推动货币政策的走向。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said on Friday the U.S. central bank is uncertain about what the economy will deliver in 2025 and will let upcoming economic data drive the course of monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-kugler-says-data-will-drive-fed-policy-choices-amid-uncertainty-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WSWY6ABINPVPAU72W3JJDCND4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:35:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国冬季风暴可能导致停电，切断天然气供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[据能源分析师和可靠性协调员称，美国各地的冰冻天气和暴风雪可能会在未来一周内造成大规模停电，并使天然气需求达到冬季最高水平。【原文：Freezing weather and snow storms across the U.S. could cause massive power outages over the next week and boost natural gas demand to its highest levels of the winter, according to energy analysts and reliability coordinators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-winter-storms-could-cause-power-outages-cut-natgas-supplies-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6RFXOB6ZNIRNDIZIA2NIS4SKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 21:21:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[犹他州诉讼称，TikTok 知道其直播剥削儿童]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据犹他州最新公布的诉讼材料，TikTok 早就知道其视频直播鼓励性行为并剥削儿童，但却视而不见，因为它从中 "获利颇丰"。【原文：TikTok has long known its video livestreams encourage sexual conduct and exploit children yet turned a blind eye because it "profited significantly" from them, according to newly unsealed material in a lawsuit by the state of Utah.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tiktok-knew-its-livestreams-exploit-children-utah-lawsuit-claims-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2USF7LOOKBLPVGW6BB473XTUP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 20:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[房利美和房地美股价在联邦机构透露私有化路径后大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[房利美（Fannie Mae）和房地美（Freddie Mac）是自 2008 年以来受美国政府控制的抵押贷款巨头，在联邦机构公布了 "有序 "解除对它们的监管的框架后，这两家公司的股价周五飙升至多年来的新高。【原文：Shares of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac , the mortgage giants under U.S. government control since 2008, surged to multi-year highs on Friday after federal agencies revealed a framework for their "orderly" release from conservatorship.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fannie-mae-freddie-mac-shares-surge-after-federal-agencies-reveal-privatization-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASLMYDZTOROLXJ4GBKFKWUV6DA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:57:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>