<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 09:05:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 09:05:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[微软总裁在美国批评声中表示公司尊重欧洲法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软总裁布拉德-史密斯（Brad Smith）周三表示，微软尊重欧洲法律，包括旨在控制大科技公司权力的里程碑式立法，这使该公司与白宫产生了矛盾，后者批评了与欧盟规则有关的制裁。【原文：Microsoft respects European laws including landmark legislation seeking to rein in the power of Big Tech, its President Brad Smith said on Wednesday, putting the company at odds with the White House, which has criticised sanctions related to EU rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-president-says-company-respects-european-laws-amid-us-criticism-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXJ4EDNBR5LITJAWSMTXS74D7A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:44:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鉴于关税不确定性，芯片设计商联发科无法给出全年业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾顶级芯片设计公司联发科技（MediaTek）首席执行官周三表示，由于美国关税的不确定性，他无法给出全年盈利指导，但鉴于人工智能需求强劲，他总体上持乐观态度。【原文：The chief executive of Taiwan's top chip design company MediaTek said on Wednesday he was unable to give full-year earnings guidance due to uncertainty about U.S. tariffs, but that he was generally optimistic given strong AI demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chip-designer-mediatek-unable-give-full-year-outlook-given-tariff-uncertainty-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BT7MWBA6ROP7PGM4RUSY4NIQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:38:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易不确定性导致荷兰支付公司阿代恩第一季度销售额不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的支付公司之一阿代恩公司周三公布的季度收入低于市场预期，表明这家荷兰公司也未能幸免全球贸易紧张局势对经济活动及其客户的影响。【原文：Adyen , one of the world's largest payment companies, reported quarterly revenue below market expectations on Wednesday, showing the Dutch company was not immune to the impact of global trade tensions on economic activity and its clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dutch-payments-firm-adyens-first-quarter-sales-miss-forecasts-amid-trade-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RW23APGSPJM7PPDJGYG2J44TXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出口大增，台湾第一季度 GDP 初值创一年来最快增速]]></title><description><![CDATA[与 2024 年最后一个季度相比，2025 年第一季度台湾依赖贸易的经济增长速度达到一年来最快，这主要得益于在美国可能征收进口关税之前，科技需求强劲导致出口激增。【原文：Taiwan's trade-reliant economy grew at its fastest pace in a year in the first quarter of 2025 compared with the final quarter of 2024 thanks to an export surge on strong tech demand ahead of the introduction of possible U.S. import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-q1-preliminary-gdp-grows-fastest-year-exports-surge-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXBY4FG3MNKNBM6ZUDLMGADKBA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:26:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软公司布拉德-史密斯在美国批评声中表示公司尊重欧洲法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软总裁布拉德-史密斯（Brad Smith）周三表示，微软尊重欧洲法律，包括旨在控制大科技公司权力的里程碑式立法，这使该公司与白宫产生了矛盾，后者批评了与欧盟规则有关的制裁措施。【原文：Microsoft respects European laws including landmark legislation which seeks to rein in the power of Big Tech, its President Brad Smith said on Wednesday, putting the company at odds with the White House which has criticised sanctions related to EU rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsofts-brad-smith-says-company-respects-european-laws-amid-us-criticism-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK6XU34WEFM3XOYUSRSTJLIW3M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:21:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国第一季度经济增长 0.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国统计局周三发布的初步数据显示，2025 年第一季度德国国内生产总值与预期一致，与前三个月相比增长了 0.2%。【原文：Germany's gross domestic product rose in line with forecasts, by 0.2%, in the first quarter of 2025 compared with the previous three-month period, preliminary data from the statistics office showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/german-economy-grew-by-02-first-quarter-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBJDPYZXWFOVPPUN7NJTBYUXIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱茵金属公司与洛克希德马丁公司扩大合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国莱茵金属公司（Rheinmetall）和美国洛克希德-马丁公司（Lockheed Martin）周三在一份联合声明中表示，双方同意扩大合作，并延长于2024年签署的谅解备忘录的有效期。【原文：Germany's Rheinmetall and U.S. firm Lockheed Martin have agreed to expand their cooperation and extended a memorandum of understanding signed in 2024, they said in a joint statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rheinmetall-lockheed-martin-extend-cooperation-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3WEDW5L5ZIZNC5T6R5ZSCWQXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 07:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[漫威电影《雷霆战警*》在贸易战肆虐之际考验中国人对好莱坞的胃口]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪斯尼新片《雷霆战警》（Thunderbolts*）将于本周三在中国各地影院上映，成为新一轮贸易战爆发以来第一部在中国上映的美国电影，这将考验中国人对好莱坞大片的胃口。【原文：New Disney movie Thunderbolts* is poised to test Chinese appetite for Hollywood blockbusters as it opens in cinemas around China on Wednesday, making it the first American film to hit movie theatres in the country since a new trade war began.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/marvels-thunderbolts-test-chinese-appetite-hollywood-trade-war-rages-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42XNY2JQENOB7M23QGGJVBXAPU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 07:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本乐天公司高层表示将在印度投资至少 1 亿美元并增加招聘人数]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本乐天公司（Rakuten）的一位高层管理人员告诉路透社，该公司的目标是今年在印度投资至少 1 亿美元，并将员工人数增加 8%，以加强其全球业务。【原文：Japan's Rakuten aims to invest at least $100 million and increase its headcount by 8% in India this year to strengthen its global operations, a top executive of the internet conglomerate told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/japans-rakuten-invest-least-100-million-india-increase-hiring-top-executive-says-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGW42PMEJRI4PABMBGCVAR437U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 07:09:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aixtron 第一季度订单高于去年同期，称美国关税目前微不足道]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国芯片系统制造商爱思强（Aixtron）周三报告称，该公司季度订单量增长了10%，并坚持其全年业绩指引，称与美国关税政策相关的风险 "目前对该行业来说微不足道"。【原文：German chip systems manufacturer Aixtron on Wednesday reported a 10% increase in quarterly orders and stood by its full-year guidance, saying the risks associated with U.S. tariffs policy were "currently insignificant for the sector".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/aixtron-q1-orders-above-last-year-says-us-tariffs-currently-insignificant-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVPYYAQ55ZNLFH27I3RVWWQBL4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:58:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可口可乐公司（Coca-Cola HBC）季度收入增长超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受主要新兴市场强劲需求的支撑，装瓶商可口可乐公司（Coca-Cola HBC AG）第一季度有机收入增长超出市场预期。【原文：Bottler Coca-Cola HBC AG beat market expectations for first-quarter organic revenue growth on Wednesday, supported by strong demand in its key emerging markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coca-cola-hbc-beats-quarterly-revenue-growth-estimates-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36XRIPSJYRPGJE2H6EM7SNGUJM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对中国出口废食用油征收关税，中国出口废食用油转向欧洲]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士表示，由于关税过高，中国对其最大买家美国的废食用油（UCO）出口量在未来几个月内将大幅下降，迫使卖家将货物转运至欧洲和其他地区。【原文：China's used cooking oil (UCO) exports to the United States, its largest buyer, are set to plunge in coming months due to steep tariffs, forcing sellers to divert shipments to Europe and elsewhere, industry players said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/china-pivots-europe-used-cooking-oil-exports-tariffs-hit-shipments-us-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2AEPBYSQ5NZ7F4VNJZUNXRAZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:41:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司第一季度利润因油价下跌和炼油利润率疲软而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国石油巨头道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）周三报告称，第一季度调整后净收入下降 17%，降至 42 亿美元，此前油价下跌，欧洲炼油燃料的利润率难以从 2024 年的急剧下滑中恢复过来。【原文：French oil major TotalEnergies reported a 17% drop in adjusted net income for the first quarter to $4.2 billion on Wednesday, after oil prices fell and margins for refining fuels in Europe struggled to recover from a steep collapse in 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/totalenergies-q1-profits-fall-lower-oil-prices-weak-refining-margins-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPEKVCJX6NMQDMDEO2DXSUOS4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯顿-马丁限制美国出口以应对特朗普关税，季度亏损收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[豪华汽车制造商阿斯顿-马丁（Aston Martin）周三表示，该公司正在限制对美国的出口，以抵消唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的关税影响。【原文：Luxury carmaker Aston Martin said on Wednesday it was limiting exports to the U.S. to offset impact from President Donald Trump's tariffs, and reported a narrower-than-expected first-quarter loss on lower expenses and higher average prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/aston-martin-posts-narrower-than-expected-quarterly-loss-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7B33JVIL5KATLSUQNESP4U6T4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:18:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱第一季度利润增长 19%，得益于固定收益交易狂潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行周三公布，由于今年前三个月疯狂的交易活动推动了投资银行业务收入和交易费用的增长，其第一季度利润增长了 19%，好于预期。【原文：Barclays reported its first quarter profit rose a better than expected 19% on Wednesday, as frenzied trading activity in the first three months of the year boosted investment banking revenue and dealmaking fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-posts-19-rise-q1-profit-beating-expectations-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LB3IHSFBDZMOLKDIAYZSQKXWYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:16:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国葛兰素史克公司称 "已做好准备 "应对可能的医药关税冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国制药商葛兰素史克（GSK）表示，如果特定行业关税实施，该公司已 "做好充分准备 "应对任何潜在影响，并已在其供应链和生产力举措中确定了减轻任何冲击的方案。【原文：British drugmaker GSK said it was "well positioned" to respond to any potential impact from sector-specific tariffs if they were implemented and it had identified options within its supply chain and productivity initiatives to mitigate any hit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/british-drugmaker-gsk-says-well-positioned-absorb-tariff-hit-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TV5ZSZVIF5PZDCSVDQSYGF4LY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Equinor 抨击特朗普政府叫停美国大型海上风电项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[Equinor 周三表示，该公司认为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府决定停止一个价值数十亿美元的海上风电项目的建设是非法的，该集团可能会采取法律行动。【原文：Equinor on Wednesday said it believes the decision of U.S. President Donald Trump's administration to halt the construction of a multi-billion dollar offshore wind power project is unlawful and that the group may take legal action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/equinor-slams-trump-administrations-halt-major-us-offshore-wind-project-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZIZJKOOPRI6LJZYULGLC3XEVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普关税影响，沃尔沃汽车新任首席执行官求助于中国所有者吉利汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税压力下，沃尔沃汽车公司新任首席执行官哈坎-塞缪尔森（Hakan Samuelsson）既要与中国大股东吉利汽车公司[RIC:RIC:GEELY.UL]合作削减成本，又要设法继续向美国消费者销售汽车。【原文：Under pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, Volvo Cars' new CEO Hakan Samuelsson is juggling the task of working with Chinese majority owner Geely [RIC:RIC:GEELY.UL] to cut costs with attempting to keep selling cars to U.S consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/troubled-by-trumps-tariffs-volvo-cars-new-ceo-turns-chinese-owner-geely-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QX52OXULXRPIXPYXZ6LSGNFFDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税不确定性影响，Stellantis 暂停全年业绩预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 公司周三表示，在 2024 年利润下降之后，由于美国关税政策演变的不确定影响，该公司将暂停今年温和复苏的指导。【原文：Stellantis said on Wednesday it was suspending its guidance for a moderate recovery this year, after a profit drop in 2024, due to the uncertain impact of evolving U.S. tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-suspends-full-year-forecasts-due-us-tariff-uncertainties-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQVJBAJXBNMUDNV37OTU27KH4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国物流集团 DHL 第一季度盈利增长，但对贸易持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国物流公司 DHL 周三公布了第一季度的销售额和盈利增长情况。【原文：German logistics company DHL on Wednesday posted higher sales and earnings in the first quarter, a period dominated by tensions over U.S. import tariffs that could both help and hinder the group's bottom line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/german-logistics-group-dhl-posts-higher-earnings-q1-cautious-trade-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTJBO3UYARPAFOIEQBSDBS373Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人头马君度称美国干邑销量反弹，中国市场疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国烈酒集团人头马君度（Remy Cointreau）周三公布的第四季度销售额未达预期，但该公司表示，关键的美国市场出现了 "急剧复苏"，该市场拖累公司业绩已长达一年多。【原文：French spirits group Remy Cointreau missed fourth quarter sales forecasts on Wednesday, but said it saw a "steep recovery" in the critical U.S. market, which has been dragging on performance for over a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/remy-cointreaus-us-sales-back-growth-q4-china-stays-weak-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJJFUFPTXVLS5CCCL2IZ6ZXA5Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:50:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[永不下跪中国利用朝鲜战争和人工智能备忘录回击特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国正在利用其宣传机器对美国的关税进行反击，利用冷战时期的形象推出视频，抨击 "帝国主义者"，并传达一个简单的信息--向恶霸屈服是危险的，我们不会退缩。【原文：China is leveraging its propaganda machine to hit back at U.S. tariffs, rolling out videos using Cold War imagery to lambaste "imperialists" and send a simple message - capitulation to bullies is dangerous, and we won't back down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/never-kneel-china-taps-korean-war-ai-memes-hit-back-trump-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRTCQQIYNVM6XE7EYMBHL5DUZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世创电子材料下调全年核心利润率目标，但确认销售前景，尽管美国仍将加征关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国半导体材料供应商世创电子材料（Siltronic）周三下调了其年度核心利润率预期，理由是预计长期协议之外的价格会带来负面影响，但确认了全年销售指导，称目前还无法估计美国关税的影响。【原文：German semiconductor materials supplier Siltronic on Wednesday cut its annual core profit margin forecast, citing expected negative price effects outside of long-term agreements, but confirmed full-year sales guidance, saying it's not yet possible to estimate the impact of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siltronic-cuts-full-year-core-profit-margin-target-confirms-sales-outlook-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEMIFSQCSVM7XGM6Q65DP3RI7Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车称贸易紧张局势和电动汽车成本将拖累利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司周三表示，预计全年营业利润将低于预期，这是汽车行业在面临关税不确定性的情况下，又一家下调业绩展望的汽车制造商。【原文：Volkswagen said on Wednesday it expects annual operative profit at the bottom end of its forecast, the latest carmaker to dampen its outlook as an industry already pressured by costs and competition grapples with tariff uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-says-trade-tensions-ev-costs-weigh-profits-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6W4VLKDN5NNBHNFSNJ7EZAFGSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于关税影响，奔驰第一季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰（Mercedes-Benz）周三报告称，第一季度汽车业务利润率下降，并警告称关税可能会影响其全年收益，贸易紧张局势迫使这家豪华汽车制造商取消了对前景的展望。【原文：Mercedes-Benz on Wednesday reported lower profitability in its cars business in the first quarter and warned that tariffs could impact its full-year earnings, as trade tensions forced the luxury carmaker to scrap its outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-reports-less-profitable-cars-segment-q1-tariffs-bite-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3FMVMYUKVIM7EPLOJGWRPHEJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:12:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲国防初创企业如何吸引人工智能人才]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些曾经可能前往美国的欧洲科技工作者正在考虑就近创办防务初创企业。还有一些人则从海外工作岗位赶回欧洲。【原文：Some European tech workers who might once have headed to the United States are looking at defence startups closer to home. Others are rushing back to Europe from jobs abroad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mission-before-money-how-europes-defence-startups-are-luring-ai-talent-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXB6VVMEZRLHNPHV4LU6VKV3W4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街混乱冲击欧洲，投资者寻求新的关税保护市场利基]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国政策冲击引发欧洲经济增长风险的一个月里，投资者纷纷撤离华尔街，将目光转向拉美货币和金矿股等利基市场，以求摆脱贸易焦虑。【原文：Investors who rushed out of Wall Street during a month of U.S. policy shocks that raised European growth risks are turning their attention to niche markets such as Latin American currencies and gold mining stocks in a new bid to out-run trade angst.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-investors-analysis-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBBRO2U6PZICRADMYVWFOPKGX4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发市场波动，瑞银第一季度利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行瑞银集团（UBS）周三公布的第一季度净利润好于预期，主要得益于美国关税动荡后市场动荡导致的交易收益增加，该行称这可能会推迟企业交易。【原文：Swiss bank UBS on Wednesday posted better than expected first-quarter net profit, helped by stronger earnings in trading driven by market turbulence in the wake of U.S. tariff turmoil, which it said could delay corporate deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-1q-profit-tops-expectations-tariff-driven-volatility-markets-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMSKX6XCP5N3PHRBIKPE5KYSEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:55:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙 Caixabank 第一季度净利润增长 46%，银行业税收影响降低]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙储蓄银行（Caixabank）周三表示，与 2024 年同期相比，该银行第一季度净利润增长了 46%，原因是银行税重新征收带来的影响降低，抵消了利率下降导致的贷款收入减少。【原文：Spain's Caixabank on Wednesday said its net profit rose 46% in the first quarter compared to the same period in 2024 as a lower impact from the renewed banking tax offset a drop in lending income caused by lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/caixabanks-first-quarter-net-profit-rises-46-same-period-2024-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBAAQAODQJPANEXZW3EXIPXGPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 数据潮为动荡的四月画上句号]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYTP6PWL4ZOBLHISJZQ64SCSBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>