<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:14:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:14:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望财报密集周，就业数据将考验美股走势，微软股价暴跌后市场承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[在科技巨头微软发布令人失望的财报拖累股市指数后，包括谷歌母公司Alphabet和亚马逊在内的又一批巨额企业财报，将在未来一周考验美国股市。【原文：Another huge batch of corporate earnings including from megacaps Alphabet and Amazon will test the U.S. stock market in the coming week after a disappointing report ​from heavyweight Microsoft weighed on equity indexes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-heavy-earnings-week-jobs-data-test-us-stocks-after-microsoft-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJEH2BRVPBOMXNX5BCTNNXU2VA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:06:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价预计将维持在每桶60美元附近，因供应过剩抵消了地缘政治风险的影响。]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五公布的调查显示，由于市场供应过剩的前景抵消了地缘政治紧张局势可能导致的货运中断影响，今年油价可能维持在每桶60美元附近。【原文：Oil prices are likely to hold near the $60 a barrel mark this year, as the prospect of oversupply in the market offsets the impact of geopolitical tensions that could disrupt cargoes, a Reuters poll showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-forceast-hover-near-60bbl-oversupply-outweighs-geopolitical-risks-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUL6TTSVJBKPFILNSIC3IWQWWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta因儿童剥削指控面临新墨西哥州诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms将于下周面临新墨西哥州提起的诉讼审判，该州指控其在平台上使儿童和青少年暴露于性剥削风险并从中牟利。这是首例针对这家社交媒体巨头的同类案件进入陪审团审理阶段。【原文：Meta Platforms is set to face trial next week in a lawsuit brought by the state of New Mexico accusing it of exposing children and teens to sexual exploitation on its platforms and profiting from it, the first case of its kind against the social media giant to reach a jury.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/meta-faces-new-mexico-trial-over-child-exploitation-claims-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBAZSIIDSJMXHO6IN7QJGOOVD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下跌，特朗普即将宣布美联储主席人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周五下跌，此前美国总统唐纳德·特朗普表示已确定美联储主席人选，有报道称前美联储理事凯文·沃什很可能成为其选择。【原文：U.S. stock index futures ​slid on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he has firmed up his choice to ‌lead the Federal Reserve, with reports suggesting that former central bank governor Kevin Warsh would be his likely pick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-fall-trump-set-announce-fed-chair-pick-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJ6YW4SSY5J7DDCEHXCJWIRLYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:27:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着油价飙升，欧佩克+计划将暂停增产措施延续至3月]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位代表向路透社透露，欧佩克+联盟很可能在周日的会议上维持暂停增产的决定，尽管受美国可能对欧佩克成员国伊朗发动军事打击的担忧影响，原油价格已攀升至每桶70美元以上。【原文：OPEC+ is likely to keep its pause on oil output increases for March when it meets on Sunday, five delegates told Reuters, even as crude climbs above $70 a barrel on concern the U.S. could launch a military strike on OPEC member Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-set-keep-oil-production-pause-march-prices-jump-sources-say-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKBCZZM7MZKADL7XF2MQHR3OZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:19:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，LVMH集团旗下干邑品牌轩尼诗已与工人达成薪酬协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[路威酩轩集团旗下干邑品牌轩尼诗——该集团规模最大的酒类品牌——已与工会达成薪酬协议，以补偿因去年销售疲软而损失的奖金，两名消息人士向路透社透露。【原文：LVMH's cognac maker Hennessy, the largest of its drink brands, has reached a pay deal with unions to compensate for bonuses lost last year due to weak sales, two sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/lvmhs-cognac-brand-hennessy-reaches-pay-deal-with-workers-sources-say-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGLNYQSEK5NBBIQKMJRX3NOGZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本外贸数据表明，其外汇市场干预仅限于口头警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[官方数据显示，日本政府上周未干预外汇市场，证实其捍卫日元的努力仅限于口头警告。【原文：Japan ​refrained from intervening in currency markets through last week, official data showed on ‌Friday, confirming that the government's efforts to defend the yen have been limited to verbal warnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-fx-market-intervention-limited-verbal-warnings-mof-data-shows-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3ELEHT6FNOIVCQ4ZVCIMBN4RI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博世警告2026年成本压力将加剧，推迟利润率目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大汽车零部件供应商博世（Bosch）周五警告称，2026年将面临又一个艰难年景，并推迟了实现7%利润率的目标。该公司预计，在全球关税冲击下，该行业的成本和竞争压力不会缓解。【原文：Bosch (ROBG.UL), the world's largest car parts supplier, on Friday warned of another tough year in 2026 and postponed a 7% margin target as it expects no let-up in cost and competitive pressure in a sector hit by tariffs worldwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bosch-warns-rising-cost-pressure-2026-delays-margin-target-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SX3B4G5OEFNB7ILEPEPPV3YSQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧元区经济2025年以稳健增长收官，尽管出口低迷且与美国贸易摩擦不断]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟统计局周五公布的数据显示，欧元区上季度经济增速超出预期，消费和投资加速增长抵消了出口疲软及美国贸易政策引发的特殊不确定性。【原文：The euro zone economy grew quicker than expected last quarter as consumption and investments kicked into higher gear, offsetting low exports and the exceptional uncertainty emanating from U.S. trade policy, Eurostat data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/euro-zone-economy-ends-2025-solid-footing-confirming-resilience-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK7N3SAKBBPZ7JH5UN2BGMBYGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰监管机构将调查Roblox平台对未成年人的风险问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰消费者保护监管机构ACM周五宣布，已对美国游戏平台Roblox展开调查，因其可能对欧盟未成年用户构成风险。【原文：The Netherlands' consumer protection regulator ​ACM has launched an investigation ‌into U.S. gaming platform Roblox over potential risks to underage users in the European Union, it said ‌on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/dutch-regulator-probe-roblox-over-risks-minors-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEX5FS2RZZMPDAQEXPCLT7TKYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:03:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[益博睿宣布10亿美元股票回购计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用数据与分析公司益博睿周五宣布启动一项新的10亿美元股票回购计划。【原文：Credit data and analytics company Experian on Friday announced the launch of a new $1 billion share repurchase programme.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/experian-unveils-1-billion-share-buyback-plan-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCQ6QPKKJ5OIDOQ76KKXVOJV64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:14:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国财政部长称，法国政府阻止了欧卫通信公司出售地面天线。]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国财政部长罗兰·莱斯库尔周五表示，他本周早些时候决定阻止法国卫星运营商欧卫通信（Eutelsat）——该企业是埃隆·马斯克旗下星链（Starlink）的竞争对手——出售地面天线，这些设备可实现与卫星的通信。【原文：French Finance Minister Roland Lescure said on Friday he had decided earlier this week to prevent French satellite operator Eutelsat , a rival to Elon Musk's Starlink, from selling ground antennas, which enable communication with satellites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/france-prevented-eutelsat-selling-ground-antennas-finance-minister-says-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3RWRFWLHBKOFBV254A6NSP3UU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：中国有条件批准DeepSeek收购英伟达H200芯片——消息人士透露]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，中国已批准顶级人工智能初创企业DeepSeek购买英伟达H200人工智能芯片，但监管条件仍在最终敲定中。【原文：China has given its top AI startup DeepSeek approval to buy Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips with regulatory conditions that are still being finalised, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-conditionally-approves-deepseek-buy-nvidias-h200-chips-sources-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FEZKY73N7RMWLKZACNKQUIZM2U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储提名将于周五公布，此前他在白宫会见了沃什]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普会见了前美联储理事凯文·沃什。这位美联储批评者曾表示，美国央行需要进行"体制变革"才能重获丧失的公信力。【原文：President Donald Trump met with former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, a Fed critic who has ​said the U.S. central bank needs "regime change" to regain lost credibility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-fed-pick-due-friday-after-meeting-warsh-white-house-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7EGWF7PZJI5BNI7MMFMCOYOIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经亚洲报道：苹果将在内存短缺背景下优先于2026年推出高端iPhone机型]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经亚洲周刊周五援引四位知情人士的消息报道称，苹果公司正优先推进2026年三款最高端iPhone机型的生产和发货，同时推迟标准机型的上市，此举源于营销策略调整及供应链限制。【原文：Apple is prioritizing production and shipment of its three highest-end iPhone models ​for 2026 while delaying the rollout of its standard ‌model due to a marketing strategy shift and supply-chain constraints, Nikkei Asia reported on Friday, citing four people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-prioritize-premium-iphone-launches-2026-nikkei-asia-reports-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOMF6VFYMFMWVN3OHWDOJ5FPSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞拍：小心你所祈求的]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔·斯图尔特·亨特带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFDJOWSVI5KW7ASZ6R52VMEPCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚表示，美国放弃最低价格要求不会影响其关键矿产战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚周五表示，将在美国放弃为关键矿产项目提供最低价格保障计划后，支持本国关键矿产供应链建设。【原文：Australia on Friday said it would support its critical mineral supply chains after the U.S. stepped back from plans to guarantee a minimum price for such projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-says-us-price-floor-backdown-wont-derail-its-critical-minerals-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVP7PVVK2NL55DLY7BAGAFW27M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币下跌，美联储主席猜测冲击风险资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币周五跌至两个月低点，因市场猜测美国联邦储备委员会下任主席可能收紧金融体系中的现金供应，打压加密货币并推高美元汇率。【原文：Bitcoin slumped to a two-month low on Friday as speculation the next chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve might tighten up on cash ​in the financial system hit cryptocurrencies and lifted the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-slips-fed-chair-speculation-hits-risky-assets-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMRNL647C5MC5J4JWLVIOY4H4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于欧元的一切：向欧洲央行提出的五个问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行将于下周四召开会议，政策制定者们松了一口气，因为特朗普总统要求购买格陵兰岛引发的美国加征新关税的威胁已然消退。【原文：The European Central Bank meets next Thursday with policymakers relieved that the threat of fresh U.S. tariffs over President Donald Trump's demands to buy Greenland proved short-lived.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/all-about-euro-five-questions-ecb-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUMCNDT4BJMTJGSMVP6E5Q3BOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名美联储人选以缓解市场不确定性，各方目光聚焦沃什]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普总统提名的美联储主席人选将驱散笼罩市场数月的不确定性阴云，为投资者预示杰罗姆·鲍威尔任期于五月结束后货币政策可能的发展方向。【原文：President Donald Trump's nomination to head the U.S. Federal ​Reserve will lift a cloud of uncertainty that has hung over markets for months, giving investors a signal ‌of how monetary policy may evolve once Jerome Powell's term ends in May.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-fed-nomination-ease-market-uncertainty-all-eyes-warsh-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPUWBV6YQBORNLVGPP6EJUAJLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时快讯：特朗普将于周五宣布美联储主席人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周四表示，他计划于周五宣布接替美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的人选，外界猜测该职位将由前美联储理事凯文·沃什接任。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday he intends to announce his pick to replace Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday, with speculation intensifying that the nod will go to former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/view-trump-announce-his-fed-chief-pick-friday-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUUMMXW5ZNKT3CIWPRRSEAOVTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:16:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴拿马法院宣告和记黄埔港口合约无效]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马最高法院周四晚间宣布，因违宪而撤销香港和记黄埔旗下子公司持有的关键港口合同，导致巴拿马运河沿线运营前景不明。【原文：Panama's Supreme Court late on Thursday annulled key port contracts held by a subsidiary of Hong Kong-based CK Hutchison because they were unconstitutional, leaving the future of operations along the Panama Canal unclear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/panama-court-voids-ck-hutchison-port-contracts-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4WMBQBD6BKVBHG77MIGSCGGNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:13:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金价暴跌，因市场押注美联储新主席将采取更强硬立场；金价有望创下1980年以来最佳月度表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五金价因市场传闻美联储可能迎来更鹰派的主席而下跌逾4%，但受持续的地缘政治和经济紧张局势推动，投资者纷纷涌向避险资产，金价仍有望录得1980年以来最强劲的月度涨幅。【原文：Gold slid more than 4% on Friday on rumours the Federal Reserve could get a more hawkish chair, but was still on track for its strongest monthly gain since 1980 as investors flocked to the safe haven amid lingering geopolitical and economic strains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/gold-slips-firmer-dollar-set-best-month-since-1980-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NANCZGKRT5I3FGNWTKDV7FRBP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 02:04:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前美联储理事沃什周四会见了特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位知情人士透露，前美联储理事凯文·沃什周四前往白宫，与美国总统唐纳德·特朗普举行会晤。【原文：Former Federal Reserve Governor Kevin Warsh ​came to the ‌White House for a meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump ‌on Thursday, according one ​source familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/former-fed-governor-warsh-met-with-trump-thursday-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TY3JJEIHZPINCVM6HBD5XRBTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 02:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[闪迪预测利润激增，在人工智能推动存储需求之际达成供应协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，闪迪公司预测其利润和销售额将远超华尔街预期，并延长了一项重大供应协议，这得益于人工智能驱动的数据存储需求激增。【原文：Sandisk on Thursday predicted profits and sales well above Wall Street estimates and extended a major supply agreement, riding a surge in artificial-intelligence-driven demand for data storage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sandisk-forecasts-profit-surge-secures-supply-deal-ai-fuels-storage-demand-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">345TN7QQMFP25JMH3JDPS6LMGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:48:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市震荡，有望创三年来最佳月度表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲早盘股市震荡，此前美国总统特朗普支持两党达成协议以避免政府再次停摆，并表示已决定提名谁来领导美联储。【原文：Stocks were volatile in early Asian trading on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump ​endorsed a bipartisan deal to avert a fresh government shutdown and said he has decided who he will nominate to lead the ‌Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3ATZEGN3NJN5AQM75EU4EEAI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价徘徊于数月高位附近，因特朗普考虑对伊朗采取军事打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着中东局势因美国可能对伊朗发动袭击而升级，可能导致该地区最大欧佩克产油国之一的石油供应中断，周五油价正朝着数年来的最大月度涨幅迈进。【原文：Oil prices are headed for their biggest monthly gains in years on Friday as tensions in the Middle East escalated over a possible U.S. attack on Iran that could disrupt supplies from one of the biggest OPEC producers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-hovers-near-multi-month-highs-trump-considers-iran-strike-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMSQLNG475PHFMHXTNUXYWDUQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:46:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼证券交易所首席执行官在800亿美元市场暴跌后辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼证券交易所周五宣布，该交易所负责人已辞职。此前指数提供商MSCI警告可能下调印尼指数评级，引发逾800亿美元的股市暴跌，其影响仍在持续发酵。【原文：The head of Indonesia's stock exchange has resigned, the exchange said on Friday, as the consequences of a warning from index provider MSCI of a possible downgrade that triggered a more than $80 billion market rout continue to reverberate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-markets-face-cautious-open-after-msci-warning-sparks-80-billion-rout-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQUSQLZFHZNPFJILZXQJV2HCCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国将取消庞巴迪环球快车认证，直至加拿大认证湾流飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周四表示，美国将取消对庞巴迪环球快车公务机的认证，并威胁对加拿大制造的其他飞机征收50%的进口关税，直至加拿大对美国竞争对手湾流公司生产的若干机型予以认证。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday the U.S. was decertifying Bombardier Global Express business jets and threatened 50% import tariffs on other aircraft made in Canada until the country certified a number of planes produced by U.S. rival Gulfstream.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trump-says-us-decertifying-bombardier-global-express-until-canada-certifies-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQSDAPYF3ZMZVCWY5X7TGPSQEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元料将录得周线下跌，因全球紧张局势加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五可能连续第二周下跌，因针对与古巴有贸易往来国家的关税威胁加剧了全球紧张局势，削弱了对美国资产的需求。【原文：The dollar was poised for a second straight weekly decline on Friday as tariff threats against countries trading with Cuba added to global tensions that have sapped demand for U.S. ​assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-poised-weekly-slide-global-tensions-rise-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CB77DKGYJRKVJIWCWNCW6YH25Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:11:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>