<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:05:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:05:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[从牛肉和猪肉到鳄梨和龙舌兰酒，特朗普关税可能会提高食品和酒类价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[农业经济学家和行业高管表示，如果当选总统唐纳德-特朗普落实对来自墨西哥和加拿大的商品加征关税的计划，明年美国鳄梨、草莓和其他新鲜农产品的价格可能会上涨，消费者可能会面临短缺。【原文：U.S. prices may rise next year for avocados, strawberries and other fresh produce, and consumers could face shortages, if President-elect Donald Trump follows through on plans to slap tariffs on goods from Mexico and Canada, agricultural economists and industry executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-tariffs-could-raise-grocery-liquor-bills-beef-pork-avocados-tequila-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMXC64JIONPXXCLR4MM27ICYFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通：夹在经济巨头之间的新兴市场面临艰难的 2025 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）在其年度展望报告中称，由于美国政策的转变和中国增长的不确定性，新兴市场将迎来艰难而不确定的一年，并预测新兴市场债券基金将出现大规模资金外流。【原文：Emerging markets are in for a tough and uncertain year due to policy shifts in the United States and uncertain growth in China, JPMorgan said in its annual outlook, predicting emerging markets bond funds were in line for sizeable outflows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging-markets-caught-between-economic-giants-face-tough-2025-jpmorgan-says-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIN4IUVJSBPCLDNLGLDLDGUHSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:34:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Twinkie制造商Hostess监督小肯尼迪的反糖、反包装食品议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：Twinkie maker JM Smucker is planning to monitor and assess any changes in food and nutrition regulations that Robert F. Kennedy Jr. could implement as President-elect Donald Trump's potential top health agency head.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/twinkie-maker-hostess-monitoring-rfk-jrs-anti-sugar-anti-packaged-food-agenda-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PW62A2OYJM33GX5D7VVLALR2Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:23:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币期权交易显示，在未能突破 100,000 美元后，有更多人押注回撤]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一家加密货币交易平台援引最近的期权活动称，在比特币未能达到 10 万美元的历史峰值后，全球最大加密货币的投资者预计比特币将大幅下行。【原文：Investors in the world's largest cryptocurrency are anticipating a significant downward move after bitcoin failed to hit an all-time peak of $100,000, according to a crypto trading platform citing recent options activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-options-trade-shows-more-bets-retreat-after-failing-breach-100000-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJZZKDNEEFNONBJVSOBTEMLRAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:22:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[削减国税局资金将增加美国赤字，减缓服务速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部副部长瓦利-阿德耶莫（Wally Adeyemo）周二表示，国会共和党人长期以来一直希望削减国内税收署的经费，这将在十年内使联邦赤字增加 1400 亿美元，并会减缓服务速度，减少对大公司的复杂审计。【原文：Cuts in funding for the Internal Revenue Service, long eyed by Republicans in Congress, would increase the federal deficit by $140 billion over a decade, slow service and reduce complex audits of big companies, Deputy Treasury Secretary Wally Adeyemo said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/irs-funding-cut-would-increase-us-deficit-slow-service-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAUJIE6LX5O6VFEHSCXFL4EFSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:18:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储以波动性和对中性利率的疑虑为由放缓宽松政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本月早些时候的会议上，美联储官员在他们可能需要将利率下调多少的问题上出现了分歧，但作为一个整体，他们一致认为这是一个避免就未来几周美国货币政策可能如何演变给出太多具体指导的时刻。【原文：Federal Reserve officials appeared divided at their meeting earlier this month over how much farther they may need to cut interest rates, but as a group agreed this was a moment to avoid giving much concrete guidance about how U.S. monetary policy is likely to evolve in the weeks ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-cites-volatility-doubts-about-neutral-rate-reasons-go-slow-easing-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGAQF3MIAJNVJKHQMBIFH5JDWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称，特朗普将根据贸易计划对来自墨西哥和加拿大的石油征收 25% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉该计划的消息人士周二告诉路透社，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普计划在上任首日对加拿大和墨西哥进口商品征收 25% 的关税，但原油不在贸易惩罚之列。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's plan to impose 25% tariffs on Canadian and Mexican imports in his first day in office does not exempt crude oil from the trade penalties, two sources familiar with the plan told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-would-impose-25-tariffs-oil-mexico-canada-under-trade-plan-sources-say-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPZRBY5JPJLHBHK4SZ4MZ3QNGM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔能源首席执行官表示，暂停对阿达尼绿色公司的投资，等待贿赂案的澄清]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国道达尔能源集团（TotalEnergies）首席执行官帕特里克-普瓦纳（Patrick Pouyanne）周二表示，在美国起诉印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）的贿赂案有进一步进展之前，道达尔能源将暂停对其阿达尼绿色能源项目的投资。【原文：TotalEnergies will pause investment in its Adani Green energy project until there is further clarity on a U.S. bribery case against Indian billionaire Gautam Adani, the French group's CEO, Patrick Pouyanne, said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/totalenergies-pauses-us-offshore-wind-project-after-trump-victory-ceo-says-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNMEJZ5MVJIAFH6YEVSEJROEDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构批准 T-Mobile 和 SpaceX 许可证，将覆盖范围扩大到死亡区域]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（Federal Communications Commission）周二表示，已批准 T-Mobile 和埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX Starlink 公司从太空提供补充覆盖，以将互联网接入扩展到偏远地区。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission said on Tuesday it has approved a license for T-Mobile and Elon Musk's SpaceX Starlink unit to provide supplemental coverage from space in a bid to extend internet access to remote areas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-agency-approves-t-mobile-spacex-license-extend-coverage-dead-zones-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYNQNXLVKBJ4PHOCB5DJKGM3GU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国谷歌搜索反垄断审判不会因特朗普司法部修改提案而改期]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位负责监督美国司法部起诉谷歌网络搜索反垄断案的法官表示，4月份就恢复市场竞争的建议进行的审判不会因为特朗普政府官员决定做出的任何改变而改期。【原文：A judge overseeing the U.S. Department of Justice's antitrust case against Google over online searches said an April trial on proposals to restore competition in the market will not be rescheduled to accommodate any changes Trump administration officials decide to make.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-google-search-antitrust-trial-will-not-be-rescheduled-trumps-doj-revise-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2KYT6XFCRJWNGGPHN7E5HJKAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普获胜后，企业加强货币对冲，关税迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[跨国公司正在加强其外汇套期保值策略，以保护其海外收益免受唐纳德-特朗普第二任总统任期内可能出现的更大货币波动的影响。【原文：Multinational companies are beefing up their foreign exchange hedging strategies to guard their overseas earnings from larger currency swings that could come from a second Donald Trump presidency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/companies-bolster-currency-hedges-after-trump-win-tariffs-loom-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3LN2YXGERM75L3H4XKYXXNLZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:56:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街银行从以色列货币和债券交易中获益]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的数据显示，由于长达 14 个月的中东战争造成的波动，世界顶级投资银行在以色列债券和货币交易方面的收入有望达到五年来的最高水平。【原文：The world's top investment banks are on track to post the highest revenue in five years from trading Israel's bonds and currency thanks to the volatility caused by the 14-month long war in the Middle East, data seen by Reuters show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wall-street-banks-get-lift-trading-israeli-currency-bonds-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X52PBA6TWNPRHKXRGJPYJZWEVM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源游说团体对特朗普关税威胁保持警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油和天然气游说团体周二表示，他们对当选总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁对加拿大和墨西哥征收关税保持警惕，称此类政策可能会影响消费者、工业和安全。【原文：U.S. oil and gas lobbying groups said on Tuesday they were wary of President-elect Donald Trump's threat of tariffs on Canada and Mexico, saying such policies could affect consumers, industry and security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-energy-lobbying-groups-wary-about-trump-tariffs-threat-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6J453U3GSRMPTABRKKFXSRY6VM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交付延迟导致阿斯顿-马丁全年核心利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国豪华汽车制造商阿斯顿-马丁（Aston Martin）周二预测，由于超独家车型Valiant的交付延迟拖累了利润率，其年度核心利润将低于2023年的水平。【原文：British luxury carmaker Aston Martin on Tuesday forecast its annual core profit to fall short of 2023 levels as delivery delays in the ultra-exclusive Valiant models drag its margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/aston-martin-expects-lower-full-year-core-profit-delivery-delays-bite-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TL6VDXZVKZOWPENYZQFCMMUPCA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克利用 X 推动他所偏好的政治选择。特朗普并不总是动摇]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）一直在利用他的社交媒体平台 X 为当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的内阁人选奔走呼号，并宣传他自己中意的候选人，他认为这些人选是变革的推动者，将有助于重塑美国政府。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk has been using his social media platform X to go to bat for President-elect Donald Trump's cabinet picks and promote his own preferred candidates, advocating for choices he views as change agents who will help remake the U.S. government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/musk-uses-x-push-his-preferred-political-picks-trump-isnt-always-swayed-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKH6WGCHE5OX3P3M3FZQYXC3WY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:21:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易伙伴警告特朗普关税将损害所有相关方的利益]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥、加拿大和中国的官员警告说，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁要对美国三大贸易伙伴的商品征收高额关税，这将损害所有相关国家的经济，并有可能加剧通货膨胀和破坏就业市场。【原文：Officials from Mexico, Canada and China warned U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's threat of imposing hefty tariffs on goods from the three largest U.S. trading partners would harm the economies of all involved and would risk aggravating inflation and damaging job markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-trade-partners-warn-trump-tariffs-would-harm-all-involved-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGP6SBNYENIE5CAB565L5PCNZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:57:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WhatsApp 将欧盟隐私委员会之争提交至欧洲最高法庭]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 的 WhatsApp 周二将其与欧洲数据保护委员会（European Data Protection Board）的斗争诉诸欧洲最高法院，称其应该能够对导致爱尔兰隐私监管机构罚款 2.25 亿欧元（2.36 亿美元）的裁决提出质疑。【原文：Meta's WhatsApp took its fight against the European Data Protection Board to Europe's highest court on Tuesday, saying it should be able to challenge a ruling that led to a 225 million euro ($236 million) fine by Ireland's privacy watchdog.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/whatsapp-takes-eu-privacy-board-battle-top-european-court-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45GPGQMGI5PUNOJU5I6CQQTB5I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:51:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师对特朗普威胁征收北美关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁说，他将在 1 月份就任第二任期总统时对主要贸易伙伴墨西哥和加拿大征收 25% 的关税，此举可能引发贸易战，金融分析师对此作出了反应。【原文：Financial analysts on Tuesday reacted to a threat from U.S. President-elect Donald Trump to impose 25% tariffs on top trade partners Mexico and Canada when he takes office for a second term in January in a move that could trigger a trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/analysts-react-trumps-threat-north-american-tariffs-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FGUHOA57KJMPZMQDPY5NYIL3BE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:25:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Orange 邀请 Meta 和 OpenAI 在非洲开发人工智能语言模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电信运营商Orange周二表示，将利用OpenAI和Meta对人工智能大型语言模型（LLM）进行微调，为其翻译非洲地区语言。【原文：Orange will enlist OpenAI and Meta to fine-tune AI Large Language Models (LLMs) to translate regional African languages for the French telecoms operator, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/orange-enlists-meta-openai-develop-ai-language-models-africa-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OW55RKOQAFJMDM35ZX57YCWZEQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:20:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对墨西哥征收关税如何伤害欧洲汽车业]]></title><description><![CDATA[据数据、分析师和专家称，唐纳德-特朗普承诺对从墨西哥进口到美国的商品征收关税，这对大众汽车和斯泰伦特等欧洲汽车制造商及其供应商的损害可能比对欧盟商品直接征收关税更大。【原文：Donald Trump's pledge to slap tariffs on imports to the U.S. from Mexico could be more damaging for European car makers like Volkswagen and Stellantis and their suppliers than any direct tariffs on EU goods, according to data, analysts and experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/how-trumps-mexico-tariffs-could-hurt-europes-auto-industry-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWMQCJJBEVJXJETEZRAMN5DH6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国旅游公司计划在 2025 年前裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[从万豪国际到 Booking Holdings ......总部设在美国的旅游公司正在削减明年的预算和员工人数，因为低收入游客对休闲旅游的需求下降影响了业绩增长。【原文：U.S.-based travel companies, from Marriott International to Booking Holdings . are trimming their budgets and workforce ahead of next year as falling leisure travel demand from lower-income travelers hits top-line growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-based-travel-companies-plan-layoffs-ahead-2025-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CQ2P6KGABIPVIBLIJBZOYSLJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司 2025 年计划假定不再经乌克兰转运至欧洲]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉该计划的人士说，俄罗斯国有控股天然气巨头俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司（Gazprom）在其 2025 年内部规划中假定，12 月 31 日之后将不再有天然气经由乌克兰流向欧洲。【原文：Russian state-controlled gas giant Gazprom is making the assumption that no more gas will flow to Europe via Ukraine after Dec. 31 in its internal planning for 2025, a person familiar with the plans said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gazprom-2025-plan-assumes-no-more-transit-via-ukraine-europe-source-says-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZMZOQVMGVNPDDWPKPBPRY45ZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢公司董事长认为有必要就产品价格采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，雀巢公司董事长保罗-布尔克（Paul Bulcke）被引述说，雀巢需要在价格方面采取行动，以鼓励消费者购买其商品，在此之前，雀巢公司经历了一个充满挑战的阶段，其首席执行官于今年早些时候离职。【原文：Nestle needs to take action on prices to encourage consumers to buy its goods, Chairman Paul Bulcke was quoted as saying on Tuesday following a challenging phase for the company that saw the departure of its CEO earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nestle-chairman-sees-need-action-product-prices-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFHHXZ2HRFLZTECLJII6U5A3UM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上任后如何全面改革美国金融监管机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[在民主党总统乔-拜登（Joe Bidenh）的领导下，美国金融监管机构为银行、私人基金和其他贷款机构制定了一系列严格的新规则。以下是特朗普上任后可能如何控制这些机构。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump is expected to overhaul U.S. financial regulators, which under Democratic President Joe Bidenhave pursued a slew of stringent new rules for banks, private funds and other lenders. Here's how Trump could take control of the agencies upon taking office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-trump-can-overhaul-us-financial-regulators-when-he-takes-office-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UOYKMAGOTZNXTKXX3BV2O6OI44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:46:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月新屋销售跌至两年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，美国新建独栋住宅的销售量降至近两年来的最低水平，这可能是因为抵押贷款利率的上升促使购房者转向观望，以及飓风扰乱了购房活动。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes dropped to the lowest level in nearly two years in October, likely as a rise in mortgage rates drove buyers to the sidelines and hurricanes disrupted activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-new-home-sales-tumble-two-year-low-october-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIW3FOXS6ZORPKCKWIY2EWJKKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用电气就电力部门达成 3.625 亿美元股东和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，通用电气公司（GE Aerospace）将支付 3.625 亿美元现金，以解决股东指控其隐瞒电力业务风险的长期诉讼。【原文：General Electric , doing business as GE Aerospace, will pay $362.5 million in cash to resolve a long-running shareholder lawsuit accusing it of hiding risks at its power business, court papers show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ge-reaches-3625-million-shareholder-settlement-over-power-unit-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTHIZUYG3FIUDINRH4DSPBD6AI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月消费者信心指数进一步上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在对劳动力市场日益乐观和股市反弹的背景下，11月份美国消费者信心进一步增强。【原文：U.S. consumer confidence improved further in November amid growing optimism over the labor market and a stock market rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-confidence-rises-further-november-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYTQV6BRBZIRNNZYR5IWYZ7FAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团聘请贝莱德的 Kate Moore 担任财富首席信息官]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周二宣布，将聘请凯特-摩尔（Kate Moore）担任新财富部门的首席投资官。【原文：Citigroup announced on Tuesday it is hiring Kate Moore as its new wealth division's chief investment officer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-hires-kate-moore-blackrock-wealth-cio-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">736O2QKY3FP7VGUBFCNOJIFUG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行称特朗普提议的关税将影响两国经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大央行周二表示，如果美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普兑现对加拿大征收关税的威胁，这将对两国经济产生影响，央行将把这些影响纳入其经济预测。【原文：The Bank of Canada said on Tuesday that if U.S. President-elect Donald Trump follows through on his threat of tariffs on Canada, it would have an impact on both economies and the central bank would incorporate those into its economic forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-says-trumps-proposed-tariffs-would-impact-both-economies-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5KR4SFAJNNQNGPA2EOTX73J2E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:31:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[库什塔德公司首席执行官表示，将继续寻求与日本 Seven & i 公司达成交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alimentation Couche-Tard 首席执行官亚历克斯-米勒（Alex Miller）周二表示，该加拿大零售商将继续坚持与日本 Seven &amp; i 公司达成交易的努力，并继续与 7-Eleven 运营商保持 "友好接触"。【原文：Alimentation Couche-Tard CEO Alex Miller said on Tuesday the Canadian retailer would remain persistent in its efforts to pursue a deal with Japan's Seven &amp; i and continue a "friendly approach" with the 7-Eleven operator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/couche-tard-persistent-pursuing-deal-with-japans-seven-i-ceo-says-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7QLKO53GZMDPPVI5PMN3OBX3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:28:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>