<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:38:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:38:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贸易乐观情绪不减，美股期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[受中美关税休战和通胀数据疲软的影响，周五美国股指期货上涨，使华尔街有望以积极的态势结束本周的交易。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday, keeping Wall Street on track to end the week on a positive note, marked by a U.S.-China tariff truce and soft inflation data, while investors focused on a likely vote on President Donald Trump's sweeping tax bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-rise-trade-optimism-lingers-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYENQKJNW5OSNG427JPDOKVYAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷放松货币管制，美元黑市摇摇欲坠]]></title><description><![CDATA[在布宜诺斯艾利斯市中心的街道上，多年来严厉的货币管制催生了一个繁荣的美元黑市，在阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱伊的经济改革下，非法货币交易商大军发现日子不好过。【原文：On the streets of downtown Buenos Aires, where years of tough currency controls fermented a thriving black market for dollars, an army of illegal money traders are finding times hard under the economic reforms of Argentine President Javier Milei.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/argentinas-black-market-dollars-falters-currency-controls-are-eased-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KX4SBSZ4FLOLJOSPIWOT6KMJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻：美国股市反弹，零售商将发表关税观点]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的一系列美国零售业财报将进一步揭示关税变化背景下的经济影响，并对股市的大幅反弹构成考验。【原文：A batch of U.S. retail earnings reports in the coming week is set to shed more light on the economic fallout from the shifting tariff backdrop and test the stock market's sharp rebound.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-retailers-set-give-tariff-view-us-stock-market-roars-back-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7N4VHWHAYFOSNMOYETM4XB26FM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着美国发动贸易战，中国成为加拿大跨山管道原油的最大买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[船舶跟踪数据显示，中国已成为通过扩建的跨山管道运输的加拿大石油的最大客户，因为自该管道开始运行以来的一年里，美国的贸易战已改变了原油的流向。【原文：China has emerged as the top customer for Canadian oil shipped on the expanded Trans Mountain pipeline, ship tracking data showed, as a U.S. trade war has shifted crude flows in the year since the pipeline started operating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/with-us-trade-war-china-now-top-buyer-canadian-crude-trans-mountain-pipeline-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4YI3TCHNVNMNBCTKZTVCDU3K4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 投资者警惕并寻求医疗保险战略变革]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）的投资者被这家曾经可以预见的医疗保健巨头的失误所震惊，他们对其医疗保险优势（Medicare Advantage）健康保险业务明年的战略变化充满了戒心。【原文：UnitedHealth Group investors, stunned by missteps at the once predictable healthcare giant, are warily expecting strategic changes in its Medicare Advantage health insurance business over the next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-investors-wary-looking-medicare-strategic-change-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUCNNHHBEBLENBWZRO5U7MRYJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊发布 Alexa+ 人工智能数周后，一个谜团出现了：用户在哪里？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alexa，你的用户在哪里？【原文：Alexa, where are your users?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/weeks-after-amazons-alexa-ai-launch-mystery-where-are-users-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMFN2N473BOCBHZHNUR7KE2QZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市从关税风波中急速反弹后涨势可能放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美贸易休战后的市场动能使股市重回历史高位，但对剩余关税带来的经济影响的担忧以及股票估值的上升可能会在短期内减缓股市的涨势。【原文：Market momentum following the U.S.-China trade truce has put stocks back in sight of record highs but wariness about the economic fallout from remaining tariffs and higher equity valuations could slow gains in the near term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-stock-market-gains-may-slow-after-torrid-rebound-tariff-swoon-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HV5NWUZ7M5IYVL2OD5EQ7JNVIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，花旗将在中国裁减多达 200 个技术承包商职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士透露，花旗集团正在中国裁减多达 200 个信息技术（IT）承包商职位，因为该银行希望在全球范围内雇佣自己的员工来开展此类业务，以改善风险管理和数据治理。【原文：Citigroup is cutting up to 200 information technology (IT) contractor roles in China, two people familiar with the matter said, as the bank looks to hire its own staff globally for such operations to improve risk management and data governance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-cut-up-200-tech-contractor-roles-china-sources-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMNSAJGAVRIJZBBG64WVAIRFUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:55:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在欧盟反垄断调查中，微软提出以较低价格销售不含团队的 Office]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构周五表示，微软已提出以低于带Teams的Office的价格出售不带Teams的Office产品，并向竞争对手提供更好的服务和产品互操作性。【原文：Microsoft has offered to sell its Office product without Teams at a lower price than Office with Teams as well as offer rivals better interoperability access to its services and products, EU antitrust regulators said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-offers-sell-office-with-teams-lower-price-eu-antitrust-probe-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZ6PDZNFCFPFTFPRQTQCSXT2NY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南批准特朗普组织及其合作伙伴的 15 亿美元投资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据越南国营报纸《Tuoi Tre》周五报道，越南政府已经批准了特朗普组织及其合作伙伴在这个东南亚国家投资 15 亿美元建设高尔夫球场、酒店和房地产项目的计划。【原文：Vietnam's government has approved a plan by the Trump Organization and a partner to invest $1.5 billion in golf courses, hotels and real estate projects in the Southeast Asian country, the state-run Tuoi Tre newspaper reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/vietnam-approves-15-billion-investment-plan-by-trump-organization-partner-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFDQMSUOPNLD7H2Y3TAHLZWH3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔就 4.214 亿美元反垄断罚款与欧盟监管机构发生争执]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国芯片制造商英特尔周五与欧盟反垄断监管机构就近两年前因将竞争对手排除在市场之外而被处以3.76亿欧元（4.214亿美元）罚款一事发生争执，认为罚款数额过高且不公平。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Intel on Friday sparred with EU antitrust regulators over a 376 million euro ($421.4 million) fine levied nearly two years ago for excluding rivals from the market, arguing that it was disproportionate and unfair.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/intel-spars-with-eu-regulators-over-4214-million-antitrust-fine-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDKQP7DHKZNFPHS2FJOKAFTSYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Epic Games 称苹果在美国和欧盟商店屏蔽了《堡垒之夜》游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[史诗游戏公司（Epic Games）周五表示，苹果公司已禁止其 "堡垒之夜"（Fortnite）视频游戏在欧盟商店和 iPhone 制造商的美国应用程序商店中销售。【原文：Epic Games said on Friday that Apple has blocked its "Fortnite" video game on its store in the European Union and the iPhone maker's U.S. app store.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/apple-blocks-fortnite-game-us-eu-stores-epic-games-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQMDRQ5CZFMRLFJ7PP3G7B4CAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国部长在格里尔会议上要求豁免美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国贸工部长安德根（Ahn Deuk-geun）周五表示，他会见了美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer），并再次要求免除华盛顿的关税措施。【原文：South Korea's minister of trade and industry Ahn Deuk-geun said on Friday that he met U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer and asked again for a waiver from Washington's tariff measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-minister-asks-exemption-us-tariffs-greer-meeting-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WILWIK5KJ5OKZGHE5BUDTUNFGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普：阿联酋和美国就阿布扎比购买最先进人工智能芯片的途径达成一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，阿拉伯联合酋长国和美国已同意为海湾国家从美国公司购买一些最先进的人工智能半导体开辟一条道路。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday the United Arab Emirates and the United States have agreed to create a path for the Gulf country to buy some of the most advanced artificial intelligence semiconductors from U.S. companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/uae-us-agree-path-abu-dhabi-buy-most-advanced-ai-chips-trump-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H26YZ6PH2NNP3KDMLMOFHHJTYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大幅抛售后资金回流美国上市的中国 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中美关税休战提振了市场情绪，跟踪中国股市的主要美国上市交易所交易基金（ETF）在 5 月份录得资金流入。【原文：Major U.S.-listed exchange-traded funds (ETFs) that track Chinese stocks recorded inflows in May as a U.S.-China tariff truce boosted sentiment, following a heavy sell-off in the previous month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/capital-flows-back-us-listed-china-etfs-post-big-sell-off-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRPJBGX5BZKSFIMHPAN35KOTDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Charter 就与考克斯合并进行深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，宽带和有线电视服务提供商 Charter 正在与考克斯通信公司（Cox Communications）就合并事宜进行深入谈判，该交易对考克斯的估值超过 300 亿美元。【原文：Broadband and cable TV provider Charter is in advanced talks to combine with Cox Communications in a deal that values Cox at more than $30 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/charter-advanced-talks-combine-with-cox-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVZQ5SXFDRJKNOWYHCZE2OSQII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗地亚《权力的游戏》拍摄地面临特朗普关税威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[克罗地亚古城杜布罗夫尼克的堡垒和鹅卵石铺就的街道上经常挤满了游客，他们都渴望参观《权力的游戏》电视剧或《星球大战：最后的绝地武士》电影中的取景地。【原文：The fortresses and cobbled streets of the ancient Croatian town of Dubrovnik are often crowded with tourists eager to visit the locations from the Game of Thrones television series or the Star Wars: The Last Jedi film.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/croatias-game-thrones-filming-sites-face-threat-trump-tariffs-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZUP3EOB3VLVXA2D4DQVXCWORQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Patria 公司推出数据中心平台，首期投资 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着云计算和人工智能在拉丁美洲的应用加速，巴西投资公司 Patria Investimentos 周五宣布推出超大规模数据中心平台 Omnia，该公司将在未来 18-24 个月内为其首个项目投资约 10 亿美元。【原文：Brazilian investment firm Patria Investimentos on Friday announced the launch of Omnia, a hyperscale data center platform that will invest about $1 billion in its first project in the next 18 to 24 months, as cloud computing and artificial intelligence adoption accelerates in Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-patria-launches-data-center-platform-with-initial-investment-1-billion-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVS2U32DONNA5DWD3EOKIKJ5LU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工资谈判陷入僵局，新泽西公交公司铁路四十年来首次罢工开始]]></title><description><![CDATA[新泽西州通勤铁路工程师周五提前下班，因为马拉松式的合同谈判在其工会为满足工资要求而设定的午夜最后期限前陷入僵局，从而引发了 40 多年来席卷美国第三大交通系统的首次罢工。【原文：New Jersey's commuter rail engineers walked off the job early on Friday after marathon contract talks stalled ahead of a midnight deadline their union set for meeting its wage demands, igniting the first strike to engulf the third-largest U.S. transit system in more than 40 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/new-jersey-transit-rail-strike-first-four-decades-begins-wage-talks-stall-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGGWGEHV7BKMHP2JGUW3JAKSKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球时报》：应延长中美90天关税休战期]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家支持的《环球时报》周五称，上周末中美两国在瑞士贸易谈判期间达成的为期90天的关税休战协议太短，因为世界上最大的两个经济体的特使正在韩国重新集结。【原文：The 90-day tariff truce agreed by the United States and China during trade talks in Switzerland last weekend is too short, China's state-backed Global Times said on Friday, as envoys from the world's two biggest economies regrouped in Korea.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-us-90-day-tariff-truce-should-be-extended-global-times-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NXPPGK47VJEDMKXCXT3URC2UE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:27:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纬创称美国新工厂将于明年为 Nvidia 服务器生产做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾电子制造商纬创（Wistron）周五表示，其为客户英伟达（Nvidia）在美国新建的生产设施将于明年完工，该公司正在与其他潜在客户进行谈判。【原文：Taiwanese electronics manufacturer Wistron said on Friday that its new U.S. manufacturing facilities for its customer Nvidia would be ready next year and the firm was in talks with potential other customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/wistron-says-new-us-plants-will-be-ready-nvidias-server-production-next-year-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIK3IDKXIFLZ5P23MKVRI6Q7YM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业巨变后，中国主动型基金以全新产品蓄势待发]]></title><description><![CDATA[本月公布的中国主动型基金新规将彻底改变中国股市的资金流向，这促使业内一些大公司立即行动起来，推出新产品。【原文：New rules for Chinese active funds unveiled this month that are set to drastically change fund flows in the country's stock markets have prompted immediate action from some of the biggest players in the industry to introduce fresh products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/chinese-active-funds-gear-up-with-fresh-products-after-dramatic-industry-reforms-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPYGN4GCZNJY7MAI66BLC2KEIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的邻国为何希望与特朗普达成货币交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着韩国、台湾和日本的货币升值，有关这些经济体可能在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易谈判中利用汇率重估作为筹码的传言也甚嚣尘上。【原文：As the currencies of South Korea, Taiwan and Japan rise, so too is chatter that these economies could use exchange rate revaluation as a carrot in trade talks with U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/why-chinas-neighbours-may-want-currency-deals-with-trump-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZANQUVMCBICFBZEQCUNT6ERRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉凯恩汽车公司交易后，美国车桥公司计划在伦敦二次上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于底特律的美国车桥与制造公司周五表示，在斥资 14 亿美元收购吉凯恩汽车公司（GKN Automotive）所有者 Dowlais 之后，该公司计划寻求在伦敦进行股票二次上市。【原文：Detroit-based American Axle and Manufacturing said on Friday it plans to seek a secondary listing of its shares in London after its $1.4 billion acquisition of GKN Automotive owner Dowlais .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/american-axle-plans-secondary-london-listing-after-gkn-automotive-deal-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QL7566PISJJGPJVHZWIPRDJIRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行：贸易休战后美国不再可能出现经济衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）在周四晚些时候发布的一份报告中称，鉴于中美贸易紧张局势出现缓和迹象，该行不再预计美国经济将在今年晚些时候陷入衰退，并上调了经济增长预期。【原文：Barclays no longer expects the U.S. economy to slip into a recession later this year and has revised up its growth forecasts, given signs of a de-escalation in U.S.-China trade tensions, the bank said in a note released late Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-recession-no-longer-likely-after-trade-truce-says-barclays-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SE42SGSLNK45D26FTT34CTP2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 4 月份核心通胀率可能升至两年来最快水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于能源补贴减少和食品成本上升，日本 4 月份的核心通胀率可能创下两年来的最快增速，这增加了央行加息的压力。【原文：Japan's April core inflation probably rose at its fastest pace in two years on the reduction of energy subsidies and higher food costs, a Reuters poll showed, adding to pressure on the central bank to raise interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-april-core-inflation-likely-sped-up-fastest-pace-two-years-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYGAFDBQK5LYBMYJO6IZWNJ6KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡地亚珠宝大放异彩，历峰集团销售额增长 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡地亚的所有者历峰集团（Richemont）周五报告称，该集团季度销售额增长了7%，略好于预期，原因是美国富裕的购物者摆脱了经济的不确定性，继续在奢侈珠宝上挥金如土，从而抵消了亚洲需求的疲软。【原文：Cartier owner Richemont on Friday reported a slightly better-than-expected 7% rise in quarterly sales as weaker demand in Asia was offset by brisk business in the United States where wealthy shoppers shrugged off economic uncertainty and continued to splash out on luxury jewellery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cartier-owner-richemont-sales-up-7-jewellery-shines-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXQETUUOMRKFTOLL52YSZ3YZGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾与美国在韩国举行关税会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾副总理郑丽群周五表示，台湾和美国的主要贸易代表在韩国举行了贸易谈判，双方对进一步谈判将导致美国降低对台湾出口产品的关税表示乐观。【原文：The main Taiwan and U.S. trade representatives met in South Korea for trade negotiations, yielding optimism that further talks would lead to reduced U.S. tariffs on Taiwan exports, the island's Vice-Premier Cheng Li-chiun said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-meets-with-us-tariff-talks-south-korea-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAMGKNGROJJORGIHWPXR22T54U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:22:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡航空公司高管表示，最近飞往中国的航班需求有所增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡航空公司首席商务官李力新周五表示，最近几个月进入中国的客流量激增，但出境游仍未恢复到大流行前的水平。【原文：Singapore Airlines has seen a surge in passenger traffic into China in recent months, but outbound travel has still not recovered to pre-pandemic levels, Chief Commercial Officer Lee Lik Hsin said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/demand-flights-china-has-risen-recently-singapore-airlines-exec-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC32NBSLLNO7PBMZ62UFF2B6EY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价贸易推动的本周反弹戛然而止]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5K7BU4YPVJL3ISUJXPK5UNL24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>