<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:37:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:37:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[曼哈顿地标摩天大楼业主完成 13 亿美元贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据代表开发商的律师事务所 Rosenberg + Estis 称，纽约市房地产开发商 The Durst Organization 周三为时代广场地标性摩天大楼签署了 2025 年曼哈顿最大的写字楼贷款之一。【原文：New York City property developer The Durst Organization sealed one of 2025's largest Manhattan office loans for a landmark Times Square skyscraper on Wednesday, according to Rosenberg + Estis, the law firm that represented the developer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/owner-landmark-manhattan-skyscraper-closes-13-billion-loan-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMBJFHOCINOLBIP55XX7CFJZKE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿波罗收购 Stream 数据中心，押注人工智能基础设施热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[另类资产管理公司阿波罗（Apollo）周三表示，同意收购 Stream Data Centers（SDC）的多数股权，押注人工智能和云计算推动的数字基础设施需求增长。【原文：Apollo agreed to buy a majority interest in Stream Data Centers (SDC), the alternative asset manager said on Wednesday, in a bet on rising demand for digital infrastructure fueled by artificial intelligence and cloud computing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apollo-buys-stream-data-centers-bet-ai-infrastructure-boom-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SONQ643ITJMS7LGHCKCQZUYIE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:09:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：卢拉计划为战略矿产制定新的 "国家主权 "政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周三告诉路透社，他计划制定一项新的国家政策，将战略性矿产视为 "国家主权 "问题，以避免出口矿产而不增加当地价值。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva told Reuters on Wednesday of his plans for a new national policy treating strategic minerals as a matter of "national sovereignty" in order to avoid exporting minerals without adding value locally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/lula-plans-new-national-sovereignty-policy-strategic-minerals-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AFEGR6SOZPXZKSW565MAAQYQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:02:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印美在贸易和石油问题上的争执有可能造成更广泛的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析家和官员们说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在贸易和俄罗斯石油采购问题上对印度的抨击有可能使印度二十年来取得的外交进展付诸东流，而且由于国内政治压力促使双方立场趋于强硬，印度的其他合作领域也可能因此脱轨。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tirade against India over trade and Russian oil purchases threatens to undo two decades of diplomatic progress, analysts and officials say, and could derail other areas of cooperation as domestic political pressures drive both sides to harden their stances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/india-us-spat-over-trade-oil-threatens-wider-fallout-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLBSBVKCIRPT7I3HFPBCEVQRBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:43:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储库克称 7 月就业数据不温不火值得关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）周三表示，上周五公布的 7 月份招聘数据在放缓招聘步伐方面 "令人担忧"。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook said on Wednesday that July hiring data released last Friday was “concerning” in the moderation of the pace of hiring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-cook-says-tepid-july-jobs-data-merits-concern-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFCF7IZKMRPAZN3YXVTY3C3KKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:36:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道卢拉拒绝就美巴关税问题致电特朗普的 "羞辱 "行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦接受路透社采访，谈论关税问题。【原文：Brazil's President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva sat down with Reuters to talk tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/lula-rejects-humiliation-calling-trump-over-us-brazil-tariff-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YTKVMDOTVMU3LVQXJ7LK3JWCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡什卡利美联储需要应对经济放缓，今年两次降息是合理的]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联储主席尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周三表示，尽管关税是否会继续推高通胀率仍不明确，但美国联邦储备委员会近期可能需要降息，以应对美国经济放缓。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve may need to cut interest rates in the near term in response to a slowing U.S. economy, even though it remains unclear whether tariffs will continue to push inflation higher, Minneapolis Fed President Neel Kashkari said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kashkari-fed-needs-respond-slowing-economy-two-cuts-this-year-would-be-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AEJE7XKQ3NNCPM6ADJURXRCMRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会寻求阻止爱德华生命科学公司收购 JenaValve 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会起诉爱德华兹生命科学公司（Edwards Lifesciences Corp），要求阻止该公司收购杰纳活瓣技术公司（JenaValve Technology Inc）。美国联邦贸易委员会周三在华盛顿提起诉讼，称这一并购将减少一种用于治疗潜在致命心脏病的设备的市场竞争。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission sued to block Edwards Lifesciences Corp's acquisition of JenaValve Technology Inc, saying in a lawsuit filed in Washington on Wednesday the merger would decrease competition in the market for a device meant to treat a potentially fatal heart condition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/ftc-seeks-block-edwards-lifesciences-acquisition-jenavalve-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYS46KHOAJMYHK7BTZJM67VWDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:41:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普下达降低欧盟汽车关税的命令尚需时日]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉欧盟与美国谈判的消息人士称，欧盟很可能还要再等几天，才能等到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下达降低欧洲汽车和汽车零部件进口关税的行政命令。【原文：The European Union will likely have to wait a few more days for an executive order by U.S. President Donald Trump lowering tariffs on imports of European cars and car parts, a source familiar with the EU-U.S. negotiations said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-order-lowering-tariffs-eu-autos-still-days-away-source-says-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIA2LHWY2BNZRPWF3W57BV2RDA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国为自动驾驶汽车 Zoox 发放豁免，结束调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，它已对亚马逊公司的自动驾驶汽车 Zoox 进行了示范使用认证，并结束了对其是否符合联邦要求的调查。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said Wednesday it has certified Amazon.com's self-driving unit Zoox vehicles for demonstration use and closed a probe into whether they had complied with federal requirements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-issues-exemption-self-driving-zoox-vehicles-closes-probe-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4MRZGAV7FJPZGM33J4JD6AQ74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:32:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌承诺出资 10 亿美元在美国大学进行人工智能培训]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司（Google）周三宣布了一项为期三年、价值 10 亿美元的承诺，将为美国高等教育机构和非营利组织提供人工智能培训和工具。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Wednesday announced a three-year, $1 billion commitment to provide artificial intelligence training and tools to U.S. higher education institutions and nonprofits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/google-commits-1-billion-ai-training-us-universities-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3I7MHTZNPJKZJD7HQF5V46XKHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利国家矿业公司（ENAMI）向投资者敞开 17 亿美元冶炼厂的大门]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利国营矿业公司ENAMI周三表示，该公司已经启动了一项程序，为一座价值17亿美元的冶炼厂吸引投资者，以换取电解铜供应。【原文：Chile's state-run mining company ENAMI has kicked off a process to draw in investors for a $1.7 billion smelter in exchange for copper cathode supply, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chiles-enami-opens-door-investors-17-bln-smelter-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3H5RL5MCANL3LK4QU667AKHK3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:58:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行不会面临抵押贷款歧视集体诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官裁定，富国银行不必面对集体诉讼的指控，该行系统性地歧视了数十万黑人和西班牙裔抵押贷款申请人。【原文：Wells Fargo won't have to face class-action claims it systematically discriminated against hundreds of thousands of Black and Hispanic mortgage applicants, a federal judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/wells-fargo-wont-face-mortgage-discrimination-class-action-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIV6DJO2KRIW5OXXXL3ZBRA37U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步与银行和私募股权公司洽谈为机器人出租车扩张提供资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步（Uber）首席执行官达拉-科斯罗萨西（Dara Khosrowshahi）表示，优步正在与私募股权公司和银行洽谈，以获得资金来建立机器人出租车业务。【原文：Uber is in talks with private equity firms and banks to secure funds to build its robotaxi business, CEO Dara Khosrowshahi said, as the ride-hailing giant bets on a mass roll-out of the nascent and much-scrutinized technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-talks-with-banks-private-equity-firms-fund-robotaxi-expansion-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IALMRZSWJKWHEJC7KE6C7VUBY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普声称受到歧视，白宫准备发布针对银行的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统表示，他认为包括摩根大通和美国银行在内的银行歧视他和他的支持者，因此白宫准备对涉嫌因政治原因而放弃客户的银行采取行动。【原文：The White House was preparing to act against banks for allegedly dropping customers for political reasons, as President Donald Trump said he believes that banks, including JPMorgan and Bank of America , had discriminated against him and his supporters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/white-house-prepares-order-targeting-banks-trump-claims-discrimination-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U7AKVIRKZOELMVZEF7O7U3AAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:43:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，诺华权衡收购生物技术公司 Avidity Biosciences]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》援引知情人士的话报道，瑞士制药商诺华已与美国生物技术公司 Avidity Biosciences 接洽，提出收购要约。【原文：Swiss drugmaker Novartis has approached U.S. biotech Avidity Biosciences for a potential takeover offer, the Financial Times reported, citing people familiar with the matter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-weighs-deal-biotech-avidity-biosciences-ft-reports-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOXZ6ZY7Z5IIZDJ43JNVHDRQWA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[导航设备制造商 Trimble 上调年度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Trimble 周三上调了年度收入和利润预期，看好建筑、运输和地理空间等行业对其集成硬件和软件解决方案日益增长的需求。【原文：Trimble raised its annual revenue and profit forecasts on Wednesday, betting on growing demand for its integrated hardware and software solutions from industries such as construction, transportation and geospatial.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/navigation-equipment-maker-trimble-raises-annual-forecasts-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZRUWMR2PVPIPBO3GWGXOS42Q4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:27:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登时代任命的官员可能会阻碍特朗普重塑美联储的努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事会的新成员将面对拜登任命的三位成员，以及美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔本人，他们加在一起可以对任何彻底改革货币政策的努力形成强有力的制衡。【原文：The new member of the Federal Reserve's Board of Governors will face three appointed by Biden, as well as Fed Chair Jerome Powell himself, who combined could offer a powerful counterweight against any efforts to overhaul monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/biden-era-appointees-could-stymie-trumps-effort-reshape-fed-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TFOUM65YFKXDG3VQHKRM6CIDI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司对新的美国销售充满希望，尽管关税依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司首席执行官认为，该飞机制造商将能够向一家美国航空公司出售其 E2 支线喷气机，但他承认，对巴西商品征收关税可能会使获得突破性首份订单的努力复杂化。【原文：Embraer's CEO believes the planemaker will be able to sell its E2 regional jets to a U.S. carrier, but acknowledges that tariffs on Brazilian goods may complicate efforts to secure a groundbreaking first order.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazil-planemaker-embraer-hopeful-about-fresh-us-sales-despite-tariffs-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34OBSIL5I5PMRDDY4FFVRUO4UI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:53:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Blackstone 就数据分析公司 Enverus 签订了 65 亿美元的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的另类资产管理公司 Blackstone 周三表示，已同意收购能源数据和分析提供商 Enverus，私募股权投资领域的交易在放缓后出现复苏迹象。【原文：Blackstone , the world's largest alternative asset manager, said on Wednesday it has agreed to buy energy data and analytics provider Enverus, as dealmaking in the private equity sector shows signs of a recovery after a slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/blackstone-signs-65-billion-deal-data-analytics-firm-enverus-source-says-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQNOH5AQPJMWPE2LXSZHMCEL4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:49:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令对印度商品征收 25% 的额外关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三发布行政命令，对来自印度的商品征收额外 25% 的关税，称印度直接或间接进口俄罗斯石油。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump issued an executive order on Wednesday imposing an additional 25% tariff on goods from India, saying the country directly or indirectly imported Russian oil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/view-trump-order-imposes-additional-25-tariff-goods-india-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNWRASJR3BJ63KVDTSQV7VCBJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:41:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[酒业集团在致特朗普的信中表示，关税使 20 亿美元的销售额面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对欧盟商品征收15%的关税可能会使酒类销售额减少近20亿美元，并使2.5万个美国工作岗位面临风险，一个由57个酒类行业组织组成的团体在周二写给美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的一封信中写道。【原文：The United States' 15% tariff on EU goods could reduce the value of alcohol sales by almost $2 billion and put 25,000 U.S. jobs at risk, a group of 57 alcohol industry groups wrote in a letter sent to U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/letter-trump-alcohol-groups-say-tariffs-put-2-billion-sales-risk-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PH72GMLC3ZN33JDO4GKJ6COU4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:34:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称加航空乘人员将于周五恢复谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[加航空乘人员工会周三表示，加航空乘人员本周以压倒性多数通过了一项罢工授权，允许他们最早于 8 月 16 日离职，本周五他们将回到与加航的谈判桌前。【原文：Air Canada flight attendants are heading back to the bargaining table with the airline on Friday, after overwhelmingly approving a strike mandate this week that could allow them to walk off the job as early as August 16, their union said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/air-canada-flight-attendants-return-bargaining-friday-union-says-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BJFNNMSWVOWROUAUKFEP4V5C4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:21:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令对印度商品征收 25% 的额外关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三发布行政命令，对来自印度的商品征收额外 25% 的关税，称印度直接或间接进口俄罗斯石油，这是在已宣布的 25% 关税基础上的额外关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump issued an executive order on Wednesday imposing an additional 25% tariff on goods from India, saying the country directly or indirectly imported Russian oil, adding to 25% tariffs already announced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/trump-order-imposes-additional-25-tariff-goods-india-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EII7PA5HPBKZXB6TWK3HMN34VY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中欧外汇将受美元提振，但福林可能从高位回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三的一项民意调查显示，尽管匈牙利福林将从约10个月的高点回落，但中欧货币在未来6个月内大多将从美元走软中获得支撑。【原文：Central Europe's currencies will mostly find support from a weaker U.S. dollar over the next six months, although the Hungarian forint is set to retreat from around 10-month highs, a Reuters poll showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/central-europes-fx-get-dollar-boost-forint-likely-fall-highs-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETFVAMYKLNPX3BPPLKYUP7B2JQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北京机器人商店备有爱因斯坦复制品和国际象棋伙伴，力推人工智能领先地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[想找一个机器人棋友来测试您的棋艺吗？或者一只机器人宠物狗？或者一个真人大小的物理学家阿尔伯特-爱因斯坦的复制品，可以教你他的相对论？【原文：Fancy a robot chess partner to test your moves on? Perhaps a robotic pet dog? Or a life-sized replica of physicist Albert Einstein that could teach you his theories on relativity?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/beijing-robot-store-stocks-einstein-replicas-chess-partners-ai-leadership-push-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBSIJODULNNU5DF7FLZU6N5UIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车与 Noveon Magnetics 签订稀土磁铁协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）磁铁制造商诺维信磁铁公司（Noveon Magnetics）周三表示，该公司已与通用汽车公司达成一项多年期协议，诺维信磁铁公司将为通用汽车公司的全尺寸SUV和卡车部件提供稀土磁铁。【原文：General Motors has entered into a multi-year deal under which Noveon Magnetics will supply rare earth magnets for use in components of the automaker's full-size SUVs and trucks, the magnet maker said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-signs-rare-earth-magnet-deal-with-noveon-magnetics-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GRQFY3QZBMTTMJVATR2IJQ22A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场波动推动交易额创下新高，MarketAxess 盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，债券交易平台 MarketAxess 的第二季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，因为市场波动加剧引发了创纪录的交易业绩。【原文：Bond trading platform MarketAxess beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit on Wednesday, as heightened market volatility sparked record trading results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/marketaxess-beats-profit-expectations-market-volatility-drives-record-trading-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBTY5OLL6JNPXCWUWCXZPG2WWI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾默生电气上调利润预期，原因是关税和强劲需求降低了成本风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[工程解决方案供应商艾默生电气周三略微上调了其年度利润预期，原因是关税带来的成本风险降低，以及其智能设备业务的需求增加。【原文：Engineering solutions provider Emerson Electric slightly raised its annual profit forecast on Wednesday, banking on reduced cost exposure to tariffs and higher demand for its intelligent devices segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/emerson-electric-bumps-up-profit-view-lower-cost-risk-tariffs-firm-demand-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPKFDNJUE5MPPMQTPNAAB2AOYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫顾问苹果公司可能做出投资承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）在讨论唐纳德-特朗普总统领导下的公司和国家做出的金融承诺时说，苹果公司很可能在周三宣布一项投资计划。【原文：White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said Apple Inc was likely to make an investment announcement on Wednesday, as he discussed the financial pledges made by companies and countries under President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/white-house-adviser-apple-likely-make-investment-commitment-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWQE4XXHPNKQZJQQEA3RJHJFXM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>