<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 15:10:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 15:10:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[在南非涉及谷歌的反垄断调查中，有哪些关键补救措施？]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非竞争委员会在对市场支配地位进行调查后，于周四公布了全球科技平台采取的一揽子全面补救措施，其中包括与谷歌和 YouTube 达成的 6.88 亿兰特（约合 4000 万美元）的媒体支持计划。【原文：South Africa's Competition Commission on Thursday unveiled a sweeping package of remedial measures from global tech platforms, including a 688 million rand ($40 million) media support package agreed with Google and YouTube, following a probe into market dominance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/what-are-key-remedies-south-africas-antitrust-probe-involving-google-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EY44S64YINPILDA22PHU53ER7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 15:03:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国全国广播公司环球公司将于 11 月 17 日推出新的体育电视频道]]></title><description><![CDATA[康卡斯特旗下的 NBCUniversal 公司周四表示，将于 11 月 17 日推出 NBC 体育网（即 NBCSN 有线频道），在此之前，该公司计划分拆大部分有线电视网。【原文：Comcast's NBCUniversal will launch NBC Sports Network, or NBCSN cable channel, on November 17, the company said on Thursday, ahead of its planned spin-off of most of the cable networks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nbcuniversal-launch-new-sports-tv-channel-november-17-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXY3NOCHNNOMPLR2YBKMZQLRPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利在风险均衡的情况下对 12 月降息持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联储主席玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周四表示，由于美联储今年迄今已两次降息，美联储实现物价稳定和充分就业两大目标所面临的风险已趋于平衡，因此她对即将于12月做出的利率决定持开放态度。【原文：Risks to the Federal Reserve's two goals of price stability and full employment are balanced now that the Fed has cut interest rates twice so far this year, San Francisco Fed President Mary Daly said on Thursday, leaving her open minded about the upcoming December rate-setting decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/feds-daly-open-minded-december-rate-cut-amid-balanced-risks-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LA7MNN3IGZMNDMDJW6MHEQJUOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈塞特：美国经济数据将不包括10月份失业率]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周四在联邦政府工作人员返回工作岗位时表示，在联邦政府长达数周的停摆之后，美国10月份的失业率数据可能永远无法公布。【原文：Data on the U.S. unemployment rate for October may never be available after the weeks-long federal government shutdown, White House economic Adviser Kevin Hassett said on Thursday as federal workers returned to work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/white-house-make-housing-recommendations-within-months-hassett-says-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C75P26LG3BO2FDKQYXEFHBLIUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，埃隆-马斯克的 xAI 在最新一轮融资中筹集了 150 亿美元资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周四援引消息人士的话报道，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 xAI 公司在 E 轮融资中筹集了 150 亿美元。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk's xAI has raised $15 billion in a series E funding round, CNBC reported on Thursday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/elon-musks-xai-raises-15-billion-series-e-round-cnbc-reports-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLCHT5KPPFJOVECF37SXZXMSZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:44:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovery 与 Luno 合作，在南非提供首个银行应用程序加密货币交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Discovery 银行将成为南非第一家将加密货币整合到其移动平台的贷款机构，从 12 月起，客户可以直接在其银行应用程序中交易加密货币。【原文：Discovery Bank is set to become the first lender in South Africa to integrate crypto into its mobile platform, allowing customers to trade cryptocurrencies directly in its banking app from December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/discovery-partners-with-luno-offer-first-bank-app-crypto-trading-south-africa-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBWYLYGFUJJPNHDYDBAYHZ3F5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鹰鸽对峙，美联储 12 月降息几率岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[越来越多的美联储政策制定者以对通胀的担忧和美国今年两次降息后劳动力市场相对稳定的迹象为由，表示对进一步宽松政策保持缄默，这帮助将基于金融市场的借贷成本在12月下调的概率推高至接近持平的水平。【原文：Citing worries about inflation and signs of relative stability in the labor market after two U.S. interest rate cuts this year, a growing number of Federal Reserve policymakers are signaling reticence on further easing, helping push financial market-based odds of a reduction in borrowing costs in December to near even.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/odds-fed-rate-cut-december-knifes-edge-hawks-doves-face-off-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DUSPJ6VC5POPA6RPR2ZAUMUOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官驳回取消参与 Citgo 拍卖的官员和顾问资格的动议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周四提交的一份法庭文件显示，一名美国法官驳回了委内瑞拉和矿商 Gold Reserve 提出的取消其本人、一名法院官员和两家负责监督美国炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份拍卖的顾问公司的资格的动议。【原文：A U.S. judge has denied motions filed by Venezuela and miner Gold Reserve to disqualify him, a court officer and two advising firms overseeing an auction of shares in the parent of U.S. refiner Citgo Petroleum, according to a court filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-judge-denies-motions-disqualify-officers-advisors-involved-citgo-auction-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO72I75ZZ5OLFOBJWCCZGOD3D4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美特斯邦威股东投票赞成辉瑞高达 100 亿美元的收购案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据初步统计，美特斯邦威股东周四批准了辉瑞公司价值高达 100 亿美元的收购要约，使这家美国制药巨头得以在与 Wegovy 制造商诺和诺德公司的激烈竞购战后，在利润丰厚的肥胖症治疗市场上占据一席之地。【原文：Metsera shareholders on Thursday approved Pfizer's takeover offer worth up to $10 billion, as per preliminary count, allowing the U.S. pharmaceutical giant to gain a foothold in the lucrative obesity treatment market after a fierce bidding war with Wegovy-maker Novo Nordisk .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/metsera-shareholders-vote-10-billion-acquisition-by-pfizer-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25AHZLK5MNJRNA2SJ3FW7N54Z4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司上诉英国应用程序商店佣金裁决遭拒]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四被伦敦法庭裁定滥用其支配地位，向应用程序开发商收取不公平的佣金，苹果公司上诉遭拒，这家科技巨头可能面临超过 10 亿英镑（13 亿美元）的账单。【原文：Apple was on Thursday refused permission to appeal against a London tribunal ruling that it abused its dominant position by charging app developers unfair commissions, leaving the tech giant facing a potential bill of over 1 billion pounds ($1.3 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/apple-refused-permission-appeal-uk-ruling-app-store-commissions-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SETKLTVCJMXXAQNNE4AS5CFMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专注于加密货币的灰度公司在美国首次公开募股文件中披露收入下降 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[这家专注于加密货币的资产管理公司周四在其美国首次公开募股文件中披露，2025 年前九个月，灰度公司的收入下降了 20%。【原文：Grayscale recorded a 20% fall in revenue for the first nine months of 2025, the crypto-focused asset manager disclosed in its U.S. initial public offering paperwork on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/crypto-focused-grayscale-makes-us-ipo-filing-public-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GREN6U5SJL5BI2FWL3IEPOQEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:13:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 年期国债收益率在通胀不出意外的情况下将小幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对市场专家进行的一项调查显示，假设通胀不出现上行意外，美国 10 年期国债收益率在未来几个月可能会小幅上升，而短期收益率预计会因降息押注而下降。【原文：U.S. 10-year Treasury yields, assuming no upside inflation surprises, are likely to rise modestly in coming months, according to a Reuters poll of market experts, while short-dated yields are forecast to decline on rate cut bets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-10-year-treasury-yields-priced-no-inflation-surprises-set-rise-modestly-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTILFGWUGJN7JB7XAIRMMSJ5AU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:04:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[反垄断调查后，南非媒体从谷歌获得资金支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非竞争监管机构周四宣布了全球科技平台做出的一系列让步，其中包括在对媒体行业进行调查后，与谷歌和YouTube达成的6.88亿兰特（约合4000万美元）媒体支持方案。【原文：South Africa's competition regulator announced on Thursday a series of concessions from global tech platforms, including a 688 million rand ($40 million) media support package agreed with Google and YouTube, following an investigation into the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/south-african-media-get-funding-package-google-after-antitrust-probe-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JT5I5JBEJLANHLWPNNBYW7VDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:51:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主要分析师和企业对人工智能市场的预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[技术高管和分析师预计人工智能将产生数千亿美元的价值，但根据所采用的基本假设和衡量标准，对市场的预测却大相径庭。【原文：Technology executives and analysts expect artificial intelligence to generate hundreds of billions of dollars in value, yet forecasts for the market diverge significantly based on the underlying assumptions and metrics employed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/major-analyst-enterprise-forecasts-ai-market-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDHGYCHNKRLONPFFWMOUKUE67E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:49:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威财富基金在 21 年禁令后可能投资顶级国防企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于受到乌克兰战争和美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于保卫欧洲的言论的影响，挪威可能允许其2.1万亿美元的主权财富基金（世界上最大的主权财富基金）在中断20多年后，从2027年起投资于大型防务公司。【原文：Unnerved by the Ukraine war and U.S. President Donald Trump's whiplash statements on defending Europe, Norway could allow its $2.1 trillion sovereign wealth fund, the world's largest, to invest in major defence companies from 2027 after a more than 20-year hiatus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/norway-wealth-fund-may-invest-top-defence-firms-after-21-year-ban-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63SPXQ4JM5L7ZGTN4YTF6VN3UI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[21shares 推出两只美国加密货币指数 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于瑞士的数字资产管理公司21shares周四表示，该公司为美国投资者推出了首批追踪一篮子加密货币（包括以太坊、索拉纳和狗狗币）价格的交易所交易基金。【原文：21shares launched its first exchange-traded funds tracking the price of a basket of cryptocurrencies, including ethereum, solana and dogecoin, for U.S. investors, the Swiss-based digital assets manager said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/21shares-launches-two-us-crypto-index-etfs-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDFGDGEK5NMFJNQKK5XFZAKW5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:42:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利 Wiit 公司九个月调整后核心利润增长 19.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利云计算和网络安全服务提供商 Wiit 周四公布，其九个月调整后核心利润（EBITDA）增长了 19.5%，达到 5090 万欧元（5940 万美元）。【原文：Italian cloud computing and cybersecurity service provider Wiit posted on Thursday a 19.5% rise in its nine-month adjusted core profit (EBITDA) to 50.9 million euros ($59.4 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italys-wiit-posts-195-rise-nine-month-adjusted-core-profit-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BK3VMQPY3NO3PFFWAGF4AAXFAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:28:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BioNTech 表示与辉瑞的合作保持不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，当被要求就辉瑞正寻求出售其在这家德国生物技术公司的股份的报道发表评论时，BioNTech 公司表示，其与辉瑞的合作没有改变。【原文：BioNTech said on Thursday that its collaboration with Pfizer has not changed, when asked to comment on a report that Pfizer is looking to sell its stake in the German biotech firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/biontech-says-collaboration-with-pfizer-remains-unchanged-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHU3WNU5ZRLKPFJJBGB6ERO2DI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RTX 第四季度将因养老金收购支出 3 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[RTX 公司周四表示，该公司第四季度将产生约 3 亿美元的非现金税前费用，涉及通过年金收购将 25 亿美元的养老金义务转移给保德信金融公司的一个部门。【原文：RTX Corp said on Thursday it will incur non-cash pretax charge of about $300 million in the fourth quarter related to the transfer of $2.5 billion in pension obligations to a Prudential Financial unit through an annuity buyout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtx-take-300-mln-fourth-quarter-charge-tied-pension-buyout-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKSYZZYWEFPQ3OPDBFI4PWRWSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 12:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mangoceuticals 与礼来和诺和诺德合作销售减肥药]]></title><description><![CDATA[远程医疗公司 Mangoceuticals 周四表示，它已与礼来和诺和诺德合作，通过其平台销售这两家制药公司的减肥药。【原文：Telehealth company Mangoceuticals said on Thursday it has partnered with Eli Lilly and Novo Nordisk to sell the drugmakers' blockbuster weight-loss drugs through its platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/mangoceuticals-partners-with-lilly-novo-nordisk-sell-weight-loss-drugs-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMOSNTJZRVJIZNOCXWR6BKRRQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 12:15:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利 Bending Spoons 公司准备 IPO，警告人工智能泡沫]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利科技公司 Bending Spoons 的首席执行官告诉路透社，该公司最早可能在明年上市，预计在收购视频流媒体平台 Vimeo 和门户网站 AOL 之后，调整后的盈利将翻一番。【原文：Italian tech company Bending Spoons could list as early as next year, when it expects to double adjusted earnings after buying video streaming platform Vimeo and web portal AOL, its chief executive told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/italys-bending-spoons-ready-ipo-warns-ai-bubble-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52YFQQJDFJPV3K6KYDQTULV5QE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 12:13:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美联储降息现在是掷硬币]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ILHMXTG4KFK2ZNHOGEFCP7P2VE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:59:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克工会咖啡师将在 40 个城市举行罢工，推动合同谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克工会称，美国 40 多个城市的 1000 多名星巴克工会咖啡师于周四发起了一场无休止的罢工，进一步推动该咖啡巨头就薪酬和其他福利问题达成集体谈判协议。【原文：More than 1,000 Starbucks unionized baristas in over 40 U.S. cities launched an open-ended strike on Thursday, the union said, escalating their push for a collective bargaining agreement over pay and other benefits at the coffee giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/starbucks-union-baristas-walk-out-40-cities-push-contract-talks-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VD5YBBEQRBK5LLIGNK6MUB33TI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:45:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼提高股息和回购，乐园和流媒体推动利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼周四表示，将把 2026 财年的股息提高 50%，并把股票回购计划增加一倍，因为这家媒体巨头的流媒体和乐园业务推动了季度盈利的增长。【原文：Walt Disney said on Thursday it would boost its dividend by 50% and double its share buyback plan for fiscal 2026, as the media giant's streaming and parks businesses powered a quarterly earnings beat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-boosts-dividend-buyback-parks-streaming-drive-profit-beat-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B32GT5QB4ZOIXOYPYQXL6YFN3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:41:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大空头》的迈克尔-伯里注销了 Scion 资产管理公司的注册资格]]></title><description><![CDATA[因在 2008 年成功押注美国房地产市场而闻名的 "大空头 "投资者迈克尔-伯利（Michael Burry）已注销了他的对冲基金 Scion Asset Management。【原文："Big Short" investor Michael Burry, known for his successful bets against the U.S. housing market in 2008, has deregistered his hedge fund, Scion Asset Management.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/michael-burry-big-short-fame-deregisters-scion-asset-management-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKKM6CJYYJM5LO4DIPTZ4DSP6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:32:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部数据封锁加剧了即将发布的作物报告前的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国政府有史以来最长的一次停摆期间，农作物数据被封锁，导致分析师对玉米和大豆产量的估计出现了十年来最大的差异，因为在收获时节和关键的贸易谈判期间出现的信息真空扭曲了美国两种最有价值农作物的市场。【原文：A crop data blackout during the longest-ever U.S. government shutdown has led to the widest range of analyst estimates in a decade for corn and soybean yields, as an information vacuum at harvest time and during critical trade negotiations distorted the market for the country's two most valuable crops.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-data-blackout-fuels-uncertainty-ahead-upcoming-crop-report-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3G23DQFB3ZLRRNZV6TQDWBCDJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:15:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党高层抨击特朗普推迟对华出口限制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括参议院少数党领袖查克-舒默（Chuck Schumer）在内的参议院民主党高层人士周三抨击特朗普政府在上一轮与中国政府的贸易谈判中暂停一项阻止数千家中国公司获取美国技术的措施，称其为 "放弃关键的国家安全工具"。【原文：Top Senate Democrats including Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer took aim at the Trump administration on Wednesday for suspending a measure that blocked thousands of Chinese companies from accessing U.S. technology in the last round of trade talks with Beijing, calling it a "giveaway of key national security tools."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-democrats-slam-trump-delaying-export-curbs-china-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNRVRNNRLJMEPLPASPUFTYK224</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:07:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经》报道：日产考虑与本田在美国合作开发汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车公司首席执行官伊万-埃斯皮诺萨（Ivan Espinosa）周四告诉《日经商业日报》，日产汽车公司正在考虑与本田汽车公司在美国联合开发汽车和动力总成项目。【原文：Nissan Motor is considering a joint project for vehicle and powertrain development with Honda Motor in the U.S., Nissan CEO Ivan Espinosa told the Nikkei business daily on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-considering-car-development-with-honda-us-nikkei-quotes-nissan-ceo-saying-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5O4EY6NBYVINZKGHUPEM2MA6L4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地区联储银行可能成为特朗普施压的下一个阵地]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）寻求对利率和其他政策施加更多影响，美联储 12 位地区银行行长的重新任命这一历来例行的程序正受到关注，以寻找是否会成为对美国中央银行独立性的最新挑战的迹象。【原文：The historically routine process of reappointing the Federal Reserve's 12 regional bank presidents is being watched for signs of becoming the newest challenge to the U.S. central bank's independence, as President Donald Trump seeks more influence over interest rates and other policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/regional-fed-banks-could-be-next-front-trumps-pressure-campaign-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMYFO3YL6FIWRMN6HCXSBMW35Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府重新开放，但深刻的政治分歧依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国历史上最长的一次停摆导致空中交通受阻、低收入美国人的食品援助被削减、100 多万工人的工资被迫拖欠一个多月之后，美国政府将于周四恢复运转。【原文：The U.S. government is due to lumber back to life on Thursday after the longest shutdown in U.S. history snarled air traffic, cut food assistance to low-income Americans and forced more than 1 million workers to go unpaid for more than a month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-government-opens-back-up-deep-political-divisions-remain-2025-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETIJZU6G6VLEJPDE4YBZDIXHWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>