<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:05:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:05:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价关税冲击，苹果上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BY5FF2QA4BIGHC7DBQJYU4GSGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kenvue在战略审查中实现预期利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kenvue 周四公布的第二季度利润基本符合华尔街的预期，与此同时，这家消费保健公司正在进行战略审查。【原文：Kenvue reported a second-quarter profit largely in line with Wall Street estimates on Thursday, amid a strategic review at the consumer health company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kenvue-meets-profit-estimates-amid-strategic-review-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XIKKWVX3FJKQHFNYUPCPSXHSLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:55:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[减重药物发力，礼来上调全年盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来（Eli Lilly）周四上调了全年利润预期，押注于其减肥特效药 Zepbound 需求的激增，因为该公司瞄准了新市场，并希望从诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）的 Wegovy 手中抢夺更多份额。【原文：Eli Lilly raised its full-year profit forecast on Thursday, betting on surging demand for its blockbuster weight-loss drug, Zepbound, as it targets new markets and looks to grab more share from Novo Nordisk's Wegovy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eli-lilly-raises-full-year-profit-forecast-weight-loss-drug-strength-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQAAAU2XVBMORGI47FJ7SL2VZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Firefly Aerospace 将在今年美国最大的太空首次公开募股后首次亮相]]></title><description><![CDATA[Firefly Aerospace 公司将于本周四开始在纳斯达克上市交易，此前该公司在美国上市融资 8.683 亿美元，是今年美国最大的太空技术公司。【原文：Firefly Aerospace will begin trading on the Nasdaq on Thursday after raising $868.3 million in the largest U.S. listing this year by a space tech company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/firefly-aerospace-set-debut-after-largest-us-space-ipo-year-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6CYACWF3VM3FJPKSB5VUIC35A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:52:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税豁免希望升温，科技股拉升华尔街期货价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周四上涨，预示着华尔街将出现新的涨势，因为有迹象表明，主要科技公司将避免美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对芯片进口征收最新关税。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Thursday, pointing to fresh gains on Wall Street, on signs that major technology companies will avoid President Donald Trump's latest tariffs on chip imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tech-shares-lift-wall-st-futures-tariff-exemption-hopes-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPDVH7KV5VOPTFFB7JHUCAI4SQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:50:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡吉宝集团为教育和数据中心资产募集 49 亿美元私人资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡吉宝集团（Keppel）是一家全球资产管理和运营商，该公司周四表示，今年迄今已为其私人基金战略（包括教育资产和数据中心）获得 63 亿新元（49.1 亿美元）的管理资金。【原文：Singapore's Keppel has secured S$6.3 billion ($4.91 billion) in funds under management so far this year for its private fund strategies, including education assets and data centres, the global asset manager and operator said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapores-keppel-raises-49-billion-private-funds-education-data-centre-assets-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUVHLL637ZOJ7NGHSCKLRCBTPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:48:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国贷款机构在关闭账户时考虑的是声誉规则而非政治因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士说，美国一些主要银行关闭账户的决定是基于有关声誉风险的规定，这回击了唐纳德-特朗普总统关于他和他的保守派支持者因政治原因而被拒绝提供服务的指责。【原文：Decisions by some major U.S. banks to close accounts were based on rules around reputational risk, people familiar with the matter said, pushing back on President Donald Trump's accusation that he and his conservative supporters were denied services for political reasons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-lenders-weighed-reputation-rules-not-politics-closing-accounts-sources-say-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7XLXY65ZRKO3BPXAN4A44KZAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:45:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道安哥拉债券反弹后从摩根大通取回2亿美元抵押品]]></title><description><![CDATA[安哥拉财政部称，在其债券价格反弹、缓解了财政压力之后，安哥拉于5月取回了2亿美元抵押品，这些抵押品是安哥拉今年早些时候不得不向摩根大通提供的。【原文：Angola got back $200 million of collateral in May that it had to post to JPMorgan earlier in the year, the finance ministry said, after the price of its bond rebounded, easing pressure on its finances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/angola-gets-back-200-million-collateral-jpmorgan-after-bond-rebound-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPRBXDNA7FJZ5LYL6USKGSFVX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:42:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[快餐需求改善，Restaurant Brands 季度销售额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，Restaurant Brands 的第二季度营收超过预期，原因是该公司的营销活动推动了美国和国际市场对汉堡王和其他品牌的需求。【原文：Restaurant Brands beat second-quarter revenue estimates on Thursday, as its marketing efforts drove demand at Burger King and other brands in the U.S. and international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/restaurant-brands-beats-quarterly-sales-estimates-improving-fast-food-demand-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQNYRE2YBRPRVF7T3R5GRW37KY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:35:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普减免关税后，苹果引领全球科技股大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）发出最新的关税警告后，全球科技股周四出现了缓解性反弹，在很大程度上豁免了对芯片和半导体征收100%关税的威胁。【原文：Global technology stocks advanced on Thursday in a relief rally after the latest tariff salvo from U.S. President Donald Trump largely exempted industry heavyweights from his threat to impose 100% levy on chips and semiconductors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/apple-leads-surge-global-tech-shares-after-trump-tariff-relief-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P27S7NYWR5OYXCRRQIZUJQ2X7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国牧场主慢慢开始重建锐减的牛群]]></title><description><![CDATA[内布拉斯加州的牧场主克雷格-乌登（Craig Uden）在五月份的几周内多买了 200 头母牛和它们的孩子，以扩大他的牛群，因为干旱的天气让位于雨水，雨水使用于放牧的土地重新焕发生机。【原文：Nebraska cattle rancher Craig Uden bought 200 extra mother cows and their babies over a few weeks in May to expand his herd as dry weather gave way to rain that rejuvenated land used for grazing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/us-cattle-ranchers-slowly-start-rebuild-decimated-herd-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQZZZRT6HZP5PEJJDLDZV6RP4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：特朗普将签署命令，为 401(k) 另类资产开辟道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周四援引一位熟悉该计划的人士的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周四签署一项行政命令，旨在允许私募股权、房地产、加密货币和其他另类资产参与 401（k）计划。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will sign an executive order on Thursday that aims to allow private equity, real estate, cryptocurrency and other alternative assets in 401(k)s, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing a person familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-sign-order-opening-way-alternative-assets-401ks-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEHSTT7IUVPTTKWQZ65BG7TZHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:17:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾调查 16 家中国企业挖走高科技人才]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾当局周四表示，他们正在调查 16 家涉嫌挖走半导体和其他高科技人才的中国公司，因为人们对技术外流的担忧与日俱增。【原文：Taiwan authorities said on Thursday they were investigating 16 Chinese companies for allegedly poaching semiconductor and other high-tech talent, amid growing concerns over technology outflows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-investigates-16-chinese-firms-poaching-high-tech-talent-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLL3CU5DCNIMNDRMS6MUA2V4S4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airbnb 下跌，因增长前景放缓再次引发对旅游需求放缓的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四收盘前，Airbnb 的股价下跌了 6%，因为该公司预测今年下半年的增长将放缓，这让该行业的投资者感到失望，因为在主要旅游公司发布强劲的业绩展望后，他们预期旅游需求将出现反弹。【原文：Shares of Airbnb slumped 6% before the bell on Thursday after the company forecast slower growth in the second half of the year, disappointing investors of the sector expecting a rebound in travel demand after strong outlooks from major travel firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/airbnb-dips-slower-growth-outlook-renews-fears-travel-demand-slowdown-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLKTNG5MBVONTPSTGN2G6QLKCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[压力重重的美国低收入购物者寻找小包装、5 美元以下的餐厅餐饮]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝洁公司、可口可乐公司和Chipotle Mexican Grill公司的高管们表示，由于美国对进口商品征收关税将进一步推高价格，美国低收入家庭正在减少外出就餐、旅游以及尿布、苏打水和啤酒等主食。【原文：Lower-income U.S. households are cutting back on eating out, travel and pantry staples like diapers, soda and beer, as U.S. tariffs on imports are set to push prices even higher, said executives from Procter & Gamble , Coca-Cola and Chipotle Mexican Grill .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/stressed-us-low-income-shoppers-hunt-smaller-packs-restaurant-meals-under-5-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35VMJ3VG5JNX7HXEPNR3NLEMRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[陷入困境的美国医疗保健股经历了艰难的 2025 年，但吸引了一些低价猎手]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年以来，美国医疗保健类股的困境进一步恶化，部分原因是特朗普政府的政策，但一些投资者打赌，这些被打压的股票现在正变得太便宜了，不能错过。【原文：Woes for U.S. healthcare stocks have worsened this year driven partly by Trump administration policies, although some investors are betting that the beaten-down shares are now becoming too much of a bargain to pass up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/struggling-us-healthcare-stocks-endure-rough-2025-draw-some-bargain-hunters-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7XMSL66QBPVPEQZCGIGN6EPXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普看似赢得了贸易战，但障碍依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[乍一看，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普似乎正在赢得他今年 1 月重返白宫后发动的贸易战，让主要贸易伙伴屈从于他的意志，对几乎所有进口商品征收两位数的关税，缩小贸易逆差，每月为联邦政府国库带来数百亿美元的急需现金。【原文：At a glance, U.S. President Donald Trump appears to be winning the trade war he unleashed after returning to the White House in January, bending major trading partners to his will, imposing double-digit tariff rates on nearly all imports, narrowing the trade deficit, and raking in tens of billions of dollars a month in much-needed cash for federal government coffers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-may-look-like-hes-winning-trade-war-hurdles-remain-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZW6TQPAKFM6DJWDMKWBS7W32Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 SAP 公司将向越南研发中心投资 1.5 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国软件制造商思爱普公司（SAP）周四表示，该公司将在未来五年内投资 1.5 亿欧元（1.7513 亿美元）在越南建立一个研发中心。【原文：German software maker SAP will invest 150 million euros ($175.13 million) in a research and development centre in Vietnam over the next five years, the firm said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/germanys-sap-invest-150-million-euros-vietnam-rd-centre-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIGDHQRU4RLVHHDHPCJWXFD3QE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中芯国际第二季度利润同比下降 19.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最大的合约芯片制造商中芯国际集成电路制造有限公司（Semiconductor Manufacturing International Corp.【原文：Semiconductor Manufacturing International Corp ，China's largest contract chip maker, reported on Thursday a 19.5% year-on-year decline in second-quarter profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/smic-second-quarter-profit-declined-195-year-on-year-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35KMNM4FURP4JMTCUQK5GPBIWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国汽车协会称欧盟-美国贸易协议必须立即生效]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车工业协会（VDA）周四表示，欧盟与美国之间承诺达成的贸易协定现在就需要实施，这样汽车行业才能得到一些缓解。【原文：Germany's VDA auto association said on Thursday that the promised trade agreement between the EU and the United States needed to be implemented now so the industry could receive some relief.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/germanys-auto-association-says-eu-us-trade-deal-must-take-effect-now-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUV7NXWT3FO5RM55P5XO4LFCUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7 月，Wegovy 和 Mounjaro 在印度的销量环比翻番]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司Pharmarack周四提供的数据显示，丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司的Wegovy和美国竞争对手礼来公司的Mounjaro七月份在印度的销量比上月翻了一番。【原文：Sales of Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk 's Wegovy and U.S. rival Eli Lilly's Mounjaro in India doubled in July from a month earlier, data from research firm Pharmarack showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/wegovy-mounjaro-sales-india-double-month-july-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6J6YWWYW35PYDO2OE6KE4VPLSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:41:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为与奇瑞的联合电动汽车品牌承诺新投资 14 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[华为与奇瑞的合资电动汽车品牌周四表示，将投资超过 100 亿元人民币（13.9 亿美元），并将其研发团队扩大到 5000 人。【原文：Huawei's joint electric vehicle brand with Chery said on Thursday that it will invest more than 10 billion yuan ($1.39 billion) and expand its research and development team to 5,000 people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/huaweis-joint-ev-brand-with-chery-pledges-14-billion-new-investment-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AS2ZR2AGHNPDNBK24EYQRVDFXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外国人因看好人工智能和经济增长而向台湾和韩国股市注入数十亿美元资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份，外资连续第三个月涌入亚洲股市，其中流入台湾的资金创下近二十年来的新高，泰国股市也结束了九个月的连跌走势。【原文：Foreign investors flocked to Asian stocks for the third straight month in July, with inflows into Taiwan hitting a near two-decade high and Thailand snapping its nine-month losing streak, buoyed by growth and AI prospects as trade worries fluctuate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/foreigners-pour-billions-into-taiwan-south-korea-stocks-ai-growth-optimism-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJ4JW5L4AVINBDERHJIXSX4F3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bumble 股价因用户数量下降和人工智能战略担忧而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，约会应用 Bumble 的股价在盘前交易中下跌超过 6%，原因是投资者对其人工智能创新步伐存疑而导致的用户数量下降以及对其提高支出能力的担忧做出了反应。
面对持续通胀和创新停滞导致的用户参与度下降，Bumble 及其较大的竞争对手 Match 一直在对其应用进行改造，以赢回用户。【原文：Shares of dating app Bumble fell over 6% in premarket trading on Thursday, as investors reacted to a drop in subscribers and concerns about its ability to boost spending amid doubts over the pace of its AI innovation.
Faced with falling user engagement driven by persistent inflation and stagnant innovation, Bumble and its larger rival Match have been revamping their apps to win back subscribers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bumble-shares-drop-subscriber-decline-ai-strategy-concerns-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGJFZYRKZZOP3POT3VJQFP3FIE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国最高法院将间谍软件的使用限制在严重犯罪范围内]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国最高法院周四裁定，只有在涉及严重犯罪的情况下，执法人员才能使用秘密安装的间谍软件监控电话和电脑。【原文：Germany's top court ruled on Thursday that law enforcement officials can use secretly installed spy software to monitor phones and computers only in cases that involve serious crimes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/germanys-top-court-limits-use-spy-software-serious-crimes-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHU6HFRYIZMI3IK24NMARC3CJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:08:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税分裂日本公司，丰田下调预期，索尼、本田上调预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策正在对日本公司造成巨大冲击，丰田汽车（Toyota Motor）等一些大型出口商下调了利润预期，而索尼（Sony）和本田（Honda）等公司则表示，关税影响将比他们担心的要小。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs are cleaving Japan Inc, as some big exporters like Toyota Motor slash their profit forecasts while Sony and Honda are among those saying the impact will be less than they had feared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-tariffs-split-japan-inc-toyota-cuts-forecast-while-sony-honda-raise-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYNR2NQD7RPT5LI6JLOADWOKUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚对特朗普威胁将美国药品关税提高至 250% 感到担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚卫生部长周四表示，澳大利亚非常关注美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最近威胁要在较长时期内将药品进口关税提高高达250%。【原文：Australia is very concerned about U.S. President Donald Trump's latest threat to raise tariffs on pharmaceutical imports by up to 250% over the longer term, its health minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-worried-by-trump-threat-raise-us-pharma-tariffs-250-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXJ2BX6W7ZJTLJU3UI3ZS4MWHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税拖累，消费疲软，日本下调经济增长预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周四下调了本财年的经济增长预期，原因是美国关税导致资本支出放缓，持续的通胀拖累了私人消费，威胁到脆弱的经济复苏。【原文：Japan's government cut its growth forecast for this fiscal year on Thursday as U.S. tariffs slow capital expenditure and persistent inflation weighs on private consumption, threatening a fragile economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-cuts-growth-forecast-us-tariffs-drag-weaker-consumption-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5YUCY3SWVJRNPIRCBJRD4LWCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印美关税僵局：新德里有哪些选择和风险？]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度很可能成为受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普贸易攻势打击最严重的国家之一，如果三周内不能达成协议，印度进口商品的关税将激增至 50%。【原文：India is likely to be among the countries worst hit by U.S. President Donald Trump's trade offensive, with tariffs on Indian imports set to surge to 50% if a deal is not struck in three weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-us-tariff-standoff-what-are-new-delhis-options-risks-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MONBF5KKY5IS3AZJ2IJ6VKHATI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港稳定币法案的客户身份规定引发业界关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士表示，香港新的稳定币法律规定了严格的客户身份识别规则，这可能会阻碍数字货币的应用，并影响香港在全球数字金融市场的竞争力。【原文：The strict customer identification rules mandated in Hong Kong’s new stablecoin law could hinder adoption of the digital currency and the city's competitiveness in global digital finance markets, sources from the industry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hong-kong-stablecoin-bills-client-identity-rules-spark-industry-concern-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QL5MEN57VKTNL5KD33MFVXHRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>