<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 21:07:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 21:07:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[桑坦德银行任命莱利为桑坦德银行美国分行首席执行官，这是更广泛改组的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[桑坦德银行执行主席安娜-博廷（Ana Botin）周五表示，克里斯蒂安娜-莱利（Christiana Riley）将接替蒂姆-温纳斯（Tim Wennes）担任桑坦德银行美国首席执行官，桑坦德银行正在进行更广泛的全球重组。【原文：Christiana Riley will succeed Tim Wennes as CEO of Santander in the United States, the bank's executive chair, Ana Botin, said on Friday, as Santander undertakes a wider global restructuring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/santander-names-riley-ceo-santander-us-part-wider-reshuffle-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MM2SDKW2MFNZVN5HKLUZK3VF7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:35:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[古巴与美国关系日益紧张，哈瓦那俱乐部仍保持朗姆酒畅销]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈瓦那俱乐部（Havana Club）的高层管理人员本周表示，即使古巴的甘蔗收成跌至历史最低点，华盛顿与哈瓦那之间的紧张局势加剧，该公司仍将继续生产其著名的顺滑朗姆酒。【原文：Havana Club will keep churning out its famously smooth rum even as Cuba's sugar cane harvests plummet to historic lows and tensions ratchet up between Washington and Havana, the company's top executive said this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/havana-club-keep-rum-flowing-even-cuba-us-tensions-grow-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEALXJSMJZLWZH7MPAZ4YAM4NQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:28:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Meta 正在商谈在得克萨斯州或其他州重新注册公司，退出特拉华州]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，Meta Platforms 正在讨论将公司注册地从特拉华州转移到德克萨斯州或其他州。【原文：Meta Platforms is discussing moving its incorporation from Delaware to Texas or other states, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-talks-reincorporate-texas-or-another-state-exit-delaware-wsj-reports-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPBVVY3PWNMWRDKEZAM4G3XUO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司裁员 4000 多人]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周五表示，尽管沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）经营的这家企业集团有望实现创纪录的年度营业利润，但该公司在过去一年中已裁员 4000 多人。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway said on Friday it has shed more than 4,000 jobs over the last year, even as the conglomerate run by Warren Buffett is on pace to post a record annual operating profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/berkshire-hathaway-has-shed-more-than-4000-jobs-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GO4FHJBBFFMYTA4ESBFXUWXHQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管承诺降低成本，特朗普关税仍将刺激美国食品通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家和食品行业高管表示，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对加拿大和墨西哥进口商品征收关税，正在努力应对牛肉和鸡蛋价格飞涨的美国消费者将面临更高的肉类、蔬菜和水果成本。【原文：U.S. consumers grappling with soaring prices for beef and eggs will face even higher costs for meat, vegetables and fruit if President Donald Trump imposes tariffs on Canadian and Mexican imports, economists and food industry executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-tariffs-stoke-us-food-inflation-despite-pledge-lower-costs-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLMFYUEQB5KHRPJDNFKCDER3OM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农产品出口/进口受到特朗普贸易行动的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正计划对从墨西哥和加拿大进口的商品征收 25% 的关税，并威胁对其他国家的商品征收关税，这引发了进口美国农产品的国家对贸易报复的担忧。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is planning to impose 25% tariffs on imports from Mexico and Canada and has threatened duties on goods from other nations, sparking concerns of trade retaliation from countries that import U.S. agricultural goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-agricultural-exportsimports-threatened-by-trump-trade-actions-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZTAEZX2SJKDVNUKSBWLLUIM34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟在新电影上映前遭遇超人版权诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[在华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros. Discovery）的新电影《超人》上映之前，超人的一位联合创作人的遗产向美国法院提起了版权诉讼。【原文：The estate of one of Superman's co-creators has filed a copyright lawsuit in a U.S. court against Warner Bros. Discovery ahead of the release of its new movie "Superman," part of a planned reboot of the DC Comics superhero film franchise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-hit-with-superman-copyright-lawsuit-ahead-new-movie-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLLQ72PGYRLUPEKW5PXN22BIIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将于周六对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫发言人卡罗琳-利维特（Karoline Leavitt）周五表示，美国将对加拿大和墨西哥征收25%的关税，并对中国征收10%的关税，但她拒绝透露是否会有豁免。【原文：The U.S. will impose 25% tariffs on Canada and Mexico, along with 10% on China, White House spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt said on Friday, but she declined to say whether there will be exemptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-will-implement-tariffs-mexico-canada-china-saturday-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUJ2H47E6BISRERJ3YXRVG6XXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 18:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高露洁希望减少墨西哥生产的牙膏可能受到的关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[高露洁棕榄公司首席财务官斯坦-苏图拉（Stan Sutula）周五在与华尔街分析师的电话会议上表示，该公司正在研究如何减少可能的关税对其牙膏的影响。【原文：Colgate Palmolive is looking at ways to reduce the impact of possible tariffs on its toothpastes, which the company manufactures in Mexico for the U.S. market, Chief Financial Officer Stan Sutula said on a call with Wall Street analysts on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/colgate-looking-reduce-impact-possible-tariffs-toothpaste-made-mexico-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKU7DXYR7JLCNF62NCMSM76PUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 18:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国高管对关税的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要对盟国墨西哥和加拿大的进口商品征收关税，在本季度财报季初，关税一直是企业高管们最关心的问题。【原文：Tariffs have been top-of-mind for corporate executives in the early days of this quarter's earnings season as U.S. President Donald Trump threatens to hit allies Mexico and Canada with levies on imported goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/what-worries-us-executives-about-tariffs-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWMU2O6YIBOF5KF32IM56AA45I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 18:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，联合利华希望冰淇淋业务在纽约上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，联合利华集团正在评估其冰淇淋业务的各种选择，包括在纽约上市。【原文：Unilever Plc is evaluating options, including a New York listing, for its ice-cream business, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-eyes-new-york-listing-ice-cream-business-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPDJUMRORJK3HCLOPJ4KC6KTWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:51:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税迫在眉睫，华尔街担忧盈利受挫和通胀压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普兑现其关税威胁，投资者将为美国企业利润即将受到的打击和通胀压力做好准备。【原文：Investors are bracing for a looming hit to U.S. corporate profits and pressure on inflation if President Donald Trump makes good on his tariff threats, with markets seen as not fully factoring in risks from higher levies on foreign imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/looming-tariffs-worry-wall-street-over-earnings-hit-inflation-pressure-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRZF3HQL55LS7FT25AGH7UTIPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔从 10.6 亿欧元欧盟反垄断罚款中获得 5.36 亿美元利息]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断主管特雷莎-里贝拉（Teresa Ribera）向欧盟立法者表示，美国芯片制造商英特尔已从欧盟反垄断监管机构收到5.1555亿欧元（5.36亿美元）的违约利息，这笔利息与2009年征收的10.6亿欧元罚款有关。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Intel has received 515.55 million euros ($536 million) in default interest from EU antitrust regulators related to a 1.06 billion euro fine levied in 2009, EU antitrust chief Teresa Ribera has told EU lawmakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-gets-536-million-interest-106-billion-euro-eu-antitrust-fine-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2REMHXU3BI2FBGW76OQQU3VGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:39:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称，特朗普将从 3 月 1 日起对墨西哥和加拿大征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉计划的人士告诉路透社记者，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普预计将宣布从3月1日起对加拿大和墨西哥征收新的关税，但其中将包括两国为某些进口产品寻求特定豁免的程序。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is expected to announce new tariffs against Canada and Mexico that will begin on March 1, but will include a process for the countries to seek specific exemptions for certain imports, three people familiar with the planning told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-set-impose-tariffs-mexico-canada-starting-march-1-sources-say-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EK2VB3KQZVPJ3MMVKYGGEGWEM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:13:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉称 MPS 竞购 Mediobanca 存在风险，但评估为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周五表示，如果托斯卡纳银行竞购成功，锡耶纳蒙地帕斯基银行（Monte dei Paschi di Siena）收购更大的竞争对手Mediobanca银行的计划将难以实施。【原文：Monte dei Paschi di Siena's acquisition of bigger rival Mediobanca would be challenging to implement if the Tuscan bank's bid succeeded, Fitch Ratings said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/fitch-says-mps-bid-mediobanca-carries-risks-too-early-assess-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5JCT47DYBI43DZO73WN24TXPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[珍珠能源支持的 Infinity Natural 公司估值 13 亿美元，股价在纽交所首次亮相时大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权支持的 Infinity Natural Resources 石油和天然气生产商的股票周五在纽约证券交易所首次上市时上涨了 10.8%，估值达 13 亿美元。【原文：Private equity-backed Infinity Natural Resources was valued at $1.30 billion after shares of the oil and natural gas producer rose 10.8% in their debut on the New York Stock Exchange on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/infinity-natural-resources-valued-13-bln-nyse-debut-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQJWQQPCQFOI7HJM6E2BB6RILA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道墨西哥石油公司与亿万富翁斯利姆重新谈判深水天然气项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥亿万富翁投资者卡洛斯-斯利姆（Carlos Slim）的团队和国家能源公司 Pemex 正在讨论对开发该国首个深水天然气田的协议进行实质性修改，五位熟悉此事的消息人士告诉路透社。【原文：Mexican billionaire investor Carlos Slim's team and state energy company Pemex are discussing substantial changes to a deal to develop the country's first deepwater natural gas field, five sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/mexicos-pemex-billionaire-slim-renegotiate-deepwater-gas-project-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ON2NF2M47JL4XPEINHBMLPJJMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄牙称 Novo Banco IPO 持股比例可能高达 30]]></title><description><![CDATA[葡萄牙财政部长若阿金-米兰达-萨门托（Joaquim Miranda Sarmento）周五表示，美国私募股权公司 Lone Star 已告知葡萄牙政府，该公司有可能通过首次公开募股的方式出售在新银行（Novo Banco）25-30% 的股份，而不是寻求全面出售。【原文：U.S. private equity firm Lone Star has told the Portuguese government that it is likely to sell a 25-30% stake in Novo Banco via an initial public offering, rather than seek a full sale, Finance Minister Joaquim Miranda Sarmento said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/portugal-says-novo-banco-ipo-likely-be-stake-up-30-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVT4GMRWCFMDXPEV45D7TAVRN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 16:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通任命塔库尔为全球市场部门唯一主管，西佩尔离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五看到的一份内部备忘录显示，摩根大通全球市场联席主管杰森-西佩尔（Jason Sippel）将离开这家华尔街贷款机构，普拉纳夫-塔库尔（Pranav Thakur）被任命为该业务的唯一主管。【原文：JPMorgan Chase's co-head of global markets, Jason Sippel, is leaving the Wall Street lender and Pranav Thakur has been named sole head of the business, an internal memo seen by Reuters showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-names-thakur-sole-head-global-markets-unit-sippel-departs-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4S4CGDDFVLB7ECGWEDIQOJ67U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LinkedIn 就人工智能模型使用客户数据提起的诉讼被驳回]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项集体诉讼提案指控微软旗下的 LinkedIn 侵犯了数百万高级客户的隐私，披露了他们的私人信息以训练生成人工智能模型，该提案已被驳回。【原文：A proposed class action accusing Microsoft's LinkedIn of violating the privacy of millions of Premium customers by disclosing their private messages to train generative artificial intelligence models has been dismissed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/linkedin-lawsuit-over-use-customer-data-ai-models-is-dismissed-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S325ZRA7NJLK3BBJYTHONOHCQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 15:46:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比对最新通胀数据感到欣慰，但对关税感到担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）表示，周五公布的通胀数据略好于预期，这让他对通胀率正朝着2%的目标前进感到欣慰，但他补充说，他仍预计美国央行的政策利率将在12至18个月内 "相当低一点"。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee said inflation data released on Friday was a bit better than expected and gives him comfort that inflation is on path to the 2% target, adding that he still expects the U.S. central bank's policy rate to be "a fair bit" lower in 12 to 18 months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-says-he-likes-inflation-data-cites-policy-uncertainties-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USSEV5Z4ZVL5TDSKUCUV7ZEBRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 15:34:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FTX 与克林顿前助手的投资公司达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[FTX 上周五表示，它已与希拉里-克林顿前助手联合创办的风险投资公司 K5 Global 达成和解，解决了这家破产的加密货币交易所去年 6 月对该公司提起的诉讼。【原文：FTX said on Friday it had reached a settlement with K5 Global, a venture capital firm co-founded by a former aide to Hillary Clinton, resolving a lawsuit the bankrupt crypto exchange had brought against the company in June last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ftx-reaches-settlement-with-ex-clinton-aides-investment-firm-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4HYEFKJ3NJ7FCFFECPNMR4OJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 15:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫官员称特朗普将于周五会见英伟达首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周五在白宫会见英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋，此前有报道称特朗普政府正在研究限制向中国销售人工智能芯片的新方法。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will meet with Nvidia chief executive Jensen Huang at the White House on Friday, a White House official said, following reports the Trump administration is studying new ways to restrict AI chip sales to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-meet-with-nvidia-ceo-friday-white-house-official-says-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GV4VI4663NIGDOBAXHOESJL3LE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:57:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司股价攀升，关税成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，全球股市上涨，结束了本周动荡不安的市场，苹果公司的财报和美国通胀数据的一致也提振了市场情绪。【原文：Global stocks rose on Friday at the end of a volatile week for markets, as sentiment was buoyed by Apple's earnings report and an in-line U.S. inflation reading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKW3GBZ2NNIK5DEK4LK43UNYM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 12 月 PCE 通胀上扬支持美联储按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 12 月份物价上涨，消费者支出激增，这表明美联储今年可能会推迟一段时间降息。【原文：U.S. prices increased in December while consumer spending surged, suggesting that the Federal Reserve could delay cutting interest rates for some time this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-us-dec-pce-inflation-uptick-supports-fed-hold-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITIQJN5EINNFPNSHDWHNGVSZ7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 的 WhatsApp 称以色列间谍软件公司 Paragon 将数十名用户作为攻击目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 流行的 WhatsApp 聊天服务的一位官员说，以色列间谍软件公司 Paragon Solutions 已将其数十名用户作为攻击目标，其中包括记者和民间社会成员。【原文：An official with Meta's popular WhatsApp chat service said the Israeli spyware company Paragon Solutions had targeted scores of its users, including journalists and members of civil society.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/metas-whatsapp-says-israeli-spyware-company-paragon-targeted-scores-users-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAQ3MBHU2JJFVF66X5LW3PJ3JI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第四季度劳动力成本温和上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳动力成本在第四季度略有上升，这为美联储官员在2024年底降低通胀的进展停滞后提供了一些安慰。【原文：U.S. labor costs rose marginally in the fourth quarter, offering some comfort to Federal Reserve officials after progress lowering inflation stalled at the end of 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-labor-costs-rise-moderately-fourth-quarter-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6YL4GQDKVJV5NOCYQES2ZE3LQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员押注美联储下次降息将等到 6 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，交易员们继续押注美联储将等到6月份再恢复降息，因为政府数据显示，12月份美国中央银行的目标通胀率上升至2.6%，符合经济学家的预期。
美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）在发表鹰派货币政策讲话的同时公布了通胀报告，在通胀报告公布后，以美联储政策利率为结算基准的期货交易商认为，美联储6月会议后短期借款利率为4.25%或更低的可能性约为70%，与当天早些时候相比变化不大。【原文：Traders on Friday kept bets that the Federal Reserve will wait until June to resume interest rate cuts, after government data showed inflation by the U.S. central bank's targeted measure ticked up to 2.6% in December, as economists had expected.
After the inflation report, released at the same time as hawkish monetary policy remarks from Fed Governor Michelle Bowman, traders of futures that settle to the Fed's policy rate priced in about a 70% chance that the short-term borrowing rate will be 4.25% or lower after the Fed's June meeting, little changed from earlier in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/traders-bet-feds-next-rate-cut-will-wait-until-june-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZCTUYAT75OARJIAOXWWVDXYM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月通胀率上升；消费支出加速]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 12 月份物价上涨，消费者支出激增，这表明美联储今年可能会推迟一段时间降息。【原文：U.S. prices increased in December while consumer spending surged, suggesting that the Federal Reserve could delay cutting interest rates for some time this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-inflation-rise-december-consumer-spending-accelerates-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAI5IBF3Z5KNVHHE4GACCUYLAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:40:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油生产商雪佛龙公司在特朗普发布更名令后使用 "美国湾 "一词]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油生产商雪佛龙公司（Chevron）在周五发布的第四季度新闻稿中使用了 "美国湾"（Gulf of America）而不是墨西哥湾，这是美国企业开始执行美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）为这一海洋盆地重新命名的命令的一个迹象。【原文：U.S. oil producer Chevron used the term "Gulf of America" instead of Gulf of Mexico in its fourth-quarter press release on Friday, a sign of corporate America beginning to implement U.S. President Donald Trump's order to rename the ocean basin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-producer-chevron-uses-term-gulf-america-after-trump-renaming-order-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LH6IZIBWURMILGOIJHMKDQJBWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>