<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:06:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:06:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税闪电战达成交易，但未能解决全球贸易问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易专家和分析人士说，唐纳德-特朗普的关税闪电战正在达成一些初步协议，包括美国和中国的天价关税暂停90天，以及与英国达成一项有限的贸易协定，但这位美国总统远未重新平衡全球贸易流动。【原文：Donald Trump's tariff blitz is yielding some initial deals, including a 90-day pause in sky-high U.S. and Chinese duties and a limited trade pact with Britain, but the U.S. president is far from rebalancing global commerce flows, trade experts and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-tariff-blitz-yields-deals-misses-global-trade-fix-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJUG2QCTFJORNL35A235HYFRVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 M&S 称客户信息在网络攻击中被窃取]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国零售商玛莎百货公司周二表示，一些客户的个人信息在网络攻击中被窃取，这次攻击使其在线业务瘫痪了三个多星期。【原文：British retailer Marks and Spencer said on Tuesday some personal customer information was taken in the cyber attack that has crippled its online operation for more than three weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uks-ms-says-customer-information-was-taken-cyber-attack-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHZGMK3XGRMIPGFIJ4SCCI5CYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行称，基金经理自 2006 年以来最看淡美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周二发布的全球基金经理调查（FMS）显示，由于唐纳德-特朗普总统混乱的贸易政策降低了投资者对美国资产的偏好，5月份全球资产经理持有19年来最大的美元减持仓位。【原文：Global asset managers held their biggest underweight position in the dollar in 19 years in May, as President Donald Trump's chaotic trade policy cut investor appetite for U.S. assets, Bank of America's global fund manager survey (FMS) showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fund-managers-most-underweight-us-dollar-since-2006-bofa-says-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJOAEMLFGBMZBCIHDQZUPXG3SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚太贸易特使讨论关税时代的多边合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚太地区的贸易特使们本周将齐聚韩国，就多边合作展开讨论，而会谈正值各国争相应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税之际。【原文：Asia-Pacific trade envoys will gather this week in South Korea for discussions on multilateral cooperation, with talks taking place at a time when countries are scrambling to respond to U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asia-pacific-trade-envoys-discuss-multilateral-cooperation-tariff-era-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7MWLEFRRNJDFO7E3A3GG4TXDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:03:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球首家商业规模的电子甲醇工厂在丹麦开业]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，全球首家商业规模的电子甲醇工厂在丹麦投入运营，航运巨头马士基公司将购买部分产品，作为其集装箱船队的低排放燃料。【原文：The world's first commercial-scale e-methanol plant began operations in Denmark on Tuesday, with shipping giant Maersk set to buy part of the production as a low-emission fuel for its fleet of container ships.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/worlds-first-commercial-scale-e-methanol-plant-opens-denmark-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFR3OCFZGJL45JXZRHGKRETIFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国暂停对中国征收关税给 "中国加一 "国家带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美达成新协议，暂停互相征收天价关税，这迫使越南和墨西哥等制造业中心与美国达成更好的协议，以继续从全球生产商的 "中国加一 "战略中获益。【原文：A new U.S.-China agreement to pause sky-high tariffs on each other is pressuring manufacturing hubs such as Vietnam and Mexico to make their own, better deals with the U.S. to continue benefiting from a "China-plus-one" strategy by global producers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-tariff-pause-beijing-puts-pressure-china-plus-one-countries-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EDLZ36JIJLIXEYTGYAQWVTRF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:51:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税影响，本田全年利润下降 59%，推迟加拿大电动车计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税带来的不确定性，日本本田汽车公司预测本财年利润将下降59%，并表示将搁置在加拿大建立电动汽车供应链的计划。【原文：Japan's Honda Motor forecast a 59% profit decrease in the current financial year and said it would put on hold a plan to build an EV supply chain in Canada, amid the uncertainty stemming from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-sees-full-year-profit-declining-59-us-tariffs-bite-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F36QBHGFJNZNBTPYPXYAHPBZ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本软银集团第四季度盈利 35 亿美元，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本投资集团软银集团（SoftBank Group）1-3 月净利润达 5,170 亿日元（约合 34.9 亿美元），原因是其持有的电信资产表现良好。【原文：Japanese investment conglomerate SoftBank Group booked a net profit of 517 billion yen ($3.49 billion) for January-March as its telecommunications holdings performed well.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/japans-softbank-group-books-35-billion-q4-profit-beats-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57BYQ2VDVZLUPKLIHPYDLPYKM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因看好贸易休战，高盛将美国经济衰退概率从 45% 下调至 35]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛将美国经济衰退预期从 45% 下调至 35%，成为首家下调预期的大型券商，此前与中国达成的临时关税休战协议提振了全球贸易战有所缓和的希望。【原文：Goldman Sachs cut its recession forecast for the U.S. to 35% from 45%, the first major brokerage to do so, after a temporary tariff truce with China boosted hopes of some easing in the global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-cuts-us-recession-odds-35-45-trade-truce-optimism-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FYRILQGMRJ3PIQ6KM2276JH5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:31:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果供应商 IQE 的年收入在市场预期之内]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国半导体公司 IQE 周二表示，预计其 2025 财年的收入将与市场预期一致，并补充说该公司正在关注出售其台湾业务的可能性。【原文：British semiconductor company IQE expects its revenue for the fiscal year 2025 to align with market expectations, the company said on Tuesday, adding that it was focusing on the potential sale of its Taiwan operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-chip-supplier-iqe-sees-fy25-revenue-within-market-view-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7FJRKLN6FKFZEIR3QKXL7UHAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:26:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称，作为重组的一部分，日产将暂停部分国内工厂的运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周二报道，作为业务重组努力的一部分，日本日产汽车公司决定暂停部分国内工厂的运营。【原文：Japan's Nissan Motor has decided to suspend operations at some domestic factories as part of a business restructuring effort, the Nikkei business daily reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-suspend-operations-some-domestic-plants-part-restructuring-nikkei-says-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JAVAJSZPBNXHEULBJ6SIVZIQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年，CATL 将在全球最大规模的上市活动中为银行提供低廉的费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[处理今年迄今为止全球最大上市交易的投资银行将获得远低于行业标准的承销费，在上市交易长期低迷之后，顾问们愿意忍受微薄的利润来赢得业务。【原文：Investment banks handling the world's largest listing so far this year are set to earn underwriting fees well below the industry norm, with advisers willing to endure skinny margins to win business following a prolonged slump in listings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/catl-offers-banks-slim-fees-worlds-largest-listing-2025-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KEZPBC4KVJCDLWOCBOMKXRHVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:26:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国贸易休战后，中国取消了对波音公司的交货禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，在与美国达成贸易休战协议后，中国取消了对航空公司接收波音飞机的禁令。【原文：China has removed a ban on airlines taking delivery of Boeing planes following a trade truce with the United States, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/china-removes-ban-boeing-deliveries-after-us-trade-truce-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MQ72IUWWVN37BCXSSUO54WT74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：在美国关税谈判之际，越南加大打击进口假冒产品的力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的文件显示，在美国指责越南是假冒伪劣和数字盗版的主要集散地并威胁要征收严厉的关税之后，越南正在加大打击假冒伪劣和数字盗版的力度。【原文：Vietnam is stepping up its fight against counterfeits and digital piracy after the United States accused the country of being a major hub for these illegal activities and threatened crippling tariffs, documents reviewed by Reuters show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/vietnam-cranks-up-fight-imported-counterfeits-amid-us-tariff-talks-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWM4O7AU4RNDJJHBPZTJ7PHYQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将对中国货物征收的 "最低 "关税从 120% 下调至 54]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫的一项行政命令称，美国将从 5 月 14 日起把对中国货物征收的 "最低 "关税从 120% 下调至 54%，并继续征收最低 100 美元的统一关税。【原文：A White House executive order said that the U.S. would cut the "de minimis" tariff on China shipments to 54% from 120%, with a minimum flat fee of $100 to remain starting from May 14.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-cut-de-minimis-tariff-china-shipments-54-120-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EC7HF6HVUFLDHKWDLOF7HY6CF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财富管理平台 Addepar 在新一轮融资中估值 32.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[财富管理平台提供商 Addepar 在新一轮 2.3 亿美元的融资中创下了 32.5 亿美元的估值，这得益于金融顾问们争相在动荡的市场中为富裕客户提供更好的数据。【原文：Wealth management platform provider Addepar has hit a valuation of $3.25 billion in a fresh $230 million funding round, as it benefits from a race by financial advisors to arm wealthy clients with better data in volatile markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/wealth-management-platform-addepar-valued-325-bln-new-funding-round-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEVUYOYJGZPWLA3QZ44Q5ZPI6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行在战略审查中坚持过去的刺激政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行的几位决策者告诉路透社记者，欧洲央行将在一次战略审查中坚持其过去十年的激进刺激政策，回避在一轮高通胀和巨额亏损之后进行自我批评的呼声。【原文：The European Central Bank will stand by its aggressive stimulus policy of the last decade in a strategy review, side-stepping calls for self-criticism after a bout of high inflation and sizeable losses, several ECB policymakers told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecb-stand-by-past-stimulus-policies-strategy-review-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRJ6IS4UWJN7VKNQZG3YAC67MM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 贸易战暂歇，重回磨合期]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZMBCOV6KFL6ZEPOGUALC6H6B4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 04:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：停电后，西班牙调查小型发电厂的网络漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周二报道，西班牙正在要求小型发电企业提供有关其网络防御的信息，因为调查上个月大停电事件的调查人员试图确定它们是否是被坏人利用来瘫痪该国电网的薄弱环节。【原文：Spain is demanding information from small electricity generators on their cyber defences as investigators probing last month’s blackout seek to determine whether they were a weak link exploited by bad actors to bring down the country’s power grid, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/spain-investigates-cyber-weaknesses-small-power-plants-after-blackout-ft-reports-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4ZIC27JUVPKTLIO3EBM4LUYDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 04:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚养老基金开始质疑美国战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对美国经济增长的信心减弱，澳大利亚 4.2 万亿澳元（约合 2.7 万亿美元）养老金领域的基金正在重新考虑其长期坚持的购买美国资产和美元的一些策略。【原文：Funds in Australia's A$4.2 trillion ($2.7 trillion) pension sector are rethinking some of their long-held strategies of buying U.S. assets and the dollar, as confidence in American growth wanes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-pension-funds-start-questioning-us-strategies-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWDOBBJBFZNTHJS5X7UUIKGHSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度向世贸组织提交的通知显示，印度拟对美国征收反关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度向世界贸易组织（WTO）表示，印度拟对美国生产并运往印度的部分产品征收关税，以对抗华盛顿对亚洲第三大经济体生产的钢铁和铝产品征收的关税。【原文：India has told the World Trade Organisation (WTO) that it proposes to levy duties on some products made in the U.S. and shipped to India, to counter Washington's tariffs on steel and aluminium products produced in Asia's No.3 economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/india-proposes-counter-duties-against-us-notice-wto-shows-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M632NJDDBNJYLDRTZVSYQUII3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:36:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：中国的人工智能仿人机器人旨在改变制造业]]></title><description><![CDATA[在上海郊区一个庞大的仓库里，数十个仿人机器人在操作员的操纵下，一遍又一遍地执行着折叠 T 恤、制作三明治和开门等任务。【原文：In a sprawling warehouse in a Shanghai suburb, dozens of humanoid robots are manoeuvred by their operators to carry out tasks like folding a T-shirt, making a sandwich and opening doors, over and over again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-ai-powered-humanoid-robots-aim-transform-manufacturing-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMSJ3CQC5JM3PKOFAK64SN5UAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年中拉贸易额突破 5000 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家主席习近平周二表示，去年中拉贸易额首次超过 5000 亿美元。【原文：Trade between China and Latin America exceeded $500 billion for the first time last year, China's President Xi Jinping said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-latin-america-trade-exceeded-500-billion-2024-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAB2H2L67NOI7E4WMZN56MCUJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易战暂停提振风险偏好，亚洲市场欢呼雀跃]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市加入了全球股市反弹的行列，美元则守住了大部分涨幅，因为中美贸易战暂时停息缓解了市场对全球经济衰退的担忧，令投资者松了一口气。【原文：Asian stocks joined the global rally and the U.S. dollar held on to most of its gains on Tuesday as investors heaved a sigh of relief after a temporary halt in the trade war between the U.S. and China eased worries of a global recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABG6TB2K6FOHDIALV4JP37TUZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:33:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元坚守中美贸易协定带来的涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周二保持强劲涨势，原因是投资者对美国和中国达成关税协议表示欢迎，该协议为世界两大经济体之间的贸易战踩下了刹车，而这场贸易战曾引发对全球经济衰退的担忧。【原文：The dollar held strong gains on Tuesday as investors cheered a tariff deal between the United States and China to tap the brakes on a trade war between the world's two largest economies that had fed fears of a global recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dollar-clings-gains-us-china-trade-pact-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCGK56XZUBJXZEB2B2NFNYPHAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:46:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚消费者信心从关税打击中部分恢复]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发动关税战的最初冲击略有减弱，衡量澳大利亚消费者情绪的一项指标在5月份出现部分反弹。【原文：A measure of Australian consumer sentiment partially rebounded in May as the initial shock of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff war faded a little, an improvement that should be underpinned by the latest truce with China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-consumer-sentiment-recovers-partially-tariff-blow-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBFAWV5S3FJBRDMSRG7ENSJJDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:38:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美暂停关税战，油价从两周高点回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国同意暂时削减关税，引发了对世界两大经济体之间的贸易战即将结束的乐观情绪，油价周二从上一交易日触及的两周高点回落。【原文：Oil prices eased on Tuesday from a two-week high reached during the previous session after the U.S. and China agreed to temporarily slash tariffs, sparking optimism that a trade war between the world's two biggest economies would come to an end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-ease-off-2-week-highs-after-us-china-pause-tariff-war-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75T4GZDBVZKP3NWTGT4PXX5NS4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北斗星为香港数据中心扩建获得融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[北斗数据中心（BDx Data Centers）周二表示，该公司已获得基础设施信贷公司 Clifford Capital、新加坡大华银行和日本三井住友银行的项目融资，用于在香港开发首个超大规模数据中心。【原文：BDx Data Centers said on Tuesday that it has secured project financing from infrastructure credit firm Clifford Capital, Singapore's United Overseas Bank and Japan's Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation for the development of its first hyperscale data centre in Hong Kong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bdx-secures-financing-data-centre-expansion-hong-kong-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42THAHVI6VLEPGCXGSM7LLOMWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行部分官员认为有恢复加息的余地，3 月份总结显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，日本央行 4 月 30 日至 5 月 1 日政策会议的意见摘要显示，一些日本央行董事会成员认为，如果美国关税问题的发展趋于稳定，那么在暂时暂停加息后仍有恢复加息的余地。【原文：Some Bank of Japan board members saw scope to resume interest rate hikes after a temporary pause if developments over U.S. tariffs stabilise, a summary of opinions at their April 30-May 1 policy meeting showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/boj-policymaker-called-keeping-rate-hike-stance-may-meeting-summary-shows-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZCBB2VNKZPLHD73FRXJVLPHKM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院共和党人寻求取消电动汽车税收抵免和贷款计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院共和党人周一提议取消电动汽车税收抵免，并废除旨在促使汽车制造商生产更多零排放汽车的燃油效率规定，作为基础广泛的税制改革法案的一部分。【原文：Republicans in the U.S. House of Representatives on Monday proposed killing the electric vehicle tax credit and repealing fuel efficiency rules designed to prod automakers into building more zero-emission vehicles as part of a broad-based tax reform bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-house-republicans-seek-kill-ev-tax-credit-loan-program-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADKNQS4JG5K2PA7XJUVI6QCSOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>