<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:31:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:31:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[蓝猫股价再度下跌，投资者消化债务基金调整影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[蓝猫资本周五盘前交易中股价下跌约4%，延续了前一交易日的跌势。此前这家另类资产管理公司公布了最新计划，拟从一只小型债务基金中返还资本，该消息令投资者惊慌，并拖累同行股价下挫。【原文：Blue Owl Capital shares fell about 4% in pre-market trading on Friday, extending the previous session's slide, after the alternative asset manager unveiled its latest plan to return capital from a small debt fund that spooked investors and dragged peers lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blue-owl-drops-again-investors-digest-debt-fund-changes-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQX5AWW6ERJXVFBISWMZMPSPGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员称，尽管面临阻力，欧盟仍应准备好实施与南方共同市场的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员马罗什·谢夫乔维奇周五表示，尽管法国反对且面临法律挑战，欧盟仍应准备在未来数月内启动其与南美洲南方共同市场集团的争议性自由贸易协定。【原文：The European Union should be ready to put into force its contentious free trade agreement with South America's Mercosur bloc in the coming months despite opposition from France and a legal challenge, EU trade chief Maros Sefcovic said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-should-be-ready-enact-mercosur-deal-despite-resistance-trade-chief-says-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7VVI55UCJISBHV3CCENGKYGYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利安德巴塞尔大幅削减季度股息]]></title><description><![CDATA[石化巨头利安德巴塞尔公司周五宣布削减第一季度股息，称这是化工行业遭遇的最长期低迷之一。【原文：Petrochemical maker LyondellBasell cut its first-quarter dividend on Friday, citing one of the longest downturns in the chemicals industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lyondellbasell-slashes-quarterly-dividend-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CI3XDUGYNZOHPOPFRHRKEUTXWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市期货在经济数据公布前表现平淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周五持平，投资者正等待关键经济数据以判断今年货币政策宽松的走向，同时密切关注与德黑兰的紧张局势以及美国最高法院对特朗普关税政策的潜在裁决。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were flat on Friday as investors awaited key economic data to gauge the path of monetary policy easing for the year while monitoring tensions with Tehran and a potential U.S. Supreme Court decision on Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-muted-ahead-economic-data-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4STPQE3MHNN3LMLBUP235ASXB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:52:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早盘竞价：原油被吞没]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克·多兰和ROI团队本周末最期待阅读、观看和收听的内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCEZV6UV6BKNPHTQVWG3HFREOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:39:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金吸引五周来最大资金流入，因人工智能相关担忧缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至2月18日的七天内，全球股票基金迎来五周来最强劲的资金流入。人工智能股票担忧情绪缓解，投资者转向其他板块支撑了需求，而美联储降息预期重燃提振了市场对美国经济增长的信心。【原文：Global equity funds received their strongest inflows in five weeks in the seven days to February 18, as easing concerns over artificial intelligence stocks and investor rotation into other sectors supported demand, while renewed hopes for Federal Reserve rate cuts lifted sentiment toward U.S. growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-pix-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DG7HV76KXRMNBL3PRAH4GDCZTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼-美国贸易协定要点]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚与美国周四敲定了一项贸易协议，将美国对东南亚最大经济体出口商品的关税从32%降至19%，此前双方进行了近一年的谈判。【原文：Indonesia and the United States finalised a trade deal on Thursday that cut U.S. levies to 19% from 32% on goods shipped from Southeast Asia's biggest economy, following nearly a year of negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/key-points-indonesia-us-trade-agreement-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPUVC3OF25LNXJZHWZE7CNNJTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周展望：英伟达与软件公司财报将考验人工智能相关股票市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者下周将关注人工智能行业风向标英伟达公司的财报，以稳定因人工智能相关担忧而动荡的美国股市。【原文：Investors turn to financial results from artificial intelligence bellwether Nvidia Corp in the coming week to steady a U.S. stock market that has been rocked by AI-related worries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-nvidia-software-reports-pose-next-tests-ai-sensitive-stock-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTAIGRYSZJIS3JCT2UHCXESJ5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国防工业新出台的网络安全规定为部分小型供应商设置了障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国针对国防领域出台的新网络安全法规，正迫使部分小型供应商重新考虑承接军工业务，因其合规成本过高。值此特朗普政府施压承包商提升产量并实现供应多元化的时期，此举正加剧生产风险。【原文：New U.S. cybersecurity rules for the defense sector are leading some small suppliers to rethink military work due to high compliance costs, raising production risks at a time when the Trump administration is pressuring contractors to boost output and diversify the supply base.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/new-cybersecurity-rules-us-defense-industry-create-barrier-for-some-small-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRXRR5XEPBIVHCWD2FN7RN7TKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：宾夕法尼亚大学沃顿商学院估算，最高法院裁决可能危及美国逾1750亿美元关税收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚大学沃顿商学院预算模型经济学家周五表示，若美国最高法院对特朗普总统广泛实施的紧急关税作出不利裁决，美国可能面临退还逾1750亿美元关税收入的风险。【原文：More than $175 billion in U.S. tariff collections are at risk of having to be refunded if the U.S. Supreme Court rules against President Donald Trump's broad emergency tariffs, Penn-Wharton Budget Model economists said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-tariff-revenue-risk-supreme-court-ruling-tops-175-billion-penn-wharton-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCJHUNSBZRJVDMMC3NX75GGNZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金创五周来最大单周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至2月18日当周，美国股票基金迎来大量资金流入。此前消费者价格通胀报告显示升温放缓，提振市场对美联储降息的预期，缓解了科技板块抛售的担忧。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw a substantial inflow of capital in the week to February 18 on easing worries over a selloff in the technology sector after a cooler consumer price inflation report boosted expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-largest-weekly-inflow-five-weeks-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJ5C6ATDGBNZ5AFUJ3S4QANW74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[秘鲁政局更迭频仍，市场却基本未受影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[秘鲁总统职位本周再度更迭，不到十年间该国已迎来第七位领导人。然而政治动荡并未引发市场剧烈波动，投资者似乎对此习以为常。【原文：Peru’s revolving-door presidency turned again this week, ushering out the country's seventh leader in less than a decade, but the political churn has produced little market turbulence as investors seem unfazed by the spin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/perus-markets-largely-unfazed-its-revolving-door-presidency-spins-again-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMBAWG5TUFIQNGU6L3AALOFIME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，特朗普盟友与俄罗斯诺瓦泰克公司就阿拉斯加天然气项目达成合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周五报道，与美国总统特朗普家族有联系的美国金融家詹特里·比奇去年秋季与俄罗斯能源巨头诺瓦泰克公司签署协议，在西方对俄实施制裁之际开发阿拉斯加天然气项目。【原文：American financier Gentry Beach, who has ties to U.S. President Donald Trump's family, signed an agreement with Russia’s energy giant Novatek last autumn to develop natural gas in Alaska amid Western sanctions against Russia, the New York Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-ally-ties-up-with-russias-novatek-natural-gas-alaska-nyt-reports-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSH4EIT7ENIJXNS33MPU7YKMN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国驻印度大使称，美方正就委内瑞拉石油销售事宜与印度进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国特使塞尔吉奥·戈尔周五表示，美国正就向印度出售委内瑞拉石油进行"积极谈判"，以帮助印度实现原油来源多元化。【原文：The United States is in "active negotiation" over the sale of Venezuelan oil to India, to help India diversify its sources of crude oil, U.S. Envoy Sergio Gor said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-negotiating-with-india-venezuelan-oil-sale-us-envoy-says-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5U2DBNR5VPBFII64ZQZEMS47A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[食品巨头达能对2026年前景充满信心，此前中国市场推动2025年销售额超预期增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国食品集团达能表示，在2025年销售额和现金流超出分析师预期后，公司正以信心开启2026年。得益于中国婴幼儿食品需求强劲，加上成本削减措施提升了利润率。【原文：French food group Danone said it was starting 2026 with confidence after it delivered 2025 sales and cash above analysts' expectations, helped by baby food demand in China, and improved its profit margin thanks to cost cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/food-group-danone-confident-over-2026-after-china-drives-2025-sales-beat-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOKE6W57M5NEHGVLC5UDLZ6DJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:34:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：乌克兰2026年国防出口额或达"数十亿美元"，官员称]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰国防部高级官员表示，该国今年可能出口价值数十亿美元的军用物资和服务，此前乌克兰首次批准了战时对外军售，并正考虑对这些出口征收关税。【原文：Ukraine could export several billion dollars of military goods and services this year after authorising its first wartime foreign sales and is considering introducing a tax on those exports, a senior Ukrainian defence official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ukraines-2026-defence-exports-could-hit-several-billion-dollars-official-says-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3ZP4OZYVRJZTL4RUSZWZ2DKIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁对伊朗动武]]></title><description><![CDATA[汤姆·韦斯特布鲁克带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/global-markets-view-europe-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKIN2Z3TY5NDTL5DKQFZ2YHMR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚养老基金UniSuper表示本币被低估，增加对冲操作]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚最大养老基金之一UniSuper已加大海外投资的对冲力度，该机构表示澳元被低估，随着澳美利差扩大，澳元汇率将走高。【原文：One of Australia's largest pension funds, UniSuper, has increased hedging of its overseas investments as it says the local currency is undervalued and will rise as the interest rate differential between Australia and the U.S. widens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-pension-fund-unisuper-says-local-currency-undervalued-increases-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2X3CFLNOVVJG7EEUWOLAV4Q2VQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》称亚马逊云服务部门遭遇至少两次涉及人工智能工具的故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[《金融时报》周五援引知情人士报道称，亚马逊云计算部门因其人工智能工具出现故障，已遭遇至少两次服务中断。【原文：Amazon's cloud unit has suffered at least two outages stemming from errors involving its own AI tools, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazons-cloud-unit-hit-by-least-two-outages-involving-ai-tools-ft-says-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQICKAVTZVLGHHF4FQPSCSGY4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:10:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经济增速在第四季度可能放缓，但仍保持强劲势头。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经济在去年政府停摆造成的干扰以及消费者支出放缓的影响下，第四季度增速可能放缓至仍属稳健的水平，不过减税政策和人工智能领域的投资预计将推动今年经济活动增长。【原文：U.S. economic growth likely slowed to a still-solid pace in the fourth quarter because of disruptions from last year's government shutdown and a moderation in consumer spending, though tax cuts and investment in artificial intelligence were expected to drive activity this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-economic-growth-likely-slowed-still-brisk-pace-fourth-quarter-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPHMKQ2ZCJPXLB2WHFNE2BN45A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱泼斯坦遗产管理方同意支付3500万美元和解金，以解决受害者集体诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周四提交的法庭文件显示，杰弗里·爱泼斯坦的遗产管理方已同意支付高达3500万美元，以解决一起集体诉讼案。该诉讼指控这位声名狼藉的金融家两名顾问协助并教唆其对年轻女性和少女实施性贩运。【原文：Jeffrey Epstein’s estate has agreed to pay as much as $35 million to resolve a class action lawsuit that accused two of the disgraced financier's advisers of aiding and abetting his sex trafficking of young women and teenage girls, according to a court filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/epstein-estate-agrees-35-million-settlement-victim-class-action-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMEJMLTPLJKBNLZZPMGHAURWBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，克里斯蒂娜·拉加德计划完成其在欧洲央行的任期。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，克里斯蒂娜·拉加德表示，她预计将完成其作为欧洲央行行长的使命直至任期结束，此前有猜测称她将提前辞职。【原文：Christine Lagarde said she expects completing her mission as president of the European Central Bank will take until the end of her term, amid speculation that she will resign early, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/christine-lagarde-intends-complete-her-term-ecb-wsj-reports-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRJXPUPEBBOW5AJTUDGTSHMK2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普会见诺华首席执行官，称制药商将在美国建11家工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普表示，他于周三在白宫会见了瑞士制药公司诺华的首席执行官瓦斯·纳拉辛汉。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said he met Vas Narasimhan, the chief executive officer of Swiss drugmaker Novartis , at the White House on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-meets-novartis-ceo-says-drugmaker-building-11-us-plants-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLLITQ2VRJKKFF3VCBIY6XHTNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫提议禁止部分投资者继续购置房产，《华尔街日报》报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普政府提议禁止拥有超过100套独栋住宅的投资者继续购置房产。该报道援引了白宫发送给国会委员会领导人的备忘录。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has proposed banning investors with more than 100 single-family homes from purchasing additional homes, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing a White House memo sent to congressional committee leaders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-proposes-banning-some-investors-buying-more-homes-wsj-reports-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO7TEIBEVRMOTFSSA4JQ6HZ75E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:45:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田车队的佐藤本是关键时刻的英雄——然而局势转瞬即变]]></title><description><![CDATA[2023年佐藤孝司被任命为丰田汽车公司首席执行官时，他似乎是当时最合适的人选：这位资深工程师能够为全球销量最高的汽车制造商在电动汽车领域注入亟需的活力。然而，在担任最高职位仅三年后，他即将被首席财务官近藤健太取代——后者是董事长丰田章男的亲密盟友兼前任秘书。【原文：When Koji Sato was named Toyota CEO in 2023, he appeared to be the man for the moment: a veteran engineer who could give the world’s best-selling automaker a badly needed boost in electric vehicles. But after just three years in the top job, he is being replaced by Chief Financial Officer Kenta Kon, a close ally and former secretary of Chairman Akio Toyoda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyotas-sato-was-man-moment-then-moment-changed-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTB3637WONIX5PVQMEQNPPV4AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:32:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在美国下调Cybertruck车型Cyberbeast售价]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周四在其官网上公布的价格信息显示，该公司最昂贵的Cybertruck皮卡车型Cyberbeast在美国市场的售价已从114,990美元下调至99,990美元。【原文：Tesla has reduced the price of Cyberbeast, its most-expensive Cybertruck pickup truck model, to $99,990 from $114,990 in the United States, according to pricing information on the automaker's website on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-cuts-price-cybertruck-cyberbeast-us-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CIZ4YEJTBI7XAJ6KXENLBNZ44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:17:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市下跌，油价攀升，特朗普对伊朗威胁升级]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲股市下跌，美元正朝着四个月来最大单周涨幅迈进，油价则持续攀升。美国在中东地区增兵以及私募股权类股的暴跌，令市场弥漫着紧张情绪。【原文：Stocks fell in Asia on Friday, the dollar headed for its largest weekly gain in four months and oil prices were rising as a U.S. military build up in the Middle East and a rout in private equity stocks sent ripples of nerves across markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HASYBP3IINIRROANCLPXEOJ5HY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车工人批准首份美国汽车工人联合会合同，标志着南方劳工运动取得胜利]]></title><description><![CDATA[田纳西州查塔努加市大众汽车工厂的工人周四以96%的赞成票通过了美国汽车工人联合会（UAW）谈判达成的劳资协议，这标志着UAW主席肖恩·费恩任期内取得的重大胜利之一。【原文：Workers at a Volkswagen plant in Chattanooga, Tennessee, on Thursday voted 96% in favor of a labor deal negotiated by the United Auto Workers union, marking one of the most significant victories of UAW President Shawn Fain's tenure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/workers-volkswagen-plant-tennessee-approve-uaw-contract-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6QGYWFTYFIX5DPCIT5Y7MEO4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价上涨，特朗普为伊朗对峙设定最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五油价走高，因美国与伊朗之间爆发冲突的担忧加剧。华盛顿方面表示，如果德黑兰在几天内不就其核活动达成协议，将遭受损失。【原文：Oil prices were higher on Friday as concern of conflict between the U.S. and Iran ratcheted up, with Washington saying Tehran will suffer if it does not agree a deal about its nuclear activity within a matter of days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-trump-puts-time-limit-iran-stand-off-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FVRSOV4Y7BJBZOVIGZY2PV2ZA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:55:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚桑托斯公司签署怀阿拉钢铁厂天然气供应协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚桑托斯公司周五宣布，已与南澳大利亚州政府签署协议，将在十年内每年供应20拍焦耳（PJ）天然气，助力怀阿拉钢铁厂转型为低排放绿色炼铁设施。【原文：Australia's Santos said on Friday it has signed an agreement with the South Australian government to supply 20 petajoules (PJ) of gas annually over 10 years to help transform Whyalla Steelworks into a low-emissions green iron facility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-santos-signs-gas-supply-agreement-whyalla-steelworks-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NETC2VOJ5PVHABO5PIOHGTFWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:45:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>