<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 21:33:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 21:33:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：反弹至薪资水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGL3VZUVSRL5NP66ALVU7BDG2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 21:06:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cadence Design将以31.6亿美元收购Hexagon的设计与工程部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cadence Design 公司周四表示，将以 27 亿欧元（31.6 亿美元）的价格收购总部位于斯德哥尔摩的 Hexagon AB 公司的设计与工程业务。【原文：Cadence Design said on Thursday it will buy the design and engineering business of Stockholm-based Hexagon AB for 2.7 billion euros ($3.16 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cadence-design-buy-hexagons-design-engineering-unit-316-billion-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSUROJRF3FIPBKN7WQMOP3JQCM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片需求增长，博通第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[博通公司（Broadcom）周四预测第四季度营收将高于华尔街预期，原因是企业客户对其定制人工智能芯片的需求强劲，大量投资于数据中心和机器学习应用。【原文：Broadcom forecast fourth-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, bolstered by strong demand for its custom AI chips as enterprise clients invest heavily in data centers and machine learning applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/broadcom-sees-fourth-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-growing-ai-chip-demand-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J72Z6ESHTZPA7EHFWF47IO2MN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:35:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫：特朗普签署行政命令，实施与日本的贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四签署了一项行政命令，以执行美日贸易协定。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Thursday implementing the U.S.-Japan trade agreement, the White House said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-signs-executive-order-implementing-trade-deal-with-japan-white-house-says-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJI2AIHERRPVPJIRD6KNKZGJRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据中心提供商 ODATA 为拉美地区获得创纪录的 10.2 亿美元绿色融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[Aligned Data Centers 公司旗下的数据中心提供商 ODATA 周四在一份声明中表示，该公司已获得 10.2 亿美元的绿色融资方案，用于在拉丁美洲各地发展可持续数据中心基础设施。【原文：Data center provider ODATA, an Aligned Data Centers company, has secured a $1.02 billion green financing package for sustainable data center infrastructure development across Latin America, it said in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/data-center-provider-odata-secures-record-102-billion-green-financing-latam-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WFE5G5JQVO65LUVBO7LHURW7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:30:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司起诉人工智能照片生成器 Midjourney 公司窃取超人和史酷比照片]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）周四起诉人工智能照片生成公司 Midjourney，称其公然盗用该公司的作品，生成蝙蝠侠、超人、神奇女侠、兔八哥、史酷比和其他受版权保护的人物形象。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery sued the AI photo generation company Midjourney on Thursday, saying it brazenly stole the studio's works to generate images of Batman, Superman, Wonder Woman, Bugs Bunny, Scooby-Doo and other copyrighted characters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/warner-bros-discovery-sues-ai-photo-generator-midjourney-stealing-superman-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJKTNXV6IVKJJB74M5CL4XJNZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:18:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lululemon 因需求和关税问题下调年度销售额和利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lululemon Athletica 周四下调了年度营收和利润预期，表明进入关键的假日季节后，由于消费者减少支出，加上关税压力，需求将放缓。【原文：Lululemon Athletica slashed its annual revenue and profit forecasts on Thursday, signaling a slowdown in demand going into the crucial holiday season as consumers cut down spending, alongside tariff pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lululemon-slashes-annual-sales-profit-forecasts-amid-demand-tariff-woes-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7Z3VBYTARL6HJW247EIRW6V7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:16:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道Starboard 大举入股 BILL Holdings，或将参与董事会争夺战]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，激进投资者 Starboard Value 持有 BILL Holdings 8%的股份，可能会向董事会发起挑战，推动这家为全球中小型企业提供服务的金融自动化软件公司进行变革。【原文：Activist investor Starboard Value owns an 8% stake in BILL Holdings and may run a boardroom challenge to push for changes at the financial automation software company that serves small and midsize businesses around the world, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/starboard-built-big-stake-bill-holdings-may-run-board-fight-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDKP3DIHGNJ3LHNVEB67R5RIUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:06:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康菲石油公司在州政府通知中表示最早将于 11 月 10 日开始裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，美国石油公司康菲石油公司（ConocoPhillips）周四在发给部分员工的州政府通知中表示，公司最早将于 11 月 10 日开始在全公司范围内进行裁员。【原文：U.S. oil company ConocoPhillips will begin company-wide layoffs as early as Nov. 10, the company said in a state notice sent to some employees on Thursday, seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/conocophillips-begin-layoffs-early-nov-10-company-says-state-notice-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YFQJIBR3VPB3IXOHMKK746I6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局拟修改新商用飞机认证速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府在周四的一份通知中表示，美国联邦航空管理局计划提出改革建议，以加快新商用飞机的认证速度。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration plans to propose changes to speed certification of new commercial airplanes, the Trump administration said in a notice on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-propose-changes-speed-certification-new-commercial-airplanes-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADFCPGBSTVJNVO7AHPFTPWFTWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:12:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音国防公司计划用新员工取代罢工工人]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音防务公司（Boeing Defense）周四表示，该公司计划招聘新工人，以替代正在圣路易斯地区举行罢工的国际机械师和航空航天工人协会成员。【原文：Boeing Defense plans to hire new workers to replace members of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers who are on strike in the St. Louis area, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeing-defense-plans-replace-striking-workers-with-new-hires-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVPDAMD2M5MBDLCS3EOCV6VF4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:53:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，派拉蒙将从 1 月起规定五天返岗时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，派拉蒙天空舞蹈公司周四表示，预计所有员工将从明年 1 月起每周返回办公室工作五天。【原文：Paramount Skydance said on Thursday it expects all employees to return to the office five days a week starting in January next year, according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/paramount-mandate-five-day-return-office-starting-january-memo-says-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTQACCBRFFNCXFKZ7HRJSFX4AU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普联邦贸易委员会首次对工人竞业禁止协议采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周四禁止美国最大的宠物火葬企业执行其与 1800 名工人签订的竞业禁止协议，称这些协议不公平地削弱了工人与雇主之间的影响力。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission barred the largest pet cremation business in the U.S. from enforcing its noncompete agreements with 1,800 workers on Thursday, saying they unfairly diminish workers' leverage with their employer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trump-ftc-takes-first-action-against-worker-noncompete-agreements-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPZPKKB4T5ONRFUQFASDKXZF6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品公司称已制定高管离职后的继任计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）本周宣布，一名被一些分析师视为可能成为未来首席执行官的高管因违规行为离职，该公司周四试图向投资者保证，公司已经制定了继任计划。【原文：Tyson Foods sought to reassure investors that it has succession plans in place on Thursday, after announcing this week that an executive seen by some analysts as a possible future CEO left the company over conduct violations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tyson-foods-says-it-has-succession-plans-after-executives-shock-departure-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5PGSMIOMJLMJNNASF2P4SL65A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大即将公布对铝、油菜籽行业的援助承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府官员周四表示，加拿大将很快公布一系列承诺措施，帮助钢铁和铝行业应对美国关税，同时还将援助油菜籽种植农。【原文：Canada will soon unveil a series of promised measures to help the steel and aluminum sector deal with U.S. tariffs, and will also aid canola farmers, government officials said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-unveil-promised-aid-aluminum-canola-sectors-soon-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJEKTSD7HZMYXMZ3TZTC3LULHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:28:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场为特朗普的美联储演习带来的波动做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家警告说，随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与美联储就货币政策施加影响的问题发生冲突，金融市场在未来六个月可能会再次出现波动。【原文：Financial markets may be looking at another bout of volatility over the next six months, economists cautioned, as U.S. President Donald Trump clashes with the Federal Reserve to exert influence on monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/markets-brace-volatility-amid-trumps-fed-maneuvers-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RW5WXKZBZL6DNBESM6DYLROZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:24:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Temenos 首席执行官 Brulard 辞职，首席财务官 Spiliopoulos 被任命为临时首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行软件集团 Temenos 周四表示，Jean-Pierre Brulard 将辞去首席执行官一职，立即生效。【原文：Swiss banking software group Temenos said on Thursday that Jean-Pierre Brulard will be stepping down from the role of chief executive officer, effective immediately.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/temenos-ceo-brulard-steps-down-cfo-spiliopoulos-named-interim-chief-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKLDQCFGSFJPVK57I66UMCJQNY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:54:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自动驾驶技术初创公司 Avride 将加强测试，作为优步推出机器人出租车的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[Avride 周四表示，该公司正在达拉斯扩大车辆测试规模，因为这家自主技术初创公司准备在优步（Uber）上推出机器人出租车。【原文：Avride said on Thursday it is scaling up the testing of its vehicles in Dallas, as the autonomous technology startup prepares to launch robotaxis on Uber .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/autonomous-technology-startup-avride-ramp-up-testing-part-uber-robotaxi-rollout-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUH3RVFXBBMXJG4ITZI5WGNBNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥总统表示墨西哥考虑对中国征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆周四表示，墨西哥政府正在考虑对来自与墨西哥没有贸易协定的国家（包括中国）的进口商品征收关税。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Thursday that her government is considering imposing tariffs on imports from countries that do not have trade agreements with Mexico, including China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/mexico-considering-imposing-tariffs-china-president-says-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GH362KDEKBMIHETAEQMLS2TZTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:19:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国生物柴油和可再生柴油进口量在税收抵免政策调整后出现下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（U.S. Energy Information Administration）周四称，在生物柴油和可再生柴油税收抵免政策生效后，2025 年上半年美国生物柴油和可再生柴油的进口量降至十年来的最低点。【原文：U.S. imports of biodiesel and renewable diesel slumped to a decade low in the first half of 2025 after a change in tax credits for the fuels went into effect, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-biodiesel-renewable-diesel-imports-slump-after-changes-tax-credits-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEYDH4Q2YRND5BX47VDVW4IZFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:15:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就 2022 年野火起诉南加州爱迪生公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周四起诉南加州爱迪生公司，要求该公司就 2022 年的一场野火赔偿损失，该公司将野火归咎于该公司运营的一条下垂的输电线。【原文：The U.S. government sued Southern California Edison on Thursday, seeking damages for a 2022 wildfire it blamed on a sagging power line operated by the utility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-sues-southern-california-edison-over-2022-wildfire-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BX7X6XIIC5IZZOJ4RRASNAQ5PA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:11:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国放弃要求航空公司为航班中断支付赔偿的拜登计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周四表示，将放弃其前任要求航空公司在美国航班中断时向乘客支付现金赔偿的计划。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration said on Thursday it will drop a plan by his predecessor to require airlines to pay passengers cash compensation when U.S. flight disruptions are caused by carriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-drops-biden-plan-require-airlines-pay-compensation-disrupted-flights-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3D3MHW7HT5KAFAG346G6OJY52I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯认为，如果经济表现符合他的预期，将逐步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周四表示，如果明年经济达到他目前预测的失业率小幅上升和通胀趋势走软的目标，那么就有理由在一段时间内逐步降低短期借贷成本。【原文：New York Federal Reserve President John Williams said on Thursday a gradual lowering in short-term borrowing costs is warranted over time if the economy meets his current forecast of modest gains in unemployment and a softening of inflation trends next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-williams-sees-gradual-rate-cuts-if-economy-performs-he-expects-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBRI5QD3JFO5NG3OF6KSCD5X7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司在贸易紧张局势中追随美国的新 "里程碑]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周四表示，将于下周在华盛顿宣布巴西飞机制造商的一个 "里程碑"。【原文：Embraer said on Thursday it would announce what it described as a "milestone" for the Brazilian planemaker in Washington next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-trails-new-us-milestone-amid-trade-tensions-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCVTPVGSYRMXLGFPGJG4H7DOHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:24:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德州仪器标明四月后增长放缓，关税导致增长飙升；不存在与《CHIPS 法案》相关的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国芯片制造商德州仪器（Texas Instruments）周四表示，由于客户在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）所谓的 "解放日"（Liberation Day）关税之前订购，需求在 4 月份激增后有所降温，导致其股价下跌 5%。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Texas Instruments said on Thursday demand cooled after a spike in April as customers ordered ahead of President Donald Trump's so-called "Liberation Day" tariffs, sending its shares down 5%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/texas-instruments-flags-post-april-slowdown-after-tariff-driven-spike-no-chips-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIN5EFVZANPIVANITZ7ONFACDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西淡水河谷重开关键矿山，计划在米纳斯吉拉斯州投资 120 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷周四表示，到2030年，该公司将向米纳斯吉拉斯州的采矿业务投资670亿雷亚尔（123.6亿美元）。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale said on Thursday it will invest 67 billion reais ($12.36 billion) in its mining operations in Minas Gerais state by 2030, as it held a ceremony to mark the reopening of a key mine in the city of Ouro Preto.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/brazils-vale-reopens-key-mine-plans-invest-12-billion-minas-gerais-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKJ2MYRUHRKLFOK6NHUSXAY4VA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:59:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：美国陡峭的收益率曲线对银行和经济意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国债收益率曲线是衡量经济状况的重要晴雨表，由于人们担心公共债务不断增加、唐纳德-特朗普总统试图对美联储施加控制以及他的激进关税政策，美国国债收益率曲线已经变得陡峭。【原文：The U.S. Treasury yield curve, a crucial barometer of how the economy is doing, has steepened on fears of mounting public debt, President Donald Trump's attempts to exert control over the Federal Reserve and his aggressive tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/what-does-steep-us-yield-curve-mean-banks-economy-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPTK5RDFQRIBDMHXC7O3P6OLK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，美国联邦贸易委员会准备就对儿童的影响问题对人工智能公司进行质询]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国联邦贸易委员会计划研究人工智能聊天机器人对儿童心理健康的影响，并要求科技公司提供相关文件。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission plans to study the impact of artificial intelligence chatbots on children's mental health and request documents from tech companies, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ftc-prepares-grill-ai-companies-over-impact-children-wsj-reports-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPICBLAAZBKRJITBVQOIKT7UCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理阿尔巴内斯与特朗普就重要矿产和安全问题进行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞的办公室称，澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞周四晚间在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普通电话时讨论了澳美两国在关键矿产方面的合作机会。【原文：Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese discussed opportunities for Australia and the United States to cooperate on critical minerals in a phone call with President Donald Trump on Thursday evening, his office said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-pm-albanese-spoke-trump-about-critical-minerals-security-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSGL34QAJFPTVG7RXLDUVSCNTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关税紧张局势下，印度制药出口的目光不再局限于美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府支持的一个贸易机构的官员周四告诉路透社，印度正在寻求加强对非洲、拉丁美洲和东南亚半管制市场的药品出口，以减少对美国的依赖，因为美国的关税问题会带来风险。【原文：India is seeking to boost drug exports to semi-regulated markets in Africa, Latin America and Southeast Asia to reduce its dependence on the U.S., where tariff concerns pose risks, officials from a government-backed trade body told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/india-looking-beyond-us-pharma-exports-amid-tariff-tensions-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXNMDZCV3RMABD45L7ZFB34G5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>