<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:09:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:09:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 购买价值 5.13 亿美元的比特币，推动加密货币发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 周三表示，该公司已经购买了价值约 5.13 亿美元的比特币，这家濒临倒闭的视频游戏零售商希望利用全球范围内加密货币日益普及的契机。【原文：GameStop has purchased bitcoin worth about $513 million, the company said on Wednesday as the ailing video game retailer looks to capitalize on the growing adoption of cryptocurrencies globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gamestop-buys-bitcoin-worth-513-million-crypto-push-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQPGPMMSXVLMXPJS4OGSDCVRSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[坎托菲茨杰拉德将收购瑞银对冲基金部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经纪公司 Cantor Fitzgerald 周三表示，将收购瑞士银行旗下对冲基金部门 O'Connor。【原文：U.S. brokerage firm Cantor Fitzgerald said on Wednesday it would buy Swiss lender UBS' hedge fund unit, O'Connor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cantor-fitzgerald-buy-ubs-hedge-fund-unit-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6C6V65TRJJKFN7NXZ75UFS6BA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求强劲，Abercrombie 季度销售额超预期，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Abercrombie & Fitch 周三公布的第一季度销售额超出预期，原因是其推出印花牛仔裤和连衣裙等新款式的举措有助于吸引更多的购物者，这使得该服装生产商的股价在盘前交易中上涨了约 26%。【原文：Abercrombie & Fitch on Wednesday beat estimates for first-quarter sales, as its move to introduce fresh styles such as printed jeans and dresses helped in drawing more shoppers, sending shares of the apparel maker up about 26% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/abercrombie-beats-quarterly-sales-estimates-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEJU4QXYQBOSDARBFW43YUUGNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，欧佩克+本周可能讨论 2027 年基准线并同意 7 月加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+组织的两位代表说，该组织可能会在周三的会议上讨论围绕2027年产量基准线的问题，而将于周六举行的单独会谈可能会同意在7月份进一步加快提高石油产量。【原文：OPEC+ may discuss issues around its baselines for 2027 production at its meeting on Wednesday, two delegates from the group said, while separate talks due on Saturday could agree a further accelerated oil output hike for July.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-may-discuss-2027-baselines-agree-july-hike-this-week-sources-say-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y576WJAT5RMIHMNR4HACJPKTOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global Payments 将以 11 亿美元向 Acrisure 出售薪资业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球支付公司（Global Payments）周三表示，将以 11 亿美元的价格把工资单业务出售给金融技术公司 Acrisure，这标志着该支付公司简化业务模式的最新尝试。【原文：Global Payments said on Wednesday it would sell its payroll business to financial technology firm Acrisure for $1.1 billion, marking the payments company's latest attempt at simplifying its business model.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-payments-sell-payroll-business-acrisure-11-billion-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFSEL44P7BMJ3JQMEV7YGVG7NE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国可能放宽对部分芯片公司的稀土出口限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家媒体周三称，中国可能放宽对中国和欧洲半导体公司及其供应链上其他公司出口稀土的限制。【原文：China may relax curbs on exports of rare earths for Chinese and European semiconductor firms and other companies in their supply chain, state media said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-may-relax-rare-earth-export-curbs-some-chip-companies-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IA6EQ73EE5LRFCAG2FPOZLQ6CE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:16:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟计划设立科技扩展基金，缩小与美国和中国的差距]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会计划设立一个至少100亿欧元（约合113亿美元）的公私基金，帮助科技公司扩大规模，以缩小与美国和中国的创新差距。【原文：The European Commission plans to create a public-private fund of at least 10 billion euros ($11.3 billion) to help tech companies scale up as the European Union aims to narrow its innovation gap with the United States and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-plans-tech-scale-up-fund-narrow-gap-with-us-china-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EO5XDVTF7BLZLOS4FUYXLH5Q5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅西百货因关税不确定性下调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅西百货公司（Macy's）周三下调了年度利润预期，因为这家美国顶级百货公司正在应对关税引发的不确定性，以及在服装和配饰方面的谨慎消费。【原文：Macy's cut its annual profit forecast on Wednesday as the top U.S. department store operator navigates tariff-led uncertainty and cautious spending on apparel and accessories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/macys-cuts-annual-profit-forecast-amid-tariff-uncertainty-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MNLEZH7RRPWXA6V3PCJ3OCIC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Michael Kors 母公司卡普里下调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克尔-科尔斯公司（Michael Kors）的所有者卡普里控股公司（Capri Holdings）周三下调了2026年的收入预期，表明与关税相关的不确定性正在拖累北美和亚洲市场对其皮革手袋和配饰本已脆弱的需求。【原文：Michael Kors-owner Capri Holdings cut its revenue forecast for 2026 on Wednesday signaling that tariff-related uncertainty was weighing on an already fragile demand for its leather handbags and accessories in North America and Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/michael-kors-parent-capri-lowers-annual-revenue-forecast-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKZS36NBJZN57LHLNA2V55QGDA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大国家银行第二季度利润因金融市场业务强劲而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大国家银行周三公布第二季度利润增长，得益于其金融市场部门的强劲表现。【原文：National Bank of Canada reported a rise in second-quarter profit on Wednesday, helped by a robust performance in its financial markets units.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/national-bank-canadas-second-quarter-profit-rises-strong-financial-markets-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNGEMUQH7NOJHOIJUBEHGVQAYI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Honeywell expected to add Elliott's Marc Steinberg to board, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Honeywell is expected to appoint Marc Steinberg, a partner at activist Elliott Investment Management, to its board later on Wednesday, the Wall Street Journal reported.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/honeywell-expected-add-elliotts-marc-steinberg-board-wsj-reports-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5R3KWBMTVMHLLMEGOEZNLJKAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:18:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who is Remy Cointreau's new CEO, Franck Marilly?]]></title><description><![CDATA[French wines and spirits company Remy Cointreau announced on Wednesday that Franck Marilly will replace CEO Eric Vallat who resigned earlier this year.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/who-is-remy-cointreaus-new-ceo-franck-marilly-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3QY2BC6DZJANO22TEQ66MLK7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Minutes of Fed's May meeting likely to show officials grappling with uncertainty]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Reserve at its May 6-7 meeting undercut expectations that it would change its policy interest rate anytime soon, and minutes from that session released on Wednesday may show just how firmly policymakers are holding onto their current wait-and-see approach.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/minutes-feds-may-meeting-likely-show-officials-grappling-with-uncertainty-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4XJ62O6TFLUBLKXSWYC24RP2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW Stellantis CEO's appointment reactions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Automaker Stellantis on Wednesday named Antonio Filosa, the Italian head of its North American operations, as its CEO, effective from June 23.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/view-stellantis-ceos-appointment-reactions-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHRM27IAANNGFG7WGWI7UWBSQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil airline Azul files for Chapter 11 to restructure high debt]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian airline Azul filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the United States, it said in a securities filing on Wednesday, despite months of efforts to restructure mostly pandemic-era debt.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazil-airline-azul-files-chapter-11-restructure-high-debt-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SJXIIOMCJMSFAIHJ7C7MXSUKM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US banks tiptoe toward crypto, awaiting more green light from regulators]]></title><description><![CDATA[Big U.S. banks are holding internal discussions about expanding into cryptocurrencies as they get stronger endorsements from regulators, but initial steps will be tentative, centering on pilot programs, partnerships or limited crypto trading, according to four industry executives.
Wall Street giants that had been largely blocked from many crypto activities by strict regulations are poised to grow quickly.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-banks-tiptoe-toward-crypto-awaiting-more-green-light-regulators-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">II72GSLHNJNMVOXVZTZGLRPAPA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:06:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ex-analyst sues Freepoint Commodities, alleges pressure to facilitate insider trading]]></title><description><![CDATA[A former senior analyst at U.S. trading company Freepoint Commodities has sued the company, alleging that top executives pressured employees to facilitate insider trading and retaliated against employees that objected.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ex-analyst-sues-freepoint-commodities-alleges-pressure-facilitate-insider-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WX33ZIFDEZI5DMLXKZ5WHEPOC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:05:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Amazon's in-car software deal with Stellantis fizzles]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amazon's deal with Stellantis to create in-car software that the companies hoped would transform the driving experience while bolstering their vehicle-tech credentials is "winding down," the companies confirmed after a Reuters inquiry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/amazons-in-car-software-deal-with-stellantis-fizzles-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QF4WFM6R5VNJDAK7Q3TWR23IMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺基亚与 Blackned 将为德国军队开发下一代战术网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[芬兰诺基亚公司和德国莱茵金属公司（Rheinmetall）控股的国防技术公司 blackned 周三表示，两家公司将为德国武装部队联合开发下一代战术网络。【原文：Finland's Nokia and defence technology firm blackned, majority-owned by Rheinmetall , will jointly develop next-generation tactical networks for the German armed forces, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/nokia-blackned-develop-next-gen-tactical-networks-german-army-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TACSGYXSEJNZ3CHHKHS3LX4ZUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼反垄断机构发现 TikTok 收购 Tokopedia 存在垄断风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼反垄断机构周三表示，去年 TikTok 收购印尼最大电子商务平台 Tokopedia 的交易存在垄断风险。【原文：Indonesia's antitrust agency said on Wednesday that last year's takeover of the country's biggest e-commerce platform Tokopedia by TikTok carried a risk of monopoly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-antitrust-agency-finds-risk-monopoly-tiktoks-tokopedia-takeover-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SY47EKNBWVNCFKWAYCBX6DBWYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:57:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称福特在美国召回超过 100 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，福特汽车公司将在美国召回1,075,299辆汽车，原因是后视摄像头可能无法显示图像，从而增加了车祸风险。【原文：Ford Motor is recalling 1,075,299 vehicles in the United States over an issue that may prevent the rearview camera from displaying images increasing the risk of a crash, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recalls-more-than-1-million-vehicles-us-nhtsa-says-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMGDBDWUJJM5VJBAMJ3HRISKMI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:52:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[捷克称中国是部委遭网络攻击的幕后黑手并召见大使]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷克共和国周三表示，中国应对针对外交部用于非机密通信的网络的 "恶意网络活动 "负责，并召见中国大使谴责这一事件。【原文：The Czech Republic said on Wednesday China was responsible for a "malicious cyber campaign" targeting a network used for unclassified communication at the Foreign Affairs ministry, and summoned the Chinese ambassador to condemn the incident.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/czech-republic-says-china-was-behind-cyberattack-ministry-summons-ambassador-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UOKGSEECHVO7BGG2XELV4NCMWA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股期货大幅反弹后回落，关注英伟达财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者关注人工智能风向标英伟达（Nvidia）即将发布的财报和贸易方面的发展，美国股指期货在前一交易日大幅反弹后于周三下滑。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Wednesday after a sharp rally in the previous session, when easing tariff tensions boosted sentiment, as investors focused on AI bellwether Nvidia's upcoming earnings and developments on the trade front.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-dip-after-sharp-rally-focus-nvidia-earnings-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XA3TIIE7IVN6TFIZTYSG4LLRXY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:44:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利经济部长表示，如果在意大利联合信贷银行-BPM 协议问题上遭到违抗，他将辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利经济部长吉安卡洛-乔盖蒂（Giancarlo Giorgetti）周三表示，如果政府在联合信贷银行竞购较小银行 Banco BPM 时附加的 "金权 "条件被否决，他将辞职。【原文：Italian Economy Minister Giancarlo Giorgetti said on Wednesday he would resign if he were overruled on "golden power" conditions the government has tied to UniCredit's bid for smaller bank Banco BPM .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/italy-economy-minister-says-would-quit-if-defied-unicredit-bpm-deal-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUTY2IEFLNI2TGSSSG65TELNTA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国劳工组织在经济放缓之际下调全球就业预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球经济前景恶化和贸易紧张局势，联合国劳工组织周三将今年全球就业增长预期下调至1.5%。【原文：The United Nation's agency for labour on Wednesday cut its global employment forecast for job growth this year to 1.5% due to a worsening global economic outlook and trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/un-labour-body-cuts-global-job-forecast-amid-economic-slowdown-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWNO3LUXVNKBDL65XY5O4RFK5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:40:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在网络攻击被归咎于中国后，欧盟声援捷克共和国]]></title><description><![CDATA[在捷克认定中国对捷克外交部的 "恶意网络攻击 "负有责任后，欧盟声援捷克。【原文：The European Union stands in solidarity with the Czech Republic, after the Czech Republic identified China as being responsible for a "malicious cyber campaign" at the Czech Ministry of Foreign Affairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-stands-solidarity-with-czech-republic-after-cyberattack-blamed-china-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYI5NDVJNFNSPIE7K5HMC4MNSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[销售、中国和美国关税：Stellantis 新老板面临的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[继卡洛斯-塔瓦雷斯（Carlos Tavares）于 12 月离职后，安东尼奥-菲洛萨（Antonio Filosa）于周三被任命为汽车制造商 Stellantis 的首席执行官。【原文：Antonio Filosa was appointed chief executive of automaker Stellantis on Wednesday, following the departure of Carlos Tavares in December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/sales-china-us-tariffs-challenges-new-stellantis-boss-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PZBTKVCPZKF3CD3FDO4CRE6KI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行发言人称拉加德决心完成任期]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》报道，克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）曾与欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）就提前离职以领导世界经济论坛（World Economic Forum）一事进行过谈判，欧洲中央银行周三表示，克里斯蒂娜-拉加德决心完成其八年的欧洲中央银行行长任期。【原文：Christine Lagarde is determined to complete her eight-year term as president of the European Central Bank, the ECB said on Wednesday after the Financial Times reported that she held talks about leaving early to lead the World Economic Forum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ecbs-lagarde-determined-complete-her-term-spokesperson-says-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3O26Q5GYUZPHHMVS7ZMB52YLUM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道飞机租赁巨头呼吁特朗普扩大飞机零关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大飞机租赁公司的负责人呼吁美国总统唐纳德-特朗普重新谈判并扩大飞机行业的免税贸易协定，将中国等新加入者纳入其中，这也是贸易战的一个新的游说转折点。【原文：The head of the world's largest aircraft leasing company has called on U.S. President Donald Trump to renegotiate and expand a duty-free trade agreement for the aircraft industry to include newcomers like China in a new lobbying twist to the trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aircraft-leasing-giant-calls-trump-expand-zero-tariff-plane-pact-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSJ7QDR23JM6RF22TAQPD3SOYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道内部邮件显示：日产向美国员工提供买断，停止全球加薪]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的内部邮件显示，日本日产汽车公司已开始向美国工人提供收购，并暂停在全球范围内根据业绩加薪。【原文：Japan's Nissan has started offering buyouts to U.S. workers and has suspended merit-based wage increases worldwide, internal emails reviewed by Reuters showed, as the automaker expands cost cuts amid weak performance in key markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/nissan-offers-buyouts-us-workers-halts-global-pay-rises-internal-emails-show-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HJQB2ZSF5KHVIX6N4E2FCQIXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:49:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>