<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:48:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:48:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[油价因需求担忧和美元走强而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心2025年的需求增长，特别是头号原油进口国中国的需求增长，周五早盘油价下跌，导致全球石油基准有望在本周结束时下跌超过2%。【原文：Oil prices fell in early trading on Friday on worries about demand growth in 2025, especially in top crude importer China, putting global oil benchmarks on track to end the week down more than 2%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-fall-demand-concerns-strong-dollar-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2U6GALDDK5LIRBT5BULIN6ZZ2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市逼近三个月低点，美元站上两年高位]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市在三个月低点附近震荡，投资者在等待可能缓解或加剧对物价压力担忧的美国关键通胀数据，而美元则在两年高位徘徊。【原文：Asian shares were pinned near three-month lows on Friday as investors awaited key U.S. inflation data that could either ease or worsen concerns about price pressures, while the dollar towered at two-year peaks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">233BAYZGINMKFOC7WQ6YRGSBAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克工会周五将在洛杉矶、芝加哥和西雅图举行罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表 10,000 多名星巴克咖啡师的工人工会表示，工会成员将于周五上午在洛杉矶、芝加哥和西雅图举行罢工。【原文：The workers' union representing more than 10,000 Starbucks baristas said that union members will go on strike in Los Angeles, Chicago, and Seattle on Friday morning.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-workers-union-strike-friday-la-chicago-seattle-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULJX5KDNCBJMRMPBJ6DLSEUOCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 01:52:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元将以高位收周，日元创五个月新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元在鹰派美国利率前景的支撑下徘徊在两年高点附近，为本周的强势行情画上了句号。【原文：The dollar was set to cap the week on a strong note on Friday as it was perched near a two-year high bolstered by a hawkish U.S. rate outlook, while the yen struggled to stay afloat as it again weakened to a new low.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-set-end-week-high-yen-five-month-low-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TORFPSEIEZP6PO3TQIIM2AZZKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 01:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：在减肥大战中，诺和诺德和礼来面临着来自授权仿制药的日益猛烈的攻势]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）和礼来（Eli Lilly）扩大其畅销的糖尿病和减肥药物的销售，其专利疗法的廉价复制品正获得海外一些监管机构的批准，对制药巨头的价格和市场份额构成威胁。【原文：As Novo Nordisk and Eli Lilly expand sales of their popular diabetes and weight-loss drugs, cheaper copies of their patented remedies are winning approval from some regulators overseas, posing a threat to the pharma giants' prices and market share.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/weight-loss-battle-novo-lilly-face-growing-offensive-licenced-copies-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBGIVNCQLRNMRFGOGOPVRW2U2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道关税威胁逼近，中国国有进口商预订购买美国大豆]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉交易的美国贸易商称，中国中储粮本周购买了近 50 万吨美国大豆，将于 3 月和 4 月装运，为国家储备支付了更多的美国大豆供应，而不是购买更便宜的巴西大豆。【原文：China's Sinograin has bought nearly 500,000 metric tons of U.S. soybeans this week for shipment in March and April, paying more for U.S. supplies for state reserves rather than buying cheaper Brazilian beans, two U.S. traders familiar with the deals said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-state-importer-books-us-soy-purchases-tariff-threat-looms-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YSTWEDCPVLNDFP6KNVXPHAIJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本核心通胀加速，使日本央行仍有机会加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，由于食品和燃料成本上升对家庭造成冲击，日本11月份的核心通胀率加速上升，使央行继续面临加息压力。【原文：Japan's core inflation accelerated in November as rising food and fuel costs hit households, data showed on Friday, keeping the central bank under pressure to raise interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-core-inflation-accelerates-keeps-boj-rate-hike-chance-alive-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5V4VUOIVTJLONAXR2BCUCJNFG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:43:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛称可能无法实现2025年和2030年气候变化目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛表示，由于能源政策、基础设施和具有成本效益的低碳技术的可用性方面的挑战，它很可能无法实现 2025 年和 2030 年减少地球变暖排放的目标。【原文：Walmart said it is likely to miss its 2025 and 2030 targets for reducing planet-warming emissions due to challenges related to energy policy, infrastructure and availability of cost-effective low-carbon technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/walmart-says-it-is-likely-miss-2025-2030-climate-change-targets-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6A6YGGHLKRPV5JXTIIIN52UBNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，TPG 正在就以 80 亿美元收购皇冠城堡光纤部门进行深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士透露，收购公司 TPG 正在就以约 80 亿美元的价格收购铁塔运营商 Crown Castle 旗下的光纤部门进行深入谈判。【原文：Buyout firm TPG is in advanced talks to buy the fiber unit of tower operator Crown Castle for about $8 billion, a person familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/tpg-advanced-talks-buy-crown-castles-fiber-unit-8-bln-source-says-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VISD4LFMVNIUXDSQCWCXOHY6QI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于航运经济疲软，预计 1 月份美国对欧洲的原油出口将下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师本周表示，美国对西北欧的原油出口在11月创下历史新高后，很可能在明年初下滑，因为跨大西洋运输的套利通道已经关闭，运费也在攀升。【原文：U.S. crude oil exports to northwest Europe are likely to slip early next year after hitting a record high in November, as the arbitrage for transatlantic shipments has slammed shut and freight rates have climbed, analysts said this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-crude-exports-europe-expected-fall-jan-shipping-economics-weaken-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIQNG5NXEJLUZORGDS756QMDXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：路易吉-曼乔内（Luigi Mangione）在联合健康高管遇害案中面临哪些指控？]]></title><description><![CDATA[路易吉-曼乔内（Luigi Mangione）是 12 月 4 日杀害联合健康集团高管布莱恩-汤普森（Brian Thompson）的嫌疑人，他在纽约州和联邦法院分别面临两起谋杀指控。【原文：Luigi Mangione, the suspect in the Dec. 4 killing of UnitedHealth Group executive Brian Thompson, faces two separate sets of murder charges in state and federal court in New York.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/what-charges-does-luigi-mangione-face-over-unitedhealth-executive-killing-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">445CNZ6RRRIYHBB4ZKKFP6G5HA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:09:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本小松公司表示，加拿大对特朗普关税的报复是最大的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[重型设备制造商小松公司（Komatsu）的负责人表示，特朗普就任总统后，该公司面临的最大商业风险不是特朗普威胁征收的关税，而是加拿大可能对美国制造的采矿设备征收报复性关税。【原文：The top business risk of the Trump presidency for heavy-duty equipment maker Komatsu is not the tariffs he has threatened, but Canada's potential retaliatory duties on American-made mining machines, the head of the Japanese company said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/canadas-retaliation-trump-tariffs-is-biggest-concern-says-japans-komatsu-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSDCAE2CPJP3ZCHQR3TPDATQBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:05:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度和澳大利亚为 2025 年亚太地区新股票销售前景增添光彩]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025 年，印度将成为全球最繁忙的首次公开募股市场，而澳大利亚也将成为全球最繁忙的首次公开募股市场。交易商们预计，印度和澳大利亚的新股销售势头将缓解中国在亚太地区交易低迷的影响。【原文：Dealmakers expect the momentum for new share sales in India, now the world's busiest market for initial public offerings, and Australia in 2025 will cushion the impact of sluggish Chinese deals in the Asia Pacific.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/india-australia-brighten-new-share-sales-prospects-2025-asia-pacific-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VG3QBGR2UBN7XGWGX67Z6HAWAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员敦促拜登给予 ByteDance 90 天的缓刑期，使其免于适用要求出售的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员埃德-马基（Ed Markey）和共和党参议员兰德-保罗（Rand Paul）周四敦促美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）将中国字节跳动公司（ByteDance）1月19日出售其短视频应用TikTok美国资产的最后期限延长90天，否则将面临禁令。【原文：Democratic Senator Ed Markey and Republican Senator Rand Paul on Thursday urged President Joe Biden to extend by 90 days a Jan. 19 deadline for China-based ByteDance to sell the U.S. assets of its short-video app TikTok or face a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/senators-urge-biden-grant-bytedance-90-day-reprieve-law-requiring-sale-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DG26ZMBSHZLGBGMGWO3GORFYHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室否认秘密谈判，民主党人敦促终止贸易协定的投资者保护措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国商会指控拜登政府正在就此事进行 "秘密 "谈判之后，37 位民主党议员周四敦促美国贸易代表办公室继续努力削弱美国贸易协定中的投资保护条款。【原文：A group of 37 Democratic lawmakers on Thursday urged the U.S. Trade Representative's office to press ahead with efforts to weaken investment protections in U.S. trade agreements after the U.S. Chamber of Commerce alleged that the Biden administration was pursuing "secret" talks on the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democrats-urge-end-trade-deal-investor-protections-ustr-denies-secret-talks-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVASXR3L5VOOHPCJ4SB5P6SE3M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称航空航天公司 AAR 就贿赂官员指控达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（Securities and Exchange Commission）周四表示，全球航空航天公司 AAR Corp 同意解决美国对其提出的两项与尼泊尔和南非官员有关的贿赂指控。【原文：The Securities and Exchange Commission said on Thursday that global aerospace company AAR Corp agreed to resolve U.S. charges in connection with two bribery schemes related to Nepalese and South African officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/sec-says-aerospace-firm-aar-settles-charges-over-bribing-officials-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTWY324ZXBMHFC35H373ACRPCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：寻求美联储的喘息机会；中国人民银行将按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TP53LYSJSZKERMPIYROJ2EBJAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:47:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司预测第四季度意外亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司（United States Steel）周四预测第四季度将出现意外亏损，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌近 5%。【原文：United States Steel on Thursday forecast a surprise loss for the fourth quarter, sending its shares down nearly 5% in aftermarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-steel-forecasts-fourth-quarter-surprise-loss-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5BD5I3RBBO45HCOGLPEY32YSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:44:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克第二季度销售额降幅低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司周四公布的第二季度营收降幅小于预期，原因是这家陷入困境的运动服饰品牌推出了新款运动鞋和跑步鞋，吸引了顾客光顾其门店和网站。【原文：Nike posted a smaller-than-expected drop in second-quarter revenue on Thursday, as the embattled sportswear brand's release of newer versions of performance and running shoes drew customers to its stores and website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-posts-smaller-than-expected-fall-second-quarter-sales-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NROQAJU6YNMGZFFVGIYAJOOU4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递将分拆零担货运业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递（FedEx）周四宣布剥离备受瞩目的零担货运部门，以调整业务结构，更加专注于核心快递业务。【原文：FedEx announced the much-anticipated spinoff of its less-than-truckload freight division on Thursday, as it looks to restructure its operations and focus more on its core delivery business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fedex-spin-off-its-less-than-truckload-freight-business-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASCQMXXCV5OMHOYJPFXVCOYDPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊同意采取工人安全措施以平息美国调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周四表示，将在其所有美国工厂实施新的安全措施，以解决联邦机构提出的该公司未能防止工人患上背部疾病和其他人体工学伤害的指控。【原文：Amazon.com will implement new safety measures at all of its U.S. facilities to settle a federal agency's claims that it failed to prevent workers from developing back problems and other ergonomic injuries, the agency said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-agrees-worker-safety-measures-settle-us-probe-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3KNIJKYM5PMZBKOLHEEKQB6DY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:34:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康德摩根公司将继续实施耗资 14 亿美元的密西西比河渡口项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[康德摩根公司（Kinder Morgan）周四表示，其田纳西天然气管道公司（Tennessee Gas Pipeline）将继续实施耗资近 14 亿美元的密西西比穿越项目（Mississippi Crossing Project，MSX 项目），从而加强该管道运营商在美国东南部市场的地位。【原文：Kinder Morgan said on Thursday its unit Tennessee Gas Pipeline will proceed with the nearly $1.4 billion Mississippi Crossing Project (MSX Project), strengthening the pipeline operator's position in the Southeast U.S. markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/kinder-morgans-unit-go-ahead-with-14-bln-mississippi-crossing-project-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAQNQYOAEZLULD7QBC6AUXQVNY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:25:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各州和环保组织撤销对美国邮政电动汽车采购计划的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[以加利福尼亚州为首的 16 个州和环保组织已经撤销了 2022 年提起的一项诉讼，该诉讼旨在阻止美国邮政服务公司购买主要以天然气为动力的新一代快递车辆的计划。【原文：A group of 16 states led by California and environmental groups have dropped a lawsuit filed in 2022 that sought to block the U.S. Postal Service's plan to buy mostly gas-powered next-generation delivery vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/states-environmental-groups-drop-lawsuit-over-us-postal-service-ev-purchase-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7AH5KTGIRONHCRJTFCSXCKXCM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:18:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Tech Mahindra 公司首席执行官表示，该公司的目标是在银行科技支出中占据更大份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度 Tech Mahindra 公司首席执行官在接受采访时表示，该公司正在加强对银行、金融服务和保险（BFSI）业务的重视，以缩小与大型同行的差距，因为这些同行历来从这一利润丰厚的领域获得更多收入。【原文：India's Tech Mahindra is stepping up focus on its banking, financial services and insurance (BFSI) business in a bid to bridge the gap with larger peers which have historically made more revenue from the lucrative segment, its CEO said in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indias-tech-mahindra-aiming-bigger-bite-bank-tech-spends-ceo-says-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7N7IJDCQORI5BNVOZWLKZEEYFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:33:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[更加鹰派的美联储政策委员会或将在 2025 年增加异议]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025 年，一批略显鹰派的美联储地区银行行长将成为美国央行利率制定小组的投票人，这使得明年任何进一步的降息措施都有可能引发更多类似克利夫兰联储主席周三所表达的异议。【原文：A slightly more hawkish set of Federal Reserve regional bank presidents will become voters on the U.S. central bank's rate-setting panel in 2025, raising the chance that any further interest rate cuts next year could spur more dissents like the one seen on Wednesday from the head of the Cleveland Fed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/more-hawkish-fed-policy-committee-may-increase-dissent-2025-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAB6CWQVLBK2BC2XCXKRSH7XOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国抵押贷款利率在连续三周下降后上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储预计 2025 年降息次数减少、10 年期国债收益率上升之后，本周美国抵押贷款利率在连续三周下降后有所上升，并可能进一步上升。【原文：U.S. mortgage rates increased this week following three straight weekly declines and could rise further after the Federal Reserve projected fewer interest rate cuts in 2025, boosting the yield on the 10-year Treasury note.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-mortgage-rates-rise-after-three-straight-weekly-declines-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4U4K23SM5NI3LJNFP74MR4DUMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:14:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织称，鉴于美国的高度不确定性，美联储在利率问题上采取了适当行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）发言人朱莉-科扎克（Julie Kozack）周四表示，鉴于美国经济的高度不确定性，国际货币基金组织认为美联储周三的降息和采取更加谨慎的前景展望是适当的。【原文：The International Monetary Fund views Wednesday's Federal Reserve interest rate cut and adoption of a more cautious outlook as appropriate given high U.S. economic uncertainty, IMF spokesperson Julie Kozack said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/imf-says-fed-taking-appropriate-action-rates-given-high-us-uncertainty-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SQT3ETLP7ZOSNN5W4OSOGJNJBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其 Pegasus 航空公司订购 100 架波音 737 MAX 10 喷气式飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周四表示，土耳其低成本航空公司飞马航空公司（Pegasus Airlines）已确定订购 100 架 737 MAX 10 飞机，这为从今年早些时候一场严重的工人罢工中恢复过来的美国飞机制造商带来了可喜的鼓舞。【原文：Boeing said on Thursday Turkish low-cost carrier Pegasus Airlines had placed a firm order for a hundred 737 MAX 10 aircraft, offering a welcome boost for the U.S. planemaker recovering from a crippling worker strike earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/turkish-carrier-pegasus-orders-100-boeing-737-max-10-jets-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76IUIBPKQFNB3DNZJT33E56Z7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:53:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管机构要求世界币必须删除所有虹膜扫描数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙数据保护监督机构 AEPD 周四表示，山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）的公司 Worldcoin 必须删除自该项目启动以来收集到的所有虹膜扫描数据。【原文：Sam Altman's company Worldcoin must delete all iris scanning data collected since the start of the project that has sparked privacy concerns in several countries, Spanish data protection watchdog AEPD said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/spanish-watchdog-tells-worldcoin-delete-all-iris-scan-data-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPR6JFXJ5ZKKPO464XDPK4FTTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储在年底增加额外的每日常备回购操作]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周四表示，将在今年年底至 1 月初这几天增加一次常备回购机制操作。【原文：The Federal Reserve Bank of New York on Thursday said it will add an extra operation of its standing repo facility in the days covering the end of the calendar year into early January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ny-fed-adds-extra-daily-standing-repo-operation-covering-year-end-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQQZL2UYWBKH3OXKIVKYP52AQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:31:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>