<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:04:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:04:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[高盛表示，选股型对冲基金的平均回报率为 2020 年以来最高]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）在一份报告中称，去年全球对冲基金在股票上的多头和空头押注取得了自 2020 年以来最高的平均回报率，并将这一结果归功于市场波动中的稳定回报。【原文：Global hedge funds taking long and short bets on stocks last year sported their highest average returns since 2020, Goldman Sachs said in a note, attributing the result to steady returns amid volatile markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-flow-stock-picking-hedge-funds-post-highest-average-returns-since-2020-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SCRQ3SEJJI5HFZ4N6MOTUU22M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 13:57:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登政府为核工业提供氢能税收抵免途径]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周五表示，核电厂生产所谓的清洁氢气将能获得丰厚的税收减免，如果这些减免有助于防止反应堆退役的话。【原文：The Biden administration said on Friday nuclear power plants will be able to secure lucrative tax credits for production of what it calls clean hydrogen if the credits help prevent reactors from retiring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/biden-administration-offers-nuclear-industry-path-hydrogen-tax-credit-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76F265P2UJJNFOMMC4OQBTCVGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 13:49:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Rivian 的交付量超出预期，供应障碍有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Rivian 公司第四季度的交付量超过了分析师的预期，并表示其生产不再受到零部件短缺的限制，这对致力于首次实现盈利的电动汽车制造商来说是一个积极的信号。【原文：Rivian surpassed analysts' expectations for fourth-quarter deliveries on Friday and said its production was no longer constrained by a component shortage, a positive sign for the electric vehicle maker aiming to turn its first profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-rivian-beats-expectations-deliveries-supply-snag-eases-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6D4TFMNPNNF5MBH5GDBJ6E7OY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 13:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国阻止新日铁收购美国钢铁公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）周五兑现了他的承诺，阻止新日本制铁公司（Nippon Steel）以 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel），理由是该交易可能会损害国家安全。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden on Friday followed through on his pledge to block Nippon Steel's $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel , citing concerns the deal could hurt national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-blocks-nippon-steels-bid-purchase-us-steel-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7FN6DN7DJK3XNKCF4MPEN4RNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 13:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关注经济数据和即将到来的政策变化，期指稳步上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货走高，投资者在等待更多数据，以了解经济的健康状况，并为即将上任的特朗普政府可能做出的政策调整做好准备。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Friday, as investors awaited more data for insights on the health of the economy and braced for likely policy changes under the incoming Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-inch-up-with-economic-data-upcoming-policy-shifts-focus-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFVEXMWA3FLLBI3VRQH2WHQS4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 11:24:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：阿根廷国有航空公司在可能出售前削减员工、航线和乘客福利]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的消息来源和文件显示，阿根廷国营航空公司阿根廷航空公司（Aerolineas Argentinas）正在为可能的出售进行瘦身，裁减了 13% 的员工，削减了亏损的国内航线，甚至取消了以前向乘客提供的小吃。【原文：Argentina's state airline, Aerolineas Argentinas, is slimming down for a potential sale, shedding 13% of its staff, cutting money-losing domestic routes and even removing snacks formerly available to passengers, according to sources and documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/argentinas-state-airline-cuts-staff-routes-passenger-perks-ahead-possible-sale-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMHQCPQG3BO5DMVJDVTMTJZ23I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 11:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者推动 2024 年美国新车销量创五年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[据分析师估计，2024 年美国新车销量将从大流行时期的低点继续回升，这主要得益于库存的补充和更高的激励措施。【原文：U.S. new-car sales in 2024 continued to rise from their pandemic lows, bolstered by replenished inventories and higher incentives, analysts estimated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/consumers-boosted-2024-us-new-car-sales-five-year-high-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6Z7LNPKPROP5JKZU3BOEOAHOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 11:07:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[门板事件后，美国联邦航空局将继续加强对波音公司的监督]]></title><description><![CDATA[在阿拉斯加航空公司（Alaska Airlines）一架新的 737 MAX 9 飞机在半空中因门板缺少四个关键螺栓而脱落近一年后，联邦航空管理局即将离任的负责人周五表示，该局对波音公司更严格的监管将无限期地持续下去。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration's tougher oversight of Boeing will continue indefinitely, the agency's outgoing head said on Friday, nearly a year after a door panel missing four key bolts flew off a new Alaska Airlines 737 MAX 9 in mid-air.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-will-maintain-enhanced-oversight-boeing-after-door-panel-incident-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUS3RMJ6VFNLXL4ZKRNSKJJVWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 11:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税威胁将在 CES 的汽车和科技盛会中凸显]]></title><description><![CDATA[在下周于拉斯维加斯举行的 CES 展会上，汽车和科技巨头们将展示他们的最新创新产品，而在这个以消费者为中心的展会上，关税问题通常并不是核心话题。【原文：Auto and tech giants showing off their latest innovations at the CES trade show in Las Vegas next week can expect a barrage of questions on a topic that is usually not central to the consumer-focused event: tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/threat-tariffs-will-loom-large-amid-auto-tech-glitz-ces-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7WEUKCMXFO6VCOQWXNVU5KB2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 11:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：华尔街五日连跌，美元占上风]]></title><description><![CDATA[塞缪尔-因迪克对美国和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by Samuel Indyk】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6M4XZAXLLJN3TAKRXTJ7Q7P4DQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 11:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 意大利 2024 年产量下降 37%，汽车产量创 68 年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[工会周五公布的数据显示，意大利汽车制造商 Stellantis 去年的汽车产量下降了 37%，尤其是受到汽车制造业急剧下滑的影响。【原文：Vehicle production by car maker Stellantis in Italy fell by 37% last year, hit in particular by a steep plunge in car manufacturing, union figures showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-italy-output-falls-475090-vehicles-2024-cars-lowest-level-since-1956-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BKRLVUSNFIUFO3OVSQYZ2B44I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 10:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债券收益率上升，美国股票流入降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 1 月 1 日的一周内，受国债收益率上升和年底获利回吐的影响，以及对美联储今年降息步伐放缓的担忧，流入美国股票基金的资金大幅减少。【原文：Inflows into U.S. equity funds fell sharply in the week through Jan. 1 hit by rising Treasury yields and year-end profit- taking, along with concerns about a slower pace of Federal Reserve rate reductions this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-inflows-cool-higher-bond-yields-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Z2RRFV7VJJMDIAZLA6WJPQWTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 10:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国商飞是 C919 飞机制造商，目标是到 2026 年开通东南亚航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国有飞机制造商中国商飞公司（COMAC）的一位高级官员告诉中国媒体，该公司的目标是到2026年，其C919喷气机将开始飞往东南亚的商业航线，作为走出国内市场的第一步。【原文：Chinese state-owned plane maker COMAC aims for its C919 jet to start flying on commercial routes to Southeast Asia by 2026 as a first step to moving beyond its domestic market, a senior company official told Chinese media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/chinas-comac-maker-c919-jet-aims-southeast-asian-flights-by-2026-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSOTXFLUWNK5XDG7I5U7ILRI3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 10:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债券收益率上升导致全球股票基金流入量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月1日的一周内，由于美国国债收益率上升导致投资者谨慎，以及投资者在年末交易淡季获利了结，全球股票基金需求萎缩。【原文：Demand for global equity funds shrank in the week through Jan. 1, as higher U.S. Treasury yields led to caution and investors took profits during the year-end trading lull.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVQ6X5YWUZOEDM3WT4D4CO35Z4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 09:53:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲股市在假期缩短的一周结束时下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲股市在假期缩短的一周结束时下跌，交易员们关注经济数据，以寻找利率走向的线索，以及唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）担任总统后美国政策的潜在变化。【原文：European stocks dipped at the end of a holiday-shortened week, with traders focussed on economic data for clues on the path of interest rates as well as potential changes in U.S. policies under a Donald Trump presidency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-stocks-dip-end-holiday-shortened-week-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEDWKFGMUZOGRMBJVCWUXDH2OA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:32:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车和起亚汽车 2024 年销量未达标，2025 年销量稳步上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国现代汽车公司（Hyundai Motor Co）和其子公司起亚汽车公司（Kia Corp）在 2024 年全球销量下降并未达标后，计划在 2025 年实现全球销量增长 2%。【原文：South Korea's Hyundai Motor Co and affiliate Kia Corp aim to grow their combined global sales by 2% in 2025, after reporting falls in 2024 sales and missing their targets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-kia-motor-see-2025-sales-inch-up-after-missing-2024-targets-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SQTPK7JUYBPIPO7IVZHYMD2JHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 07:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[11 月中国外资智能手机出货量下滑 47]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一家隶属于政府的研究公司周五公布的数据显示，包括苹果公司 iPhone 在内的外国品牌智能手机 11 月份在中国的出货量同比下降了 47.4%。【原文：Shipments of foreign-branded smartphones, including Apple Inc's iPhone, in China fell in November by 47.4% from a year earlier, according to data released on Friday from a government-affiliated research firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/foreign-smartphone-shipments-china-slump-47-november-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJMF424WJZMTFIOPX4AZ7LVOAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 07:15:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价股市摇摆不定，美元仍是最可靠的赌注]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CODYTP7KERP23EHW2YZTAOKFQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 05:34:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年中国将大幅增加国债融资以刺激经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位国家规划官员周五表示，中国将在 2025 年大幅增加超长期国债的融资，以刺激商业投资和促进消费的举措，因为中国政府正在加大财政刺激力度，以重振摇摇欲坠的经济。【原文：China will sharply increase funding from ultra-long treasury bonds in 2025 to spur business investment and consumer-boosting initiatives, a state planner official said on Friday, as Beijing ramps up fiscal stimulus to revitalise a faltering economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-will-sharply-increase-funding-treasury-bonds-spur-growth-2025-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSAC2FAWGZIQZL2LKGJCUSVLVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 04:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》报道：拜登决定阻止美国钢铁公司出售给新日铁公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》周四援引两位无权公开谈论此事的政府官员的话报道称，美国总统乔-拜登已决定正式阻止新日铁收购美国钢铁公司的提议。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden has decided to officially block Nippon Steel's proposed purchase of U.S. Steel, Washington Post reported on Thursday, citing two administration officials who were not authorized to speak publicly about the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/biden-decides-block-us-steel-sale-nippon-steel-washington-post-reports-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWOZJHXNSFJEPFKZ4GSI2NG2VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 04:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[致命坠机事故发生后，韩国延长了波音 737-800 飞机的检查时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着喷气发动机制造商通用电气（GE）加入对韩国本土最致命航空灾难的调查，韩国交通部已将对该国航空公司运营的全部 101 架波音 737-800 喷气式飞机的特别检查延长了一周。【原文：South Korea's transport ministry has extended by a week special inspections of all 101 of the Boeing 737-800 jets run by the country's airlines, as jet engine maker GE joined a probe into the deadliest aviation disaster on the country's soil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-extends-boeing-737-800-inspections-following-fatal-crash-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZUQ64K4M5KXVEPYB6UD4GX5QQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 12 月在华销量增至 8.3 万辆，创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[据特斯拉中国公司称，特斯拉电动汽车 12 月份在全球最大汽车市场的销量比上月增长了 12.8%，达到 83,000 辆，创历史新高。【原文：Tesla 's electric vehicle sales in the world's largest auto market increased in December by 12.8% from a month earlier to a record high of 83,000 units, according to Tesla China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-china-sales-rise-record-high-83000-december-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WH3RXVZARBN37HELOGUVOG33J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 02:49:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海南免税店消费下降 29%，中国购物天堂面临困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于经济疲软，国内游客急剧减少，去年中国海南省的免税消费下滑了 29.3%。【原文：Duty-free spending in China's island province of Hainan, where global luxury players from LVMH to Kering have set up shop, slumped 29.3% last year as a weak economy saw a sharp drop in domestic visitors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trouble-chinas-shopping-paradise-hainan-duty-free-spending-falls-29-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXT5IFJPHVO5XCTYOETXKBXGDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 02:41:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市上涨，美元创两年新高，美国利率和特朗普成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周五上涨，旨在摆脱2025年开局乏力的局面，而美元兑一篮子货币则创下两年来的新高，因为投资者担心美国利率会在更长时间内持续走高。【原文：Asian stocks rose on Friday, aiming to shrug off a lacklustre start to 2025, while the dollar was perched at a two-year high against a basket of currencies as investors fret about U.S. rates staying higher for longer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4IV44WODFIVVNTOSQA6A6EXCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 02:36:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油从两个月高点回升，因对政策支持经济增长持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在上一交易日创下两个多月以来的最高收盘价后，周五延续涨势，原因是市场希望各国政府可能加大政策支持力度，以恢复经济增长，从而提升燃料需求。【原文：Oil prices extended their gains on Friday after closing at their highest in more than two months in the previous session on hopes governments across the world may increase policy support to revive economic growth that would lift fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-two-month-highs-optimism-over-policy-support-growth-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNBAAGHRZVJFVOLJAKCT6S64BM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据哥伦比亚广播公司新闻报道，拜登最早将于周五宣布关于新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司的决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[据哥伦比亚广播公司（CBS News）周四晚些时候援引熟悉这一过程的人士的话报道，美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）可能最快于周五宣布是否批准新日铁收购美国钢铁公司的决定。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden is likely to announce a decision as soon as Friday on whether he will approve Nippon Steel's acquisition of U.S. Steel , CBS News reported late on Thursday, citing people familiar with the process.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/biden-reveal-decision-us-steel-acquisition-early-friday-cbs-news-reports-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LGKDHPNP5LJTHPAVVZJJFAFZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:46:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国利率和经济前景影响，美元将迎来 11 月以来最好的一周]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元有望创下一个多月以来的最佳单周表现，这主要是受到美联储今年降息次数将减少的预期以及美国经济表现将继续优于全球其他国家的观点的支撑。【原文：The dollar was on track for its best weekly performance in over a month on Friday, underpinned by expectations of fewer Federal Reserve rate cuts this year and the view that the U.S. economy will continue to outperform the rest of its peers globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-headed-best-week-since-november-us-rates-economic-outlook-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2HRHWOVYBKYNOQUVYLYTPZXNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skydance 和派拉蒙驳回对 84 亿美元合并计划的反对意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[Skydance Media 和 Paramount Global 周四为其 84 亿美元的合并计划辩护，敦促联邦通信委员会驳回批评者的反对意见，称其 "毫无根据"、"毫无价值"。【原文：Skydance Media and Paramount Global on Thursday defended their planned $8.4 billion merger, urging the Federal Communications Commission to dismiss opposition from critics, calling them "unwarranted" and "meritless".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/skydance-paramount-dismiss-objections-planned-84-bln-merger-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SYU7DZO6JJUXDEKT4DA5XTLUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国央行可能在 2025 年将利率从目前的 1.5% 下调]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引中国央行对该报的评论报道称，中国央行可能会在2025年 "适当的时候 "将利率从目前的1.5%水平下调。【原文：China's central bank said it was likely it would cut interest rates from the current level of 1.5% “at an appropriate time” in 2025, the Financial Times reported on Friday citing comments the bank made to the newspaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-central-bank-might-cut-interest-rates-current-level-15-2025-ft-reports-2025-01-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7AKLXFVQZKPPFMFKG53M5EX6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:20:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月液化天然气出口飙升，全年增长 4.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融公司 LSEG 的初步数据显示，12 月份美国液化天然气出口量接近创纪录水平，随着两家新工厂的开工，出口量增至 850 万公吨，推动全年出口量比 2023 年增长 4.5%。【原文：U.S. LNG exports reached near record levels in December, rising to 8.5 million metric tonnes (MT) as two new plants started, and driving up full-year shipments 4.5% over 2023, according preliminary data from financial firm LSEG.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-lng-exports-soar-december-lifting-full-year-growth-by-45-2025-01-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XSZF53JZRIBJJMIWREZCM6UKY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 21:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>