<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 21:04:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 21:04:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[破产的 Steward Health 获准亏本出售马萨诸塞州六家医院]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的私营医院运营商 Steward Health Care 周三获得了破产法官的批准，可以出售马萨诸塞州的六家医院，尽管这笔价值 3.43 亿美元的出售没有带来任何利润。【原文：Steward Health Care, the largest private hospital operator in the U.S., received a bankruptcy judge's approval on Wednesday to sell six Massachusetts hospitals, despite taking no profit from the $343 million sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bankrupt-steward-health-approved-sell-six-massachusetts-hospitals-loss-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDHUFV2VB5N6RET7JWC4RYWKBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 21:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司和罗尔斯公司将向航空公司介绍情况，以缓解 A350 的检查压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士说，航空公司可能会被告知没有必要立即对空客A350-1000进行全球检查，从而结束了国泰航空因发动机突发事件而对其机队进行审查后数日的不确定性。【原文：Airlines will likely be told there is no immediate need for global checks on the Airbus A350-1000, ending days of uncertainty after an engine emergency prompted Cathay Pacific to review its fleet, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-rolls-brief-airlines-pressure-a350-checks-eases-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVQEYF743JP6BDPVCLGNIRBD2M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASML 首席执行官称美国限制对华设备出口是出于 "经济动机]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰计算机芯片设备供应商ASML公司首席执行官周三表示，由美国主导的以国家安全为名限制该公司向中国客户出口的运动随着时间的推移已变得更具 "经济动机"。【原文：The chief executive of Dutch computer chip equipment supplier ASML on Wednesday said a U.S.-led campaign to restrict the company's exports to customers in China in the name of national security has become more "economically motivated" over time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/asml-ceo-says-us-motivation-restricting-equipment-exports-china-is-economically-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRTEIOMQJJNUHHSKE3TXL66X3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，强生公司在滑石粉和解问题上战胜了长期以来的顽固派]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道，强生公司在提高了对索赔人的报价后，有望获得更多支持其滑石粉和解计划的选票，这动摇了一个长期的法律对手。【原文：Johnson &amp; Johnson is expected to secure more votes in favor of its talc settlement plan after increasing its offer to claimants, which has swayed a longtime legal adversary, WSJ reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/johnson-johnson-wins-over-longtime-holdout-talc-settlement-wsj-reports-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPTTFCX6GBLGXHYZQW3LVUQ2RM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:12:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达发言人称未收到美国司法部传票]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达发言人在周三的一份声明中说，英伟达没有收到美国司法部的传票。【原文：Nvidia did not receive a U.S. Justice Department subpoena, a spokesperson said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-did-not-receive-us-justice-department-subpoena-spokesperson-says-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OHWR7ZN3RKNFGSTPR5DIJS3HQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 19:59:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席财务官称，英特尔制造业务将在 2027 年实现 "有意义的 "收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司首席财务官周三在投资者会议上表示，英特尔将于 2027 年开始从其合约芯片制造业务中获得 "可观 "的收入。【原文：Intel will begin to generate a "meaningful" amount of revenue from its contract chip manufacturing business in 2027, the company's CFO said at an investor conference on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-manufacturing-business-will-see-meaningful-revenue-2027-cfo-says-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6A5ZEA7Y5PNBOSZJNLEO5DHJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 19:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储调查显示，最近几周美国企业经济活动放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[从 7 月中旬到 8 月下旬，美国经济活动的扩张速度放缓，企业报告的招聘人数减少，这些信号都强调了美联储将在本月晚些时候降低利率的原因。【原文：U.S. economic activity expanded more slowly from mid July through late August and businesses reported less hiring, signals that underscore why the Federal Reserve is set to lower interest rates later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-firms-saw-slowing-economic-activity-recent-weeks-fed-survey-shows-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRQKDRDQZVLRNJWRXT53JTCYLE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主要图书出版商驳回互联网档案馆关于数字扫描的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院支持四家主要图书出版商的诉讼请求，他们指控非营利性机构互联网档案馆非法扫描版权作品，并未经许可在网上免费向公众出借这些作品。【原文：A U.S. appeals court sided with four major book publishers that accused the nonprofit Internet Archive of illegally scanning copyrighted works and lending them to the public online for free and without permission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/major-book-publishers-defeat-internet-archive-appeal-over-digital-scanning-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JM3R4OHD2JJINC7C7UTQB73E5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:18:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行调查显示，美国加快结汇的冲击比预期更大]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团（Citigroup）的一项调查显示，今年早些时候美国证券交易转向短期结算，对市场参与者的影响超出预期，其中欧洲受到的冲击最大。【原文：A shift to shorter settlement for U.S. securities transactions earlier this year had a greater-than-anticipated impact on market participants across the board, with Europe reporting the greatest hit, a Citigroup survey showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/faster-us-settlement-hit-harder-than-expected-says-citi-survey-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPR6VAPJ5JMQ3MR4K7N22GGHTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称拜登准备阻止新日铁收购美国钢铁公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周三称，美国总统乔-拜登正准备阻止新日铁收购美国钢铁公司。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden is preparing to block Nippon Steel's acquisition of U.S. Steel, a source said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/biden-preparing-block-nippons-us-steel-takeover-washington-post-reports-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U23PY6BGQFJPXKWKKCDFACZYGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，哈里斯将削减拜登的资本利得税提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三援引知情人士的话报道，民主党总统提名人卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）正计划提议降低资本利得税的最高税率。【原文：Democratic presidential nominee Kamala Harris is planning to propose a less drastic increase in the top capital gains tax rate, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/harris-pare-back-bidens-capital-gains-tax-proposal-wsj-reports-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DPEFVNQRRKKLO6BASWFXVSIJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:47:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟监管机构就谷歌避免被指控的合规建议征求反馈意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接知情人士周三表示，欧盟反垄断监管机构将于下周就谷歌为遵守旨在促进公平竞争的技术规则而提出的建议征求反馈意见，这可能会决定谷歌是否面临正式指控。【原文：European Union antitrust regulators will seek feedback next week on Google's proposals to comply with tech rules aimed at promoting fair competition, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Wednesday, which could decide whether it faces formal charges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-regulators-seek-feedback-googles-compliance-proposals-avert-charges-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAY4Y7GJTJKBXA63JQU76MX6JU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:32:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴姆勒卡车任命董事会成员卡琳-拉德斯特罗姆（Karin Radstrom）为新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国戴姆勒卡车控股公司（Daimler Truck Holding AG）周三表示，已任命卡琳-拉德斯特罗姆（Karin Radstrom）为公司新任首席执行官，自 10 月 1 日起生效。【原文：Germany's Daimler Truck Holding AG said on Wednesday it had appointed Karin Radstrom as its new CEO, effective Oct. 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/daimler-truck-appoints-board-member-karin-radstrom-new-ceo-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWK24HBXYFIHNKGPK7SR6VBSWA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:28:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的 X 公司上诉获胜，阻止了加州内容节制法的部分规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体平台 X 周三赢得上诉，部分阻止了加州要求社交媒体公司公布打击虚假信息、骚扰、仇恨言论和极端主义政策的法律。【原文：Elon Musk’s social media platform X on Wednesday won an appeal to partially block a California law requiring social media companies to publish their policies for combating disinformation, harassment, hate speech and extremism.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/elon-musks-x-wins-appeal-block-part-california-content-moderation-law-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QKWNZPMIJKGJMNGVGWZV232A4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:19:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜嘉班纳 2023-24 年营业亏损扩大至 1300 万欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份文件显示，杜嘉班纳控股公司（Dolce &amp; Gabbana Holding）在截至 3 月份的财年中，加大了对其店铺网络和美容部门的投资，并将该部门纳入公司内部，从而扩大了营业亏损，亏损额达 1300 万欧元（1440 万美元）。【原文：Dolce &amp; Gabbana Holding posted a wider operating loss of 13 million euros ($14.4 million) in the fiscal year through March after stepping up investments in its shop network and its beauty division which it brought in house, a filing showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dolce-gabbanas-operating-loss-widens-13-mln-euros-2023-24-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GC6BB7DTOBOWTICC4VS7B6MFXM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国代理劳工部长鼓励波音公司与工人达成 "公平合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[在9月12日即将就新协议进行投票之际，美国代理劳工部长朱莉-苏（Julie Su）周三鼓励波音公司和该飞机制造商工厂的3万多名工人弥合谈判中的分歧，达成一份公平的合同。【原文：Acting U.S. Labor Secretary Julie Su on Wednesday encouraged Boeing and more than 30,000 of the planemaker’s factory workers to bridge a divide in negotiations and reach a fair contract, as a vote on a new deal looms on Sept. 12.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/acting-us-labor-secretary-encourages-boeing-workers-reach-fair-contract-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6SHLWL73JMRDJKJDARLU3M7VA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:12:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国奥拉诺公司选址田纳西州建造铀浓缩厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[田纳西州和奥拉诺公司的官员周三表示，法国国有核燃料公司奥拉诺公司已选定田纳西州橡树岭作为建造一座耗资数十亿美元的美国铀浓缩厂的首选地点。【原文：France's state-owned nuclear fuel company Orano has selected Oak Ridge, Tennessee as a preferred site to build a multi-billion dollar U.S. uranium enrichment plant, Tennessee and Orano officials said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/frances-orano-selects-tennessee-site-build-uranium-enrichment-plant-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEC5B4NGQNMJLLQM4KPX73W6JQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 监督委员会要求公司不要自动删除支持巴勒斯坦的短语]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 平台监督委员会周三表示，Facebook 母公司不应自动删除被一些人视为声援巴勒斯坦人、被另一些人视为支持对犹太人施暴的短语。【原文：Meta Platforms' Oversight Board said on Wednesday the Facebook parent should not automatically remove a phrase seen by some as displaying solidarity with Palestinians and by others as an endorsement of violence against Jews.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-oversight-board-asks-firm-not-automatically-remove-pro-palestinian-phrase-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLCCFCCJ5BJZ3D7PATKI2JSNUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗技创始人试图罢免董事长未果]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗技国际公司（Logitech International）创始人丹尼尔-博雷尔（Daniel Borel）指责温迪-贝克尔（Wendy Becker）未能在这家电脑鼠标和键盘制造商中发挥领导作用，但博雷尔周三试图赶走温迪-贝克尔主席的行动失败了。【原文：Logitech International founder Daniel Borel on Wednesday failed in his attempt to oust Chairperson Wendy Becker, having accused her of failing to provide leadership at the maker of computer mice and keyboards.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/logitech-founder-fails-attempt-oust-chairperson-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V66IEGPHKVKOHOV47KL2W7KRGI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:57:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Trafigura 将贸易商合同的通知期延长至最短 6 个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士透露，大宗商品贸易公司 Trafigura 在最近发生员工离职事件后，已将交易员离职通知期延长至至少六个月或最长一年。【原文：Commodities trading company Trafigura has extended the notice period for traders leaving the firm to a minimum of six months or up to one year, three sources with knowledge of the matter said, after recent employee departures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trafigura-extends-notice-period-traders-contracts-6-month-minimum-sources-say-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YW5RAOVKI5NDFBSYHZ2GM4KT7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:51:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达股价暴跌让人们开始关注大科技对市场的影响力]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）和其他大型科技股今年帮助市场创下历史新高。它们最近的动荡令投资者感到紧张。【原文：Shares of Nvidia and other Big Tech stocks have helped power the markets run to record highs this year. Their recent wobble is making investors nervous.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidias-stock-swoon-turns-attention-big-techs-sway-over-markets-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5EV7UJWSRRKIBGDWZYDKK5SL2M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:42:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官称，X 公司必须面对因大规模裁员而提出的年龄偏见集体诉讼请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山的一名联邦法官裁定，在埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）收购社交媒体平台 X 时被该公司解雇的约 150 名老年员工可以集体起诉该公司的年龄歧视行为，从而使该公司面临数百万美元的潜在赔偿。【原文：A federal judge in San Francisco has ruled that roughly 150 older workers who were laid off by social media platform X when Elon Musk acquired the company can sue for age discrimination as a class, exposing the company to millions of dollars in potential damages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-says-x-must-face-class-action-age-bias-claims-over-mass-layoff-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAAWEV2DIZLCNJMCV2YHDLO2KU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:20:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rystad称美国石油天然气并购接近2023年纪录，重点不再是二叠纪]]></title><description><![CDATA[咨询公司 Rystad 的分析师周三表示，美国石油和天然气生产商的交易欲望正在接近去年的纪录，对小型油田兴趣的上升抵消了二叠纪盆地顶级产油地区交易活动的放缓。【原文：U.S. oil and gas producers' appetite for dealmaking is closing in on last year's record, with rising interest in smaller oilfields offsetting slower activity in the top oil-producing Permian basin, analysts at consultancy firm Rystad said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-oil-gas-ma-nears-2023-record-focus-shifts-away-permian-rystad-says-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX6Q73FID5MTHDRH6U5AMUIHJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:13:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定 J&J 欠 Auris 10 亿美元，与 2019 年机器人交易有关]]></title><description><![CDATA[特拉华州一名法官周三裁定，强生公司（Johnson &amp; Johnson）应向 Auris Health Inc 赔偿 10 亿美元，因为该公司违反了 2019 年收购这家私营公司机器人技术的协议。【原文：A Delaware judge ruled on Wednesday that Johnson &amp; Johnson owed Auris Health Inc $1 billion in damages for breaching a 2019 agreement to acquire the private company's robot technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-rules-that-jj-owes-auris-1-bln-related-2019-robot-deal-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GD3VDB56ORL77LTTLICH6B7ZAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[费城联储表示正在寻找哈克的继任者]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联邦储备银行（Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia）周三表示，该行正在物色接替将于明年 6 月退休的现任领导人帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）的人选。【原文：The Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia said Wednesday it is launching a search to replace its current leader Patrick Harker, who will retire next June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/philadelphia-fed-says-its-now-looking-harker-successor-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AF7RITFFDJOA7OGJSWV5EIDBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通称，有关美元消亡的报道大为夸张]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）周三表示，尽管大宗商品市场和某些贸易集团出现了一些戏剧性的变化迹象，但有关美元在全球金融体系中的主导地位即将终结的说法并不准确。【原文：Suggestions that the dollar's dominance of the global financial system is ending are wide of the mark, JPMorgan said on Wednesday, despite some dramatic signs of change in commodity markets and certain trading blocs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/reports-dollars-demise-are-greatly-exaggerated-jpmorgan-says-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REAGVBPCBNKFJF6GPQBMC4FMLQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月份工厂订单超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在国防飞机的推动下，7 月份美国制成品的新订单增幅超过预期，但在借贷成本上升的情况下，其他方面的需求也很一般。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods increased more than expected in July, boosted by defense aircraft, but demand elsewhere was moderate amid higher borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-factory-orders-beat-expectations-july-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABPOBOJEONOHDOJ6PLNB5CFZOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:48:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着职位空缺减少，美联储更有可能大幅降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，交易商加大了对美联储将在下次会议上降息半个百分点的押注，此前的数据显示，美联储7月份的职位空缺降至三年半以来的最低水平。
交易商仍认为美联储在9月17-18日的会议上降息四分之一个百分点的可能性略大，但认为降息50个基点的可能性从41%上升到49%。【原文：Traders on Wednesday added to bets that the Federal Reserve will deliver a half-a-percentage-point reduction at its next meeting, after data showed job openings in July fell to the lowest level in three and a half years.
Traders still see a quarter-point reduction at the Fed's Sept 17-18 meeting as the slightly more likelier move, but give a 50-basis-point cut about a 49% chance, up from 41% immed】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-seen-more-likely-deliver-bigger-rate-cuts-job-openings-fall-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSJTIE6R6JOD7FRXATWO5IQJUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:21:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月职位空缺降至 3 年半新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国7月份的职位空缺降至3年半以来的新低，表明劳动力市场正在失去动力，但可能还不足以让美联储考虑在本月大幅降息。【原文：U.S. job openings dropped to a 3-1/2-year low in July, suggesting the labor market was losing steam, but probably not enough for the Federal Reserve to consider a big interest rate cut this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-fall-3-12-year-low-july-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q64PGHAQ7JJNDPZKTWF4FZQSOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:19:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行称，如果欧佩克+不进一步减产，2025 年的平均油价可能为 60 美元/桶]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行周三在一份报告中说，如果产油国集团欧佩克+不进一步减产，由于需求减少和非欧佩克国家的供应增加，2025 年的平均油价可能降至每桶 60 美元。【原文：If producer group OPEC+ doesn't reduce production further, the average price of oil could drop to $60 per barrel in 2025 due to reduced demand and increased supply from non-OPEC countries, Citi said in a note on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/citi-says-2025-oil-prices-could-average-60bbl-without-deeper-opec-cuts-2024-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3CNPQ54ZJNSVPTEW6BNZ5EVGA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>