<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:06:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:06:25 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：特朗普瞄准电动汽车补贴，通用汽车的电动汽车收益面临严峻考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[几十年来，通用汽车斥资数十亿美元试图开辟一条电动汽车发展之路，推出了许多电动汽车和混合动力汽车的先驱，但最终都未能在市场上实现大规模销售，最终被废弃。这一次可能会有所不同。【原文：General Motors has spent billions over decades trying to blaze an electric trail, releasing pioneering EVs and hybrids that ultimately failed to achieve mass-market sales before being scrapped. This time might be different.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gms-electric-gains-face-critical-test-trump-targets-ev-subsidies-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CXHAGJZ75I4BF5KNKCZ4CEKQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金因关税问题吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 2 月 26 日的一周内，受今年晚些时候降息预期持续升温的刺激，全球股票基金资金大幅流入，而本周报告的疲软经济数据又为这一预期提供了支撑。【原文：Global equity funds witnessed sharp inflows in the week through February 26, spurred by sustained expectations of rate cuts later this year, which were bolstered by weaker economic data reported during the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEQWMJLUZRKPHG7D36NH36ZDPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国规定自动驾驶软件升级须经监管部门批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国工业部周五表示，与自动驾驶相关的空中软件升级必须获得监管部门的批准，这是旨在防止汽车制造商利用软件升级隐瞒缺陷或逃避责任的新规定的一部分。【原文：Autonomous driving-related over-the-air software upgrades will be subject to regulatory approvals, China's industry ministry said on Friday, part of new regulations aimed at preventing automakers using them to conceal defects or avoid liability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-mandates-regulatory-approvals-autonomous-driving-software-upgrades-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CDMUM4JSBORTA4K4N3MFCWMEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新华社：中国空间站将在未来几年迎来首位外国宇航员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据新华社报道，中国和巴基斯坦周五签署了关于航天员选拔和培训的合作协议。【原文：China and Pakistan signed a cooperation agreement on the selection and training of astronauts on Friday, Xinhua reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/chinas-space-station-welcome-first-foreign-astronaut-next-few-years-xinhua-says-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYBY7A5ARBKWZCM72H2UU6UJK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:22:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀疲软、增长乏力支持欧洲央行降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的最新数据显示，欧元区的通胀前景有所改善，但经济增长依然乏力，这为欧洲央行进一步降息以刺激已停滞近两年的经济提供了更充分的理由。【原文：Euro zone inflation prospects improved while growth remained anaemic, fresh data showed on Friday, solidifying the case for further ECB rate cuts to stimulate an economy that has been stagnant for nearly two years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/softer-inflation-weak-growth-bolster-case-ecb-rate-cuts-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTBAGNIXMRLCHNLPVHTNQMI2NU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two dozen arrested for distributing AI-generated child abuse images]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two dozen people were arrested this week for their role in a criminal group that distributed images generated by artificial intelligence of children being sexually abused, Europol said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/two-dozen-arrested-distributing-ai-generated-child-abuse-images-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JN5RZSMODVNQXBGFQ4VFFOZ7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New World Development reports $852 million first-half net loss]]></title><description><![CDATA[New World Development , one of the biggest property developers in Hong Kong, reported an interim net loss of HK$6.63 billion ($852.45 million) on Friday, following a prolonged property downturn and high interest costs.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/new-world-development-reports-852-million-first-half-net-loss-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP7VGSMWKBL33FCCEDAG2SIBEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK chip parts supplier Morgan Advanced flags revenue hit as trade tariff woes hit demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Semiconductor parts supplier Morgan Advanced Materials on Friday forecast a drop in organic revenue this year due to uncertain demand, sparked, in part, by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-chip-parts-supplier-morgan-advanced-flags-revenue-hit-trade-tariff-woes-hit-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TCXYJMUIVKEBC5PCM4KZ44QNU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Euro zone consumers lower near-term inflation expectations, ECB survey shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Euro zone consumers lowered their near-term inflation expectations last month but continued to see economic contraction ahead, indicating that households remain relatively downbeat on the bloc's prospects, an ECB survey showed on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-consumers-lower-near-term-inflation-expectations-ecb-survey-shows-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTIGZMP37RM55N3X64FRYFR47U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chinese mainland investors drive surge in Hong Kong stocks]]></title><description><![CDATA[China's mainland investors have played an unprecedented role in a rally on Hong Kong's equity market that has pushed the benchmark index to its highest level since 2022.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-mainland-investors-drive-surge-hong-kong-stocks-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHJ7F2VVVRKHDKOJG5TWH5PMU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citi raises first-quarter average tin price forecast, sees easing in second quarter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citi Research raised its average tin price forecast for the first quarter of 2025 to $32,000 per metric ton from $29,000 on Friday but noted that prices will start easing from the second quarter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-raises-first-quarter-average-tin-price-forecast-sees-easing-second-quarter-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLXKOWOLUJMRHLWDY5SCV2FYH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citigroup mistakenly credits customer account with $81 trillion in "near miss", FT reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citigroup erroneously credited $81 trillion, instead of $280, to a customer's account and took hours to reverse the transaction, a "near miss" that shows up the bank's operational issues it has sought to fix, the Financial Times reported on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-mistakenly-credits-customer-account-with-81-trillion-near-miss-ft-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZQR55CGGJLVNLXK42ZJRGJXAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:52:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[British Airways owner IAG profit beats estimates, plans share buyback]]></title><description><![CDATA[British Airways owner IAG reported a 27% jump in annual operating profit on Friday, beating market expectations as it curbed costs and growth in its lucrative transatlantic routes took off.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/british-airways-owner-iags-annual-earnings-beat-expectations-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5ZV3SAGQRL2LOYK75CDJRDQBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡指控三人诈骗，媒体称与英伟达芯片有关]]></title><description><![CDATA[Singapore charged three men with fraud in a case domestic media have linked to the movement of Nvidia's advanced chips from the city state to Chinese artificial intelligence firm DeepSeek.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/singapore-charges-three-with-fraud-that-media-link-nvidia-chips-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LISWVWPYMRLXJNDYZUEJNQWBXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:57:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Car parts supplier Forvia forecasts 2025 sales at around last year level]]></title><description><![CDATA[French car parts supplier Forvia said on Friday it sees sales in 2025 at around last year's level, reflecting a downturn in European and North American automotive demand dragging into the new year.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/car-parts-supplier-forvia-forecasts-2025-sales-around-previous-year-level-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6RC753U2JKANPYCPV3SBQOBUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Chinese banks heed PBOC call to cut dollar deposit rates, say sources]]></title><description><![CDATA[China's banks are cutting the interest rates offered on U.S. dollar deposits after being asked to do so by the central bank, possibly to curtail dollar hoarding and also prop up a weakening yuan, sources said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-banks-heed-pboc-call-cut-dollar-deposit-rates-say-sources-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6NGMEO2OJPZRNXPLGP322KY6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bytedance's TikTok to invest $8.8 bln in Thailand data centres, official says]]></title><description><![CDATA[ByteDance's TikTok will invest $8.8 billion in data centres in Thailand over five years, Helena Lersch, TikTok's Vice President of Public Policy, said on Friday at an event in Bangkok.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bytedances-tiktok-invest-88-bln-thailand-data-centres-official-says-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F5OVD43XJO6LPYHQTSJFGE4CI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia's seizures offer warning to Western firms hoping for Trump-inspired return]]></title><description><![CDATA[One morning in October 2024, three men entered the Moscow headquarters of Glavprodukt, the largest maker of canned food in Russia. One announced himself as the new director general and said he would now be making the decisions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russias-seizures-offer-warning-western-firms-hoping-trump-inspired-return-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAJSAILJHFI6ZK23RTB6BN3OJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto prices tumble as Trump-fuelled euphoria fades]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency prices are down sharply in recent weeks and not expected to rebound soon, with some of the biggest digital currencies erasing nearly all of the gains they made after Donald Trump's election win triggered a wave of excitement across the industry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/crypto-prices-tumble-trump-fuelled-euphoria-fades-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJA5RQ7QMBKPDPF7Z7Z6TOMGBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[水泥生产商 Holcim 第四季度盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Holcim 公司周五公布的第四季度财报好于预期，该建材公司公布了分拆北美业务计划的更多细节。【原文：Holcim reported better-than-expected earnings for its fourth quarter on Friday as the building materials company gave more details of its plan to spin off its North American business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/cement-maker-holcim-beats-earnings-forecasts-fourth-quarter-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RLYX2SWG5JTFFEOEQX4L5T6YI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:43:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标特朗普关税忧虑无处藏身]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7QN7EXFQRISNBEXPDWTC4SFNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国表示反对美国最新关税威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五表示，反对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普因致命毒品流入美国而对中国进口商品额外征收10%关税的最新威胁，指责白宫 "推卸责任 "并采取措施破坏全球供应链的稳定。【原文：China on Friday said it opposed President Donald Trump's latest threat to slap an extra 10% duty on Chinese imports over deadly drug flows into the U.S., accusing the White House of "shifting the blame" and taking steps to destabilise global supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-says-it-opposes-latest-us-tariff-threat-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X66WMCSY6JNZHBUZEBJIK3O4KY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：英国能源大臣将于三月访华，重启能源谈判并会见投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位直接了解该计划的消息人士告诉路透社，英国能源大臣埃德-米利班德（Ed Miliband）将于 3 月访华，重启能源合作谈判并会见中国投资者。【原文：British Energy Secretary Ed Miliband will visit China in March to restart talks on energy cooperation and meet Chinese investors, three sources with direct knowledge of the plan told Reuters, as the Labour government seeks closer China ties amid worsening U.S.- and EU-China relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/british-energy-secretary-visit-china-march-restart-energy-talks-meet-investors-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6CE2JYSP5OMNJKCV65TJBA2SI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 04:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受中国钢铁出口担忧影响，铁矿石将出现月度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国关税担忧和针对中国钢铁出口的贸易摩擦加剧的打压，铁矿石期货价格周五下跌，并将出现小幅月度跌幅。【原文：Iron ore futures prices fell on Friday and were set for modest monthly losses, pressured by U.S. tariff concerns and mounting trade frictions against Chinese steel exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/iron-ore-set-monthly-loss-china-steel-export-concerns-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MORNXDOQSFIPDBB3AXQ6SEOQ3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 TPG 电信公司因盈利向好而创下四个月以来的最高纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，澳大利亚 TPG 电信公司的股价飙升至四个多月来的新高，该公司在截至 12 月 31 日的一年中基本盈利增长了 3.4%，达到 19.9 亿澳元（12.4 亿美元）。【原文：Shares of Australia's TPG Telecom surged to a more-than-four-month high on Friday after the telco logged a 3.4% rise in its underlying earnings to A$1.99 billion ($1.24 billion) for the year ended December 31.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australias-tpg-telecom-hits-four-month-peak-upbeat-earnings-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MB6OECEJZFNY3JDMGAWPJSS6LA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国制造业活动将在 2 月份连续第二个月萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[2 月份，中国的工厂活动可能连续第二个月萎缩，在制造商为美国新关税做准备之际，要求采取更多刺激措施以支撑世界第二大经济体低迷的内需的呼声依然不绝于耳。【原文：China's factory activity likely contracted for a second month in February, keeping alive calls for even more stimulus to prop up depressed domestic demand in the world's second-largest economy as manufacturers brace for fresh U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-manufacturing-activity-set-contract-second-month-feb-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLHQJKKGWVNWXIVFVC6Z32MAXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:17:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币下滑超过 5%，跌至 11 月 11 日以来最低水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关税计划和加密货币政策不确定性的拖累，以及竞争对手加密货币以太坊被黑客攻击15亿美元后投资者信心下滑的影响，比特币周五跌至3个半月以来的最低水平。【原文：Bitcoin dropped to its lowest level in 3-1/2 months on Friday, dragged by uncertainty about U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff plans and crypto policy and flagging investor confidence after a $1.5 billion hack in rival crypto currency ether.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-slides-more-than-5-lowest-level-since-november-11-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IY4VROBC3JKRDCZ6PIZNJH3OKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计上半年亏损 8.75 亿美元，新世界发展债务偿还成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[受房地产长期低迷和利息成本高企的影响，过去三年一直与流动性压力作斗争的香港新世界发展将于周五公布中期净亏损高达 8.75 亿美元。【原文：Hong Kong's New World Development , which has been battling liquidity stress for the past three years, is set to report an interim net loss of up to $875 million on Friday, hurt by a prolonged property downturn and high interest costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/new-world-developments-debt-repayment-focus-amid-875-million-expected-h1-loss-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIOTU2X2P5NLVKUGSD4UR4Z6WA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:41:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首尔：韩美两国财政部长讨论关税、投资和外汇问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部周五表示，韩国代总统兼财政部长崔相木与美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特在视频通话中讨论了关税、投资和外汇政策。【原文：South Korea's acting President and Finance Minister Choi Sang-mok and U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent discussed tariffs, investment and forex policy in a video call, South Korea's finance ministry said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-us-finance-chiefs-discuss-tariffs-investment-fx-says-seoul-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYDFH6ZWXBLFXL6QYV66ADHU4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税威胁引发市场动荡，股市暴跌，美元走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心全球贸易战升级，市场情绪低落，周五亚洲股市暴跌，美元兑该国主要贸易伙伴货币的汇率徘徊在数周高点附近。【原文：Equities slumped in Asia on Friday and the U.S. dollar hovered near multi-week highs against the currencies of the country's top trading partners as concerns about an escalating global trade war soured market sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFFTYPYL3FJTFKF57YS7MEQ52Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:12:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>