<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:05:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:05:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[BNSF 和 CSX 启动新的美国海岸至海岸连接，以促进货运服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[CSX 和伯克希尔-哈撒韦（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的 BNSF 周五宣布推出新的海岸至海岸服务，以促进美国的货运连接。【原文：CSX and Berkshire Hathaway-owned BNSF on Friday announced new coast-to-coast services to boost freight connectivity in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bnsf-csx-launch-new-us-coast-to-coast-linking-boost-freight-services-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WRGM7ML4NN3ZOBZ3LZC4N33BY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西出口商集团称美国关税是全球阿拉比卡价格飙升的幕后推手]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西咖啡出口商理事会（Cecafe）负责人周五表示，8月份全球阿拉比卡咖啡市场大幅上涨，ICE交易所的价格涨幅超过30%，主要原因是美国大幅提高了关税。【原文：The global arabica coffee market has surged in August with prices gaining more than 30% on the ICE exchange, driven mainly by steep tariff hikes from the United States, the head of Brazil's coffee exporters council, Cecafe, said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-tariffs-behind-surge-global-arabica-prices-brazil-exporters-group-says-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXXD5FSWANJBZJ7FDQMW67CR3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:55:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔在杰克逊霍尔发表讲话，鸽派倾向令市场火热]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周五发表了备受关注的杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）演讲，令市场对美国央行准备放宽利率的乐观情绪升温，投资者纷纷涌入风险较高的资产和对利率敏感的行业。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's closely watched Jackson Hole speech on Friday boosted optimism in markets that the U.S. central bank is poised to ease rates, sending investors to pile into riskier assets and interest-rate-sensitive sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/powells-jackson-hole-address-fires-up-markets-with-dovish-tilt-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KV7Q6EY3XZKHRHYVMZ4FXISCYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，随着数据争夺战白热化，维萨关闭了美国开放银行部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，支付处理商 Visa 已关闭其在美国的开放银行业务。【原文：Payments processor Visa has shut its open-banking business in the United States, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/visa-shutters-us-open-banking-unit-data-fight-heats-up-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARXFKMU4OVKH3LUTTHLSOVGRII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:51:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国葡萄酒制造商担心特朗普关税将打击其在至关重要的美国市场的销量]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国葡萄酒和烈酒生产商正准备对其出口到美国这一重要市场的产品征收 15%的关税，尽管欧盟委员会承诺将继续为该行业争取优惠税率。【原文：French wine and spirits producers are bracing for a 15% tariff on their exports to the United States, a crucial market, even as the European Commission pledges to keep pressing for a preferential rate for the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/french-winemakers-fear-trump-tariffs-will-hit-sales-crucial-us-market-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXO2FKHL35O2JGLJCDVTVQKZO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利国家石油公司下调产量预期，税前利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界最大的铜生产商智利科德尔科公司 [RIC:RIC:COBRE.UL] 周五公布，2025 年上半年税前利润为 4.29 亿美元，比去年同期的 6.53 亿美元下降了 34%。【原文：Chile's Codelco [RIC:RIC:COBRE.UL], the world's largest copper producer, on Friday posted a pre-tax profit of $429 million for the first half of 2025, down 34% from the $653 million reported in the same period last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chiles-codelco-lowers-production-outlook-posts-pre-tax-profit-dip-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBN5HKGX7JPPRBZ2AAH64Z2WVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:19:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国环保局开始清理积压的炼油厂生物燃料规则豁免申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护局周五开始清理积压的小型炼油厂提出的国家生物燃料法豁免申请，批准了其中的 63 项，拒绝了 28 项，77 项获得部分批准。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency on Friday began clearing a backlog of requests from small oil refineries for exemptions from the nation's biofuel laws, granting 63 and denying 28 of the them, with 77 receiving partial approvals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-epa-begins-clearing-backlog-oil-refiner-requests-biofuel-rule-waivers-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTQ636VWKFNLTNMEK5YV6AR3PE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:17:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士 Safra Sarasin 银行在 "洗车 "调查中被罚款 350 万瑞士法郎]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士总检察长周五表示，在围绕巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）的一起长达数年的腐败和洗钱案中，瑞士私人银行 J. Safra Sarasin SA 被处以 350 万瑞士法郎（430 万美元）的罚款。【原文：Switzerland's attorney general has fined Swiss private bank J. Safra Sarasin SA 3.5 million Swiss francs ($4.3 million) under a years-long corruption and money laundering case surrounding Brazilian state oil company Petrobras, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/swiss-bank-safra-sarasin-fined-35-million-francs-car-wash-probe-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3BKYQ5DAJOZHLXVJXL4EZIYFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:12:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称加拿大将取消多项针对美国商品的报复性关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士称，加拿大将于周五宣布取消对美国商品征收的多项报复性关税，以此作为重启停滞不前的贸易谈判的善意姿态。【原文：Canada will announce on Friday that it is removing many retaliatory tariffs on U.S. goods as a goodwill gesture designed to restart stalled trade talks, a source familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-remove-many-retaliatory-tariffs-us-goods-says-source-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2SQNKWGM5PEVC256UVRXBEU2U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪将精神航空的信用评级进一步降至垃圾级]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，穆迪评级公司（Moody's Ratings）将美国航空运营商精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）的信用评级下调两级，使其再次跌入垃圾级。【原文：U.S. airline operator Spirit Airlines took another hit to its credit rating on Friday after Moody's Ratings downgraded it two notches deeper into junk territory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/moodys-cuts-spirit-airlines-credit-rating-further-into-junk-territory-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNRISVPU4FIHFEGM5SSRY6YMK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，亚马逊游说印度政府免除出口产品的外商投资限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位直接了解此事的人士称，亚马逊正在游说印度政府放宽外商投资规定，允许这家美国公司直接从印度卖家那里购买产品在海外市场销售。【原文：Amazon is lobbying the Indian government to ease its foreign investment rules to allow the U.S. company to buy products directly from Indian sellers to sell in overseas markets, four people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-lobbies-indian-government-exempt-exports-foreign-investment-rules-sources-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GATBTNBN5OD5O7ZODUPOBGKTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗提升埃里克-萨沃拉（Erik Savola）为欧洲企业银行业务负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份备忘录，花旗集团提升埃里克-萨沃拉（Erik Savola）为欧洲企业银行业务主管，立即生效。【原文：Citigroup promoted Erik Savola to become its head of corporate banking for Europe, effective immediately, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-promotes-erik-savola-lead-corporate-banking-europe-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J3JE5ICVR5JP5FA3SNSO3WN6MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称必要时可延长 TikTok 的最后期限，美国有买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五表示，他已为 TikTok 物色到了美国买家，他可能会进一步延长总部位于中国的字节跳动剥离该应用美国资产的最后期限，并补充说他并不担心隐私或安全问题。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday said he has American buyers lined up for TikTok and that he could further extend the deadline for China-based ByteDance to divest the app's U.S. assets, adding that he did not have privacy or security concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-says-he-could-extend-tiktok-deadline-if-needed-has-us-buyers-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCH5BCJPZRI2FGCVSEEYTCZOYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称若美联储主席库克不辞职将解雇她]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，如果美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）不辞职，他将解雇她，这加大了他对美国中央银行施加影响的力度。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday said he would fire Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook if she doesn't resign, intensifying his effort to gain influence over the U.S. central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-hell-fire-feds-cook-if-she-doesnt-resign-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EZMNHJHTFK6ZIIKASAPFU4564</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美联储鲍威尔为 9 月宽松政策敞开大门]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周五在讲话中指出，该央行可能在9月份的会议上降息，但并未做出承诺，他在讲话中谨慎地承认了就业市场面临的日益增长的风险，同时还表示通胀上升的风险依然存在。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday pointed to a possible rate cut at the central bank's September meeting but stopped short of committing to it in remarks that walked a narrow line acknowledging growing risks to the job market while also saying risks of higher inflation remain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-feds-powell-opens-door-september-easing-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4BEXCLLERO2TLSAOOHZCZVKHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国碧桂园预计上半年亏损将因减值增加而扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[陷入困境的中国房地产开发商碧桂园周五预计，2025 财年上半年将出现更大亏损，原因是资产减值增加和房地产项目结算规模缩小。【原文：Embattled Chinese property developer Country Garden on Friday forecast a bigger loss for the first half of fiscal 2025, citing higher asset impairments and reduced scale of real estate project settlements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-country-garden-expects-bigger-first-half-loss-higher-impairments-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E25WHU5RDZOA5FG5TUWTAHZTKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔宣布调整政策框架以应对经济形势变化]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周五宣布了美国中央银行的最新运营框架，反映了过去五年来经济格局的重大变化，该框架反映了通胀压力的回升和短期利率接近零的前景的减弱。【原文：Nodding toward significant changes in the economic landscape over the last five years, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday announced an updated operating framework for the U.S. central bank that reflects the return of higher inflation pressures and reduced prospect of near zero short-term interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-powell-announces-policy-framework-tweaks-changed-economic-landscape-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMNX63SAVFLZJKCGSQQJGSKG6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金流入降温，因对科技行业大跌持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至8月20日的一周内，全球股票基金流入量大幅下降，原因是市场对领先科技股的下挫持谨慎态度，而美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔即将于本周末在杰克逊霍尔年度研讨会上发表的讲话也加剧了市场的避险情绪。【原文：Global equity fund inflows dropped sharply in the week through August 20 on caution over a selloff in leading technology stocks, with the Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's upcoming speech at the annual Jackson Hole symposium this weekend, also adding to risk aversion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ITEYIAGAZJL7ATY5UAIWJUKOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:33:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威巨型基金因以色列投资问题陷入选举漩涡]]></title><description><![CDATA[在以色列的投资已成为挪威竞选活动的中心议题，引发了一场关于世界上最大的主权财富基金如何运作的不同寻常的公开辩论。【原文：Investments in Israel have taken centre stage in Norway's election campaign, sparking an unusually public debate over how the world's largest sovereign wealth fund operates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/norways-giant-fund-election-crosshairs-over-israel-investments-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJ5SMBY5T5JYDI3HYIHFUXUBQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:30:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟对俄罗斯进口化肥征收关税后，欧洲农民面临更高的成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟对俄罗斯进口化肥征收关税的目的是削减莫斯科在乌克兰战争中的资金投入，但迄今为止，这些关税打击了欧洲农民，提高了成本，并可能导致消费者价格上涨，而俄罗斯公司则表示，他们可以将出口转向其他市场。【原文：EU tariffs on Russian fertiliser imports that aim to cut funding for Moscow's war in Ukraine have so far hit European farmers, raising costs and risking higher consumer prices while Russian companies say they can divert exports to other markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-farmers-facing-higher-costs-after-eu-tariffs-russian-fertiliser-imports-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBVCYX322NL6VARRHRSRIXK5OQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:01:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银将标普 500 指数年度目标上调至 6,600 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银全球财富管理公司（UBS Global Wealth Management）将上证 500 指数的年底目标上调至 6600 点，理由是企业盈利强劲、贸易紧张局势缓解以及降息预期。【原文：UBS Global Wealth Management has lifted its year-end target for the S&amp;P 500 index to 6,600, citing corporate earnings strength, easing trade tensions and expectations of interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ubs-lifts-sp-500-annual-target-6600-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YI6YRA6LD5KHNMR3REHFIPFAWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美联储鹰派再现，国债收紧]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CR26MWJI5RONZJYMJHMLPLU64Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，银行游说监管机构制定国家标准，以遏制州政府的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士称，美国银行正在向货币监理署（Office of the Comptroller of the Currency）请愿，要求制定提供银行服务的国家标准，以凌驾于各州的规定之上。
 这些消息人士在私下会谈时拒绝透露身份，他们说，特别是大型银行，正在游说制定统一的美国法规，概述它们如何发放贷款、发行债券或提供投资银行服务，或评估反洗钱风险，同时限制州政府对其业务的权力。
 路透社首次报道的这一重新推动国家标准的举措，是银行业为在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府下锁定更有利规则而做出的全面努力的一部分。
 消息人士称，这些变化将使贷款机构更容易运营。这些修改还将削弱各州通过所谓的 "去银行化"（debanking）规则干扰银行运营的权力，"去银行化 "是指银行基于政治或宗教信仰拒绝为客户提供服务。
 此前，个别州曾因贷款人在枪支、气候变化、多样性和其他社会问题上的政策而惩罚银行并禁止其开展业务。【原文：U.S. banks are petitioning the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency to seek national standards for providing banking services that would override state-imposed rules, three sources familiar with the matter said.
 Large banks, in particular, are lobbying for uniform U.S. regulations outlining how they can make loans, issue bonds or provide investment banking services, or assess anti-money laundering risks while curbing state powers over their operations, said the sources, who declined to be identified while discussing private talks.
 The renewed push for national standards, which is being reported by Reuters for the first time, is part of a sweeping effort by the banking industry to lock in more favorable rules under U.S. President Donald Trump's administration.
 The changes would make it easier for lenders to operate, the sources said. They would also curtail states' power to disrupt banks' operations with rules on so-called "debanking," a practice in which banks allegedly deny services to customers based on political or religious beliefs.
 Individual states have previously punished banks and barred them from doing business based on lenders' policies on guns, climate change, diversity and other social issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/banks-lobby-regulators-national-standards-curb-state-influence-sources-say-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYQ5U2MRYBO5ZLY3JN4DWPLDT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:34:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构开始调查 Getty Images-Shutterstock 交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国反垄断监管机构周五表示，已对在美国上市的盖蒂图片公司（Getty Images）以 37 亿美元与竞争对手 Shutterstock 合并一事展开调查。【原文：Britain's antitrust watchdog on Friday said it has launched an investigation into U.S.-listed Getty Images' $3.7 billion merger with rival Shutterstock .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uk-competition-watchdog-begins-probe-into-getty-images-shutterstock-deal-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JXWBR4LEZNJDIFM5EDUCQLBBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美国科技股动荡不安，投资者聚焦英伟达业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技股的震荡提高了英伟达公司（Nvidia Corp）周三公布季度业绩的风险，这家半导体巨头的财报将对炙手可热的人工智能交易构成关键考验。【原文：A wobble in U.S. technology shares has raised the stakes for Nvidia Corp's quarterly results on Wednesday, with earnings from the semiconductor giant posing a crucial test for the scorching AI trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-zero-nvidia-results-us-tech-stocks-waver-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHALUE4GFJKD5GELYXBN6DLNP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cenovus Energy 将以 69.3 亿加元收购 MEG Energy]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大石油生产商 MEG Energy 周五表示，该公司已同意被更大的同行 Cenovus Energy 以现金加股票的方式收购，交易价值 69.3 亿加元，从而创建加拿大最大的油砂公司之一。【原文：Canadian oil producer MEG Energy said on Friday it has agreed to be acquired by larger peer Cenovus Energy in a cash-and-stock deal worth C$6.93 billion, to create one of the largest oil sands companies in Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/cenovus-energy-acquire-meg-energy-c693-billion-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZOOGTZDMJLHXOMG5W7OO77KVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰克逊霍尔会议前聚焦美国各行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）将在杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）研讨会上发表讲话，届时华尔街将寻求9月降息的确认，这对市场尤其是对利率敏感的行业来说可能是一个关键时刻。【原文：Wall Street will search for confirmation of a September interest rate cut when Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell speaks at the Jackson Hole symposium on Friday, a potentially pivotal moment for the market and rate-sensitive sectors in particular.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-sectors-spotlight-ahead-feds-jackson-hole-gathering-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAQIL65NUJMY3BB2XYLOGNF5SM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通同意向马来西亚支付 3.3 亿美元以解决 1MDB 问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通与马来西亚政府双方周五表示，摩根大通将向马来西亚政府支付 3.3 亿美元，作为解决其在国家基金 1MDB 数十亿美元丑闻中所扮演角色的所有相关事宜的和解协议的一部分。【原文：JPMorgan Chase will pay the Malaysian government $330 million as part of a settlement to resolve all matters related to its role in the multi-billion dollar scandal at state fund 1MDB, both parties said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/jpmorgan-agrees-pay-malaysia-330-million-settle-1mdb-issues-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBRSMMU2JFMSBD746PIKS4PTXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克着眼中国发展，以户外运动改革为中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克将于本周一推出一款新的越野跑鞋，以此拉开进军蓬勃发展的户外休闲市场的序幕，这将考验耐克能否将一个鲜为人知的子品牌打造成一个有意义的增长引擎。【原文：Nike's push into the booming outdoor recreation market — which will kick off on Monday with the launch of a new trail running shoe — will test whether it can turn a little-known sub-brand into a meaningful growth engine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nike-eyes-china-growth-with-outdoor-sports-revamp-center-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQRLZVVZEZNUXINPAXYZWQDIVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加航工会违抗加拿大政府命令可能会使工人更加大胆]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府去年曾四次出面援助七家公司，利用《劳动法》的一项模糊条款制止了罢工。然而，由于加拿大航空公司的空乘人员拒绝服从，罢工持续了三天，周日的类似法令宣告失败。【原文：Canada's government stepped in four times to aid seven companies last year, stopping strikes using an obscure Labour Code provision. A similar decree on Sunday failed, however, as Air Canada's flight attendants refused to obey and stayed on strike for three days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-canada-unions-defiance-canadian-government-order-could-embolden-workers-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBTJLILXENOINMG4XIQX3J3YO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>