<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:08:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:08:04 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[挪威邮轮公司门票销售额创历史新高，再次上调盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威邮轮公司（Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings）受第三季度创纪录的收入和预售票房的鼓舞，周四第四次上调了今年的年度利润预期。【原文：Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings on Thursday raised its annual profit forecast for a fourth time this year, encouraged by record third-quarter revenue and advance ticket sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/norwegian-cruise-lifts-profit-forecast-again-after-record-ticket-sales-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCLHDHIIOVLB7K6AEISUWODXYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约证券交易所母公司 ICE 季度利润因交易量强劲而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[洲际交易所（Intercontinental Exchange）周四公布，由于地缘政治风险和降息预期的变化，各类资产交易量强劲，第三季度利润增加。【原文：Intercontinental Exchange reported a higher third-quarter profit on Thursday, helped by strong trading volumes across asset classes due to geopolitical risks and shifting expectations of interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nyse-parent-ices-quarterly-profit-rises-strong-trading-volumes-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7WAEMRSEZML7O2SLXXVQ43X3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:52:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[招聘公司 Challenger 称，10 月份美国计划裁员人数再次下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四发布的月度裁员公告统计显示，10月份美国的裁员公告降至三个月来的最低点，这再次表明在下周的总统大选之前，就业市场依然保持良好态势。【原文：U.S. layoff announcements tumbled in October to a three-month low in another sign the job market remains in good shape ahead of next week's presidential election, a monthly tally of workforce reduction announcements showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-planned-layoffs-drop-again-october-recruitment-firm-challenger-says-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDVRHWDNIFNSVBJZOX6PT3Q5KE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟监管机构表示，英伟达拟收购人工智能初创公司 Run:ai 需要获得欧盟批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周四表示，美国芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）拟收购人工智能初创公司Run:ai的交易必须获得欧盟反垄断监管机构的批准才能完成。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Nvidia's proposed acquisition of AI startup Run:ai will have to be approved by EU antitrust regulators before the deal can be completed, the European Commission said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nvidias-proposed-buy-ai-startup-runai-requires-eu-approval-eu-regulators-say-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD7QOQCZT5KQTMRX3JESLESQGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:37:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton 聘请前苹果公司高管 Peter Stern 担任首席执行官，指导扭亏为盈工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[健身器材制造商 Peloton Interactive 周四表示，已任命苹果公司前高管彼得-斯特恩（Peter Stern）为公司首席执行官兼总裁，自 1 月 1 日起生效，以指导公司在经历大流行后的需求下滑后的扭亏为盈工作。【原文：Peloton Interactive has appointed former Apple executive Peter Stern as its CEO and president effective Jan. 1, the fitness-equipment maker said on Thursday, to steer its turnaround efforts after a post-pandemic slump in demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/peloton-names-former-apple-executive-peter-stern-ceo-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NEH3SIVPYNNLFE6QJPCOEK7VOI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:31:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于湿疹治疗和眼科药物的需求，Regeneron 业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受湿疹治疗药物 Dupixent 和大片眼病药物 Eylea 的强劲需求推动，美国制药商 Regeneron Pharmaceuticals 周四公布的第三季度利润和收入均超出华尔街预期。【原文：U.S. drugmaker Regeneron Pharmaceuticals beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter profit and revenue on Thursday, driven by strong demand for its eczema treatment Dupixent and blockbuster eye disease drug Eylea.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/regeneron-beats-results-estimates-demand-eczema-treatment-eye-drug-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VFU3IOV4FNR5FA3VFGSQBGUVY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[炼油厂 PBF Energy 第三季度亏损超预期，利润率大幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于燃料需求疲软导致炼油利润缩水，美国炼油商遭受重创，PBF 能源公司周四公布的第三季度亏损超过预期。【原文：PBF Energy posted a bigger-than-expected third-quarter loss on Thursday as the U.S. refiner took a hit from weak fuel demand which shrunk refining margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/refiner-pbf-energy-posts-bigger-than-expected-q3-loss-margins-collapse-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EN6WTROGU5KQPDOBRC2YXLN534</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受惠于老药销售，百时美施贵宝第三季度盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[布里斯托尔-迈尔斯-施贵宝公司周四公布的第三季度财报好于预期，原因是血液稀释剂 Eliquis 和癌症治疗药物 Revlimid 等老牌药物以及心脏治疗药物 Camzyos 和癌细胞治疗药物 Breyanzi 等新药销售强劲。【原文：Bristol Myers Squibb posted better-than-expected third-quarter earnings on Thursday citing strong sales of established drugs like blood thinner Eliquis and cancer treatment Revlimid as well as newer drugs like heart treatment Camzyos and cancer cell therapy Breyanzi.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bristol-myers-q3-earnings-beat-expectations-helped-by-sales-older-drugs-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKDV46K57RONTOTRIHMWWOEMRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:19:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康菲石油公司第三季度利润增长，原因是产量增加，并提高了股票回购比例]]></title><description><![CDATA[康菲石油公司（ConocoPhillips）周四的第三季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，这家总部位于得克萨斯州的石油和天然气生产商从产量增加中获益，使其股价在盘前交易中上涨 2.6%，报 105.5 美元。【原文：ConocoPhillips exceeded Wall Street's third-quarter profit estimates on Thursday as the Texas-based oil and gas producer reaped the benefits of higher production, sending its shares rising 2.6% at $105.5 in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/conocophillips-quarterly-profit-beats-estimates-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4JTNDJLM5PLXLQ2A2QADZROQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康卡斯特因奥运广告和大片上映而收入超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[康卡斯特周四公布的第三季度营收超出预期，主要得益于其制片厂的强劲票房表现、2024 年巴黎奥运会期间广告销售额的增长以及宽带用户下降幅度低于预期。【原文：Comcast beat third-quarter revenue estimates on Thursday, driven by strong box office performance for its studio, higher ad sales during the 2024 Paris Olympics and a smaller-than-expected decline in broadband subscribers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/comcast-tops-revenue-expectations-olympics-ad-boost-blockbuster-releases-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PIQLPG64FN7PLDJEMKGK4V2UQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步总预订量增长放缓，股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步（Uber Technologies）的总预订量以一年多来最慢的速度增长，这表明乘客正在选择价格较低的公共交通而不是出租车，导致其股价在盘前交易中下跌超过 6%。【原文：Uber Technologies's gross bookings grew at its slowest pace in over a year in a sign that riders were opting for less expensive public transportation over taxis, sending its shares down more than 6% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-beats-third-quarter-profit-estimates-gross-bookings-growth-slows-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLXAFUXEO5IZRLGFFIKS4EJ4OE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波尔公司公布第三季度利润超预期，原因是价格上涨、成本降低]]></title><description><![CDATA[铝包装生产商波尔公司（Ball Corp）周四公布的第三季度利润超出预期，原因是消费者和装瓶商寻求更可持续的选择，饮料容器价格上涨。【原文：Aluminum packaging maker Ball Corp beat estimates for third quarter profit on Thursday buoyed by higher prices for its beverage containers as consumers and bottlers seek more sustainable options.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ball-corp-reports-third-quarter-profit-beat-higher-prices-lower-costs-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLZFWU4BYFI5HHSBKYFCU7M5UA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求改善，Mobileye 第三季度收入超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动驾驶技术公司 Mobileye Global 周四公布的季度营收超出华尔街预期，原因是中国汽车销量反弹导致对其驾驶辅助芯片的需求增加。【原文：Self-driving tech firm Mobileye Global topped Wall Street expectations for quarterly revenue on Thursday as a rebound in car sales in China led to improved demand for its driver-assistance chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/mobileye-tops-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HKJLG3GXRN7BCQTBUTL5UB7Y4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉扎德（Lazard）投资银行因交易复苏而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[受整个行业交易复苏的推动，投资银行拉扎德（Lazard）第三季度利润激增。【原文：Investment bank Lazard's profit surged in the third quarter, driven by an industry-wide recovery in dealmaking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investment-bank-lazards-profit-surges-dealmaking-recovery-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4Y3477Q3JKKJGH4U2HGRKM2DY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛撤销年度预测，削减股息]]></title><description><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛（Estee Lauder）周四下调了2025年的销售和利润预期，因为这家MAC口红生产商正努力应对中国等大市场对奢侈美容产品的需求疲软。【原文：Estee Lauder pulled back its 2025 sales and profit forecasts on Thursday, as the MAC lipstick maker struggles with weak demand for luxury beauty products in big markets such as China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/estee-lauder-withdraws-annual-forecasts-slowing-china-sales-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2UVV5GHMBJPJJWFH6WURXEYXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:37:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克第三季度业绩好于预期，但加卫苗在中国的销量再次下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司（Merck &amp; Co）周四公布了高于预期的第三季度财报，原因是其癌症治疗大片 Keytruda 的销售强劲，但这家美国制药商也指出，中国市场对其加卫苗（Gardasil）的需求连续第二个季度疲软。【原文：Merck &amp; Co posted higher-than-expected third-quarter earnings on Thursday on strong sales of its blockbuster cancer treatment Keytruda, but the U.S. drugmaker also flagged a second straight quarter of weak demand for its Gardasil vaccine in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-third-quarter-better-than-expected-gardasil-sales-sag-china-again-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCDNOFD7UZN2PEP4V6B3W55Y4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大型企业受惊，全球债券岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKTDA2TUMZIW3CJYWPMEHKLDA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券监察机构日益头疼的法律问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国行业和其他团体提起诉讼，要求推翻证券交易委员会（SEC）主席加里-根斯勒（Gary Gensler）通过的规则，并对其议程上的其他规则产生了连锁影响。以下是根据法律文件、美国证券交易委员会议程和法律专家提供的受影响规则和行动清单。【原文：U.S. industry and other groups have sued to overturn rules adopted under Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler, with knock-on implications for others on his agenda. Here's a list of rules and actions affected, according to legal filings, the SEC's agenda, and legal experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-securities-watchdogs-mounting-legal-headaches-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55ANGK3PTRPU7A7AZPYQYDCAL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于药房福利管理部门的强劲表现，Cigna 季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cigna 周四公布的第三季度利润超出华尔街预期，原因是其负责药房福利管理业务的部门增加了新客户，而且对一种关节炎特效药的近似复制品需求强劲。【原文：Cigna beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter profit on Thursday, as its unit that runs the pharmacy benefit management business added new clients and saw strong demand for close copies of a blockbuster arthritis drug.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cigna-tops-quarterly-profit-estimates-strength-pharmacy-benefit-management-unit-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5RAFQPTL5ZLLVCMMNYDZDWYZRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特木考虑加入欧洲反假冒集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份会议议程，中国在线零售商特姆优正在考虑加入一个由电子商务平台和品牌组成的团体，共同合作防止假冒产品在欧洲的在线销售。【原文：Chinese online retailer Temu is considering joining a group of ecommerce platforms and brands that collaborate to prevent the sale of fake products online in Europe, according to a meeting agenda seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/temu-considers-joining-european-anti-counterfeit-group-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VG5NIYCJERIUPPDPXREFTEQ3M4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在环境、社会和公司治理的逆流中，企业加强社会和气候报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的数据显示，即使面临保守派政客的持续压力，许多美国公司近年来仍加强了对环境和社会事务的报告。【原文：Many U.S. companies have stepped up reporting on environmental and social matters in recent years even with sustained pressure from conservative politicians, data reviewed by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/companies-boost-social-climate-reporting-amid-esg-backlash-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAMVIJK23VLNPASNTTVD7SAMNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第三季度业绩受增长影响，Robinhood 股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood Markets 的股价在今年翻了一番多之后，在周四开盘前下跌了近 11%，原因是旨在吸引客户资产的激励措施损害了第三季度的业绩。【原文：Shares of Robinhood Markets fell nearly 11% before the market open on Thursday after more than doubling in value this year, as incentives aimed to attract customer assets hurt third-quarter results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/robinhood-shares-drop-growth-push-takes-toll-q3-results-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6DFBYB3ANL7HEMPFY7L6FRRT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赫斯交易受阻，雪佛龙首席执行官面临股价止跌压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[五年前，雪佛龙首席执行官迈克尔-沃思（Michael Wirth）在拒绝与西方石油公司（Occidental Petroleum）就竞争对手展开竞购战后，这家美国第二大石油公司的市值短暂超过了埃克森美孚，赢得了华尔街的赞誉。【原文：Five years ago, Chevron CEO Michael Wirth won Wall Street acclaim as the No. 2 U.S. oil company briefly achieved a market value larger than Exxon Mobil's after he refused to get into a bidding war with Occidental Petroleum over a rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-ceo-under-pressure-halt-share-slide-hess-deal-stalls-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYCOBNIJDNPY3PM2I22WE7D3PE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[无论谁赢得白宫，美国加密产业都期待华盛顿更加友好]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币行业多年来一直在监管问题上与民主党总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）的政府发生冲突，但高管们预计，无论下周谁赢得白宫，华盛顿都会给加密货币行业带来更多便利。【原文：The cryptocurrency industry has spent years clashing with Democratic President Joe Biden's administration over regulatory issues, but executives expect an easier ride from Washington, regardless of who wins the White House next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-crypto-industry-expects-friendlier-washington-whoever-wins-white-house-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORFW6UGSXVN7TMIL7LXOSTQPT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关键的大选年，法律攻击正在延缓美国证券交易委员会的规则制定工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[在乔-拜登总统执政初期，美国证券交易委员会的规则制定速度曾创下历史新高，但随着该机构在充满敌意的新法律环境中摸爬滚打，制定速度已明显放缓。【原文：Rulemaking at the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, which hit a record pace early in President Joe Biden's administration, has slowed significantly as the agency navigates a hostile new legal climate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legal-attacks-are-slowing-sec-rulemaking-crucial-election-year-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTNCQZGQPBNU7DDWPJRMNVXW44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司承诺投资摩洛哥航空航天业]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩洛哥工业部周三晚些时候表示，巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）已与摩洛哥签署了一项初步协议，将投资摩洛哥的民用和国防航空航天领域，包括建立一家维护和修理厂。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer has signed a preliminary deal with Morocco to invest in the nation's civilian and defence aerospace sector, including setting up a maintenance and repair plant, Morocco's industry ministry said late on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-pledges-investment-moroccos-aerospace-sector-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YTXAF6PRFNATIMNIYLBE2574I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:53:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta、微软成本警告凸显人工智能贸易风险，期货价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街期货周四大幅下跌，原因是 Meta Platforms 公司和微软公司就人工智能相关成本上升发出的警告，抑制了市场对巨型企业的乐观情绪，而巨型企业一直是今年市场的主要推动力。【原文：Wall Street futures fell sharply on Thursday, as warnings from Meta Platforms and Microsoft about rising artificial intelligence-related costs dampened optimism around megacaps, which have been the market's primary driver this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-tumble-meta-microsoft-cost-warnings-highlight-ai-trade-risks-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2DKGGTEZGZJPHOEIBMBEVIIE4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:48:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[明年全球经济将稳健增长 3%：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对大约 500 位经济学家进行的一项调查显示，随着主要央行在美国经济强劲的背景下实施一系列降息措施，明年全球经济增长将保持强劲步伐。【原文：Global economic growth will maintain its robust pace next year as major central banks implement a series of interest rate cuts against the backdrop of a strong U.S. economy, according to a Reuters poll of around 500 economists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-market-data/global-economy-set-cruise-solid-3-growth-rate-next-year-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URKO77XDWZP3JILWY7LA5AIOFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乘着经济增长的东风，大多数亚洲国家央行的降息步伐将慢于美联储：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的民意调查显示，大多数亚洲国家央行未来一年的降息速度将慢于美国联邦储备委员会，原因是稳健的经济增长缓解了维持货币稳定以对抗美元持续走强的压力。【原文：Most Asian central banks will cut interest rates slower than the U.S. Federal Reserve over the coming year, Reuters polls showed, as solid growth has eased pressure to maintain currency stability against a persistently strong dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/riding-growth-wave-most-asian-central-banks-go-slower-than-fed-rate-cuts-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MO5E5AD25M53ID7G4C2446J3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国计划为纽约半导体研发机构投资 8.25 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周四宣布投资 8.25 亿美元，在纽约州奥尔巴尼新建一座半导体研发设施，旨在促进高科技制造业的发展，减少对外国技术的依赖。【原文：The Biden administration on Thursday announced an $825 million investment in a new semiconductor research and development facility in Albany, New York, aiming to boost high-tech manufacturing and reduce reliance on foreign technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/biden-administration-selects-new-york-semiconductor-rd-facility-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2DIGNE3UVK7TOHFO5GWQY4ZME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>