<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:11:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:11:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[倍耐力中意股东就公司治理问题发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，倍耐力的中国股东和意大利股东在集团治理问题上意见不一，可能导致这家轮胎制造商无法在定于周三召开的董事会上批准其2024年的财务业绩。【原文：Chinese and Italian shareholders in Pirelli are at odds over the group's governance, two sources said, potentially leading to a failure to approve the tyremaker's financial results for 2024 at a board meeting scheduled for Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/pirellis-italian-chinese-shareholders-clash-over-governance-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCLQU4NVXJLE3AASSSL6NFBA3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒商品通胀上升 "无济于事]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周二表示，美联储的利率政策仍然是限制性的，而且定位良好，但自去年夏天以来，将通胀率拉回到央行2%目标的进展已经放缓，最新数据中出现的商品通胀上扬 "于事无补"。【原文：Federal Reserve interest rate policy remains restrictive and well-positioned, Fed Governor Adriana Kugler said on Tuesday, but progress on bringing inflation back to the central bank's 2% target has slowed since last summer and the uptick in goods inflation seen in the latest data is "unhelpful."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-uptick-goods-inflation-unhelpful-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6JLK54TENNATCHTPSHHUPPNFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:44:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，激进投资者 Keith Meister 将加入 Illumina 董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周二援引知情人士的话报道，激进投资者基思-梅斯特（Keith Meister）将加入基因测序制造商 Illumina 董事会，现任董事会成员斯科特-戈特利布（Scott Gottlieb）将出任董事长。【原文：Activist investor Keith Meister will join the board of gene-sequencing maker Illumina , and current board member Scott Gottlieb will become chairman, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/activist-investor-keith-meister-join-illuminas-board-wsj-reports-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7EMBVQRA5OB7OMCZV7XOGWZ5A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:18:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于特朗普助手用于分享战争计划的 Signal 消息应用程序的须知]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府的高级官员使用消息应用程序 Signal 分享战争计划，并错误地将一名记者纳入了加密聊天，这引发了民主党议员要求国会调查这一安全漏洞的呼声。【原文：Top Trump administration officials used messaging app Signal to share war plans and mistakenly included a journalist in the encrypted chat, spurring calls by Democratic lawmakers for a congressional investigation into the security breach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/what-know-about-signal-messaging-app-used-by-trump-aides-share-war-plans-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BBRIZMIC5NVJLS2FAFO3EFSIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:14:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[物流公司 Kuehne+Nagel 将从全球贸易战的复杂性中获利]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士物流集团 Kuehne und Nagel 周二表示，该公司一直在利用日益复杂的全球贸易问题--从美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税到红海危机--向客户收取更高的增值服务费。【原文：Swiss logistics group Kuehne und Nagel on Tuesday said it has been capitalizing on increasingly complex global trade issues - from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs to the Red Sea crisis - by charging customers more for value-added services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/logistics-firm-kuehnenagel-profit-complexities-around-global-trade-war-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCKGKAVSA5PJNJQPHDYETEYCRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调味品制造商麦考密克因支出增加，季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦考密克周二公布的第一季度利润未达预期，原因是促销费用增加以及香料、调味汁和调味品降价未能刺激需求。【原文：McCormick missed first-quarter profit estimates on Tuesday, as higher promotional expenses and price cuts for its spices, sauces and seasonings fell short of boosting demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spice-maker-mccormick-misses-quarterly-profit-estimates-higher-expenses-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXU7KTWEVRIJVKJG43UMAESJVM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调味品制造商麦考密克因支出增加，季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦考密克周二公布的第一季度利润未达预期，原因是促销费用增加以及香料、调味汁和调味品降价未能刺激需求。【原文：McCormick missed first-quarter profit estimates on Tuesday, as higher promotional expenses and price cuts for its spices, sauces and seasonings fell short of boosting demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spice-maker-mccormick-misses-quarterly-profit-estimates-higher-expenses-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXU7KTWEVRIJVKJG43UMAESJVM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国商务部长会见波音全球总裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部在一份声明中说，中国商务部长王文涛周二会见了波音全球总裁布兰登-尼尔森，并呼吁该飞机制造商深化与中国航空业的合作。【原文：China's Commerce Minister Wang Wentao met with President of Boeing Global Brendan Nelson on Tuesday, and called on the planemaker to deepen cooperation with China's aviation industry, the commerce ministry said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/chinas-commerce-minister-meets-with-boeing-global-president-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFFKBLUX7VMDJADIV4WVOW45W4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:34:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下达新命令后，委内瑞拉对华石油贸易陷入停滞]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国针对中国从伊朗进口石油实施制裁几天后，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令威胁对从加拉加斯购买石油的国家征收关税，从而带来了新的不确定性。【原文：Trade of Venezuelan oil to top buyer China stalled on Tuesday after U.S. President Donald Trump's order threatening tariffs on countries buying from Caracas created fresh uncertainty, days after U.S. sanctions targeting China's imports from Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trade-venezuelan-oil-china-stalls-after-new-trump-order-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVDUYMURXRJLHDZU5QXVQESR2E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:30:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称欧盟将结束对苹果浏览器选项的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的人士周二表示，在苹果公司做出修改以符合里程碑式的规定之后，欧盟反垄断监管机构将结束对苹果公司 iPhone 浏览器选项长达一年的调查。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are set to close their year-long investigation into Apple's browser options on iPhones after the company made changes to comply with the requirements set out in landmark rules, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-set-close-investigation-into-apples-browser-options-sources-say-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CHVIWKNXNPDHPYO4SNC6W5YGQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标信心游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAFZ3NULX5IVLKNHGCGZTYB4YU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔任命大卫-斯威尔（David Sewell）领导先进材料部门，为分拆上市做准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔周二表示，已任命大卫-斯威尔（David Sewell）领导其先进材料业务，该业务将于今年年底或 2026 年初分拆为一家独立的上市公司。【原文：Honeywell said on Tuesday it has appointed David Sewell to lead its advanced materials business, which is set to be spun off into an independently listed company by late this year or early 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/honeywell-appoints-david-sewell-lead-advanced-materials-unit-ahead-spin-off-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZMFNHZGWFPQNNRDEYP4ALK544</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下 Waymo 公司计划于 2026 年在华盛顿特区推出自动驾驶汽车。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 的自动驾驶部门 Waymo 周二表示，它的目标是明年在美国首都推出完全自动驾驶的打车服务。【原文：Alphabet's self-driving unit Waymo said on Tuesday it aims to launch its fully autonomous ride-hailing service in the U.S. capital city next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alphabets-waymo-aims-2026-self-driving-ride-hailing-launch-washington-dc-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6XA3U4MKVJWTBLZ7QFQMUJA2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克在最新中国交易中购买心脏病药物的权利]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司与江苏恒瑞医药集团签署了一项价值高达 20 亿美元的心脏病药物许可协议，这是美国制药商最近与中国企业签署的一系列交易中的最新一笔。【原文：Merck has signed a licensing agreement for a heart disease drug with Jiangsu Hengrui Pharmaceuticals worth up to $2 billion, the latest in a series of deals U.S. drugmakers have recently signed with China-based firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-signs-deal-with-jiangsu-hengrui-worth-up-2-billion-access-heart-drug-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2BK4Y7H2JMXVBAFMY2N3ISBN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:59:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[同步银行：美国消费者因通胀而放缓支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[消费金融公司 Synchrony Financial 的数据显示，由于物价高企和经济前景恶化，美国消费者开始抑制消费。【原文：U.S. consumers are starting to curb their spending in response to high prices and a worsening economic outlook, according to consumer finance company Synchrony Financial .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumers-slow-spending-inflation-bites-synchrony-says-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPTBG6276VNEPKBB7PTWYRGZPI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普主导的反弹势头减弱，华尔街期货下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周二下跌，此前一天，华尔街股指因特朗普政府可能对关税采取较温和态度的暗示而飙升至两周高点。【原文：U.S. stock index futures dipped on Tuesday, a day after Wall Street indexes surged to two-week highs on hints that the Trump administration might adopt a softer approach to tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-futures-slip-trump-led-rally-loses-steam-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBM54SIR6FIABOUMIUETRQY2LU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:23:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空航天集团警告说，新关税可能会提高发动机维修和零部件成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[据加拿大航空航天贸易团体称，随着美国主导的新一轮贸易战迫在眉睫，美国关税升级和加拿大报复性关税可能会提高从飞机零部件到发动机维修等项目的成本。【原文：Escalating U.S. tariffs and Canadian retaliatory duties could raise costs on items from aircraft components to engine repairs, according to aerospace trade groups in Canada, as a fresh round of the U.S.-led trade war looms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/canadian-aerospace-groups-warn-fresh-tariffs-could-raise-costs-engine-repairs-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDDNRDSYINIVPNT3CKYMW46R6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国国家安全审查拖延，Cerebras IPO 进一步推迟]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位熟悉内情的消息人士称，Cerebras Systems 公司的高管们希望特朗普政府能通过国家安全审查，因为这项审查已让这家人工智能芯片制造商的首次公开募股（IPO）陷入了数月的僵局。【原文：Cerebras Systems executives were hoping the Trump administration would wave through a national security review that has left the AI chipmaker's IPO in limbo for months, five sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cerebras-ipo-further-delayed-us-national-security-review-drags-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDH5Y53MJBK7LBG3KS4IJVWG3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债券投资者在近期国债收益率下跌中权衡 "凸性 "风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近美国收益率的下降引起了人们的猜测，认为抵押贷款投资组合经理和保险公司购买国债和名为利率掉期的衍生产品的浪潮是导致收益率下降的部分原因。【原文：The recent drop in U.S. yields has raised speculation that a wave of buying of Treasury securities and derivative products called interest rate swaps by mortgage portfolio managers and insurance companies was partly responsible for their decline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/us-bond-investors-weigh-convexity-risk-recent-treasury-yield-decline-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GRJ4ELH4ZPBLHB7VBWK6QBXIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:04:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对于马斯克的 "星链"（Starlink）来说，印度的批准可以打开新兴市场的大门]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析人士称，随着星链公司在印度的卫星宽带服务即将获得监管部门的批准，在印度的胜利将为该公司进入更多新兴市场铺平道路，并推动该公司实现每年新增一百万用户的雄心壮志。【原文：As Starlink nears regulatory approval in India for satellite broadband services, analysts say a victory there could pave a road into more emerging markets and boost the company's ambitions to add a million subscribers every year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/musks-starlink-india-approval-could-unlock-emerging-markets-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OW3KEYV4DZONTPVIRJCRLPXIFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国经济将出现滞胀，但不会重蹈 70 年代的覆辙]]></title><description><![CDATA[用一位经济学家的话说，美联储官员最近的经济预测有 "轻滞胀 "的影子，其他美国经济和央行观察家也越来越认同这种看法，他们怀疑美国在大流行病期间的优异表现是否即将滑坡。【原文：Recent economic projections from Federal Reserve officials had shades of "Stagflation-lite," in the words of one economist, a sentiment increasingly echoed among other observers of the U.S. economy and central bank wondering if the country's outperformance during the pandemic is about to slide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/stagflation-radar-us-economy-no-repeat-70s-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U42HG2RMPVMD7JOWB5D3OXELCY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳航首席执行官称 "日出项目 "航班将于 2027 年启动]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚澳航（Qantas）首席执行官瓦内萨-哈德森（Vanessa Hudson）周二表示，在明年年底接收首批12架专用空客A350-1000飞机后，澳航将于2027年初启动 "日出计划 "超远程航班。【原文：Australia's Qantas will start Project Sunrise ultra-long-haul flights in early 2027 after receiving the first of 12 dedicated Airbus A350-1000 aircraft at the end of next year, Chief Executive Vanessa Hudson said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/qantas-ceo-says-project-sunrise-flights-start-2027-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ILE5LRUEDRL7RLUE5C3VQFF4CI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[史密斯菲尔德食品公司预计销售额和利润将因包装肉类需求强劲而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[史密斯菲尔德食品公司（Smithfield Foods）周二预测，受杂货店对其包装肉类的强劲需求以及成本削减措施带来的好处的帮助，该公司的年销售额和调整后营业利润将实现增长。【原文：Smithfield Foods forecast growth in annual sales and adjusted operating profit on Tuesday, helped by strong demand for its packaged meats at grocery stores and benefits from its cost-cutting measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/smithfield-foods-expects-growth-sales-profit-strong-packaged-meats-demand-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHHWFHHBTNMKBJ5I5EOOBDMXOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，波音公司和诺斯罗普-格鲁曼公司本周等待美国海军下一代战斗机合同的签订]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士称，美国海军预计将于本周宣布谁将建造其下一代航母隐形战斗机--该项目在其生命周期内价值数千亿美元，是对抗中国计划的关键部分。【原文：The U.S. Navy is expected to announce this week who will build its next-generation carrier-based stealth fighter - a program worth hundreds of billions over its lifetime and a key part of plans to confront China, people familiar with the decision said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-northrop-grumman-await-us-navy-next-generation-fighter-contract-this-week-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RVEWQY23EBNONK52WCGKDCBBJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：印度向三星提出 6.01 亿美元的电信进口征税要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项政府命令显示，印度已责令三星及其在该国的高管补缴 6.01 亿美元的税款和罚款，原因是他们在进口关键电信设备时逃避关税，这是近年来最大的此类要求之一。【原文：India has ordered Samsung and its executives in the country to pay $601 million in back taxes and penalties for dodging tariffs on import of key telecoms equipment, a government order showed, for one of the biggest such demands in recent years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-slaps-samsung-with-tax-demand-601-million-telecom-imports-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7P4KEO2M4VKA3MQADTN2HKFZVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德在欧洲推出首个比特币产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德（BlackRock）在欧洲推出了首款比特币交易所交易产品，以满足新市场对加密货币日益增长的需求，此前贝莱德已在美国为类似产品吸引了超过 500 亿美元的资金。【原文：BlackRock has launched its first bitcoin exchange-traded product in Europe, in a bid to tap growing demand for cryptocurrency exposure in new markets after attracting more than $50 billion into similar products in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/blackrock-launches-first-bitcoin-product-europe-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLE5Q24X3NISZLWWML6DXSOWFE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:43:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 DeepSeek 发布人工智能模型升级版，加剧与 OpenAI 的竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创公司 DeepSeek 发布了其 V3 大型语言模型的重大升级版，加剧了与 OpenAI 和 Anthropic 等美国技术领导者的竞争。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence startup DeepSeek released a major upgrade to its V3 large language model, intensifying competition with U.S. tech leaders like OpenAI and Anthropic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinas-deepseek-releases-ai-model-upgrade-intensifies-rivalry-with-openai-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJQE2FF4JZKRVKUBSNZZH3SIXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乐天卡瞄准 1,100 万亿日元利润，着眼于 1,100 万亿日元的 B2B 市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大的信用卡公司乐天卡公司（Rakuten Card）的新任首席执行官表示，该公司的目标是在中期内将其年度营业利润几乎翻一番，达到 1000 亿日元（6.637 亿美元），并在很大程度上尚未开发的企业对企业支付市场中寻找机会。【原文：Japan's largest credit card company, Rakuten Card, is aiming to almost double its annual operating profit to 100 billion yen ($663.7 million) in the medium term and sees opportunity in expanding into the largely untapped business-to-business payments market, its new chief executive officer said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rakuten-card-aiming-100-billion-yen-profit-eyes-1100-trillion-yen-b2b-market-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KV5DPEEZVL57H35UH7WLLTUCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众将与法雷奥、Mobileye 合作开发驾驶辅助系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车周二表示，将与汽车零部件供应商法雷奥和 Mobileye 合作，为其汽车开发更好的驾驶辅助系统。【原文：Volkswagen said on Tuesday it would collaborate with automotive parts suppliers Valeo and Mobileye to develop better driver assistance systems for its cars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-work-with-valeo-mobileye-driver-assistance-systems-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWXNLIBWNJNPLJBJTBXE3724RU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻独家：印度希望削减 230 亿美元美国进口商品关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位政府消息人士称，印度愿意在两国正在谈判的贸易协议的第一阶段削减价值 230 亿美元的一半以上美国进口商品的关税。【原文：India is open to cutting tariffs on more than half of U.S. imports worth $23 billion in the first phase of a trade deal the two nations are negotiating, two government sources said, the biggest cut in years, aimed at fending off reciprocal tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-eyes-tariff-cut-23-bln-us-imports-shield-66-bln-exports-sources-say-2025-03-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIY4WRGG35MZJGASX4INXD7LYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:53:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>