<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:05:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:05:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空破产威胁小镇航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）因一年内第二次破产而削减或取消阿诺德帕尔默地区机场的服务，宾夕法尼亚州拉特罗布（Latrobe）的居民可能很快就不得不驱车 65 英里前往匹兹堡，才能飞到任何地方。【原文：If Spirit Airlines slashes or eliminates service at Arnold Palmer Regional Airport due to the carrier's second bankruptcy in a year, residents of Latrobe, Pennsylvania, may soon have to drive 65 miles to Pittsburgh if they need to fly anywhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spirit-airlines-bankruptcy-threatens-small-towns-flights-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKFHNRWYKVLRFIF4ZCVB5VFLPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达斥资 1000 亿美元打造 OpenAI 引发重大反垄断问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家称，主导人工智能芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）与领先的人工智能公司 OpenAI 之间价值 1000 亿美元的合作关系，可能会使两家公司获得对竞争对手不公平的优势。【原文：The $100 billion partnership between dominant AI chipmaker Nvidia and leading artificial intelligence company OpenAI could give both companies an unfair advantage over their competitors, experts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/nvidias-100-billion-openai-play-raises-big-antitrust-issues-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5M6VPTG4OBPDDI5O74ZEX7X5NY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，J&J 将从非美国市场撤出胃酸倒流设备]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二援引强生公司发给医生的一封信报道，强生公司将从美国以外的市场撤回一种治疗胃酸倒流疾病的设备。【原文：Johnson & Johnson will withdraw a device to treat acid reflux disease from markets outside the U.S., Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a company letter sent to doctors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/jj-withdraw-acid-reflux-device-non-us-markets-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KV7KUHGVSFORRMZMF5NOMKKFSI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国监管机构就违规内容传唤字节跳动和阿里巴巴旗下平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国网络空间管理局周二表示，中国网络空间监管机构传唤了字节跳动旗下新闻平台头条号和阿里巴巴旗下互联网浏览器运营商 UCWeb，原因是内容违规。【原文：China's cyberspace regulator summoned ByteDance's news platform Toutiao and Alibaba's internet browser operator UCWeb over content violations, the Cyberspace Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-regulator-summons-bytedance-alibabas-platforms-over-content-violations-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LLKKN6CDRKG7FTJ4KGLD6MJ3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:27:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济合作与发展组织（OECD）称美国关税冲击尚未全面爆发，经济增长尚可维持]]></title><description><![CDATA[经合组织（OECD）周二表示，全球经济增长好于预期，但美国进口关税冲击的全部影响仍未显现，因为人工智能投资暂时支撑了美国的经济活动，财政支持也缓解了中国的经济放缓。【原文：Global growth is holding up better than expected, but the full brunt of the U.S. import tariff shock is still to be felt as AI investment props up U.S. activity for now and fiscal support cushions China's slowdown, the OECD said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/oecd-says-full-brunt-us-tariff-shock-yet-come-growth-holds-up-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UGMCQAWLRODRMOPJEAZANKOSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部对阿根廷的支持暂时为比索和米莱提供了友好的支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）承诺采取 "大规模、强有力 "的行动，利用有 91 年历史的美国危机基金来稳定阿根廷摇摆不定的货币，这可能会帮助比索站稳脚跟，至少暂时如此。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent's pledge of "large and forceful" actions to stabilize Argentina's wobbling currency by using a 91-year-old U.S. crisis fund could help the peso find its footing, at least for a while.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-treasurys-support-argentina-gives-peso-milei-friendly-leg-up-now-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RU6EDZQXDRKP5CWEJOTQI3HAKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:03:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 DHL 从周四起恢复飞往美国的商业包裹服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国敦豪快递公司（DHL）将从本周四起恢复向美国运送企业标准包裹的服务，这是该公司因美国即将对低价值包裹征收关税而暂停这项服务约四周后的又一举措。【原文：Germany's DHL will resume the shipment of standard parcels for businesses to the United States from Thursday, roughly four weeks after suspending the service over looming U.S. customs duties for low-value packages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/germanys-dhl-resume-us-bound-business-parcel-service-thursday-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HT6ETP23ZNWBPCEF7IUWRSD4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 08:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰诺制药商肯维股价反弹，特朗普的主张面临回击]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将泰诺（Tylenol）生产商肯维（Kenvue）的常用止痛药与怀孕期间的自闭症风险联系在一起，但肯维的股票在周二的欧洲交易中仍然上涨。【原文：Tylenol-maker Kenvue stock rose in European trading on Tuesday, even after U.S. President Donald Trump linked its popular pain medication to autism risk during pregnancy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/tylenol-maker-kenvue-shares-bounce-trump-claims-face-pushback-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3WRYX2OKNMWHBZKJUJJSMXQ7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 08:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国贸易特使会见美国中西部代表团，农业出口成为谈判重点]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周二表示，中国高级贸易谈判代表李成钢会见了美国中西部地区的政界和商界领袖，分析人士推测该地区的食品出口将是任何中美贸易协议的关键。【原文：Senior Chinese trade negotiator Li Chenggang met political and business leaders from the U.S. Midwest, the commerce ministry said on Tuesday, with analysts speculating the region's food exports will be key to any U.S.-China trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/china-trade-envoy-meets-us-midwest-delegation-agriculture-exports-loom-large-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RQ5J3DO4VKZBJVL3COON2HK7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国捷豹路虎因网络攻击停产四周]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国最大的汽车制造商捷豹路虎（JLR）在 9 月初遭到网络攻击后，将其工厂的关闭时间延长至 10 月 1 日，这次攻击导致其运营瘫痪，小型供应商也陷入困境。【原文：Britain's biggest car maker Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) is extending the closure of its factories until October 1 following a cyber attack in early September which has left its operations paralysed, and smaller suppliers struggling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uks-jaguar-land-rover-cyber-attack-shutdown-hit-four-weeks-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGIMFCXSCVL7TP7CAE7YWC5V3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官解除特朗普对 Revolution Wind 项目的禁令后，Orsted 股价大涨 12]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，在美国联邦法官裁定奥尔斯特可以恢复上个月被美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府叫停的已基本完工的革命风电项目后，奥尔斯特的股价最高上涨了12%。【原文：Shares in Orsted rose as much as 12% in early trade on Tuesday after a U.S. federal judge ruled that it can resume work on the almost completed Revolution Wind project halted by U.S. President Donald Trump's administration last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/orsted-shares-jump-12-after-us-judge-lifts-trump-ban-revolution-wind-project-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXULB56SVBJABDKVLEW65QSY4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国贸易协议到期对非洲经济意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[非洲官员和企业高管对与美国的一项重要免税贸易计划即将于 9 月底到期感到焦虑不安，而华盛顿方面却没有任何关于是否延长该计划的消息。【原文：African officials and business executives are fretting over the impending expiry of a crucial, duty-free trade programme with the United States at the end of September, without any word from Washington on whether it will be extended or not.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/what-does-expiry-us-trade-deal-mean-african-economies-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UI7IJISPVJM7BBQDTPHHIOSKKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国诺玛公司以 10 亿美元向美国公司出售水管理业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车和工业供应商 Norma 公司周二表示，将把利润丰厚的水管理业务出售给美国竞争对手 Advanced Drainage Systems 公司，交易价值 10 亿美元。【原文：German automotive and industrial supplier Norma will sell its lucrative water management business to U.S. rival Advanced Drainage Systems in a deal valued at $1 billion, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/advanced-drainage-systems-buy-norma-groups-water-management-business-1-billion-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3X7AW7R35ND3GXSTIUHAP55CU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:27:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Raspberry Pi 公司上半年盈利下降，但需求仍在增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[单板计算机制造商树莓派（Raspberry Pi）表示，其下半年开局良好，收益高于去年同期，需求也有所增长，但截至 6 月底的 6 个月调整后收益下降了 7%，为 1940 万美元。【原文：Raspberry Pi , the single-board computer maker, said its second half had started well, with earnings ahead of last year and demand strengthening as it reported a 7% drop in adjusted earnings to $19.4 million for the six months to end-June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uks-raspberry-pi-sees-demand-strengthening-after-first-half-earnings-drop-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5D5CFZ3LKFMO5DDYJBQUHYM6YY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASM 国际公司下调 2025 年下半年收入展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[计算机芯片设备制造商 ASM International 在本周二的投资者日之前下调了 2025 年下半年的收入目标。【原文：Computer chip equipment maker ASM International cut its revenue target for the second half of 2025, ahead of its investor day on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asm-international-cuts-h2-2025-revenue-outlook-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4MX3AFTQRNQHA5Q6XHOBA7524</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:23:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一些中国企业在经营困难的情况下假装按规定缴纳社会保险费]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一项具有里程碑意义的解释中，中国最高法院最近强化了雇主和工人之间为逃避社会保险缴费而采取的变通办法是无效的，此举既承诺为枯竭的养老金计划提供资金，又威胁到就业和企业。【原文：In a landmark interpretation, China's top court recently reinforced that workarounds between employers and workers to evade social insurance contributions are invalid, a move that both promises to fund depleted pension plans and threatens jobs and businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/some-chinese-firms-pretend-comply-with-mandated-social-insurance-payments-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVGBP34AMRIIZMNKAQEFAYW4FY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 06:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南首次公开募股市场和股市反弹未能激起外国投资者的兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[在股价上涨、监管变化和信贷激增的推动下，越南的首次公开募股（IPO）市场正在升温，但尽管指数提供商富时罗素（FTSE Russell）有望提升该市场的评级，却未能激起外国投资者的新兴趣。【原文：Vietnam's IPO market is heating up, fuelled by a share rally, regulatory changes and a credit splurge, but has failed to stir fresh interest from foreign investors despite the prospect that the market could be upgraded by index provider FTSE Russell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vietnams-ipo-market-stocks-rally-fail-stir-foreign-investors-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZRMIK7FRRM2VMC5STQ6U4FILI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 05:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，土耳其计划购买数百架波音客机和洛克希德-马丁战斗机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，土耳其总统塔伊普-埃尔多安（Tayyip Erdogan）计划购买数百架波音客机和洛克希德-马丁（Lockheed Martin）战斗机，并推动在该国生产这些飞机的部分零部件。【原文：Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan plans to buy hundreds of Boeing airliners and Lockheed Martin fighters and also push for some of their parts to be produced in the country, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/turkey-plans-buy-hundreds-boeing-airliners-lockheed-martin-fighters-bloomberg-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53CNWHGHMBIZTGATAOHITBDV3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 05:07:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星展银行支持的家庭办公室平台资产达到 7.8 亿美元，到 2026 年底将翻一番]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡最大银行星展集团（DBS Group）旗下的星展私人银行（DBS Private Bank）周二表示，其银行支持的多家族办公室平台在推出两年后管理的资产已达到10亿新元（7.8亿美元），并有望在2026年底达到20亿新元。【原文：DBS Private Bank, part of Singapore's biggest bank DBS Group , said on Tuesday its bank-backed multi-family office platform has reached S$1 billion ($780 million) in assets under management two years after launch and is on track to hit S$2 billion by end-2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dbsbacked-familyoffice-platform-hits-780-million-assets-double-by-end2026-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDMQCAVSIVJXPOYBCOC75OEFRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 05:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：亚洲创下新高，鲍威尔发表讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLDMNEZA5RMV3LTUBO5TPAXPSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 04:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员在访华期间大谈波音大交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国民主党众议员亚当-史密斯（Adam Smith）在周二举行的新闻发布会上说，一群罕见地访问北京的美国议员向中国最高领导人提出了一项协议，中国将承诺购买更多波音喷气式飞机。【原文：A group of U.S. lawmakers on a rare visit to Beijing raised a deal with top Chinese leaders which would see China commit to buy more Boeing jets, Adam Smith, a U.S. Democratic Representative, told a press conference on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-lawmakers-talk-up-big-boeing-deal-during-china-visit-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2G3OKX4ARBK2HOBLPQZZVDWKFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 04:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息称中国买家预订了至少 10 批阿根廷大豆货物]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位贸易商周二告诉路透社，中国买家已从阿根廷预订了至少10船大豆，在中美贸易紧张局势下利用低价为第四季度建立库存。【原文：Chinese buyers have booked at least 10 cargoes of soybeans from Argentina, three traders told Reuters on Tuesday, taking advantage of low prices to build inventories for the fourth quarter amid Sino-U.S. trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-buyers-book-least-10-argentine-soybean-cargoes-sources-say-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ5POCXT5VOWHNQCGADF2RJMUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 04:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国航空会议在网络攻击和地缘政治紧张局势的阴影下开幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二将在蒙特利尔召开全球航空业领袖会议，这次会议将面临高科技威胁、航班污染加剧和劳动力短缺等问题，因此需要妥善处理国际分歧。【原文：A global gathering of aviation leaders starting on Tuesday in Montreal will need to navigate international rifts as it confronts high tech threats, rising pollution from flights and labor shortages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/un-aviation-gathering-opens-under-shadow-cyberattacks-geopolitical-tensions-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5ZFP2HYO5LIHMO4STGH3G7OIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 04:05:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 在东京召开首次亚洲董事会，日本引领公司的地区增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于纽约的 KKR & Co 公司发言人周二表示，该公司本周将在东京召开其在亚洲的首次董事会，这凸显了日本对这家全球另类资产管理公司的重要性。【原文：New York-headquartered KKR & Co is holding its first board meeting in Asia this week in Tokyo, a spokesperson for the firm said on Tuesday, underscoring how important Japan has become for the global alternative asset manager.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kkr-holds-first-asia-board-meeting-tokyo-japan-leads-firms-regional-growth-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3OWHBQRXVKOHMJKDTPYBEHYEI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 03:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，中国要求经纪商暂停在香港的真实资产业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，中国证券监督管理局已建议一些本地券商暂停在香港开展真实资产（RWA）代币化业务，这表明中国政府对离岸数字资产市场蓬勃发展的担忧。【原文：China's securities watchdog has advised some local brokerages to pause their real-world asset (RWA) tokenisation business in Hong Kong, said two sources, signalling Beijing's concerns of a euphoric drive towards a booming digital assets market offshore.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/china-ask-brokers-pause-real-world-asset-business-hong-kong-sources-say-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBIVTKPOZJIH5COKMK4PVZC6GY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 03:37:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国总统称美国关税谈判令外汇市场担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统李在明办公室周二发表声明称，与美国就关税问题进行的谈判引发了外汇市场的担忧，但他相信双方将达成解决方案。【原文：South Korean President Lee Jae Myung said negotiations with the U.S. on tariffs have stirred concerns in the foreign exchange market but he was confident the two sides will reach a solution, a statement from Lee's office said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korean-president-says-us-tariffs-talks-worrying-fx-market-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VG6OWSBAQ5N3NK4KJYSLLSBCJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 03:28:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市受人工智能热潮提振，黄金再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市有望在近期大幅上涨的基础上再接再厉，因为对人工智能的乐观情绪吸引了大量资金流入科技行业，而对美国再次降息的押注则使黄金持续走热。【原文：Asian share markets looked to build on recent hefty gains on Tuesday as optimism around all things AI sucked money into the tech sector, while wagers on several more U.S. interest rate cuts kept gold on a hot streak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GO7HGLGYAZL5TIEFQ25PUU5PPQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 02:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，Celltrion 部门为礼来生产设施支付了 3.3 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Celltrion Inc. 周二在韩国提交的一份监管文件中称，其美国子公司以 3.3 亿美元的价格从美国礼来公司手中收购了 Imclone Systems LLC。【原文：Celltrion Inc. said in a regulatory filing in South Korea on Tuesday its U.S. subsidiary has acquired Imclone Systems LLC from Eli Lilly in the United States for $330 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/celltrion-unit-pays-330-million-eli-lilly-production-facility-filing-shows-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27J5QMBW6VMY3BREFROANJFLFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CFPB 提前数年结束对苹果和美国银行的监控]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据本月早些时候的法庭文件，消费者金融保护局取消了与苹果公司和 U.S. Bank (USBUB.UL) 的和解协议，这些协议是在前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）执政期间实施的，提前数年结束了监督要求。【原文：The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau has scraped settlements with Apple and U.S. Bank (USBUB.UL) that were implemented under former President Joe Biden's administration, ending oversight requirements years early, according to court filings dated earlier this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/cfpb-ends-monitoring-apple-us-bank-years-ahead-schedule-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2LNDIU32NME3I7RUKMSE325ME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:31:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储发言人成为焦点，美元暂停喘息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元在周二的亚洲早盘交易中继续承压，因为交易员们在分析美联储成员的言论，以寻找利率走势的线索。【原文：The U.S. dollar faced continued pressure in early trading in Asia on Tuesday as traders parsed comments by members of the Federal Reserve for clues on the path of interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-pauses-breath-with-fed-speakers-focus-2025-09-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6C2TTXRWVNBZCRLX2WIKSYOGE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>