<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:09:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:09:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行认为 2028 年初通胀仍未达到目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行周四发布的最新季度货币政策报告预计，2028 年第一季度的通胀率将在官方目标附近徘徊，但仍无法达到官方目标。【原文：Brazil's central bank projected on Thursday that inflation will hover near the official goal in the first quarter of 2028, but still fail to meet it, according to the bank's latest quarterly monetary policy report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-central-bank-sees-inflation-still-missing-target-early-2028-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPY2ES43DZLDNBYLLMV7NM5ASM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国石油公司将石油需求峰值预测从 2025 年推迟至 2030 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国石油公司（BP）周四表示，预计全球石油需求将增长到 2030 年，比一年前的预测晚五年，并强调提高能源效率的努力将放缓。【原文：BP said on Thursday it expects global oil demand to grow until 2030, five years later than its forecast a year ago, stressing slowed efforts to increase energy efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bp-postpones-oil-demand-peak-prediction-2030-2025-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72LNE4GBZBJR5PW6HU2TOHUUH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑莓上调年度收入预期，原因是软件支出恢复性增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大黑莓公司（BlackBerry）周四上调了 2026 财年的收入预期，原因是网络黑客攻击事件增多，对其网络安全软件的需求强劲。【原文：Canada's BlackBerry raised its fiscal 2026 revenue forecast on Thursday, banking on strong demand for its cybersecurity software amid a rise in online hacking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/blackberry-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-resilient-software-spending-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKNBQF6FHNOF3LRNSTPHYX4NKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:59:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其竞争管理机构对 Spotify 展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其竞争管理机构周四表示，已对 Spotify 展开调查，调查在线音乐流媒体市场可能存在的歧视性做法和掠夺性定价。【原文：Turkey's competition authority said on Thursday that it has launched an investigation into Spotify to look into possible discriminatory practices and predatory pricing in the online music streaming market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/turkish-competition-authority-launches-probe-into-spotify-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNS6PTXFZVJ2RKNC62YU46PR7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞安航空相信波音公司将按时交付首架 MAX 10 喷气机]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空集团首席执行官迈克尔-奥利里（Michael O'Leary）周四表示，在波音公司预计于2026年第三季度对飞机进行认证后，瑞安航空有信心在2027年初如期收到首批交付的737 MAX 10喷气机。【原文：Ryanair is confident of receiving its first delivery of 737 MAX 10 jets from Boeing on schedule in early 2027 after the expected certification of the planes by the third quarter of 2026, Group Chief Executive Michael O'Leary said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ryanair-confident-boeing-will-deliver-first-max-10-jets-time-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6OD5C4HVJIGROG2DBWCIXWVXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡塔尔财富基金与蓝猫头鹰合作，投资 30 亿美元推动数据中心发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡塔尔投资局（QIA）和另类资产管理公司蓝猫鹰资本（Blue Owl Capital）周四表示，双方已签署了一项合作协议，旨在启动一个规模达 30 亿美元、以数据中心为重点的全球数字基础设施平台。【原文：Qatar Investment Authority (QIA) and alternative asset manager Blue Owl Capital have signed a partnership aimed at launching a $3 billion global digital infrastructure platform focused on data centres, they said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/qatars-wealth-fund-teams-up-with-blue-owl-3-billion-data-centre-push-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2IZUXV6MBL2ZMWDBCL3GAEN4Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:27:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞安航空老板称无人机干扰不太可能影响盈利能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空公司老板迈克尔-奥利里（Michael O'Leary）周四表示，无人机对机场造成的干扰是一种刺激，但不太可能影响盈利能力。【原文：Disruption to airports caused by drones is an irritant but is unlikely to affect profitability, Ryanair boss Michael O'Leary said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/drone-disruption-unlikely-hit-profitability-ryanair-boss-says-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNT4SQFCPVIBTAL2NIH7MQ52PM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:14:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国赫尔辛公司推出 "欧罗巴 "作战无人机]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国防务初创企业赫尔辛公司（Helsing）周四发布了一款新型自主军用无人机，加入了一场制造遥控系统的竞赛，该系统可与其他无人机一起蜂拥作战，或与载人喷气式飞机联手，重塑未来空战。【原文：German defence startup Helsing unveiled a new autonomous military drone on Thursday, joining a race to build remote-piloted systems that can swarm into battle with other drones or team up with crewed jets to reshape the future of air combat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/germanys-helsing-unveils-europa-combat-drone-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RARYGNICYJM7DDTVYSPJH6Z5QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克将在最新重组中关闭业绩不佳的门店并裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克周四表示，公司已经批准了一项重组计划，将关闭北美地区表现不佳的咖啡馆，并裁减部分工作岗位，公司希望在首席执行官布莱恩-尼科尔（Brian Niccol）的领导下重振销售和利润。【原文：Starbucks said on Thursday it has approved a restructuring plan to close underperforming coffee houses in North America, and cut some jobs as the company looks to revive sales and profits under CEO Brian Niccol.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/starbucks-close-some-stores-part-restructuring-plan-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMJ24O4AABMQZP7NR2KLISRD74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片冷却初创公司 Corintis 募集 2400 万美元，英特尔首席执行官陈立武加入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士初创公司 Corintis 承诺提供更快速的液体芯片冷却技术，该公司已融资 2400 万美元，英特尔公司首席执行官陈立武也加入了公司董事会，因为人工智能推动了对更好的半导体热管理工具的需求。【原文：Corintis, a Swiss startup promising more rapid liquid chip-cooling technology, has raised $24 million and added Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan to its board as artificial intelligence fuels demand for better heat management tools for semiconductors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chip-cooling-startup-corintis-raises-24-million-adds-intel-ceo-lip-bu-tan-board-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNDVLBRDDNPIFNFV4BV6T2OMXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富达为散户投资者推出新交易平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[富达投资公司（Fidelity Investments）周四将对其交易平台进行重大升级，以满足自主个人投资者对新工具快速增长的需求。【原文：Fidelity Investments is rolling out a major upgrade to its trading platform on Thursday to meet the rapidly growing demand for new tools by self-directed individual investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/fidelity-launches-new-trading-platform-retail-investors-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAHOMLW7LVOAROJZX4OVOLJWUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外长称美挪就财富基金退出卡特彼勒的争执正在平息]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威外交大臣埃斯彭-巴特-艾德（Espen Barth Eide）表示，美国和挪威之间因北欧国家财富基金从美国建筑设备制造商卡特彼勒撤资而引发的争执似乎即将结束。【原文：A spat between the United States and Norway over the Nordic country's wealth fund's divestment from U.S. construction equipment-maker Caterpillar appears to be coming to an end, Norwegian Foreign Minister Espen Barth Eide said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-norway-spat-over-wealth-funds-caterpillar-exit-is-settling-foreign-minister-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNSOFOZNQNOU7BKH6NDWKUAMA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:55:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金流动 美国、亚洲投资者转向欧洲和中东对冲基金，美国银行调查显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四看到的一份美国银行调查显示，美国和亚洲的富裕投资者取消了今年将资金投入美国对冲基金的计划，同时增加了对欧洲和中东的投资。【原文：Wealthy investors in the United States and Asia have cancelled plans to put money into U.S. hedge funds this year, while increasing their exposure to Europe and the Middle East, according to a Bank of America survey seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hedge-flow-us-asian-investors-turn-european-mideast-hedge-funds-bofa-survey-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6ER7TTDKZNYZFQA326YEB64WU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：更多美联储言论，更多问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VYRBRAXZZOVHJKDQTOVTNKVKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃森哲第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃森哲周四公布的第四季度营收略高于华尔街预期，原因是企业客户对其人工智能驱动的咨询和服务的需求保持强劲。【原文：Accenture on Thursday reported fourth-quarter revenue slightly above Wall Street estimates, driven by resilient demand from enterprise clients for its AI-driven consulting and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/accenture-posts-fourth-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T32PLCOOJJJV7I44DNJO3UDOJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国政府关门如何影响金融市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着国会民主党和共和党在如何继续为联邦政府提供资金的问题上陷入僵局，美国政府下周开始部分停摆的风险正在上升。【原文：The risk of a partial U.S. government shutdown beginning next week is rising as congressional Democrats and Republicans hit an impasse over how to continue to fund the federal government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/how-us-government-shutdown-could-affect-financial-markets-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSVA4HMMT5L5BHOCC4LXQT4F6Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货持平，通胀数据公布前谨慎情绪升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国股指期货变化不大，表明在本周创纪录的涨势之后，投资者在等待新的催化剂来保持市场在这个异常强劲的九月的势头。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were little changed on Thursday, pointing to a pause after a record-breaking rally this week as investors awaited fresh catalysts to keep up the momentum in what has been an unusually strong September for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-flat-caution-builds-ahead-inflation-data-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5M6ZWEUQJLAFKJZZ4AXXU5B24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，关税可能会削弱美元的储备地位，但尚未扭转这一地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在 4 月份的 "解放日 "提出的大规模关税措施使美元作为世界锚定货币的地位岌岌可危，而新的经济研究得出结论认为，美国政府最终向更温和的税率妥协很可能使美元的地位更加稳固。【原文：The massive tariffs proposed by President Donald Trump on "Liberation Day" in April put the U.S. dollar's role as the world's anchor currency at risk, while the administration's eventual climbdown to more modest rates has likely left it secure, new economic research has concluded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tariffs-could-weaken-not-yet-reverse-dollars-reserve-status-research-shows-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FBC2OAOXROHZPREKSYMC3D3RQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机场跑道险情刺激人们希望更广泛地采用驾驶舱警报技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[当一架波音 757 飞机准备降落时，驾驶舱里响起了警报声："跑道上有飞机！跑道上有飞机！"几秒钟后，导航显示屏上也出现了同样的警告。【原文：As a Boeing 757 aircraft prepared to land, an audio alert started blaring in the cockpit: "Traffic on runway! Traffic on runway!" Seconds later, the same warning popped up on the navigation display.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airport-runway-close-calls-spur-hopes-wider-adoption-cockpit-alert-technology-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMBMVRDRC5K3XCVQDXXJ2QYKDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[两家竞标者争当美国联邦航空局大规模空中交通改造项目经理]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局的高级官员告诉路透社记者，该局只有两名候选人竞争数十亿美元的美国空中交通管制大修项目经理的职位。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration has just two candidates vying to become the project manager of a multi-billion dollar effort to overhaul air traffic control in the United States, the agency's top official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/two-bidders-vie-be-project-manager-massive-faa-us-air-traffic-overhaul-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIMOOPBT3JPRZHST6P6J6ESXFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股持续反弹可能受制于通胀、盈利和估值风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[过去几个月来，美国股市在波动极小的情况下接连创下历史新高，但投资者表示，通胀率居高不下、盈利可能令人失望以及估值过高等因素可能会削弱美股的涨势。【原文：U.S. stocks have hit a string of record highs with minimal turbulence over the past few months, but investors say the rally could be undermined by persistently high inflation, possible earnings disappointments and elevated valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/relentless-us-stocks-rally-could-teeter-inflation-earnings-valuation-risks-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLAKZ6H2LRJQ5CXZI4KVS5RJSI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田在富士山附近启动 "梭织城市 "试验场进行技术测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司在日本富士山附近的 Woven City 测试基地的第一部分于本周四开放，这是在该项目推出五年多之后开放的，其目的是加速下一代技术的实际试验。【原文：Toyota Motor opened the first section of its Woven City testing site near Japan's Mt. Fuji on Thursday, more than five years after unveiling the project aimed at accelerating real-world trials of next-generation technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-launches-woven-city-test-site-near-mt-fuji-tech-testing-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHJN2W3ELNMURL7WPJTLECSHLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家 - 消息人士称，Blackstone 正在考虑 ancestry.com 的各种选择，包括可能的出售或首次公开募股]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/exclusive-blackstone-mulls-options-ancestrycom-including-possible-sale-or-ipo-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MICW3G2GVMZ7HKD4IKPEMY6WY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟对 SAP 可能的反竞争行为展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会对欧洲最大的软件制造商德国 SAP 公司可能采取的反竞争做法展开了调查，调查涉及该公司流行的商业管理软件。【原文：The European Commission has opened an investigation into possible anticompetitive practices by Germany's SAP , Europe's largest software maker, related to its popular business management software.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-opens-probe-into-possible-anticompetitive-practices-by-sap-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLWTQD3I2BKZDDSZ2O3I37OAPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Planet Labs 将向柏林卫星生产基地投资八位数的资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于加利福尼亚州的行星实验室（Planet Labs）计划在柏林建立其在美国以外的首个卫星生产基地，该公司首席执行官威尔-马歇尔（Will Marshall）表示，将为该企业投资八位数的资金，这将使该公司的高分辨率卫星生产能力翻一番。【原文：California-based Planet Labs plans to set up its first satellite production site outside the U.S. in Berlin, investing an eight-figure sum in the venture that will see the firm double its high-resolution satellite capacity, said CEO Will Marshall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/planet-labs-invest-eight-figure-sum-berlin-satellite-production-site-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNV6PPWQCZJODEAKO3S366M3OI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业协会称中国正在研究如何调控铜冶炼产能]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家国家新闻媒体周四称，由于加工费持续走低导致冶炼利润减少，中国正在研究如何加强对铜冶炼产能扩张的监管。【原文：China is studying ways to strengthen regulation on the expansion of copper smelting capacity, a state news outlet said on Thursday, as persistently low processing fees have reduced smelting profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-studies-how-regulate-copper-smelting-capacity-industry-association-says-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AC3AW6ROXFI2JBK2JW337FKI34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:31:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道称，在其他岗位裁员之际，美国立法者对科技公司使用 H-1B 签证的情况进行了严格审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国立法者正在审查包括亚马逊和苹果在内的大型科技公司使用 H-1B 签证的情况，即使这些公司正在裁员。【原文：U.S. lawmakers are scrutinizing large technology companies including Amazon and Apple over their use of H-1B visas even as they lay off other workers, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-lawmakers-scrutinize-tech-firms-over-h-1b-visa-use-amid-other-job-layoffs-wsj-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXDB3UM7EJMCZJWDG76VWHZUJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:22:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发出购买美国大豆取决于取消关税的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部发言人周四在被问及中国是否会购买美国大豆时表示，美国应取消中国所称的不合理关税，并为扩大双边贸易创造条件。【原文：The United States should remove what China described as unreasonable tariffs and create conditions to expand bilateral trade, a Chinese commerce ministry spokesperson said on Thursday when asked if China would purchase U.S. soybeans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-signals-that-purchases-us-soybeans-hinge-tariff-removal-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYTVZPARRFIQBFWWNEGIOV643Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:54:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飞利浦与美国就医疗技术进口调查进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[飞利浦公司周四表示，正在就美国进口医疗技术产品的调查问题与华盛顿的政策制定者积极接触，但预计调查不会产生直接影响。【原文：Philips is actively engaged with policymakers in Washington about investigations into U.S. imports of medical technology items but does not expect an immediate impact from the probes, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/philips-talks-with-us-over-probes-medical-technology-imports-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYBABD2TAZNMPFZKVOSJTLS2OI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:48:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司向中国苏帕尔纳航空公司交付一架 777 货机]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国飞机制造商波音公司周四通过其官方微信账号表示，波音于周三交付了中国苏鹏航空公司订购的两架777货机中的第一架。【原文：Boeing on Wednesday delivered the first of two 777 freighters ordered by China's Suparna Airlines, the U.S. planemaker said on Thursday via its official WeChat account.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-handed-777-freighter-chinas-suparna-airlines-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WKMWY66ONICDJUMIL2X5VJHQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>