<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:10:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:10:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普和欧盟冯德莱恩将于周日会晤，以达成贸易协议，避免贸易战]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）将于周日与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）会面，以达成一项针对欧洲的贸易协议，该协议可能会对大多数欧盟商品征收 15%的基准关税，但会结束欧盟公司数月来的不确定性。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen is set to meet U.S. President Donald Trump on Sunday to clinch a trade deal for Europe that would likely see a 15% baseline tariff on most EU goods, but end months of uncertainty for EU companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-eus-von-der-leyen-meet-sunday-clinch-trade-deal-avert-trade-war-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45DY7JEYBBKSZJFMITNULXGPQE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 04:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 月份中国工业利润进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日的数据显示，6月份中国工业利润继续下降，原因是在国内需求低迷和全球贸易不确定性挥之不去的情况下，根深蒂固的生产通缩给企业带来了更大的利润压力。【原文：China's industrial profits continued to fall in June, data showed on Sunday, as entrenched producer deflation put more margin pressure on businesses in the face of subdued domestic demand and lingering global trade uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-industrial-profits-fall-further-june-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7SC6PBVZNOLXHFB2VGS5CSF6U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 01:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》报道，特斯拉向机器人出租车用户介绍加州司机式服务的最新情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》（Business Insider）援引特斯拉周六发送给用户的通知截图报道，特斯拉向机器人出租车用户发送了一份新的服务条款协议，详细说明了其计划在加州湾区推出的服务。
该通知称："如果您的乘车服务在加利福尼亚州进行，则将根据加利福尼亚州公用事业委员会的授权，由一名安全驾驶员使用全自动驾驶（监督）系统进行。"通知还补充说，在加利福尼亚州以外的乘车服务将 "自动进行"，这证实了路透社一天前的报道。【原文：Tesla sent robotaxi users a new terms-of-service agreement detailing its planned launch in California's Bay Area, Business Insider reported citing a screenshot of the notification sent to users on Saturday.
The notification said, "If your ride is taking place in California, it is being conducted with a safety driver using Full Self-Driving (Supervised) pursuant to authority from the California Public Utilities Commission," adding that rides taken outside California are "conducted autonomously," confirming Reuters reporting from a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-updates-robotaxi-users-about-chauffeur-style-service-california-business-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DELZOX6RNJPSRJ7P64SAE4UEOQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 00:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[女性交友应用 Tea 报告 7.2 万张图片在安全漏洞中被盗]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tea 是一款允许女性匿名评论和评论与男性约会的应用程序，该公司称遭遇了数据泄露，黑客获得了 72,000 张用户图片。【原文：Tea, an app that lets women anonymously comment and review dates with men, said it has suffered a data breach, with hackers gaining access to 72,000 user images.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/womens-dating-app-tea-reports-72000-images-stolen-security-breach-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVMQHPE3PRIXVJKFSX45V3CRUY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 20:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，联合太平洋公司可能在下周初达成收购诺福克南方公司的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，美国最大的铁路运营商联合太平洋铁路公司（Union Pacific）最快可能在下周初达成收购竞争对手诺福克南方铁路公司（Norfolk Southern）的协议。【原文：Union Pacific , the largest U.S. railroad operator, could reach an agreement to acquire rival Norfolk Southern as soon as early next week, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/union-pacific-could-reach-agreement-acquire-norfolk-southern-early-next-week-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RV3472KEFNMC3BKI6OV72TYSJI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:28:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟首脑冯德莱恩前往苏格兰与特朗普举行贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人称，欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）在周日下午与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）会晤前于周六前往苏格兰，欧盟官员称双方正接近达成贸易协议。【原文：EU Commission President Ursula von der Leyen headed to Scotland on Saturday ahead of a meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump on Sunday afternoon, commission spokespeople said, as EU officials said the two sides were nearing a trade agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/eu-chief-von-der-leyen-heads-scotland-trade-talks-with-trump-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SE4MMVFV6RIKJFS25ES6I72ZQE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，KKR 正在洽谈收购 ST Telemedia 全球数据中心事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周六援引知情人士的话报道，美国投资公司 KKR 正在洽谈收购总部位于新加坡的 ST Telemedia Global Data Centres，这笔交易可能会使这家亚洲基础设施供应商的估值超过 50 亿美元。【原文：U.S. investment firm KKR is in talks to buy Singapore-based ST Telemedia Global Data Centres in a deal that could value the Asian infrastructure provider at more than $5 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Saturday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kkr-talks-buy-st-telemedia-global-data-centres-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASVIPH73JRMERKANKAFKGBINKI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 16:18:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeRide 在上海获得机器人轴许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国自动驾驶技术公司WeRide周六表示，它已获得上海市政府颁发的经营自动驾驶机器人出租车打车服务的许可证。【原文：Chinese autonomous driving technology company WeRide said on Saturday it has been granted a permit from the Shanghai municipal government to operate autonomous robotaxi ride-hailing services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/weride-receives-permit-robotaxis-shanghai-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEIHW5E35JN7PA7XTKZ47U4PAY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 15:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称贸易协议中的 5500 亿美元一揽子方案可为美国的台湾芯片制造商提供资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最高贸易谈判代表 Ryosei Akazawa 周六表示，日本在本周美国关税协议中达成的 5500 亿美元投资一揽子计划可能有助于资助一家台湾公司在美国建设半导体工厂。【原文：Japan's $550 billion investment package agreed in this week's U.S. tariff deal could help finance a Taiwanese firm building semiconductor plants in the U.S., Japan's top trade negotiator Ryosei Akazawa said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-says-550-billion-package-trade-deal-could-finance-taiwanese-chipmaker-us-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRWS7W4HENODZNWQXBOZSEBVEY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 15:26:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国卫生官员和科技高管将启动数据共享计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周六报道，特朗普政府的高级卫生官员预计将于本周把科技公司带到白宫，推出一项鼓励更无缝共享医疗数据的计划。【原文：Top Trump administration health officials are expected to bring tech companies to the White House this week to roll out a plan to encourage more seamless sharing of health-care data, Bloomberg News reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-health-officials-tech-executives-launch-data-sharing-plan-bloomberg-news-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFBWFBJUI5NPDDC6YSL2HTSKEU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 14:51:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安联人寿称大部分客户数据在黑客攻击中被盗]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国保险巨头安联人寿（Allianz Life）周六表示，黑客窃取了其大部分客户、金融专业人士和部分安联人寿员工的个人信息。【原文：U.S. insurance giant Allianz Life said on Saturday that hackers stole the personal information of the majority of its customers, financial professionals, and select Allianz Life employees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/allianz-life-says-majority-customers-data-stolen-hack-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ICEQSXRKRP2ZGFY3VP7KHL5PA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 14:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI&US "这是我生命中最具同理心的声音"：人工智能如何改变神经变异者的生活]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于来自开普敦的电影制片人凯特-多特曼（Kate D'hotman）来说，与电影观众建立联系是一件自然而然的事情。与他人交谈则要困难得多。"这位 40 岁的恐怖片导演说："我一直不明白人们是如何（解读）社交暗示的。【原文：For Cape Town-based filmmaker Kate D’hotman, connecting with movie audiences comes naturally. Far more daunting is speaking with others. “I’ve never understood how people [decipher] social cues,” the 40-year-old director of horror films says.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/aius-its-most-empathetic-voice-my-life-how-ai-is-transforming-lives-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JWFOO6UXVJSXLZYXHZZRR5OKE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为展示人工智能计算系统，媲美英伟达顶级产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国华为技术公司周六展示了一套人工智能计算系统，一位业内专家称这套系统可与英伟达（Nvidia）最先进的产品相媲美。【原文：China's Huawei Technologies showed off an AI computing system on Saturday that one industry expert has said rivals Nvidia's most advanced offering, as the Chinese technology giant seeks to capture market share in the country's growing artificial intelligence sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/huawei-shows-off-ai-computing-system-rival-nvidias-top-product-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTGG5YPQ2ZN5BJ5KZZME27NRKE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:11:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税最后期限临近，韩国将准备双方都同意的贸易方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统府周六表示，在计划于下周举行的部长级会议和美国规定的 8 月 1 日关税暂停截止日期之前，韩国将准备一份与美国相互同意的贸易方案。【原文：South Korea will prepare a trade package that is mutually agreeable with the United States ahead of minister-level meetings planned next week and a U.S. tariff-pause deadline of August 1, the presidential office said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-prepare-mutually-agreeable-trade-package-us-tariff-deadline-looms-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UVLURUHVRLSHOION7XKBO6RBE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pony AI 称已获得上海地区无人驾驶机器人出租车服务许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国机器人出租车运营商小马智行（Pony AI）周六表示，它已获得在上海浦东金融区提供完全无人驾驶商用机器人出租车服务的许可。【原文：Chinese robotaxi operator Pony AI said on Saturday it had received a permit to provide fully driverless commercial robotaxi services in Shanghai's Pudong financial district.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/pony-ai-says-it-has-permit-driverless-robotaxi-services-shanghai-area-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXGTIM7FFVKR3ALU6TGBI3JFDQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国总理提议成立全球人工智能合作组织]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国务院总理李强周六表示，中国建议成立世界人工智能合作组织，呼吁各国协调发展与安全。【原文：China proposes establishing a world artificial intelligence cooperation organisation, Premier Li Qiang said on Saturday, calling on countries to coordinate development and security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-premier-proposes-global-ai-cooperation-organisation-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O43JHW3WIJMP3DFOUMIMBKURME</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 02:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局称 20% 的员工将离开航天局]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）发言人周五表示，美国国家航空航天局约20%的员工将离开航天局。【原文：About 20% of the employees at the U.S. National Aeronautics and Space Administration are set to depart the space agency, a NASA spokesperson said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/nasa-says-20-workforce-depart-space-agency-2025-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKZWEO7TLRPB7IOX4UJOWM4WPM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 01:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 任命 ChatGPT 联合创始人为超级智能实验室首席科学家]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 首席执行官马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）周五表示，Meta Platforms 已任命 ChatGPT 的联合创始人赵胜家（Shengjia Zhao）为其超级智能实验室（Superintelligence Lab）的首席科学家，公司正加速向高级人工智能领域推进。【原文：Meta Platforms has appointed Shengjia Zhao, co-creator of ChatGPT, as chief scientist of its Superintelligence Lab, CEO Mark Zuckerberg said on Friday, as the company accelerates its push into advanced AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-names-chatgpt-co-creator-chief-scientist-superintelligence-lab-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUBB7QD7FRN2RPSPAGDPB6ZI5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉收到多份与 xAI 投资相关的股东提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周五表示，已收到一些股东关于该公司投资首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的人工智能初创公司 xAI 的提案。【原文：Tesla said on Friday it has received a number of shareholder proposals regarding the automaker investing in CEO Elon Musk's artificial intelligence startup xAI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-gets-multiple-shareholder-proposals-related-investment-xai-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F67X7RXMRP3XKLKYZ7ROB53JY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:23:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院驳回美国证券交易委员会关于 "审计线索 "资金的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，一家联邦上诉法院周五驳回了美国证券交易委员会通过的关于资助全面市场监管系统的 2023 年法规，认为华尔街的最高监管机构没有提供足够的依据，允许证券交易所将其成本转嫁给会员。【原文：A federal appeals court on Friday struck down 2023 regulations adopted by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on funding a comprehensive market surveillance system, finding that Wall Street's top regulator had not provided a sufficient basis for allowing stock exchanges to pass on its costs to their members, court papers showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-appeals-court-strikes-down-sec-rule-audit-trail-funding-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3CUMGXVERID3G3VY6MQSPBCV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最后期限临近，投资者关注美欧可能达成的贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者希望美国和欧盟之间可能达成的贸易协议能在下周五关税截止日期前为市场带来更多确定性。【原文：Investors are hopeful a potential trade deal between the U.S. and European Union could bring more certainty to markets ahead of next Friday's tariffs deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/investors-eye-possible-us-europe-trade-deal-deadline-looms-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DVYSMJHQZIALOBXUHCKYNGMWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司称 Skydance 合并将在两周内完成]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司（Paramount Global）周五表示，在政府批准这项价值 84 亿美元的交易后，该公司预计将于 8 月 7 日前完成与 Skydance Media 的合并。【原文：Paramount Global said on Friday it expects to complete its merger with Skydance Media by August 7, following government approval for the $8.4 billion deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/paramount-global-says-skydance-merger-should-close-two-weeks-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQCC3SVUJ5OZTCUWWYSJNY5VLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:51:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[- 交易日【原文：- TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOIUNZ5UP5PBHBWTTBXMUYBIRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:42:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普和联邦通信委员会希望从哥伦比亚广播公司开始重塑媒体格局]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统和联邦通信委员会誓言要迫使美国广播媒体做出重大改变。【原文：President Donald Trump and the Federal Communications Commission have vowed to force American broadcast media outlets to make significant changes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-fcc-want-reshape-media-landscape-starting-with-cbs-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QR2ZNBIF2RJETKBQ2Q3NOFZB2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州监管机构称，特斯拉计划扩大包车运输服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，加州监管机构表示，特斯拉已告知加州将扩大湾区包车运输服务的运营。【原文：Tesla has told California it would expand operations of a chartered transportation service in the Bay Area, a state regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-plans-expand-chartered-transport-service-california-regulator-says-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NB2XLBJ2TNMQ3AM2KETZ2DRLFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Centene 让华尔街对医疗补助保险公司提高利润持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[Centene 公司周五表示，该公司预计能够提高向各州收取的 2026 年低收入美国人医疗保险计划的费率，并提高利润率，华尔街因此对医疗补助保险公司重拾信心。【原文：Wall Street regained confidence in Medicaid insurers after Centene said on Friday it expects to be able to raise rates charged to states for 2026 health plans for low-income Americans and strengthen profit margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/centene-raises-wall-street-optimism-that-medicaid-insurers-can-improve-profits-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TINAM6XVMJL6XATPZQEPAHHBL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 19:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税对巴西化学品出口商造成压力，引发订单取消]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁从 8 月 1 日起对南美国家的出口产品征收 50% 的新关税，去年向美国出口 24 亿美元的巴西化工产品公司面临着大量合同被取消的局面。【原文：Chemical products companies in Brazil, which exported $2.4 billion to the U.S. last year, face a slew of contract cancellations as President Donald Trump has threatened a new 50% tariff on the South American nation's exports from August 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-tariffs-weigh-brazil-chemical-exporters-spark-order-cancellations-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZSEA2G3FFZJHLOKP4A46I76XAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，LVMH 集团正在洽谈出售 Marc Jacobs 事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，奢侈品集团 LVMH 正在讨论出售时尚品牌 Marc Jacobs，交易价格可能在 10 亿美元左右。【原文：Luxury goods group LVMH is in discussions to sell fashion label Marc Jacobs in a deal that could fetch around $1 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lvmh-talks-sell-marc-jacobs-wsj-reports-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSIFJIKIFJJEZDSL5RPKGDG35I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:46:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔转至独立网络单元]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔周五表示，公司计划将网络与通信业务独立出来，并已开始寻找投资者，新任首席执行官陈立武希望精简这家陷入困境的芯片制造商。【原文：Intel said on Friday it planned to establish its networking and communications business as a stand-alone company and has begun the process of identifying investors, as new CEO Lip-Bu Tan looks to streamline the struggling chipmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/intel-separate-networking-unit-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCBDZKNLDBKV5EFMQ3VW572AHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，微软正在调查中国黑客是否通过警报了解到 SharePoint 的缺陷]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，微软正在调查其针对网络安全公司的早期预警系统是否发生泄密事件，导致中国黑客在其 SharePoint 服务中的漏洞得到修补之前就利用了这些漏洞。【原文：Microsoft is investigating whether a leak from its early alert system for cybersecurity companies allowed Chinese hackers to exploit flaws in its SharePoint service before they were patched, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-probing-if-chinese-hackers-learned-sharepoint-flaws-through-alert-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y26TEMWFX5JPPO4E53ZXQ5LDKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:26:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>