<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:38:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:38:55 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普推动能源扩张，美国输油管道公司面临买入/建造难题]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的支持能源政策旨在加快美国下一代能源基础设施的建设，但由于一系列阻碍大型项目的因素，许多石油和天然气管道运营商仍然宁愿购买也不愿建设，以实现扩张。【原文：President Donald Trump's pro-energy policies were meant to speed the construction of the United States' next generation of energy infrastructure, but many oil and gas pipeline operators would still rather buy than build their way to expansion due to a host of factors impeding large projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-pipeline-firms-wrestle-buybuild-conundrum-trump-pushes-energy-expansion-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MN2C2FQ555IVXK4JBQHI4DZXCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：马斯克的 DOGE 在美国政府中推广其 Grok 人工智能，引发冲突担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉此事的人士表示，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的DOGE团队正在扩大其人工智能聊天机器人Grok在美国联邦政府中的使用，以分析数据，这可能违反了利益冲突法，并危及数百万美国人的敏感信息。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk’s DOGE team is expanding use of his artificial intelligence chatbot Grok in the U.S. federal government to analyze data, said three people familiar with the matter, potentially violating conflict-of-interest laws and putting at risk sensitive information on millions of Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/musks-doge-expanding-his-grok-ai-us-government-raising-conflict-concerns-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHYHHROTE5PB5MAQQ7TRUXFXLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 英伟达财报受关注，美国收益率和债务上升扰动市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[半导体巨头、人工智能风向标英伟达（Nvidia）的财报将在下周成为华尔街的焦点，而股市则因联邦赤字导致国债收益率上升的担忧而遭遇减速。【原文：An earnings report from semiconductor giant and artificial intelligence bellwether Nvidia takes center stage for Wall Street in the coming week, as stocks hit a speed bump of worries over federal deficits driving up Treasury yields.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-nvidia-earnings-focus-rising-us-yields-debt-rattle-markets-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTNSUI7KPRKITBN3XQI63TVDDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货持平，因债务问题引发担忧，市场正在考虑特朗普的税收法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的税收和支出法案在前一天的众议院关键投票中获胜，引发了人们对美国财政前景恶化的担忧，此后投资者避险情绪高涨，周五美国股指期货走势低迷。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were muted on Friday as investors were risk-averse after President Donald Trump's tax and spending bill won a crucial House vote the previous day, raising concerns about the country's deteriorating fiscal outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-flat-debt-worries-markets-mull-trumps-tax-bill-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUQ3NV6ENVOOTFE2KDLPHRYPKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:53:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴基斯坦部长表示，巴基斯坦将在关税谈判中向美国公司提供矿业投资优惠条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴基斯坦商务部长告诉路透社记者，作为与华盛顿就关税问题进行谈判的一部分，巴基斯坦计划为美国公司投资其采矿业提供优惠，因为伊斯兰堡希望利用特朗普政府对促进与南亚贸易的兴趣。【原文：Pakistan plans to offer concessions to U.S. companies to invest in its mining sector as part of negotiations with Washington over tariffs, its commerce minister told Reuters, as Islamabad seeks to capitalize on the Trump administration’s interest in boosting trade with South Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/pakistan-offer-us-firms-concessions-mining-investment-tariff-talks-says-minister-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZ3YVYQKTZPKTGX3PEMWZSVN34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:47:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新兴市场股票基金吸引投资者逃离估值过高的美国资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年，新兴市场股票基金在全球表现领先，这主要得益于有吸引力的估值、投资者多年来仓位不足以及美国总统唐纳德-特朗普暂停征收关税后经济压力的缓解。【原文：Emerging market equity funds are leading the global performance this year, bolstered by attractive valuations, years of under-positioning by investors and an easing of economic pressures after U.S. President Donald Trump's pause on tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/emerging-market-equity-funds-lure-investors-fleeing-overvalued-us-assets-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWODVGIQUZIIBFVILIWKMFEU5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:24:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据报道，特朗普将颁布行政命令促进核工业发展，核电股因此大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最快将于本周五签署旨在启动核能产业的行政命令，核能股在盘前交易中飙升。【原文：Shares of nuclear power soared in premarket trading after a Reuters report said U.S. President Donald Trump will sign executive orders aimed to jumpstart the nuclear energy industry as soon as Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nuclear-stocks-surge-report-trump-executive-orders-boost-industry-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNUZACRGKROSPP2ACKITLMCCEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:12:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，富士康是新加坡芯片组装公司UTAC 30 亿美元交易的潜在竞购者之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，台湾富士康是新加坡半导体组装和测试企业UTAC Holdings的潜在竞购者之一，该交易可能使该公司估值约30亿美元。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn is among potential bidders for the Singaporean semiconductor assembly and testing business UTAC Holdings in a deal that could value the company at about $3 billion, two people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/foxconn-among-potential-bidders-singaporean-chip-assembly-firm-utac-3-billion-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7LVL7YRJNPPXFGSQNEYFZIZMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:07:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽瓦克机场停电后需求和客流量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[两家旅游公司的数据显示，在一系列空中交通中断事件促使谨慎的旅客通过附近的机场中转之后，新泽西纽瓦克自由国际机场的客流量和需求量急剧下降。【原文：Passenger traffic and demand have declined sharply at New Jersey's Newark Liberty International Airport, according to data from two travel companies, after a series of air traffic disruptions prompted cautious travelers to transit through nearby airports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/demand-traffic-falls-newark-airport-following-outages-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOVTGXB7NZLVLMNR3GUZ7KN42Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 "Jensanity "中，英伟达发出了保住人工智能桂冠的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）周五飞离台北，此前一周他一直陶醉于台湾科技产业的崇拜之中，并传达了美国人工智能芯片之王的一个微妙而关键的信息，即它计划如何保住自己的王位。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang flew out of Taipei on Friday after a week revelling in the adoration of Taiwan's tech industry, and delivering a subtle but crucial message from the U.S. AI chip king on how it plans to keep its crown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/amid-jensanity-nvidia-signals-plans-keep-ai-crown-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSC6RKH4LJIOFO4XRZLMVU32FA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 08:50:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道塔利班正与俄罗斯和中国就使用当地货币进行贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿富汗代理商务部长表示，塔利班政府正在与俄罗斯进行深入谈判，以便两个受制裁影响经济体的银行能够用当地货币结算价值数亿美元的贸易交易。【原文：The Taliban administration is in advanced talks with Russia for banks from both sanctions-hit economies to settle trade transactions worth hundreds of millions of dollars in their local currencies, Afghanistan's acting commerce minister said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/taliban-talks-with-russia-china-trade-transactions-local-currencies-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VIW7BGRM45IONOVC2ILUAT72MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 08:13:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟和美国当局摧毁恶意软件网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟刑事司法合作机构欧洲司法组织（Eurojust）在一份声明中说，欧洲、美国和加拿大当局在打击恶意软件的行动中已在全球范围内关闭了 300 多个服务器，并对 20 名嫌疑人发出了国际逮捕令，这是 "终局行动 "的最新阶段。【原文：European, American and Canadian authorities have taken down over 300 servers worldwide and issued international arrest warrants against 20 suspects in a crackdown on malware, EU agency for criminal justice cooperation Eurojust said in a statement, the latest phase in Operation Endgame.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-us-authorities-take-down-malware-network-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWDJYXCM7FNUVFCDDVPTRY5FLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:54:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯受制裁油轮集团 Sovcomflot 大幅亏损 3.93 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯领先的油轮集团 Sovcomflot 第一季度净亏损骤降至 3.93 亿美元，将业绩下滑归咎于西方新制裁导致的运营问题、收入减少以及一些受制裁船只闲置。【原文：Russia's leading tanker group Sovcomflot plunged to a net loss of $393 million in the first quarter, blaming the slump on new Western sanctions that have led to operational problems, lower revenues and some sanctioned vessels sitting idle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russias-sovcomflot-posted-net-loss-393-million-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FT4MUY5J5KLDI7KYASZ3ZAPEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:21:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称印度可能让美国和外国公司竞标政府合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位政府消息人士称，印度正在向包括美国在内的外国公司开放一块受保护的政府采购市场，在本月根据一项贸易协议向英国开放后，这一转变可能会扩展到其他贸易伙伴。【原文：India is opening up a chunk of its protected government procurement market to foreign firms, including the U.S, two government sources said, in a shift that could extend to other trading partners after it was offered to the UK under a trade deal this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-may-let-us-foreign-firms-bid-government-contracts-sources-say-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LPWSYGZHRN3RKMB7WXXKG3UTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:21:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件显示，随着经济放缓，俄罗斯主要出口商削减了铁路货运量]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份俄罗斯铁路公司文件显示，包括俄罗斯铝业公司（Rusal）和俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司（Gazpromneft）在内的俄罗斯主要出口商已经削减了通过铁路运输的金属和石油产品等大宗商品的计划运输量，这是该国战争经济放缓导致需求低迷的最新迹象。【原文：Major Russian exporters including Rusal and Gazpromneft have cut the planned volume of commodities like metal and oil products they send by rail, a Russian Railways document seen by Reuters showed, the latest sign of subdued demand as the country's war economy slows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/russias-major-exporters-cut-rail-cargo-volumes-economy-slows-document-shows-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPPFITUKVZPZTF5HXSDJZEGRJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国邀请亚洲官员访问阿拉斯加，着眼于价值 440 亿美元的液化天然气项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国已邀请日本、韩国和中国台湾的官员前往阿拉斯加，讨论包括一条大型天然气管道在内的项目，两位熟悉规划的人士说，亚洲各国政府正在考虑美国的投资，希望能从唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税中获得减免。【原文：The U.S. has invited officials from Japan, South Korea and Taiwan to Alaska to discuss projects including a vast gas pipeline, two people familiar with the planning said, as Asian governments consider U.S. investments in the hopes of relief from President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-invites-asian-officials-alaska-eyes-44-billion-lng-project-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOOTLBBGGFKTLC6JBJHZEJDBFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社看到的越南政府文件显示，越南将封杀消息应用程序 Telegram]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的一份政府文件显示，越南技术部已指示电信服务提供商封杀信息应用 Telegram，原因是 Telegram 不配合打击其用户涉嫌犯罪的行为。【原文：Vietnam's technology ministry has instructed telecommunication service providers to block the messaging app Telegram for not cooperating in combating alleged crimes committed by its users, according to a government document reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/vietnam-acts-block-messaging-app-telegram-government-document-seen-by-reuters-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXHIBVHURNI6HBY4KX7A5VZTP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:11:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司在中国为新款 iPhone 提供更多以旧换新折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[据苹果公司网站周五报道，苹果公司将在 6 月 18 日前在中国为新款 iPhone 提供额外的以旧换新折扣。【原文：Apple is offering additional trade-in discounts for new iPhones in China until June 18, according to its website on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/apple-offers-additional-trade-in-discounts-new-iphones-china-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CC6LJNKPZ5I3DPQU2C5VN2IQXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 05:25:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税迷雾笼罩的市场让投资者无所适从]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球投资者承认，在美国反复无常的贸易言论和混乱的经济预测肆虐的市场中，他们只能盲目跟风，并强调现在比 2020 年 COVID 危机以来的任何时候都更难下长期赌注。【原文：Global investors admit to flying blind in markets roiled by erratic U.S. trade rhetoric and chaotic economic forecasting, stressing that placing long-term bets was harder now than at any time since the 2020 COVID crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-flows-investors-analysis-pix-graphic-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EM6PDEOVYNJJ5EXNP4CM3ORAOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 05:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价债券市场占据主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFWV2YEGGVIDZHEYE4ONHEP6WA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:36:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：特朗普敦促欧盟削减关税，否则将面临额外关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易谈判代表正在推动欧盟单方面降低对美国商品的关税，称如果欧盟不做出让步，避免额外20%"对等 "关税的谈判将不会取得进展。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's trade negotiators are pushing the EU to make unilateral tariff reductions on U.S. goods, saying without concessions the bloc will not progress in talks to avoid additional 20% "reciprocal" duties, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-pushes-eu-cut-tariffs-or-face-extra-duties-ft-reports-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUYLMMAZAFME5IXYKJKPJY3SRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:28:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田、日产和福特在日本的供应商受到关税交火的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kyowa Industrial 等六家汽车供应商告诉路透社，他们担心自己是否有能力承受日本汽车业面临的关税压力。【原文：Companies like Kyowa Industrial were among six auto suppliers that told Reuters they were concerned about their ability to withstand the tariff pressure on Japan's car industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tariff-crossfire-hits-toyota-nissan-ford-suppliers-japan-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U37BFS4JZPSJAX7DCUYKXU2GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:32:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政状况令人担忧，美元将结束四周连涨势头]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五走软，对欧元和日元的汇率将出现五周以来的首次单周下跌，原因是对美国财政健康状况恶化的担忧使投资者纷纷寻找避风港。【原文：The U.S. dollar was soft on Friday, poised to make its first weekly drop in five weeks against the euro and the yen as worries over the United States' worsening fiscal health sent investors scurrying for safe havens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-set-snap-4-week-winning-streak-us-fiscal-health-worries-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5I7VD3NKCJNXDL5N7USY5G6DYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:14:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市谨慎上扬，受挫的国债寻求支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的税收法案在下议院以微弱优势获得通过后，尽管债务忧虑仍挥之不去，但受挫的国债找到了买家，亚洲股市周五出现了一些试探性上涨。【原文：Asian shares made some tentative gains on Friday as beaten-down Treasuries found buyers after U.S. President Donald Trump's tax bill narrowly passed the lower house, although debt worries still lingered.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HYXT2GTIBJNPLOEC7KQHDQWJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡央行官员：亚洲绝不能屈服于关税报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡金融管理局副总经理周五表示，亚洲经济体必须保持灵活，不能屈服于针锋相对的关税报复。【原文：Asian economies must remain agile and not succumb to tit-for-tat tariff retaliation, a deputy managing director of the Monetary Authority of Singapore said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asia-must-not-succumb-tariff-retaliation-singapore-cbank-official-says-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24DMPMWMZBKZXOFNPHWQ7IVWKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：一些美国银行探索通过联合稳定币涉足加密货币领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国一些最大的银行正在探讨是否联手发行一种联合稳定币。【原文：Some of the biggest U.S. banks are exploring whether to team up to issue a joint stablecoin, The Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/some-us-banks-explore-venturing-into-crypto-with-joint-stablecoin-wsj-reports-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNQMPWPZMZNJHPODMACJ55U3E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本超长收益率徘徊在纪录高位附近，原因是通胀和财政担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府债券周五保持稳定，此前一周波动剧烈，由于通胀和财政担忧削弱了债务需求，超长收益率创下历史新高。【原文：Japanese government bonds remained stable on Friday, after a volatile week in which super-long yields hit record highs as inflation and fiscal concerns sapped demand for debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-super-long-yields-hover-near-record-highs-inflation-fiscal-concerns-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6SEWWUX6RPHRHKLCQ2HWZDR5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚对中国网络商品的新一轮采购有助于抑制通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球企业都在担心美国的天价关税会导致通胀率飙升，而在澳大利亚，中国廉价商品的转向有望缓解消费者和决策者对顽固成本压力的担忧。【原文：As businesses globally fret about sky-high U.S. tariffs reviving rampant inflation, in Australia, the redirection of cheap Chinese goods is expected to provide relief for consumers and policymakers worried about stubborn cost pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/australias-new-haul-chinese-online-goods-helps-tame-inflation-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OORZ5EELJMS3O5BYUK5UAJO3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:27:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元走强，欧佩克+产量可能增加，石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美元走强和欧佩克+可能进一步增加原油产量的影响，周五油价下滑。【原文：Oil prices slipped on Friday, weighed down by a stronger U.S. dollar and the possibility that OPEC+ will further increase its crude oil output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-falls-stronger-us-dollar-possibility-higher-opec-output-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHP5TSROXNIUDJFXY2C2BE3XUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:54:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，日本关税特使赤泽可能于 5 月 30 日前后访美]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士周五称，日本最高关税谈判代表赤泽亮世打算在 5 月 30 日前后访问美国，进行第四轮贸易谈判。【原文：Japan's top tariff negotiator Ryosei Akazawa intends to visit the United States around May 30 for a fourth round of trade talks, two sources familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-tariff-envoy-akazawa-may-visit-us-around-may-30-sources-say-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJVINEGOZFK3VGGBWKMTSO75AU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>