<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 05:08:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 05:08:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[桑坦德银行押注英国，与 TSB 达成交易，显示银行对规模的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[桑坦德银行以 26.5 亿英镑（约合 36.1 亿美元）收购 TSB 并提升其在英国地位的计划是几周前刚刚达成的，此前这家西班牙银行一直在权衡退出英国的可能性，三位接近这一进程的消息人士说。【原文：Santander's plan to buy TSB for 2.65 billion pounds ($3.61 billion) and boost its position in the UK came together just a few weeks ago, after the Spanish bank had been weighing a possible exit from Britain, three sources close to the process said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/santanders-bet-britain-with-tsb-deal-shows-banks-need-scale-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3SINENBVRIQFDG4HJCXRXDA6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 05:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银储备经理调查称美联储独立性和美国法治面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银资产管理公司（UBS Asset Management）周四在一项调查中称，每三位储备经理中就有两位担心美联储的独立性受到威胁，近一半的人认为美国的法治状况可能恶化到足以严重影响他们的资产配置。【原文：Two in three reserve managers fear Federal Reserve independence is at risk and nearly half think the rule of law in the United States may deteriorate enough to influence their asset allocation significantly, UBS Asset Management said in a survey on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-independence-us-rule-law-risk-ubs-reserve-managers-survey-says-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72FKUGS3ARPA7DTXFIMDH6XZRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 05:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价贸易乐观让位于对美国就业的谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJHLE7JTH5LANHDPG6AHB44HMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 04:49:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元交易引人注目，但也要付出代价]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于央行的谨慎态度、贸易战和令人望而却步的持币成本，全球投资者正在解除对日元快速升值的押注，这也是今年最受欢迎的交易之一。【原文：Global investors are unwinding their wagers on Japan's yen rising quickly as a cautious central bank, a trade war and the prohibitive cost of holding the currency sour one of the year's most popular trades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-yen-is-compelling-trade-comes-cost-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMYKBFSZVZPRLLY3B6W6PYDMFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 04:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者做好准备，应对突发事件对市场造成的数周冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[这些事件可能会打破股市的平静，并导致他们认为可能出现正面或负面意外的资产（从黄金到企业信贷）大幅波动。【原文：Big investors are mobilising to trade through weeks packed with wild-card events that may shatter the calm in stock markets and drive big swings for assets they see as exposed to both positive or negative surprises, from gold to corporate credit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/global-markets-risk-events-graphic-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOQU5CDW4RIDLFTV6ZJ5HJORSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 04:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月就业增长预计放缓，失业率预计上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于特朗普政府政策带来的经济不确定性抑制了招聘，6月份美国劳动力市场可能进一步放缓，失业率预计将升至4.3%，超过3年半以来的新高。【原文：The U.S. labor market likely slowed further in June, with the unemployment rate expected to have edged up to more than a 3-1/2-year high of 4.3%, as economic uncertainty stemming from the Trump administration's policies curbed hiring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-job-growth-expected-slow-june-unemployment-rate-forecast-rise-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFZSCDUUEZN23DHWNSTEAPV7XM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 04:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司和司法部寻求法官批准遭空难遇难者家属反对的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司和美国司法部周三请求美国法官批准一项协议，尽管在2018年和2019年两起737 MAX坠机事故中遇难的346人中有一些人的亲属提出反对，但该协议允许波音公司避免被起诉。【原文：Boeing and the Justice Department on Wednesday asked a U.S. judge to approve an agreement that allows the company to avoid prosecution despite objections from relatives of some of the 346 people killed in two 737 MAX crashes in 2018 and 2019.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-justice-department-seek-judges-approval-deal-opposed-by-crash-victims-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26B4VE3TXBO43FHUHI5RUQFKA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 03:54:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 6 月在华电动车销量同比增长 3.7% 至 61,000 辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉中国公司周四公布的数据显示，特斯拉电动汽车 6 月份销量同比增长 3.7%。【原文：Tesla's electric vehicle sales in June rose 3.7% from a year earlier, according to Tesla China on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-china-ev-sales-rise-37-yy-61000-vehicles-june-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EROJX5LOTNKJVFADXSLSCH4DGY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 02:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行决策者呼吁在暂时停止加息后恢复加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行董事会成员高田恒指（Hajime Takata）表示，日本央行在为评估美国关税的影响而暂时停止加息后，应恢复加息，并对日本有望持久实现央行的物价目标表示乐观。【原文：The Bank of Japan should resume interest rate hikes following a temporary pause to evaluate the impact of U.S. tariffs, board member Hajime Takata said, signalling optimism the country was on track to durably achieve the central bank's price goal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/boj-should-resume-rate-hikes-after-pause-board-member-takata-says-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFQUL657JNOQ5LTIXJ5665MNKA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 02:21:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国非农就业数据测试前亚洲股市上扬；特朗普的税收法案成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲股市走高，原因是投资者在等待一份关键的美国就业报告，该报告可能为美联储即将降息提供理由，同时也在等待国会通过一项大规模的美国税收和支出法案。【原文：Asian shares edged higher on Thursday as investors braced for a key U.S. jobs report that may justify imminent rate cuts by the Federal Reserve and waited on the passage of a massive U.S. tax and spending bill in Congress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWLVEB33JVOGPCI2GWGOGXZYCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 02:16:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国取消出口限制后，Cadence 表示将恢复在中国的软件准入]]></title><description><![CDATA[鏗騰設計系統公司（Cadence Design Systems）周四表示，美國已解除對中國芯片設計軟件的出口限制，該公司正在恢復受影響客戶對軟件和技術的使用。【原文：Cadence Design Systems said on Thursday the U.S. had lifted export restrictions on chip design software for China and that it was in the process of restoring access to software and technology to affected customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cadence-says-restoring-software-access-china-after-us-lifts-export-curbs-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZWCEIQE7JIITF2DSQ4UTKVEWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 02:10:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行调整亚太地区投资银行领导层，提升地区影响力]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）周四宣布了亚太地区投资银行部的一系列高管任命，旨在推动该地区的增长，同时在全球范围内审查该业务的资本分配。【原文：Barclays announced on Thursday a series of executive appointments within its Asia Pacific investment banking division, aiming to drive regional growth even as it globally reviews capital allocation to the business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-reshuffles-apac-investment-banking-leadership-boost-regional-presence-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBWMTZRXZNPTFI3BN33VM73SPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 01:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员翘首以待美国非农就业数据，美元随之漂移]]></title><description><![CDATA[在7月9日关税最后期限到来之前，美国和越南之间达成的一项贸易协定助长了对未来可能达成的交易的乐观情绪，而投资者则将目光投向了薪资数据，以评估美联储的下一步行动。【原文：The dollar wobbled on Thursday after a trade agreement between the United States and Vietnam fuelled optimism over potential future deals ahead of a July 9 tariff deadline, while investors looked to payrolls to assess the Federal Reserve's next steps.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-drifts-traders-hunker-down-us-payrolls-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQEM6JK73NMDVBAOHF27642CUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 01:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关键就业报告发布前，美国需求疲软的迹象导致石油下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四油价下跌，扭转了上一交易日的涨势，原因是政府数据显示全球最大的原油消费国美国的库存意外增加，市场担心美国需求疲软。【原文：Oil prices eased on Thursday, reversing gains from the previous session, on concerns over weak U.S. demand after government data showed a surprise build in inventories in the world's biggest crude consumer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-falls-signs-weak-us-demand-ahead-key-jobs-report-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBAJJCBBG5P73EKBPPKT6ATTLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 01:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，西门子称美国已解除对中国的芯片软件禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三援引德国西门子公司的一份声明报道称，该公司已收到美国政府的通知，称对华芯片设计软件出口限制已被取消。【原文：Germany's Siemens AG has received a notice from the U.S. government saying that export restrictions on chip design software for China have been lifted, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing a statement from the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/siemens-says-us-has-lifted-chip-software-curbs-china-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-07-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHRLMILBLVM6NKQBJQZEWM5ZJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普与越南达成协议后，美国和印度推动贸易协定的达成]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉谈判情况的消息人士称，美国和印度的贸易谈判代表周三正在努力争取在唐纳德-特朗普总统规定的7月9日谈判截止日期之前达成一项降低关税的协议，但有关美国乳制品和农业的分歧仍未得到解决。【原文：U.S. and India trade negotiators were pushing on Wednesday to try to land a tariff-reducing deal ahead of President Donald Trump's July 9 negotiating deadline, but disagreements over U.S. dairy and agriculture remained unresolved, sources familiar with the talks said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-india-push-trade-pact-after-trump-strikes-deal-with-vietnam-sources-say-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5ANH4HAPBNOZA3CQTQBHX3ZT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:47:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Starboard Value 持有 Tripadvisor 超过 9% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，激进投资者 Starboard Value 已持有在线旅游公司 Tripadvisor 超过 9% 的股份。【原文：Activist investor Starboard Value has built an over 9% stake in online travel firm Tripadvisor , the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/starboard-value-builds-over-9-stake-tripadvisor-wsj-reports-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQWN2OZLBVOMVPHV3RE5S5445A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:31:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邦吉公司（Bunge）与谷物装卸商 Viterra 完成拖延已久的大型合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球农业综合企业邦吉全球公司（Bunge Global）表示，在宣布与嘉能可（Glencore）支持的维泰拉公司（Viterra）进行价值 340 亿美元的巨额交易两年后，该公司于本周三正式完成了拖延已久的合并交易。【原文：Global agribusiness Bunge Global said it officially closed a long-delayed deal to merge with Glencore-backed Viterra on Wednesday, two years after announcing the $34 billion mega-deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/bunge-completes-long-delayed-mega-merger-with-grain-handler-viterra-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APVPFT4FE5IEDBR4W3D767NTKM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:08:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森、卡塔尔能源合资公司请求美国监管机构批准从 10 月 1 日起再出口液化天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚和卡塔尔能源公司（QatarEnergy）拥有的金色通道液化天然气公司（Golden Pass LNG）已向美国监管机构申请从 10 月 1 日起重新出口液化天然气的许可，因为该出口工厂在之前的延误后已接近投产。【原文：Golden Pass LNG, which is owned by Exxon Mobil and QatarEnergy, has asked U.S. regulators for permission to re-export liquefied natural gas from October 1, as the export plant nears production after previous delays.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-qatarenergy-jv-asks-us-regulators-permission-re-export-lng-october-1-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWTGJKAJSVIXHCMTX42SBWEMDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国解除对企业产品公司向中国运输乙烷的限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国企业产品合伙公司（Enterprise Products Partners）周三表示，美国已为该公司恢复对中国的乙烷运输扫清了障碍，取消了几周前因中美贸易战从关税转向供应链而实施的限制性许可要求。【原文：The U.S. has cleared the way for Enterprise Products Partners to resume ethane shipments to China, the company said on Wednesday, revoking a restrictive license requirement that was put in place just weeks ago as the U.S.-China trade war turned from tariffs to supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-lifts-restrictions-enterprise-products-ethane-shipments-china-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWBFYP7JEZIH5PRWLWEQ65CXNY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:21:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邮件称美国联邦储备委员会银行监管主管接受收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的吉布森发给美联储官员的一封电子邮件，美国联邦储备委员会监督和监管部主任迈克尔-吉布森（Michael Gibson）已接受自愿买断，并将于本月底退休，此前他已在央行工作了 33 年。【原文：Michael Gibson, director of the U.S. Federal Reserve's supervision and regulation division, has accepted a voluntary buyout and will retire at the end of this month after 33 years at the central bank, according to an email from Gibson to Fed officials seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-fed-bank-supervision-chief-takes-buyout-email-says-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIG5GTBYB5ITBKWGZPS6S4Z4J4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：为就业报告做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWKZQ5K6NNJD5GSNTZCVUUZGZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司第二季度交付 61 架飞机，同比增长 30]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周三表示，2025 年第二季度交付了 61 架飞机，同比增长 30%。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer said on Wednesday it delivered 61 aircraft in the second quarter of 2025, a 30% increase from a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-delivers-61-aircraft-q2-30-rise-year-on-year-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJBE6JRLMFNBVII2LQFUUBBY4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 称未与 Robinhood 合作开发股票代币]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周三表示，它尚未与 Robinhood 合作开发该交易平台本周早些时候推出的股票代币。【原文：OpenAI said on Wednesday it has not partnered with Robinhood for the stock tokens the trading platform unveiled earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-says-it-has-not-partnered-with-robinhood-stock-token-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZDXTFMJPJK2PE25LS7HY6LKY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国长安汽车高管表示计划在欧洲建厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高管周三告诉路透社，中国汽车制造商长安汽车计划在欧洲建厂，以支持其未来在欧洲大陆的销售。【原文：Chinese automaker Changan plans a European factory to support its future sales on the continent and is already weighing up possible locations for the plant, an executive told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-changan-plans-european-factory-executive-says-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQEEN7EPGROLZH6PJH3IOJTJNM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:16:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Lucid 因需求疲软，第二季度交付量不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lucid 周三未能达到华尔街对其第二季度交付量的预期，原因是消费者在应对经济不确定性和成本上升时对其豪华电动汽车的需求疲软。【原文：Lucid missed Wall Street expectations for second-quarter deliveries on Wednesday, hit by softer demand for its luxury electric vehicles as consumers grapple with economic uncertainty and higher costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-lucid-misses-second-quarter-delivery-estimates-soft-demand-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SFEUAY5INOXVFJM3D3ZEKUFCM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:09:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会与 SolarWinds 达成初步协议，结束违约诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周三在一份法庭文件中表示，该委员会已与 SolarWinds 公司及其高级安全官原则上达成协议，结束与该软件公司与俄罗斯有关的网络攻击相关的诉讼。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has reached a deal in principle with SolarWinds Corp and its top security officer to end litigation tied to a Russia-linked cyberattack involving the software firm, they said in a court filing on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-sec-solarwinds-reach-preliminary-deal-end-breach-lawsuit-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZIW4LI25NNUTFOFT3LEVINNFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AOS 就未经授权运输华为产品与美国达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国商务部周三发布的一项命令，Alpha and Omega Semiconductor Limited 已同意支付 425 万美元，与美国商务部达成和解，原因是该公司向中国华为技术公司运送物品违反了出口法规。【原文：Alpha and Omega Semiconductor Limited has agreed to pay $4.25 million to settle with the U.S. Department of Commerce for shipping items to China's Huawei Technologies in violation of export regulations, according to a department order posted on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/aos-settles-with-us-over-unauthorized-huawei-shipments-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7IWSEU45FLA5MHTQ7JZCKFRGY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普和解引发 CBS 新闻 "广泛困扰]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙环球公司（Paramount Global）与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提起的《60 分钟》（60 Minutes）诉讼达成和解，周三引发了哥伦比亚广播公司（CBS News）现任和前任员工、新闻自由倡导者和立法者的谴责。【原文：Paramount Global's settlement of the "60 Minutes" lawsuit filed by U.S. President Donald Trump provoked condemnation on Wednesday from CBS News current and former employees, press freedom advocates and legislators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-settlement-triggers-widespread-distress-cbs-news-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VN3JYRZKFNK27BB3OMIVGROBJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 18:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币关注下一个前沿领域，瑞波币申请美国国家银行特许经营权]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币公司瑞波（Ripple）的首席执行官布拉德-加林豪斯（Brad Garlinghouse）周三在社交媒体上发文称，该公司正在申请美国国家银行的特许经营权。【原文：Crypto firm Ripple is applying for a national bank charter in the U.S., its CEO Brad Garlinghouse wrote in a social media post on Wednesday, shortly after a similar step by stablecoin giant Circle .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ripple-applies-us-national-bank-charter-crypto-eyes-next-frontier-2025-07-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7RBKN3XNNOCZKZ34N5Z2QBZJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 18:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>