<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:40:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:40:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Chinese banks heed PBOC call to cut dollar deposit rates, say sources]]></title><description><![CDATA[China's banks are cutting the interest rates offered on U.S. dollar deposits after being asked to do so by the central bank, possibly to curtail dollar hoarding and also prop up a weakening yuan, sources said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-banks-heed-pboc-call-cut-dollar-deposit-rates-say-sources-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6NGMEO2OJPZRNXPLGP322KY6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bytedance's TikTok to invest $8.8 bln in Thailand data centres, official says]]></title><description><![CDATA[ByteDance's TikTok will invest $8.8 billion in data centres in Thailand over five years, Helena Lersch, TikTok's Vice President of Public Policy, said on Friday at an event in Bangkok.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bytedances-tiktok-invest-88-bln-thailand-data-centres-official-says-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F5OVD43XJO6LPYHQTSJFGE4CI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia's seizures offer warning to Western firms hoping for Trump-inspired return]]></title><description><![CDATA[One morning in October 2024, three men entered the Moscow headquarters of Glavprodukt, the largest maker of canned food in Russia. One announced himself as the new director general and said he would now be making the decisions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russias-seizures-offer-warning-western-firms-hoping-trump-inspired-return-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAJSAILJHFI6ZK23RTB6BN3OJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto prices tumble as Trump-fuelled euphoria fades]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency prices are down sharply in recent weeks and not expected to rebound soon, with some of the biggest digital currencies erasing nearly all of the gains they made after Donald Trump's election win triggered a wave of excitement across the industry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/crypto-prices-tumble-trump-fuelled-euphoria-fades-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJA5RQ7QMBKPDPF7Z7Z6TOMGBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[水泥生产商 Holcim 第四季度盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Holcim 公司周五公布的第四季度财报好于预期，该建材公司公布了分拆北美业务计划的更多细节。【原文：Holcim reported better-than-expected earnings for its fourth quarter on Friday as the building materials company gave more details of its plan to spin off its North American business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/cement-maker-holcim-beats-earnings-forecasts-fourth-quarter-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RLYX2SWG5JTFFEOEQX4L5T6YI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:43:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标特朗普关税忧虑无处藏身]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7QN7EXFQRISNBEXPDWTC4SFNM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国表示反对美国最新关税威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五表示，反对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普因致命毒品流入美国而对中国进口商品额外征收10%关税的最新威胁，指责白宫 "推卸责任 "并采取措施破坏全球供应链的稳定。【原文：China on Friday said it opposed President Donald Trump's latest threat to slap an extra 10% duty on Chinese imports over deadly drug flows into the U.S., accusing the White House of "shifting the blame" and taking steps to destabilise global supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-says-it-opposes-latest-us-tariff-threat-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X66WMCSY6JNZHBUZEBJIK3O4KY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：英国能源大臣将于三月访华，重启能源谈判并会见投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位直接了解该计划的消息人士告诉路透社，英国能源大臣埃德-米利班德（Ed Miliband）将于 3 月访华，重启能源合作谈判并会见中国投资者。【原文：British Energy Secretary Ed Miliband will visit China in March to restart talks on energy cooperation and meet Chinese investors, three sources with direct knowledge of the plan told Reuters, as the Labour government seeks closer China ties amid worsening U.S.- and EU-China relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/british-energy-secretary-visit-china-march-restart-energy-talks-meet-investors-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6CE2JYSP5OMNJKCV65TJBA2SI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 04:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受中国钢铁出口担忧影响，铁矿石将出现月度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国关税担忧和针对中国钢铁出口的贸易摩擦加剧的打压，铁矿石期货价格周五下跌，并将出现小幅月度跌幅。【原文：Iron ore futures prices fell on Friday and were set for modest monthly losses, pressured by U.S. tariff concerns and mounting trade frictions against Chinese steel exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/iron-ore-set-monthly-loss-china-steel-export-concerns-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MORNXDOQSFIPDBB3AXQ6SEOQ3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 TPG 电信公司因盈利向好而创下四个月以来的最高纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，澳大利亚 TPG 电信公司的股价飙升至四个多月来的新高，该公司在截至 12 月 31 日的一年中基本盈利增长了 3.4%，达到 19.9 亿澳元（12.4 亿美元）。【原文：Shares of Australia's TPG Telecom surged to a more-than-four-month high on Friday after the telco logged a 3.4% rise in its underlying earnings to A$1.99 billion ($1.24 billion) for the year ended December 31.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australias-tpg-telecom-hits-four-month-peak-upbeat-earnings-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MB6OECEJZFNY3JDMGAWPJSS6LA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国制造业活动将在 2 月份连续第二个月萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[2 月份，中国的工厂活动可能连续第二个月萎缩，在制造商为美国新关税做准备之际，要求采取更多刺激措施以支撑世界第二大经济体低迷的内需的呼声依然不绝于耳。【原文：China's factory activity likely contracted for a second month in February, keeping alive calls for even more stimulus to prop up depressed domestic demand in the world's second-largest economy as manufacturers brace for fresh U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-manufacturing-activity-set-contract-second-month-feb-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLHQJKKGWVNWXIVFVC6Z32MAXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:17:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币下滑超过 5%，跌至 11 月 11 日以来最低水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关税计划和加密货币政策不确定性的拖累，以及竞争对手加密货币以太坊被黑客攻击15亿美元后投资者信心下滑的影响，比特币周五跌至3个半月以来的最低水平。【原文：Bitcoin dropped to its lowest level in 3-1/2 months on Friday, dragged by uncertainty about U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff plans and crypto policy and flagging investor confidence after a $1.5 billion hack in rival crypto currency ether.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-slides-more-than-5-lowest-level-since-november-11-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IY4VROBC3JKRDCZ6PIZNJH3OKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计上半年亏损 8.75 亿美元，新世界发展债务偿还成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[受房地产长期低迷和利息成本高企的影响，过去三年一直与流动性压力作斗争的香港新世界发展将于周五公布中期净亏损高达 8.75 亿美元。【原文：Hong Kong's New World Development , which has been battling liquidity stress for the past three years, is set to report an interim net loss of up to $875 million on Friday, hurt by a prolonged property downturn and high interest costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/new-world-developments-debt-repayment-focus-amid-875-million-expected-h1-loss-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIOTU2X2P5NLVKUGSD4UR4Z6WA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:41:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首尔：韩美两国财政部长讨论关税、投资和外汇问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部周五表示，韩国代总统兼财政部长崔相木与美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特在视频通话中讨论了关税、投资和外汇政策。【原文：South Korea's acting President and Finance Minister Choi Sang-mok and U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent discussed tariffs, investment and forex policy in a video call, South Korea's finance ministry said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-us-finance-chiefs-discuss-tariffs-investment-fx-says-seoul-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYDFH6ZWXBLFXL6QYV66ADHU4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税威胁引发市场动荡，股市暴跌，美元走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心全球贸易战升级，市场情绪低落，周五亚洲股市暴跌，美元兑该国主要贸易伙伴货币的汇率徘徊在数周高点附近。【原文：Equities slumped in Asia on Friday and the U.S. dollar hovered near multi-week highs against the currencies of the country's top trading partners as concerns about an escalating global trade war soured market sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFFTYPYL3FJTFKF57YS7MEQ52Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 02:12:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受经济不确定性影响，石油价格将出现 11 月以来的首次月度下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，油价下跌，创下自11月以来的首次月度跌幅，原因是华盛顿的关税威胁和美国经济放缓的进一步迹象给全球经济增长和燃料需求带来的不确定性超过了对供应的担忧。【原文：Oil prices eased on Friday, heading for their first monthly drop since November, as uncertainty over global economic growth and fuel demand from Washington's tariff threats and further signs of a U.S. economic slowdown outweighed supply concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-heads-first-monthly-drop-since-november-economic-uncertainty-weighs-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UCNHNSXWVOMXNNAEBV2TCVV2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:43:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税在即，美元走强，日元将实现月度上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）即将征收关税之前，美元在周五获得了避险支撑，但由于投资者将这些威胁与日益暗淡的美国经济增长前景进行权衡，美元仍将面临月度跌幅。【原文：The dollar drew safe-haven support on Friday ahead of U.S. President Donald Trump's impending tariffs, though was still headed for a monthly loss as investors weighed those threats against a darkening U.S. growth outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-firms-trumps-tariffs-loom-yen-set-monthly-gain-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLB2BYLNYZN6JBQVUXOOVVSFMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:33:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[敦促中国高瞻远瞩，努力重振疲软的消费]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coco Wen 利用中国的消费补贴政策，以大约原价三分之二的价格为自己购买了一部新 iPhone。与此同时，她还减少了其他方面的开支。【原文：Coco Wen took advantage of China's consumer subsidies to buy herself a new iPhone for about two thirds of the original price. At the same time, she's cutting spending on other things.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-urged-think-big-go-hard-reviving-battered-consumption-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJT3YN74HBNH5N6YLMRUFWEVWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:05:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能机器人可能是护理日本老龄人口的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近，在东京，一个人工智能驱动的机器人俯身在一名仰卧的男子身上，轻轻地将一只手放在他的膝盖上，另一只手放在他的肩膀上，然后将他翻到自己的一侧--这种动作用于给老人换尿布或预防褥疮。【原文：Recently in Tokyo an AI-driven robot leaned over a man lying on his back and gently put a hand on his knee and another on a shoulder and rolled him onto his side -- a manoeuvre used to change diapers or prevent bedsores in the elderly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-robots-may-hold-key-nursing-japans-ageing-population-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHG2XGFXZNPO7PHGPE5LNBBBWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 1 月份工厂产出月率下降 1.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周五公布的数据显示，日本 1 月份工厂产出环比下降 1.1%，与市场预测中值下降 1.2%基本一致。【原文：Japan's factory output fell 1.1% in January from the previous month, roughly in line with a median market forecast for a 1.2% decline, government data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-january-factory-output-falls-11-month-on-month-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRMAPARHHJO4FPBAMDEQV3EE5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[坠机事件悬而未决，航空安全报告受到审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[下个月是中国东方航空公司一架喷气式客机坠入山坡造成 132 人死亡的三年。【原文：Next month marks three years since a China Eastern jet plunged into a hillside killing 132 people, with relatives still waiting to learn what caused China's deadliest air disaster in three decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-safety-reporting-under-scrutiny-crashes-lie-unresolved-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJTH4YQKWBNJHCB5VZUH6AV5TU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:52:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首都核心通胀放缓，但仍高于日本央行目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，日本首都 2 月份的核心消费价格同比上涨 2.2%，这是四个月来首次因能源补贴恢复而放缓，但仍远高于央行 2% 的目标。【原文：Core consumer prices in Japan's capital rose 2.2% in February from a year earlier, data showed on Friday, slowing for the first time in four months due to revived energy subsidies but remaining well above the central bank's 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/core-inflation-japans-capital-slows-february-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7JKZYMWGNPIFIMMP5LJIJRIDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:49:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公司称，加州野火基金可使爱迪生公司资产负债表免受火灾索赔影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱迪生公司首席执行官周四表示，如果爱迪生国际电力公司拥有的设备被发现导致了上个月洛杉矶的一场致命火灾，那么加州 210 亿美元的野火基金可能会保护爱迪生国际电力公司的资产负债表。【原文：California's $21 billion wildfire fund may shield Edison International's balance sheet if equipment owned by the company's electric utility is found to have caused a deadly Los Angeles fire last month, Edison's CEO said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/california-wildfire-fund-may-shield-edison-balance-sheet-fire-claims-company-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z7OQ2AQXERLD3CD6ULLDZBUTMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚赌场运营商星际娱乐公司股票暂时停牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚证券交易所周五表示，澳大利亚赌场运营商 Star Entertainment 的股票已暂时停牌。【原文：Australian casino operator Star Entertainment's shares have been temporarily halted, the Australian Stock Exchange said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australian-casino-operator-star-entertainments-shares-temporarily-halted-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRESE3X4FBIRFGEF76GN6MX7HQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大隐私监管机构在接到投诉后对 X 展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大隐私监管机构在接到投诉后，对社交媒体平台 X 是否遵守联邦隐私法展开了调查。【原文：Canada's privacy watchdog has opened an investigation into the social media platform X's compliance with federal privacy law after receiving a complaint.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/canadas-privacy-watchdog-opens-investigation-into-x-following-complaint-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATRLQUA7VJOBPLQ5NZBNKP3WOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国科技初创企业竞相利用 DeepSeek 热和习近平会晤的契机]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着 DeepSeek 引发的人工智能热潮，以及习近平主席最近对中国民营企业的支持，中国科技初创企业正竞相筹集新的资金。【原文：Chinese technology startups are racing for fresh fundraising to capitalise on the DeepSeek-induced fervor towards artificial intelligence, as well as President Xi Jinping's recent show of support to the country's private enterprises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/china-tech-startups-race-capitalise-deepseek-fever-xis-meeting-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N734V35HGRMUHBEKYLVBQV35GE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[设计软件需求稳定，欧特克预计全年收入乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[受建筑和制造等行业对其设计和工程软件的强劲需求推动，欧特克公司周四预计全年营收和利润将高于华尔街预期。【原文：Autodesk forecast annual revenue and profit above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, boosted by strong demand for its design and engineering software across industries such as construction and manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/autodesk-forecasts-upbeat-annual-revenue-steady-design-software-demand-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIQVUNIVXFMPREVSWO3LTQA43U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 22:51:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，高盛选中 Elizabeth Overbay 担任资产管理业务首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份备忘录，高盛任命 Elizabeth Overbay 为其资产和财富管理部门的首席财务官，从而加强了这家华尔街巨头在其重点领域的力量。【原文：Goldman Sachs appointed Elizabeth Overbay as the chief financial officer of its asset and wealth management division, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Thursday, bolstering ranks in a key area of focus for the Wall Street giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-picks-elizabeth-overbay-cfo-asset-management-business-memo-says-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HEE4YXMTZNUBNRA7BGFML6B2A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 22:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西检察官调查桑坦德银行高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西联邦检察官已对伊塔乌国民银行（Itau Unibanco）一名前高管涉嫌挪用资金展开调查，该高管将在未来几个月内在西班牙桑坦德银行 [RIC:RIC:SOVAN.UL]担任要职。【原文：Brazil's federal prosecutors have launched an investigation into alleged fund diversion by a former senior executive at Itau Unibanco , set to take a key role at Spanish bank Santander [RIC:RIC:SOVBAN.UL] in coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazilian-prosecutors-investigate-top-santander-executive-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2TJSSUO4RIMTEXZFBRJUXHMOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 22:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 为部分付费用户推出 GPT-4.5，下周将扩大访问范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[ChatGPT 开发商 OpenAI 周四表示，它已面向全球专业用户和开发人员发布了最新 GPT-4.5 模型的研究预览版，并计划在未来几周内扩大访问范围。【原文：ChatGPT developer OpenAI said on Thursday it has released a research preview of its latest GPT-4.5 model for its Pro users and developers worldwide, with plans to expand access in the coming weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-rolls-out-gpt-45-some-paying-users-expand-access-next-week-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6O5DUVZGRBKBPPT2SULQKXBYK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 22:21:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>