<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:37:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:37:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部干预后，花旗做多阿根廷 BONTE 30 指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行周四表示，在美国财政部采取干预措施支撑阿根廷货币后，该行将做多阿根廷 BONTE 30 债券。【原文：Citi said on Thursday it was going long into Argentina's BONTE 30 bonds following intervention by the U.S. Treasury to shore up the country's currency, adding it saw room for local assets to continue gains ahead of a key legislative vote.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/citi-is-going-long-argentina-bonte-30-after-us-treasury-intervention-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDI7IODLMFOE7BFBJKYRXP6RXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[李维斯-斯特劳斯（Levi Strauss）上调年度销售额和利润预期，原因是牛仔布需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 周四上调了全年销售额和利润预期，原因是尽管关税提高，但欧洲和美洲市场对阔腿牛仔裤的需求强劲。【原文：Levi Strauss raised its full-year sales and profit forecasts on Thursday, banking on strong demand for wide-leg denim bottoms in Europe and the Americas despite higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-lifts-annual-sales-profit-forecasts-resilient-denim-demand-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JPJFAWVPZKX5IFIG5UFCBCR7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国资金外流对 "成长型 "股票基金打击最大，全球 "价值型 "基金倾斜加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[基金经理们表示，越来越多的全球投资者开始转向非美国的 "价值型 "股票，因为美国的估值捉襟见肘、财政紧张加剧以及现金流预测减弱，使得美国股市的涨势看起来相对不那么吸引人。【原文：More global investors are rotating into non-U.S. "value" stocks, fund managers say, as stretched U.S. valuations, rising fiscal strains, and weakening cash flow forecasts make rallying American equities look comparatively less attractive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-value-tilt-intensifies-us-outflows-hit-growth-stock-funds-hardest-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CFVRVFUNBMD5JTLZFJIITHI3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 向欧盟监管机构表达竞争关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周四表示，它上个月向欧盟当局提交的论据反映了其关于人工智能领域竞争的公开声明，尤其是在对 Alphabet 旗下谷歌公司进行反垄断调查的背景下。【原文：OpenAI said on Thursday the arguments it presented to EU authorities last month mirrored its public statements about competition in the AI space, particularly in the context of antitrust investigations into Alphabet's Google.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/openai-flags-competition-concerns-eu-regulators-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITIQUA7G4VLTDOOAJ3U4F5K3XA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:15:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司利润增长放缓，人工智能支出成焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公司第三季度的盈利增长可能会比今年早些时候温和，部分原因是可能会受到关税打击，同时投资者也在寻找人工智能方面的大量支出正在得到回报的迹象。【原文：U.S. companies could report milder earnings growth in the third quarter than earlier this year, partly due to a likely tariff hit, while investors look for signs that heavy spending on artificial intelligence is paying off.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-companies-profit-growth-seen-softer-spotlight-ai-spending-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DU4WVLYYLNNNZJMI6ZBNLYPQAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：美国在高级财政官员会议后购买了阿根廷比索]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，本周两国高级财政官员在华盛顿举行会议后，美国购买了阿根廷比索，并与阿根廷中央银行敲定了一项价值 200 亿美元的货币互换框架。【原文：The United States purchased Argentine pesos and finalized a $20 billion currency swap framework with Argentina's central bank after a meeting between the two countries' top finance officials in Washington this week, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-purchased-argentine-pesos-after-top-finance-officials-meeting-bessent-says-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JA5VBMYMWNJK5AZKKW7FAF56TY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称今年万圣节美国巧克力价格仍将居高不下]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行农业食品研究所（Wells Fargo's Agri-Food Institute）周四发布的一份报告显示，由于可可成本自 2024 年初以来翻了一番多，美国巧克力消费者在即将到来的万圣节期间将面临巧克力价格上涨的问题。【原文：U.S. chocolate consumers will face elevated chocolate prices this coming Halloween period as cocoa costs have more than doubled since early 2024, according to a report released on Thursday by Wells Fargo's Agri-Food Institute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chocolate-prices-set-remain-high-this-halloween-us-report-says-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GHMPO7VFIZLHFP4GOFWON2IJAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:49:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示数千用户的 Microsoft 365 出现故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 的数据，周四有数千名用户的微软生产力软件套件出现故障。【原文：Microsoft's suite of productivity software was down for thousands of users on Thursday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-365-down-thousands-users-downdetector-shows-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HB3K4FPIU5LXDNV3MNCTQFLDTE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，美国司法部对 First Brands 倒闭展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引知情人士的话报道称，美国司法部已对破产汽车零部件制造商 First Brands 集团的倒闭展开调查。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice has launched an inquiry into the collapse of bankrupt auto parts maker First Brands Group, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-justice-department-opens-inquiry-into-first-brands-ft-reports-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIJGFICGLZIDRNAGMNMXQJBRTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:40:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国前首相苏纳克加入微软和 Anthropic，担任顾问职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国前首相苏纳克（Rishi Sunak）周四表示，他已加入美国科技巨头微软和人工智能初创公司 Anthropic，担任高级顾问。【原文：Former British Prime Minister Rishi Sunak said on Thursday he has joined U.S. tech giant Microsoft and AI startup Anthropic as a senior adviser.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/former-british-pm-sunak-joins-microsoft-anthropic-advisory-roles-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXSOL75JMZMLHJSS6GTBWMNVDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alliance Laundry 首次登陆纽交所，股价上涨，估值达 48 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alliance Laundry Systems 周四在纽约首次上市时股价大涨 11.4%，估值接近 48.3 亿美元，使这家商用洗衣机生产商成为最新一家利用繁荣上市市场的公司。【原文：Alliance Laundry Systems was valued at nearly $4.83 billion after its shares jumped 11.4% in their New York debut on Thursday, making the commercial laundry machine maker the latest to capitalize on a buoyant listings market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/alliance-laundry-systems-valued-48-billion-shares-rise-nyse-debut-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QB3MUL4MJZNITBMI4R4FZVHLVM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国与沙特芯片协议可能很快敲定]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，美国和沙特阿拉伯正在推进一项允许美国芯片公司向沙特阿拉伯出口半导体的协议，该协议可能很快就会敲定。【原文：The U.S. and Saudi Arabia are advancing on an agreement that would allow U.S. chip companies to export semiconductors to Saudi Arabia and a deal could be finalized soon, the Wall Street Journal reported Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/us-saudi-chips-agreement-could-be-finalized-soon-wsj-reports-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OCNTPBQQFMBPL5BHZTXCALSYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:11:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[偏空 ETF 因押注股市回调而大量流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[偏空的交易所交易基金押注于股指以及科技和人工智能等快速上涨的行业，正吸引着大量资金流入，因为高昂的价格和政策风险刺激一些投资者为回调做准备。【原文：Short-bias exchange-traded funds, which bet against stock indexes and fast-rising sectors like technology and artificial intelligence, are drawing strong inflows as lofty prices and policy risks spur some investors to position for a pullback.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-shortbias-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QPL6XPR6FJMZHYMET3CQA6QFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[每个电子都很重要可再生能源股票为何重获关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[资金重新流入可再生能源股票，为这些公司的股票注入了新的活力，推动了这些股票自本十年初可持续发展热潮以来最强劲的季度上涨。【原文：A return of fund inflows into renewable energy stocks is helping to breath new life into these companies' shares, powering their strongest quarterly rise since the sustainability boom early this decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/every-electron-counts-why-renewables-stocks-are-back-play-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32B7XZXRVFKGXNGDGLDSTH5NEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期固定抵押贷款利率下降，潜在购房者保持观望态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国抵押贷款利率本周有所下降，但不确定的经济前景和不温不火的招聘使潜在购房者保持观望。【原文：U.S. mortgage rates fell this week, but an uncertain economic outlook and tepid hiring are keeping prospective homebuyers on the sidelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-30-year-fixed-mortgage-rate-falls-prospective-buyers-stay-sidelines-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NS2HZCSDPZOZLOMX342FIVT3TQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴尔称，美联储应谨慎对待降息，因为存在通胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）理事迈克尔-巴尔（Michael Barr）周四发表讲话称，美国央行应在进一步降息的问题上谨慎行事，他在讲话中大力强调了通胀风险，同时也承认 "大致平衡 "的劳动力市场存在潜在的脆弱性。【原文：The U.S. central bank should move cautiously on further interest rate cuts, Federal Reserve Governor Michael Barr said on Thursday, in a speech that leaned heavily into the risks of inflation, even as he acknowledged the potential vulnerabilities in a "roughly balanced" labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-should-be-cautious-due-inflation-risks-barr-says-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOR7RR63LRJHDN47OF4OFW6BFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯利康耗资 45 亿美元的弗吉尼亚工厂破土动工，制药商纷纷讨好特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康（AstraZeneca）位于弗吉尼亚州的新工厂周四破土动工，并表示将斥资 45 亿美元建造该工厂，制药商们希望响应唐纳德-特朗普总统的号召，以更低的成本在美国生产更多的药品。【原文：AstraZeneca broke ground on a new plant in Virginia on Thursday and said it would spend $4.5 billion on the facility as drugmakers look to respond to President Donald Trump's call for more medicines to be made in the U.S. and at lower costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-breaks-ground-45-billion-virginia-plant-drugmakers-court-trump-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQIGZXAP4VJSXLJ6Q463DBND2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国药店和药品折扣店正与政府讨论 TrumpRx 的作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[零售药店和处方药储蓄网站 GoodRx 正在与特朗普政府商讨加入其 TrumpRx 网站的事宜，他们告诉路透社，这表明该网站的范围将扩大，而不是像早期描述的那样，只是一个与制药公司直接折扣的链接。【原文：Retail pharmacies and prescription drug savings site GoodRx are talking with the Trump administration about joining its TrumpRx website, they told Reuters, suggesting an expansion beyond the early description of it as a link to pharmaceutical companies' direct discounts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-pharmacies-drug-discounters-are-discussing-trumprx-role-with-administration-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">US3ORWE6FFOGRLSNUKSDOOQ4FY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:27:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凤凰城大学首次登陆纽交所，股价飙升，估值达 13.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[凤凰城教育合伙公司（Phoenix Education Partners）周四在纽约证券交易所首次公开发行股票，股价大涨 18.8%，凤凰城大学所有者的估值达到 13.5 亿美元，因为它经受住了美国政府停摆的考验，进入了蓬勃发展的 IPO 市场。【原文：Phoenix Education Partners shares jumped 18.8% in their New York Stock Exchange debut on Thursday, valuing the University of Phoenix owner at $1.35 billion as it weathered a U.S. government shutdown to tap a booming IPO market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/university-phoenix-owner-valued-over-13-billion-shares-jump-nyse-debut-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2EXUMYM6ZJNBAVXP5FYXS2VLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车重新推出经济型博尔特电动车]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）周四表示，该公司将重新推出价格低廉的 Bolt 电动汽车，因为这家底特律汽车制造商希望扩大其在电动汽车领域的产品范围。【原文：General Motors said on Thursday it was bringing its affordable Bolt electric vehicle back, as the Detroit automaker looks to widen its offerings in the space.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-relaunches-affordable-bolt-ev-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBGKQQ2ZPJPTZNQCV4TH7U2OTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MercadoLibre 收购首家药店后将进军巴西在线医药市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉丁美洲电子商务公司 MercadoLibre 当地负责人周四表示，该公司将通过其在巴西新收购的药店试水在线药品销售，这是进军巴西数十亿美元在线医药市场的第一步。【原文：Latin American e-commerce firm MercadoLibre will test the waters for online pharmaceutical sales through its newly acquired drugstore in Brazil, the company's local head said on Thursday, a first step in entering the country's multi-billion-dollar online medicine market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mercadolibre-enter-brazils-online-medicine-market-after-acquiring-first-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMRPDKWFGFKDFJLZXGFMIDSIPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大统计局警告称贸易数据可能因美国政府停摆而延迟发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大联邦统计局周四表示，如果美国政府停摆持续下去，该局可能不得不推迟在下个月发布九月份的国际贸易数据。【原文：Canada's federal statistics agency said on Thursday it might have to postpone releasing September international trade data next month if the U.S. government shutdown drags on.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/canadas-stats-agency-warns-trade-data-could-be-delayed-by-us-government-shutdown-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYJO7DSVQ5O4VFPVZGYEX4IQTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:54:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行拒绝墨西哥集团竞购 Banamex 分公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团（Citigroup）周四拒绝了墨西哥矿业和运输集团墨西哥集团（Grupo Mexico）对其在墨西哥的零售部门（即 Banamex）的竞购，而是选择推进之前达成的交易。【原文：Citigroup on Thursday rejected Mexican mining and transport conglomerate Grupo Mexico's bid for its retail unit in the country, known as Banamex, opting instead to push forward with a previously agreed-upon deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-rejects-grupo-mexico-bid-banamex-unit-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BJV5FXE5BLU3IYOFXFWWQZBPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[非洲贸易集团东南非共同市场推出数字支付系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[东部和南部非洲共同市场（Common Market for Eastern and Southern Africa）周四表示，该市场已推出数字支付系统，允许企业以当地货币结算交易，从而降低交易成本。【原文：The Common Market for Eastern and Southern Africa has launched a digital payments system to cut transaction costs by allowing businesses to settle deals in local currencies, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/african-trade-bloc-comesa-launches-digital-payments-system-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCFZMBDF75NBLKLXIHIREZKU4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:51:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[致命矿难发生后，智利 Codelco 公司 8 月份铜产量下滑 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[铜业委员会 Cochilco 周四提供的数据显示，智利国营矿业公司 Codelco 8 月份的铜产量下降了 25%，此前该公司盈利能力最强的矿山发生了致命的坍塌事故，导致产量受阻。【原文：Copper production from Chilean state-run miner Codelco tumbled 25% in August, data from copper commission Cochilco showed on Thursday, after a deadly collapse stunted output from its most-profitable mine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/copper-output-chiles-codelco-slides-25-august-after-deadly-mine-accident-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJWGV3IFCJI2RKUU6EKODUHOFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金突破 4000 美元/盎司，巩固全球风向标地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[黄金本周以前所未有的速度跃上每盎司 4,000 美元的里程碑，使其有望在今年取得自 1979 年伊朗革命以来的最好成绩，巩固其作为全球地缘政治和经济晴雨表的地位。【原文：Gold's unprecedented ascent this week to the $4,000 an ounce milestone and beyond puts it on course for its best year since the Iranian Revolution in 1979, solidifying its status as a barometer for global geopolitics and the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/golds-rush-above-4000oz-cements-status-global-bellwether-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LRYHQCTXX5OW3O222POIQ5ZHC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，德国 PSI 软件公司接近被收购，投资者正在围观]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士周四告诉路透社，德国 PSI 软件公司即将被收购，多家金融投资者正在围攻这家能源网络软件制造商。【原文：Germany's PSI Software is close to being taken over, with several financial investors circling the maker of software for energy networks, three people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/germanys-psi-software-nears-takeover-investors-circle-say-sources-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYPYLTAMPJONPO7CC4QBR6WO7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在中国注册更长距离的 "Model Y+"计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据中国工业部网站周四公布的申报信息，电动汽车制造商特斯拉已计划在中国推出续航里程更长的Model Y车型。【原文：EV-maker Tesla has registered plans for a longer-range variant of its Model Y in China, according to filing information that appeared on China's industry ministry website on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-registers-plans-longer-range-model-y-china-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHM5IJYILRM5NI6O4LJANRA7QM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股票估值过高引发投资者对市场泡沫的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街股市的大幅反弹引发了投资者对泡沫形成的担忧，这可能导致股市大幅回调。【原文：The steep rally in Wall Street stocks is sparking worries among investors of a bubble forming, which could lead to a significant correction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/high-stock-valuations-sparking-investor-worries-about-market-bubble-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTNIDMGBOFNOJCGHOWYMQ4SZCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达支持的 Reflection AI 获得 20 亿美元融资，估值升至 80 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）支持的初创公司 Reflection AI 周四表示，该公司在新一轮融资中筹集了 20 亿美元，估值达 80 亿美元，投资者对人工智能的兴趣有增无减。【原文：Reflection AI, a startup backed by Nvidia, said on Thursday it has raised $2 billion in a new funding round that values the company at $8 billion, as investor interest in artificial intelligence remains unabated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-backed-reflection-ai-raises-2-billion-funding-boosts-valuation-8-billion-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNZODQRUYNPZREHF4DDS7PPBGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>