<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 04:06:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 04:06:54 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[奥地利地产大亨雷内-本科（Rene Benko）欺诈案即将开庭审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥地利前亿万富翁雷内-本科（Rene Benko）将于本周二出庭受审，这是他的地产集团 Signa 倒闭后的第一起案件。【原文：Austrian former billionaire Rene Benko goes on trial on Tuesday in the first case tackling the collapse of his property group Signa, which at its peak acquired stakes in New York's Chrysler Building and the British department-store chain Selfridges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/austrian-fraud-trial-property-tycoon-rene-benko-set-open-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4DLIUCNQNIBHF54WPG7RZV624</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 04:06:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片供应商 ASML 将搭乘人工智能巨头的顺风车]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能公司与计算机芯片制造商之间的数十亿美元交易有望在本周三公布的第三季度财报中增强顶级半导体设备制造商 ASML 的前景。【原文：Multi-billion dollar deals between AI firms and computer chipmakers are expected to strengthen top semiconductor equipment maker ASML's outlook when it reports third-quarter earnings on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chipmaking-supplier-asml-set-ride-ai-megadeals-wave-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CM5QRSC7ZJCXKO7F27HVIBLS4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 04:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度纺织品出口商转向欧洲，提供折扣以抵消美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度纺织品出口商正在欧洲寻找新的买家，并向现有的美国客户提供折扣，以减轻美国高达 50%的陡峭关税带来的打击。【原文：Indian textile exporters are seeking new buyers in Europe and offering discounts to existing U.S. customers to cushion the blow from steep U.S. tariffs of as much as 50%, industry executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-textile-exporters-turn-europe-offer-discounts-offset-us-tariffs-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4I2QTJVOIZJ7DHUPAWOM467MYM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 03:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，西班牙是中国汽车制造商比亚迪在欧洲建立第三家工厂的首选之地]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士告诉路透社，中国第一大汽车制造商比亚迪认为西班牙是其建立第三家汽车厂以服务欧洲市场的首选之地，因为该公司正寻求在欧洲大陆扩大销售。【原文：China's No. 1 automaker BYD considers Spain to be its top candidate for a third car factory to serve the European market, two people briefed on the matter told Reuters, as the company seeks to grow sales on the continent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/spain-frontrunner-chinese-carmaker-byds-third-european-plant-sources-say-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPNP547EZNNODC7YEH7PBCC3AE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 03:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌将投资 100 亿美元在南印度建设数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度安得拉邦的一位部长表示，Alphabet 公司旗下的谷歌公司将投资 100 亿美元，在印度南部的安得拉邦建立一个 1 千兆瓦的数据中心。【原文：Alphabet Inc's Google will invest $10 billion to set up a 1-gigawatt data centre in the southern Indian state of Andhra Pradesh, a state minister said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/google-invest-10-billion-data-centre-south-india-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYRE7R5JIJP7DNPBXROAXJKFKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 02:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲市场在华尔街复苏之际奋力上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，亚洲股市出现试探性反弹，在有迹象表明中美贸易谈判仍在按部就班进行之后，各地区股市出现了不均衡的复苏。【原文：Asian stocks made a tentative rebound in early trade on Tuesday, with an uneven recovery taking place across regional equity markets after signs that trade negotiations between the U.S. and China remain on track.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BJZLVHNSVI5FKYTTZ7KYSGGSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美缓和贸易紧张局势，石油价格上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，油价上涨，因为中美贸易紧张局势解冻的早期迹象提振了市场情绪，缓解了对全球燃料需求的担忧。【原文：Oil prices rose on Tuesday as early signs of a thaw in U.S.-China trade tensions bolstered market sentiment, alleviating concerns over global fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-edges-up-us-china-de-escalate-trade-tensions-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHB3HYZKEZPVLLDIKBTUXFVPHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易摩擦再起的担忧减弱，美元反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周二持稳，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普淡化了对中国征收关税的言论，而且他可能与中国总统会晤，这使人们对这两个经济重镇之间的紧张局势有望缓和产生了希望。【原文：The dollar held steady on Tuesday as U.S. President Donald Trump's watered down rhetoric against tariffs on China and a potential meeting with his Chinese counterpart raised hopes of de-escalation in tensions between the two economic heavyweights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dollar-rebounds-fears-renewed-us-china-trade-feud-abate-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWLBVTSFOJLBTHAJOVZATWZTOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行将保持谨慎，数据取决于未来政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社悉尼10月14日电）澳大利亚央行在9月份的政策会议上认为，鉴于服务业通胀的一些粘性和稳定的就业，没有必要立即降息，而未来的宽松政策将取决于数据。【原文：SYDNEY, Oct 14 (Reuters) - Australia's central bank saw no need for an immediate cut in interest rates at its September policy meeting given some stickiness in services inflation and steady employment, while future easing would be data dependent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-be-cautious-data-dependent-future-policy-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6XDD2YCWNMOZAMLYG7QQVEIXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示：澳大利亚九月份商业活动保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项调查显示，由于销售和利润的增长被就业人数的下降所抵消，澳大利亚九月份的商业状况保持稳定。【原文：Australian business conditions remained steady in September as improvements in sales and profits were offset by a fall in employment, a survey showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-business-activity-holds-steady-september-survey-shows-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRL7CQBGM5JL7BLHMTRYDMUTTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美将推出针锋相对的港口费，海上动荡恐将加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国周二将开始向运输从节日玩具到原油等各种物品的远洋运输公司收取港口费，使公海成为世界两大经济体之间贸易战的一个关键战场。【原文：The United States and China on Tuesday will begin charging port fees on ocean shipping firms that move everything from holiday toys to crude oil, making the high seas a key front in the trade war between the world's two largest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-roll-out-tit-for-tat-port-fees-threatening-more-turmoil-sea-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGBMOXT5QJIKDPFQVTWAHFGUIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔预计未来十年公务机交付量将创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空航天供应商霍尼韦尔周一表示，预计未来十年新商务喷气机的交付量将创下历史新高，这是私人航空旅行需求保持稳定的最新迹象。【原文：Aerospace supplier Honeywell said on Monday it expects record deliveries of new business jets over the next decade, providing the latest sign that demand for private air travel, which surged during the COVID-19 pandemic, is holding up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/honeywell-expects-record-business-jet-deliveries-over-next-decade-2025-10-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3IHVMYFJFOCDLMDVMQN3GPRYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国开始向美国船只收取港口费，中国建造的船只免收费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家广播电视公司（CCTV）报道，中国已于周二正式开始向美国拥有、经营、建造或悬挂美国国旗的船只征收特别港口费，但表示中国建造的船只将免于征收。【原文：China has officially started collecting special port fees from U.S.-owned, operated, built, or flagged vessels on Tuesday but said Chinese-built ships would be exempted from the levies, according to state broadcaster CCTV.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-begins-charging-port-fees-us-ships-exempts-china-built-ones-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A52OJPPCUFMR3OWPZA4WQ6KVQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行将放宽住房贷款规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰央行周二表示，计划从12月1日起放宽按揭贷款价值比（LVR）限制，因为房价在持续下跌后目前已达到可持续的估计值。【原文：New Zealand's central bank on Tuesday said it planned to ease mortgage loan-to-value ratio (LVR) restrictions from December 1 as house prices are now with sustainable estimates after a sustained fall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-central-bank-ease-home-lending-rules-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZB7DTLWS2VKPFFPH5VPOCNPZZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:22:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通称杠杆 ETF 加剧了周五的华尔街大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通美洲股票衍生品策略团队周日晚些时候发布的一份报告显示，杠杆式交易所交易基金的大规模抛售在很大程度上导致了周五美国股市的暴跌。【原文：Large-scale selling of leveraged exchange-traded funds contributed significantly to Friday's U.S. stock market rout, according to a report published late on Sunday by JPMorgan's Americas equities derivatives strategy team.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-says-leveraged-etfs-worsened-fridays-wall-st-selloff-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOACTMIQ7BNE3ONPLWHGIGRB6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[重大 "网络事件增加 50%，英国警告企业领导者]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国国家网络安全中心（NCSC）负责人将于本周二表示，被列为 "高度重大 "的英国网络事件比一年前增加了 50%。
最近几个月发生的一系列网络攻击已导致包括玛莎百货（Marks & Spencer）、Co-op 和捷豹路虎（JLR）在内的一些英国最大的品牌断网。
"NCSC首席执行官理查德-霍恩（Richard Horne）将在伦敦举行的年度审查发布会上说："每个领导者，无论你是厨房餐桌上的一个人，还是成千上万人的老板，你都必须有一个抵御犯罪网络攻击的计划。
在截至今年 8 月的 12 个月里，英国国家计算机安全委员会（NCSC）应邀协助处理了 429 起网络事件，其中一半被认为具有 "国家意义"。
霍恩说，其中 18 起被列为 "高度重大"，因为它们 "对中央政府、英国基本服务、英国大部分人口或英国经济造成了严重影响"。
英国科学、创新与技术新闻部在一份声明中说，部长们已经致函公司，包括富时指数最大的350家公司，敦促它们了解可以获得哪些支持，并将网络恢复能力作为董事会层面的责任。
英国国家计算机安全委员会称，截至2025年8月的一年中，该委员会共处理了204起最严重的三类攻击，比前一年的89起增加了一倍多。
这让人们看到了企业，尤其是供应链中的小企业的应变能力，如果客户无法运营，这些企业可能更容易突然失去订单和付款。
据分析师估计，JLR 因停产每周损失约 5000 万英镑，在停产近六周后，上周重新开始了部分生产。
这家豪华汽车制造商隶属于印度塔塔汽车公司（Tata Motors），英国政府在 9 月底为其提供了 15 亿英镑的贷款担保，以帮助其支持供应商。
"如果你的 IT 基础设施明天就瘫痪了，你的所有屏幕都变成了空白，你还能运行你的薪资系统，让你的机器继续运转，或者给你的货架上货吗？霍恩在演讲中说。
如果答案是 "不能"，或者更可能是 "不知道"，请立即行动起来。【原文：British cyber incidents classed as "highly significant" have risen by 50% over a year ago, the head of the country's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) will say on Tuesday.
A series of cyber attacks in recent months has knocked some of Britain's biggest brands, including Marks & Spencer , Co-op and Jaguar Land Rover (JLR), offline.
"Every leader, whether you're one person at your kitchen table  or the boss of thousands of people,  you must have a plan to defend against criminal cyberattacks," NCSC CEO Richard Horne is due to say at the launch of its annual review in London.
The NCSC, part of Britain's GCHQ spy agency, was asked to help with 429 cyber incidents in the 12 months to August, half of which were considered of "national significance".
Of those, Horne said, 18 were classed as "highly significant" because they had "serious impact on central government, UK essential services, a large proportion of the UK population, or the UK economy".
Ministers have written to companies, including the largest 350 on the FTSE Index, urging them to understand what support is available and to make cyber resilience a board-level responsibility, Britain's Department for Science, Innovation & Technology Press said in a statement.
The NCSC said it had dealt with 204 attacks in the three most serious categories in the year to August 2025, more than doubling from 89 the year before.
That has cast a light on the resilience of companies and particularly the smaller businesses in their supply chains, which may be more vulnerable to suddenly losing orders, and payments, if their clients are unable to operate.
JLR, which analysts estimated was losing around 50 million pounds per week from the shutdown, last week restarted some manufacturing after an almost six-week pause.
The luxury carmaker, owned by India's Tata Motors , was given a 1.5 billion pound loan guarantee by the British government in late September to help it support suppliers.
"If your IT infrastructure was crippled tomorrow  and all your screens went blank,  could you run your payroll systems, keep your machinery working, or stock your shelves? ," Horne said in his speech.
"If the answer is no, or more likely ‘don’t know’, act now".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-warns-business-leaders-highly-significant-cyber-incidents-rise-50-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEQ2TSTKHRPJTDK3G23PN4IRSQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西戈尔公司（Gol）计划提出重组方案，将其私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一公布的 11 月 4 日股东大会投票公告，巴西航空公司 Gol Linhas Aereas Inteligentes SA 计划私有化，作为公司重组进程的一部分。【原文：Brazilian airline Gol Linhas Aereas Inteligentes SA plans to go private as part of a corporate reorganization process, according to the voting bulletin for a November 4 shareholder meeting published on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-gol-plans-restructuring-proposal-that-would-take-it-private-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32SFAQA3IRLDZLKZ242HLE7KLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受人工智能芯片需求拉动，三星预计季度利润为三年多来最高]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子（Samsung Electronics）周二预计，由于传统存储芯片的需求帮助抵消了高带宽存储芯片销售的疲软，第三季度营业利润同比增长 32%，远高于分析师的预期。【原文：Samsung Electronics on Tuesday projected a 32% rise in third-quarter operating profit from a year earlier, well ahead of analysts' estimates, as demand for conventional memory chips helped offset weaker high bandwidth memory chip sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-elec-estimates-32-rise-q3-operating-profit-beating-expectations-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQFO5RZWGRPRRIXU3WRDDEU2WQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DHT 称其船队在中国收取新港口费后与美国没有联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[油轮运营商 DHT Holdings 周一表示，其船队不属于中国针对与美国有关联的船舶新征收的特别港口费的范围。【原文：Oil tanker operator DHT Holdings said on Monday that its fleet does not fall under the scope of China's new special port fees targeting U.S.-linked vessels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dht-says-its-fleet-has-no-us-links-after-chinas-new-port-fee-move-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVQJSNSUZ5PSHGCVA7HKVRUFJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓第三季度铁矿石发货量环比增长 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓（Rio Tinto）周二报告称，尽管计划中的大型维护活动和基础设施工程将在第四季度继续进行，但第三季度铁矿石发货量仍连续增长了 6%。【原文：Rio Tinto , reported a 6% sequential rise in third-quarter iron ore shipments on Tuesday, despite planned major maintenance activities and infrastructure works which will continue in the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rio-tintos-third-quarter-iron-ore-shipments-rise-6-sequentially-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAQPA5JS3NNXZKQE2BK3M4BU3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：鲍威尔访华，银行将开启盈利闸门]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSWBCTXSS5LDJOI3AZ5UUAQ2JM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能驱动升级，第三季度全球智能手机出货量上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际数据公司（International Data Corporation）周一发布的初步数据显示，受消费者对高端和人工智能设备强劲需求的推动，今年第三季度全球智能手机出货量增长了2.6%。【原文：Global smartphone shipments grew 2.6% in the third quarter this year, fueled by strong consumer demand for premium and AI-enabled devices, according to preliminary data from the International Data Corporation on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-smartphone-shipments-rise-third-quarter-ai-driven-upgrades-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAYGYEW4TFLOXCPKPYGZWN7BK4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛收购风险投资公司 Industry Ventures]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）周一表示，已同意收购管理着 70 亿美元资产的领先风险投资公司 Industry Ventures，以扩大对科技企业家的服务。【原文：Goldman Sachs has agreed to buy Industry Ventures, a leading venture capital firm that manages $7 billion of assets, in a bid to expand its services to technology entrepreneurs, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/goldman-sachs-buys-venture-capital-firm-industry-ventures-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7AGRQANMFLK5GRXFL44PVLKEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在创纪录的加密货币暴跌之后，人们急于对冲再次暴跌的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[继上周五发生史上最大规模的加密货币清算之后，期权市场投资者正在为比特币和以太坊的更大波动性和进一步下跌做好准备，积极进行交易定位，以防再次出现潜在的自由落体。【原文：Following the largest crypto liquidation in history last Friday, options market investors are bracing for more volatility and further declines in bitcoin and ether, aggressively positioning in trades that offer protection against another potential freefall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/after-record-crypto-crash-rush-hedge-against-another-freefall-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OR2SMEB6TVIXPCABGHX7SWQK2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对供应过剩的担忧加剧，美国石油期货后市跌幅收窄至 20 个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于欧佩克+增加供应，而美国炼油厂的季节性检修又对速冻原油桶的需求构成压力，美国前月原油期货周一以 2024 年 1 月以来对第七个月合约的最小溢价收盘。【原文：Front-month U.S. crude oil futures ended Monday's trading at their smallest premium since January 2024 over the seventh-month contract, as OPEC+ ramps up supply while seasonal refinery maintenance in the U.S. pressures demand for prompt barrels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-futures-backwardation-narrows-20-month-low-mounting-fears-glut-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CBWN7B3ABI2HP3E2A5FX6G2WE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织的格奥尔基耶娃说，各国缺乏人工智能的监管和道德基础]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周一表示，世界各国缺乏应对人工智能快速发展的监管和道德基础，她敦促民间社会团体 "敲响警钟"。【原文：Countries around the world lack the regulatory and ethical foundation to deal with the rapid advent of artificial intelligence, IMF chief Kristalina Georgieva said on Monday, urging civil society groups to "ring the alarm bells."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imfs-georgieva-says-countries-lack-regulatory-ethical-foundation-ai-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YF5YAQAVJRJPHHRIFMCHZAGBYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局喷气推进装置将裁员约 550 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局喷气推进实验室（NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory）周一表示，作为重组的一部分，该实验室将裁员近 550 人，这与美国政府目前的停摆无关。【原文：NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory said on Monday it will cut nearly 550 jobs as part of a restructuring, not related to the current U.S. government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/nasas-jet-propulsion-unit-lay-off-about-550-workers-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VOAMMJTMSRNXPPTBFRRRDYJ72A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[庞巴迪宣布 Comlux Aviation 成为环球 8000 商务喷气机的新客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大飞机制造商庞巴迪公司周一在美国国家公务航空协会年会上宣布，该公司的积压订单中又增加了一份来自Comlux Aviation公司的Global 8000公务机订单。【原文：Bombardier added a new order from Comlux Aviation for its Global 8000 business jet to its backlog, the Canadian planemaker announced on Monday during the National Business Aviation Association's annual conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/bombardier-announces-comlux-aviation-new-global-8000-business-jet-customer-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2LHD3RQFFPRDNU5X2UJIQO67I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪将克莱斯勒公司的信用评级展望定为负面]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评级机构穆迪评级公司（Moody's Ratings）周一将欧洲汽车制造商 Stellantis 的评级展望改为负面，但维持其目前的评级。【原文：Credit rating agency Moody's Ratings changed European automaker Stellantis' ratings outlook to negative on Monday, though maintained its current ratings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/moodys-puts-chrysler-owners-credit-ratings-negative-outlook-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZ5RSIZFVVOKJNSAZX42GP4RUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国贸易机构称关税不确定性可能抑制对小企业的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国贸易和发展会议秘书长周一告诉路透社记者，由于关税的不确定性，中小企业和发展中经济体可能面临投资放缓的特别风险。【原文：Small and medium-sized businesses and developing economies are likely to be at particular risk of a slowdown in investment due to ongoing tariff uncertainty, the Secretary-General of the UN Trade and Development Agency told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tariff-uncertainty-could-curb-investment-small-businesses-un-trade-agency-says-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4MGSOOY5NPY5NXPX4PLVGUPVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>