<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 20:47:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 20:47:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部耶伦称国会应就非银行抵押贷款部门采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周五呼吁国会赋予监管机构更多权力，以监督日益增长的非银行抵押贷款行业，她说该行业给金融稳定带来了独特的风险。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Friday called for Congress to give regulators more power to oversee the growing nonbank mortgage industry, which she said presented unique risks to financial stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-treasurys-yellen-says-congress-should-act-nonbank-mortgage-sector-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B52XWRDBGFOUBH4WBRM4V6YE7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 20:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在气候谈判中讨论中国太阳能制造业 "产能过剩 "和煤炭问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院高级官员周五表示，在为期两天的气候变化问题双边会谈中，美国和中国讨论了中国在太阳能和电池制造、钢铁生产和煤炭发电方面的产能过剩问题。【原文：The United States and China discussed Chinese overcapacity in solar and battery manufacturing, steel production and coal power during two days of bilateral meetings on climate change, senior State Department officials said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-discussed-overcapacity-chinese-solar-manufacturing-coal-climate-talks-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAUW6ONFLRPCJFBQ7SM6YDF5VI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 18:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[量化投资先驱吉姆-西蒙斯（Jim Simons）逝世，享年 86 岁]]></title><description><![CDATA[西蒙斯基金会（Simons Foundation）周五表示，帮助推广量化投资的数学教授、金融家吉姆-西蒙斯（Jim Simons）去世，享年 86 岁。【原文：Jim Simons, the math professor turned financier who helped popularize quantitative investing, has died aged 86, the Simons Foundation said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/investor-philanthropist-jim-simons-dies-age-86-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2MMP67EFFKYBKE4AADO7RYIAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，麦当劳将推出 5 美元套餐，以吸引顾客回流]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引一位熟知内情的人士的话报道称，麦当劳正准备在美国的餐厅推出 5 美元一餐的优惠活动，以吸引更多受到通胀打击的顾客回到其连锁店。【原文：McDonald's is preparing to launch a $5 meal deal at its restaurants in the U.S. to lure back more inflation-hit customers to its chains, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mcdonalds-launch-5-meal-deal-lure-back-customers-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBLYWDPB2JLJJIEWWXULSKGGAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:19:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克称特斯拉将斥资 5 亿美元扩建充电网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉公司首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周五表示，特斯拉将斥资5亿多美元扩建其快速充电网络，几天前他突然解雇了负责该业务的员工。【原文：Tesla will spend more than $500 million to expand its fast-charging network, CEO Elon Musk said on Friday, days after abruptly laying off employees who were running the business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/elon-musk-says-tesla-will-spend-500-mln-expand-charging-network-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBS6RNB53RNRNF4DAMEMTJ4DKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，美国上市障碍重重，申银万国加紧伦敦上市准备工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，在试图在纽约上市面临监管障碍和美国立法者的反对之后，快时尚巨头Shein正在加紧伦敦上市的准备工作。【原文：Fast-fashion giant Shein is stepping up preparations for a London listing after its attempt to float itself in New York faced regulatory hurdles and pushback from U.S. lawmakers, two people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/shein-steps-up-london-ipo-preparations-amid-us-hurdles-listing-sources-say-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JB3JOWPEWFOMTBNK6QQEZITHEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:01:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着通胀预期跃升，美联储官员考虑利率是否足够高]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美联储官员之间关于美国利率是否足够高的争论进一步加深，而在一项关键调查显示消费者的通胀预期出现跳升之后，这种争论可能会进一步加剧。【原文：Debate over whether U.S. interest rates are high enough deepened among Federal Reserve officials this week, and may be stoked further after a key survey showed a jump in consumers' inflation expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-officials-mull-if-rates-are-high-enough-inflation-expectations-jump-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7ONWZHJDBISJKADMLRZ7TM2YY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士：拜登将对中国医疗用品征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉拜登政府决定的消息人士透露，拜登政府预计将在下周公布新的贸易战略时对中国制造的注射器和个人防护设备等医疗器械征收新的关税。【原文：The Biden administration is expected to issue new tariffs on Chinese-made medical devices like syringes and personal protective equipment when it unveils its new trade strategy next week, according to two sources familiar with the decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/biden-put-tariffs-china-medical-supplies-sources-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6P5SCUOFUBKEJITMHZHJJFIMFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会寻求禁止对选举和灾难进行衍生品押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会（CFTC）主席表示，该委员会周五准备提议禁止用于押注美国大选和其他重大现实事件的上市衍生品。【原文：The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) on Friday was poised to propose a ban on listed derivatives used to bet on U.S. elections and other major real world events, its chair said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-cftc-seeks-ban-derivatives-bets-elections-calamities-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKHU5J3SGNMULLJEG4FNX7Y6W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:24:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 4 月通胀略超预期，降息步伐放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西官方数据周五显示，4月份巴西年度通胀率继续呈下降趋势，但略低于预期，这是在巴西央行投票决定降低利率步伐后的首次消费价格读数。【原文：Brazil's annual inflation continued to trend down but slightly less than expected in April, official data showed on Friday, in the first consumer price readings after the nation's central bank voted to reduce the pace of its interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-inflation-slightly-exceeds-forecasts-april-pace-rate-cuts-slows-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WD2QCDV6SBIKTGRSXQANM2G6VM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 X 公司在与以色列数据挖掘公司的诉讼中败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 公司指控一家以色列数据抓取公司非法复制和出售社交媒体平台上的内容，并出售允许他人复制和出售内容的工具，美国法官驳回了该公司的诉讼。【原文：A U.S. judge dismissed a lawsuit in which Elon Musk's X Corp accused an Israeli data-scraping company of illegally copying and selling content, and selling tools that let others copy and sell content, from the social media platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/musks-x-corp-loses-lawsuit-against-israeli-data-scraping-company-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7HTR6YITVLRDCMMST6D2XKEQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根称美国货币政策可能不够紧缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-罗根（Lorie Logan）周五表示，目前还不清楚货币政策是否足够紧缩，以将通胀率降至美国央行设定的2%的目标，现在降息还为时过早。【原文：Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan on Friday said it's not clear if monetary policy is tight enough to bring inflation down to the U.S. central bank's 2% goal, and it is too soon to be cutting interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-logan-says-us-monetary-policy-may-not-be-tight-enough-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUES5XH5RRMJTNVWAVD5DULZ3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月消费者信心指数降至六个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，由于对通胀、失业和利率的担忧日益加剧，5月份美国消费者情绪降至六个月来的最低点。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment sagged to a six-month low in May amid growing anxiety about inflation, unemployment and interest rates, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-slides-six-month-low-may-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OAMQAPQPZMGNDGH2PXKMDZY3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息希望重燃，美国股票基金周流入量增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 5 月 8 日的七天内，美国股票基金六周来首次出现单周资金流入，这要归功于一份低于预期的薪资报告，该报告重燃了美联储今年降息的希望。【原文：U.S. equity funds registered their first weekly inflow in six weeks in the seven days to May 8 thanks to a softer than anticipated payrolls report that revived hopes that the Federal Reserve would trim interest rates this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-gain-weekly-inflows-amid-renewed-hopes-rate-cut-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZ2AYNCPC5M3LNIQ6FE2QB56JQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息押注上升，全球股票基金吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 5 月 8 日的七天内，全球股票基金的需求急剧上升，原因是美国就业报告比预期疲软后，市场对美联储降息的押注再次升温。【原文：Demand for global equity funds rose sharply in the seven days to May 8, driven by renewed bets on Federal Reserve interest rate cuts after a softer than anticipated U.S. employment report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5G4NHKMXSJJFTJXT2XJTQF4HX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大就业岗位增幅超出预期，抑制了对 6 月降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，加拿大经济4月份新增就业人数是预测值的五倍，失业率意外保持在6.1%，这抑制了市场对6月份降息的押注。【原文：Canada's economy added five times the number of jobs that were forecast for April and the unemployment rate unexpectedly held at 6.1%, data showed on Friday, dampening market bets for a June rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-job-gains-blow-past-forecasts-wage-growth-slows-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JY7VYD7LVZLFNL66YPIALFLQAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:45:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特首席财务官劳勒将于 2025 年初卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司周五表示，约翰-劳勒将于 2025 年初辞去首席财务官一职，前 Lucid 汽车公司财务总监 Sherry House 将成为他的继任者。【原文：Ford Motor said on Friday John Lawler was stepping down as CFO in early 2025 and that former Lucid Motors finance chief Sherry House would be his successor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-cfo-become-vice-chair-lucid-motors-exec-house-succeed-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3ZEV5TCJFPHBMBTW45C2K2YLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:05:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特将于 2027 年起在巴伦西亚地区的西班牙工厂每年组装 30 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙工业部周五表示，美国汽车制造商福特公司计划从 2027 年起在其位于瓦伦西亚地区的西班牙工厂每年组装 30 万辆新车型。【原文：U.S. car maker Ford plans to assemble 300,000 units of a new model per year at its Spanish plant in the Valencia region starting 2027, the Spanish Industry Ministry said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-assemble-300000-cars-year-spanish-plant-valencia-region-2027-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DALFF5LS4ZL6NDD5LY3KUKKCUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:56:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的 Zeekr 在扩大首次公开募股规模后将在纽约证券交易所首次亮相]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 Zeekr 智能科技公司的股票原定于周五在纽约证券交易所开始交易，此前这家电动汽车制造商将其首次公开募股的定价定在了市场范围的最高端。【原文：Shares of China's Zeekr Intelligent Technology were scheduled to start trading on the New York Stock Exchange on Friday after the electric-vehicle maker priced its initial public offering at the top end of its marketed range.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-zeekr-set-debut-nyse-after-upsized-ipo-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V2RAYJHASVKSRP5VULZG3FWBPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在数据和美联储官员讲话前，期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五上涨，重点关注美联储官员的讲话，此前本周的经济数据支持了对美国降息的押注，并提振了投资者情绪。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday with focus on speeches from Federal Reserve officials, after economic data this week supported bets of U.S. interest rate cuts and lifted investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-rise-ahead-data-speeches-fed-officials-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCMRMLNJRBMDPLO4ZRKWDE5ZEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:24:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 盈利支撑美股，但至关重要的通胀报告迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[强劲的财报季和科技行业巨头的大卖场报告推动美国股市从 2024 年的首次真正低迷中反弹。下周的通胀数据可能会决定这种良好的氛围是否会继续。【原文：A strong earnings season and blockbuster reports from tech industry titans fueled a U.S. stock market rebound from the first real swoon of 2024. Next week’s inflation data could determine whether the good vibes continue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-earnings-bolster-us-stocks-crucial-inflation-report-looms-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7X6RVT7YRVLFTGUW6MOW5FB3VY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储博斯蒂克称经济可能放缓，但降息时间不确定]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联储主席拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）在接受路透社采访时表示，即使政策放松的时机和程度尚不确定，通胀进一步下降的速度也很缓慢，美国央行仍有可能在今年降息。【原文：The U.S. central bank likely remains on track to cut interest rates this year even if the timing and extent of the policy easing is uncertain and further declines in inflation come only slowly, Atlanta Federal Reserve President Raphael Bostic said in an interview with Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-bostic-says-economy-likely-slowing-though-rate-cut-timing-uncertain-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KKX6KCVFDJMC5DTAZTFRFC5654</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉电动汽车充电团队裁员威胁减缓拜登的高速公路电气化计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）决定裁撤特斯拉电动汽车充电团队，这使得推出新的快速充电站的计划陷入混乱，并可能推迟乔-拜登（Joe Biden）总统实现美国高速公路电气化的努力。【原文：Elon Musk's decision to gut Tesla's electric-vehicle charging team is scrambling plans for rolling out new fast-charging stations and may delay President Joe Biden's efforts to electrify U.S. highways.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-ev-charging-team-layoffs-threaten-slow-bidens-program-electrify-highways-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRTJADHOQRKMVBFJXSXCFG5CAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻失业率跳升、英国央行转向、香港股市大涨挽救了梅]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KLEFL2PTZK5DEAAHCETX2JUB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车监管机构对 20 多万辆福特汽车展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构周五表示，正在对 210,960 辆福特汽车进行初步评估，因为有投诉称这些汽车的柴油泄漏可能导致起火。【原文：The U.S. auto safety regulator said on Friday it was opening a preliminary evaluation into 210,960 Ford vehicles following complaints alleging diesel fuel leaks that may result in a fire.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-auto-regulator-opens-probe-into-over-200000-ford-vehicles-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N44MFYTIERKIDLSTP5MCHDUI5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:41:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就菲斯科汽车制动系统问题展开初步调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构周五对菲斯科公司在 2023 年生产的 6813 辆遨游 SUV 展开初步调查，此前有投诉称这些电动汽车使用的自动紧急制动系统在无意中启动。【原文：The U.S. auto safety regulator on Friday opened a preliminary probe into 6,813 Ocean SUVs made by Fisker in 2023 after complaints that the automatic emergency braking system used in the electric vehicles had activated inadvertently.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-auto-regulator-opens-preliminary-evaluation-into-fiskers-ocean-vehicles-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXSKLHTOVFKUVA2AYQ6ZFTUESQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 4 月汽车销量转为萎缩，尽管新能源汽车具有里程碑意义]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的行业数据显示，由于激烈的价格战和优惠措施未能摆脱消费者在经济复苏动荡时期对大件消费的谨慎态度，4月份中国汽车销量同比下降了5.8%。【原文：China's car sales fell 5.8% in April from a year earlier, industry data showed on Friday, as a ferocious price war and incentives failed to shake off consumers' caution about spending on big items during a shaky economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-april-car-sales-swing-contraction-despite-nev-milestone-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V25FOKILZFLT3E62CPUKCPOIOI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于消费疲软，预计日本第一季度经济将出现萎缩：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于前景不明朗，经济增长的所有关键驱动因素都出现下滑，日本经济在1-3月季度可能按年率计算萎缩1.5%。【原文：Japan's economy likely contracted an annualised 1.5% in the January-March quarter as all key drivers of growth slumped due to an uncertain outlook, a Reuters poll showed, which will probably set back Bank of Japan efforts to raise interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-economy-expected-shrink-q1-due-weak-consumption-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WEBEZC2IZLRLHCLQ6EPHWQ6DU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商利德尔英国公司 12 个月内第三次提高员工工资]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国超市集团利德尔（Lidl）的英国分公司表示，6 月份将把工资提高 3% 以上，数千名工人将在 12 个月内第三次加薪。【原文：The British arm of German supermarket group Lidl said it would lift wages by over 3% in June, giving thousands of workers a third pay rise in 12 months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retailer-lidl-uk-raises-staff-pay-third-time-12-months-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRY24QLZDJLZ7KDDJXCSUYPPJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国表示坚决反对美国的出口管制工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国出于国家安全考虑将 37 家中国公司列入贸易限制名单后，中国外交部发言人周五表示，中国坚决反对滥用美国实体清单等出口管制工具。【原文：China firmly opposes the abuse of export control tools such as the U.S. entity list, a foreign ministry spokesperson said on Friday, after the U.S. added 37 Chinese firms to a trade restriction list over national security concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/china-says-it-firmly-opposes-us-export-control-tools-2024-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JBJT4IA7BJOJHZOXOILKSHJ2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:24:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>