<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:05:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:05:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[字节跳动和 TikTok 寻求在最高法院审查前暂时停止美国的镇压法]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于中国的字节跳动及其短视频应用 TikTok 周一请求上诉法院暂时阻止一项法律，该法律要求母公司字节跳动在 1 月 19 日前剥离 TikTok，否则将面临禁令，等待美国最高法院的审查。【原文：Chinese-based ByteDance and its short video app TikTok on Monday asked an appeals court to temporarily block a law that would require that parent company ByteDance divest TikTok by Jan. 19 or face a ban pending a review by the U.S. Supreme Court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/bytedance-tiktok-seek-temporary-halt-us-crackdown-law-pending-supreme-court-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67RJTNYZCZJPXJUAKA2VSGE7UA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:21:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合利华首席财务官在运营改革中承担更多责任]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华周一表示，首席财务官费尔南多-费尔南德斯（Fernando Fernandez）将承担更多职责，包括监督供应链和采购，因为公司正在全面改革运营，以专注于 "强势 "品牌。【原文：Unilever said on Monday CFO Fernando Fernandez would take on more responsibilities, including overseeing supply chain and procurement, as the company overhauls its operations to focus on its "power" brands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-cfo-takes-additional-responsibility-amid-operational-overhaul-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IICOCMYTRBI23NUNK7O6L5J2OQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康卡斯特与华纳兄弟探索频道达成多年发行协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟 Discovery 公司周一表示，该公司与康卡斯特公司签署了一项多年协议，将通过康卡斯特的线性电视、应用程序和流媒体服务向英国和爱尔兰的 Xfinity 和 Sky 用户分发其内容。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery signed a multi-year deal with Comcast to distribute its content to Xfinity and Sky UK and Ireland customers using Comcast's linear television, apps, and streaming services, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/comcast-warner-bros-discovery-enter-multi-year-distribution-deal-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6HDSCYQVRMSLIAHBPO7WFIIHQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 13:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国小米宣布推出全新 SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国小米公司周一表示，预计将于明年 6 月或 7 月推出一款全新 SUV--YU7。【原文：China's Xiaomi said on Monday that it expects to launch a new SUV, the YU7, in June or July next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-xiaomi-announces-new-suv-launch-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSLG6J6YAZJYBOQMSFW3CEMCO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 12:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[陶氏将以 24 亿美元出售美国墨西哥湾沿岸部分基础设施资产的 40% 股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[陶氏公司周一表示，将以 24 亿美元的价格向麦格理资产管理公司（Macquarie Asset Management）管理的一家基金出售美国墨西哥湾沿岸部分基础设施资产 40% 的股份，以更加专注于核心化工业务。【原文：Dow said on Monday it would sell a 40% stake in some U.S. Gulf Coast infrastructure assets to a fund managed by Macquarie Asset Management for $2.4 billion as it looks to focus more on its core chemicals business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/dow-sell-40-stake-some-us-gulf-coast-infrastructure-assets-24-bln-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXJTJ3CSFZLY7KYC6TKGQOU35A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 12:09:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）工程师寻求帮助结束美国缺乏特种铀燃料的局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[前太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）工程师斯科特-诺兰（Scott Nolan）是初创公司 General Matter 的首席执行官，他的使命是在美国以商业规模生产一种浓缩核燃料并降低其成本，从而帮助俄罗斯结束对这种燃料的垄断。【原文：Former SpaceX engineer Scott Nolan, CEO of startup General Matter, is on a mission to help end Russia's monopoly on a type of more-enriched nuclear fuel by producing it at commercial scale in the United States and slashing its costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/former-spacex-engineer-seeks-help-end-us-dearth-special-uranium-fuel-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NX6E2MXB7NOD5PWH7XTAMQ5WFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 12:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）结束对软件更新后的 7745 辆菲斯科 Ocean SUV 的初步调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构周一表示，已经结束了对 7745 辆菲斯科 Ocean SUV 未能挂入驻车档的初步评估，此前这家电动汽车初创公司发布了召回公告，并发布了软件更新。【原文：The U.S. auto safety regulator said on Monday it has closed a preliminary evaluation into 7,745 Fisker Ocean SUVs over failure to shift vehicles into the park gear, after the electric-vehicle startup issued recalls and released a software update.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-closes-preliminary-probe-into-7745-fisker-ocean-suvs-after-software-update-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3C34DOD6BJ7JMELBBXPSEXEEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对英伟达涉嫌违反反垄断法进行调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周一表示，已就英伟达涉嫌违反中国反垄断法展开调查。【原文：China's market regulator has opened an investigation into Nvidia over suspected violation of the country's antimonopoly law, the regulator said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/china-investigates-nvidia-over-suspected-violation-antimonopoly-law-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5B5PFVZJNNMIHJV5ISHG3LW3X4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:42:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，激进投资者巴林顿资本敦促梅西百货削减开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周一报道，激进投资者巴林顿资本（Barington Capital）已在梅西百货建仓，并敦促这家连锁百货公司削减开支，考虑在公司内部分离出一个房地产部门。【原文：Activist investor Barington Capital has built a position in Macy's and is urging the department store chain to cut spending and consider the separation of a real-estate unit within the company, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/activist-investor-barington-capital-urges-macys-cut-spending-wsj-reports-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KC5YRZDUV5OYPEQF2SMCHEMQUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者关注通胀数据，期货价格持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货表现低迷，上一交易日 S&amp;P 500 指数和纳斯达克指数因乐观的企业业绩预期而创下收盘新高，而投资者则在等待本周晚些时候将公布的一份关键的通胀报告。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were subdued on Monday after the S&amp;P 500 and the Nasdaq notched record closing highs in the previous session on upbeat corporate forecasts, while investors awaited a key inflation report due later in the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-steady-investor-focus-turns-inflation-data-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCL6C36I25NHBDESIYVWD4BDRI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arthur J. Gallagher 将以 134.5 亿美元收购 AssuredPartners]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arthur J. Gallagher 周一表示，该公司已同意以 134.5 亿美元的价格收购保险经纪公司 AssuredPartners，以加强其在庞大且快速增长的中端市场的业务。【原文：Arthur J. Gallagher said on Monday it has agreed to acquire insurance broker AssuredPartners in a $13.45 billion deal, as it looks to bolster its presence in the vast and fast-growing middle-market segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/arthur-j-gallagher-buy-assuredpartners-1345-bln-deal-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZU6MXABZNOPVBXVU62LPKPK44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:11:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电创始人：英特尔本应专注于人工智能而非芯片制造]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾半导体制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：Intel should have focused on artificial intelligence rather than trying to become a contract chipmaker, the founder of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co said on Monday, in relation to the recent departure of Intel's CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-should-have-focused-ai-rather-than-chipmaking-tsmc-founder-says-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6FO5EEJSVPCFOSYH42Q7HESIY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储减息预期升温，中国转变货币政策立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPAYZAD34FM35FHEK4FGT64VR4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:10:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官权衡洋葱收购 Infowars 的命运]]></title><description><![CDATA[阴谋论者亚历克斯-琼斯（Alex Jones）将于周一在休斯敦举行的法庭听证会上敦促美国破产法官阻止将其 Infowars 网站出售给 Onion 新闻模仿网站。【原文：Conspiracy theorist Alex Jones is set to urge a U.S. bankruptcy judge to block the sale of his Infowars website to the Onion news parody site at a Monday court hearing in Houston.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-weighs-fate-onions-buyout-infowars-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSW55LHPONJZFG7V2T2FRBC5GU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国人面临医疗保险成本上升和延误增多的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[珍-沃森（Jen Watson）是华盛顿州联邦路市一位 41 岁的母亲，多年来她一直与医生合作，寻找合适的药物来治疗她的多种慢性疾病，其中包括癫痫和纤维肌痛。【原文：Jen Watson, a 41-year-old mother in Federal Way, Washington, has worked for years with her doctor to find the right medications to deal with her multiple chronic illnesses, which include epilepsy and fibromyalgia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/americans-face-challenges-health-insurance-costs-rise-delays-mount-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NCEZ5WN7VK7DCX6IUGG5DLE2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普领导的马斯克提高效率运动或将促进国防科技合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）计划推动美国政府提高效率，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）参与其中，根据对公司高管的采访，大型国防承包商和小型科技公司可能会在人工智能、无人机和无人驾驶潜艇等领域开展更多联合项目。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's planned U.S. government efficiency drive involving Elon Musk could lead to more joint projects between big defense contractors and smaller tech firms in areas such as artificial intelligence, drones and uncrewed submarines, according to interviews with company executives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-musk-led-efficiency-drive-may-spur-defense-tech-partnerships-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MALV4HR7QBOAXPPZPGW5KXSMJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:03:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车公司表示，工会必须为德国工厂找到新的解决方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司首席谈判代表阿尔内-迈斯温克尔（Arne Meiswinkel）周一表示，在公司拒绝了工会提出的难以为继的建议后，工会和管理层需要为德国工厂找到其他解决方案。【原文：Volkswagen's chief negotiator Arne Meiswinkel said on Monday that unions and management needed to find alternative pathways to a solution for its German plants after the company rejected a proposal put forward by unions as unsustainable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-unions-must-find-new-solutions-german-plants-company-says-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORLVOHXGA5IQLKRZTDOM4WB2UU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 08:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度反垄断机构寻求最高法院听证，以加快亚马逊和 Flipkart 案件的审理速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度反垄断机构要求最高法院审理针对亚马逊和沃尔玛旗下 Flipkart 电子商务平台调查的法律挑战，称三星、vivo 等公司向印度高等法院提出的这些挑战旨在破坏调查。【原文：India's antitrust body has asked the Supreme Court to hear legal challenges to an investigation of Amazon and Walmart's Flipkart e-commerce platforms, saying those challenges, filed by Samsung, Vivo and others at Indian high courts, were aiming to scuttle the probe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-antitrust-body-seeks-supreme-court-hearing-expedite-amazon-flipkart-cases-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQVFSNKJFRKTVHMHNELB6M6B2I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 08:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国宣布自 2010 年以来首次货币政策转向以刺激经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[国家媒体周一援引政治局会议的消息报道称，作为支持经济增长措施的一部分，中国明年将采取 "适度宽松 "的货币政策，这是自2010年以来中国货币政策首次转向宽松。【原文：China will adopt an "appropriately loose" monetary policy next year as part of steps to support economic growth, state media reported on Monday citing a Politburo meeting, marking the first such shift towards loosening since 2010.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-announces-first-monetary-policy-shift-since-2010-spur-growth-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVVCTCZ6OVK7NJ6JQ5A37J7B6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 08:29:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息称中国监管机构要求银行加快离岸公司上市进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，中国大陆和香港的监管机构已告知全球最大的几家投资银行，帮助中国企业加快在香港上市的速度，以促进海外融资，振兴世界第二大经济体。【原文：Regulators in mainland China and Hong Kong have told some of the world's biggest investment banks to help speed up Chinese companies' listings in the city, said sources, in a bid to boost fundraising overseas and revitalise the world's No. 2 economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/china-regulators-tell-banks-expedite-offshore-company-listings-sources-say-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PANJENVGBBIAPJOKXBWUFQAADI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 08:16:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国亿万富豪马云罕见亮相，为蚂蚁金服集团展望人工智能未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴联合创始人马云对其关联公司蚂蚁金服集团的未来充满信心，认为这家金融科技巨头将在人工智能领域迎来重大机遇，这是自中国停止蚂蚁金服集团 2020 年上市计划以来，马云罕见地公开露面。【原文：Alibaba co-founder Jack Ma voiced confidence in its affiliate Ant Group's future, seeing significant opportunities in artificial intelligence for the fintech giant, at a rare public appearance since China halted its planned IPO in 2020.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinese-billionaire-jack-ma-sees-ai-future-ant-group-rare-appearance-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B65HCWC7QBOKDLCKIEMQJAXRCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 07:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国多米诺比萨公司与特许经营合作伙伴签订为期 5 年的新框架协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国多米诺比萨集团（Domino's Pizza Group）周一表示，它已与其特许经营合作伙伴达成了一项新的五年框架协议。【原文：UK's Domino's Pizza Group said on Monday it has reached a new five-year framework with its franchise partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uks-dominos-pizza-enters-into-new-5-year-framework-with-franchise-partners-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PE4SU4SPJJT7DFZCE3FOAX37Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 07:16:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 Kioxia 公司首次公开募股价格处于区间中位，募集资金 8 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周一提交的一份证券文件显示，贝恩资本支持的芯片制造商 Kioxia 首次公开募股已募集到 1200 亿日元（约合 8 亿美元），其中包括一次超额配售，股票定价处于市场区间的中间位置。【原文：Bain Capital-backed chipmaker Kioxia's initial public offering has raised 120 billion yen ($800 million) including an overallotment after shares were priced in the middle of their marketed range, according to a securities filing on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kioxia-prices-ipo-1455-yen-per-share-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBPAGMG4B5KC3JN4ROV54SGJLI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 06:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着经济刺激政策的启动，中国 11 月份银行贷款增长一倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周一的一项民意调查显示，11月份中国新增人民币贷款预计比10月份几乎翻了一番，这表明信贷需求更加强劲，因为中国政府最近为支撑经济增长所做的努力提升了人们的信心。【原文：China's new yuan loans are expected to have almost doubled in November from October, a Reuters poll showed on Monday, demonstrating firmer credit demand as Beijing's recent efforts to prop up economic growth lift confidence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-nov-bank-lending-seen-doubling-stimulus-kicks-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5EAGLO4ZWRNJZBE2D2BOUUQBSM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 06:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在欧洲经济萎靡不振的同时，领导层也出现了空缺]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国和德国的政治危机是欧洲苦苦挣扎的经济现代化努力的一个挫折，已经使企业更难做出在全球竞争中所需的投资决策。【原文：France and Germany's political crises are a setback for efforts to modernise Europe's struggling economy and are already making it harder for companies to take the investment decisions they need to compete globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/europes-economic-malaise-add-leadership-void-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECFWLZT4DVLI3MPSSQA3CZFNQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 06:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强劲势头令 "货运列车 "美股涨势难以逆转]]></title><description><![CDATA[进入年底，美国股市的无情反弹几乎没有放缓的迹象，尽管估值的上升和过度投机的迹象加剧了人们的担忧，认为回调可能早该到来。【原文：A relentless rally in U.S. stocks is showing few signs of slowing into year-end, even as rising valuations and signs of excessive speculation fuel worries that a pullback may be overdue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/strong-momentum-makes-it-hard-bet-against-freight-train-us-stock-rally-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37XB65VYXFL4RHHTXTKSVQOK7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 06:03:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢布、澳元受关注，美元扩大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[加元和澳元在本周央行会议前成为周一的焦点，而欧元和其他主要货币则因美元走强而略有下跌。【原文：The Canadian dollar and Australian dollar were in focus on Monday ahead of their central bank meetings this week, while the euro and other major currencies lost a bit more ground to a strong U.S. dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/loonie-aussie-focus-while-us-dollar-extends-gains-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SS2MZ6WWL5JXTKXKJLQLB7SEPQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 05:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价叙利亚匆忙沦陷，市场保持冷静]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EPUCGSESORMCRIRWPTDXAAMQZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 05:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车与工人就工厂停工问题举行新一轮谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车和劳工代表将就减薪和可能的工厂关闭问题举行第四轮谈判，双方的僵持已变得越来越激烈，周一这家汽车制造商在德国的主要生产基地还将举行罢工。【原文：Volkswagen and labour representatives will hold a fourth round of talks over wage cuts and possible plant closures, in what has become an increasingly bitter standoff that will be flanked by strikes at the carmaker's main German sites on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-workers-clash-latest-round-talks-over-factory-shutdowns-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QU6RRRIHVOXXMA6W3NMKGKNOA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 05:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，2024 年日本破产数量将创 11 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[东京商工研究所（TSR）的私营部门数据周一显示，在下周备受关注的央行会议召开之前，日本今年的破产申请将突破1万件，创下2013年以来的最高纪录。【原文：Japan's bankruptcy filings this year are set to surpass 10,000 and hit the highest since 2013, private-sector data by Tokyo Shoko Research (TSR) showed on Monday, ahead of a closely watched central bank meeting next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-bankruptcies-set-hit-11-year-high-2024-data-shows-2024-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X7SLRSBEINMLHDTCORJ2GNL7FE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 04:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>