<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:07:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:07:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道墨西哥反垄断监管机构指控银行联合操纵价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥反垄断监督机构 COFECE 发现，根据路透社看到的一份政府机构文件，在该国运营的 21 家银行和金融机构可能对信用卡延期付款相关费用的定价负有责任。【原文：Mexico's antitrust watchdog COFECE has found that 21 banks and financial institutions operating in the country are likely responsible for fixing fees related to deferred credit card payments, according to a document produced by the government agency that was seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mexicos-antitrust-watchdog-accuses-banks-joint-price-fixing-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBT6WKZ44FOHFHZVR65KRTT7DQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:43:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国结束对 Waymo 自动驾驶汽车碰撞和意外行为的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，已结束对 Alphabet 旗下 Waymo 自动驾驶汽车发生的一系列轻微碰撞和意外行为进行的为期 14 个月的调查，但未采取进一步行动。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said Friday it has closed a 14-month investigation into a series of minor collisions and unexpected behavior from Alphabet's Waymo self-driving vehicles without taking further action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-closes-probe-into-waymo-self-driving-collisions-unexpected-behavior-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRGNK5TZZ5OQ7NVWJWCGZDNLTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普：强势美元听起来不错，但弱势美元 "赚得更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他喜欢强势美元，但弱势美元 "会让你赚得更多"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he liked a strong dollar but "you make a hell of a lot more money" with a weaker one.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-strong-dollar-sounds-good-you-make-hell-lot-more-with-weaker-one-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RF5KPRRTVOELNH7FYUBVSHBLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，花旗集团能源转型主管离职，转任 Moelis 职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周五表示，花旗集团清洁能源转型投资银行业务全球主管即将离开这家美国贷款公司，前往精品银行 Moelis 担任并购顾问。【原文：Citigroup's global head of clean energy transition investment banking is leaving the U.S. lender for a role advising on mergers and acquisitions at boutique bank Moelis , people familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/citigroups-head-energy-transition-decamps-moelis-role-sources-say-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6FBLS4OU5O3VF65B6J3TGWD7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税最后期限临近，谈判陷入僵局，巴西陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西官员和行业领袖表示，巴西正竭力避免美国在一周内征收50%的惩罚性关税，但高层会谈陷入僵局，美国公司也不愿就此问题与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对抗。【原文：Brazil is scrambling to avert punishing 50% U.S. tariffs in a week's time, but high level talks are stalled and U.S. companies are reluctant to confront U.S. President Donald Trump over the issue, officials and industry leaders say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/brazil-scrambles-us-tariff-deadline-looms-talks-stall-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEMYVTTE6VJ47FYLZWXPVE4APQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国可能无法与加拿大通过谈判达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，美国可能不会与加拿大通过谈判达成贸易协议，并暗示其政府可能单方面设定关税税率。【原文：The United States may not reach a negotiated trade deal with Canada, U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday, suggesting his administration could set a tariff rate unilaterally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-says-us-may-not-have-negotiated-trade-deal-with-canada-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">526JP237HJOKROXW3CM2ZOPF4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称与欧盟达成贸易协议的几率为 50]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，美国与欧盟达成贸易协议的可能性为50%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday said there was a 50-50 chance that the United States would reach a trade agreement with the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-there-is-50-50-chance-trade-deal-with-eu-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KSA6R6ZAFNCBH5LRNRPJS4UUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普暗示美联储主席可能降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他与美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）进行了良好的会晤，并得到了鲍威尔可能准备好降低利率的印象。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday he had a good meeting with Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell and got the impression Powell might be ready to lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-suggests-fed-chair-may-cut-interest-rates-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BV2OJW34O5K6TDJ27FTHXSZIUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:20:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，西班牙电信正在就将墨西哥业务出售给 Beyond ONE 进行排他性谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士透露，西班牙电信巨头 Telefonica 正在就将其墨西哥业务出售给维珍移动墨西哥公司（Virgin Mobile Mexico）的所有者 Beyond ONE 进行独家谈判。【原文：Spanish telecom giant Telefonica is in exclusive talks to sell its Mexican business to Beyond ONE, the owner of Virgin Mobile Mexico, three sources with knowledge of the negotiations said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/telefonica-exclusive-talks-sell-its-mexican-unit-beyond-one-sources-say-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BY25FZ5OH5NY3LALMSXP5QAQ4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:16:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯电子商务公司 Ozon 称企业家 Chachava 持有其 28% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯电子商务公司 Ozon 周五表示，商人 Alexander Chachava 已从 Vostok Investments 收购了该公司 27.7% 的股份。【原文：Russian e-commerce company Ozon said on Friday that businessman Alexander Chachava had acquired a 27.7% stake in the company from Vostok Investments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/russian-e-commerce-firm-ozon-says-entrepreneur-chachava-takes-28-stake-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CS5OC5NB6VPX3AQ463BOJFG6PE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:09:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月核心资本货物订单意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[6 月份，美国主要制造业资本货物的新订单出人意料地下降，这表明，由于进口关税前的活动所带来的提振作用减弱，企业在设备方面的支出出现回落。【原文：New orders for key U.S.-manufactured capital goods unexpectedly fell in June, suggesting a pullback in business spending on equipment as the boost from front-loading of activity ahead of tariffs on imports faded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-core-capital-goods-orders-unexpectedly-fall-june-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3OYLGI5EFNSTDKOIX2JZ4PYQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 12:48:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彪马库存问题凸显零售商关税困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[彪马在美国面临着两难境地：在匆忙从亚洲发货以躲避即将到来的关税之后，这家德国运动装品牌目前正在打折以清理库存，同时计划在今年提价以抵消不断上涨的成本。【原文：Puma faces a dilemma in the United States: after rushing shipments from Asia to beat incoming tariffs, the German sportswear brand is now discounting to clear stock, while planning to raise prices this year to offset rising costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/puma-inventory-headache-highlights-tariff-dilemma-retailers-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJR5ZOATIVN4REAWC6UJZJRCAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 12:46:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Business Insider 报道，特斯拉计划本周末在旧金山推出 Robotaxis]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Business Insider 周五援引一份内部员工备忘录报道，特斯拉准备最快于本周末在旧金山推出机器人出租车服务。【原文：Tesla is preparing to launch its robotaxi service in San Francisco as soon as this weekend, Business Insider reported on Friday, citing an internal staff memo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-plans-launch-robotaxis-san-francisco-this-weekend-business-insider-reports-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6E6LTP7LNJSJIJCH3N5WMJPDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 12:38:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车首席执行官希望通过 "有吸引力 "的投资达成自己的关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的汽车制造商大众汽车公司首席执行官奥利弗-布卢姆（Oliver Blume）周五对投资者表示，一旦华盛顿和欧盟达成广泛的贸易协议，大众汽车希望投资承诺能够帮助其在美国关税问题上谈判取得进一步让步。【原文：Europe's largest car manufacturer Volkswagen is hoping investment commitments can help it negotiate further concessions on U.S. tariffs once Washington and the European Union strike a broad trade deal, CEO Oliver Blume told investors on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-ceo-hopes-own-tariff-deal-with-attractive-investments-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LI66X4MUBFNXRCJNRXTMZZOSRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 12:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金因对贸易协议持乐观态度每周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至7月23日的一周里，全球股票基金的资金流入再次回升，原因是对美国贸易协议的乐观情绪、强于预期的美国经济报告以及令人鼓舞的企业财报季开端提振了风险情绪。【原文：Inflows into global equity funds picked up again in the week through July 23 as optimism over U.S. trade deals, stronger than expected U.S. economic reports and an encouraging start to the corporate earnings season boosted risk sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6KKCPVEUJMD3AHZTTNTGXUGNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 12:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着竞争白热化，Charter 第二季度失去更多宽带用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[Charter Communications 周五公布的第二季度宽带用户亏损高于预期，因为这家有线电视巨头正在努力应对来自无线运营商的竞争，这些无线运营商将高速互联网服务与 5G 移动计划捆绑在一起。【原文：Charter Communications reported a higher-than-expected broadband subscribers loss in the second quarter on Friday, as the cable giant grappled with competition from wireless carriers that are bundling high-speed internet services with 5G mobile plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/charter-loses-more-broadband-customers-q2-competition-heats-up-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQRFAEJKGZJKRIYSI2DZM6ELVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:55:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行发言人希望缓和市场对不再减息的看法，但欧元区经济依然保持增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一系列数据显示，欧元区经济在全球贸易战造成的普遍不确定性面前依然保持了韧性，即使欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）的决策者们似乎缓和了市场对不再降息的押注。【原文：The euro zone economy has remained resilient to the pervasive uncertainty caused by a global trade war, a slew of data showed on Friday, even as European Central Bank policymakers appeared to temper market bets on no more rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/euro-zone-economy-holds-up-even-ecb-speakers-look-temper-market-view-no-more-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPDRMKEWFNNQLCZCKJVPECQU3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家称美国经济数据质量堪忧，当局行动不够紧急]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社调查的 100 位顶级政策专家中，有 89 位对长期以来被视为黄金标准的美国官方经济数据质量所面临的风险感到担忧，其中大多数人还担心政府没有足够紧迫地解决这一问题。【原文：Risks to the quality of official U.S. economic data - long seen as the gold standard - are worrying 89 of 100 top policy experts polled by Reuters, with most also concerned that the authorities are not addressing the issue urgently enough.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economic-data-quality-worry-authorities-not-acting-urgently-enough-experts-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RTNTQJCNBM2BO77WXB7JPWJ5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:49:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HCA 上调年度盈利预期，原因是医疗保健需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[HCA Healthcare周五上调了2025年的利润预期，因为该公司预计医疗程序的持续需求将缓解美国总统唐纳德-特朗普可能征收关税带来的冲击。【原文：HCA Healthcare raised its 2025 profit forecast on Friday as it expects sustained demand for medical procedures to cushion a hit from U.S. President Donald Trump's potential tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hca-raises-annual-profit-forecast-resilient-demand-medical-care-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSQRT4BWPJOW7JP22WE6KE3K7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与意大利能源穹顶公司合作实现零排放供电]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利储能公司 Energy Dome 周五表示，它已与谷歌建立了商业合作伙伴关系，为这家美国科技巨头的运营电网提供无碳能源。【原文：Italian energy storage firm Energy Dome said on Friday it had entered a commercial partnership with Google to supply carbon-free energy to the grids that power the operations of the U.S. tech giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/google-partners-with-italys-energy-dome-zero-emission-power-supply-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SD4OHTTEHJLKVGG2GTQWXND3LI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将从 10 月起停止在欧盟投放政治广告，并指责欧盟的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国社交媒体公司 Meta Platforms 周五表示，由于欧盟针对政治广告的规定所带来的法律不确定性，Meta Platforms 将于 10 月初停止在其欧盟平台上发布政治、选举和社会问题广告。【原文：Meta Platforms will end political, electoral, social issue advertising on its platform in the European Union in early October because of the legal uncertainties due to EU rules targeting political advertising, the U.S. social media company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/meta-halt-political-advertising-eu-october-blames-eu-rules-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7K2TOM4MLZJVXCSA3LLC3NW6HM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 第二季度利润超出预期，炼油利润率上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，炼油商菲利普斯 66 第二季度利润超出华尔街预期，得益于炼油利润率上升和周转费用下降。【原文：Refiner Phillips 66 beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit on Friday, helped by higher refining margins and lower turnaround expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/phillips-66-beats-second-quarter-profit-estimates-higher-refining-margins-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TJ6QUIRMVNHTBDCARIUFSXSIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国有媒体称，特斯拉在部分辅助驾驶测试中击败中国竞争对手，Bytedance]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 TikTok 所有者 Bytedance 旗下汽车部门 Dcar 公布的结果，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的特斯拉在中国高速公路辅助驾驶技术测试中的表现优于比亚迪、小米和华为等中国竞争对手。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk's Tesla outperformed Chinese rivals including BYD, Xiaomi and Huawei in a test of assisted driving technologies on China's highways, according to results published by TikTok owner Bytedance's auto unit Dcar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-beats-chinese-rivals-some-driving-assisted-tests-say-china-state-media-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HN7RDECWDFK6FHXOTWZDOSOFQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:03:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标热闹的市场周转为平淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTPPEZS5DVJOXADTUFZNBBWAUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车零部件供应商下调销售预期，法雷奥股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五早盘，法雷奥股价下跌超过 16%，此前这家法国汽车零部件供应商将其年度销售预期下调了至少 10 亿欧元（12 亿美元），原因是美元走软以及全球汽车销售量萎缩。【原文：Shares in Valeo fell over 16% in early Friday trading, after the French car parts supplier cut its annual sales forecast by at least 1 billion euros ($1.2 billion), blaming a weaker dollar and shrinking global car sales volumes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/valeo-shares-slump-car-parts-supplier-cuts-sales-forecast-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIIJC4BFG5OKZKHURWU37HB7UM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 10:15:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔 500 指数和纳斯达克指数创下历史新高后，美股期货暂停上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街期货周五持稳，因为投资者在上一交易日创下 S&amp;P 500 指数和纳斯达克指数收盘纪录后稍事喘息，并在下周关税截止日期前等待贸易谈判的明朗化。【原文：Wall Street futures held steady on Friday as investors took a breather following record closes for the S&amp;P 500 and the Nasdaq in the previous session and awaited clarity on trade negotiations ahead of next week's tariff deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-pause-after-record-sp-500-nasdaq-run-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GP6N4MIPBKJHECURANS6JJ7MI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 10:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗保险公司 Centene 因医疗费用上涨意外亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[Centene 周五公布了意外的季度亏损，部分原因是与保险计划相关的医疗成本上升，导致其股价在盘前交易中暴跌近 13%。【原文：Centene on Friday posted a surprise quarterly loss, partly hurt by higher medical costs related to its insurance plans, sending its shares tumbling nearly 13% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/health-insurer-centene-reports-surprise-loss-rising-medical-costs-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAQFXNOZRROXHKUOJ5MMUB6TFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 10:08:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒙特利尔战胜迈阿密爱国的加拿大人改变了暑假计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大人将他们每年一度的南半球假期换成了渥太华周边的公路旅行、育空地区的午夜阳光、新斯科舍省的观鲸或班夫的徒步旅行。【原文：Canadians are trading their annual vacation south of the border for road trips around Ottawa, the midnight sun in Yukon, whale watching in Nova Scotia or hiking in Banff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/montreal-over-miami-patriotic-canadians-change-summer-vacation-plans-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5DHL73ZJBNC5POMGZVNF6BSQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 10:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者权衡鲍威尔可能提前退市对市场的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）任期的不确定性正促使投资者评估，如果美国央行领导层过早更迭，市场可能会做出哪些反应。【原文：Uncertainty over Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell’s tenure is prompting investors to assess potential market reactions should there be an premature change in leadership at the U.S. central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/investors-weigh-market-impact-possible-early-powell-exit-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YARCE7S5PVLRLOLJV2XESLT2YY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 10:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美湾炼油商寻求中东和南美石油抵消委内瑞拉和墨西哥的损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[据船舶跟踪数据显示，美国墨西哥湾沿岸的炼油商正在抢购更多的中东和南美原油，以抵消委内瑞拉和墨西哥原油的损失，如果美国允许部分受制裁的委内瑞拉原油重返市场，这种变通办法可能会昙花一现。【原文：U.S. Gulf Coast refiners are snapping up higher volumes of Middle Eastern and South American crudes to offset the loss of Venezuelan and Mexican barrels, according to ship tracking data, a workaround solution that might be short-lived if the U.S. allows some sanctioned Venezuelan crude to return to the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-gulf-refiners-seek-mideast-samerican-oil-offset-venezuela-mexico-losses-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAZZE6BEQJI57MTLZQ7YVKFTKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 10:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>