<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:12:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:12:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将吸纳 Chipotle 公司高管杰克-哈同加入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉电动汽车制造商杰克-哈顿（Jack Hartung）周五表示，特斯拉将于今年 6 月将奇波特尔公司（Chipotle）高管杰克-哈顿（Jack Hartung）纳入董事会和审计委员会。【原文：Tesla will add Chipotle executive Jack Hartung to its board of directors and audit committee in June, the electric vehicle maker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tesla-add-chipotle-executive-jack-hartung-board-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLQSJ7IALNNC7LYOYWZHP2CQFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车股东要求汽车制造商改革 "问题严重 "的治理结构]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，大众汽车的股东们再次对这家汽车制造商的公司治理提出批评，要求提高董事会的独立性，并对这家德国公司的控股家族的主导地位表示日益担忧。【原文：Volkswagen's shareholders renewed their criticism of the automaker's corporate governance on Friday, demanding greater board independence and expressing growing concern over the dominance of the German company's controlling families.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-shareholders-demand-carmaker-reform-highly-problematic-governance-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7VMSZOV2VPLHLD6MYCBBM4UTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰执政党报告其网站在选举前遭到攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰执政党公民纲领党（Civic Platform）的一位高级官员说，该党的网站周五遭到了网络攻击。【原文：The website of Poland's ruling Civic Platform party was hit by a cyberattack on Friday, a senior party official said, hours before the start of a campaign blackout before the first round of Sunday's presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/polish-ruling-party-reports-attack-its-website-before-election-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWUGTAOZRNMAXGZBEKABP7UMGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:58:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月份独户住宅开工量和建筑许可量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于进口材料关税和抵押贷款利率居高不下仍是住房市场的主要障碍，4 月份美国单户住宅建设出现下滑。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding fell in April as tariffs on imported materials and high mortgage rates remained major obstacles for the housing market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-single-family-housing-starts-building-permits-fell-april-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKHEEPXW3ZJPDASIG2QQUEZGI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国加密货币社区在接连发生绑架案后感到恐惧和愤怒]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一系列暴力绑架事件发生后，法国加密货币公司的老板们感到恐惧和愤怒。一些人加强了安保措施，并考虑配备保镖，而另一些人则呼吁加大打击犯罪的力度，同时放松监管，使加密货币的文件记录更加匿名。【原文：French crypto bosses have reacted with fear and anger after a series of violent kidnappings. While some have stepped up security and are considering bodyguards, others are calling for a tougher crackdown on crime plus deregulation to keep the crypto paper trail more anonymous.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/fear-anger-frances-crypto-community-after-spate-kidnappings-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBB5EK5XJBKLVDHW2UMWP5AYUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:40:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美空运因 "微量 "关税而下滑；航空公司调整航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业数据显示，本月中国对出境低值物品的免税政策被取消后，中国与美国之间的航空货运能力下降了近三分之一，削弱了亚洲主要航空公司的重要收入来源。【原文：Air freight capacity between China and the U.S. dropped by almost a third after a tax-free exemption for low-value items out of China was removed this month, industry data showed, denting a significant revenue stream for Asia's major airlines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-air-freight-tumbles-de-minimis-tariff-airlines-adjust-routes-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRTX5RBDZZJT5NNOMQCKZY5SYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点：肥胖症药物市场竞争白热化，威戈威生产商诺和诺德辞退首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wegovy生产商诺和诺德公司周五表示，公司首席执行官拉尔斯-弗鲁尔加德-约根森（Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen）将因担心公司在竞争激烈的肥胖症药物市场上失去先发优势而下台。【原文：Wegovy-maker Novo Nordisk said on Friday its CEO Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen will step down over concerns the company is losing its first-mover advantage in the highly competitive obesity drug market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/view-wegovy-maker-novo-nordisk-ousts-ceo-competition-obesity-drug-market-heats-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FIGD3JBWBJ6VCU3TCIVOS2K2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利和阿联酋宣布达成人工智能中心协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利工业部长阿道夫-乌尔索（Adolfo Urso）周五表示，意大利和阿拉伯联合酋长国已同意在意大利发展人工智能中心。【原文：Italy and the United Arab Emirates have agreed to develop an artificial intelligence hub in Italy, Industry Minister Adolfo Urso said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/italy-uae-announce-deal-artificial-intelligence-hub-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTUFMC4FTBPWHH3H6OBAJS6UEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，英伟达在美国芯片禁令后寻求上海研发基地]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位接近此事的消息人士称，Nvidia 正在上海寻找研发中心的选址，这反映了中国市场的战略意义，美国对先进芯片出口的限制打击了中国市场的销售。【原文：Nvidia is seeking a site in Shanghai for a research and development centre, three sources close to the matter said, reflecting the strategic significance of the Chinese market where U.S. curbs on advanced chip exports have hit sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-seeks-shanghai-rd-site-after-us-chip-curbs-say-sources-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BF6BGXZCMJO6BPT5GC3NCZAHYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:52:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 公司获得 19 亿美元退出融资，期限 5 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司在周五提交的一份文件中说，在破产保护的背景下，该公司获得了具有约束力的退出融资承诺，为期 5 年，总额达 19 亿美元。【原文：Brazil's airline Gol secured binding commitments for exit financing with a 5-year term totaling $1.90 billion, in context of chapter 11, it said in a filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/brazils-gol-secures-19-billion-exit-financing-with-5-year-term-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JLNAKET2BLA5A4LWHSVKRQ7RI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标贸易和通胀缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFJ2TLKW65K2LNZSOAUWMGAAT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:19:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因对关税协议持乐观态度，美国股票基金五周来首次吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至5月14日的一周内，美国股票基金五周来首次吸引资金流入，原因是对关税谈判取得进展的乐观情绪以及对消费价格上涨的担忧有所缓解，提振了投资者情绪。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted inflows for the first time in five weeks in the week through May 14 as optimism over progress in tariff negotiations and easing concerns about rising consumer prices lifted investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-draw-first-inflow-five-weeks-tariff-deal-optimism-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DL65CTPBMNJ7DB2I2C2LS6HSYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肥胖症药物制造商诺和诺德公司首席执行官将在市场困境中下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）周五表示，在肥胖症药物市场竞争加剧导致公司股价暴跌之后，公司首席执行官拉尔斯-弗鲁尔加德-约根森（Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen）将下台。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Friday its CEO Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen will step down following a plunge in the company's share price amid intensifying competition in the obesity drug market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-ceo-step-down-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4PCGHBTAFOBXC2K5YINNTUWM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:07:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易乐观、通胀缓解，全球股票基金流入激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 5 月 14 日的一周内，全球股票基金吸引了七周以来最大的单周资金流入，这主要是受到中美贸易战休战大大降低了全球经济衰退风险的影响。【原文：Global equity funds attracted the largest weekly inflow in seven weeks in the week through May 14, buoyed by a U.S.-China trade war truce that has significantly reduced the risk of a global recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTREDUODMVMWPKLWF33E6BZFXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易乐观情绪不减，美股期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[受中美关税休战和通胀数据疲软的影响，周五美国股指期货上涨，使华尔街有望以积极的态势结束本周的交易。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday, keeping Wall Street on track to end the week on a positive note, marked by a U.S.-China tariff truce and soft inflation data, while investors focused on a likely vote on President Donald Trump's sweeping tax bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-rise-trade-optimism-lingers-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYENQKJNW5OSNG427JPDOKVYAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷放松货币管制，美元黑市摇摇欲坠]]></title><description><![CDATA[在布宜诺斯艾利斯市中心的街道上，多年来严厉的货币管制催生了一个繁荣的美元黑市，在阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱伊的经济改革下，非法货币交易商大军发现日子不好过。【原文：On the streets of downtown Buenos Aires, where years of tough currency controls fermented a thriving black market for dollars, an army of illegal money traders are finding times hard under the economic reforms of Argentine President Javier Milei.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/argentinas-black-market-dollars-falters-currency-controls-are-eased-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KX4SBSZ4FLOLJOSPIWOT6KMJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻：美国股市反弹，零售商将发表关税观点]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的一系列美国零售业财报将进一步揭示关税变化背景下的经济影响，并对股市的大幅反弹构成考验。【原文：A batch of U.S. retail earnings reports in the coming week is set to shed more light on the economic fallout from the shifting tariff backdrop and test the stock market's sharp rebound.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-retailers-set-give-tariff-view-us-stock-market-roars-back-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7N4VHWHAYFOSNMOYETM4XB26FM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着美国发动贸易战，中国成为加拿大跨山管道原油的最大买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[船舶跟踪数据显示，中国已成为通过扩建的跨山管道运输的加拿大石油的最大客户，因为自该管道开始运行以来的一年里，美国的贸易战已改变了原油的流向。【原文：China has emerged as the top customer for Canadian oil shipped on the expanded Trans Mountain pipeline, ship tracking data showed, as a U.S. trade war has shifted crude flows in the year since the pipeline started operating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/with-us-trade-war-china-now-top-buyer-canadian-crude-trans-mountain-pipeline-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4YI3TCHNVNMNBCTKZTVCDU3K4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 投资者警惕并寻求医疗保险战略变革]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）的投资者被这家曾经可以预见的医疗保健巨头的失误所震惊，他们对其医疗保险优势（Medicare Advantage）健康保险业务明年的战略变化充满了戒心。【原文：UnitedHealth Group investors, stunned by missteps at the once predictable healthcare giant, are warily expecting strategic changes in its Medicare Advantage health insurance business over the next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-investors-wary-looking-medicare-strategic-change-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUCNNHHBEBLENBWZRO5U7MRYJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊发布 Alexa+ 人工智能数周后，一个谜团出现了：用户在哪里？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alexa，你的用户在哪里？【原文：Alexa, where are your users?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/weeks-after-amazons-alexa-ai-launch-mystery-where-are-users-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMFN2N473BOCBHZHNUR7KE2QZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市从关税风波中急速反弹后涨势可能放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美贸易休战后的市场动能使股市重回历史高位，但对剩余关税带来的经济影响的担忧以及股票估值的上升可能会在短期内减缓股市的涨势。【原文：Market momentum following the U.S.-China trade truce has put stocks back in sight of record highs but wariness about the economic fallout from remaining tariffs and higher equity valuations could slow gains in the near term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-stock-market-gains-may-slow-after-torrid-rebound-tariff-swoon-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HV5NWUZ7M5IYVL2OD5EQ7JNVIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，花旗将在中国裁减多达 200 个技术承包商职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士透露，花旗集团正在中国裁减多达 200 个信息技术（IT）承包商职位，因为该银行希望在全球范围内雇佣自己的员工来开展此类业务，以改善风险管理和数据治理。【原文：Citigroup is cutting up to 200 information technology (IT) contractor roles in China, two people familiar with the matter said, as the bank looks to hire its own staff globally for such operations to improve risk management and data governance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-cut-up-200-tech-contractor-roles-china-sources-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMNSAJGAVRIJZBBG64WVAIRFUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:55:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在欧盟反垄断调查中，微软提出以较低价格销售不含团队的 Office]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构周五表示，微软已提出以低于带Teams的Office的价格出售不带Teams的Office产品，并向竞争对手提供更好的服务和产品互操作性。【原文：Microsoft has offered to sell its Office product without Teams at a lower price than Office with Teams as well as offer rivals better interoperability access to its services and products, EU antitrust regulators said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-offers-sell-office-with-teams-lower-price-eu-antitrust-probe-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZ6PDZNFCFPFTFPRQTQCSXT2NY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南批准特朗普组织及其合作伙伴的 15 亿美元投资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据越南国营报纸《Tuoi Tre》周五报道，越南政府已经批准了特朗普组织及其合作伙伴在这个东南亚国家投资 15 亿美元建设高尔夫球场、酒店和房地产项目的计划。【原文：Vietnam's government has approved a plan by the Trump Organization and a partner to invest $1.5 billion in golf courses, hotels and real estate projects in the Southeast Asian country, the state-run Tuoi Tre newspaper reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/vietnam-approves-15-billion-investment-plan-by-trump-organization-partner-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFDQMSUOPNLD7H2Y3TAHLZWH3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔就 4.214 亿美元反垄断罚款与欧盟监管机构发生争执]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国芯片制造商英特尔周五与欧盟反垄断监管机构就近两年前因将竞争对手排除在市场之外而被处以3.76亿欧元（4.214亿美元）罚款一事发生争执，认为罚款数额过高且不公平。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Intel on Friday sparred with EU antitrust regulators over a 376 million euro ($421.4 million) fine levied nearly two years ago for excluding rivals from the market, arguing that it was disproportionate and unfair.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/intel-spars-with-eu-regulators-over-4214-million-antitrust-fine-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDKQP7DHKZNFPHS2FJOKAFTSYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Epic Games 称苹果在美国和欧盟商店屏蔽了《堡垒之夜》游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[史诗游戏公司（Epic Games）周五表示，苹果公司已禁止其 "堡垒之夜"（Fortnite）视频游戏在欧盟商店和 iPhone 制造商的美国应用程序商店中销售。【原文：Epic Games said on Friday that Apple has blocked its "Fortnite" video game on its store in the European Union and the iPhone maker's U.S. app store.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/apple-blocks-fortnite-game-us-eu-stores-epic-games-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQMDRQ5CZFMRLFJ7PP3G7B4CAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国部长在格里尔会议上要求豁免美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国贸工部长安德根（Ahn Deuk-geun）周五表示，他会见了美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer），并再次要求免除华盛顿的关税措施。【原文：South Korea's minister of trade and industry Ahn Deuk-geun said on Friday that he met U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer and asked again for a waiver from Washington's tariff measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-minister-asks-exemption-us-tariffs-greer-meeting-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WILWIK5KJ5OKZGHE5BUDTUNFGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普：阿联酋和美国就阿布扎比购买最先进人工智能芯片的途径达成一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，阿拉伯联合酋长国和美国已同意为海湾国家从美国公司购买一些最先进的人工智能半导体开辟一条道路。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday the United Arab Emirates and the United States have agreed to create a path for the Gulf country to buy some of the most advanced artificial intelligence semiconductors from U.S. companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/uae-us-agree-path-abu-dhabi-buy-most-advanced-ai-chips-trump-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H26YZ6PH2NNP3KDMLMOFHHJTYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大幅抛售后资金回流美国上市的中国 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中美关税休战提振了市场情绪，跟踪中国股市的主要美国上市交易所交易基金（ETF）在 5 月份录得资金流入。【原文：Major U.S.-listed exchange-traded funds (ETFs) that track Chinese stocks recorded inflows in May as a U.S.-China tariff truce boosted sentiment, following a heavy sell-off in the previous month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/capital-flows-back-us-listed-china-etfs-post-big-sell-off-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRPJBGX5BZKSFIMHPAN35KOTDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Charter 就与考克斯合并进行深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，宽带和有线电视服务提供商 Charter 正在与考克斯通信公司（Cox Communications）就合并事宜进行深入谈判，该交易对考克斯的估值超过 300 亿美元。【原文：Broadband and cable TV provider Charter is in advanced talks to combine with Cox Communications in a deal that values Cox at more than $30 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/charter-advanced-talks-combine-with-cox-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVZQ5SXFDRJKNOWYHCZE2OSQII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>