<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:38:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:38:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子称电视机业务受美国关税影响较小，因为墨西哥有产出]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子的一位高管周一表示，由于三星电子的电视机主要在墨西哥生产，预计其电视机业务受美国关税的影响将小于竞争对手。【原文：Samsung Electronics' television business is expected to be less affected by U.S. tariffs than rivals because its TVs are mainly produced in Mexico, an executive said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-elec-says-tv-business-be-less-affected-by-us-tariffs-than-rivals-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YN73C6HHYNISJAPFUXM7D5MLXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:16:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度塔塔汽车公司下滑 8%，因为豪华车部门 JLR 暂停对美出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）25%的关税生效后，生产豪华汽车的捷豹路虎（JLR）暂停向美国出口其英国制造的汽车，印度汽车制造商塔塔汽车公司（Tata Motors）的股价周一下挫8%。【原文：Shares of Indian automaker Tata Motors sank 8% on Monday after Jaguar Land Rover (JLR), which makes luxury cars, paused exports of its British-made cars to the U.S. following President Donald Trump's 25% tariff came into effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/indias-tata-motors-slides-8-after-luxury-arm-jlr-pauses-exports-us-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IC5KJU5SEBMMNN3XBOTTC4F6UY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛将美国经济衰退几率上调至 45]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）将美国未来12个月经济衰退的几率上调至45%，与其他投资银行一道修订了他们的预测，因为在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收关税之后，市场担心会爆发贸易战。【原文：Goldman Sachs has raised the odds of a U.S. recession to 45% in the next 12 months, joining other investment banks in revising their forecast as fears of a trade war grip markets after sweeping tariffs from U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-raises-odds-us-recession-45-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TISX7SIFQVIPZGZG4CZSZJT3UQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:56:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 Horizon Robotics 公司宣布与大众汽车合作开发先进的智能驾驶技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的地平线机器人公司（Horizon Robotics）周一宣布将与大众汽车公司合作开发先进的驾驶辅助解决方案，从而扩大了与德国汽车制造商的合作。【原文：China's Horizon Robotics announced on Monday that it would cooperate with Volkswagen on advanced driver assistance solution, extending its co-operation with the German automaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-horizon-robotics-announces-partnership-with-volkswagen-advanced-smart-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IULCQT7F6ZPNTI47TX4QOUGANM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:45:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税 "药方 "为全球市场注入动荡因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）警告外国政府，要取消全面关税，他们将不得不支付 "一大笔钱"，并将这些关税称为 "药品"，这引发了周一全球金融市场的进一步动荡。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump warned foreign governments they would have to pay "a lot of money" to lift sweeping tariffs, characterising the duties as "medicine" and triggering further carnage across global financial markets on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trumps-tariff-medicine-injects-turmoil-into-global-markets-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2QFVOZCXRLJ7E4PGSTX646Y2I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度官员称，尽管美国加征关税，印度仍将维持 2025/26 年的经济增长预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度财政部一位官员表示，尽管美国新关税导致全球经济混乱，但如果油价保持在每桶70美元以下，印度很可能实现2025/26财年（4月至3月）6.3%-6.8%的预期增长目标。【原文：India is likely to meet its projected growth target of 6.3%-6.8% for the 2025/26 fiscal year (April-March) if oil prices remain below $70 per barrel, despite global disruptions due to new U.S. tariffs, a finance ministry official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-maintains-202526-growth-projection-despite-us-tariffs-official-says-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYZKTSYJIVLWTOMA343LKR2WRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行将降息25个基点，经济学家称美国加征关税后可能进一步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计新西兰央行将于周三将其官方现金利率下调25个基点至3.50%，经济学家称，随着该行对美国关税及其潜在的全球经济影响做出反应，2025年可能会有更多的降息举措。【原文：New Zealand’s central bank is expected to cut its official cash rate by 25 basis points to 3.50% on Wednesday and economists say the bank could make more cuts in 2025 as it reacts to U.S. tariffs and their potential global economic fallout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/rbnz-cut-rates-by-25bps-economists-say-more-cuts-possible-after-us-tariffs-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SM45I7UO7BNULJJELSJK6LOSMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国茶壶炼油厂开工率提高，但需求困境和制裁带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士和分析师表示，中国陷入困境的独立炼油企业的运行率最近有所回升，但近期仍面临国内燃料需求不振的压力，以及美国制裁和关税带来的供应风险。【原文：Run rates for China's struggling independent oil refiners have nudged up recently, but still face near-term pressure over tepid domestic fuel demand and supply risks from U.S. sanctions and tariffs, industry participants and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/china-teapot-oil-refiners-improve-run-rates-demand-woes-sanctions-weigh-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PDAMZUKK5OMBKOAOQ2V6U3BFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 02:58:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税在即，韩国准备采取支持措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部长周一表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的25%关税于本周生效之前，韩国政府将为有迫切需求的行业准备支持措施。【原文：South Korea's finance minister said on Monday the government would prepare support measures for sectors with urgent needs, ahead of U.S. President Donald Trump's 25% tariff, which will come into force this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-prepare-support-measures-us-tariffs-loom-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBQT2TZHGFP6NDJ6OI4DD6WYN4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 02:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LG 能源解决方案第一季度营业利润增长 138]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车和特斯拉的电动汽车（EV）电池供应商 LG 能源解决方案公司（LGES）周一预计，其季度营业利润将增长 138%。【原文：LG Energy Solution (LGES) , an electric vehicle (EV) battery supplier for General Motors and Tesla , estimated on Monday a 138% rise in its quarterly operating profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lg-energy-solution-flags-138-rise-q1-operating-profit-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVGKMIY7YZMHNGYJAODDMKF7CI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 01:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 AFR 报道，Star Entertainment 同意 Bally's 提出的控制权收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《澳大利亚金融评论报》（AFR）周一报道，澳大利亚明星娱乐公司（Star Entertainment）已同意一项再融资协议，美国同行百利公司（Bally's）将控制这家陷入困境的赌场运营商。【原文：Australia's Star Entertainment has agreed to a refinancing deal that would see U.S. peer Bally's take control of the embattled casino operator, the Australian Financial Review (AFR) reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/australias-star-entertainment-agrees-take-control-offer-ballys-afr-reports-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATEEPYUHXNJYRDZVZ3XS3SSVEE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 01:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比尔-阿克曼警告特朗普正在失去商界领袖的信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[支持唐纳德-特朗普竞选总统的亿万富翁基金经理比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）说，美国领导人正在失去商界领袖的信任，应该暂停贸易战。【原文：Billionaire fund manager Bill Ackman, who endorsed Donald Trump's run for President, said the U.S. leader was losing the confidence of business leaders and should pause his trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bill-ackman-warns-trump-is-losing-business-leaders-confidence-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4YLTBNQSBK5XC5Q5GME3PPPTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 01:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛预计中国进一步放宽财政政策将抵消更高的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）在一份报告中表示，预计中国将进一步放宽财政政策，以抵消美国上周末宣布提高关税对经济增长的拖累。【原文：Goldman Sachs said it expects further fiscal easing from China to offset growth drag from higher tariffs announced by the United States late last week, it said in a report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/goldman-sachs-expects-further-fiscal-easing-china-offset-higher-tariffs-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLREHNAKYBOIVFVDHFAQNBQ3JM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:49:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税打击美元，避风港日元和瑞郎大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对全球征收全面关税后，投资者周一抛售美元，涌入日元和瑞士法郎等避险货币。【原文：Investors sold the dollar and poured into safe havens like the yen and Swiss franc on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump unleashed sweeping tariffs on the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/safe-havens-yen-swiss-franc-surge-trumps-tariffs-hit-dollar-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZPMYN4DBBMZHF7NUALBJSMQWE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:13:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚伍德赛德能源公司将向斯通尼克公司出售路易斯安那液化天然气项目 40% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚能源公司伍德赛德能源（Woodside Energy）周一表示，将向美国投资公司斯顿皮克（Stonepeak）出售其路易斯安那液化天然气基础设施项目 40% 的股份。【原文：Australian energy company Woodside Energy said on Monday that it will sell a 40% stake in its Louisiana LNG Infrastructure project to U.S.-based investment firm Stonepeak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-woodside-energy-sell-40-stake-louisiana-lng-project-stonepeak-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQG2CTLVJFPTFMIH6VD6MZPBWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受通胀影响，日本 2 月份实际工资连续两个月下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本劳工部周一的数据显示，由于通胀率上升，日本2月份实际工资连续第二个月下降，同时日本国内对美国关税的影响产生了更广泛的担忧。【原文：Japanese real wages dropped for a second straight month in February due to higher inflation, labour ministry data showed on Monday, amid broader worries in Japan about the impact of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-feb-real-wages-down-2nd-straight-month-inflation-bites-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYS6BXXPA5NEBHVE6R37QBT2A4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 23:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普被问及市场时说，有时你必须 "吃药]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日在被问及市场下跌问题时说，有时你必须吃药，并补充说他并非有意制造市场抛售。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Sunday said that sometimes you have to take medicine when asked about falling markets, adding that he was not intentionally engineering a market selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-asked-about-markets-says-sometimes-you-have-take-medicine-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXCNG4BOQJNKZMA5IIDK7O7NLI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 23:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称，丰田将把电动车型增加到 15 款，目标是到 2027 年生产 100 万辆电动车]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经新闻》（Nikkei）周日称，丰田的目标是到 2027 年自主开发出约 15 款电动汽车，届时年产量将达到约 100 万辆。【原文：Toyota aims to have about 15 electric vehicle models developed on its own by 2027 and is targeting production of about 1 million cars a year by then, the Nikkei newspaper said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-boost-ev-models-15-targets-producing-1-million-by-2027-nikkei-says-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2XABZ4H7FLX3CKMMRR7QZT4YI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 23:34:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国股票期货暴跌预示华尔街将再次暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日晚间，美国股票期货大幅低开，表明在特朗普政府上周宣布加征关税后连续两天的大跌仍在继续，这两天的大跌使数万亿美元的股票价值化为乌有。【原文：U.S. stock futures opened sharply lower late on Sunday, suggesting a continuation of the two-day selloff that wiped trillions from equity values after the Trump administration's tariffs announcement last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-us-stock-futures-tumble-indicating-another-plummet-wall-street-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JENOHB35OBKYPKEME2VBU2RI7I</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 23:17:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货和原油暴跌，市场期待美国降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲市场开局不利，因为华尔街期货大跌，市场认为美国经济衰退的风险不断增加，美国最早可能在五月降息。【原文：Asian markets were in for a rough start on Monday as Wall Street futures plunged and markets wagered the mounting risk of a U.S. recession could see U.S. rate cuts as early as May.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6XTXBVQKBJSFM4Y26FYXRFWNM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 22:56:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[担心全球贸易战可能拖累经济，油价跌幅扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税进行报复之后，人们越来越担心全球贸易战可能导致全球经济放缓并削弱石油需求，因此油价周一下跌超过 3%，延续了前一周的跌势。【原文：Oil prices fell more than 3% on Monday, extending losses from the previous week, on growing concerns that a global trade war could slow the global economy and weaken oil demand, following China's retaliation against U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-extend-losses-fears-global-trade-war-could-slow-economy-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4QU4YQYCVMNNHEYA4SB6ZCPB4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 22:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街股票期货大幅低开]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普上周宣布对美国贸易伙伴全面征收关税后，投资者担心全球贸易战可能会将美国经济推向衰退，华尔街股票期货周日大幅低开，暗示本交易周开局不利。【原文：Wall Street stock futures opened sharply lower on Sunday suggesting a rough start to the trading week as investors worried that a global trade war could push the U.S. economy into a recession after President Donald Trump's announcement last week of sweeping tariffs against U.S. trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-stock-futures-open-sharply-lower-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSY5QIHRFZM4TL4WOY5X4Y2DCI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 22:19:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于人工智能芯片销售疲软和代工厂亏损，三星第一季度利润将下降 21]]></title><description><![CDATA[受人工智能芯片销售低迷和合约芯片制造业务持续亏损的影响，三星电子周二预计第一季度利润将下降 21%。【原文：Samsung Electronics is expected to forecast a 21% drop in the first quarter profit on Tuesday, hurt by sluggish sales of artificial intelligence chips and continued losses in its contract chip manufacturing business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/samsung-q1-profit-drop-21-weak-ai-chip-sales-foundry-losses-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWWEYXQJ3FOUTE7CH4VVQZM3M4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 22:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币最后下跌 5%，报 78892.92 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币是全球市值最大的加密货币，格林尼治标准时间周日18时55分，比特币下跌约5%，报78892.92美元。【原文：Bitcoin, the world's largest cryptocurrency by market value, was down by around 5% at $78,892.92 at 1855 GMT on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-last-down-5-7889292-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTX2XTQCGNKK3AQ46OOO6RB34Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 19:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[周一开盘前美国投资者将面临更多波动和颠簸]]></title><description><![CDATA[在上周华尔街因特朗普政府宣布加征关税而大跌之后，投资者紧张地等待着美国股市开盘，预计随着其他国家做出反应，本周又将出现动荡。【原文：Investors were nervously awaiting the open of U.S. trading after Wall Street's selloff last week following the Trump administration's tariffs announcement, anticipating another week of turbulence as other nations react.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-investors-braced-more-volatility-bumps-ahead-monday-trading-open-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSA7V4QVL5P7FE4W3RHJFNBT34</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 18:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航运巨头达飞轮船公司（CMA CGM）与法国人工智能初创企业合作，瞄准客户服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[航运巨头法国达飞海运集团（CMA CGM）与科技初创公司 Mistral AI 周日公布了一项价值 1 亿欧元的合作计划，预计将迅速提高生产力。【原文：Shipping giant CMA CGM and tech startup Mistral AI expect rapid productivity gains from a 100 million euro partnership unveiled on Sunday, which the French firms also touted as a commitment to their home country amid the global trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/shipping-giant-cma-cgm-french-ai-startup-target-customer-service-tie-up-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLOS7SR4M5KRTDWFCHTDMLOMTM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普顾问称50多个国家已与白宫联系开始贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的一位高级经济顾问周日表示，在美国官员试图为引发全球动荡的全面新关税辩护之际，已有50多个国家与白宫接触，希望开始贸易谈判。【原文：More than 50 countries have reached out to the White House to begin trade talks, a top economic adviser to U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday as U.S. officials sought to defend sweeping new tariffs that have unleashed global turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/more-than-50-countries-have-contacted-white-house-start-trade-talks-trump-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GD2GAAVWPJKWTEDCVVMXELHJFI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 14:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普征收 20% 关税为意大利葡萄酒在美国的前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对欧洲进口商品征收 20% 的关税后，生产商和进口商表示，普罗塞克、布鲁内罗-蒙塔尔奇诺和其他意大利葡萄酒在美国的前景越来越暗淡。【原文：The outlook for Prosecco, Brunello di Montalcino and other Italian wines in the United States is increasingly gloomy, producers and importers said, following President Donald Trump's imposition of a 20% tariff on European imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-20-tariff-clouds-future-italian-wines-us-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2FAEUJYMNI2ZPLEGJBTAITS5U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 13:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[内塔尼亚胡表示将在与特朗普的会晤中寻求关税减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列总理本雅明-内塔尼亚胡周日表示，他希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普本周在华盛顿会晤时能放宽对以色列征收的关税。【原文：Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said on Sunday he hopes U.S. President Donald Trump will ease tariffs imposed on Israel when the two meet in Washington this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/netanyahu-says-will-seek-relief-tariffs-meeting-with-trump-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FX5J32FORFJKPHTSYL6XO4GZ6Y</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 12:56:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着协议谈判取得进展，印度不太可能对特朗普的关税进行报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位印度政府官员表示，印度不打算对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对来自亚洲国家的进口商品征收 26% 的关税进行报复，并引述了两国正在进行的协议谈判。【原文：India does not plan to retaliate against U.S. President Donald Trump's 26% tariff on imports from the Asian nation, an Indian government official said, citing ongoing talks for a deal between the countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india-unlikely-retaliate-against-trumps-tariffs-deal-talks-progress-sources-say-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3PZT2ZU4ZMNPN4ZXZLAZHARDE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 12:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>