<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 18:36:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 18:36:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[以色列 8 月 CPI 跃升至 3.6% 的 10 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列中央统计局周日公布的数据显示，以色列 8 月份的通货膨胀率飙升至近一年以来的最高水平，这降低了以色列在短期内下调更多利率的可能性。【原文：Israel's inflation rate surged in August to its highest rate in nearly a year, data from the Central Bureau of Statistics showed on Sunday, reducing the likelihood of more interest rate cuts anytime soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-cpi-jumps-10-month-high-36-august-2024-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MM4WGURNFRJ7RPD6B7U6QV5UII</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 15:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[秘鲁 7 月经济同比增长 4.47]]></title><description><![CDATA[秘鲁政府统计局（INEI）周日发布报告称，7 月份秘鲁经济同比增长 4.47%。【原文：Peru's economy expanded 4.47% in July compared with the same month last year, the government's INEI statistics agency reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/peru-economy-expands-447-july-year-on-year-2024-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZD2UG7YGZPDBFCNSIESC5T2WY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 15:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铝业公司将以 11 亿美元的价格出售其在 Ma'aden 合资企业中持有的 25.1% 股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铝业公司周日表示，将以 11 亿美元的价格向 Ma'aden 公司出售其在 Ma'aden 合资企业中 25.1% 的股份。【原文：U.S. aluminium maker Alcoa said on Sunday that it would sell a 25.1% stake in its Ma'aden joint venture to Ma'aden for $1.1 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/alcoa-sell-its-251-stake-maaden-joint-venture-11-billion-2024-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZ5VV3ZSBZNB3GRLU2RPARNLTI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 13:58:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司与飞行员工会达成协议，避免了罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司周日早些时候表示，该公司已与飞行员工会就一项为期四年的新集体协议达成临时协议，该协议将避免近期的罢工或停工。【原文：Air Canada said early on Sunday it had reached a tentative agreement with its pilots union over a new four-year collective agreement, in a deal that will avert a near-term strike or lockout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/air-canada-reaches-agreement-with-pilots-union-averting-strike-2024-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUUWVKMIFFKK7NYBWF3WURKKYU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 05:10:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，由于对经济增长的担忧加剧，加拿大央行行长提高了降息前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周日报道，加拿大央行行长蒂夫-马克莱姆（Tiff Macklem）为加快降息步伐敞开了大门。【原文：Bank of Canada Governor Tiff Macklem opened the door to increasing the pace of interest rate cuts, the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/bank-canada-head-raises-prospect-rate-cuts-growth-fears-mount-ft-reports-2024-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXZWUF2ZXBLVDKSJJWP7FF7G4M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 04:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会领导人称，工人要求提高工资，波音罢工可能会持续下去]]></title><description><![CDATA[工会领导人乔恩-霍尔登（Jon Holden）周六在接受美国国家公共广播电台（NPR）采访时说，波音公司的罢工 "可能会持续一段时间"，因为工人们相信他们可以获得更大的工资增长和更好的养老金。【原文：A strike at Boeing "could go on for a while" as workers are confident they can get bigger wage increases and an improved pension, union leader Jon Holden said in an interview with National Public Radio (NPR) on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-could-drag-workers-push-higher-wages-union-leader-says-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5V6FXLS55I33JCQO2P6JMEOCI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 22:53:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，阿克塞尔-施普林格与 KKR 接近达成 135 亿美元的分拆协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周六援引四位知情人士的话报道，德国亿万富翁马蒂亚斯-多普弗纳（Mathias Doepfner）和 KKR 即将达成一项协议，分拆传媒巨头阿克塞尔-施普林格（Axel Springer）。【原文：German billionaire Mathias Doepfner and KKR are nearing a deal to split up the media giant Axel Springer, the Financial Times reported on Saturday, citing four people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/axel-springer-kkr-near-deal-135-bln-break-up-financial-times-reports-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIRJUE62JVNVZCZA4SE6ODOQLQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 18:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[风暴过后，美国墨西哥湾近 30% 的石油产量停产]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国近海能源监管机构称，飓风弗朗辛过后，周六美国墨西哥湾近 30% 的原油生产和 41% 的天然气生产仍处于停产状态。【原文：Nearly 30% of U.S. Gulf of Mexico crude oil production and 41% of its natural gas production remained offline on Saturday following Hurricane Francine, the U.S. offshore energy regulator said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/nearly-30-us-gulf-mexico-oil-output-offline-after-storm-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAMSVP5RRRJRVLQQC76AFUVAOE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 18:13:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿联酋不打算与美国重启 F-35 战斗机谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿联酋政府的一位高级官员周六表示，无论11月谁入主白宫，阿联酋都不会恢复与美国就价值数十亿美元的F-35战机交易进行谈判。【原文：The United Arab Emirates does not expect to resume talks with the U.S. about a multi-billion dollar deal for F-35 warplanes, irrespective of who is elected to the White House in November, a senior UAE government official said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/uae-does-not-plan-re-open-f-35-fighter-jet-talks-with-us-uae-official-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EK7SGNRHPJLDHJKHGJOXPBBBRY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 14:38:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼与 DirecTV 达成协议，恢复 1100 万卫星电视用户的节目服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔特-迪斯尼（Walt Disney）和 DirecTV 周六宣布双方已达成原则性协议，恢复向卫星电视供应商的 1100 多万用户提供大学橄榄球和其他节目。【原文：Walt Disney and DirecTV announced they have reached an agreement in principle on Saturday, restoring college football and other programming to the satellite TV provider's more than 11 million subscribers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-directv-reach-deal-that-restores-programming-11-million-satellite-tv-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOZNL3IHGNJP3OL4YWNTBQDQLM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 13:11:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官称，受波音罢工影响，瑞安航空明年夏季可能减少五架飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空集团首席执行官迈克尔-奥利里（Michael O'Leary）周六表示，波音公司工人的长期罢工可能会使该公司到明年夏季接收的飞机数量从预计的 25 架减少到 20 架。【原文：Ryanair Group CEO Michael O'Leary said on Saturday a prolonged Boeing workers' strike may cut the number of aircraft it receives by next summer to 20 from an anticipated 25.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ryanair-may-get-five-fewer-planes-by-next-summer-due-boeing-strike-ceo-says-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OY243VWVP5KJHPL5G45TT2NHI4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国反对美国加征关税，誓言采取措施捍卫本国企业利益]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周六发表声明称，北京坚决反对美国对中国进口商品加征关税，并敦促美国立即纠正其 "错误行为"，取消对中国商品加征的所有关税。【原文：Beijing firmly opposes U.S. tariff hikes on Chinese imports, China's commerce ministry said in a statement on Saturday, urging the U.S. to immediately correct its "wrongdoings" and lift all tariffs imposed on Chinese goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/china-opposes-us-tariff-hikes-vows-steps-defend-its-firms-interests-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNWJAN52QBLRBINMLV6K7JLEWU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 11:33:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度对亚马逊和 Flipkart 的反垄断调查结果如何？]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度的反垄断调查发现，亚马逊和沃尔玛旗下的 Flipkart 违反了当地的竞争法，它们优先照顾某些卖家，优先刊登某些商品，并大幅打折，损害了其他公司的利益。【原文：Indian antitrust investigations have found that Amazon and Walmart's Flipkart violated local competition laws by giving preference to some sellers, prioritising certain listings, and steeply discounting products, hurting other companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/what-are-indias-antitrust-findings-against-amazon-flipkart-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZJMZZVWXZOGFPWXTBXNGSCZ6M</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 09:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：印度指责三星、小米与亚马逊和 Flipkart 勾结]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的监管报告称，三星、小米和其他智能手机公司与亚马逊和沃尔玛旗下的 Flipkart 相互勾结，在这两家电子商务公司的印度网站上独家发布产品，违反了反垄断法。【原文：Samsung, Xiaomi and other smartphone companies colluded with Amazon and Walmart's Flipkart to exclusively launch products on the e-commerce firms' Indian websites in breach of antitrust laws, according to regulatory reports seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-accuses-samsung-xiaomi-colluding-with-amazon-flipkart-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCH2IPIJB5KCLHFZ5SGLQXFCJE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 09:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国1-8月外商直接投资同比下降31.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周六表示，1-8月，外商对华直接投资达5,801.9亿元人民币（818.0亿美元），同比下降31.5%。【原文：Foreign direct investment into China amounted to 580.19 billion yuan ($81.80 billion) in January-August, down 31.5% from the same period last year, the Chinese commerce ministry said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-jan-aug-fdi-down-315-yy-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTRVI3SBYBLQPPN6QAF22AHQVA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 09:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚被禁教派涉嫌虐童案再次成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[Global Ikhwan Services and Business Holdings (GISB) 在其网站上称自己是马来西亚的一家企业集团，其愿景是按照先知穆罕默德的教导，实现伊斯兰的生活方式。【原文：On its website, Global Ikhwan Services and Business Holdings (GISB) describes itself as a Malaysian conglomerate with a vision to implement the Islamic way of life in line with the teachings of the Prophet Muhammad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/alleged-child-abuse-case-puts-banned-malaysian-sect-back-spotlight-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VICB5IQJ7BIOBGCO3RCU7L23AI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 09:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相希望之星：日美面临中国廉价钢铁的共同挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本首相主要候选人小泉晋二郎周六表示，日本和美国应避免在钢铁业问题上发生对抗，并在全球第一大钢铁生产国中国的竞争中携手合作。【原文：Japan and the United States should avoid confrontation about the steel industry and work together amid competition from China, the world's top steelmaker, leading prime ministerial candidate Shinjiro Koizumi said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/japan-us-face-shared-challenge-cheap-china-steel-japan-pm-hopeful-says-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6RPWDGRDRKWXOUO3IEYCKKBOU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 08:46:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相希望之星高市敦促日本央行避免加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本负责经济安全的大臣、执政党领导人竞选的主要候选人佐佐江-高市（Sanae Takaichi）周五表示，由于经济正处于摆脱停滞的边缘，央行不应加息。【原文：Sanae Takaichi, Japan's minister in charge of economic security and a leading candidate in the ruling party's leadership race, said on Friday the central bank should not raise interest rates yet as the economy is on the cusp of emerging from stagnation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/japans-pm-hopeful-takaichi-urges-boj-avoid-raising-rates-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFRA2PN53NPPVPK6AHPG52PJXM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 03:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国工厂产出和零售销售下滑，需要加强刺激政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份，中国工业产值增长放缓至五个月来的最低点，零售销售和新房价格也进一步走低。【原文：China's industrial output growth slowed to a five-month low in August, while retail sales and new home prices also weakened further, raising the case for bolder stimulus to shore up the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-august-factory-output-retail-sales-miss-expectations-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGV37ESPSFNABLD5XK7HZ3Y4YI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 02:27:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 8 月新房价格创逾 9 年最快降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六的官方数据显示，由于支持性措施未能刺激房地产行业出现有意义的复苏，8月份中国新房价格创下九年多来的最快降幅。【原文：China's new home prices fell at the fastest pace in more than nine years in August, official data showed on Saturday, as supportive measures failed to spur a meaningful recovery in the property sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-new-home-prices-fall-fastest-pace-over-9-years-august-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UMCK27Y6ZMKBORKVNGED6SLTU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 01:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，OpenAI 1500 亿美元的惊人估值取决于对公司结构的颠覆]]></title><description><![CDATA[据直接了解此事的消息人士称，OpenAI 的新一轮融资预计将以可转换票据的形式进行，其 1,500 亿美元的估值将取决于这家 ChatGPT 制造商能否改变其公司结构并取消投资者的利润上限。【原文：OpenAI's new financing round is expected to come in the form of convertible notes, according to sources with direct knowledge of the matter, who said its $150 billion valuation will be contingent on whether the ChatGPT-maker can upend its corporate structure and remove a profit cap for investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openais-stunning-150-billion-valuation-hinges-upending-corporate-structure-2024-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTP6GAMGNBM73LFVUWRDMVU2I4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，DirecTV 和 Dish 正在就合并卫星电视业务再次进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，AT&amp;T 公司和合资伙伴 TPG 公司正在洽谈将其 DirecTV 服务与 Dish 合并的事宜。【原文：AT&amp;T Inc and joint-venture partner TPG Inc are in talks to combine their DirecTV service with Dish , Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/directv-dish-are-talks-again-merge-satellite-tv-businesses-bloomberg-news-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6C3CPJOHORMXLH6XKL54SQD6CU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 23:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，英特尔获得 35 亿美元资助，为美国军方生产芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，英特尔公司已正式获得高达 35 亿美元的联邦拨款，为美国国防部生产半导体，此前该芯片制造商与美国官员达成了一项具有约束力的协议。【原文：Intel Corp has officially qualified for as much as $3.5 billion in federal grants to make semiconductors for the U.S Department of Defense, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter, after the chipmaker reached a binding agreement with U.S officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-qualifies-35-billion-grants-make-chips-us-military-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGNYDQ6SZVPSJLR2JHV54W6VX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 22:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家称波音罢工可能加剧全球喷气客机短缺]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内高管和分析师表示，波音公司16年来的首次罢工可能会进一步加剧全球喷气式客机的短缺，而这种短缺一直在推高机票价格，迫使航空公司延长老式喷气式客机的飞行时间。【原文：Boeing's first strike in 16 years could further compound global shortages of jetliners that have been pushing up airfares and forcing airlines to keep older jets flying longer, industry executives and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-could-exacerbate-global-jetliner-shortage-experts-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WC47EAY3TZOW3AS54I4N6N7P2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 22:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊坎企业赢得投资者诉讼驳回令]]></title><description><![CDATA[伊坎企业（Icahn Enterprises）赢得了一项诉讼的撤诉，该诉讼称伊坎企业通过发放不可持续的高股息来支持其主要投资者、亿万富翁卡尔-伊坎（Carl Icahn）的个人借贷和经济利益，从而人为抬高了股价。【原文：Icahn Enterprises won the dismissal of a lawsuit claiming it artificially inflated its share price by issuing unsustainably high dividends to support the personal borrowing and financial interests of billionaire Carl Icahn, its majority investor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/icahn-enterprises-wins-dismissal-investor-lawsuit-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXQS4DBJ2JMKJNAQV2PFI26Y7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 21:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美联储准备开始缩表，利率变动的规模和速度成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储是下周的焦点，因为美国央行将在货币政策会议上降息多少以及未来几个月降低借贷成本的步伐都存在不确定性。【原文：The Federal Reserve is in focus next week, as uncertainty swirls over how much the U.S. central bank will cut interest rates at its monetary policy meeting and the pace at which it will reduce borrowing costs in coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-size-speed-rate-moves-focus-fed-poised-start-cuts-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KS4L2V2JBKD7CRC7TN56HNWZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 21:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司面临 9 月 23 日的审查截止日期]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士称，美国一个强大的国家安全小组正在审查新日铁以 149 亿美元竞购美国钢铁公司的交易，该小组将在 9 月 23 日的最后期限前就白宫是否应阻止该交易提出建议。【原文：A powerful U.S. national security panel reviewing Nippon Steel's $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel faces a Sept. 23 deadline to recommend whether the White House should block the deal, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steel-bid-us-steel-faces-sept-23-review-deadline-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROXQ5FSAIJMUXMZ7F7G6NVG5OE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 21:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司寻求推迟恢复每天四班飞往中国的美国航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周五以中国市场持续面临挑战为由，请求美国交通部允许其推迟恢复每天四班飞往中国的航班。【原文：Delta Air Lines on Friday asked the U.S. Transportation Department to allow it to delay resuming four daily flights to China, citing ongoing challenges in the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-seeks-delay-resuming-four-daily-us-flights-china-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EZ6TJTOA5MDLPMDLJKJY7JFSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ADM 公司碳捕集项目发生泄漏，违反了美国水法和许可证规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护署（U.S. Environmental Protection Agency）发现，位于伊利诺伊州的美国首个大型地下碳封存设施发生泄漏，阿彻-丹尼尔斯-米德兰（Archer-Daniels-Midland）农业综合企业周五证实，该公司违反了联邦安全饮用水规定及其地下注入许可。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has found that Archer-Daniels-Midland violated federal safe drinking water rules and its underground injection permit with a leak at the first major U.S. underground carbon sequestration facility in Illinois, the agribusiness company confirmed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/adm-violates-us-water-laws-permit-after-leak-carbon-capture-project-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2OXTM3C35OG7LV2GZAXBX2ZXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[山姆-班克曼-弗里德的律师在上诉中称，陪审团只看到了 "一半的情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[山姆-班克曼-弗里德的律师周五在上诉中辩称，陪审团判定山姆-班克曼-弗里德从其 FTX 加密货币交易所的客户那里窃取了数十亿美元，但只看到了 "一半的情况"，因为法官不允许引入关键证据。【原文：The jury that convicted Sam Bankman-Fried of stealing billions of dollars from customers of his FTX cryptocurrency exchange only saw "half the picture" because the judge did not allow in critical evidence, his lawyer argued in their appeal on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/sam-bankman-frieds-jury-only-saw-half-picture-lawyer-says-appeal-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K36SGEKVZFMWTIFMLWANFRDFQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:05:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>