<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 22:10:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 22:10:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[REUTERS 活动 汽车制造商应对美国电动车市场低迷的办法：混合动力车和廉价车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦政府取消了为电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车提供 7500 美元的税收减免，一个月后，汽车制造商正在重新考虑他们的产品线，并把重点放在更便宜的车型上，以保持汽车买家的兴趣。【原文：One month after a $7,500 federal U.S. tax credit for electric vehicles and plug-in hybrids was scrapped, automakers are rethinking their product pipelines and focusing on cheaper models to keep car buyers interested, company executives said on Wednesday at a Reuters conference in Detroit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/reuters-events-carmakers-answer-to-us-ev-lull-hybrids-cheaper-models-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTWRRCG655LJTPRYQF376L2PW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 22:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将维持利率不变，日元压力迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[人们普遍预计日本央行周四将维持利率稳定，但重申决心继续提高仍然较低的借贷成本，以抵御日元进一步下跌可能扩大通胀压力的风险。【原文：The Bank of Japan is widely expected to keep interest rates steady on Thursday, but reiterate its resolve to continue pushing up still-low borrowing costs to fend off the risk of further yen falls that could broaden inflationary pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-seen-keeping-rates-hold-yen-pressure-looms-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IJDC6LYQRN25CANSRDYBXBU5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 22:01:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚杂货商 Coles 第一季度销售收入增长 3.9]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Coles 集团周四公布，第一季度销售收入增长 3.9%，主要得益于电子商务销售的两位数增长，从而推动了超市部门的盈利。【原文：Australia's Coles Group reported a 3.9% rise in first-quarter sales revenue on Thursday, driven by a double-digit growth in e-commerce sales that boosted its supermarket division earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/australian-grocer-coles-posts-39-rise-first-quarter-sales-revenue-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTOIRSERQJOJBGKYLPS5YH2HFA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[劳动力市场疲软，Dayforce 季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，Dayforce 公布的第三季度利润低于分析师预期，原因是劳动力市场的不确定性和对贸易关税日益增长的担忧促使企业控制软件支出。【原文：Dayforce reported third-quarter profit below analysts' estimates on Wednesday, as uncertainty in the labor market and growing concerns over trade tariffs prompted companies to rein in software spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dayforce-misses-quarterly-profit-estimates-labor-market-softens-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7FABXTEEFKURBK3XC4VLLXKSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自由亚洲电台在政府关门之际暂停新闻业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[自由亚洲电台（Radio Free Asia）周三表示，在美国联邦政府关门即将满一个月之际，该台将在 "资金不确定 "的情况下暂停编辑业务。【原文：Radio Free Asia said on Wednesday it was suspending its editorial operations amid "funding uncertainty" as the U.S. federal government shutdown edges toward its one-month mark.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/radio-free-asia-suspend-news-operations-amid-government-shutdown-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJLLO3S77RNPXOO7FCKXOU2UEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:19:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森美孚任命格雷戈里-加兰为董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[石油巨头埃克森美孚（Exxon Mobil）周三表示，已任命业内资深人士格雷戈里-加兰（Gregory Garland）为公司董事会成员，自 11 月 3 日起生效。【原文：Oil major Exxon Mobil said on Wednesday it has named industry veteran Gregory Garland to its board of directors, effective November 3.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-mobil-names-gregory-garland-board-directors-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YK7N7XY3BBJQTEQU2SCLJ6XVCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：英伟达蓬勃发展，美联储宽松政策降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，华尔街涨跌不一，此前美联储降低了利率，但表示 12 月份降息的可能性不大，而英伟达（Nvidia）成为全球首家市值达 5 万亿美元的公司。投资者现在将注意力转向周四美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与中国国家主席习近平的会晤。【原文：Wall Street was mixed on Wednesday after the Federal Reserve lowered interest rates but signaled a cut in December was in the balance, while Nvidia became the world's first $5 trillion company. Investors now turn their attention to Thursday's meeting between U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5RAPUXEWFITZD3FSNZO5YEZLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KLA 预测第二季度收入增长，但中国市场持续疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[KLA 公司周三预计第二季度营收将高于华尔街预期，主要得益于人工智能对其芯片制造工具的强劲需求，但同时也指出了中美贸易紧张局势对其中国业务造成的重大风险。【原文：KLA Corp forecast second-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, banking on strong AI-linked demand for its chipmaking tools, while flagging significant risks to its China business amid Sino-U.S. trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kla-forecasts-upbeat-second-quarter-revenue-china-weakness-persists-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMDYVLQYT5K4XLGG5VLYZ64VDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:04:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利特纳里斯公司销售额意外增长 2%，得益于美国和加拿大钻井的稳定发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利钢管制造商 Tenaris 周三公布，第三季度净销售额意外增长 2%，原因是北美地区稳定的钻探活动帮助抵消了其他地区的疲软，但 Tenaris 警告称，利润率将受到关税成本 "全面影响 "的打击。【原文：Italian steel pipe maker Tenaris posted a surprise 2% rise in third-quarter net sales on Wednesday, as stable drilling activity in North America helped offset weakness in other regions, but warned margins would be hit by the "full impact" of tariff costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italys-tenaris-posts-2-rise-quarterly-net-sales-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQTVH46BTVJQPI7EFGWTQZACPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wolfspeed 退出破产程序后第一季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wolfspeed 公司周三公布的第一季度利润疲软，凸显了这家美国芯片制造商在从破产中恢复和面对低迷需求时所面临的挑战，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌超过 7%。【原文：Wolfspeed on Wednesday reported a weaker first-quarter profit, highlighting the challenges facing the U.S. chipmaker as it recovers from bankruptcy and confronts subdued demand, sending its shares down more than 7% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wolfspeed-posts-weaker-profit-first-quarter-after-exiting-bankruptcy-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2O4NZDIVVNNPCREA67R2FCM4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院民主党人敦促特朗普不要为贸易协议放宽对中国的国家安全限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[以查克-舒默（Chuck Schumer）为首的一群参议院民主党人周三敦促唐纳德-特朗普总统不要为了达成贸易协议而取消对中国的国家安全限制。【原文：A group of Senate Democrats led by Chuck Schumer on Wednesday urged President Donald Trump not to lift national security restrictions on China in pursuit of a trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/senate-democrats-urge-trump-not-ease-national-security-restrictions-china-trade-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3ATIJA3OZNTDEJOXA4VSPZ3PQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能需求激增，ServiceNow上调年度订阅收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受人工智能软件解决方案需求增长的推动，ServiceNow 周三上调了年度订购收入预期。【原文：ServiceNow raised its annual subscription revenue forecast on Wednesday, driven by growing demand for its artificial intelligence powered software solutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/servicenow-raises-annual-subscription-revenue-forecast-ai-demand-surges-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5KKWL2YUFKILKQIY4D3UD4EEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:16:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求不振，Chipotle 再次下调年销售额预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[奇波特尔墨西哥烧烤公司（Chipotle Mexican Grill）周三今年第三次下调了年度销售预期，这表明在成本压力不断增加的情况下，即使是其典型的富裕食客也在减少外出就餐。【原文：Chipotle Mexican Grill on Wednesday slashed annual sales forecast for the third time this year, signaling that even its typically affluent diners are cutting back on eating out amid mounting cost pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chipotle-cuts-annual-sales-forecast-again-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7V6EEKJVCVMN7BMXW2RXGUJEKE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EBay 预计第四季度利润低于市场预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在宏观经济不确定性持续存在的背景下，电子商务公司eBay预计关键假日季度的利润将低于华尔街预期，导致其股价在周三收盘后下跌6%。【原文：E-commerce firm eBay forecast profit for the crucial holiday quarter below Wall Street estimates amid ongoing macroeconomic uncertainty, sending its shares down 6% after the bell on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ebay-forecasts-annual-revenue-above-street-estimates-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3PYLSIS5FIMRDFM55WM7PKYSY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:14:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据中心运营商 Equinix 下调 2025 年收入预期，面临交易关闭延迟问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[Equinix 首席执行官周三表示，由于数据中心运营商在完成一项交易方面面临延误以及汇率的负面影响，Equinix 下调了年收入预期，而华尔街则寄希望于该公司从人工智能基础设施的蓬勃发展中获益。【原文：Equinix lowered its forecast for annual revenue due to the data center operator facing delays in closing a deal and a negative impact from foreign exchange rates, its CEO said on Wednesday, while Wall Street counts on the company to benefit from booming spending on AI infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/data-center-operator-equinix-lowers-2025-revenue-forecast-facing-deal-closure-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JL2DGU5ZZJPKFLSFAHT7YVWX5A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美达公司利润受约 160 亿美元一次性税费影响，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 在第三季度记录了与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的 "美丽大法案 "有关的近 160 亿美元的一次性费用，并表示明年的资本支出将比 2025 年 "明显增加"。【原文：Meta recorded a nearly $16 billion one-time charge in the third quarter related to U.S. President Donald Trump's Big Beautiful Bill, and said its capital expenditure next year would be "notably larger" than in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/metas-profit-hit-by-16-billion-one-time-tax-charge-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJRQOAPD2ZIFBDYIYZMGWJGN7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克七个季度以来首次实现同店销售增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克周三公布，在国际市场的带动下，其全球可比销售额在近一年半之后实现了第一季度的增长，但其美国业务仍未实现增长，首席执行官布莱恩-尼科尔（Brian Niccol）正在对美国业务进行全面改革。【原文：Starbucks on Wednesday posted its first quarter of global comparable sales growth after nearly a year-and-a-half, led by international markets, though growth still eluded its U.S. operation, which is undergoing an overhaul by CEO Brian Niccol.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/starbucks-beats-global-comparable-sales-estimates-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VWNE2STG5N7JLCYQ4AKOSLKMI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[二手车需求带动 Carvana 第三季度业绩增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[二手车零售商 Carvana 周三公布，受惠于强劲的二手车需求，第三季度利润和收入均有所增长。【原文：Used car retailer Carvana reported higher third-quarter profit and revenue on Wednesday, aided by strong demand for preowned vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carvanas-third-quarter-results-rise-used-vehicle-demand-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2SKUAQI5FOLJAUYU2DDYBKZEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广告和云计算需求强劲，Alphabet 季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌母公司 Alphabet 周三公布的第三季度营收超出华尔街预期，原因是其核心广告业务和云计算部门均实现了稳步增长。【原文：Google-parent Alphabet beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue on Wednesday, as both its core advertising business and cloud computing unit showed steady growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/alphabet-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-strong-ad-cloud-demand-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UOTVNZMR3BJLJFQUMTLW54NBUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软云计算业务激增，营收超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周三公布了其云计算业务的大幅增长，使其季度收入超过了华尔街的预期，这表明尽管存在泡沫的担忧，但企业仍在为人工智能服务挥金如土。【原文：Microsoft reported blockbuster growth in its cloud-computing business on Wednesday that pushed its quarterly revenue past Wall Street estimates, showing businesses are still splurging on artificial intelligence services despite fears of a bubble.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsofts-cloud-surge-lifts-revenue-above-expectations-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVJUJ662EVIDNIBZAQIBOZCO2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《财富》报道，万事达卡准备以近 20 亿美元的价格收购加密货币公司 Zerohash]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《财富》周三报道，万事达卡（Mastercard）正处于收购加密初创公司 Zerohash 的后期谈判阶段，收购价格在 15 亿至 20 亿美元之间。【原文：Mastercard is in late-stage talks to acquire crypto startup Zerohash for between $1.5 billion and $2 billion, Fortune reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mastercard-poised-buy-crypto-firm-zerohash-nearly-2-billion-fortune-reports-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IJE32VMBJOR5HSKUGLTHY4MDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:04:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达黄仁勋加入资助特朗普的科技巨头行列]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋告诉记者，他与其他支持该项目的科技界领袖一起，为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的白宫宴会厅建设捐款。
"他周二在华盛顿对记者说："我很高兴能参与其中。
在白宫上周公布的捐赠者公开名单中，英伟达（Nvidia）并未榜上有名。今年 5 月，黄仁勋的个人净资产估计为 1,200 亿美元。
拆除工人拆掉了白宫东翼，为新宴会厅让路。特朗普表示，该项目将耗资 3 亿美元。亚马逊（Amazon）、苹果（Apple）和谷歌（Google）等科技公司也支持这项工程。
Nvidia 周三成为首家市值达到 5 万亿美元的公司。该公司是全球人工智能产业的中心。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang donated to fund the construction of U.S. President Donald Trump’s White House ballroom, he told reporters, joining other tech leaders supporting the project.
“I’m delighted to be part of it,” he told reporters in Washington on Tuesday.
Nvidia was not named on the White House’s public list of donors released last week. Huang's personal net worth was estimated at $120 billion in May.
Demolition workers tore down the East Wing of the White House to make way for the new ballroom. Trump has said the project will cost $300 million. Amazon, Apple and Google are among the technology companies also supporting the construction.
Nvidia on Wednesday became the first company to reach $5 trillion in market value. The company is at the center of the global AI industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidias-huang-joins-tech-titans-funding-trumps-ballroom-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNK3EFILV5I7DFELNGPH5BJSI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:53:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉吉公司将在明尼苏达州裁员 80 人，并在全球范围内裁员更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业综合企业嘉吉公司（CARG.UL）周三表示，它将在明尼苏达州永久性裁员80人，全球裁员人数不详，这是农业公司受更广泛的农业行业不景气影响而出现的最新一波裁员潮。【原文：U.S. agribusiness Cargill Inc (CARG.UL) said Wednesday it is permanently laying off 80 employees in Minnesota and an undisclosed number globally in the latest wave of job cuts among agricultural companies hit by a broader farm sector slump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/cargill-lay-off-80-workers-minnesota-more-globally-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GAWFNTGZQFIWBJ65ROTR6S2B2E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[致命事故发生后，NTSB 敦促部分 Learjet 机型的机主检查主起落架]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会周三向10种型号庞巴迪里尔喷气飞机的运营商发出紧急建议，要求确保主起落架连接正确。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board on Wednesday issued an urgent recommendation to operators of 10 Bombardier Learjet airplanes models to ensure main landing gear are attached correctly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ntsb-urges-owners-some-learjet-models-check-main-landing-gear-after-fatal-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5SNFCMS6NOEVIQ6M7QIASZ47U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:41:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美联储实现预期降息；鲍威尔称不保证 12 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[在货币市场出现流动性变得稀缺的迹象之后，意见分歧的美国联邦储备委员会周三将利率下调了四分之一个百分点，并宣布将重新开始有限度地购买国债。【原文：A divided U.S. Federal Reserve cut interest rates by a quarter of a percentage point on Wednesday and announced it will restart limited purchases of Treasury securities after money markets showed signs that liquidity was becoming scarce, a condition the U.S. central bank has pledged to avoid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-fed-delivers-expected-rate-cut-nods-limits-data-during-shutdown-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V35X7LWZQBJLVPNYKJNVYKRKW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[能访问最大电信公司的美国公司发现了民族国家黑客的漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ribbon Communications 是美国一家重要的电信服务公司，该公司发言人周三在一份声明中证实，为一个未具名的民族国家工作的黑客入侵了该公司的网络，并在该公司的系统中停留了近一年而未被发现。【原文：Hackers working for an unnamed nation-state breached networks at Ribbon Communications , a key U.S. telecommunications services company, and remained within the firm’s systems for nearly a year without being detected, a company spokesperson confirmed in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-company-with-access-biggest-telecom-firms-uncovers-breach-by-nation-state-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6ARK7G7BJKBJMNYONWYOMTTYQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:09:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储将于 12 月 1 日结束缩减资产负债表]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三表示，将结束缩减其 6.6 万亿美元的资产负债表，因为有证据表明货币市场的流动性状况已经开始收紧，银行准备金水平也在下降。【原文：The Federal Reserve on Wednesday said it is ending the drawdown of its $6.6 trillion balance sheet amid evidence money market liquidity conditions have begun tightening and bank reserve levels dropping.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-end-balance-sheet-reduction-december-1-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAZ3PYTHHFK7RNDXPXMJUHPEO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储双向异议的历史]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三决定将利率下调四分之一个百分点，但有两位决策者投了反对票，一位赞成更大幅度的降息，另一位则倾向于不降息。【原文：The Federal Reserve's decision on Wednesday to lower interest rates by a quarter percentage point was met with dissenting votes by two policymakers, one favoring a larger cut and another preferring no reduction at all, a rare example over the last few decades of multiple dissents in opposing directions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/history-federal-reserve-dissents-two-directions-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AGD5N6YJ5JHDOUB3SUZZGGYMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国希思罗机场网站瘫痪后重新上线]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国最大的机场希思罗机场周三表示，已意识到影响网站的问题，并已将此事提交给技术团队，随后希思罗机场网站重新上线。【原文：Heathrow Airport's website went back online after Britain's largest airport said on Wednesday that it was aware of issues affecting the website and had referred the matter to its technology team.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/britains-heathrow-airport-reports-website-issues-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4OQQTDW7RKOVNU6GUANUJHCLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，特朗普实施制裁后，德国正在研究将俄罗斯石油公司的业务国有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉谈判情况的消息人士告诉路透社，美国对俄罗斯石油生产商俄罗斯石油公司（Rosneft）的制裁重燃了德国关于将该公司在德国的业务国有化的讨论，其中包括柏林大部分燃料都依赖的一家炼油厂。【原文：U.S. sanctions on Russian oil producer Rosneft have rekindled discussions in Germany about nationalising the company's business there, including a refinery that Berlin depends on for most of its fuel, two sources familiar with the talks told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/germany-examines-nationalising-rosneft-arm-after-trump-sanctions-say-sources-2025-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWJU5YANTVOUXCULTWFPCBJ7DE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:24:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>