<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:34:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:34:04 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，沙特 Humain 公司将于 2026 年初推出采用美国芯片的数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一报道，沙特阿拉伯新成立的人工智能公司 Humain 已开始在沙特王国建设首个数据中心，并计划使用从美国进口的半导体，于 2026 年初投入使用。【原文：Humain, Saudi Arabia's new artificial intelligence company, has begun construction of its first data centers in the kingdom, and plans to bring them online in early 2026 using semiconductors imported from the U.S., Bloomberg News reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudis-humain-launch-data-centers-with-us-chips-early-2026-bloomberg-news-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U2O4TMR7JM5RGAYHW6W3N5JH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:11:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡夫等公司打赢超标加工食品检测官司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国宾夕法尼亚州联邦法官驳回了卡夫、蒙代尔、可口可乐和其他几家大型食品公司指控它们设计的 "超加工 "食品会让儿童上瘾并导致慢性疾病的诉讼。【原文：Kraft, Mondelez, Coca-Cola and several other major food companies have beaten a lawsuit accusing them of designing "ultra-processed" foods to be addictive to children, causing chronic disease, after a Pennsylvania federal judge dismissed the lawsuit, which was seen by legal experts to be a key test case of the claims.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/kraft-other-companies-beat-test-lawsuit-over-ultra-processed-foods-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3DJ5ZELUZOMZB4W662DWJDHPU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称美国停止风电项目有损新英格兰电网可靠性和就业机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源和劳工官员周一表示，特朗普政府下令停止罗德岛海岸正在建设的一个大型风电场的工作，这威胁到电网的可靠性和就业。【原文：The Trump administration's order to halt work on a major wind farm under construction off the coast of Rhode Island threatens grid reliability and jobs, energy and labor officials said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-halt-wind-project-hurts-new-england-grid-reliability-jobs-officials-say-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I35BWGIEVPSFCQBKPUQ4WSTQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:43:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根认为仍有下调储备金的空间，预计下月SRF使用量将上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-洛根周一表示，她认为美国央行有更多的空间来削减储备金，她预计银行下个月会求助于常备回购机制来缓解任何流动性压力。【原文：Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan on Monday said she feels the U.S. central bank has more room to reduce its reserves, and she expects banks to turn to its standing repo facility next month to alleviate any liquidity pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-sees-room-lower-reserves-expects-uptick-srf-use-next-month-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZOP2XRI2FIIVHMXQK4ZZAVQZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国内政部建议将铜列入重要矿产清单]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周一提议将铜和钾肥等矿产列入 2025 年关键矿产清单草案，因为它们对经济和国家安全具有重要意义。【原文：The U.S. on Monday proposed adding copper and potash among others to the draft critical minerals list for 2025, for their importance to the economy and national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-interior-department-proposes-adding-copper-critical-minerals-list-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFBISPSABFP3JJEAR7H7Y45YPM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院命令美国证券交易委员会审查卖空规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周一下令美国证券交易委员会评估乔-拜登总统时代旨在提高卖空交易透明度的规定对经济的影响，这是提起诉讼的对冲基金取得的部分胜利。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Monday ordered the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to assess the economic impact of President Joe Biden-era rules aimed at boosting transparency of short sell trades, in a partial victory for hedge funds that brought the case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-appeals-court-orders-sec-review-short-selling-rules-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7AFDKG4MVL53A2JFQI4JKRNAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中国必须向美国提供磁铁，否则将面临 200% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周一对记者说，在两国贸易争端中，中国必须给美国磁铁，否则 "我们必须向他们征收 200% 的关税或其他什么"。【原文：President Donald Trump told reporters on Monday that China has to give the United States magnets or "we have to charge them 200% tariff or something" amid a trade dispute between the two nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-china-has-give-us-magnets-or-face-200-tariff-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WHVX36K3ZIIXICVKD563L5IDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司无意收购一家火车公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）首席执行官沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）周一在接受 CNBC 采访时表示，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司并不打算收购一家火车公司。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway is not in the market to buy a train company, CEO Warren Buffett said to CNBC on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/berkshire-hathaway-not-looking-buy-train-company-cnbc-reports-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5II6ZMDIZIATFUFI3QOYAEPXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特朗普政府正权衡对执行欧盟科技法的官员实施制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑对欧盟或成员国负责执行该集团具有里程碑意义的《数字服务法案》的官员实施制裁，因为美国抱怨该法案审查美国人并给美国科技公司带来成本。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering imposing sanctions on European Union or member state officials responsible for implementing the bloc's landmark Digital Services Act, two sources familiar with the matter said, over U.S. complaints that the law censors Americans and imposes costs on U.S. tech companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-weighs-sanctions-officials-implementing-eu-tech-law-sources-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5Q6DZB465NSRIZ4XQOIBUH2L4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业组织称，巴西咖啡零售价格可能因美国加征关税而飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西咖啡行业协会周一表示，由于巴西烘焙商的生豆成本激增，巴西烘焙咖啡和研磨咖啡的零售价格可能会出现逆转，8月份迄今为止平均下跌了12%。【原文：Retail prices for roasted and ground coffee in Brazil, which have fallen an average of 12% so far in August, could reverse course as costs of raw beans surge for Brazilian roasters, the country's coffee industry association said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-retail-coffee-prices-could-surge-amid-us-tariffs-industry-group-says-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DORROF2TMJL3XFQWUALER5RJKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SpaceX 希望通过第十次飞行测试克服 "星际飞船 "的挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索公司（SpaceX）将于周一在得克萨斯州第十次发射巨型 "星际飞船"（Starship）火箭，以克服连续的研发挫折，实现几个长期追求的里程碑，这对火星火箭系统的可重复使用设计至关重要。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX will try to launch its giant Starship rocket for a tenth time from Texas on Monday to overcome a streak of development setbacks and achieve several long-sought milestones essential to the Mars rocket system's reusable design.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spacex-aims-overcome-starship-setbacks-with-tenth-flight-test-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5AENV3F3FJNDLBVBBMNQG5TYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次推动美国机构吊销 NBC 和 ABC 电视台执照]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统在批评美国两大广播公司的新闻节目时，重申了他长期以来推动联邦通信委员会吊销两家美国主要广播公司的电台执照并向它们收取使用公共电波费用的主张。【原文：President Donald Trump reiterated a long-running push for the Federal Communications Commission to revoke station licenses of two major U.S. broadcasters and charge them for using the public airwaves, as he criticized their news programming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-again-pushes-us-agency-revoke-nbc-abc-station-licenses-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NV2XG5FG3NN4ZB2S5QX6BVELGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部撤销拜登的 74 亿美元半导体研究资助协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，将废除乔-拜登总统时期与一家外部中心达成的协议，该中心将负责监管 74 亿美元的半导体研究基金。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Monday it was voiding an agreement finalized under President Joe Biden with an outside center to oversee $7.4 billion in semiconductor research funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-commerce-department-voids-bidens-74-billion-semiconductor-research-grant-deal-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QN2WWXH75BLNBFKACZG4JZYGTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Squishmallows 制造商与 Build-A-Bear 在毛绒玩具官司中休战]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据向洛杉矶联邦法院提交的一份文件，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的 Squishmallows 制造商 Jazwares 已同意结束对 Build-A-Bear Workshop 的诉讼，因为该公司涉嫌山寨流行的毛绒玩具。【原文：Jazwares, the Berkshire Hathaway-owned maker of Squishmallows, has agreed to end a lawsuit against Build-A-Bear Workshop over its alleged knockoffs of the popular plush toys, according to a filing in Los Angeles federal court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/squishmallows-maker-build-a-bear-call-truce-plush-toy-legal-battle-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XI7BVXEKZZMPDN7VZAPLXNSPUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的 xAI 就人工智能竞争和应用商店排名起诉苹果和 OpenAI]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁企业家埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的人工智能初创公司 xAI 周一在美国得克萨斯州联邦法院起诉苹果公司和 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI，指控它们非法合谋阻挠人工智能竞争。【原文：Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence startup xAI sued Apple and ChatGPT maker OpenAI in U.S. federal court in Texas on Monday, accusing them of illegally conspiring to thwart competition for artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/elon-musks-xai-sues-apple-openai-over-ai-competition-app-store-rankings-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DC6MCVW5MRNHFLK6ZWWZEPFLNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔将 Keurig Dr Pepper 列入负面信用观察名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国软饮料巨头 Keurig Dr Pepper 周一宣布将收购荷兰咖啡集团 JDE Peet's 之后，评级机构 S&amp;P Global 将该公司的信用展望定为负面。【原文：Ratings agency S&amp;P Global put a negative credit outlook on U.S. soft drinks giant Keurig Dr Pepper after the company announced Monday it will buy Dutch coffee group JDE Peet's .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/sp-puts-keurig-dr-pepper-negative-credit-watch-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOZA5MXZ55M4NNV3N7NAZW42KU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月新屋销售下降；6 月销售修正为上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[继上月销售速度大幅上调之后，7 月份美国新建独户住宅的销售量有所下降，总体趋势仍然是住房市场在高抵押贷款利率的环境中苦苦挣扎。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell in July following a sharp upward revision to the prior month's sales pace, and the overall trend remained consistent with a housing market struggling in an environment of high mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-july-june-sales-revised-higher-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LH6HTVIRFFPTJJBTLZMHRUZENU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将继续达成类似英特尔的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他将与其他公司达成类似于上周宣布的与英特尔公司（Intel）的交易。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he would make deals with other companies similar to the one he announced last week with Intel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-continue-make-deals-like-intel-one-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2R3AJ3OB2RJLVNBQFLRAEE4XX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇率飙升和特朗普关税影响欧洲业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国关税和美元疲软导致的欧洲货币升值削弱了企业在第二季度的业绩表现，增加了企业将业务迁往美国或将工作岗位迁往美国的压力。【原文：U.S. tariffs and an appreciation in European currencies caused by dollar weakness have eroded companies' top line performance in the second quarter, increasing pressure on them to relocate operations or put jobs into the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/currency-spikes-trump-tariffs-take-bite-out-european-results-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIQOIBDYNVKPBEE7O67QNXLIXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，皮纳尔家族正在探索出售彪马公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道称，Pinault 家族正在权衡 Puma SE 的各种选择，包括出售。【原文：The Pinault family is weighing options for Puma SE , including a sale, Bloomberg News reported on Monday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pinault-family-explores-sale-puma-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPLEWCTLMNLE3DHWUZTJFESFJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拥有优质信用的美国消费者在付款方面开始出现滑坡]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评分公司 VantageScore 在周一发布的一份报告中称，信用评分最高的美国消费者在偿还债务方面开始落后，这表明美国人的财务健康状况可能正在更广泛地恶化。【原文：U.S. consumers with the highest credit scores are starting to fall behind in debt repayments, credit scoring company VantageScore said in a report published on Monday, in a sign that Americans' financial health may be deteriorating more broadly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumers-with-prime-credit-are-starting-slip-payments-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APIJM3WJQRLSVGIPDTJQV764M4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoma Bravo 拟斥资 20 亿美元收购 Verint，软件并购步伐加快]]></title><description><![CDATA[客户参与平台 Thoma Bravo 周一表示，将以包括债务在内的 20 亿美元收购 Verint Systems，这标志着私募股权公司越来越多地押注于人工智能，以应对不确定的经济形势，这也是最新的软件收购交易。【原文：Thoma Bravo will acquire Verint Systems in a $2 billion deal, including debt, the customer engagement platform said on Monday, marking the latest software buyout as private equity firms increasingly bet on AI to navigate an uncertain economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/thoma-bravo-buy-verint-2-billion-deal-software-acquisitions-ramp-up-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWNI5I2HOZIIHIS6XM4LZ5WEUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔警告称美国股份可能损害国际销售和未来拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司周一表示，美国政府持有这家芯片制造商 10% 的股份可能会给其业务带来风险，从可能损害国际销售到限制其未来获得政府拨款的能力。【原文：Intel said on Monday that the 10% stake by the U.S. government in the chipmaker could pose risks to its business, from potentially harming international sales to limiting its ability to secure future government grants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/intel-warns-us-stake-could-hurt-international-sales-future-grants-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2QM5P4DTRLHTM3EPTVN6RCAJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫哈塞特称美国可参股其他行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[继入股英特尔（Intel）之后，白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周一在接受 CNBC 采访时表示，联邦政府可能会入股其他美国半导体公司，甚至转向其他行业。【原文：The federal government could take stakes in other U.S. semiconductor companies or even move to other industries, White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett told CNBC in an interview on Monday following its stake in Intel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/white-houses-hassett-says-us-could-take-stakes-other-industries-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCULR7H76BKTZBPQCVHYSDJPYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法律修改后，Flutter 关闭了印度的付费在线游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线博彩公司 Flutter 上周修改法律后关闭了其在印度的货币在线游戏，该公司首席执行官彼得-杰克逊（Peter Jackson）表示，他对事态发展 "极为失望"。【原文：Online betting company Flutter , has shut down its money-based online games in India following a law change last week, with CEO Peter Jackson saying he was "extremely disappointed" by the development.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/flutter-shuts-down-money-based-online-games-india-following-law-change-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZH3F6FSDBZJ2HBKZ4DN26TAACA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:32:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper 180 亿美元收购 JDE Peet's 的内幕交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper 周一宣布将以 157 亿欧元（184 亿美元）的现金收购荷兰 JDE Peet's，以打造全球咖啡巨头。【原文：Keurig Dr Pepper on Monday announced it would buy Dutch company JDE Peet's for 15.7 billion euros ($18.4 billion) in cash, in a bid to create a global coffee heavyweight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/inner-workings-keurig-dr-peppers-18-billion-move-jde-peets-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH4MKP5RARMYXPSWLWQOALPQB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Figma 获得 "中性 "评级，华尔街认为估值过高、竞争加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街券商周一开始给予 Figma 中性评级，因为他们权衡了这家设计软件制造商在激烈竞争中的高估值和人工智能驱动的增长潜力。【原文：Wall Street brokerages on Monday started their coverage of Figma with neutral ratings, as they weighed the design software maker's lofty valuation amid stiff competition against its potential for artificial intelligence-driven growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/figma-draws-neutral-ratings-wall-street-flags-lofty-valuation-rising-competition-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZS6GL4QXWRMNLE4Z5S2VMV7F6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[信心增强刺激交易反弹，华尔街增聘高级银行家]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几个月，华尔街银行招聘了数十名高级管理人员，因为在今年早些时候由于担心美国关税的影响而陷入低迷之后，经济景气的改善刺激了兼并和首次公开募股。【原文：Wall Street banks have hired dozens of senior executives in recent months, as improved economic sentiment has spurred mergers and IPOs after a lull earlier in the year due to concerns over the effect of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/wall-street-hires-more-senior-bankers-growing-confidence-spurs-deal-rebound-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKINH3KGQRINRNKYPVER7K3ZZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特木公司所有者 PDD 季度收入超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子商务公司点点客控股公司（PDD Holdings）周一公布的季度收入超出市场预期，表明尽管全球贸易存在不确定性，但国内需求反弹，国际业务增长也有所改善。【原文：E-commerce firm PDD Holdings beat market estimates for quarterly revenue on Monday, signaling a rebound in domestic demand and improved growth in its international business despite global trade uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/temu-owner-pdd-tops-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCMSUH722FN7XFFOXRWHI6UQRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国立法者和工会反对铁路自动化轨道安全检查计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铁路行业计划更多地依靠技术而不是人力来进行日常轨道安全检查，这一计划引起了劳工团体和立法者的反弹，他们担心自动检查会导致更多事故。【原文：A U.S. railroad industry plan to rely more heavily on technology instead of humans to conduct routine track safety inspections has drawn a backlash from labor groups and lawmakers who voiced worry that automated inspections will result in more accidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-lawmakers-unions-oppose-railroad-plan-automate-track-safety-inspections-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OK7PGHASI5PTVKGY5OLSHPURDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:34:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>