<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:46:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:46:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降，劳动力市场暂时保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数有所下降，表明在进口关税带来潜在波动之前，劳动力市场将继续保持稳定。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell last week, pointing to continued labor market stability ahead of potential volatility from import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-labor-market-stays-stable-now-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZS2CVJ5MZNNNG2MBX2MUUFX6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国副总统称 TikTok 协议 "进展顺利]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府副总统万斯（JD Vance）周四表示，随着竞标的增加，特朗普政府为短视频社交网站 TikTok 寻找美国买家的工作正在按部就班地进行，比 4 月 5 日达成非中国所有权交易的最后期限提前了。【原文：The Trump administration's work to find an American buyer for the short-video social media site TikTok is on track ahead of the April 5 deadline to reach a deal for non-Chinese ownership, Vice President JD Vance said on Thursday as bids mounted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/work-tiktok-deal-is-in-good-place-us-vice-president-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYKXJE2USFIYLBOCXITWWH3O7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:38:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国公布美国可能加征关税的商品清单]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普决定对英国征收10%的进口关税，英国周四公布了一份可能被列入任何报复性关税对策的商品清单。【原文：Britain on Thursday published a list of goods that could be included in any retaliatory tariff response to U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to impose import tariffs of 10% on the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-publishes-list-goods-potential-us-tariff-response-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCCVKTA3Z5PZTJJ3K77L7IV4AY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被特朗普关税震惊的投资者准备应对全球经济增长冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）巨额新关税的冲击，大型投资者们正拿出他们的全球衰退手册，急于分散投资，避开遭受重创的华尔街股票和美元。【原文：Big investors reeling from the shock of U.S. President Donald Trump's hefty new tariffs are pulling out their global recession playbooks and rushing to diversify away from battered Wall Street stocks and the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/investors-stunned-by-trump-tariffs-prepare-global-growth-shock-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQVKDVZFPVNVNOZ73KDEB5T664</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABB 预计将转嫁新关税带来的成本增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士工程集团ABB周四表示，该公司正在评估新进口关税的影响，并预计将转嫁由此导致的更高成本。【原文：Swiss engineering group ABB said on Thursday it is evaluating the implications of new import tariffs and expects to pass on higher costs that result from them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/abb-expects-pass-cost-increases-new-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZYFT34Y7NMGBHXMYOSYWYT3CM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，汽车关税第一年将使美国消费者损失超过 300 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[咨询公司安德森经济集团（Anderson Economic Group）周四在一份报告中称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对汽车进口征收 25% 的关税，可能会使美国消费者在第一个完整年度中因汽车价格上涨和汽车销量减少而损失超过 300 亿美元。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's 25% tariff on auto imports may cost American consumers more than $30 billion in higher vehicle prices and reduced car sales in the first full year, consultancy firm Anderson Economic Group said in a report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/auto-tariff-cost-us-consumers-more-than-30-bln-first-year-report-shows-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUUCH6NKIFLHRI75NLOWV4ASWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰总理称考虑支持受关税冲击的企业为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰总理米歇尔-马丁（Micheal Martin）周四表示，现在考虑支持受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收20%进口关税影响的企业还为时过早，但他期待与美国就征税的影响进行谈判。【原文：Irish Prime Minister Micheal Martin said on Thursday it was still too early to consider supporting businesses hit by President Donald Trump's import tariffs of 20% but that he expected talks with the U.S. on the impact of the levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/irish-pm-says-too-early-consider-supporting-businesses-hit-by-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZULOYSHBNZNGHA27IGKDUPO5LU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[约翰逊爸爸希望人工智能改变披萨订购方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[约翰爸爸国际公司（Papa John's International）周四表示，希望通过扩大与谷歌云（Google Cloud）的合作，将人工智能技术注入顾客订购披萨的方式中。【原文：Papa John's International wants to inject artificial intelligence technology into how its customers order pizza through an expanded partnership with Google Cloud, the chain said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/papa-johns-wants-ai-transform-pizza-ordering-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RM4NMU5YFJZLA4ZRYV2R45DPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国需求增长放缓，矿业整合将加速]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于制造业的放缓和工业金属需求的增长，尤其是在最大消费国中国，采矿业的整合时机已经成熟，预计合资企业和资产出售将加速发展。【原文：Joint ventures and asset sales are expected to accelerate in the mining industry, which is ripe for consolidation due to the slowdown in manufacturing and demand growth for industrial metals, particularly in top consumer China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/mining-consolidation-speed-up-chinese-demand-growth-slows-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZ7EZGQBV5PUFATVE6DDPZMTNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税冲击刺痛孟加拉国和斯里兰卡服装巨头，但可能有助于印度]]></title><description><![CDATA[孟加拉服装出口商沙希杜拉-阿齐姆（Shahidullah Azim）周四一觉醒来，就被美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对孟加拉出口产品征收 37% 的关税所震惊，这危及到这个已经因国内政治动荡而岌岌可危的服装中心。【原文：Bangladeshi garment exporter Shahidullah Azim woke up on Thursday to the shock of U.S. President Donald Trump slapping a 37% tariff on his country's exports, endangering an apparel hub already reeling from domestic political upheaval.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/trump-tariff-shock-stings-bangladesh-sri-lanka-garment-giants-may-help-india-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QVI2RT5AFFNKDOKRORFEIDQO7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，WTO负责人将回答成员有关美国关税的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封信称，世界贸易组织负责人周四告诉各成员国，该组织已收到 "许多 "有关美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税对贸易的影响的问题，并将对这些问题做出回应。【原文：The head of the World Trade Organization told member states on Thursday that it had received "many" questions about the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on trade and would respond to their questions, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/wto-chief-will-answer-members-questions-about-us-tariffs-document-shows-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNBYKKI7WJN43MUUN6TRMODCPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:54:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称乌克兰玉米可从美国关税中受益]]></title><description><![CDATA[ASAP Agri 分析师周四表示，乌克兰玉米是该国谷物行业的关键要素，可能会从美国征收的关税中受益，因为如果美国实施报复性制裁，乌克兰玉米可以部分替代美国玉米。【原文：Ukrainian corn, a key element of the country's grain sector, could benefit from the tariffs imposed by the U.S., as it is able to partially substitute for U.S. corn if retaliatory sanctions are imposed, ASAP Agri analysts said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ukraines-corn-could-benefit-us-tariffs-analyst-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYKCBNH4INMG7EAYD5FZHHZZPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行账目显示对关税增长和通胀影响的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行 3 月 5-6 日会议的记录显示，美国贸易壁垒将拖累经济增长，但其对通胀的影响却不那么确定，因此欧洲央行在获得大量数据证据之前，必须不采取任何具体措施。【原文：U.S. trade barriers will weigh on growth but their impact on inflation was far less certain, making it imperative that the ECB did not commit to any particular move until it had a body of evidence in data, the accounts of their March 5-6 meeting showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecb-accounts-show-worries-over-tariffs-growth-inflation-impact-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EN2KU2254RJTZGQYJ2BQL5QOE4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:45:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应紧张导致 Conagra Brands 季度销售额不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[康奈格拉品牌公司（Conagra Brands）周四公布的第三季度销售额不及华尔街预期，原因是冷冻食品和冷藏业务的供应链中断削弱了其满足需求的能力。【原文：Conagra Brands missed Wall Street expectations for third-quarter sales on Thursday, as supply-chain disruptions in frozen food and refrigerated business hurt its ability to meet demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/conagra-brands-misses-quarterly-sales-estimate-supply-constraints-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUCAJMWPVFMHJNIETQBZ7WUFIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[招聘公司 Challenger 称，受 Doge 法案影响，美国 3 月份宣布的裁员人数激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于政府为削减开支而清理联邦雇员和承包商，3 月份美国雇主宣布的裁员人数激增，达到大流行性经济衰退以来的最高水平。【原文：Layoffs announced by U.S. employers surged in March to the highest level since the pandemic recession as the government purged federal workers and contractors to slash spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-announced-job-cuts-surge-march-doge-hit-recruitment-firm-challenger-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DP4SGNQN3VKQ3FSGPOUVZTDRCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥地利称欧盟关税对策应针对共和党领导的美国各州和科技公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥地利经济部长周四表示，欧盟为应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的普遍关税而采取的反制措施应针对共和党领导的各州和科技公司，以迫使他坐到谈判桌前。【原文：The European Union's countermeasures in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's universal tariffs should target Republican-led states and tech firms so as to force him to the negotiating table, Austria's economy minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/eus-tariff-response-should-target-republican-led-us-states-tech-firms-austria-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XDTHMRWXNO2ZAEQVKCYXL3KBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:32:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的贸易政策引发亚洲股市第一季度出现至少 15 年来最大规模的资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布征收重大关税之前，外国投资者在截至3月份的一个季度里从亚洲股市撤出了约15年来最大规模的资金--有人说，随着投资者转向避险资产，该地区可能会出现更多的抛售。【原文：Foreign investors withdrew the largest amount of money from Asian equities in about 15 years in the quarter to March ahead of U.S. President Donald Trump's major tariffannouncement - and some say the region may see more selling as investors head for safe-haven assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-trade-policies-triggered-largest-asian-equity-outflows-least-15-years-q1-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34YZJV743JL5PGY4YJV44Q42VY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+加快提高石油产量，石油下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+"八国周四同意推进石油增产计划，在5月份将石油日产量增加41.1万桶，这一出人意料的决定促使油价扩大了早些时候的跌幅。【原文：Eight OPEC+ countries agreed on Thursday to advance their plan for oil output hikes by increasing oil output by 411,000 barrels per day in May, an unexpected decision that prompted oil prices to extend earlier losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/opec-advance-oil-output-hike-plan-with-bigger-may-boost-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYF6F5YGGNIRZAPFFYQIOEVPD4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[依赖出口的中欧权衡特朗普关税的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷克和波兰领导人周四表示准备对美国的新关税进行报复，匈牙利则指责布鲁塞尔与华盛顿关系紧张，中欧开始计算贸易战的可能成本。【原文：Leaders in the Czech Republic and Poland signalled a readiness on Thursday to retaliate to new U.S. tariffs, while Hungary blamed Brussels for tensions with Washington, as central Europe began counting the likely costs of a trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/export-reliant-central-europe-weighs-repercussions-trump-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD7AQAOPRBNCLAJL7SIP5GC2GY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:24:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯、古巴和朝鲜躲过特朗普最严厉的关税惩罚]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对包括欧洲、印度、日本和中国在内的盟友和敌人征收关税的同时，世界上一些受到最严厉制裁的国家--俄罗斯、白俄罗斯、古巴和朝鲜--却没有被单独挑出来接受特殊的惩罚性待遇。【原文：While U.S. President Donald Trump announced tariffs on allies and foes including Europe, India, Japan and China, some of the world's most heavily sanctioned countries - Russia, Belarus, Cuba and North Korea - avoided being singled out for special punitive treatment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/russia-cuba-north-korea-escape-worst-trumps-tariff-wrath-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTDG6Y5FQJOELBTY3QX5SAZWVY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政策将刺激央行进一步买入黄金]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政策所带来的风险，各国央行有望通过买入黄金来进一步分散美元储备，从而帮助黄金在今年继续保持惊人的涨势。【原文：Central banks are expected to help keep gold's stunning rally going this year with buying aimed at further diversifying reserves away from the dollar due to risks stemming from U.S. President Donald Trump's policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-policies-spur-further-central-bank-gold-buying-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTS6LODI7FO4XEV6JTEP7EC5UY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对非洲征收巨额关税预示着旨在促进发展的贸易协议将宣告终结]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易专家周四表示，美国政府对非洲国家征收高额关税预示着《非洲增长和机会法案》（AGOA）贸易协议的终结，该协议本应通过优惠准入美国市场来帮助非洲经济发展。【原文：The U.S. government's imposition of steep tariffs on African nations signals the end of the AGOA trade deal that was supposed to help African economies develop through preferential access to U.S. markets, trade experts said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/steep-us-tariffs-africa-signal-end-trade-deal-meant-boost-development-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYKJEOQODZLSDOTZ5X5NNPNA7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:05:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[避免关税 "是欧洲市场的意外亮点之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对全球经济衰退的担忧导致欧洲市场大跌，制药和饮料公司等意外规避关税的股票以及房地产等对利率敏感的股票成为周四欧洲少数上涨的股票。【原文：Shares of surprise tariff avoiders like pharmaceuticals and drinks firms and rate-sensitive stocks such as real estate were among the few to post gains in Europe on Thursday, as fears of a global recession sent wider markets tumbling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/tariff-avoiders-among-surprise-bright-spots-dappling-europe-markets-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QT3RMTBIMBP6XI25WRDPUSCFDU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标恐惧日]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWRC6FFBYRJHBKW6CNQYZRQ4KQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 3 月份德国汽车销量继续大幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据德国道路交通机构 KBA 的数据，特斯拉 3 月份在德国的销量下降了 42.5%，尽管电池电动汽车的销量总体上有所上升。【原文：Tesla saw its sales volume in Germany fall by 42.5% in March, according to the German road traffic agency KBA, although sales of battery electric vehicles picked up overall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-german-car-sales-continue-plummet-march-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DA7X5MDJPNP2RAKBVJLR46JQ5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:45:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟高级官员表示，欧盟成员国将于4月9日就针对美国关税的反制措施进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位欧盟高级官员周四表示，欧盟成员国将于4月9日（周三）就美国征收钢铝关税的反制措施进行投票。【原文：European Union member states are set to vote on Wednesday April 9 on countermeasures to the United States' steel and aluminum tariffs, a senior EU official, said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-members-vote-april-9-countermeasures-us-tariffs-says-senior-eu-official-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYPK3GHDEVOTLLMDGB4SEXJSDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙 Acerinox 公司称关税原则上是积极的，但要警惕过剩产品涌入欧盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙钢铁制造商 Acerinox 周四表示，美国的关税 "原则上 "会对该公司产生积极影响，因为西班牙是其主要市场，也是其主要钢厂所在地。【原文：Spanish steel maker Acerinox said on Thursday that the U.S. tariffs would have "in principle" positive effects on the company as the country is its main market and where its main steel mills are located.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/spains-acerinox-says-tariffs-positive-principle-wary-surplus-flooding-eu-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5G2QT6BDNMFLICV6QU7QFZB5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:28:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊机器人出租车部门更新软件后，NHTSA 终止了对 258 辆 Zoox 汽车的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周四表示，在亚马逊自动驾驶汽车部门召回 258 辆 Zoox 汽车并更新其软件后，该局已结束对这些汽车制动问题的调查。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Thursday it has closed its probe into 258 Zoox vehicles over a braking issue, after the Amazon self-driving car unit recalled them and updated their software.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-closes-probe-into-258-zoox-vehicles-after-amazons-robotaxi-unit-updates-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWVDUJTWNFO3FNDQHCF3RCX6YY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:21:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙将推出安全网保护企业和消费者免受美国关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙经济部长卡洛斯-奎尔波（Carlos Cuerpo）表示，西班牙首相佩德罗-桑切斯将于周四晚些时候宣布一揽子措施，以减轻美国新关税对企业和消费者的影响。【原文：Spanish Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez is due to announce a package of measures later on Thursday to cushion the impact of new U.S. tariffs on companies and consumers, Economy Minister Carlos Cuerpo said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/spain-roll-out-safety-net-protect-companies-consumers-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NZ72BECNJKQ5E637YIJPMCS7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:16:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰称，报复美国数字服务并非欧盟立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易部长西蒙-哈里斯（Simon Harris）周四表示，在潜在的互惠贸易措施中将美国的数字服务作为目标并非欧盟的立场，这将对爱尔兰造成极大的损害，并敦促双方进行谈判。【原文：Targeting U.S. digital services in potential reciprocal trade measures is not the European Union's position and would be very damaging for Ireland, trade minister Simon Harris said on Thursday, urging negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/retaliating-against-us-digital-services-not-eu-position-ireland-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBZEWX224BO4DJ2VRTZ4RGSN2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:14:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>