<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 21:04:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 21:04:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：市场崛起]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-markets-trading-day-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAOCVMUWLJLDTGBARHDA2DFIRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 20:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gol 退出破产保护程序，计划增加新航线并扩大机队规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司首席执行官塞尔索-费雷尔（Celso Ferrer）告诉路透社记者，该公司周五正式结束了在美国的破产程序，为机队扩张以及在巴西和其他国家开设新航班和新航线创造了条件。【原文：Brazilian airline Gol formally exited its bankruptcy proceedings in the United States on Friday, setting the stage for fleet expansion and new flights and routes within Brazil and other countries, Chief Executive Officer Celso Ferrer told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/gol-exits-chapter-11-with-plans-add-new-routes-expand-fleet-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24BBBSAG2BJXZJR2RHAY4EFKEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 20:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税战趋于缓和，波音准备恢复向中国交付飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 FlightRadar24 网站上的飞行记录，一架涂有厦门航空公司涂装的新型波音 737 MAX 飞机于周五离开西雅图，飞往该公司在中国的交付中心。【原文：A new Boeing 737 MAX painted with Xiamen Airlines livery left Seattle on Friday on the first leg of the route used to shuttle jets to the company's delivery center in China, according to flight records on FlightRadar24.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-prepares-resume-plane-deliveries-china-tariff-war-eases-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLN3YMW555ML7MDVJLODE2HXII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:49:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，英国泰晤士水务公司将获得 Silver Point 和 Elliott 超过 135 亿美元的救援交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美国投资公司银点资本（Silver Point Capital）和埃利奥特管理公司（Elliott Management）正在为英国泰晤士水务公司制定一项价值 100 多亿英镑（约合 135.3 亿美元）的拯救计划。【原文：U.S. investment firms Silver Point Capital and Elliott Management are formulating a 10-billion-pound-plus ($13.53 billion) rescue package for Britain's Thames Water, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uks-thames-water-set-over-135-billion-rescue-deal-by-silver-point-elliott-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YAM2B4TFNOBNBESEMPBPC74FE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国石油/天然气钻井平台数量连续第 6 周下降至 2021 年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第六周削减石油和天然气钻井平台数量，这是自2023年9月以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating for a sixth week in a row for the first time since September 2023, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oilgas-rig-count-falls-6th-week-2021-lows-baker-hughes-says-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GYBH3KANRK23AK65JUIUBAPNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与马斯克的口水战打击特斯拉股价，散户交易员抢购特斯拉股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[散户投资者似乎从美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与其前盟友、特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）之间突如其来的争斗中发现了商机，在这家电动汽车制造商的股票因激烈的对峙而暴跌时，他们纷纷抢购。【原文：Retail investors seem to have spotted an opportunity in the sudden feud between U.S. President Donald Trump and his former ally, Tesla CEO Elon Musk, scooping up shares of the electric car maker as they tumbled on the acrimonious standoff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/retail-traders-scooped-up-tesla-trump-musk-spat-hit-stock-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYTOASDIENKFXPXE7JS73QTTXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对华出口受限，美国乙烷船停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[据贸易消息来源和周五的船舶跟踪数据显示，在华盛顿要求美国出口商申请将页岩气运往中国这一最大买家的许可证之后，超过半打原本驶往中国的美国装载乙烷的船舶在美国墨西哥湾沿岸停滞不前。【原文：Over half a dozen U.S.-loaded ethane vessels, originally bound for China, have stalled around the U.S. Gulf Coast after Washington requested U.S. exporters seek licenses to ship the shale gas to the top buyer, according to trade sources and ship tracking data on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-ethane-vessels-stall-amid-curbs-exports-china-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZUKBXEPVVJBTDWPOOQVT5G2ZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:59:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼公司与 YPF 签署协议参与阿根廷液化天然气项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利总理乔治亚-梅洛尼和阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱伊在罗马会晤期间，意大利能源集团埃尼和阿根廷 YPF 周五签署了关于阿根廷液化天然气（ARGLNG）项目的协议。【原文：Italian energy group Eni and Argentina's YPF on Friday signed an agreement on the Argentina LNG (ARGLNG) project during a meeting in Rome between Italian Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni and Argentine President Javier Milei.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eni-ypf-sign-agreement-participation-argentina-lng-project-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSTAM453CNMPLB7TRB4EITXYQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:50:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[壳牌报告宾夕法尼亚壳牌石化联合企业熔炉装置发生火灾]]></title><description><![CDATA[壳牌周五表示，6月4日下午2:20左右，壳牌宾夕法尼亚石化联合企业五号炉发生火灾。【原文：Shell on Friday said that at approximately 2:20 p.m. on June 4, a fire occurred at furnace unit number five at the Shell Pennsylvania Petrochemicals Complex.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-reports-fire-furnace-unit-shell-pennsylvania-petrochemicals-complex-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RX3DFN4WNJ7VKHCXHBRC3LSDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普-马斯克诱发特斯拉下滑，凸显巨量股票带来的市场风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与特斯拉公司总裁埃隆-马斯克之间的裂痕作为一出政治大戏吸引了全世界的目光，但同时也成为华尔街的一大奇观，凸显了全球最大的股票给股市带来的风险。【原文：The rift between President Donald Trump and Tesla chief Elon Musk has captivated the world as a political drama, but it has also become a Wall Street spectacle, highlighting the risk to equity markets from the world's biggest stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-musk-induced-tesla-slide-points-market-risks-massive-stocks-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ3A23XNQBJ5NK6O7KQM6J5VWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前曼哈顿美国律师威廉姆斯离开保罗-魏斯律师事务所]]></title><description><![CDATA[前曼哈顿联邦检察官达米安-威廉姆斯（Damian Williams）已经离开了他于今年 1 月加入的保罗-魏斯律师事务所，成为这家华尔街律所自 3 月与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普达成协议取消针对该律所的行政命令以来，最新一位离职的合伙人。【原文：Former Manhattan U.S. Attorney Damian Williams has left Paul Weiss, the law firm he joined in January, becoming the latest partner to depart the Wall Street firm since it struck a deal with U.S. President Donald Trump in March to rescind an executive order against it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/former-manhattan-us-attorney-williams-leaves-law-firm-paul-weiss-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IFCNGEANZIC5MU6ESHSR762W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[危机动摇，瑞士束缚了瑞银的全球梦想]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士周五宣布进行改革，使其最大的银行瑞银集团（UBS）更加安全，避免再次发生危机。【原文：Switzerland announced reforms on Friday to make its biggest bank UBS safer and avoid another crisis, hampering the global ambitions of a lender whose financial weight eclipses the country's economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/shaken-by-crises-switzerland-fetters-ubss-global-dream-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STAQWAX7FFKTRHT6PLJ6B3C3TE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管负担减轻，标普全球 "看好 "富国银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P Global周五表示，将富国银行的评级展望从 "稳定 "上调至 "积极"，这家美国银行本周早些时候被解除了1.95万亿美元的资产上限。【原文：S&amp;P Global upgraded its outlook on Wells Fargo to "positive" from "stable", the ratings provider said on Friday, after the U.S. bank was released from a $1.95 trillion asset cap earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/sp-global-positive-wells-fargo-regulatory-burden-lifts-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETTDW6MO65LD5E7VHLL3FOTW5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司双子座秘密申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币公司双子座（Gemini）周五表示，该公司已秘密申请在美国首次公开募股，这表明数字资产公司正采取行动，在市场条件改善的情况下利用投资者重新燃起的风险偏好。【原文：Crypto firm Gemini said on Friday it had confidentially filed for a U.S. initial public offering, as digital asset companies move to tap into renewed investor risk appetite amid improving market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/crypto-firm-gemini-confidentially-files-us-ipo-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7B6KLGMZRFNC7H7D6ADKSYLTWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:04:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈克称今年仍有可能降息，因数据质量令人担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联储主席帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）在本月底即将退休之际表示，在经济形势非常不确定的情况下，今年仍有可能降息，同时他还对决策者用于决策的经济数据的质量表示担忧。【原文：As he heads toward retirement at month’s end, Philadelphia Federal Reserve President Patrick Harker says interest rate cuts remain a possibility this year amid a very uncertain economic landscape, as he also flagged worries about the quality of economic data policymakers use to make their decisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-harker-says-rate-cuts-this-year-still-possible-amid-data-quality-worries-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CN5AEGI5C5K7BFAGAELJBCUZIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，保时捷考虑将部分车型的组装工作转移到美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，保时捷正在考虑将其车型组装的某些部分转移到美国，以减轻唐纳德-特朗普总统对进口汽车征收关税的影响。【原文：Porsche is considering shifting certain parts of its model assembly to the U.S. to mitigate the impact President Donald Trump's tariffs on imported vehicles, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-mulls-shifting-parts-model-assembly-us-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHXWMQOSXFJKFCNSYZPUKYY5MY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称美国暂停向中国运输核电站部件的许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国最近几天暂停了核设备供应商向中国电厂出售核设备的许可证，因为中美两国正在进行一场破坏性的贸易战。【原文：The U.S. in recent days suspended licenses for nuclear equipment suppliers to sell to China's power plants, according to four people familiar with the matter, as the two countries engage in a damaging trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-suspends-licenses-ship-nuclear-plant-parts-china-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMDOND5Y25ORLJDTOI7D6MRJLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:22:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[稳定币公司 Circle 在纽约证券交易所上市后创下历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，稳定币发行商 Circle Internet 的股价攀升 41%，创下历史新高，延续了前一天在纽约证券交易所首次亮相便一鸣惊人的辉煌表现。【原文：Stablecoin issuer Circle Internet's shares climbed 41% to hit a record high on Friday, extending a stellar run after a blowout market debut on the New York Stock Exchange a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stablecoin-firm-circle-scales-record-high-after-blockbuster-nyse-listing-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGF5WIJ3W5MIHBKCFM4G45QUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在阿根廷，随着美元流出，储备增加停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据阿根廷中央银行的最新报告，在过去 11 个月中，阿根廷的资金净流出 123 亿美元，影响了中央银行积累储备的能力。【原文：The last eleven months have seen a net outflow of $12.3 billion from Argentina, affecting the central bank's ability to accumulate reserves, according to the bank's latest report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-reserves-build-up-stalls-dollars-exit-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2X3MXPU4T5NEPKKGNJCOEYI4UI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:49:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，X 为避免欧盟可能开出的罚单，大肆宣传蓝色勾选免责声明]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士说，埃隆-马斯克的社交媒体公司 X 在其蓝色勾选标记上突出了一个免责声明，试图避免欧盟反垄断监管机构可能开出的巨额罚单。【原文：Elon Musk's social media company X has highlighted a disclaimer to its blue checkmark in an attempt to head off a possible hefty fine from EU antitrust regulators, a person familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/x-plays-up-blue-checkmark-disclaimer-stave-off-possible-eu-fine-source-says-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGXAGMJJ4RMRRBF35IZSMDNTPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国向美国三大汽车制造商的供应商发放稀土许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，中国已向美国三大汽车制造商的稀土供应商发放了临时出口许可证，因为中国政府对稀土材料的出口限制已开始造成供应链中断。【原文：China has granted temporary export licenses to rare-earth suppliers of the top three U.S. automakers, two sources familiar with the matter said, as supply chain disruptions begin to surface from Beijing's export curbs on those materials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-issues-rare-earth-licenses-suppliers-top-3-us-automakers-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FK4ZV62VHFJ43BEHTHLZC3FMLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美欧数十亿美元的人工智能数据园区交易远未敲定]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，由于对安全问题的持续担忧，一项利用美国技术在阿联酋建设全球最大数据中心之一的数十亿美元交易远未达成。【原文：A multi-billion dollar deal to build one of the world's largest data centre hubs in the United Arab Emirates with U.S. technology is far from being concluded due to persistent concerns around security, sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-uae-multi-billion-dollar-ai-data-campus-deal-far-finalised-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7BUCHNMDVKALH5KMMFS5SWAFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储应将利率下调整整一个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）应将利率下调整整一个百分点，他同时重申了自己的观点，即美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在降低借贷成本方面过于迟缓。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve should cut interest rates by a full percentage point, President Donald Trump said on Friday as he reiterated his view that Fed Chair Jerome Powell has been too slow to lower borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-should-cut-interest-rate-by-full-point-trump-says-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7VLG3K46FOVPCR4QXSS3JUNAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉寻求阻止奥斯汀市政府公开机器人出租车试验记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉正试图阻止德克萨斯州奥斯汀市向路透社公开该电动汽车制造商本月计划在该市推出自动驾驶机器人出租车的相关记录。【原文：Tesla is trying to prevent the city of Austin, Texas, from releasing public records to Reuters involving the EV maker’s planned launch of self-driving robotaxis in the city this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-seeks-block-city-austin-releasing-records-robotaxi-trial-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56QJ7WIW4NNYVLPVFXUP2XWEHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼提出全面改革和放松银行监管的宏伟议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储新任最高监管官员制定了一项雄心勃勃的议程，重新审视和放宽众多银行规则和监督政策，她认为这些规则和政策已经变得繁琐和不必要。【原文：The Federal Reserve's new top regulatory official laid out an ambitious agenda for revisiting and easing numerous bank rules and oversight policies which she argued have become onerous and unnecessary.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-bowman-lays-out-ambitious-agenda-overhaul-ease-bank-oversight-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BQMAEUOQ5O6TAU44DV7RHON5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度与美国的贸易谈判随着达成临时协议的最后期限临近而延长]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士称，印度和美国官员之间的贸易谈判已延长至下周，双方寻求就农业和汽车行业的关税削减达成共识，以期在7月9日的最后期限之前敲定一项临时协议。【原文：Trade talks between Indian and U.S. officials have been extended into next week as both sides seek consensus on tariff cuts in the farming and auto sectors, aiming to finalise an interim deal before a July 9 deadline, Indian government sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/india-us-trade-talks-extended-deadline-looms-interim-deal-say-sources-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHKYBIM7KRKDTNILXPPVXTCUEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:46:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士要求瑞银增加 260 亿美元资本；股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政府周五对瑞银收购瑞士信贷后提出了更严格的规定，这可能会使瑞银多持有 260 亿美元的核心资本，从而证实了该银行对即将出台的新规定的一些最坏担心。【原文：The Swiss government on Friday proposed stricter rules for UBS following its takeover of Credit Suisse, which could make it hold $26 billion more in core capital, confirming some of the bank's worst fears about incoming new regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-faces-tough-new-swiss-banking-sector-rules-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PWMAL7IRJJG5CAQTTPZYQSJAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府：瑞银回购可能受资本新规影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政府周五表示，在提出瑞银应持有更高水平核心资本的建议后，瑞银未来可能会减少股票回购的次数。【原文：UBS may be able to carry out fewer share buy-backs in future following proposals that it should hold higher levels of core capital, the Swiss government said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-buybacks-may-be-hit-by-new-capital-rules-government-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRG4QTNVSZOETLFVIXQ6YDFDGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国货币市场基金流入激增，因对关税持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至6月4日的一周里，美国货币市场基金出现了大量资金流入，原因是投资者对美国提高钢铁进口关税持谨慎态度，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与中国的贸易争端存在不确定性，以及周五将公布一份至关重要的就业报告，这些因素都刺激了投资者对更安全的投资渠道的需求。【原文：U.S. money market funds witnessed huge inflows in the week ended June 4 as investor caution over a rise in U.S. tariffs on steel imports, uncertainties over President Donald Trump's trade disputes with China and a crucial employment report on Friday, boosted demand for safer investment avenues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-money-market-fund-inflows-surge-caution-over-tariffs-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNR47VYF2BJUPGUTJBCJYVRORE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点：美国 5 月就业人数增长放缓，失业率保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份美国就业增长放缓，失业率保持稳定，这可能会给美联储推迟恢复降息提供缓冲。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed in May, while the unemployment rate held steady, potentially giving the Federal Reserve a buffer to delay the resumption of interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-us-payrolls-growth-slows-may-unemployment-rate-steady-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHXT3TCYMRPF7JSC2S37F54FFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>