<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:50:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:50:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司和墨西哥航空公司要求延期完成反垄断协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司和墨西哥航空公司周二表示反对美国交通部提出的终止反垄断协议的建议，同时要求在必要时延长协议期限。【原文：Carriers Delta and Aeromexico on Tuesday argued against winding down their antitrust agreement, as proposed by the U.S. Department of Transportation, while asking for an extension to do so if needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/delta-aeromexico-request-extension-wrap-up-antitrust-agreement-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ECYAZ5LNNLLZAY4C4U2EGZO4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:18:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Tyro Payments 公司确认来自不同方面的收购意向]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tyro Payments 公司周三表示，近几个月来已收到来自多方的收购邀约，此举是为了澄清上一交易日该公司股票在澳大利亚交易所停牌后的猜测。【原文：Tyro Payments said on Wednesday it has received takeover approaches from multiple parties in recent months, moving to clarify speculation after its shares were halted on the Australian exchange in the prior session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-tyro-payments-confirms-takeover-interest-separate-parties-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4ZMZVBXZFMDHLF5VSTOWP53MU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:12:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 7 月份批发通胀率连续第 4 个月放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的数据显示，日本 7 月份的年度批发通胀率连续第四个月放缓，这凸显了日本央行的观点，即原材料成本带来的价格上涨压力将逐渐消散。【原文：Japan's annual wholesale inflation slowed for the fourth straight month in July, data showed on Wednesday, underscoring the central bank's view that upward price pressure from raw material costs will dissipate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-wholesale-inflation-slows-4th-month-july-2025-08-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFQWSUVYEJJMBGSMFJ6R5N6VBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究公司称，7 月电动汽车销量增速放缓至 21]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场研究公司 Rho Motion 周三表示，由于中国插电式混合动力汽车销售势头放缓，7 月份全球电动汽车销量同比增长 21%，为 1 月份以来最慢，低于 6 月份的 25%。【原文：Global electric vehicle sales grew 21% year-on-year in July, the slowest rate since January and down from 25% in June, as momentum in plug-in hybrid sales in China slackened, market research firm Rho Motion said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/electric-vehicle-sales-growth-eases-21-july-research-firm-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJ63UZF7CVMHLPVUZNASP33Z5A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:08:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国达成贸易协议后，8 月日本制造商信心上升，但关税给前景蒙上阴影：路透社 Tankan 民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社 Tankan 民意调查显示，在东京与华盛顿达成贸易协议后，日本制造商对 8 月份的经营状况信心增强，但由于美国关税的潜在影响，他们对前景仍持谨慎态度。【原文：Japanese manufacturers grew more confident about business conditions in August after a trade agreement between Tokyo and Washington, but remained cautious about the outlook due to potential U.S. tariff impacts, a Reuters Tankan poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japan-manufacturers-sentiment-rises-august-after-us-trade-deal-tariffs-cloud-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4RTU75UCRJZFJPW7IJLWDEQFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西将提供 56 亿美元帮助出口商应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周二表示，巴西政府将提供 300 亿雷亚尔（约合 55.5 亿美元）的信贷，作为支持出口商品的公司的计划的一部分，这些公司受到了来自华盛顿的更高关税的影响。【原文：Brazil's President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva on Tuesday said his government would provide 30 billion reais ($5.55 billion) in credit as part of a plan to support companies that export goods and are affected by steeper tariffs imposed from Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-provide-56-billion-help-exporters-navigate-us-tariffs-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z72V3RFKBFLPDGYF2HVVQKE2BI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 22:50:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会解决 "清洁卡车伙伴关系 "反垄断问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周二表示，它已经解决了 "清洁卡车伙伴关系 "引起的反垄断问题，该伙伴关系涉及主要的卡车制造商。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Tuesday it had resolved antitrust concerns arising from the "Clean Truck Partnership," which involves major truck manufacturers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/ftc-resolves-clean-truck-partnership-antitrust-concerns-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D33UIZVNENNXPB63IHLXRW7IJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 22:28:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国库葡萄酒庄年度利润增长 15.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚财政部葡萄酒公司（Treasury Wine Estates）周三报告称，其年度基本利润增长了 15.5%，这反映了其豪华产品组合的强劲表现，尤其是奔富（Penfolds）。【原文：Australia's Treasury Wine Estates reported a 15.5% rise in its annual underlying profit on Wednesday, reflecting strong performance in its luxury portfolio, particularly Penfolds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-treasury-wine-estates-posts-155-rise-annual-profit-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VELJ2CQCKFKLRNOKOQ77P3IM6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 22:26:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚保险集团年度盈利增长，股息上调]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚保险集团（Insurance Australia Group）周三发布报告称，由于保费上涨和自然灾害成本低于预期，集团利润大幅增长，年度现金收益飙升近 30%，并上调了股息。【原文：Insurance Australia Group reported on Wednesday a near 30% jump in annual cash earnings and raised its dividend, as higher premiums and lower-than-expected natural peril costs boosted profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/insurance-australia-group-annual-earnings-rise-hikes-dividend-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJQOY6MA4FLITC3RGFM2PMROJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚联邦银行全年现金利润创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚联邦银行（Commonwealth Bank of Australia）周三公布了全年最佳现金收益报告，并宣布派发创纪录的股息，因为住房和企业贷款额的强劲增长以及稳定的基本利润率提高了其利润。【原文：Commonwealth Bank of Australia reported its best full-year cash earnings and announced a record dividend payout on Wednesday, as strong growth in home and business lending volumes and stable underlying margins bolstered its profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commonwealth-bank-australias-posts-record-full-year-cash-profit-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRZTMY6KXFOZHJO7QHYHUDJROQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西总统卢拉表示监管社交媒体平台的提案已准备就绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周二表示，一项规范国内社交媒体平台的提案已经准备就绪，并将提交国会。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Tuesday that a proposal to regulate social media platforms in the country is ready and will be sent to Congress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-lula-says-proposal-regulate-social-media-platforms-is-ready-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIF6EBRPZ5PEVJR3YGD2NQ5BMM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Venture Global 在与壳牌的液化天然气合同货物仲裁案中胜诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国液化天然气巨头 Venture Global 周二表示，该公司在与壳牌的法律诉讼中获胜，因为壳牌未能按照从 2023 年开始的长期合同交付液化天然气。【原文：Venture Global has won a legal battle against Shell over its failure to deliver liquefied natural gas under long-term contracts starting in 2023, the U.S. LNG major said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venture-global-wins-arbitration-case-against-shell-over-contracted-lng-cargoes-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2IGGXQLDNVL35NO4V7C4MQYBCI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡瓦公司自上市以来首次下调年度销售增长目标，股价大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡瓦公司的股票在周二的延时交易中下跌了 21%，因为这家地中海连锁餐厅自两年前在纽约证券交易所上市以来首次下调了年度同店销售增长目标。【原文：Shares of Cava dropped 21% in extended trading on Tuesday, after the Mediterranean restaurant chain lowered its annual same-store sales growth target for the first time since it listed on the New York Stock Exchange two years ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cavas-shares-crater-after-first-annual-sales-growth-target-cut-since-ipo-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OD2NIQ5JS5LZRPVFIUJDWM7PIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 世界股市大涨，美联储减息迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGL2ZG662RP3TDXRORUSRCMSZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[获得美国新许可后，雪佛龙包租油轮停靠委内瑞拉装载石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[LSEG的跟踪数据显示，一艘雪佛龙公司租用的油轮周二停靠在委内瑞拉国营公司PDVSA的何塞码头，根据雪佛龙公司7月份获得的新许可证，这艘油轮将成为第一艘向美国出口原油的油轮。【原文：A Chevron-chartered tanker docked at Venezuelan state company PDVSA's Jose terminal on Tuesday, positioning it to be the first to export crude to the United States under a new license Chevron received in July, LSEG tracking data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-chartered-tanker-docks-venezuela-load-oil-after-new-us-license-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFC2MCBZXROABDPFLQQ2UOHPEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:58:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：关税收入使最高法院难以做出不利于特朗普的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，关税给美国政府国库带来的收入不断增加，如果下级法院的案件提交到最高法院，最高法院将很难就这一问题做出不利于特朗普政府的裁决。【原文：Increasing revenues flowing into U.S. government coffers from tariffs would make it difficult for the Supreme Court to rule against the Trump administration on the issue if a lower court case makes its way to country's top court, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/tariff-revenue-makes-it-hard-supreme-court-rule-against-trump-bessent-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GIZVJYR5NKEHMBAHSXKTMUFLQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:51:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西游说团体称美国咖啡买家要求推迟进口巴西咖啡]]></title><description><![CDATA[当地出口商组织 Cecafe 周二表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对巴西商品征收 50%的关税后，美国的咖啡买家已开始要求推迟进口巴西咖啡。【原文：Coffee buyers in the United States have started requesting to postpone imports of Brazilian coffee following a 50% tariff imposed on Brazilian goods by U.S. President Donald Trump, local exporters' group Cecafe said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-coffee-buyers-requesting-postpone-brazil-imports-brazilian-lobby-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WILREZ2OX5KPVHI3XXR2GUC6LM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:47:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，他希望米兰能在九月份的会议上被确认担任美联储职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，他希望参议院能够确认现任经济顾问委员会（Council of Economic Advisers）主席斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）在 9 月份美联储下一次会议之前填补美联储董事会的临时空缺。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Tuesday said he was hopeful the Senate would confirm Stephen Miran, now chair of the Council of Economic Advisers, to fill a temporary vacancy on the Federal Reserve board before its next meeting in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-says-he-is-hopeful-miran-can-be-confirmed-fed-post-by-september-meeting-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I33P75FGHNPPZL6GI3VV7HPTN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:39:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：美国贸易团队将在未来两三个月内会见中国官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，美国贸易官员将在未来两三个月内再次与中国贸易官员会面，讨论两国经济关系的未来。【原文：U.S. trade officials will meet again with their Chinese counterparts within the next two or three months to discuss the future of the economic relationship between the two countries, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Tuesday, a day after the Trump administration extended a pause on sharply higher U.S. tariffs on Chinese imports for another 90 days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-trade-team-will-meet-chinese-officials-next-2-3-months-bessent-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBYO2DSRLNKU3MG476VSZZEIII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国为小型核试验反应堆快速通道计划挑选 11 家公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部周二表示，它已初步选定 11 家公司参与一项旨在开发高科技试验核反应堆的试点计划，并让其中至少三家公司在不到一年的时间内开始运行。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy said on Tuesday it has made an initial selection of 11 companies for a pilot program seeking to develop high-tech test nuclear reactors and get at least three of them to begin operating in less than a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-selects-11-firms-program-fast-track-small-nuclear-test-reactors-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WHXJSVRURIDDHL4PNBFR66T5A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:15:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能需求强劲，CoreWeave 季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，CoreWeave 的第二季度营收超过了华尔街的预期，原因是市场对这家由英伟达（Nvidia）支持的人工智能云计算公司的服务需求加速增长。【原文：CoreWeave topped Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue on Tuesday, driven by accelerating demand for the Nvidia-backed AI cloud computing firm's services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coreweave-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-sturdy-ai-demand-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">453Z4NKUHNKDPLUOZL6YKUMJVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:11:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，美国计划继续发布月度就业报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周二表示，按照 "计划"，劳工统计局将继续发布其备受关注的月度就业报告，此前，唐纳德-特朗普总统挑选的劳工统计局局长提议暂停发布该报告，同时解决导致近期就业增长预估出现历史性大幅修正的问题。【原文：The White House on Tuesday said it is "the plan" that the Bureau of Labor Statistics will continue to publish its closely watched monthly employment report after President Donald Trump's pick to head the agency proposed suspending its release while it addresses problems that resulted in historically large revisions to recent job growth estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-plans-keep-publishing-monthly-jobs-report-white-house-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USUKIF5B6RM37ODDYRF6GQ4CQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CPI 公布后，投资者加倍看好美联储 9 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[上个月通胀率温和上扬，表明唐纳德-特朗普总统的全面进口关税对商品价格的传导迄今为止还很有限，因此投资者加大了对美联储 9 月份降息的押注。【原文：Investors are betting harder on a September Federal Reserve interest rate cut after last month's mild inflation bump, which indicated the pass-through from President Donald Trump's sweeping import duties to goods prices has so far been limited.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-double-down-september-fed-cut-after-cpi-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMEUW2EWXVMEZIV2KC6QEUO2V4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:58:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加航空乘人员在可能的罢工前拒绝接受具有约束力的仲裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大公共雇员工会（Canadian Union of Public Employees）周二表示，加航空乘人员拒绝了航空公司提出的具有约束力的仲裁建议，并继续进行直接谈判。【原文：Air Canada flight attendants rejected the airline's proposal for binding arbitration on Tuesday and continued direct talks, the Canadian Union of Public Employees said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-canada-flight-attendants-reject-binding-arbitration-ahead-possible-strike-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CNCICXFBNNBLB7ADZ2ISY4P3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》报道：俄罗斯被怀疑是美国联邦法院文件系统遭黑客攻击的幕后黑手]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周二援引几位知情人士的话报道，调查人员发现有证据表明，俄罗斯至少对最近黑客入侵管理美国联邦法院文件的计算机系统负有部分责任。【原文：Investigators have uncovered evidence that Russia is at least in part responsible for a recent hack of the computer system that manages U.S. federal court documents, the New York Times reported on Tuesday, citing several people briefed on the breach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russia-is-suspected-be-behind-hack-us-federal-court-filing-system-new-york-times-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUIDN4ZBA5MIDGHK3RTKJVVRAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:49:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[能源部长表示，如果埃克森公司在特立尼达发现石油和天然气，将投资高达 217 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源部长鲁达尔-穆尼拉尔（Roodal Moonilal）表示，如果埃克森美孚在特立尼达和多巴哥计划勘探石油和天然气的大片深水区发现储量，这家能源巨头可能会在特立尼达和多巴哥投资多达 217 亿美元。【原文：Exxon Mobil could invest as much as $21.7 billion in Trinidad and Tobago if the energy major finds reserves in a large deepwater area it plans to explore for oil and gas in the Caribbean country, energy minister Roodal Moonilal said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-could-invest-much-217-billion-if-it-finds-oil-gas-trinidad-energy-minister-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPJ42COZKJPTRJCHLKBNJ2MO5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，加拿大房地产软件供应商 Altus 集团正在探索出售事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，两位熟悉内情的人士称，专注于房地产行业的加拿大软件和数据分析提供商 Altus Group 在收到收购意向后，正在探索潜在的出售方案。【原文：Altus Group , a Canadian software and data analytics provider focused on the real estate industry, is exploring a potential sale after receiving inbound acquisition interest, two people familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/canadian-real-estate-software-provider-altus-group-explores-sale-sources-say-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5EJAAF6YRIADBECTDHF6JHRZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:56:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西橙汁副产品将受到特朗普关税的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业贸易组织 CitrusBR 周二表示，由于美国 8 月初对巴西许多产品征收 50%的高额关税，巴西橙汁副产品出口商的收入将大幅下降。【原文：Brazilian exporters of orange juice byproducts will suffer a major revenue decline from a hefty 50% U.S. tariff imposed on many of the country's products in early August, industry trade group CitrusBR said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-orange-juice-byproducts-will-suffer-trump-tariffs-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECFLZTMYEVNJ5EXHXBPK7TIJOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称特朗普正考虑就装修问题起诉美联储主席鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫发言人卡罗琳-利维特（Karoline Leavitt）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正在考虑对美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）就其管理美联储华盛顿总部装修一事提起诉讼。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is considering a lawsuit against Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell related to his management of renovations at the Fed's Washington headquarters, White House spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trump-weighing-lawsuit-against-feds-powell-over-renovations-white-house-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AEH5HQYULNPZZLTP23KPSTPA5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:11:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管关税收入激增，美国 7 月赤字仍增至 2910 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周二表示，尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税带来了 210 亿美元的关税收入，但美国政府 7 月份的预算赤字仍增长了近 20%，达到 2910 亿美元，支出增长快于收入增长。【原文：The U.S. government's budget deficit grew nearly 20% in July to $291 billion despite a $21 billion jump in customs duty collections from President Donald Trump's tariffs, with outlays growing faster than receipts, the Treasury Department said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-deficit-grows-291-billion-july-despite-surge-tariff-revenue-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAPZAMLKBNJZ7D4HTBLOPWDIWA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>