<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 06:08:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 06:08:34 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，随着矿山关闭和中国电动汽车销售缓解供应过剩，2025 年锂价将趋于稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和交易商表示，由于关闭的矿山和中国强劲的电动汽车销售消化了供应过剩，锂价在经历两年的急剧下跌后，有望在2025年企稳，不过矿山重新开放的可能性可能会限制涨幅。【原文：Lithium prices are expected to stabilise in 2025 after two years of steep declines as shuttered mines and robust electric vehicle sales in China soak up an oversupply, although the potential for mines to reopen may cap gains, analysts and traders said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/lithium-prices-stabilise-2025-mine-closures-china-ev-sales-ease-glut-analysts-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVT3TSZJNZNQHKHH2MD2WREFQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 05:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标忘记软着陆，继续飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVSXMEWJ2RLWRF3DMBKSLBZYMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 05:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚明星娱乐公司在跌至历史最低点后缩减亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚赌场运营商 Star Entertainment 的股价周一跳涨 13.6%，分析师认为股价上涨是由于投资者在该股上周跌至历史新低后以更低的价格买入了该股。【原文：Shares of Australian casino operator Star Entertainment jumped 13.6% higher on Monday, with analysts citing the rise to investors buying the stock at a cheaper price after it fell to a record low last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australias-star-entertainment-pares-losses-after-slipping-record-low-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4M6ZTKFH7BPABONDYD6YQPOJHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 05:21:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片需求强劲，台积电第四季度利润大增 58]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾中芯国际集成电路制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co , the main global producer of advanced chips used in artificial intelligence applications, is expected to report a 58% leap in fourth-quarter profit on Thursday because of surging demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-fourth-quarter-profit-seen-jumping-58-strong-ai-chip-demand-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQ5S6UFENFMDFN4FLMXXVSUOG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 05:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易风险下中国出口增长加快，进口出人意料]]></title><description><![CDATA[12 月份，中国的出口增长加快，进口也有所恢复，在世界第二大经济体准备应对与即将上任的美国政府之间日益加剧的贸易风险之际，中国以积极的态势结束了今年的经济增长。【原文：China's export growth picked up steam in December, while imports recovered, closing out the year on a positive note as the world's second-largest economy braces for mounting trade risks with the incoming U.S. administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-export-growth-quickens-amid-trade-risks-imports-surprise-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZEBMNY3PZO7RMIXH2WECYRV2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 03:29:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国加强政策措施捍卫脆弱的人民币]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，在人民币兑美元汇率徘徊在16个月低点附近之际，中国放宽了允许更多离岸借款的规定，并发出口头警告，加大了政策措施的力度，以捍卫不断走软的人民币。【原文：China stepped up its policy measures on Monday to defend a weakening yuan by relaxing rules to allow more offshore borrowing and sending verbal warnings as the Chinese currency hovered around 16-month lows against a strong dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-steps-up-policy-measures-defend-fragile-yuan-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTQQ55KEL5OBNEO2Z56G7MKX4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 03:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赞成 Chemist Warehouse-Sigma Healthcare 58 亿美元交易的所有权事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[代理权咨询公司 Ownership Matters 周一表示，建议 Sigma Healthcare 的股东投票支持 Chemist Warehouse 对该制药公司的反向收购，理由是股东价值巨大。【原文：Proxy advisory firm Ownership Matters said on Monday it recommends that shareholders of Sigma Healthcare vote in favour of Chemist Warehouse's reverse takeover of the pharmaceutical company, citing significant shareholder value.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/ownership-matters-favour-chemist-warehouse-sigma-healthcare-58-bln-deal-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COC4ZC4BY5I4BLUXRGMB3LFSMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 02:49:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[开发商收到清算申请后，中国世茂下跌 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国房地产开发商世茂集团收到清盘申请后，其股价周一下跌 15%，至 0.73 港元，为 9 月 26 日以来最低。【原文：Shares of China's Shimao Group dropped 15% to HK$0.73 on Monday, their lowest since Sept. 26, after the property developer received a liquidation petition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-shimao-drops-15-after-developer-receives-liquidation-petition-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NA3A3AIHENJC5EYLKG2XLYO27U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 01:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[扎实的就业数据让美元巍然不动，同行却在苦苦挣扎]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美元以强劲的势头开始了本周的走势，在一份井喷式的美国就业报告凸显出世界最大经济体相对于世界其他经济体的优异表现之后，美元离开了在多年低点附近徘徊的同类货币。【原文：The dollar began the week on a strong note on Monday, leaving its peers languishing near multi-year lows after a blowout U.S. jobs report that underlined the outperformance of the world's largest economy versus the rest of the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/towering-dollar-after-solid-jobs-data-leaves-peers-struggling-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5FQE3OV7ZK2VPHHR72MBXXTKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 01:23:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相要求拜登缓解商界对新日铁与美国钢铁交易状况的担忧，《日本经济新闻》称]]></title><description><![CDATA[据日本时事通讯社周一报道，日本首相石破茂要求美国总统拜登消除日本和美国商界对新日铁收购美国钢铁公司计划的担忧。【原文：Japan Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba asked U.S. President Joe Biden to allay concerns in the Japanese and U.S. business community over the status of Nippon Steel's planned acquisition of U.S. Steel , Jiji news agency said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japan-pm-asks-biden-allay-business-community-concern-over-status-nippon-steel-us-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WW2ULWMYR5PCLO4C4YLGPSP5CE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝索斯认为马斯克与特朗普在太空竞赛中的关系不会造成威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA["埃隆一直非常清楚，他这样做是为了公众利益，而不是为了个人利益。【原文："Elon has been very clear that he's doing this for the public interest and not for his personal gain," said the founder of Blue Origin, which rivals SpaceX in the space industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/bezos-optimistic-about-trumps-space-agenda-not-concerned-about-musk-influence-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5QCXA26G5JMZAHC33Y7BFRQBA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市下滑，美元坚挺，原因是通胀和盈利问题迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市下滑，美元则维持在 14 个月高位附近，因为就在财报季开始之际，一份明确强劲的就业报告推高了债券收益率，并测试了股票的高估值。【原文：Asian shares slipped on Monday while the dollar held near 14-month peaks after an unambiguously strong payrolls report shoved up bond yields and tested lofty equity valuations just as the earnings season gets under way.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMPKXJI6MVNL7PKTDKLCPJ6C5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球航空金融峰会将评估飞机短缺和贸易风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[受强劲的租赁率和相对稳定的油价提振，但也面临着飞机短缺和贸易紧张局势带来的不确定性。【原文：Financiers and lessors who make the global air travel industry tick gather for an annual meeting in Dublin on Monday, buoyed by strong lease rates and relatively stable oil prices but facing uncertainty over jet shortages and trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/global-air-finance-summit-take-stock-jet-shortages-trade-risks-2025-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXHMIURLMFMOJCTKB5GNMV553U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁打击俄罗斯出口，石油创逾三个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一开盘，油价创下三个多月来的最高水平，涨势延续，原因是市场预期美国扩大制裁将影响俄罗斯对世界第一和第三大进口国中国和印度的原油供应。【原文：Oil prices hit their highest level in more than three months on Monday's open, extending their rally on expectations that wider U.S. sanctions will affect Russian crude supplies to the world's top and third largest importers China and India.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-hits-more-than-3-month-high-us-sanctions-hit-russia-exports-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUMEPUPSYBIGXOL5MC62ERIUDY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 23:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究称，预计的航空旅行增长与气候目标背道而驰]]></title><description><![CDATA[气候倡导组织 "运输与环境 "周一发布的一份研究报告显示，预计到2050年，航空旅客人数将增加一倍以上，这将导致燃料需求激增，并削弱航空业的减排措施。【原文：The number of air passengers is projected to more than double by 2050, causing surging fuel demand and undermining the aviation industry's steps to reduce its emissions, a study from climate advocacy group Transport and Environment showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/projected-air-travel-growth-runs-counter-climate-goals-study-says-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIUU27CDNBMQZKLOCMFKYTXJFY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 23:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：火热的美国就业数据点燃收益率之火，抨击股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNUHOJX36FPYRIN4B3IFL26IUE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 21:47:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩资本将收购澳大利亚 Insignia Financial 的出价提高至近 18 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Insignia Financial 公司周一表示，私募股权公司贝恩资本（Bain Capital）提高了对这家拥有 178 年历史的财富管理公司的出价，目前的估值为 28.7 亿澳元（17.6 亿美元）。【原文：Australia's Insignia Financial said on Monday, private equity firm Bain Capital has sweetened its bid for the 178-year-old wealth manager, now valuing it at A$2.87 billion ($1.76 billion), weeks after Insignia rejected Bain's earlier offer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-capital-sweetens-bid-australias-insignia-financial-nearly-18-bln-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYXWDKZVGJO5HAOEWEXTUBX2EY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 21:43:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，银行监管机构就银行股权问题向贝莱德发出新的最后期限要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周日援引三位知情人士的话报道，美国联邦存款保险公司（Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation）给贝莱德公司（BlackRock）规定了一个新的最后期限，即在 2 月 10 日之前解决该公司持有的银行股票的监管问题。【原文：The Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation gave a fresh deadline of Feb. 10 to BlackRock to resolve an issue regarding oversight into the firm's stock in banks, Bloomberg News reported on Sunday, citing three people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-regulator-gives-blackrock-new-deadline-bank-stakes-bloomberg-reports-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKXJ3SGWBFIZZI5MBGIGXUS6KI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 17:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 TCS 预计银行业复苏后零售业和制造业将复苏]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度第一大软件服务出口商塔塔咨询服务公司的一位高层管理人员说，该公司预计，继银行和金融服务部门出现类似的增长之后，其在北美的零售和制造业客户将增加在技术方面的支出。【原文：India's Tata Consultancy Services expects its retail and manufacturing clients in North America to step up spending on tech, following a similar upturn in its banking and financial services segment, a top executive of the nation's No. 1 software-services exporter, said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indias-tcs-expects-retail-manufacturing-revival-after-banking-recovery-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46ZYZG73G5LJHBRJ5ENK3EAZ6A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 07:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登政府推迟执行阻止新日铁、美国钢铁交易的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府将暂缓执行本月行政命令中要求新日铁放弃以 149 亿美元竞购美国钢铁公司的规定。
 两家公司周六表示。【原文：The Biden administration will hold off enforcing a requirement laid out in an executive order this month that Nippon Steel abandon its $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel 
 , the companies said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/biden-admin-delays-enforcement-order-blocking-nippon-steel-us-steel-deal-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FLD5HQ5LFMS7KYAVVABVNBKCM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 01:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果董事会建议股东投票反对取消多元化计划的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据苹果公司提交的代理文件，该公司董事会建议投资者投票反对股东提出的取消公司多元化、公平与包容（DEI）计划的提案。【原文：Apple's board of directors recommended investors vote against a shareholder proposal to abolish the company's Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) programs, according to a proxy filing from the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apples-board-recommends-shareholders-vote-against-proposal-eliminate-diversity-2025-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYEW6UJDZZJ7XB6BAGTUAKFNBI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 01:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德与 LEO 制药公司合作开发炎症性疾病项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司（Gilead Sciences）周六表示，该公司与丹麦 LEO Pharma 公司建立了合作伙伴关系，共同开发治疗炎症性疾病患者的项目。【原文：Gilead Sciences said on Saturday that it entered into a partnership with Denmark's LEO Pharma to develop programs to treat patients with inflammatory diseases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/gilead-leo-pharma-partner-develop-programs-inflammatory-diseases-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOQNGV24OZKG3CDMQSD3KJRDH4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 17:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，赞比亚证监会就中国房地产债券不当销售制裁渣打银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位知情人士透露，赞比亚证券交易委员会（SEC）已经对渣打银行进行了制裁，原因是渣打银行在亚洲国家房地产危机最严重的时候向该行的一位当地财富客户错误地销售了一家中国房地产公司的债券。【原文：Zambia's Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has sanctioned Standard Chartered for mis-selling a Chinese property company's bonds to one of the bank's local wealth clients at the height of the Asian country's real-estate crisis, according to a source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/zambias-sec-sanctions-standard-chartered-over-china-property-bond-mis-selling-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OC3WB77ENJLJPEVZENW5DM62KE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:02:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 警告称，如果美国最高法院允许禁令，将会产生更广泛的后果]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 及其中国母公司字节跳动（ByteDance）的律师在最高法院就一项法律进行辩论时提出了警告，该法律将强制在美国销售短视频应用程序或禁止其使用：如果美国国会可以这样对待 TikTok，那么它也可以这样对待其他公司。【原文：The lawyer for TikTok and its Chinese parent company ByteDance offered a warning during Supreme Court arguments over a law that would compel the sale of the short-video app or ban it in the United States: If Congress could do this to TikTok, it could come after other companies, too.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tiktok-warns-broader-consequences-if-us-supreme-court-allows-ban-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3BTGJXDMFKZ3EOVETEEE72LDY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 11:09:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报刊称瑞士前财长对扩大后的瑞银集团规模提出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士前财政部长乌利-毛雷尔（Ueli Maurer）周六表示，瑞银收购瑞士信贷后，可能会被认为对瑞士来说过于庞大，需要采取措施降低这家扩大后的银行的风险。【原文：UBS could be seen as being too big for Switzerland following its takeover of Credit Suisse, former Swiss Finance Minister Ueli Maurer said on Saturday, with measures needed to reduce the risks of the enlarged bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/former-swiss-finance-minister-warns-about-size-enlarged-ubs-newspaper-says-2025-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFQA46VKQNMZBETTLBM3E2FCNA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 08:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百健公司拟以 4.42 亿美元收购赛捷公司剩余股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一份文件显示，制药公司百健将以每股7.22美元的价格收购其尚未持有的Sage Therapeutics公司的所有流通股，这使得后者的股价在盘后交易中上涨了34%。【原文：Drugmaker Biogen will buy all outstanding shares of Sage Therapeutics that it does not already own for $7.22 apiece, a filing showed on Friday, sending the latter's stock up 34% in extended trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/biogen-proposes-buy-remaining-stake-sage-442-million-deal-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YYOXFWIVRKCBEB64RTKGZ5NC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国提出 2026 年医疗保险优势保险公司支付标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周五提出了 2026 年由私营保险公司经营的医疗保险优势计划的补偿标准，该标准将使支付额增加 2.2%，而去年则下降了 0.2%。【原文：The U.S. government on Friday proposed 2026 reimbursement rates for Medicare Advantage plans run by private insurers that will result in a 2.2% increase in payments, compared with a decline of 0.2% last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-proposes-payment-rate-2026-medicare-advantage-insurers-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBG7QO6GNBKRLNALNBN7MQLHUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部研究证实，美国鸡肉和猪肉工厂工人面临更高的健康风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部周五发布的两份研究报告显示，美国鸡肉和猪肉工厂的工人比其他制造业工人面临更高的患肌肉骨骼疾病（如腕管综合征）的风险。【原文：Workers in U.S. chicken and pork plants face higher risks than other manufacturing workers for musculoskeletal disorders such as carpal tunnel syndrome, according to two studies the U.S. Department of Agriculture issued on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-chicken-pork-plant-workers-face-higher-health-risks-usda-studies-confirm-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26XV2SOZHBMGBFZXPAG6EMPMVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷蒙多：台积电开始在亚利桑那州生产 4 纳米芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长吉娜-雷蒙多（Gina Raimondo）告诉路透社记者，台湾积体电路制造股份有限公司已开始在亚利桑那州为美国客户生产先进的 4 纳米芯片，这是拜登政府半导体努力的一个里程碑。【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co has begun producing advanced 4-nanometer chips for U.S. customers in Arizona, Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo told Reuters, a milestone in the Biden administration's semiconductor efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-begins-producing-4-nanometer-chips-arizona-raimondo-says-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SI5BYKBY4JNHRKHQXTDPE5HZII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 22:13:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁认为 2025 年世界经济将保持稳定增长，通货紧缩仍将持续]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周五告诉记者，IMF将在1月17日发布《世界经济展望》时预测全球经济将稳步增长，通货紧缩将持续。【原文：The International Monetary Fund will forecast steady global growth and continuing disinflation when it releases its World Economic Outlook on Jan. 17, IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva told reporters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-chief-sees-steady-world-growth-2025-continuing-disinflation-2025-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2JMU3YUWRKUBDDHJYDZ3ZB6HE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 22:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>