<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:16:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:16:04 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，本田将因车轮脱落问题召回超过 40.6 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，本田公司将在美国召回406290辆装有铝合金车轮的汽车，这些车轮作为配件出售，由于生产错误，车轮可能会从汽车上脱落。【原文：Honda is recalling 406,290 vehicles in the U.S. that have aluminium alloy wheels sold as accessories as the wheel may detach from the vehicle due to a manufacturing error, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-recall-over-406000-us-vehicles-over-wheel-detachment-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7F72WBFKRONDO45BHM2A5UXWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:14:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克预计特斯拉的全自动驾驶软件将于 2026 年初在中国获得全面批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）表示，他预计该公司的全自动驾驶软件（一种驾驶辅助系统）将于明年年初在中国获得全面批准。【原文：Tesla CEO Elon Musk said he expects the automaker's Full Self-Driving software, a driver assistance system, will be fully approved in China early next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-expects-teslas-full-self-driving-software-win-full-china-approval-early-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6LVABHN5JNBPG4NWJSCSI64YU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国开始放宽稀土出口规定，但与特朗普的希望相差甚远]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士表示，中国已开始设计新的稀土许可制度，该制度可能会加快稀土的运输，但不可能像华盛顿所希望的那样完全取消限制。【原文：China has begun designing a new rare earth licensing regime that could speed up shipments, but it is unlikely to amount to a complete rollback of restrictions as hoped by Washington, industry insiders said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-starts-work-easing-rare-earth-export-rules-short-trump-hopes-sources-say-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CBPKOCV7NLIZJEFPMOQXIYQVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储威廉姆斯：美联储可能很快需要扩大资产负债表以满足流动性需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，该央行上周决定停止缩减债券存量，可能很快就需要通过购买债券来增加资产负债表。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams said on Friday that the central bank, which last week decided to stop shrinking its stock of bonds, may soon need to grow its balance sheet through bond purchases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-williams-fed-may-soon-need-expand-balance-sheet-liquidity-needs-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBOUUBBIUJO6RIPDWQJC7KS2DM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩资本私人信贷高管撇开系统性担忧，放眼亚洲发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝恩资本私人信贷部的一位高级主管告诉路透社，全球私人信贷市场目前没有系统性风险，而亚洲则提供了最大的增长机会。【原文：The global private credit market currently has no systemic risks, while Asia offers the biggest growth opportunities, a senior Bain Capital private credit executive told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bain-capital-private-credit-executive-brushes-off-systemic-concerns-eyes-asia-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DM2RBTEOFFKORJB4QQXHFUMJQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:50:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，如果芯片供应恢复，荷兰准备放弃对 Nexperia 的控制权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道，如果中国恢复关键芯片的出口，荷兰政府准备搁置赋予其阻止或改变芯片制造商 Nexperia 关键公司决策的权力的命令。【原文：The Dutch government is ready to shelve the order that gave it power to block or change key corporate decisions at chipmaker Nexperia if China resumes exports of critical chips, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/netherlands-ready-drop-control-nexperia-if-chip-supply-resumes-bloomberg-news-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOXUFOJWFZNWXH5VT7MFQUBNBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ITV 正在与康卡斯特旗下的天空电视台洽谈 21.5 亿美元的媒体部门出售事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[ITV 周五表示，它正在与康卡斯特（Comcast）旗下的天空电视台（Sky）就可能以 16 亿英镑（21.5 亿美元）（包括债务）的价格出售这家英国广播公司的媒体和娱乐部门进行谈判。【原文：ITV said on Friday it was talks with Sky, owned by Comcast , over a potential sale of the British broadcaster's media and entertainment unit for 1.6 billion pounds ($2.15 billion) including debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/itv-talks-with-comcasts-sky-215-billion-media-unit-sale-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CB3A7VY4DVLGFMQ7QWWJBINU7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:05:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创企业 Anthropic 拓展欧洲市场，在巴黎和慕尼黑设立办事处]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国人工智能初创公司Anthropic周五表示，它正计划将业务扩展到整个欧洲，并在法国首都巴黎和德国慕尼黑开设办事处。【原文：U.S. AI startup Anthropic said on Friday it was planning to expand its operations across Europe, and open offices in the French capital Paris and Munich in Germany.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ai-startup-anthropic-expands-europe-with-offices-paris-munich-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZT62IBGZRBOBTMT3GF3RNQXONI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:01:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达首席执行官称公司不打算向中国发货]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）周五在抵达台南市进行他今年第四次公开访问台湾时表示，这家美国人工智能芯片制造商不打算向中国运送任何产品，但希望未来能再次为中国市场提供服务。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang said on Friday, upon arriving in the city of Tainan for his fourth public visit to Taiwan this year, that the U.S. AI chipmaker did not plan to ship anything to China but hoped to serve the Chinese market again in the future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nvidia-ceo-says-company-not-planning-ship-anything-china-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDRDEFJV55KNFE7JL4FFHE4CT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 06:51:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本田在第二季度业绩下滑后削减年度营业利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[本田汽车周五将其年度利润预期下调了约五分之一，并公布其第二季度营业利润下降了 25%，原因是其业绩受到了美国进口关税和与电动汽车相关的一次性成本的打击。【原文：Honda Motor cut its annual profit forecast by about a fifth and posted a 25% drop in its second-quarter operating profit on Friday, as its performance took a hit from U.S. import tariffs and one-off costs related to electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/honda-reports-25-fall-q2-operating-profit-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GHEWJB5OCJPNTK3N6U3DVULDX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 06:39:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴姆勒卡车公司季度利润下降 40%，但维持全年预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[戴姆勒卡车公司周五报告称，第三季度营业利润下降了 40%，降幅高于预期，但由于欧洲市场的积极势头和北美市场的复苏，该公司仍坚持其年度预测。【原文：Daimler Truck reported a bigger-than-expected 40% drop in third-quarter operating profit on Friday, but stuck to its annual forecasts on the back of a positive momentum in Europe and a recovery in North America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/daimler-truck-posts-40-drop-quarterly-profit-keeps-annual-forecasts-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VIAACYTZKJKPHPK7OOACNUY5BA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 06:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子任命关键决策机构新负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子周五表示，已任命 Park Hark-kyu 为其业务支持办公室的新负责人，该办公室是这家科技巨头的重要决策机构，为董事长李在镕提供服务。【原文：Samsung Electronics said on Friday it had named Park Hark-kyu as the new head of its business support office, a key decision-making body of the technology giant that serves chairman Jay Y. Lee.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-elec-names-new-head-its-business-support-division-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVZU2OTPOFI45OGPQ67KM7WMVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 06:20:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标人工智能可能还没完]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7DJDR5XEJIBDDTYGACCVW6XCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:35:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税可能使日本陷入六个季度以来的首次经济萎缩：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，在受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策打击后，日本经济在7-9月份可能出现了六个季度以来的首次萎缩。【原文：Japan's economy probably contracted for the first time in six quarters in the July-September period after being battered by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff policies, a Reuters poll showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-tariffs-likely-push-japan-into-first-economic-contraction-six-quarters-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6TJISFIOJJKDKDXHZLAYSKYEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:18:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：面对美国和大型科技公司的压力，欧盟权衡暂停具有里程碑意义的人工智能法案的部分内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，在大型科技公司和美国政府的强大压力下，欧盟委员会正在提议暂停实施其具有里程碑意义的人工智能法律的部分内容。【原文：The European Commission is proposing a pause to parts of its landmark artificial intelligence laws amid intense pressure from big tech companies and the U.S. government, Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-weighs-pausing-parts-landmark-ai-act-face-us-big-tech-pressure-ft-reports-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R24CSNTTP5I5BBWZSYXFK2N4IA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:17:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西太平洋银行不会就裁员失利提起上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚西太平洋银行（Westpac）的一位发言人表示，该行在强制一名员工每周两次到办公室上班的案件中败诉，因此不会对劳工法庭的裁决提起上诉。【原文：Australian bank Westpac will not appeal a labour tribunal ruling after it lost a case to compel one of its workers to be in the office twice a week, according to a bank spokesperson.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/westpac-will-not-appeal-work-from-home-ruling-loss-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFZUIAWUA5JHJM7I42DXU3HPWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:08:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本投资者因对美联储言论和估值担忧持谨慎态度而抛售外国股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月1日的一周内，日本投资者大量减持外国股票，因为他们在美国联邦储备委员会一些官员发表鹰派言论后转为谨慎，并倾向于在近期市场反弹后锁定利润。【原文：Japanese investors divested significant holdings in foreign stocks in the week to November 1, as they turned cautious amid hawkish remarks from some U.S. Federal Reserve officials and favoured locking in profits after the recent market rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japanese-investors-sell-foreign-stocks-caution-over-fed-comments-valuation-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUHKRRKMPJJULFOUXBLFKS2N3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本财务大臣表示，日本政府将支持大银行发行稳定币的项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣片山聪树周五表示，日本金融厅已决定支持日本三大银行联合发行稳定币的项目。【原文：Japan's Financial Services Agency has decided to support a project by the country's three largest banks to jointly issue stablecoins, Finance Minister Satsuki Katayama said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-government-support-big-banks-project-issue-stablecoins-finance-minister-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHOUCKOLXROS7E3ATMHNKF3ZEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:42:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡电信出售约 12 亿美元的印度巴帝电信股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡电信公司（Singapore Telecommunications）周五表示，该公司以 15 亿新元（11.6 亿美元）的价格出售了印度第二大移动运营商 Bharti Airtel 0.8% 的股份。【原文：Singapore Telecommunications said on Friday its unit sold a 0.8% stake in India's second-largest mobile carrier Bharti Airtel for S$1.5 billion ($1.16 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/over-51-million-shares-indias-bharti-airtel-change-hands-via-block-deals-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KZGLRMNSZMPFPGXHT372KYMPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相高市让大手大脚的拥护者担任小组成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本主张扩张性财政政策的通货再膨胀主义者在经济决策中卷土重来，其中一些人被首相高市真奈钦点担任政府重要部门的职务。【原文：Japan's reflationist advocates of expansionary fiscal policy are making a comeback in economic decision-making with some hand-picked by Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi to fill posts in key government panels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japan-pm-takaichi-fills-panel-posts-with-advocates-big-spending-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3XLLQNVDRN63FJZSVO3IVS7RM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示，约 15,000 名用户的 Apple TV 出现故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 称，周四美国有近 14907 名用户的苹果流媒体服务 Apple TV 出现故障。【原文：Apple's streaming service Apple TV was down for nearly 14,907 users in the U.S. on Thursday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-tv-down-about-15000-users-downdetector-shows-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHD24D547RKVTGANPXAERM5RQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:56:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球贸易压力增大，中国出口意外下滑至2月以来最差水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 10 月份的出口出人意料地下滑，原因是海外订单减少，而此前几个月，中国为抵御美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税而采取了前置措施。【原文：China's exports unexpectedly slumped in October as overseas orders tapered off following months of front-loading to beat President Donald Trump's tariffs, and as buyers watched to see how a volatile month in U.S.-China trade ties would play out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-exports-unexpectedly-slide-worst-since-feb-global-trade-pressure-mounts-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NCFVVCUJFLVLBJU3KC5PVYDDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国与乌兹别克斯坦达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，美国和乌兹别克斯坦已达成经贸协议，乌兹别克斯坦计划在未来三年内采购和投资350亿美元，在未来十年内采购和投资超过1000亿美元，用于美国的一些行业。【原文：The United States and Uzbekistan have reached a trade and economic deal, President Donald Trump said on Thursday, stating that Uzbekistan plans to purchase and invest $35 billion in the next three years and more than $100 billion in the next 10 years in some U.S. sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-says-us-uzbekistan-reach-trade-deal-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHOLXPIVXVNGRMPP3PZN7UAHKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应忧虑加重，石油将迎来第二周下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心供应过剩和美国需求放缓，石油价格在连续三天下跌后于周五略有回升，但似乎将迎来第二周的下跌。【原文：Oil edged up on Friday following three days of declines on worries about excess supply and slowing demand in the U.S., though prices appeared to be headed for a second week of losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-heads-second-weekly-loss-supply-concerns-weigh-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PULJJJVRZFIUXCOME54XSAC3B4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，美国将阻止英伟达向中国出售缩小版人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《The Information》周四援引三位熟悉内情的人士的话报道，白宫已通知其他联邦机构，不允许英伟达向中国出售其最新的缩小版人工智能芯片。【原文：The White House has informed other federal agencies that it will not permit Nvidia to sell its latest scaled-down AI chips to China, The Information reported on Thursday, citing three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-block-nvidias-sale-scaled-back-ai-chips-china-information-says-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSSBFFO4QZK3XKWPLDD3QB4IIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:47:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[低迷情绪令科技股周线下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于投资者对人工智能股的涨势感到不安，科技股市场迎来了七个月来最严重的单周跌幅，而债券和日元等更安全的资产则走高。【原文：Tech-heavy stock markets were bracing for their heaviest weekly falls in seven months on Friday as investors have turned uneasy about how far the rally in artificial intelligence stocks has run, while safer assets such as bonds and the yen went higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPALNDD7DBLYZE7RVFW5LUE3VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:37:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克计划建立特斯拉超大型人工智能芯片工厂，并考虑与英特尔建立潜在合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周四表示，特斯拉可能需要建造 "一座巨大的芯片工厂 "来生产人工智能芯片，并公开表示这家电动汽车制造商可以与英特尔合作。【原文：CEO Elon Musk on Thursday said Tesla probably will have to build "a gigantic chip fab" to make artificial intelligence chips and publicly mused the EV maker could work with Intel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-plans-tesla-mega-ai-chip-fab-mulls-potential-intel-partnership-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LB4LPFPWNFIH5AANKSTJQZK7YU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示美国就业市场出现裂痕，美元处于守势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲早盘，美元回落，领跌主要货币，原因是缺乏美国劳动力市场官方数据的投资者抓住了私营部门调查疲软的迹象。【原文：The dollar retreated in early Asia trade on Friday, leading declines among major currencies as investors lacking official data on the U.S. labour market seized upon signs of weakness in private sector surveys.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-defensive-data-show-cracks-us-jobs-market-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FE7X6O7LD5OQDGEVKJXJSORIUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敲定周五开始削减国内航班 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周四以政府停摆期间空中交通管制的安全问题为由，命令航空公司从美国东部时间周五上午6点（格林尼治标准时间11点）开始将40个高流量机场的国内航班运营削减4%。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration on Thursday ordered airlines to cut domestic flight operations by 4% at 40 high-traffic airports starting at 6 a.m. ET (1100 GMT) on Friday, citing safety concerns about air traffic control during the government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-finalizes-domestic-flight-cuts-start-4-friday-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3R742EMWZLZRNIH4OXU7O5RQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈弗分析公司预计美国每周申请失业救济人数温和增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈弗分析公司（Haver Analytics）周四估计，上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数略有增加，表明尽管宣布的裁员人数激增，但10月份劳动力市场状况稳定。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased marginally last week, Haver Analytics estimated on Thursday, pointing to stable labor market conditions in October despite a surge in announced layoffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-moderately-haver-analytics-estimates-2025-11-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUHOZFOZYJJR3EDYQLYDD7PFCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>