<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:08:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:08:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[行业巨变后，中国主动型基金以全新产品蓄势待发]]></title><description><![CDATA[本月公布的中国主动型基金新规将彻底改变中国股市的资金流向，这促使业内一些大公司立即行动起来，推出新产品。【原文：New rules for Chinese active funds unveiled this month that are set to drastically change fund flows in the country's stock markets have prompted immediate action from some of the biggest players in the industry to introduce fresh products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/chinese-active-funds-gear-up-with-fresh-products-after-dramatic-industry-reforms-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPYGN4GCZNJY7MAI66BLC2KEIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的邻国为何希望与特朗普达成货币交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着韩国、台湾和日本的货币升值，有关这些经济体可能在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易谈判中利用汇率重估作为筹码的传言也甚嚣尘上。【原文：As the currencies of South Korea, Taiwan and Japan rise, so too is chatter that these economies could use exchange rate revaluation as a carrot in trade talks with U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/why-chinas-neighbours-may-want-currency-deals-with-trump-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZANQUVMCBICFBZEQCUNT6ERRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉凯恩汽车公司交易后，美国车桥公司计划在伦敦二次上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于底特律的美国车桥与制造公司周五表示，在斥资 14 亿美元收购吉凯恩汽车公司（GKN Automotive）所有者 Dowlais 之后，该公司计划寻求在伦敦进行股票二次上市。【原文：Detroit-based American Axle and Manufacturing said on Friday it plans to seek a secondary listing of its shares in London after its $1.4 billion acquisition of GKN Automotive owner Dowlais .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/american-axle-plans-secondary-london-listing-after-gkn-automotive-deal-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QL7566PISJJGPJVHZWIPRDJIRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行：贸易休战后美国不再可能出现经济衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）在周四晚些时候发布的一份报告中称，鉴于中美贸易紧张局势出现缓和迹象，该行不再预计美国经济将在今年晚些时候陷入衰退，并上调了经济增长预期。【原文：Barclays no longer expects the U.S. economy to slip into a recession later this year and has revised up its growth forecasts, given signs of a de-escalation in U.S.-China trade tensions, the bank said in a note released late Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-recession-no-longer-likely-after-trade-truce-says-barclays-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SE42SGSLNK45D26FTT34CTP2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 4 月份核心通胀率可能升至两年来最快水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于能源补贴减少和食品成本上升，日本 4 月份的核心通胀率可能创下两年来的最快增速，这增加了央行加息的压力。【原文：Japan's April core inflation probably rose at its fastest pace in two years on the reduction of energy subsidies and higher food costs, a Reuters poll showed, adding to pressure on the central bank to raise interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-april-core-inflation-likely-sped-up-fastest-pace-two-years-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYGAFDBQK5LYBMYJO6IZWNJ6KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡地亚珠宝大放异彩，历峰集团销售额增长 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡地亚的所有者历峰集团（Richemont）周五报告称，该集团季度销售额增长了7%，略好于预期，原因是美国富裕的购物者摆脱了经济的不确定性，继续在奢侈珠宝上挥金如土，从而抵消了亚洲需求的疲软。【原文：Cartier owner Richemont on Friday reported a slightly better-than-expected 7% rise in quarterly sales as weaker demand in Asia was offset by brisk business in the United States where wealthy shoppers shrugged off economic uncertainty and continued to splash out on luxury jewellery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cartier-owner-richemont-sales-up-7-jewellery-shines-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXQETUUOMRKFTOLL52YSZ3YZGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾与美国在韩国举行关税会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾副总理郑丽群周五表示，台湾和美国的主要贸易代表在韩国举行了贸易谈判，双方对进一步谈判将导致美国降低对台湾出口产品的关税表示乐观。【原文：The main Taiwan and U.S. trade representatives met in South Korea for trade negotiations, yielding optimism that further talks would lead to reduced U.S. tariffs on Taiwan exports, the island's Vice-Premier Cheng Li-chiun said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-meets-with-us-tariff-talks-south-korea-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAMGKNGROJJORGIHWPXR22T54U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:22:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡航空公司高管表示，最近飞往中国的航班需求有所增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡航空公司首席商务官李力新周五表示，最近几个月进入中国的客流量激增，但出境游仍未恢复到大流行前的水平。【原文：Singapore Airlines has seen a surge in passenger traffic into China in recent months, but outbound travel has still not recovered to pre-pandemic levels, Chief Commercial Officer Lee Lik Hsin said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/demand-flights-china-has-risen-recently-singapore-airlines-exec-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC32NBSLLNO7PBMZ62UFF2B6EY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价贸易推动的本周反弹戛然而止]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5K7BU4YPVJL3ISUJXPK5UNL24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行中村呼吁因美国关税不确定性暂停加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行董事会成员中村丰明（Toyoaki Nakamura）周五表示，央行目前必须暂缓加息，以仔细研究美国提高关税的不确定性会如何影响企业利润、资本支出和工资。【原文：Bank of Japan board member Toyoaki Nakamura said on Friday the central bank must hold off raising interest rates for the time being to scrutinise how uncertainty over higher U.S. tariffs could affect corporate profits, capital expenditure and wages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bojs-nakamura-calls-pause-rate-hikes-us-tariff-uncertainty-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXHMPDQBXJNBHPUHHCHVODFYQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，英伟达计划在上海建立研究中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，英伟达正在寻求在中国建立一个研发中心，该公司的最高负责人黄仁勋在四月份与上海市市长龚正会面时讨论了这一计划。【原文：Nvidia is seeking to build a research and development center in China, and the company's top boss Jensen Huang discussed the plan with Shanghai's mayor Gong Zheng when they met in April, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-plans-shanghai-research-center-ft-reports-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4HXKN44VVJH7DUXYGGD2XEKTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称中国佛山海天将在香港上市融资约 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位直接知情人士透露，中国佛山海天调味食品公司已获得香港联交所批准在港上市，该公司的目标是融资约 10 亿美元。【原文：China's Foshan Haitian Flavouring and Food Company has received approval from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange to list in the city and it aims to raise about $1 billion, according to two sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-foshan-haitian-raise-about-1-billion-hong-kong-listing-sources-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMGKU2UBGNIOZCDL6JC3MBB34Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇率飙升，惠誉下调台湾寿险公司评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评级机构惠誉（Fitch）周四对五家台湾寿险公司进行了评级下调的审查，因为本月台币的大幅飙升给这些公司的资产负债表带来了压力。【原文：Credit ratings agency Fitch on Thursday placed five Taiwanese life insurers under review for potential downgrades after a sharp surge in the Taiwanese dollar this month put stress on their balance sheets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fitch-puts-taiwan-life-insurers-downgrade-watch-after-currency-surge-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FU2MSFG7SZOAZEMZLNVI6LLJUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalWafers 在美国开设新工厂；计划追加 40 亿美元投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾硅晶圆制造商环球晶圆公司（GlobalWafers）周五表示，将在美国追加投资 40 亿美元，以满足美国客户日益增长的需求，同时该公司在得克萨斯州新建的价值 35 亿美元的晶圆厂正式开业。【原文：Taiwanese silicon wafer manufacturer GlobalWafers said on Friday it would invest an additional $4 billion in the United States to meet growing customer demand there, as it officially opened its new $3.5 billion wafer facility in Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/globalwafers-opens-new-us-factory-plans-additional-4-bln-investment-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHXEUA422VMWFMFRYXHGPAEDAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税下调缓解了中国大规模裁员的威胁，但就业市场的痛苦依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国进口关税在 4 月份飙升至三位数，迫使广东一家照明产品工厂和一家鞋类制造商减少产量，中国工人刘胜尊在短短一个月内失去了两份工作。【原文：Chinese worker Liu Shengzun lost two jobs in just one month as U.S. import tariffs shot up to triple digits in April, forcing a Guangdong lighting products factory, and then a footwear maker, to reduce output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/tariff-cuts-ease-mass-china-layoffs-threat-job-market-pain-persists-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJYPBN2I6VMKZD44QIWIM2XMG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普实施 100% 关税计划后，新西兰加强了电影制作激励措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对美国境外制作的电影征收 100%关税之后，新西兰将拨出更多预算资金，为在该国拍摄电影的外国电影公司提供回扣。【原文：New Zealand will allocate more budget funds to give rebates to foreign studios for filming movies in the country - a move which follows U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of 100% tariffs on films made outside the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/new-zealand-boosts-movie-production-incentives-after-trumps-100-tariff-plan-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZIX3NZXVZM43EH7C5N4VXR3XI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:25:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市本周将以疲软态势强势收官，债券则将迎来缓解性反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，随着中美贸易谈判的喜悦逐渐消退，亚洲股市以疲软的走势结束了本周的强劲走势，而对美国宽松政策的押注重燃，引发了跌势乏力的债券市场的反弹。【原文：Asian stocks were ending a strong week on a softer note on Friday as the euphoria over U.S.-China trade talks faded, while revived bets for policy easing in the United States sparked a rally in beaten-down bond markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDGRR4BIPVKQXKHPPNUKIFIQBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国数据向好，美元追随国债收益率走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五与美国国债收益率同步下跌，此前本周美国经济数据意外下行，巩固了美联储今年将进一步降息的预期。【原文：The dollar fell in tandem with U.S. Treasury yields on Friday after downside surprises on U.S. economic data this week cemented bets of more Federal Reserve rate cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-tracks-treasury-yields-lower-benign-us-data-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIFPFAWZXNNFJP2YWAIG5CZ2RM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:50:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易缓和，油价有望实现 1%的周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美中贸易的乐观情绪超过了伊朗供应重返市场的前景，周五油价在前一交易日大幅下跌后上扬，周涨幅超过1%。【原文：Oil prices edged up on Friday following a sharp drop in the previous session, heading for a weekly gain of more than 1% as U.S.-China trade optimism outweighed the prospects of Iranian supply returning to the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-heading-1-weekly-gain-us-china-trade-detente-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2KPZKYST5K6ZHWUECWHYMXJWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Third Point 在提交的文件中详细说明了其在美国钢铁公司和 Kenvue 公司的股份情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者丹尼尔-勒布（Daniel Loeb）的对冲基金Third Point周四详细公布了其在美国钢铁公司和Kenvue公司的持股规模，股东们希望这两家公司不久将因被收购而受益。【原文：Billionaire investor Daniel Loeb's hedge fund Third Point on Thursday detailed the size of its stakes in U.S. Steel and Kenvue , companies that shareholders hope will soon benefit from being bought by someone.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/third-point-details-stakes-us-steel-kenvue-filing-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BBQKD6YLBLLPM6ETCCN7RTNF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:12:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税冲击迫在眉睫，日本经济出现萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，日本经济在 3 月份出现了一年来的首次萎缩，这凸显了日本经济复苏的脆弱性质，目前正受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普贸易政策的威胁。【原文：Japan's economy shrank for the first time in a year in the March quarter, data showed on Friday, underscoring the fragile nature of its recovery now under threat from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-economy-shrinks-us-tariff-hit-looms-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AITFYEREFNOOBNEJWQUILQJJMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 1-3 月经济按年率计算萎缩 0.7]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，日本第一季度经济按年率计算萎缩了0.7%，这凸显了日本脆弱的经济复苏正受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普贸易政策的威胁。【原文：Japan's economy shrank an annualised 0.7% in the first quarter, data showed on Friday, underscoring a fragile recovery now under threat from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-economy-shrinks-annualised-07-jan-march-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6I5MPTBLNFM3JBTXSKB76HMS6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税成为亚太经合组织贸易会议的焦点，联合声明存疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一些外交官称，亚太经济合作组织的贸易会议将于周五落下帷幕，由于在美国关税和世界贸易机构改革问题上存在分歧，会议能否通过一份联合声明尚存疑问。【原文：The Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation's trade gathering comes to a close on Friday with divisions over U.S. tariffs and reforms to the world trade body putting the adoption of a joint statement in doubt, according to some diplomats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-tariffs-take-centre-stage-apec-trade-gathering-joint-statement-doubt-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNK5OWJ22JNPXF7SM3Y5ZFFJKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国文件显示，机构投资者在比特币 ETF 持有量上做文章]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据最近的监管文件显示，由于加密货币价格在2025年第一季度下跌了12%，一些知名资产管理公司削减了他们在现货比特币交易所交易基金中的股份。【原文：A number of high-profile asset managers cut their stakes in spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds amid a 12% drop in the cryptocurrency's price in the first quarter of 2025, according to recent regulatory filings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/institutional-investors-juggle-bitcoin-etf-holdings-us-filings-show-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6UAYRL7SZJYJGNLTMJSRRUWXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 要求法官裁定联邦贸易委员会未能证明其垄断案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Facebook 母公司 Meta Platforms 周四请求华盛顿法官撤销美国联邦贸易委员会指控其非法垄断社交媒体的案件，称该机构未能在有关该公司收购 Instagram 和 WhatsApp 的高风险反垄断审判中证明自己的理由。【原文：Facebook parent company Meta Platforms asked a Washington judge on Thursday to throw out the U.S. Federal Trade Commission's case accusing it of an illegal social media monopoly, saying the agency failed to prove its case at a high-stakes antitrust trial over the company's acquisitions of Instagram and WhatsApp.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-asks-judge-rule-that-ftc-failed-prove-its-monopoly-case-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JHGDLKIZZRINVKZLRKLLGH4YUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为刑事案美国法官质疑特朗普针对律师事务所的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责监督美国起诉中国电信公司华为刑事案件的法官在听证会上说，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的行政命令剥夺了詹纳-布洛克（Jenner & Block）律师事务所律师的安全许可，这可能会成为该公司在此案中辩护的障碍。【原文：The judge overseeing the U.S. criminal case against Chinese telecom Huawei said at a hearing that President Donald Trump's executive order stripping security clearances from lawyers at Jenner & Block could be a hurdle for the company's defense in the case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-huawei-criminal-case-questions-trump-order-against-law-firm-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMQDRTFJ3VJ5DGWBJSKJ2FVU5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:25:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：美国希望将更多中国公司列入 "实体名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引五位知情人士的话报道称，美国商务部正在考虑将包括长鑫存储器（CXMT）在内的更多中国公司列入其 "实体名单"。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department is considering placing more Chinese companies, including ChangXin Memory (CXMT), on its "Entity List," the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing five people familiar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-eyes-placing-more-chinese-companies-entity-list-ft-reports-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4C2SKNGWNLAVNXALTNKYB7I4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局批准修改 SpaceX 星际飞船 9 号飞行任务许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局（FAA）周四表示，已批准修改 SpaceX 星际飞船 9 号（Starship Flight 9）任务的许可证，其中包括允许其将在得克萨斯州博卡奇卡（Boca Chica）的运营次数增加到每年最多 25 次。【原文：The FAA on Thursday said it approved license modifications for the SpaceX Starship Flight 9 mission, including allowing it to increase the number of operations to up to 25 per year at Boca Chica in Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/faa-approves-license-modifications-spacex-starship-flight-9-mission-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QU6N4IQ46VIL5HGC52V6AKWH7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:12:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，拜耳寻求Roundup解决方案，探讨孟山都破产事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，拜耳公司正在寻求解决与其 "Roundup "除草剂有关的诉讼，同时探讨如果和解计划失败，其孟山都公司将面临破产。【原文：Bayer is seeking to resolve lawsuits related to its Roundup weedkiller, while exploring a bankruptcy for its Monsanto unit if the settlement plan fails, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bayer-seeks-roundup-settlement-explores-monsanto-bankruptcy-wsj-reports-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLF5WAI7LJJPHHVMX73IMIDECY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称巴西食品公司 Marfrig 和 BRF 将合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位不愿透露姓名的知情人士告诉路透社记者，巴西食品公司 Marfrig 和 BRF 预计将于今晚宣布合并，其中涉及股权交换，因为该交易尚未公开。【原文：Brazilian food companies Marfrig and BRF are expected to announce a merger involving a share swap this evening, a source briefed on the matter told Reuters on condition of anonymity because the deal has not been made public yet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/brazil-food-companies-marfrig-brf-merge-says-source-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQ55YMGPPNPQDFHYJ7UC2V3KDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:22:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>