<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:46:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:46:12 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国买家以最高价抢购西班牙房产]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的数据显示，在去年所有外国买家中，腰缠万贯的美国公民为西班牙房产支付了最高的价格，同时在中部和北部一些地区购买了最多的房产，这加剧了该国的住房危机。【原文：Deep-pocketed U.S. citizens paid the highest prices for Spanish property of all foreign buyers last year, while making the most purchases in some central and northern regions, data showed on Thursday, exacerbating a housing crisis in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-buyers-pay-highest-prices-snap-up-spanish-property-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DA6OXQJ2BVNL5JFTY3W43ZNJGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息称新加坡 SC Capital 正在洽谈收购英国数据中心集团 Global Switch]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，总部位于新加坡的房地产投资管理公司 SC Capital Partners 已成为英国数据中心集团 Global Switch 的潜在竞购者。【原文：Singapore-headquartered real estate investment manager SC Capital Partners has emerged as a potential bidder for British data centre group Global Switch, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/singapores-sc-capital-talks-buy-british-data-centre-group-global-switch-sources-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U5UZSCF3ZPXJLAO6B6B67QUXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:41:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月份消费者价格意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者价格在 3 月份意外下降，但在唐纳德-特朗普总统在降低对其他国家的关税的同时加倍征收进口中国商品的关税之后，通胀风险向好的方向倾斜。【原文：U.S. consumer prices unexpectedly fell in March, but inflation risks are tilted to the upside after President Donald Trump doubled down on tariffs on imported Chinese goods even as he lowered duties on other nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-prices-unexpectedly-fall-march-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OT5FBMITHBJZBBXVKMA4JBDMZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税激怒市场，2025 年石油价格接近股票价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球石油基准布伦特原油与美国股票之间的正相关性在 2025 年再次出现，反映了人们对经济放缓和美国总统唐纳德-特朗普贸易战影响的担忧。【原文：A positive correlation between global oil benchmark Brent crude and U.S. equities has reemerged in 2025, reflecting concern about the slowing economy and the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's trade wars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-moves-closer-stocks-2025-trump-tariffs-roil-markets-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NV72XEDO2NNZFMPSBIJD63SR3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利普拉达同意收购时装竞争对手范思哲]]></title><description><![CDATA[普拉达（Prada）已达成协议，将从卡普里控股公司（Capri Holdings）手中收购规模较小的竞争对手范思哲（Versace），从而将意大利时尚界的两大巨头联合起来。普拉达周四表示，该交易的企业价值为 13.75 亿美元。【原文：Prada has struck a deal to buy smaller rival Versace from Capri Holdings in a move to unite two of the biggest names in Italian fashion. The deal has an enterprise value of $1.375 billion, Prada said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/italys-prada-agrees-buy-fashion-rival-versace-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KI3KLF2LUVPHLHFUURI7KFOPZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:32:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫哈塞特称美国接近与贸易伙伴达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周四表示，美国正在考虑15个国家提出的关税协议，并接近与其中一些国家达成协议。【原文：The United States is considering offers from 15 countries on tariff agreements and is close to deals with some of them, White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said on Thursday after President Donald Trumplowered some of the duties in a stunning reversal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-close-trade-deals-with-trading-partners-white-houses-hassett-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GPFJKZKRRJ2HFZH7HU6K3MYSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:27:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，宝洁公司与可口可乐装瓶商一起成为欧盟反垄断调查的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四援引知情人士的话报道，汰渍洗涤剂生产商宝洁公司已被确定为欧盟反垄断监管机构上月启动的调查对象，该调查还针对可口可乐装瓶商。【原文：Tide detergent maker Procter & Gamble has been identified as the subject of an EU antitrust regulators' investigation initiated last month that had also targeted Coca-Cola bottlers, Bloomberg reported on Thursday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/procter-gamble-was-target-eu-antitrust-probe-alongside-coca-cola-bottlers-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OJWVPIWIRJS5CW3IITFI5PZWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[二手车零售商 CarMax 第四季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[二手车零售商 CarMax 周四公布的第四季度利润不及华尔街预期，原因是较高的借贷成本使一些消费者不敢购买大件商品。【原文：Used-car retailer CarMax on Thursday reported a fourth-quarter profit that missed Wall Street estimates, as higher borrowing costs kept some consumers from making big ticket purchases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/used-car-retailer-carmax-misses-fourth-quarter-profit-expectations-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIEIKNU34BI4LPR5HPFAT666HE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球首个仿人机器人半程马拉松赛因大风天气推迟举行]]></title><description><![CDATA[北京推迟了原定于周日举行的半程马拉松比赛，在这场比赛中，仿人机器人将与人类选手并肩作战，这是一场里程碑式的比赛，旨在展示中国在前沿产业领域取得的进步。【原文：Beijing has postponed a half marathon originally scheduled for Sunday in which humanoid robots will race alongside human runners, a milestone designed to showcase China's advances in a frontier industry the country is intent on dominating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/worlds-first-humanoid-robot-half-marathon-postponed-due-windy-weather-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZZA2OBED5KDHOGNILENXDRE5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银股东以 90% 的选票再次选举科尔姆-凯莱赫为主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银股东周四以 90% 的选票再次选举科尔姆-凯莱赫（Colm Kelleher）为主席，而 2024 年的得票率为 96%。【原文：UBS shareholders on Thursday reelected Chairman Colm Kelleher with 90% of votes, compared to 96% of votes in 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-shareholders-reelect-chairman-colm-kelleher-with-90-votes-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPCSUU2TSVPIJLCDTFU3M4EIBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:31:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构称可能接受 SLB 和 ChampionX 提出的补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构周四表示，可能会接受油田服务公司 SLB 和规模较小的竞争对手 ChampionX 提出的措施，以解决两家公司拟议的 80 亿美元交易中的反垄断问题。【原文：Britain's competition regulator said on Thursday it might accept the measures offered by oilfield services firm SLB and smaller rival ChampionX to address antitrust concerns regarding the two companies' proposed $8 billion deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/uk-watchdog-says-it-might-accept-remedial-measures-offered-by-slb-championx-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2BMCAMP35JU7IQGKDACK6REQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:18:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标再猜测九十天]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKM36VIZSNLBJNCRWXCAQPB7B4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:15:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊首席执行官在年度股东信中阐述人工智能投资使命]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊首席执行官安迪-贾西（Andy Jassy）周四为公司数十亿美元的人工智能开发支出进行了辩解，称这项投资是保持竞争力所必需的。【原文：Amazon chief executive Andy Jassy on Thursday justified the company's billions of dollars in outlays for artificial intelligence development, saying the investment was necessary to remain competitive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-ceo-sets-out-ai-investment-mission-annual-shareholder-letter-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3SUC5HVRFM7JJREG222CNUISQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 的季度销售额因优惠和折扣而猛增]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，电动汽车制造商 Polestar 的第一季度销售额猛增 76%，原因是折扣和优惠帮助抵消了激烈的竞争和不确定的经济前景。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Polestar's first-quarter sales jumped 76% on Thursday as discounts and offers helped offset stiff competition and an uncertain economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestars-quarterly-sales-jump-offers-discounts-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5QTJDPZSBLSHNAFOWQCLCXJFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意法半导体寻求就投资和就业水平向意大利作出保证]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商意法半导体（STMicroelectronics）周四向意大利保证其对意大利的承诺，因为罗马政府向该公司首席执行官施加了辞职压力。【原文：Chipmaker STMicroelectronics moved on Thursday to reassure Italy of its commitment to the country as the Rome government puts pressure on the company's chief executive to quit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/stmicro-seeks-reassure-italy-over-investment-job-levels-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PEB355L5ROELF7OFOG33LMB2M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银股东以 86.7% 的票数支持 2024 年薪酬报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周四的咨询投票中，瑞银股东以 86.7% 的票数支持该行 2024 年的薪酬报告，而去年同期的支持率为 83.5%。【原文：In an advisory vote, UBS shareholders on Thursday backed the bank's 2024 compensation report with 86.7% of votes, compared to 83.5% for the same report a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-shareholders-back-2024-compensation-report-with-867-votes-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTQXI4XYW5I7JL23TZIX3ZW6OU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国国债市场刚刚发生了什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[一周前，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）决定暂停他曾表示要对数十个国家征收的巨额关税，随后金融市场出现动荡，包括 29 万亿美元的国债市场急剧下挫。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to pause the hefty duties he had said he would impose on dozens of countries one week ago followed turmoil in financial markets that included an acute selloff in the $29 trillion Treasury market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/what-just-happened-us-treasury-market-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YASG4ZPU3ZJOVHSQLGOP44WJP4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:08:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔首席执行官陈立武在中国的广泛投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔首席执行官陈立武数十年来通过他于 1987 年在旧金山创立的风险投资公司华登国际和两家香港控股公司，对中国公司进行了数百次投资。【原文：Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan has made hundreds of investments in Chinese companies over decades through Walden International, the San Francisco venture capital firm he founded in 1987, and two Hong Kong-based holding companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-ceo-lip-bu-tans-wide-ranging-investments-china-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFOGG36J35ITBL7YT24V6LPSEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行称关税不确定性下决定利率路径为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚最高央行行长周四表示，现在决定利率路径还为时过早，并补充说在评估美国贸易政策对经济的影响时需要保持耐心，因为这些政策已经颠覆了金融市场。【原文：Australia's top central banker said on Thursday that it was still too early to decide on the path for interest rates, adding it needed to be patient as it assesses the economic impact of U.S. trade policies that have upended financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-says-too-early-decide-rate-path-amid-tariff-uncertainty-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTA7Q77KGFPA5FHE4ITBHTJQOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：华尔街对关税冲击的反应：客户来电和奖金担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布征收最新关税后，市场暴跌，花旗集团银行业主管维斯瓦斯-拉加万（Viswas Raghavan）周一召集全球高级银行家开会，让他们与客户通电话。【原文：With markets crashing after U.S. President Donald Trump announced his latest tariffs, Citigroup’s banking head Viswas Raghavan called a global meeting of senior bankers on Monday and told them to get on the phone with their clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-streets-response-tariff-shock-client-calls-bonus-worries-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBL4EMURTJJRHHPTSSIYQG2HB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察：英特尔首席执行官投资了数百家中国公司，其中一些与军事有关]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社对中国和美国公司文件的审查，被选中领导美国最大芯片制造商英特尔的陈立武投资了数百家中国科技公司，其中至少有八家与中国人民解放军有关联。【原文：Lip-Bu Tan, the man chosen to lead Intel, the U.S.'s largest chip maker, has invested in hundreds of Chinese tech firms, including at least eight with links to the People's Liberation Army, according to a Reuters review of Chinese and U.S. corporate filings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-ceo-invested-hundreds-chinese-companies-some-with-military-ties-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDPWHDPJSROQTDNMWPJA6HQ5LY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪拜的 Mashreq 公司将与高盛集团合作，为富裕客户提供服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于迪拜的 Mashreq 公司与高盛资产管理公司（Goldman Sachs Asset Management）建立了合作伙伴关系，以提供全权委托投资服务，满足海湾地区对专业管理投资组合日益增长的需求。【原文：Dubai-based Mashreq has entered a partnership with Goldman Sachs Asset Management to offer discretionary investment services and tap growing demand for professionally managed portfolios in the Gulf.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dubais-mashreq-work-with-goldman-sachs-cater-rich-clients-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SXMMWKQWRNL7MZXVHBPBG3KVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场反弹，全球信用违约利差收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲和亚洲主权债务和企业债务违约保险成本下降，原因是美国暂停征收部分最重关税，令投资者松了一口气。【原文：The cost of insuring against sovereign and corporate defaults on European and Asian debt fell on Thursday as investors breathed a sigh of relief at a pause on some of the heaviest U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-tariffs-credit-update-1-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6R5XLWO7GRLQJBCBFPCUGCQPLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴里-卡乐宝将扩大美国生产规模以应对 "破坏性环境]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士巧克力制造商巴里-卡乐堡（Barry Callebaut）首席执行官周四表示，该公司正计划增加在美国的生产，以抵御北美 "破坏性环境 "的影响，并贴近客户。【原文：Barry Callebaut is planning to increase its U.S.-based production to fend off effects of the "disruptive environment" in North America and stay close to its customers, the Swiss chocolate maker's chief executive said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/barry-callebaut-scale-up-us-production-cope-with-disruptive-environment-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBRYD4F3MNIEJBXAU3TNA6L2O4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因特朗普关税逆转而大幅反弹后期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）暂时降低对数十个国家征收的高额关税，同时提高对中国的征税，在引发了令人瞠目的涨势一天之后，美国股指期货周四下跌。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Thursday, a day after an eye-watering rally set off by U.S. President Donald Trump's move to temporarily lower the heavy tariffs on dozens of countries, while raising the levies on China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-fall-after-sharp-rally-trump-tariff-reversal-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4K3FJBUMNRMWZPLQLFFGWDYDHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰副总理表示，美国和乌克兰将于周五就矿产交易展开会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰副总理奥尔哈-斯特凡尼希娜（Olha Stefanishyna）周四表示，美国和乌克兰将于周五在华盛顿就矿产交易展开技术磋商，磋商不会干扰基辅的其他财政承诺。【原文：Technical consultations between the U.S. and Ukraine on a minerals deal will begin in Washington on Friday and will not interfere with Kyiv's other financial commitments, Ukrainian Deputy Prime Minister Olha Stefanishyna said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/technical-talks-between-us-ukraine-minerals-deal-start-friday-interfax-ukraine-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33BESVORINOX5B2A26GTDNYJOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌部署人工智能，加快美国最大电网 PJM 的连接速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet Inc.旗下的谷歌公司（Google）周四表示，该公司正在与北美最大的电网运营商PJM互联公司（PJM Interconnection）合作，推出人工智能技术，旨在更快地连接新的电力供应。【原文：Alphabet Inc's Google unit is partnering with the largest electrical grid operator in North America, PJM Interconnection, to roll out artificial intelligence technologies aimed at getting new power supplies connected faster, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-deploys-ai-speed-up-connections-pjm-largest-us-power-grid-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NDAMA5E45OPRBNYOTJBACC7HA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:06:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马第一季度电池电动汽车交付量猛增三分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商宝马公司周四表示，今年第一季度的电池电动汽车销量增加了约三分之一。【原文：German carmaker BMW said on Thursday that it sold around a third more battery electric vehicles in the first quarter of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-q1-battery-electric-vehicle-deliveries-jump-by-third-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BMLVEE3PRMNFH3D2RUNNYYTS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普不断升级的关税有可能逆转美国的进口热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易高管们表示，3月份美国集装箱进口同比增长11%，延续了今年以来的月度超高增幅，但美国总统唐纳德-特朗普不断升级的关税正在使今年晚些时候的前景变得暗淡。【原文：U.S. container imports rose 11% year over year in March, continuing this year's outsized monthly gains, but U.S. President Donald Trump's escalating tariffs are dimming the outlook for later this year, trade executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-escalating-tariffs-threaten-reverse-us-import-boom-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQ2VDJFHBJLZTH4DK2UXPDRITM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:03:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，苹果从印度空运 600 吨 iPhone "以抵御 "特朗普关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，科技巨头苹果公司在印度加强生产以抵御美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税之后，包租货运航班从印度向美国运送 600 吨或多达 150 万部 iPhone。【原文：Tech giant Apple chartered cargo flights to ferry 600 tons of iPhones, or as many as 1.5 million, to the United States from India, after it stepped up production there in an effort to beat President Donald Trump's tariffs, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-airlifts-600-tons-iphones-india-to-beat-trump-tariffs-sources-say-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UOHUUU2QDFMCJLXTNHYC3FKYOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 08:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>