<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 05:45:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 05:45:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银支付 3 亿美元解决美国抵押贷款证券案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团周一表示，将支付 3 亿美元，以了结与瑞士信贷在美国误售抵押贷款挂钩投资相关的未偿债务。【原文：UBS on Monday said it will pay $300 million to settle outstanding obligations related to the misselling of mortgage-linked investments by Credit Suisse in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-pay-300-million-resolve-us-mortgage-securities-cases-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUOHJTIOTNPMNJ3YXNUHRL6V6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 05:36:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[超过 3,000 名波音战斗机工人拒绝合同提议后举行罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[在圣路易斯地区和伊利诺伊州组装波音战斗机的3200多名工会成员在前一天拒绝了第二次合同提议后，于周一举行了罢工。【原文：More than 3,200 union members who assemble Boeing's fighter jets in the St. Louis area and Illinois went on strike on Monday after rejecting a second contract offer the previous day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/over-3000-boeing-fighter-jet-workers-go-strike-after-rejecting-contract-offer-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAYUL5DSJVKRFDBZ7DPF3ZJGIE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 05:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国移动以 1.38 亿美元收购香港宽频逾 14% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[按用户计算，全球最大的无线运营商中国移动周一表示，它已以 10.8 亿港元（1.3758 亿美元）的价格收购了香港宽带服务提供商香港宽频 14.4% 的股份。【原文：China Mobile , the world's biggest wireless carrier by users, said on Monday it had bought a 14.4% stake in Hong Kong-based broadband service provider HKBN for HK$1.08 billion ($137.58 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/china-mobile-buys-over-14-stake-hkbn-138-million-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YRHZOEJXNOQ7LLAHJUH52E2JE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价买入跌势，就业问题稍后再说]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJDOXN65VZM55EJWB6DQXQQTTA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行上调未来 3 个月黄金预期至 3,500 美元/盎司，因美国前景不容乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行周一将未来三个月的金价预期从每盎司3300美元上调至3500美元，预期交易区间从3100美元至3500美元上调至3300美元至3600美元，原因是认为近期美国经济增长和通胀前景已经恶化。【原文：Citi raised its gold price forecast over next three months to $3,500 per ounce on Monday from $3,300, and the expected trading range to $3,300–$3,600 from $3,100–$3,500, on the belief that near-term U.S. growth and inflation outlook has deteriorated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/citi-raises-gold-forecast-3500oz-over-next-3-months-negative-us-outlook-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZRQ7GMCI5JDZMNL47NOV4AZLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:22:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾通过夏令营和大学课程培养年轻的海外芯片人才]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nicolas Chueh 穿着白色防护服，戴着口罩，聚精会神地听导游介绍用于制造台湾尖端半导体的一系列银色机器。【原文：Dressed in a white protective suit and face mask, Nicolas Chueh listened intently as a guide introduced a series of silver machines used in manufacturing Taiwan's cutting-edge semiconductors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-cultivates-young-overseas-chip-talent-with-summer-camps-university-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7F65GW2PFMQVDVCSGQFLUPX2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国工业部长仍担心美国关税对出口商的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国工业部长周一表示，通过达成美国关税协议，韩国成功避免了最坏情况的发生，但出口商的盈利能力将如何受到15%关税率的影响仍令人担忧。【原文：South Korea's industry minister said on Monday that the country managed to avoid the worst-case scenario by clinching a U.S. tariff deal, but concerns remained over how the profitability of exporters would be affected by a 15% tariff rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-industry-minister-still-concerned-about-us-tariff-impact-exporters-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SHOFJHWW5NJXJMDACDLULYYCM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 03:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛维持布伦特原油预期，但指出需求面临下行风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）周日重申了其油价预测，即 2025 年第四季度布伦特平均油价为每桶 64 美元，2026 年为 56 美元，但预计近期的事态发展将对其基线估计造成越来越大的风险。【原文：Goldman Sachs on Sunday reiterated its oil price forecast with Brent averaging $64 per barrel in the fourth quarter of 2025 and $56 in 2026, but expects an increasing range of risks to its baseline estimates from recent developments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/goldman-keeps-brent-oil-forecast-flags-downside-risks-demand-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RJLSVWQOZOAVM6T4RAIEJCGV4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：老树和农民老龄化使顶级棕榈油出口国的前景恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚农民苏拉特曼-莫斯曼（Suratmen Mosman）面临的困境是，未来五年内，世界顶级棕榈油出口国的棕榈油供应有可能减少，全球数十亿消费者必不可少的植物油价格也有可能上涨。【原文：Malaysian farmer Suratmen Mosman faces a dilemma that threatens to sap supply from the world's top palm oil exporters and drive up prices of the vegetable oil essential to billions of consumers worldwide in the next five years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/old-trees-ageing-farmers-worsen-outlook-top-palm-oil-exporters-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2PVJTLMSRIIVKWYABF4UHDG4Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者关注美联储即将减息，美元在暴跌后企稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，在一份令人沮丧的美国就业报告和唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇一名高级劳工官员的消息震惊了投资者，并导致他们加大了对美联储即将降息的押注之后，美元小幅走高。【原文：A battered dollar edged marginally higher on Monday after a dismal U.S. jobs report and President Donald Trump's firing of a top labour official stunned investors and led them to ramp up bets of imminent Federal Reserve rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/dollar-steadies-after-tumble-investors-eye-imminent-fed-cuts-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JSYBDUZABO53GVEOHB5GSHPHE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:52:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市受美国经济忧虑影响，石油价格下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对美国经济的担忧卷土重来，亚洲股市周一跟随华尔街走低，刺激投资者对几乎确定的 9 月份降息进行定价，并削弱了美元的走势。【原文：Asian share markets followed Wall Street lower on Monday as fears for the U.S. economy returned with a vengeance, spurring investors to price in an almost certain rate cut for September and undermining the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKT4WHIOXVNHZB44TOXL3WTNYU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:40:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在伊拉克的独立石油公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[少数几家独立的中国石油公司正大举进军伊拉克，计划开展数十亿美元的项目来开发伊拉克的巨大储量，向在欧佩克第二大产油国中占据主导地位的全球和北京支持的国有大型石油公司发起挑战。【原文：A handful of independent Chinese oil companies are piling into Iraq, planning multi-billion-dollar projects to develop its vast reserves in a challenge to global and Beijing-backed state majors that dominate output in OPEC's number two producer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinese-independent-oil-companies-iraq-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJGBHVGE6ROENH4VFU35VG3TKQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 23:06:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国独立石油公司进军伊拉克石油巨头主导的市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的独立石油公司正在加强在伊拉克的业务，向欧佩克第二大产油国伊拉克投资数十亿美元，尽管一些全球大型石油公司已经从中国大型国有企业主导的市场中撤出。【原文：China's independent oil companies are ramping up operations in Iraq, investing billions of dollars in OPEC's number two producer even as some global majors have scaled back from a market dominated by Beijing's big state-run firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-independent-oil-firms-elbow-into-iraqs-majors-dominated-market-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKAUW47LBZPNPBKKWJN7I74XR4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 23:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚博思格引领全球钢铁巨头争夺古普塔 Whyalla 工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚博思格钢铁公司（BlueScope Steel）周一表示，在当地政府正式启动出售程序一个多月后，该公司已组建了一个由全球钢铁制造商组成的重量级财团，竞购桑吉夫-古普塔（Sanjeev Gupta）陷入困境的怀亚拉钢铁厂（Whyalla Steelworks）。【原文：Australia's BlueScope Steel said on Monday it has assembled a heavyweight consortium of global steelmakers to bid for Sanjeev Gupta's troubled Whyalla Steelworks, over a month after the local government formally opened a sale process.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-bluescope-leads-global-steel-giants-push-guptas-whyalla-plant-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNZG7RUMGVONDD4BP6AJ3CUSNI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 22:55:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+同意在九月份提高产量后石油价格下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一亚市早盘，油价在欧佩克+同意9月份再次大幅增产后下滑。【原文：Oil prices slipped in early Asian trade on Monday after OPEC+ agreed to another large production hike in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-slips-after-opec-agrees-hike-output-september-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMR6JHXQA5NS7HJPKN4INWH5IQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 22:40:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司圣路易斯工会工人拒绝最新报价，将于周一罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际机械师和航空航天工人协会（International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers）工会表示，在圣路易斯地区组装波音战斗机的工会工人周日拒绝了波音公司的最新报价，并将于周一午夜举行罢工。【原文：Unionized workers who assemble Boeing's fighter jets in the St. Louis area rejected Boeing's latest offer on Sunday and will strike at midnight on Monday, the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers union said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/boeings-st-louis-union-workers-reject-latest-offer-will-strike-monday-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWNNYXSMWBPIDEX7MPFVX4YBPM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 17:51:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士商业部长表示，瑞士可能修改对特朗普关税的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士商业部长居伊-帕梅林（Guy Parmelin）表示，瑞士政府愿意修改对美国的报价，以应对美国计划征收的高额关税。【原文：The Swiss government is open to revising its offer to the United States in response to planned heavy tariffs, Business Minister Guy Parmelin said, as experts warned the 39% import duties announced by President Donald Trump could trigger a recession in Switzerland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/switzerland-could-revise-offer-trump-tariffs-business-minister-says-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OABJKNRCTVN7LIUNQLMNS5LINY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，铁路客户敦促监管机构阻止联合太平洋公司与诺福克南方公司的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周日报道，美国铁路客户团体要求监管机构阻止联合太平洋公司（Union Pacific）和诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern）的拟议合并，或对合并提出苛刻条件。【原文：U.S. railroad customer groups have demanded regulators block or put onerous conditions on the proposed merger of Union Pacific and Norfolk Southern , the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/rail-customers-urge-regulators-block-union-pacific-norfolk-southern-deal-ft-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2YZXEMWIFOBZNILTA7QTCGAZQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫官员为解雇劳工官员辩护，批评者警告信任受损]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫高级经济顾问周日为唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇劳工统计局局长一事进行了辩护，回击了有关特朗普此举可能会削弱人们对美国官方经济数据的信心的批评。【原文：Top White House economic advisers on Sunday defended President Donald Trump's firing of the head of the Bureau of Labor Statistics, pushing back against criticism that Trump's action could undermine confidence in official U.S. economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-officials-defend-firing-labor-official-critics-warn-trust-erosion-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWQMRI3XOZOG3IR2BDLKY2ML4M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大官员称，特朗普和卡尼将在未来几天发表讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位加拿大官员周日表示，在美国对美墨加贸协定未涵盖的商品征收35%的关税后，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和加拿大总理马克-卡尼可能将在 "未来几天 "进行会谈。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump and Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney will likely talk "over the next number of days" after the U.S. imposed a 35% tariff on goods not covered by the U.S.-Mexico-Canada trade agreement, a Canadian official said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-carney-speak-coming-days-canadian-official-says-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOENNYHKCNMJNFPHTWLBY4AJNY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税后，中国欢迎 183 家巴西咖啡销售商]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国驻巴西大使馆周六在社交媒体上发布的消息，中国已批准183家新的巴西咖啡公司向中国市场出口产品。【原文：China has approved 183 new Brazilian coffee companies to export products to the Chinese market, according to a social media post of the Chinese embassy in Brazil on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-welcomes-183-brazil-coffee-sellers-wake-us-tariffs-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UCK2CBJ2VKUJHVZXY2LX65BFY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:45:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高级谈判代表称特朗普最新关税政策不可能让步]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周日表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普上周对数十个国家征收的关税很可能会继续执行，而不会作为持续谈判的一部分被削减。【原文：The tariffs U.S. President Donald Trump imposed last week on scores of countries are likely to stay in place rather than be cut as part of continuing negotiations, Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/latest-trump-tariffs-unlikely-budge-top-negotiator-says-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBE622RUWVP7BHYNUVZ2QMSK2Y</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 13:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称欧佩克+原则上同意再次大幅提高石油产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+组织的两位消息人士周日称，欧佩克+组织原则上同意将9月份的石油日产量提高54.8万桶，因为该组织即将完成其最大一批减产计划，人们担心俄罗斯会进一步中断供应。【原文：OPEC+ agreed in principle to boost oil output by 548,000 barrels per day in September, two OPEC+ sources said on Sunday as the group finishes unwinding its biggest tranche of production cuts amid fears of further supply disruptions from Russia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-agrees-principle-another-large-oil-output-hike-sources-say-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YQZ63QO2JMPPMEB6TRMLCETJ4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 06:29:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 BRF 小股东支持 Marfrig 交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周六的一份证券文件显示，巴西家禽和猪肉加工商 BRF 的多数小股东已经批准了与牛肉加工商 Marfrig 的合作建议。【原文：The majority of minority shareholders of Brazilian poultry and pork processor BRF have approved a proposed tie-up with beefpacker Marfrig , according to a securities filing on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/brazils-brf-minority-shareholders-back-marfrig-deal-2025-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPLKQIAKJFPZVAQMXEDYCJ42GA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 01:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利 Codelco 公司向被困 El Teniente 矿工伸出援手]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利铜矿商 Codelco 周六表示，该公司已清理了超过五分之一被堵塞的地下通道，以便与旗舰矿山 El Teniente 的被困工人取得联系，但尚未与他们取得联系。【原文：Chilean copper miner Codelco said on Saturday it has cleared just over a fifth of the blocked underground tunnels needed to reach trapped workers at its flagship El Teniente mine, but has not yet made contact with them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chiles-codelco-makes-headway-reach-trapped-el-teniente-miners-2025-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NG7HUY43RRJNRNACYOAUFTVU44</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 18:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Azul 公司获得 6.5 亿美元投资承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Azul 航空公司周五晚些时候提交的一份证券文件显示，该公司与某些利益相关方签署了一项协议，将在未来的资本化交易中投资 6.5 亿美元。【原文：Brazilian airline Azul said it signed an agreement with certain stakeholders for a $650 million investment in a future capitalization deal, according to a late Friday securities filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-azul-secures-650-million-investment-commitment-2025-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36OBIM2OP5OHTDP3NGFBQWM6HM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 13:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税打击伯克希尔消费品业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔哈撒韦公司拥有 Fruit of the Loom、Jazwares 和 Brooks Sports。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway owns Fruit of the Loom, Jazwares and Brooks Sports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-hit-buffetts-berkshire-consumer-goods-businesses-2025-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RVWRHIVPNFI27LDF7SQYXDLKVE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 13:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔对卡夫亨氏进行减记，营业利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周六减记了对卡夫亨氏公司（Kraft Heinz）的部分投资，并报告称，由于保险承销保费下降，第二季度营业利润下降了 4%。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway on Saturday wrote down part of its investment in Kraft Heinz , and reported a 4% decline in second-quarter operating profit as premiums from insurance underwriting fell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/berkshire-takes-kraft-heinz-writedown-operating-profit-falls-2025-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLVVAZ6XCBJ4ZIBQTBDFKD3JRE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 12:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》报道：尽管特朗普发出威胁，印度仍将购买俄罗斯石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周六报道，印度官员表示，尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要实施惩罚，但他们仍将继续从俄罗斯购买石油。【原文：Indian officials have said they would keep purchasing oil from Russia despite the threat of penalties that U.S. President Donald Trump said he would impose, the New York Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/india-will-buy-russian-oil-despite-trumps-threats-nyt-reports-2025-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y25RAXSMIJLJJL4RDFKDOIH2BE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:42:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[起亚美国召回201,149辆Telluride汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周六表示，起亚美国公司已在美国召回约201,149辆Telluride汽车，原因是车门皮带成型饰条可能会脱层并从车辆上脱落。【原文：Kia America has recalled about 201,149 Telluride vehicles in the U.S. as the door belt molding trim can delaminate and detach from the vehicle, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/kia-america-recalls-201149-us-telluride-vehicles-2025-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7VPH46QFFKUFGW7QOS5ZAQRQE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>