<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:04:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:04:34 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰部分电子支付系统中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[据乌克兰官员和路透社的目击者称，乌克兰邮局、餐馆和地铁系统的电子支付系统在周六早些时候已经失灵。【原文：Electronic payments systems in post offices, restaurants and the metro system were out of action in Ukraine early on Saturday, according to officials and Reuters witnesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/some-electronic-payments-systems-ukraine-disrupted-2025-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUUKJTT5CBKYTCBG37LRRURGZ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 07:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国的竞争中，中国国家主席习近平呼吁自给自足地发展人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家媒体周六报道，中国国家主席习近平承诺 "自力更生、自强不息"，在中国发展人工智能，因为中国正与美国争夺人工智能这一关键战略领域的霸主地位。【原文：China's President Xi Jinping pledged "self-reliance and self-strengthening" to develop AI in China, state media reported on Saturday, as the country vies with the U.S. for supremacy in artificial intelligence, a key strategic area.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-xi-calls-self-sufficiency-ai-development-amid-us-rivalry-2025-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RCHJGPJUZOAZPVOUUB7LH7OY4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 04:21:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产将终止武汉工厂的汽车生产-读卖新闻]]></title><description><![CDATA[读卖新闻》援引未透露姓名的消息来源报道称，日产汽车将在截至 2026 年 3 月 31 日的本营业年度内停止在中国武汉工厂的汽车生产。【原文：Nissan Motor will end vehicle production at its Wuhan plant in China during the current business year which ends March 31, 2026, the Yomiuri newspaper reported citing sources it did not identify.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-end-vehicle-production-wuhan-plant-yomiuri-2025-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MKP43ZKYBKNHEZ4RT23JSJ63E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，埃隆-马斯克的 XAI 控股公司正在洽谈向投资者融资 200 亿美元事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的XAI控股公司正在与投资者谈判，为其新合并的人工智能初创公司和社交媒体业务筹集约200亿美元资金。【原文：Elon Musk's XAI Holdings is in talks with investors to raise roughly $20 billion in funding for his newly combined artificial intelligence startup and social media business, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/elon-musks-xai-holdings-talks-raise-20-billion-investors-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6E5HWNXYZL4HGQXDQ3ZRAONTQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 01:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合利华称未要求 Ben & Jerry's 首席执行官下台，敦促驳回诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华（Unilever）周五驳斥了其试图以支持公司的进步社会活动为由赶走 Ben & Jerry's 前首席执行官戴夫-斯蒂弗（Dave Stever）的说法，称联合利华为他提供了更大的职位和更高的薪酬，但他选择了辞职。【原文：Unilever on Friday rejected the claim it tried to oust former Ben & Jerry's chief executive Dave Stever for supporting his company's progressive social activism, saying it offered him a bigger role and more pay but he chose to resign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/unilever-says-it-didnt-seek-ben-jerrys-ceo-ouster-urges-lawsuit-be-dismissed-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2CEI2TF6FJ5BDUHM67CADTBJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和欧盟尚未就关税问题达成协议--欧盟官员东布罗夫斯基斯]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟经济专员瓦尔蒂斯-东布罗夫斯基斯（Valdis Dombrovskis）周五表示，美国和欧盟仍需做大量工作才能达成一项协议，防止对彼此的商品征收关税。【原文：The United States and the European Union still need a lot of work to reach a deal that would prevent the imposition of tariffs on each other's goods, EU Economic Commissioner Valdis Dombrovskis said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-eu-not-close-deal-tariffs-eus-dombrovskis-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SS5IMQAPVJOJDD7OZU2TBSMVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 22:57:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[勒布的 Third Point 公司增持创可贴制造商 Kenvue 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者丹尼尔-勒布（Daniel Loeb）的对冲基金Third Point正在增持Kenvue的股份，熟悉此事的消息人士周五透露，一些投资者正在推动这家消费保健公司进行战略调整。【原文：Billionaire investor Daniel Loeb's hedge fund Third Point is building a stake in Kenvue , sources familiar with the matter said on Friday, as some investors are pushing for strategic changes at the consumer healthcare company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/loebs-third-point-builds-stake-band-aid-maker-kenvue-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WCQFH6QERNWFPNGL7NCRVRHUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 22:16:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行首席经济学家就新兴市场债务问题敲响警钟，敦促实现自由化]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行首席经济学家英德米特-吉尔（Indermit Gill）表示，贸易不确定性的激增加剧了新兴市场和发展中国家面临的债务上升和增长疲软问题，但削减本国关税可能会带来巨大的推动力。【原文：Spiking trade uncertainty is compounding rising debt and sluggish growth problems facing emerging markets and developing countries, but cutting their own tariffs could provide a big boost, said Indermit Gill, the World Bank's chief economist.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/world-bank-chief-economist-sounds-alarm-emerging-market-debt-issues-urges-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTIMUAL2AFJWRDKP7EXM5KZGVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 22:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Totvs 就收购 StoneCo 旗下 Linx 公司的谈判签署排他性协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西软件公司 Totvs 周五表示，它已恢复了收购 StoneCo 旗下 Linx 公司的谈判，并签署了一项协议，在一定期限内享有谈判的排他性。【原文：Brazilian software company Totvs said on Friday it has resumed talks to acquire StoneCo's unit Linx, signing an agreement to have exclusivity in the negotiations for a set period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-totvs-signs-exclusivity-agreement-talks-buy-stonecos-linx-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IO4OPKLB2FJJFMJXQ4LDKPCOD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克工会拒绝公司最近提出的每年至少加薪 2% 的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[工人联合组织称，参与合同谈判的星巴克工会代表投票否决了该咖啡连锁店的最新提案，该提案保证每年至少加薪 2%。【原文：Starbucks union delegates involved in contract bargaining voted to reject the coffee chain's latest proposal that guaranteed annual raises of at least 2%, Workers United said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/starbucks-union-rejects-companys-recent-offer-least-2-annual-pay-raise-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXKREJOD5ZKRND6Y3OE4DBQY5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:19:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克因关闭加密货币业务被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司周五被耐克主题的不可兑换代币（NFTs）和其他加密货币资产的购买者告上法庭，这些购买者称，当这家运动服装公司突然关闭创建这些资产的业务时，他们蒙受了巨大损失。【原文：Nike was sued on Friday by purchasers of Nike-themed non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and other cryptocurrency assets who said they suffered significant losses when the athletic wear company abruptly closed the business that created those assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nike-sued-over-closure-crypto-business-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCK3TY7WWZLMRMCHIOFIFOGE4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通调查显示美元疲软和美国滞胀已成共识]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周五公布的一项调查结果显示，明年美国经济出现滞胀的风险远高于衰退，而最有望在2025年跑赢大盘的资产类别是现金。【原文：There is a much higher risk of stagflation than recession in the U.S. economy over the next year, while the asset class most expected to outperform in 2025 is cash, according to the results of a JPMorgan survey published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-survey-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R75OXJD7WZP4TGOYMCMI7WV77E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道巴里克黄金公司在马里的承包商因政府纠纷而裁员--文件、消息来源]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的文件和熟悉内情的人士透露，巴里克黄金公司在马里的矿场至少有四家分包商正在裁员，这些分包商雇用了数百名员工，而这家加拿大矿商与马里政府之间的纠纷已经持续了两年。【原文：At least four subcontractors employing several hundred people at Barrick Gold's complex in Mali are laying off staff following a two-year dispute between the Canadian miner and the state, according to documents seen by Reuters and people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/barrick-gold-contractors-mali-lay-off-staff-amid-government-dispute-documents-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S24ZZOAKCFJNNE7V4XLC52QQHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前美联储理事沃什称美国央行应改弦更张]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，前美联储理事凯文-沃什（Kevin Warsh）曾与唐纳德-特朗普总统讨论过解雇美国央行行长杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）并让他取而代之的问题。【原文：Former Federal Reserve Governor Kevin Warsh, with whom President Donald Trump is reported to have discussed firing U.S. central bank chief Jerome Powell and installing him in his place, on Friday unleashed a barrage of criticism of the Fed and argued for fundamental changes to how it operates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/former-fed-governor-warsh-says-us-central-bank-should-change-its-ways-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34OLQSI3ARODNOYNMCBANTWRYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储调查发现全球贸易战、政策不确定性是金融稳定的首要风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周五公布的一项最新调查显示，全球贸易风险上升、总体政策不确定性以及美国债务的可持续性在美国金融体系面临的潜在风险中名列前茅。【原文：Rising risks around global trade, general policy uncertainty, and the sustainability of U.S. debt topped the list of potential risks to the U.S. financial system in a new Federal Reserve survey released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-survey-finds-global-trade-fight-policy-uncertainty-top-financial-stability-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6D54HO32JLELHPGF6VLZZMM5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:06:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国批评美国 "近期滥用 "关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行行长周五批评美国 "最近滥用 "关税威胁全球金融稳定，此前双方最近都采取了被视为缓和贸易战的举措。【原文：China's central bank governor on Friday criticized the U.S. for threatening global financial stability with its "recent abuse" of tariffs, in the wake of recent moves seen by both sides as efforts to de-escalate their trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-criticizes-us-recent-abuse-tariffs-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIVFS277GFPN3D7GXV3OMFDDKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:23:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，TikTok 所有者正在权衡巴西的数据中心项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[其中一位消息人士说，初步谈判的重点是一个 300 兆瓦的数据中心，但该项目最终可能在第二阶段扩大到 900 兆瓦。【原文：One of the sources said initial talks are focused on a 300-megawatt data center, but the project could eventually expand to 900 megawatt in a second phase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/tiktok-owner-weighs-data-center-project-brazil-sources-say-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3WFFPTYQJMYXOAMTI4SCP3OWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:18:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官定于 5 月 2 日举行听证会，讨论谷歌数字广告诉讼案的补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官已定于 5 月 2 日举行听证会，讨论美国司法部和一些州可能要求法院对谷歌采取的补救措施，因为法院裁定 Alphabet 旗下公司非法主导了两个在线广告技术市场。【原文：A U.S. judge has set a May 2 hearing to discuss remedies the U.S. Justice Department and a group of states might ask the court to impose on Google after it ruled the Alphabet unit illegally dominates two markets for online advertising technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-judge-sets-may-2-hearing-discuss-remedies-google-digital-ads-lawsuit-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJN53SSLBZKZFCDP7E4F6YRN54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 科技巨头财报、美国就业数据凸显本周市场繁忙景象]]></title><description><![CDATA[即将到来的一周市场将考验美股的反弹，投资者将关注由苹果和微软领衔的企业业绩浪潮，而全球贸易发展的前景随时都有可能引发波动。【原文：A packed upcoming week for markets will test a U.S. stocks rebound, with investors focused on a wave of corporate results led by Apple and Microsoft, while the prospect of global trade developments threatens to cause volatility at any time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-big-tech-earnings-us-jobs-data-highlight-busy-week-markets-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YMDTMPGAZKZXOVMTIVJDPHI7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州建议允许自动驾驶重型卡车测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州机动车辆管理局周五表示，拟允许在州公共道路上对重型卡车和其他大型车辆进行测试。【原文：The California Department of Motor Vehicles said Friday it is proposing to allow testing of heavy-duty trucks and other large vehicles on state public roads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/california-proposes-allow-self-driving-heavy-duty-truck-testing-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">US5HCCSL55PLLHFLEZAFOHK5ME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:46:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼日利亚法庭维持对 Meta 公司罚款 2.2 亿美元的判决，因其违反消费者和数据法]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼日利亚竞争与消费者保护法庭周五表示，尼日利亚竞争监督机构对 Meta Platforms 公司违反当地消费者、数据保护和隐私法的 2.2 亿美元罚款在上诉未果后维持原判。【原文：A $220 million fine against Meta Platforms by Nigeria's competition watchdog for violating local consumer, data protection and privacy laws has been upheld following an unsuccessful appeal, Nigeria's Competition and Consumer Protection Tribunal said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nigerian-tribunal-upholds-220-million-fine-against-meta-violating-consumer-data-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPG63E2U6NJKBLPNRHBE2SHDS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:19:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[非同寻常的利益冲突沃伦要求美国证券交易委员会提供特朗普传媒投资产品的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）周五要求美国证券监管机构分享其对由总统唐纳德-特朗普创建并拥有多数股权的公司即将推出的交易所交易基金的监管计划。【原文：Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren asked the U.S. Securities regulator on Friday to share its plans for regulating exchange-traded funds due to be launched by a company founded and majority-owned by President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/extraordinary-conflict-interest-warren-asks-sec-records-trump-medias-investment-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHMAYILTRJL27CYBXXRIF3LU6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受外汇影响，智利矿业公司 Codelco 税前利润大幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利矿业公司 Codelco 是世界上最大的铜生产商，该公司周五报告称，第一季度产量略有增长，但这一增长不足以抵消汇率的影响，汇率影响导致其利润下滑。【原文：Chilean miner Codelco, the world's largest copper producer, on Friday reported a slight bump in production in the first quarter, though the boost was not enough to offset exchange-rate effects, which caused its profits to tumble.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chilean-miner-codelcos-pre-tax-profit-tumbles-fx-effects-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5GCDU5EINI4HBFGUPVBW2MN6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:41:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deliveroo 收到 DoorDash 提出的每股 180 便士的收购方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国送餐公司 Deliveroo 周五证实，它于 4 月 5 日收到了来自 DoorDash 以每股 180 便士的价格收购其全部股份的提议。【原文：British meal delivery company Deliveroo confirmed on Friday that it received a proposal from DoorDash on April 5 to buy all of its shares for 180 pence each.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/deliveroo-receives-buyout-proposal-doordash-180-pence-per-share-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ENVVMWONFJPFA22OG3IB34IQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元、日本央行利率政策可能仍是日美贸易谈判的焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本在周四的双边财政会谈中可能避免了美国要求日元走强的压力，但仔细研究一下官员们对会议的描述，就会发现货币和日本央行的利率政策可能仍然是更广泛贸易谈判中的关键因素。【原文：Japan may have averted U.S. pressure for a stronger yen in bilateral finance talks on Thursday, but a closer look at officials' descriptions of the meeting suggests currencies and the Bank of Japan's interest rate policy may remain key factors in broader trade negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/yen-bojs-rate-policy-may-remain-focus-japan-us-trade-talks-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X63IGKQE3BKZ3ATRFDEQXQ5OSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会新任主席称加密货币行业应受到明确监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）新任负责人周五表示，该机构在过去几年中助长了 "监管的不确定性"，从而扼杀了加密货币行业的创新。【原文：The new head of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday said that the agency has stifled innovation for the cryptocurrency sector by fostering "regulatory uncertainty" in prior years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/new-us-sec-chair-says-crypto-sector-deserves-clear-regulations-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O46TT27G75PBTP3WR753X54SAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安进公司将扩建俄亥俄州生物技术生产厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[安进公司周五宣布斥资9亿美元扩建其在俄亥俄州的生物技术生产设施，成为在特朗普政府威胁可能征收进口关税之际承诺提高美国产能的一系列制药商中的最新一家。【原文：Amgen on Friday announced a $900 million expansion of its Ohio biotech manufacturing facility, becoming the latest in a string of drugmakers pledging to increase U.S. capacity amid Trump administration threats of potential import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/amgen-expand-ohio-biotech-manufacturing-plant-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7274IFYD3VOC3GB3WAJU4U32VQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前 CISA 老大称特朗普的行动有可能 "危险地降低 "美国的网络防御能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国网络安全和基础设施安全局（CISA）前局长周五在一篇文章中说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对高级网络官员的清洗和明显的报复行为使国家的数字防御面临风险。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's purges and apparent acts of retribution aimed at top cyber officials put the nation's digital defenses at risk, the former head of the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) said in a post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ex-cisa-boss-says-trump-actions-risk-dangerously-degrading-us-cyber-defenses-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFMJLOJ65FK6DAEN5MZPYZQBJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股东批准家乐福将巴西业务私有化的申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的一份证券文件显示，家乐福巴西分公司 Atacadao SA 的股东在法国零售商提出私有化要求后，投票决定将其私有化。【原文：Shareholders in Carrefour's Brazil unit, Atacadao SA , voted to take it private after a bid by the French retailer to do so, according to a securities filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shareholders-approve-carrefour-bid-take-brazil-unit-private-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7YZMW4V6JPHXHY4OUPGQTZSWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰多诺霍表示，欧盟将 "不遗余力 "地减少与贸易有关的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰财政部长帕夏尔-多诺霍（Paschal Donohoe）周五表示，欧盟将尽其所能与美国就贸易问题进行接触，减少拖累全球经济的巨大不确定性，这凸显了欧盟成员国之间的团结。【原文：The European Union will do all it can to engage with the U.S. on trade and reduce the massive uncertainty that is weighing down the global economy, Irish Finance Minister Paschal Donohoe said on Friday, underscoring unity among the bloc's members.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-will-leave-no-stone-unturned-reduce-trade-related-uncertainty-irelands-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GUY5EWRVRJOTC7PJYMMTHMHL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:15:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>