<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:06:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:06:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[优衣库运营商 Fast Retailing 第二季度利润增长 33%，并上调业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本优衣库（Uniqlo）运营商周四表示，第二季度盈利飙升 33%，这是在美国征收进口关税给这家全球服装连锁店连续第四年创纪录盈利的目标蒙上阴影之前的最后一段平静时期。【原文：The Japanese operator of Uniqlo on Thursday said earnings soared 33% in its second quarter, the last period of calm before the U.S. imposition of import tariffs clouded the global clothing chain's aim for a fourth successive year of record profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uniqlo-operator-fast-retailings-q2-profit-jumped-33-raises-forecast-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZN2HRURANKKXNAZEAGATEBSXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 06:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟冯德莱恩对特朗普宣布暂停互惠关税表示欢迎]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）周四对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布暂停互惠关税表示欢迎。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen on Thursday welcomed US President Donald Trump's announcement of a pause in reciprocal tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eus-von-der-leyen-welcomes-trumps-announcement-pause-reciprocal-tariffs-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KP67VCS42VOYLMOG3LUR6KFAZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 06:34:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[东盟集团寻求就关税问题与美国对话，但不会采取报复行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[地区集团东盟（ASEAN）的经济部长们周四表示，东南亚国家正在敦促与美国就贸易关税问题进行对话，不会采取报复性措施。【原文：Southeast Asian countries are pressing for dialogue with the United States on trade tariffs and will not impose retaliatory measures, economic ministers of the regional bloc ASEAN said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asean-bloc-says-it-wont-impose-retaliatory-measures-over-us-tariffs-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ76VU6H6JLAXBDZU5X3F76LVY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 06:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长维勒鲁瓦称特朗普政策削弱了对美元的信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（ECB）决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最近几周的政策削弱了人们对美元的信心。【原文：US President Donald Trump's policies in recent weeks have eroded confidence in the US dollar, European Central Bank (ECB) policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/ecbs-villeroy-says-trump-policies-have-eroded-confidence-us-dollar-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QP5AW6YEONNDPGAZBAYCTL7FF4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 06:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师报告称，保时捷在关税生效前向美国运输了更多存货]]></title><description><![CDATA[据伯恩斯坦研究公司（Bernstein Research）的一份报告称，保时捷高管在周三的一次电话会议上告诉分析师和投资者，保时捷已向美国运送了更多库存，以抢在关税之前，并保持 3 月份订单的价格不变。【原文：Porsche has shipped added inventory to the United States to get ahead of tariffs and kept prices constant for orders made in March, executives told analysts and investors in a call on Wednesday, according to a note by Bernstein Research.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-shipped-added-inventory-us-ahead-tariffs-analyst-note-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TAWQFIBVNMLLB7UF3JB753CMU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 06:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waymo 将在东京开始收集数据，并进行驾驶员试乘测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 的自动驾驶部门 Waymo 周四表示，将于下周开始在东京收集数据，并由人类司机进行试乘，这标志着该公司将首次在美国以外的公共道路上使用其汽车。【原文：Alphabet's self-driving unit Waymo said on Thursday it will start collecting data in Tokyo with test rides operated by human drivers next week, marking the first time the company will be using its cars on public roads outside the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/waymo-begin-data-collection-tokyo-with-driver-operated-test-rides-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYYYE4ZFVVMRVJ6XKYR2GS4WL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:46:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛下调中国 GDP 增长预期，理由是关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国投资银行高盛（Goldman Sachs）以关税的负面影响为由，下调了对中国2025年和2026年GDP增长的预测，分别从之前预测的4.5%和4.0%下调至4%和3.5%。【原文：U.S. investment bank Goldman Sachs revised down its forecasts for China's GDP growth to 4% in 2025 and 3.5% in 2026, from previous projections of 4.5% and 4.0% respectively, citing the negative effects of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/goldman-sachs-revises-down-china-gdp-growth-forecasts-cites-tariff-effects-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YW5YBZBEGBI4BJFOU2DTDYDX5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:40:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第一季度营收大幅超出市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约芯片制造商台积电周四公布第一季度营收为 8392.5 亿新台币（约合 255.5 亿美元），高于市场预期，原因是该公司从人工智能需求中获益。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest contract chipmaker, on Thursday reported first-quarter revenue of T$839.25 billion ($25.55 billion), beating market forecasts, as the company reaps the benefit from artificial intelligence demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmcs-first-quarter-revenue-handily-beats-market-forecast-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOLUUYBTTNLXFLYGSP7BEUWLBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:36:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对中美贸易紧张局势加剧的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三在对大多数贸易伙伴征收新的高额对等关税的同时，加紧了与中国的贸易战。【原文：U.S. Donald Trump ratcheted up a trade war with China even as he did an about turn on steep new reciprocal tariffs on most trading partners on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/investors-react-intensifying-sino-us-trade-tensions-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WXPMZIG4NNKPGS5HBJ4CCSWUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:24:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度官员称，印度希望在关税暂停之际与美国迅速达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普做出暂停对除中国以外的数十个国家征收高额互惠关税的惊人决定后，一位政府官员表示，印度希望尽快与美国达成贸易协议。【原文：India wants to move quickly on a trade deal with the United States, a government official said, after President Donald Trump's stunning decision to pause hefty reciprocal tariffs he had just imposed on dozens of countries, except for China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india-eyes-quick-trade-deal-with-us-amid-tariff-pause-official-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2HTMHETFVK45LQK7THEQLUNVA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果根据世贸组织规则发现不公平行为，日本将对中国钢铁进口采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本贸易和工业部的一位官员周四表示，如果根据世界贸易组织的规则发现任何不公平的做法，日本贸易和工业部将考虑对进口中国钢铁采取行动。【原文：Japan's trade and industry ministry will consider taking action on imports of Chinese steel if any unfair practices are identified under World Trade Organization rules, a ministry official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/japan-act-chinese-steel-imports-if-unfair-practices-found-under-wto-rules-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWMLVLEXJBMXHL3MXSCZ74YWXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官告诉《金融时报》，特朗普关税将影响 Orsted 美国项目的成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦 Orsted 公司首席执行官拉斯穆斯-埃尔博（Rasmus Errboe）在周四发表的一篇采访中告诉《金融时报》，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税，该公司在美国的项目成本将受到 "有意义的影响"。【原文：Denmark's Orsted would have a "meaningful impact" on the cost of its projects in the U.S. due to President Donald Trump's tariffs, CEO Rasmus Errboe told the Financial Times in an interview published on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-tariffs-have-impact-cost-orsteds-us-projects-ceo-tells-ft-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NN6F2VB2GJIS3L5PQXCZST5B44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：路威酩轩集团发现在得克萨斯州制作路易威登手袋很麻烦]]></title><description><![CDATA[六年前，路威酩轩集团（LVMH）的亿万富翁首席执行官伯纳德-阿诺特（Bernard Arnault）和美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）为位于德克萨斯州乡村的一家工厂剪彩，这家工厂将为世界最知名的奢侈品牌之一路易威登（Louis Vuitton）生产名牌手袋。【原文：Six years ago, LVMH's billionaire CEO Bernard Arnault and President Donald Trump cut the blue ribbon on a factory in rural Texas that would make designer handbags for Louis Vuitton, one of the world’s best-known luxury brands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lvmh-finds-making-louis-vuitton-bags-messy-texas-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DI36WIWROFO4BALTZWINE4S5LU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街本周的鞭打带来了恐惧、解脱和谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[过去一周，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策将华尔街的交易员和投资者推向了风口浪尖，他们争先恐后地制定策略，安抚客户，因为数万亿美元的股票市值化为乌有。【原文：Wall Street traders and investors have been sent to the brink over the past week by President Donald Trump's tariff policy, scrambling to figure out strategies and calming clients as trillions were wiped off stock market values.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-streets-week-whiplash-brought-fear-relief-caution-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ISAXSELG5PAXHAOE7C4VQIQYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者比尔-阿克曼称中国在特朗普撤销关税后陷入孤立]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）令人震惊地推翻其关税决定后，中国现在已被孤立，其他美国贸易伙伴正在排队等候达成交易。【原文：Billionaire investor Bill Ackman said on Thursday China was now isolated and other U.S. trading partners were lining up to make deals following President Donald Trump's stunning reversal of his tariff decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/investor-bill-ackman-says-china-is-isolated-after-trump-tariff-reversal-move-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDUQYQTTYBNH7CJYDCBHDBAP3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 04:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标救市反弹中的麻烦迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GINBPJIZF5NVHDUUWCEBMBA6BE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 04:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税导致美国国债市场混乱，引发长期担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，国债因关税问题而大幅下挫，导致全球最大的债券市场出现混乱，对冲基金平仓了一些由债务引发的押注，投资者对美国市场受到的持久损害表示担忧。【原文：The searing selloff in Treasuries this week in response to tariffs caused dislocations in the world’s biggest bond market, as hedge funds unwound some debt-fuelled bets and investors raised concerns about lasting damage to U.S. markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-bonds-trading-analysispix-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPFWPJB7CNPHZN6QDMOYPQCBOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 04:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源署称，全球贸易战可能给新兴的人工智能行业带来逆风]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际能源机构（IEA）技术总监劳拉-科齐（Laura Cozzi）告诉路透社，全球关税战的升级可能会给新兴的数据中心行业带来挑战，并导致增长放缓。【原文：An escalating global tariff war could provide challenges for the emerging data centre sector and cause slower growth, Laura Cozzi, the International Energy Agency (IEA) Director of Technology told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/global-trade-war-may-produce-headwinds-nascent-ai-sector-iea-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4RIEXA2IBOYFK2QX5VV4ZMJDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 04:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者价格在关税海啸前的 3 月份表现温和]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者价格在 3 月份可能略有上涨，但在唐纳德-特朗普总统加倍征收进口中国商品的关税，甚至降低对其他国家的关税之后，通胀风险偏向上行。【原文：U.S. consumer prices likely increased marginally in March, but inflation risks are tilted to the upside after President Donald Trump doubled down on tariffs on imported Chinese goods even as he lowered duties on other nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-prices-seen-mild-march-before-tariffs-tsunami-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGALKTZGQVN4JEVV3R7IW6NUHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 04:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷-达里奥呼吁美国与中国达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大对冲基金的创始人雷-达里奥（Ray Dalio）呼吁美国与中国就关税问题达成协议，并表示美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府的下一个目标应该是将国家赤字削减至国内生产总值的 3%。【原文：Ray Dalio, founder of the world's largest hedge fund, called for a U.S. deal with the Chinese on tariffs and said that the next goal for U.S. President Donald Trump's administration should be to cut the country's deficit to 3% of GDP.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ray-dalio-calls-us-trade-deal-with-china-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQOVH4IRF5NKRLDNPHC5P27LDU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 03:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南航空公司签署 3 亿美元融资协议，正与波音公司商谈扩大订单事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南廉价航空公司 Vietjet 周四表示，它已与投资基金 KKR 的合作伙伴 AV AirFinance 签署了一项价值 3 亿美元的协议，为其机队扩建提供资金。【原文：Vietnamese budget carrier Vietjet said on Thursday it has signed an agreement worth $300 million with AV AirFinance, a partner of investment fund KKR , to fund the expansion of its fleet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietjet-signs-300-million-finance-deal-talks-expand-order-with-boeing-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOE2HP6JLBPXJO4FYZZWKNTVYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿克曼的 Pershing Square Holdings 基金今年迄今下跌近 14]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）的潘兴广场控股公司（Pershing Square Holdings）周三告诉投资者，该公司的投资组合今年迄今已亏损近 14%。【原文：Billionaire investor Bill Ackman's Pershing Square Holdings portfolio has lost nearly 14% so far this year, the firm told investors on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ackmans-pershing-square-holdings-fund-drops-nearly-14-so-far-this-year-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYGHNZTWJ5NNJENNBU3COEQ76A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:53:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称 CATL 将获香港联交所批准 50 亿美元上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位直接知情人士透露，中国电池巨头 CATL 在香港上市融资至少 50 亿美元的计划将于本周四获得香港证券交易所的批准。【原文：Chinese battery giant CATL's Hong Kong listing to raise at least $5 billion is due to be approved by the city's stock exchange on Thursday, according to two sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-catl-seeks-hong-kong-stock-exchange-approval-least-5-billion-listing-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCHEQ734I5PLRAK7JYNLSDRPQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:51:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在关税问题上做出让步，但继续保持对中国的贸易战热度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）刚刚决定暂停对数十个国家征收高额关税，这一令人震惊的决定使得全球股市在周四大幅上扬，即使在他与世界第二大经济体中国的贸易战愈演愈烈之际也是如此。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's stunning decision to pause the hefty duties he had just imposed on dozens of countries sent battered global stock markets surging on Thursday even as he ratcheted up a trade war with the world's No. 2 economy China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-u-turns-tariffs-turns-trade-war-heat-china-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73XVHV7SGJJUTACWNFV2KCG2OE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚拒绝中国 "联手 "对抗美国关税的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚周四拒绝了中国政府提出的合作应对美国关税的建议，并表示将继续实现贸易多元化，降低对最大贸易伙伴中国的依赖。【原文：Australia on Thursday declined Beijing's proposal to work together to counter U.S. tariffs, saying instead it would continue to diversify its trade and lower its reliance on China, its largest trading partner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australia-turns-down-chinas-offer-join-hands-fight-us-tariffs-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVDNTLISKRK53NJIAUMMGBIJWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道关税飙升，亚马逊上的中国卖家要么涨价要么撤出美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[该协会表示，关税将严重影响中国的小型企业和制造商。【原文：The tariffs will severely impact China's small enterprises and manufacturers, the association said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-sellers-amazon-hike-prices-or-exit-us-tariffs-soar-association-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5BJ5IV27JNC5EIOTO5GD354QA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易战焦虑盖过关税转向，避险天堂反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普突然暂停对其他许多国家征收关税90天后，交易员们又涌向日元和瑞士法郎等避险货币，并抛售了澳元。【原文：Traders swept back into safe havens like the yen and Swiss franc and sold the Australian dollar on Thursday, after U.S. President Donald Trump ramped up his trade war against China even as he abruptly paused tariffs for 90 days on many other nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/safe-havens-rebound-sino-us-trade-war-anxiety-overshadows-tariff-u-turn-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEZVT4FYNFIP5GSQJTTSM3ZTLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 3 月份居民消费价格涨幅扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份，中国居民消费价格连续第二个月下降，而生产者通货紧缩持续存在，在关税风险日益加剧的情况下，人们对经济前景的谨慎情绪与日俱增。【原文：China's consumer prices fell for the second straight month in March while producer deflation persisted, as caution grows over the economic outlook amid mounting tariff risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-consumer-prices-extend-declines-march-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWM65MVD4VMZTJ4LEJ53YTE6G4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 01:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普升级对华贸易战，油价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布暂停对其他国家征收 90 天的关税，但他还是加紧了与中国的贸易战，导致油价周四下跌了约 1%。【原文：Oil prices fell around 1% on Thursday as U.S. President Donald Trump ramped up a trade war with China, even as he announced a 90-day pause on tariffs aimed at other countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-fall-trump-escalates-trade-war-with-china-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNDQ7EQ7URKK3DWCEVZ5CEN7NM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 01:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普暂停加征关税后，股市出现缓解性反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将暂时降低他刚刚对数十个国家征收的高额关税后，全球股市反弹，美元站稳了脚跟，狂热的债券抛售也趋于稳定。【原文：Global stocks rallied, the dollar found footing and a manic bond selloff stabilised on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would temporarily lower the hefty duties he had just imposed on dozens of countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Y3S7CU3RBPTTKYSVENJJ7YYGY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>