<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 06:08:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 06:08:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[干邑生产商人头马君度第一季度销售额增长 5.7%，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国干邑公司人头马君度（Remy Cointreau）周五公布，第一季度有机销售额增长 5.7%，远高于分析师预期的 2.3%。【原文：French cognac company Remy Cointreau reported a 5.7% rise in first-quarter organic sales on Friday, well ahead of analyst expectations of 2.3% growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/cognac-maker-remy-cointreau-first-quarter-sales-up-57-beating-forecast-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5MTUMDE5ZL37BPXBD4K2K2DOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:33:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税影响第二季度利润，大众汽车下调业绩指引]]></title><description><![CDATA[在关税对德国汽车巨头大众汽车第二季度的营业利润造成打击之后，大众汽车周五首次对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与欧洲的贸易战预计将如何影响其2025年的盈利做出了评估。【原文：Volkswagen on Friday gave its first assessment of how U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war with Europe is expected to impact its 2025 earnings after tariffs dealt a blow to the German auto giant's operating profit in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-lowers-guidance-tariffs-hit-profit-second-quarter-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIDASN7KLNLPBHECNFBURFRBEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[起亚公司第二季度因美国关税损失 5.7 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国起亚公司周五表示，在4月至6月期间，该公司因美国关税遭受了7860亿韩元（约合5.7亿美元）的损失。【原文：South Korea's Kia Corp said on Friday that it suffered a hit of 786 billion won ($570 million) from U.S. tariffs in the April to June period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/kia-corp-takes-570-million-hit-us-tariffs-second-quarter-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGP3NZYS3JN2TJVARQJTXXRBPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称美国在贸易协议中的投资利润将按贡献分配]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周五表示，在本周与美国达成的关税协议中商定的 5,500 亿美元投资计划所产生的利润将根据日美双方的贡献程度进行分配。【原文：Japan's government said on Friday that profits from a $550 billion investment package agreed in this week's tariff deal with the U.S. would be split between Japan and the U.S. according to the degree of contributions by each side.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japan-says-profits-us-investments-trade-deal-be-shared-according-contributions-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWOT3VWIBBPERFJB7M3FNSUCDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，由于中美关系紧张，长江和记港口交易最后期限可能延长]]></title><description><![CDATA[长江和记出售其价值 228 亿美元的大部分港口业务的计划不可能很快敲定，政治边缘政策仍将继续，消息人士称周日独家谈判的最后期限可能会延长。【原文：CK Hutchison's plan to sell most of its $22.8 billion ports business is unlikely to be finalised anytime soon, with political brinkmanship set to continue, and sources saying that a Sunday deadline for exclusive talks was likely to be extended.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ck-hutchison-ports-deal-deadline-likely-be-extended-us-china-tensions-weigh-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2Y4I52JSFNC5H7FWOSQ5TZJQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:54:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价贸易协定眩晕周后市场趋于平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔-斯图尔特-亨特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKBIXNV3ENLJ3AAFG2YQUVSO3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:45:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注欧洲小型企业，以躲避关税影响和欧元强势]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲的小型公司正在成为投资者的热门投资工具，帮助投资组合抵御关税和欧元走强的影响，因为更低廉的信贷和更多政府支出的前景增强了投资者对经济前景的信心。【原文：Europe's smaller companies are emerging as a popular vehicle for investors to help insulate portfolios against both tariffs and a stronger euro, as cheaper credit and the prospect of more government spending bolster confidence in the economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-bet-europes-smaller-companies-dodge-tariff-fallout-strong-euro-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LU6LJNERLRPPLDHFTJACIXCRA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:41:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，斯塔默将就削减英国进口钢铁关税的协议向特朗普施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，英国首相基尔-斯塔默（Keir Starmer）将游说美国总统唐纳德-特朗普加快达成削减英国钢铁关税的最终协议。【原文：British Prime Minister Keir Starmer will lobby U.S. President Donald Trump to accelerate a final deal to cut tariffs on British steel, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/starmer-press-trump-over-deal-cut-tariffs-uk-steel-imports-ft-reports-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWESNXXDQROL5PXZQSRTBXIUEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技公司将在受美国制裁的中国展示人工智能创新成果]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周末，大大小小的科技公司将齐聚上海，展示他们的人工智能创新成果，并在中国面临美国制裁之际支持中国蓬勃发展的人工智能产业。【原文：Tech firms huge and small will converge in Shanghai this weekend to showcase their artificial intelligence innovations and support China's booming AI sector as it faces U.S. sanctions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tech-firms-showcase-ai-innovations-china-under-us-sanctions-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGK6IS5NRZN57LBPETNAO7JNFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易协议为日本央行重启加息扫清障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）与东京达成的贸易协议为日本央行今年再次加息打开了空间。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's trade deal with Tokyo opens scope for the Bank of Japan to raise interest rates again this year, sources say, a prospect the central bank may start to telegraph by offering a less gloomy view on the economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trade-deal-clears-way-boj-tiptoe-back-rate-hikes-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQHUKAXU4FMZRBRQXM5QD3MPU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电商领军者撇开监管风险，继续 "即时零售 "价格战]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最大的电子商务平台并没有停止 "即时零售 "价格战的迹象，这种价格战对国家批评的承受力非同寻常，这表明即时零售作为电子商务的未来几乎具有举足轻重的地位。【原文：China's largest e-commerce platforms show no signs of halting an "instant retail" price war unusual in its resilience to state criticism, indicating the almost existential importance placed on instant retail as the future of e-commerce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/chinese-e-commerce-leaders-brush-off-regulatory-risk-continue-instant-retail-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZU5GMWLVNMRZI5TGGUFS6MS24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市从高位回落，美元上涨，市场为关键的一周做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市从高位回落，日本股市从创纪录的高位回落，原因是投资者在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税最后期限和一系列央行会议等关键的一周到来之前锁定了利润。【原文：Asian shares eased from highs on Friday, with Japanese markets retreating from a record peak, as investors locked in profits ahead of a crucial week that includes U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff deadline and a host of central bank meetings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SOF6UKPPYVISDHAXSWKF7I63AU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔代工厂的未来取决于下一代芯片制造技术能否获得客户青睐]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司周四警告投资者，如果不能找到外部客户在其工厂生产芯片，它可能不得不退出芯片制造业务。【原文：Intel warned investors on Thursday that it may have to get out of the chip manufacturing business if it does not land external customers to make chips in its factories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/intels-foundry-future-depends-securing-customer-next-gen-chipmaking-tech-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KB2QYGYBZOSDN5OTZLQ22BVO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡经济意外增长，经济学家对新加坡货币政策看法不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管全球经济增长疲软，但新加坡经济依然充满活力，因此经济学家对新加坡央行在下周预定的审查中是放松货币政策还是维持货币政策不变意见不一。【原文：Economists are split on whether Singapore's central bank will loosen monetary policy or leave settings unchanged in its scheduled review next week as the economy remains resilient despite weakening global growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/economists-split-singapore-monetary-policy-after-surprise-growth-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TJJJICOABOCBB7Q7SEYH2N66E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点转向美联储和日本央行会议，美元创一个月来最大单周跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元在两周低点附近企稳，有望创下一个月来的最大单周跌幅，原因是投资者在最后期限前仍在争论美国关税谈判，同时期待下周的央行会议提供政策线索。【原文：The dollar steadied near two-week lows on Friday, on track for its biggest weekly drop in a month, as investors contended with U.S. tariff negotiations ahead of a deadline while looking ahead to central bank meetings next week for clues on policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-heads-biggest-weekly-drop-month-focus-shifts-fed-boj-meets-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NF4UWEEKRL6TALHTOCQP6XEPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因美欧贸易乐观和俄罗斯汽油下调而攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，受美国和欧盟可能达成贸易协议的乐观情绪以及有关俄罗斯计划限制向大多数国家出口汽油的报道提振，油价上涨。【原文：Oil prices rose on Friday, buoyed by optimism over a potential trade deal between the U.S. and the European Union and reports of Russian plans to restrict gasoline exports to most countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-climb-us-eu-trade-optimism-russian-gasoline-cuts-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POYSTDOE45MMTDYX6PD6PQPNJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称澳大利亚同意接受美国牛肉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，澳大利亚已同意向美国牛肉开放市场，此前美国的盟友放松了对进口牛肉的限制，这激怒了美国领导人。【原文：Australia has agreed to open its market to U.S. beef, President Donald Trump said on Thursday, after the U.S. ally eased restrictions on imports that had angered the American leader.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-says-australia-has-agreed-accept-american-beef-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CV367YBUKBPFBBG3HRFMYUMXPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车电池公司 LG Energy Solution 第二季度利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国电池公司 LG Energy Solution（LGES）周五公布的季度利润增长了 152%，主要原因是一些客户在美国可能征收关税之前囤积了电池，从而带动了前期需求。【原文：South Korean battery firm LG Energy Solution (LGES) on Friday posted a 152% rise in quarterly profit, driven by front-loaded demand as some customers stockpiled batteries ahead of potential U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-battery-firm-lg-energy-solution-q2-profit-jumps-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43OFJVMGRBPUXJ7GKAB5DOYMC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[烘焙巨头宾堡（Bimbo）誓言在 2026 年底之前减少人工色素的使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的面包生产商之一宾博集团（Grupo Bimbo）周四表示，随着消费者在购买主食时更加注重健康，该公司将在明年年底之前从所有产品中减少人工色素的使用。【原文：Grupo Bimbo , one of the world's largest breadmakers, said on Thursday it would cut artificial colorings from all of its products by the end of next year, as consumers turn more health-conscious when shopping for staple foods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/baking-giant-bimbo-vows-cut-artificial-colorings-by-end-2026-2025-07-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42WW65NFGFMUZNR5MBRZHBIS6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:12:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国部长会见美国商务部长，努力达成关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国工业部周五表示，韩国工业部长金正昆（Kim Jung-kwan）周四会见了美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick），重申了在8月1日最后期限之前就关税问题达成贸易协议的承诺。【原文：South Korea's Industry Minister Kim Jung-kwan met U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick on Thursday and reaffirmed a commitment to reach a trade deal on tariffs by the August 1 deadline, South Korea's industry ministry said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-minister-meets-us-commerce-secretary-effort-reach-tariff-deal-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTKEUXDGCRNNVJOKAO2GSVR3OA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:24:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西副总统称赞与卢特尼克就关税问题进行的对话 "良好 "且 "富有成效]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西副总统杰拉尔多-阿尔克明（Geraldo Alckmin）周四表示，在周六与美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）的会谈中，他重申巴西愿意就美国对来自拉美第一大经济体的进口商品征收关税的提议进行谈判。【原文：Brazilian Vice President Geraldo Alckmin said on Thursday that he had reiterated his country's willingness to negotiate proposed U.S. tariffs on imports from Latin America's No. 1 economy during a conversation on Saturday with U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-vp-hails-good-fruitful-conversation-with-lutnick-tariffs-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECD5EWDJM5O77KSMX4RLRZN6KY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官重新安排波音公司寻求终止刑事起诉的听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官重新安排了对司法部和波音公司请求批准一项协议的听证会，该协议允许波音公司避免因两起造成数百人死亡的 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故而被起诉。【原文：A U.S. judge has rescheduled a hearing on the Justice Department and Boeing's request to approve an agreement that allows the planemaker to avoid prosecution on a charge stemming from two fatal 737 MAX plane crashes that killed hundreds people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-judge-reschedules-boeing-hearing-seeking-end-criminal-prosecution-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KZS2RZ3GJI7LPTGUCOVINTH7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:30:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会为派拉蒙与天舞公司 80 亿美元的合并扫清障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会周四批准了派拉蒙全球公司（Paramount Global）与 Skydance Media 的合并，为 84 亿美元出售娱乐业最著名的公司扫清了障碍，这些公司包括哥伦比亚广播公司（CBS）广播电视网、派拉蒙电影公司（Paramount Pictures）和尼克儿童频道（Nickelodeon）有线电视频道。【原文：The U.S. Federal Communications Commission on Thursday approved the merger between Paramount Global and Skydance Media, clearing the way for an $8.4 billion sale of some of the most prominent names in entertainment, including the CBS broadcast television network, Paramount Pictures, and the Nickelodeon cable channel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-fcc-clears-way-8-billion-paramount-skydance-merger-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZQAHG3DAZLURNF626DMP2ATXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[域名需求稳定，VeriSign 第二季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[互联网服务公司威瑞信（VeriSign）周四公布的第二季度利润高于华尔街预期，这主要得益于企业加强数字足迹后对域名注册的稳定需求。【原文：Internet services company VeriSign posted second-quarter profit above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, helped by stable demand for domain name registrations as businesses bolster their digital footprints.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/verisign-beats-second-quarter-profit-estimates-steady-demand-domain-names-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QQUZBC3IZOQPBRYLKFMN7XUXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意法半导体将以最高 9.5 亿美元收购恩智浦半导体的部分传感器业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国-意大利芯片制造商意法半导体公司（STMicroelectronics）周四表示，将以最多9.5亿美元的现金收购恩智浦半导体公司（NXP Semiconductors）传感器部门的部分股权。【原文：French-Italian chipmaker STMicroelectronics said on Thursday it would acquire part of NXP Semiconductors' sensor unit for up to $950 million in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/stmicro-buy-part-nxp-semiconductors-sensor-business-up-950-million-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GAXVQSKFGVLN7OG3SHYU3KJ6HQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:46:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pinnacle Financial Partners 与 Synovus Financial 将以 86 亿美元交易合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pinnacle Financial Partners 和 Synovus Financial 已同意以 86 亿美元的全股票交易合并，组建美国东南部最大的地区性银行之一，合并资产超过 1,150 亿美元。【原文：Pinnacle Financial Partners and Synovus Financial have agreed to merge in an $8.6 billion all-stock deal, forming one of the largest regional banks in the southeastern United States with over $115 billion in combined assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/pinnacle-financial-partners-synovus-financial-merge-86-billion-deal-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBYO4KRS6NNYLLSMRHGX5F7TXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:12:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与鲍威尔就美联储翻修费用发生争执]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔周四就央行华盛顿总部的翻修费用问题进行了面对面的争论。【原文：President Donald Trump and Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell sparred face to face Thursday over the cost of renovations of the central bank’s Washington headquarters, with the Fed leader saying the president was wrong about the cost of the overhaul.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-powell-spar-over-costs-fed-renovations-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GW5KJ7XCJBI4BEWSYTWSTPMFFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Digital Realty 因数据中心需求提高年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Digital Realty Trust 公司周四上调了年度营收和核心运营资金的预期，因为该公司预计，由于企业加速数字化转型，对数据中心服务的需求将会增加。【原文：Digital Realty Trust raised its annual revenue and core funds from operations forecast on Thursday, as it expects an increase in demand for data center services due to businesses accelerating digital transformation efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/digital-realty-boosts-annual-revenue-forecast-data-center-demand-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWQB65GXJNINPEHKES4EK7EGTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:07:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日人工智能推动创下新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJ3UVVRK4VI4NACFZJSKWOVG34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国，被禁用的英伟达人工智能芯片组的维修需求激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国对一种理论上不应该存在的业务的需求开始激增：美国禁止向其贸易和技术竞争对手出口先进的英伟达（Nvidia）人工智能芯片组的维修业务。【原文：Demand in China has begun surging for a business that, in theory, shouldn't exist: the repair of advanced Nvidia artificial intelligence chipsets that the U.S. has banned the export of to its trade and tech rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-repair-demand-banned-nvidia-ai-chipsets-booms-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2W22LGPR7VMSXKMEG6DUSLIPDE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>