<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 09:34:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 09:34:31 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士法院将对具有里程碑意义的特拉菲古拉腐败案做出裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士法官将于周五对一宗涉及大宗商品贸易商Trafigura和其他三名被告的贪污案作出判决，他们涉嫌向一名安哥拉石油官员行贿以换取石油交易。【原文：Swiss judges will issue a verdict on Friday in a corruption trial involving commodities trader Trafigura and three other defendants who allegedly paid bribes to an Angolan oil official in exchange for oil deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/swiss-court-rule-landmark-trafigura-corruption-case-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UCSQ7TULFNDDDD7LONNWUTDUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 08:59:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美国不参与气候问题，但 SAP 发现对可持续发展软件的需求不断增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国 SAP 公司首席财务官多米尼克-阿萨姆（Dominik Asam）在接受路透社采访时说，尽管美国的气候保护目标有减弱的趋势，但该公司认为全球对管理和记录公司可持续发展努力的软件的需求仍在增长。【原文：Germany's SAP sees a growing global demand for software to manage and document companies' sustainability efforts despite a trend of weakening climate protection targets in the United States, its chief financial officer, Dominik Asam, said in an interview with Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sap-sees-growing-demand-sustainability-software-despite-us-climate-disengagement-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U2JIBYP4NJZTB7NJLZ47AEUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 08:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[设计师金-琼斯（Kim Jones）离开 LVMH 旗下 Dior Homme 品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[时装设计师金-琼斯（Kim Jones）周五表示，将离开路威酩轩集团（LVMH）旗下的 Dior Homme 品牌。【原文：Fashion designer Kim Jones is leaving LVMH's Dior Homme brand, said the company on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/designer-kim-jones-leaving-lvmhs-dior-homme-brand-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBU3FFGL55PTRCLW5YXPTVD7WQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 08:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可再生能源集团 Orsted 更换首席执行官以遏制股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦可再生能源公司 Orsted 周五表示，该公司首席执行官 Mads Nipper 将卸任，由公司内部人士 Rasmus Errboe 接替，以避免股价自 2021 年最高点以来暴跌 83%。【原文：Orsted Chief Executive Mads Nipper will step down to be replaced by company insider Rasmus Errboe, the Danish renewable energy company said on Friday as it seeks to arrest an 83% slump in its share price since its 2021 peak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/orsted-ousts-ceo-appoints-company-insider-new-boss-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2KFQPL7GFKU5CZ7GN3ODXGRBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 07:45:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[销售前景乐观，苹果欧洲股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周五在法兰克福股价上涨 2.5%，原因是该公司预测本季度销售增长相对强劲，这表明该公司将从 iPhone 销量下滑中恢复过来。【原文：Shares in Apple rose 2.5% in Frankfurt on Friday after results the day before, as the company forecast relatively strong sales growth in the current quarter, a sign it will recover from a dip in iPhone sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-shares-rise-europe-after-upbeat-sales-outlook-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSOJ2VIPMZLVNELIYQOWXCM7JY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 07:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[叙利亚伊斯兰统治者通过解雇和国有企业私有化全面整顿经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[叙利亚新任伊斯兰教领导人正在对该国支离破碎的经济进行大刀阔斧的改革，包括计划解雇三分之一的公共部门员工，并将阿萨德家族半个世纪统治期间占主导地位的国营公司私有化。【原文：Syria's new Islamist leaders are undertaking a radical overhaul of the country's broken economy, including plans to fire a third of all public sector workers and privatising state-run companies dominant during half a century of Assad family rule.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/syrias-islamist-rulers-overhaul-economy-with-firings-privatization-state-firms-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDWHKVQDYZILXMPMXXVTEU7UFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 07:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国电动汽车产量将大幅增长，在伤痕累累的市场上引发价格战]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家表示，中国汽车制造商在当地的产量激增，泰国正准备应对由此引发的电动汽车价格战，此举很可能会进一步打击本已因销量下滑而举步维艰的国内汽车业。【原文：Thailand is bracing for an extended EV price war triggered by a surge in local production from Chinese car makers, a move likely to deal a further blow to a domestic auto industry already struggling with tumbling sales, industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/thai-ev-output-set-jump-sparking-price-war-bruised-market-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6T2AJJRGVZISHMDE5HDUCF2IBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepSeek 大跌中闪烁红色市场信号的五张图表]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，人工智能芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）遭遇了有史以来最大的单日价值损失，美联储也表示不急于再次降息。【原文：In a week when AI chipmaker Nvidia suffered the biggest one-day loss of value on record and the Federal Reserve said it was in no hurry to cut rates again, a few gauges underscore markets' vulnerability to big swings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-positioning-graphic-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EMO2ZE6FFMSFNTZFP25I2UJDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:17:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华第四季度盈利大幅超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺华周五公布的季度调整后净收入远高于分析师的预期，原因是心力衰竭治疗药物 Entresto 和多发性硬化症治疗药物 Kesimpta 的销售额超出预期。【原文：Novartis on Friday posted quarterly adjusted net income well above analyst estimates on forecast-beating sales of established heart failure drug Entresto and multiple sclerosis drug Kesimpta.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-beats-consensus-q4-earnings-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QASRS6PKKVMB5EQVTOVZQC47IQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:14:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[除了美联储，特朗普正从所有人那里获得他要求的更低利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）正如愿以偿地在全球范围内降低利率，但在美国国内却并非如此，强劲的经济和对其自身政策的不确定性为美联储与其他央行的分歧埋下了伏笔。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is getting his wish that interest rates drop across the world, just not at home where a strong economy and uncertainty over his own policies have set the stage for the Federal Reserve to diverge from its central bank peers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/trump-is-getting-lower-interest-rates-he-demanded-everyone-fed-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIWJTTR3BFM5VJ7AY2W3MYYF4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:13:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列初创企业在战争中发挥关键作用后制定全球计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，去年 10 月追踪哈马斯领导人叶海亚-辛瓦尔（Yahya Sinwar）并拍摄他奄奄一息画面的无人机是由以色列初创公司 Xtend 制造的。【原文：The drone that tracked Hamas leader Yahya Sinwar and filmed him as he lay dying in footage beamed around the world last October was made by Israeli startup Xtend, according to media reports, one of many such firms to get a boost from Israel's war needs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-startups-make-global-plans-after-key-role-war-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIDPKXIDXBPA3PELPXIPTMWA7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 06:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道日本权衡阿拉斯加液化天然气管道承诺以赢得特朗普青睐]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉内情的官员透露，日本正在考虑为阿拉斯加一条价值 440 亿美元的天然气管道提供支持，以讨好美国总统唐纳德-特朗普并防止潜在的贸易摩擦。【原文：Japan is considering offering support for a $44 billion gas pipeline in Alaska as it seeks to court U.S. President Donald Trump and forestall potential trade friction, according to three officials familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/japan-weighs-alaska-lng-pipeline-pledge-win-trumps-favour-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LZDU53GZJKWPLPEUBY5G4MOEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 05:28:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国隐私监管机构将询问 DeepSeek 个人信息使用情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国信息隐私监管机构的一位官员周五表示，该机构计划向 DeepSeek 询问如何管理用户的个人信息。【原文：South Korea's information privacy watchdog plans to ask DeepSeek about how the personal information of users is managed, an agency official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/south-korea-privacy-watchdog-ask-deepseek-about-personal-information-use-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74JAYK55SFO27E75AER6L5ZGN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 04:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Graphika 称，中国与国家有关的账户在美股暴跌前大肆宣传 DeepSeek 人工智能的发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[据在线分析公司Graphika称，上周，在这一消息导致美国科技股暴跌的前几天，与中国国家有关的社交媒体账户放大了庆祝中国初创公司DeepSeek推出人工智能模型的言论。【原文：Chinese state-linked social media accounts amplified narratives celebrating the launch of Chinese startup DeepSeek's AI models last week, days before the news tanked U.S. tech stocks, according to online analysis firm Graphika.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinese-state-linked-accounts-hyped-deepseek-ai-launch-ahead-us-stock-rout-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5UWRMYCKZLOZFBL32Z3EVLJGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 03:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次威胁征收关税以阻止金砖国家取代美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四重申了他在赢得 11 月总统大选数周后发出的 100% 关税威胁，警告金砖国家不要取代美元作为储备货币。【原文：President Donald Trump on Thursday warned off BRICS member countries from replacing the U.S. dollar as a reserve currency by repeating a 100%-tariffs threat he had made weeks after winning the November presidential elections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/trump-repeats-tariffs-threat-dissuade-brics-nations-replacing-us-dollar-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBPRNFSHWRJ3ZDEE7QOPO4MA3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:48:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产表示，日产和本田将于 2 月中旬宣布可能的整合方向]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车公司发言人周五表示，该公司将争取在 2 月中旬之前宣布与本田汽车公司可能进行的整合方向，从而将该计划从 1 月底推后。【原文：Nissan Motor will aim to announce the direction of its possible integration with Honda Motor by mid-February, a company spokesperson said on Friday, pushing back the plan from the end of January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nissan-honda-announce-direction-possible-integration-by-mid-feb-nissan-says-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CCSWLH6OBOHRA3EFVL6DHUDLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:08:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价在美国关税威胁下上涨，但仍将出现周跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁对墨西哥和加拿大这两个美国最大的原油出口国征收关税，并可能于本周末生效，市场权衡利弊后，周五油价上涨。【原文：Oil prices rose on Friday as markets weigh the threat of tariffs by U.S. President Donald Trump on Mexico and Canada, the two largest crude exporters to the U.S., that could take effect this weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-rise-amid-us-tariff-threat-still-set-weekly-loss-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UN4QBTCUDFJT3JJE277P3Z24MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国正在调查 DeepSeek 是否使用了受限制的人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉此事的人士说，美国商务部正在调查 DeepSeek（其人工智能模型的性能震撼了科技界的中国公司）是否一直在使用不允许运往中国的美国芯片。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department is looking into whether DeepSeek - the Chinese company whose AI model's performance rocked the tech world - has been using U.S. chips that are not allowed to be shipped to China, a person familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-looking-into-whether-deepseek-used-restricted-ai-chips-source-says-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRV35PXOSBOX7LMLJRRNYSYWNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利率走势分化，日元将在 1 月份创七年来最佳表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周五，日元有望创下2018年以来的最佳月度开局，这得益于日本央行（BOJ）今年可能继续加息，而全球其他地区的同行则寻求放宽政策的观点。【原文：The yen was on track for its best monthly start to the year since 2018 on Friday, helped by the view that the Bank of Japan (BOJ) is likely to keep raising rates this year while its global peers elsewhere look to ease policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yen-set-best-january-seven-years-rates-path-diverge-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VLO653MG5KQHGCQN6DIFOATIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 01:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[好市多将把大多数美国商店员工的时薪提高到 30 美元以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据本周发给员工的一份备忘录，零售商好市多批发公司（Costco Wholesale）将把大部分美国商店小时工的工资提高到 30 美元以上。【原文：Retailer Costco Wholesale will increase pay for most of its hourly U.S. store workers to more than $30, according to a memo sent to employees this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/costco-raise-hourly-pay-most-us-store-workers-over-30-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6H4RB2VY5NUHJP7LTBLCVX7DE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:59:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nationwide 将以 12.5 亿美元收购 Allstate 的止损保险业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国保险公司 Nationwide 周四表示，它将以 12.5 亿美元的价格收购财产和意外保险公司 Allstate Corp 的雇主止损险部门，以扩大其止损险产品。【原文：U.S. insurer Nationwide said on Thursday that it would acquire property and casualty insurer Allstate Corp's employer stop-loss segment in a $1.25 billion deal, as it seeks to expand its stop-loss insurance offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nationwide-acquire-allstates-stop-loss-insurance-business-125-billion-deal-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CROQX5ITJJO7JIS4OA7WT4W2IE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片业务疲软，三星第一季度盈利增长有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子（Samsung Electronics）周五表示，由于存储芯片业务状况疲软，预计第一季度盈利增长有限，公司将继续努力向 Nvidia 公司提供高端芯片。【原文：Samsung Electronics said on Friday it expected limited first-quarter earnings growth due to weak memory chip business conditions, as it continues to work towards providing high-end chips to Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-q4-profit-growth-slows-chip-issues-weigh-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOIL2PLWO5I6LMWVHPNKZ3CXKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PPG 工业公司第四季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于工业和建筑涂料产品需求下降以及价格疲软，PPG 工业公司周四未能达到华尔街对其第四季度利润的预期。【原文：PPG Industries missed Wall Street's fourth-quarter profit expectations on Thursday, due to lower demand for its industrial and architectural coatings products and weak prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ppg-industries-misses-estimates-fourth-quarter-profit-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6G7EZGLYBIOLGH3OQ3HTPD7IM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:44:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚阿尔戈斯集团 2024 年利润增长两倍多]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚阿尔戈斯集团（Grupo Argos）周四在一份声明中宣布，该集团 2024 年的净利润增长了 221%，达到 2.53 万亿比索（约合 6.09 亿美元）。【原文：Colombia's Grupo Argos reported a 221% increase in net profit in 2024 to 2.53 trillion pesos ($609 million), the conglomerate announced in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/colombias-grupo-argos-more-than-triples-profit-2024-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUBO7M4ASVPNVOZIT44PVCCG6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普重申关税威胁，墨西哥比索下跌 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普重申威胁要对墨西哥和加拿大这两个最大的贸易伙伴征收 25% 的关税之后，墨西哥比索兑美元汇率在周四的一个波动交易时段下跌了 1%。【原文：The Mexican peso fell 1% against the dollar in a volatile session on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump reiterated his threat to impose 25% tariffs on Mexico and Canada, two of its top trade partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/mexican-peso-drops-1-trump-reiterates-tariff-threat-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQISMRGJWNOLVPFITAU6YP76K4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局称信息技术问题导致边疆航空公司航班短暂停飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国联邦航空管理局发布的公告，边疆航空公司（Frontier Airlines）的信息技术问题导致该公司所有目的地在周四晚间短暂停飞。【原文：IT issues at Frontier Airlines triggered a brief ground stop at all of the U.S. budget carrier's destinations on Thursday evening, according to an advisory from the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/it-issues-trigger-brief-ground-stop-frontier-airlines-flights-us-faa-says-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INUVWT5UTVLEZCDAN3LHUQMA5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:18:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税不确定性推动避险黄金创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[地缘政治的不确定性和美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关税计划引发的对全球经济增长的担忧所导致的避险需求将金价推向了历史新高，再次将3000美元的关键门槛推向了投资者的视线。【原文：Safe-haven demand due to geopolitical uncertainties and concerns over global economic growth amid U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff plans have hoisted gold prices to a record high, once again bringing the key $3,000 threshold onto investors' radar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-tariff-uncertainties-push-safe-haven-gold-record-high-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRT7ISUW3JMQLEREPEVLFPABHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[资源匮乏的日本正准备迎接人工智能能源的激增。DeepSeek 提高了赌注。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在日本披露了一项具有里程碑意义的能源计划的细节（该计划的部分目的是应对预期的人工智能激增）几周后，中国初创公司 DeepSeek 的崛起颠覆了人们对该行业未来电力需求的传统看法。【原文：Weeks after Japan revealed details of a landmark energy plan partly designed to keep up with an expected AI surge, the shock rise of Chinese startup DeepSeek has upended conventional wisdom over the sector's future power demands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/resource-poor-japan-was-girding-an-ai-energy-surge-deepseek-raised-stakes-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQ2OEOMW6JPM5M4NKM7RIGXVIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管壳牌注销，大西洋海岸仍重申对新泽西州海上风电的承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，壳牌公司（Shell Plc）和法国电力公司（EDF）的合资企业大西洋海岸公司（Atlantic Shores）重申了其交付新泽西州首个海上风电项目的承诺，尽管壳牌公司最近对该合资企业进行了 10 亿美元的注销。【原文：Atlantic Shores, a joint venture between Shell Plc and France's EDF, reiterated its commitment to delivering New Jersey's first offshore wind project on Thursday, despite Shell's recent $1 billion write-off related to the venture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/atlantic-shores-reaffirms-commitment-new-jersey-offshore-wind-despite-shells-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5H4VM2DQ7NMKXEENYADNMURWUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 22:46:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁交易受阻，美国钢铁公司季度业绩低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）周四公布的第四季度财报显示，受价格下跌和需求环境不稳定的影响，该公司第四季度的亏损和收入均低于华尔街的预期。【原文：U.S. Steel reported fourth-quarter loss and revenue that matched Wall Street estimates on Thursday, dented by price declines and a bumpy demand environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-steel-posts-muted-quarterly-results-amid-nippon-deal-snag-2025-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHCU7Q27INI3TP7RDVX3NRD7GU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 22:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>