<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:33:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:33:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资级信用风险指数创 2023 年 11 月以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国全面征收关税引发的市场动荡中，作为信用风险指标的一篮子信用违约掉期的Markit CDX北美投资级指数周四扩大至2023年11月以来的最高点。【原文：The Markit CDX North American Investment Grade Index , a basket of credit default swaps that serves as a gauge of credit risk, widened to its highest since November 2023 on Thursday amid market turmoil fueled by U.S. sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-tariffs-credit-urgent-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7MXYBH2HFMXJE7VY6ACSAP4LA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:23:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股票多空对冲基金在市场下跌中抹去了年内收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府宣布全面征收关税后，股市暴跌，全球股票多空对冲基金周四抹去了今年以来的涨幅。【原文：Global equity long/short hedge funds erased their gains for the year on Thursday as stocks plunged after the Trump administration announced sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/equity-longshort-hedge-funds-wipe-out-year-gains-market-rout-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z2SUZ7B5KZJ35GYNPRUR23X35I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:17:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔与台积电初步同意组建芯片制造合资企业，信息报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《信息时报》周四援引两位参与部分讨论的人士的话报道，英特尔公司和台湾半导体制造股份有限公司的高管最近达成了一项初步协议，将组建一家合资企业来运营这家美国公司的芯片制造设施。【原文：Executives from Intel and Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co recently reached a preliminary agreement to form a joint venture to operate the U.S. firm's chipmaking facilities, the Information reported on Thursday, citing two people involved in some of the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-tsmc-tentatively-agree-form-chipmaking-joint-venture-information-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRQD7EDIGFJDJBCJ5YQYHEFNMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准安进公司的 Uplizna 首次用于治疗罕见免疫性疾病]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四表示，该局已批准扩大安进公司药物Uplizna的使用范围，以帮助降低一种罕见的免疫系统相关疾病患者的复发风险。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has approved expanded use of Amgen's drug, Uplizna, to help reduce the risk of flares in patients with a rare immune system-related condition, the regulator said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-expanded-use-amgens-rare-disease-drug-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIMOP3CXR5KKDJBPG3BV3MQTNY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:49:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储库克表示，在高度不确定的情况下，美联储是时候观察数据了]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）周四表示，在高度不确定性的情况下，央行现在应该慢慢观察数据的变化，然后再改变货币政策的设定。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook said Thursday that amid high levels of uncertainty now is a time for the central bank to take its time to watch how the data comes in before it changes the setting of monetary policy again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-cook-says-amid-high-uncertainty-time-fed-watch-data-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNNEL7SUPBN2BLP6LFFAD7EFQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:33:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 NTSB 敦促 FAA 要求对波音 757 飞机门闩进行检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会周四敦促联邦航空管理局要求航空公司在2023年田纳西州联邦快递一架航班紧急撤离后检查波音757飞机舱门的锁扣，并在必要时进行更换。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board on Thursday urged the Federal Aviation Administration to require airlines to inspect latches on Boeing 757 airplane doors after a 2023 emergency evacuation of a FedEx flight in Tennessee, and to replace them if needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-ntsb-urges-faa-require-boeing-757-airplane-door-latch-inspections-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUAKBJUOB5PZLBXJYZN2LPRDNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛：美国关税威胁冲击经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）警告说，美国全面征收关税将拖累全球经济增长，并促使美联储比之前预期的更积极地降息。【原文：Goldman Sachs warned sweeping U.S. tariffs will weigh on global growth and prompt the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates more aggressively than previously expected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-tariffs-threaten-growth-shock-goldman-sachs-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NM3LSU2QMJI65C464BZTDLZQZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咖啡进口税对已经面临高价的美国烘焙商造成压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[自殖民时代以来，美国首次对咖啡进口征收关税，这将增加进口商和烘焙商的成本和复杂性，而他们已经在应对接近创纪录的价格。【原文：The first U.S. tariffs on coffee imports since colonial times will increase costs and complexity to importers and roasters already dealing with near-record prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/import-tax-coffee-pressures-us-roasters-already-facing-high-prices-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXHWALHZE5L5HFFTICND2YXMCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资者对关税深度措手不及，将面临更多痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三宣布全面征收新关税，投资者对此早有心理准备，但许多人表示，现在的情况是市场最坏的情况。他们的信息是系好安全带，做好心理准备。【原文：Investors had been prepared for a shock heading in to U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of sweeping new tariffs on Wednesday, but many said that what played out was the worst-case-scenario for markets. Their message: Buckle up and brace yourself.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-tariffs-funds-pix-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BH42JSVWXVNUHMMLTR7R7NV53U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉下调西南航空公司评级至负面]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周四将西南航空公司的评级展望从之前的 "稳定 "下调至 "负面"，理由是该航空公司可能会转向不太保守的资本分配和财务政策。【原文：Fitch Ratings on Thursday downgraded Southwest Airlines to a "negative" outlook from its earlier "stable" rating, citing the carrier's possible shift to a less conservative capital allocation and financial policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-downgrades-southwest-airlines-outlook-negative-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIWXYEPN4RNA5F6FZUPRROSBSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，Capital One 以 350 亿美元收购 Discover 的交易通过了美国司法部的审核]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周四报道，Capital One 金融公司收购发现金融服务公司（Discover Financial Services）的提议获得了美国司法部的批准，因为司法部告诉其他负责调查该并购案的监管机构，它认为没有足够的竞争问题来阻止该交易。【原文：Capital One Financial Corp got a greenlight from the Justice Department for its proposed acquisition of Discover Financial Services after the DOJ told other regulators looking into the merger that it doesn't see sufficient competition concerns to block the deal, the New York Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/capital-ones-35-billion-deal-discover-clears-us-doj-hurdle-nyt-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4U7UDXMSXNIDFLRN36PH5CZAO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:51:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嗨得更高特朗普关税将提高美国大麻价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[考虑通过吸烟来摆脱关税阴霾？再想想吧。【原文：Contemplating smoking your way out of the tariff gloom? Think again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/high-just-got-higher-trump-tariffs-raise-prices-us-cannabis-users-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGVU4NSZMJMNBEZVKKQWBOXZJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亨特公司番茄生产商 Conagra 首席执行官表示，可能会提高价格以抵消关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chef Boyardee生产商Conagra Brands首席执行官肖恩-康诺利（Sean Connolly）周四表示，Conagra Brands可能不得不提高价格，以抵消对可可、橄榄油、棕榈油和一种用于罐头食品的钢材等原料征收关税的成本。【原文：Chef Boyardee maker Conagra Brands may have to hike prices to offset the cost of tariffs on ingredients like cocoa, olive oil, palm oil and a type of steel used for its canned food products, CEO Sean Connolly said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hunts-tomato-maker-conagra-may-hike-prices-offset-tariffs-ceo-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4DEH4BPM5MRHE5HZDK7ZDZP3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西枪支制造商金牛座认为美国工厂是最大限度减少关税冲击的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西枪支制造商金牛座阿玛斯公司首席执行官 Salesio Nuhs 告诉路透社，该公司在美国的生产线有望帮助其最大限度地减少美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三征收关税的影响。【原文：Brazilian gunmaker Taurus Armas expects its production line in the United States to help it minimize the impact of tariffs imposed on Wednesday by U.S. President Donald Trump, its chief executive Salesio Nuhs told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-gunmaker-taurus-sees-us-plant-key-minimizing-tariff-hit-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q57HHJSSVZIFPHJTHTYT3CXSWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税豁免降低了纽约贵金属相对伦敦的溢价]]></title><description><![CDATA[在华盛顿将贵金属排除在美国广泛的进口关税之外，缓解了继续向美国空运贵金属的刺激之后，最活跃的Comex贵金属期货周四降低了对伦敦现货价格的溢价。【原文：The most active Comex futures for precious metals reduced their premium over the London spot prices on Thursday after Washington excluded the metals from broad U.S. import tariffs, easing stimulus to continue flying them to the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/exclusion-trumps-tariffs-reduces-premium-new-york-precious-metals-over-london-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5YLOCF2WFNVJKQMTY62R667FY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:10:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的全球贸易战可能使美国对华战略目标落空]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府在上任后的头几个月里，已采取行动阻止中国威胁其邻国，并表示美国将加强其在印度洋-太平洋地区的军事存在，为台湾提供更多支持。【原文：In its first months, U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has moved to deter China from threatening its neighbors, signalling that the U.S. will ramp up its military presence in the Indo-Pacific and offer more support to Taiwan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trumps-global-trade-war-may-defeat-us-strategic-goals-china-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBJF5T7YNZKWFFROXMQLBVEBUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士抨击美国关税，就下一步行动与欧盟保持密切联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政府周四称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对瑞士征收贸易关税是不可理解的，并誓言将与欧盟就如何处理此事保持密切沟通。【原文：Switzerland's government on Thursday described trade tariffs imposed on the country by U.S. President Donald Trump as incomprehensible, and vowed to stay in close communication with the European Union on how they proceed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/switzerland-slams-us-tariffs-stays-close-eu-over-next-steps-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EINIYLOOZ5J5NE3B2ONMFEYLZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:01:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普加征关税后，通用汽车将增加美国卡车产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一份发给工厂员工的网络广播称，通用汽车公司正在增加印第安纳州韦恩堡装配厂的轻型卡车产量。【原文：General Motors is moving to increase production of light-duty trucks out of its Fort Wayne, Indiana, assembly plant, according to a webcast sent to plant employees and obtained by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-increase-us-truck-production-following-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BF52MBZT2BNLDEHXMDUAV2W3SY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:48:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，欧盟国家考虑改变 2025 年天然气储存目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟外交官告诉路透社记者，欧盟各国正在谈判对未来欧盟天然气储存目标的修改，如果能尽快获得批准，也会软化今年具有约束力的储气充装要求。【原文：Changes to future EU gas storage targets being negotiated by European Union countries could, if approved quickly enough, also soften this year's binding storage-filling requirements, EU diplomats told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eu-countries-consider-changing-2025-gas-storage-targets-sources-say-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2BUO7PFZFLRXMRMJGKD4EXGVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:40:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世贸组织称关税可能导致全球商品贸易量萎缩 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织总干事表示，美国宣布的新关税以及今年年初开始实施的新关税可能导致 2025 年全球商品贸易量萎缩约 1%。【原文：The Director-General of the World Trade Organization said new tariffs announced by the U.S. along with those introduced at the start of the year could lead to a contraction of around 1% in global merchandise trade volumes in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wto-says-tariffs-could-bring-contraction-1-global-merchandise-trade-volumes-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LRA5YE5L55MSFPJE6Z3U3EQ7DA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官裁定，多家公司必须面对有毒婴儿食品诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官称，包括沃尔玛、山毛榉坚果和嘉宝（Gerber）在内的几家公司必须面对一项全国性诉讼，该诉讼声称有毒重金属污染了他们的婴儿食品，对食用这些食品的儿童的大脑和神经发育造成了损害。【原文：A U.S. judge said several companies including Walmart , Beech-Nut and Gerber must face a nationwide lawsuit claiming that toxic heavy metals contaminated their baby food, causing brain and neurodevelopmental damage to children who ate it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/several-companies-must-face-lawsuit-over-tainted-baby-food-us-judge-rules-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YFHCHMASRN4ZGYAPEDS4NPZPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国计划在能源部土地上开发人工智能项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周四表示，已在美国能源部的土地上确定了 16 个潜在地点，可在这些地点开发数据中心和发电厂，以支持人工智能的蓬勃发展。【原文：The administration of President Donald Trump said on Thursday it has identified 16 potential sites on U.S. Energy Department lands where data centers and power plants to support the boom in artificial intelligence can be developed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/us-plans-develop-ai-projects-energy-department-lands-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HA3WVKP6M5NPLD5PYV2QPPOWEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:32:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰斐逊不急于调整利率，政策定位良好]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储副主席菲利普-杰斐逊（Philip Jefferson）周四表示，由于美国经济状况稳健，关税已经推高了商品通胀，而且前景的不确定性也高于往常，他倾向于将政策利率维持在目前的适度限制水平，同时密切关注就业和物价的下一步走势。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson on Thursday said that with the U.S. economy in solid shape, tariffs already pushing upward on goods inflation, and higher than usual uncertainty over the outlook, he is inclined to leave the policy rate at its currently modestly restrictive level while keeping a close eye on what happens next with jobs and prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-jefferson-no-hurry-adjust-rates-policy-well-positioned-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFRSTMNN2RNZZDMZRZYQ5MK2MM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:31:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税会让苹果 iPhone 更贵吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于关税的原因，您最喜爱的 iPhone 很快就会变得更加昂贵。【原文：Your favorite iPhone could soon become pricier, thanks to tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/will-trump-tariffs-make-apple-iphones-more-expensive-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTQVH36SVJI4LHMM32C6DAVBLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税可能阻碍大科技公司在美国数据中心的投资热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析人士周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全面互惠关税可能会阻碍大科技公司（Big Tech）斥资数十亿美元在美国建设人工智能基础设施的努力，这很可能会破坏美国政府的一个关键目标。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping reciprocal tariffs could hamstring Big Tech's billion-dollar efforts to build artificial intelligence infrastructure in the country, likely undermining a key goal of the administration, analysts said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-tariffs-could-stymie-big-techs-us-data-center-spending-spree-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQLLVWDBCNLDPASU6QZ6M3GXCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士钟表业看到特朗普关税带来的严峻考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士钟表销售商萨沙-大卫杜夫（Sacha Davidoff）周四忙于了解美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布的美国对瑞士征收的新关税对他本周将从其位于日内瓦的商店出口的商品意味着什么。【原文：Swiss watch seller Sacha Davidoff was scrambling on Thursday to understand what new U.S. tariffs on Switzerland announced by President Donald Trump meant for the goods he was due to export from his shop in Geneva this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/swiss-watch-industry-sees-tough-times-ahead-over-trump-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ST5JKGIHMVM3DO4D5VZDLCSDTE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税之后，美国悬赏数十亿美元投资刚果矿产]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的非洲事务高级顾问周四在访问刚果时表示，美国正在商谈向矿产资源丰富的刚果投资数十亿美元，并希望帮助结束该国东部肆虐的冲突。【原文：The United States is in talks to invest billions of dollars in mineral-rich Congo and wants to help end a conflict raging in the country's east, President Donald Trump's senior adviser for Africa said during a visit on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/after-tariffs-us-dangles-billions-dollars-congo-mineral-investment-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2XZLDJGNNMPHF4UJ2QYZWUYGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:01:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济学家称巴西可能成为美国全面关税的赢家]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家周四表示，尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对巴西出口到美国的商品征收10%的关税，但美国的全面关税可能会对巴西这个拉丁美洲最大的经济体相对有利。【原文：Sweeping U.S. tariffs could prove relatively advantageous for Brazil, Latin America's largest economy, despite President Donald Trump's move to impose a 10% levy on its exports to the United States, economists said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-may-emerge-winner-sweeping-us-tariffs-economists-say-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHQYYYWGN5JHLNWYXNMOUZICXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国总统马克龙呼吁在征收关税后暂停对美投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对美国进口商品全面征收全球关税后，法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙周四呼吁欧洲企业暂停在美国的投资计划。【原文：French President Emmanuel Macron called on Thursday for European companies to suspend planned investment in the United States after U.S. President Donald Trump announced sweeping global tariffs on American imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/frances-macron-calls-suspension-investment-us-after-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUWKQKP7NZM7VARBLEYG2LYUFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡尼表示，加拿大将对不符合 USMCA 协议的美国汽车征收 25% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）在周四的新闻发布会上表示，加拿大将对所有不符合美墨加贸易协定的美国进口汽车征收25%的关税。【原文：Canada will impose a 25% tariff on all vehicles imported from the United States that are not compliant with the U.S.-Mexico-Canada trade deal, Prime Minister Mark Carney told a press conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-impose-25-tariffs-us-autos-that-are-non-compliant-with-usmca-says-carney-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKSILEXD5ZOOBJGKKBRACZGHUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:46:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>