<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 09:04:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 09:04:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国称美国 PVH 公司从事与新疆有关的 "不当 "行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周四表示，初步调查结果显示，Calvin Klein 和 Tommy Hilfiger 的母公司 PVH Corp 在新疆地区有 "不当 "行为，但未作详细说明。【原文：Preliminary findings showed that PVH Corp , the parent company of Calvin Klein and Tommy Hilfiger, engaged in "improper" conduct related to the Xinjiang region, China's commerce ministry said on Thursday, without elaborating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/china-says-us-firm-pvh-engaged-improper-conduct-related-xinjiang-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3E3LTERI65JULPL4JNZAK76K3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 08:54:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gartner 在报告中称，2025 年欧洲和北美的汽车工厂将面临关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究与咨询公司 Gartner 周四在一份报告中说，随着汽车品牌在产能过剩和价格竞争中挣扎，今年欧洲和北美的几家汽车厂面临关闭或出售的风险。【原文：Several European and North American car factories are at risk of being closed or sold this year as automobile brands struggle with overcapacity and price competition, research and advisory firm Gartner said in a report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/car-plants-europe-n-america-face-closures-2025-gartner-says-report-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NW44BBNLNNNPXFXEJGJFOQMZW4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 08:35:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 第四季度发货量同比下降 9]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 公司周四表示，其第四季度汽车出货量为 139.5 万辆，同比下降了 9%。【原文：Stellantis' said on Thursday its fourth quarter shipments were down 9% compared to the previous year, to 1.395 million vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-fourth-quarter-shipments-fall-9-yy-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7KKVUSCBNIFJHKIRYBSZ7L56U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 06:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok和其他5家中国公司遭欧盟隐私投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 、Shein、小米和其他三家中国公司在奥地利权益组织 Noyb 周四提交的一份隐私投诉中被点名，该投诉称这些公司非法向中国发送欧盟用户数据。【原文：TikTok, Shein, Xiaomi and three other Chinese companies were named in a privacy complaint filed on Thursday by Austrian advocacy group Noyb which claimed the firms were unlawfully sending European Union user data to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-5-other-chinese-firms-hit-by-eu-privacy-complaints-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKXJUV26EZJJTLV4ZFYP3HIHQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 06:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡地亚所有者历峰集团第三季度销售额增长 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡地亚珠宝公司历峰集团（Richemont）周四报告称，截至 12 月底的三个月内，固定汇率销售额增长了 10%，这是欧洲奢侈品公司在最重要的假日季表现的一个强有力的先行指标。【原文：Cartier jewellery owner Richemont on Thursday reported a 10% increase in constant currency sales during the three months to the end of December, a strong early indicator for the performance of European luxury companies over the all-important holiday season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/cartier-owner-richemont-posts-10-increase-q3-sales-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUJES5RVSBI75AMWT3UPIOQYVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 06:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦敦凋零的 AIM 市场今年将失去更多会员]]></title><description><![CDATA[AIM 公司的银行家和财务顾问告诉路透社，即使英国决策者试图重振该国的资本市场，进入 2025 年后，伦敦另类投资（AIM）市场的公司外流速度仍将加快。【原文：An exodus of companies from London's Alternative Investment (AIM) market is set to accelerate into 2025, even as Britain's policymakers try to revive the country's capital markets, bankers and financial advisers to AIM companies told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/londons-withering-aim-market-set-lose-more-members-this-year-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J54YXUD77FNCFDJTILQLYH6QXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 06:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺 2024 年销量增长 1.3%，混合动力车功不可没]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国汽车制造商雷诺（Renault）周四表示，2024 年的销量增长了 1.3%，第四季度在新产品上市的推动下表现强劲，帮助抵消了年初的需求疲软。【原文：French automaker Renault said on Thursday that sales grew by 1.3% in 2024, with a strong fourth quarter driven by new launches helping to offset weak demand earlier in the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-2024-sales-volumes-grow-13-helped-by-hybrids-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22VCN5NKMFMB7JIC6IWO5INAH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 06:01:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普财政部长人选贝森特就税收、贸易和赤字问题接受参议院质询]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的财政部长人选、对冲基金经理斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）誓言要维持美元作为世界储备货币的地位，因为他准备在周四面对美国参议员就如何实施特朗普的减税、关税和放松管制计划提出的问题。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's pick for Treasury secretary, hedge fund manager Scott Bessent, vowed to maintain the dollar's status as the world's reserve currency as he prepared to face questions from U.S. senators on Thursday on how he will implement Trump's tax cut, tariff and deregulation plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-treasury-pick-bessent-faces-senate-grilling-taxes-trade-deficits-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5ZYEL7EY5LYFDLYEO3LIWX5KE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 05:51:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美国通胀趋缓，市场稍感宽慰]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYOWIV5UIFPHREQHRC5XKCO4QM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 05:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第四季度利润增长 57%，创历史新高，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾芯片制造商台积电周四表示，第四季度净利润增长 57%，创下历史新高，符合预期，原因是受益于人工智能处理所用半导体需求的激增。【原文：Taiwanese chipmaker TSMC said fourth-quarter net profit rose 57% to a record on Thursday, in line with expectations, as it benefits from surging demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence processing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmcs-q4-profit-rises-57-record-line-with-forecast-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAH3SEOZKRNJXLRBLI7DBLMTLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 05:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称中国买家对德国大众无用工厂感兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位了解中国政府想法的人士告诉路透社，中国官员和汽车制造商正在关注即将关闭的德国工厂，尤其对大众汽车的厂址感兴趣。【原文：Chinese officials and automakers are eyeing German factories slated for closure and are particularly interested in Volkswagen's sites , a person with knowledge of Chinese government thinking told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-buyers-interested-unwanted-german-volkswagen-factories-source-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MSCVMUTIZLC5GTPINCEZITYBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 05:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，TikTok 首席执行官计划出席特朗普就职典礼]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周三援引两位熟悉该计划的人士的话报道，TikTok 的首席执行官计划出席美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的就职典礼。【原文：The chief executive of TikTok plans to attend U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's inauguration, the New York Times reported on Wednesday, citing two people familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-ceo-plans-attend-trump-inauguration-nyt-reports-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NEG3OYCYWNNI7FAREAF27VGF5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 04:44:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[REDD 报道：在市场低迷之际，中国万科没有延长债券期限的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据财经媒体 REDD 援引两位知情人士的话报道，房地产开发商中国万科周三告诉一些投资者，在市场抛售之际，该公司没有计划延长债券期限。【原文：Property developer China Vanke told some investors on Wednesday that it had no plans to extend its bonds amid a market sell-off, financial news outlet REDD reported, citing two persons briefed by the company on the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-vanke-has-no-plans-extend-bonds-amid-market-slump-redd-reports-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UABFEVZG4JLEDOFKSFSPYUMQHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 04:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将于 3 月底加息，多数分析师倾向于 1 月加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查的绝大多数经济学家表示，日本央行将在本季度的两次会议中的一次会议上再次加息至 0.50%，大多数人倾向于在 1 月份加息。【原文：The Bank of Japan will raise interest rates again at one of the two meetings this quarter to 0.50%, an overwhelming majority of economists surveyed by Reuters said, with most leaning toward a January move.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/boj-raise-rates-by-end-march-most-analysts-lean-toward-january-hike-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVSG2NWF5VKRTOT4K3LJXJ7AQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 04:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据美国全国广播公司（NBC）报道，随着禁令临近，美国正在权衡让 TikTok 继续运营的方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国全国广播公司（NBC）周三晚些时候援引三位熟悉讨论情况的人士的话报道，拜登政府正在探索如何在禁令将于周日生效的情况下仍能让美国人访问 TikTok。【原文：The Biden administration is exploring ways to keep TikTok accessible in the United States even as a ban is set to take effect on Sunday, NBC News reported late on Wednesday, citing three people familiar with the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-weighs-options-keep-tiktok-operational-ban-nears-nbc-reports-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7D2GAVVVBN27K56QUF5DFFWFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 04:14:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部人选贝森特称美元必须继续作为世界储备货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）选择的财政部负责人斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三在阐述 "新经济黄金时代 "的愿景时，誓言要确保美元继续作为世界储备货币。【原文：Scott Bessent, U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's choice to head the Treasury Department, on Wednesday vowed to ensure that the dollar remains the world's reserve currency as he laid out a vision for a "new economic golden age".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-us-treasury-pick-bessent-says-dollar-must-remain-worlds-reserve-currency-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X42BFZABNJP25AYS7DM6YAZLHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 02:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀缓解打压美元，日元在日本央行会议前上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国通胀数据降温导致债券收益率下降，美元汇率周四下滑至略低于近期高点的水平，而日元则因对日本加息的押注上升而创下一个月来的新高。【原文：The dollar slipped on Thursday to stand just off recent peaks as cooling U.S. inflation data knocked down bond yields, while the yen hit a one-month high on rising bets on a rate hike in Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/us-inflation-relief-dents-dollar-yen-gains-ahead-boj-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LRR4RVC45NNVNP4R4R7ZDFNMEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 02:23:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年新加坡船用燃料枢纽的船用燃料销售额创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[官方数据周三显示，受创纪录的集装箱吞吐量和替代船用燃料交付量增加的推动，全球最大的船用燃料枢纽新加坡的船用燃料销售量在2024年达到新高。【原文：Marine fuel sales reached fresh highs at the world's largest bunker hub of Singapore in 2024, official data showed on Wednesday, driven by record container throughput and higher deliveries of alternative marine fuels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/marine-fuel-sales-singapore-bunker-hub-hit-record-highs-2024-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KKNBPSOOKZNEJIYUHFH7KX2VGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 02:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国库存下降加剧供应担忧，石油上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国原油库存降幅大于预期，加剧了美国对俄罗斯能源贸易制裁引发的供应担忧，油价周四连续第二天上涨。【原文：Oil prices rose for a second day on Thursday after a larger-than-expected decline in U.S. crude oil stockpiles added to supply concerns stoked by U.S. sanctions against Russian energy trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-rises-us-inventory-declines-heighten-supply-concerns-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3Q5QUPXZXFJCJEHP5TFRKWM4SE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 02:14:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷将改革反倾销制度以促进竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷经济部长路易斯-卡普托（Luis Caputo）周三在社交媒体上表示，阿根廷将对本国的反倾销制度进行改革，以促进竞争和降低价格。【原文：Argentina will roll out changes to the country's anti-dumping system in an effort to promote greater competition and bring down prices, Economy Minister Luis Caputo said on social media on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/argentina-reform-anti-dumping-system-boost-competition-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUQIZI77ENLPBBI6Q7QPWASYMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 01:10:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称丰田公司将认罪并支付逾 16 亿美元以了结欺诈计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周三在一份声明中表示，丰田汽车公司的一个部门同意认罪，并在与美国政府机构达成的和解协议中支付超过16亿美元，以解决与排放欺诈计划有关的违规行为。【原文：A Toyota Motor Corp unit agreed to plead guilty and pay over $1.6 billion in a settlement with U.S. government agencies to settle violations related to an emissions fraud scheme, the U.S. Justice Department said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-says-toyota-unit-plead-guilty-pay-over-16-bln-settle-fraud-scheme-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THL6YK425VPVRIVOZ2QWMBDNSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 01:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称特朗普的新税收机构计划不会为纳税人省钱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周三表示，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）计划成立一个新的政府机构来征收关税，这将与现有机构重复，而且不太可能节省开支。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Wednesday U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's plan to set up a new government agency to collect tariffs would duplicate an existing agency and was unlikely to save money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/yellen-says-trumps-plan-new-revenue-agency-wont-save-money-taxpayers-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4K55Y3PNVBNQHD2T2VIJ5Z7LBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canalys 称第四季度中国苹果智能手机出货量下降 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司 Canalys 周四的数据显示，第四季度苹果智能手机在中国的出货量下降了 25%，而华为则增长了 24%。【原文：Apple smartphone shipments in China fell 25% in the fourth quarter, while Huawei's rose 24%, data from research firm Canalys showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-smartphone-shipments-china-fell-25-q4-canalys-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37LIIGVXWROJXOJCFR54SGRFZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:57:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 12 月就业人数超预期，失业率上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于兼职工作激增，澳大利亚 12 月份的就业率超过了预期。【原文：Australian employment sped past forecasts in December thanks to a surge in part-time jobs, though the jobless rate ticked higher as more people went looking for work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-jobs-jump-56300-dec-unemployment-rises-4-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4X5OZBJNLJM7JCE2YSRP3JYJYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:46:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华输掉在美国阻止恩曲斯托仿制药上市的紧急竞标]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿特区的一名联邦法官周三拒绝了诺华公司在第十一小时内提出的阻止制药商 MSN 制药公司推出诺华公司的心脏衰竭特效药 Entresto 的仿制药的请求。【原文：A Washington, D.C. federal judge on Wednesday refused Novartis' eleventh-hour bid to block drugmaker MSN Pharmaceuticals from launching a generic version of Novartis' blockbuster heart-failure drug Entresto.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-loses-emergency-bid-block-entresto-generic-us-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDA346XWVNKMVJD6VS7ZNIQQEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿克曼的潘兴广场公司要求 UMG 将第二上市地迁至美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）周三表示，亿万富翁比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）领导的潘兴广场公司（Pershing Square）已行使权利，要求该唱片公司在美国发行股票并二次上市。【原文：Universal Music Group said on Wednesday that billionaire Bill Ackman-led Pershing Square has exercised its right to request an offering and secondary listing of the record label in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ackmans-pershing-square-requests-umg-move-secondary-listing-us-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJK3R54BINPUTPTSDXCQ72RHUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 23:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称加拿大可能对价值 1,500 亿加元的美国进口商品征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士周三表示，如果美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普对加拿大商品和服务征收关税，加拿大可能会对价值高达1500亿加元的美国进口商品采取反制措施。【原文：Canada could impose countermeasures on up to C$150 billion worth of U.S. imports if President-elect Donald Trump puts tariffs on Canadian goods and services, a source familiar with the matter said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/canada-could-slap-tariffs-c150-billion-worth-us-imports-source-says-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJNF2QG3OFOFJK6SQXJXAY725U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 23:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示：日本企业面临人口老龄化带来的严重劳动力危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项调查显示，由于日本人口持续萎缩并迅速老龄化，三分之二的日本公司正在经受工人短缺对业务造成的严重影响。【原文：Two-thirds of Japanese companies are experiencing a serious business impact from a shortage of workers, a Reuters survey showed on Thursday, as the country's population continues to shrink and age rapidly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/japan-firms-face-serious-labour-crunch-aging-population-survey-shows-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2TX52CNKRKNDPEZG2SEHLRGKA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 23:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bytedance 挥舞 "白旗"，美国 TikTok 用户陷入混乱和绝望]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国 TikTok 用户在得知中国公司字节跳动计划在周日之前关闭其 1.7 亿美国用户使用的应用程序的消息后，失望、否认和困惑涌上心头。【原文：Disappointment, denial and confusion flooded U.S. TikTok on Wednesday upon hearing the news that Chinese owner ByteDance planned to shut off the app for its 170 million U.S. users by Sunday, seemingly throwing in the towel on efforts to keep the popular video-sharing platform going.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-tiktok-users-scramble-despair-bytedance-waves-white-flag-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHRJOKIEAVNV7GMYUA7WJBBKXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 23:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，苹果公司正与巴克莱银行和同步银行谈判，以取代高盛集团的信用卡交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，苹果公司正在与巴克莱银行谈判，以取代高盛成为这家科技巨头的信用卡合作伙伴。【原文：Apple is in talks with Barclays to replace Goldman Sachs as the tech giant's credit card partner, said two sources familiar with the matter, as the Wall Street giant steps back from its consumer finance ambitions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-talks-with-barclays-synchrony-replace-goldman-credit-card-deal-sources-say-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7GVWC573NN6PEXHXQKNYEDZLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 22:55:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>