<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 04:19:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 04:19:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，美国人工智能初创企业融资激增，而更多风险投资基金却举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[PitchBook周二发布的一份报告显示，得益于人工智能的持续繁荣，2025年上半年美国初创企业的融资额激增了75.6%，有望成为有史以来融资额第二高的一年，尽管风险投资公司在融资方面举步维艰。【原文：U.S. startup funding surged 75.6% in the first half of 2025, thanks to the continued AI boom, putting it on track for its second-best year ever, even as venture capital firms struggled to raise money, a report from PitchBook on Tuesday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-ai-startups-see-funding-surge-while-more-vc-funds-struggle-raise-data-shows-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2ZCFVQCPFOEDESTRVTR7MBSEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 04:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计美国 6 月通胀率将随着关税推动的物价上涨而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者价格在 6 月份可能有所回升，这可能标志着人们期待已久的、由关税引发的通胀开始上升，这使得美联储对恢复降息持谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. consumer prices likely picked up in June, potentially marking the start of a long-anticipated, tariff-induced increase in inflation that has left the Federal Reserve cautious about resuming its interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-inflation-expected-rise-june-with-tariff-driven-price-hikes-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K3LXBJAOUBOLDH65QPDMHS27P4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 04:03:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将在印度销售起价为 69,766 美元的 Model Y 汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的特斯拉公司网站上的价格目录显示，其 Model Y 汽车将在印度销售，起价为 600 万卢比。【原文：Elon Musk's Tesla will sell its Model Y cars in India starting at 6 million rupees, a price catalogue on its website showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-sell-model-y-cars-starting-69766-india-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVSOZUJ4ZVKKLHXHGGKUZVKMRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 03:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SpaceX 预计从第四季度开始在越南推出 Starlink 服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南国家媒体周二援引一位政府官员的话称，SpaceX 预计将从今年第四季度开始在越南发射 Starlink 卫星互联网服务。【原文：SpaceX is expected to launch Starlink satellite internet services in Vietnam from the fourth quarter of this year, state media cited a government official as saying on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/spacex-expected-launch-starlink-services-vietnam-fourth-quarter-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSIX6TFD5JMR3EO47TKNJMSMFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 03:15:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电季度利润飙升创纪录，但特朗普关税和外汇问题令人担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[台积电（TSMC）是全球先进人工智能芯片的主要生产商，预计其第二季度利润将增长 52%，达到创纪录水平，但美国关税和强劲的台币汇率可能会对其前景造成影响。【原文：TSMC , the world's main producer of advanced AI chips, is expected to post a 52% jump in second-quarter profit to record levels, though U.S. tariffs and a strong Taiwan dollar could weigh on its outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tsmc-quarterly-profit-seen-soaring-record-trump-tariffs-forex-concern-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRRNEPQ5MNIRTBUDQXRU3Q2NQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 03:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马与 Momenta 合作，共同开发适合中国国情的驾驶辅助技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝马集团周二宣布，将与中国自动驾驶公司 Momenta 合作，专门为中国市场开发先进的辅助驾驶技术。【原文：BMW Group announced on Tuesday that it would join hands with Chinese autonomous driving firm Momenta to develop advanced driving assistance technology specifically for the China market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/bmw-partners-with-momenta-co-develop-china-tailored-driving-assistance-tech-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZAUFMAIANOT5NMBNKUTHRRKOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 02:49:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 中国第二季度 GDP 同比增长 5.2%，高于市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国第二季度经济增速略高于预期，显示出在美国关税面前的韧性，但分析师警告说，不利因素正在加剧，这将增加决策者推出更多刺激措施的压力。【原文：China's economy grew at a slightly faster pace than expected in the second quarter, showing resilience in the face of U.S. tariffs, though analysts warn of intensifying headwinds that will ramp up pressure on policymakers to roll out more stimulus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/view-chinas-q2-gdp-grows-52-yy-above-market-forecast-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQSZPNSFS5J3JFYS3YXPNJZL34</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 02:43:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市上涨，美元在美国财报公布前走强；日本国债收益率飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市攀升，美元保持涨势，原因是贸易谈判仍是本周的焦点，美国通胀和银行盈利的关键数据将在本周公布。【原文：Asian shares climbed and the dollar held gains on Tuesday as trade talks remained in the spotlight in a week that will see key readings on U.S. inflation and bank earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34DBYZDQTZMQRKETY2TX5BOSDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 02:20:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税风险加剧，中国第二季度GDP增速仍超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国经济增长速度略高于预期，显示出在美国关税面前的韧性，但分析师警告说，不利因素正在加剧，这将增加决策者推出更多刺激措施的压力。【原文：China’s economy grew at a slightly faster pace than expected, showing resilience in the face of U.S. tariffs, though analysts warn of intensifying headwinds that will ramp up pressure on policymakers to roll out more stimulus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-q2-gdp-grows-52-yy-above-market-forecast-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2BWIAVDMRLINJWF4DYUHMQJXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 02:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达恢复向北京销售 H20 GPU 芯片，并推出符合中国标准的机型]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周一表示，将恢复向中国销售其 H20 图形处理器（GPU）芯片，并推出了一款为满足中国市场监管要求而定制的新机型。【原文：Nvidia said on Monday that it will resume sales of its H20 graphics processing unit (GPU) chips to China and has introduced a new model tailored to meet regulatory requirements in the Chinese market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-resume-h20-gpu-sales-china-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BKHRBEZ7MRKZBAKLK5QXX7EEVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 01:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 6 月新房价格创 8 个月来最快月度降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的官方数据显示，中国 6 月份新房价格创下 8 个月来最快月度降幅，这凸显出即使在多轮支持政策出台后，政策制定者在重振这一低迷行业的需求方面仍面临挑战。【原文：China's new home prices in June fell at the fastest monthly pace in eight months, official data showed on Tuesday, underscoring the challenges policymakers face in reviving demand in the sluggish sector even after multiple rounds of support policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-new-home-prices-fall-fastest-pace-8-months-june-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4FSHTIJSRKULO7KMQ2AZWFEHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 01:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示：澳大利亚七月消费者乐观情绪受利率意外影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项调查显示，7月份澳大利亚消费者情绪略有改善，但对经济的乐观情绪因央行决定不降息而有所减弱。【原文：A measure of Australian consumer sentiment improved marginally in July, a survey showed on Tuesday, though optimism on the economy was tempered by a central bank decision to skip a cut in interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-july-consumer-optimism-restrained-by-rate-surprise-survey-shows-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGH2RPUAHFLFLLHXWO632UEYWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场考虑潜在制裁和关税，石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场消化了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）要求俄罗斯在50天内结束乌克兰战争并避免对其石油买家实施制裁的最后期限，同时对特朗普贸易关税的担忧继续挥之不去，周二油价略有下跌。【原文：Oil prices edged down on Tuesday as the market digested U.S. President Donald Trump's 50-day deadline for Russia to end the Ukraine war and avoid sanctions on buyers of its oil, while worries continued to linger over Trump's trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-edges-down-market-contemplates-potential-sanctions-tariffs-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMHBDBJ35JPGJFQAIPKVRD6YNI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:21:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大批员工外流后，美国机构缩减裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位人事官员周一表示，在数万名员工接受买断或提前退休以避免被解雇后，特朗普政府将减少联邦工作人员的裁员计划。【原文：The Trump administration will reduce planned federal worker layoffs, a personnel official said on Monday, after tens of thousands of employees accepted buyouts or retired early to avoid dismissal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-agencies-shrink-layoff-plans-after-mass-staff-exodus-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BQCI4PSZ5MIHMAOANG7F3XV4U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国中央电视台称英伟达首席执行官将出席中国供应链博览会]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国中央电视台周二称，英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋将于周三出席中国国际供应链博览会开幕式。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang will attend the opening ceremony of China's international supply chain expo on Wednesday, Chinese state broadcaster CCTV said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-ceo-attend-china-supply-chain-expo-chinas-cctv-says-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKFDS44SDNKTDBG5YZUWTLHGBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:16:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管征收关税，但亚洲传统汽车制造商仍以美国为先]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车和现代汽车可能对美国的保护主义心存芥蒂，但它们与唐纳德-特朗普总统有一个共同点：在全球汽车市场上，亚洲的传统汽车制造商都是美国优先。【原文：Toyota and Hyundai Motor may have a beef with U.S. protectionism, but they have one thing in common with President Donald Trump: when it comes to global car markets, it's America first for Asia's legacy automakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/despite-tariffs-its-still-america-first-asias-legacy-automakers-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZC2I5OJMTVMJREZ2F53GYWYQ2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:58:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚希望取消大部分银行卡支付附加费]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚中央银行周二建议取消对消费者的大部分借记卡和信用卡支付附加费，同时降低企业支付的交换费，这些措施每年将为这两个群体节省约 24 亿澳元（15.7 亿美元）。【原文：Australia's central bank on Tuesday proposed to scrap surcharges on most debit and credit card payments for consumers while lowering interchange fees paid by businesses, steps that would save the two groups around A$2.4 billion ($1.57 billion) a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-looks-scrap-surcharges-most-card-payments-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMSB5EGUCNICDJPS6CTKY2MGOQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究公司称，尽管北美市场举步维艰，但 6 月份全球电动汽车销量仍猛增 24]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场研究公司 Rho Motion 周二表示，由于中国和欧洲向电动汽车转换的势头保持良好，6 月份全球电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车的销量比去年同期猛增 24%。【原文：Global sales of electric and plug-in hybrid vehicles jumped 24% in June from a year ago, as a switch to electric vehicles maintained momentum in China and Europe, market research firm Rho Motion said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-ev-sales-jump-24-june-though-north-american-market-struggles-research-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KC2HHOYRBITXED2GAL6DYR5KE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:11:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税压力增大，中国第二季度经济增速将放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于贸易紧张局势和房地产长期低迷拖累了需求，中国经济在经历了年初的稳健增长后，很可能在第二季度出现降温，从而加大了政策制定者推出额外刺激措施以支撑经济增长的压力。【原文：China's economy is likely to have cooled in the second quarter after a solid start to the year, as trade tensions and a prolonged property downturn drag on demand, raising pressure on policymakers to roll out additional stimulus to underpin growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-economy-set-slow-q2-pressure-us-tariffs-mounts-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5FDSPDBJBIR7CF6LPTYEOSWFY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行称，新西兰老年人的行为将影响利率和资产价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰中央银行在周二发布的一份报告中说，随着人口老龄化，新西兰的储蓄、借贷和投资行为可能会发生变化，从而影响利率、资产价格和对金融产品的需求。【原文：New Zealand’s savings, borrowing and investment behaviour is likely to change as its population ages, affecting interest rates, asset prices and demand for financial products, New Zealand’s central bank said in a report released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/behaviour-aging-new-zealanders-impact-interest-rates-asset-prices-rbnz-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43HNS2ULZRLSLNO6YX2XAP5WII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，洛克希德-马丁公司交付 72 架面临升级延误的 F-35 喷气式战斗机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引五角大楼项目办公室的消息报道，洛克希德-马丁公司已经向美国政府交付了72架F-35喷气式战斗机，截至5月1日，由于软件改进不及时，交付时间推迟了几个月。【原文：Lockheed Martin has delivered 72 F-35 jets to the U.S. government as of May 1, after several months of delay due to late software improvements, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing the Pentagon's program office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-martin-delivers-72-f-35-jets-facing-upgrade-delays-bloomberg-news-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRMF67TQ5NMK7I2Q775VSFZOXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Politico 报道，美联储鲍威尔要求监督机构重新审视翻新项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Politico 周一援引鲍威尔写给立法者的一封信报道，美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）已要求美联储委员会的监察长重新审视旨在彻底改造美联储大楼的项目。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell has asked the Fed board's inspector general to take a fresh look at the project aimed at overhauling Fed buildings, Politico reported on Monday, citing a letter to lawmakers by Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-powell-asks-watchdog-take-fresh-look-renovation-project-politico-reports-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFJH4TULJVNLVDKGB25NXMQDJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 22:46:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对进口无人机和多晶硅展开国家安全调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，已对无人机和相关部件以及太阳能电池板和半导体的关键部件多晶硅的进口展开国家安全调查。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Monday it has opened national security investigations into the import of drones and related components as well as polysilicon, a key component in solar panels and semiconductors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-opens-national-security-probes-into-imported-drones-polysilicon-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJ2LR4Z5HJO6XDMP3LXVWAS6JQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 22:27:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精灵宝可梦 X 账户遭黑客攻击，发布反犹太主义和种族主义信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[儿童电视节目制作者周一表示，黑客侵入了《芝麻街》卡通人物精灵宝可梦的 X 账户，并发布了反犹太主义和种族主义信息。【原文：Hackers broke into the X account of Sesame Street character Elmo and posted antisemitic and racist messages, the makers of the children's TV show said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/elmos-x-account-gets-hacked-posts-antisemitic-racist-messages-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UM3CMV33OJMPFO7JU7ZDUOR7HQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 22:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帝亚吉欧称龙舌兰酒纯度指控 "毫无根据"，美国诉讼仍在继续]]></title><description><![CDATA[帝亚吉欧公司（Diageo）周一对一起指控该烈酒巨头误导美国消费者的诉讼做出了初步回应，称其一些广受欢迎的龙舌兰酒品牌的纯度是 "毫无根据的"。【原文：Diageo on Monday filed an initial response to a lawsuit accusing the spirits giant of misleading U.S. consumers about the purity of some of its popular tequila brands, calling the claim "baseless".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/diageo-calls-tequila-purity-allegation-baseless-us-lawsuit-proceeds-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQKLPKHFXNP23NK36ZTB54P744</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:53:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[万豪财务总监 Leeny Oberg 将于明年退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[万豪国际酒店集团（Marriott International）周一表示，其首席财务官利尼-奥伯格（Leeny Oberg）将于明年退休，他在这家美国酒店运营商工作了二十多年。【原文：Marriott International said on Monday its chief financial officer, Leeny Oberg, would retire next year after spending more than two decades with the U.S. hotel operator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/marriott-finance-chief-leeny-oberg-retire-next-year-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG53ZSTOFJKN3P6GNJ63NRHLFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国退出与墨西哥的番茄协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，将退出2019年暂停对墨西哥新鲜番茄征收反倾销税调查的协议，并将对从美国邻国进口的大部分番茄征收17.09%的关税。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Monday it was withdrawing from a 2019 deal suspending an anti-dumping duty investigation on fresh tomatoes from Mexico, and that it will issue duties of 17.09% on most of those imports from the U.S. neighbor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-withdraws-tomatoes-agreement-with-mexico-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7G3HQ2RXZNNSDNPOE4TVCDX6AA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:32:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽蒙特首席财务官 Karyn Ovelmen 辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[黄金矿商纽蒙特公司（Newmont Corp）周一表示，其首席财务官 Karyn Ovelmen 已辞职，并任命内部人士 Peter Wexler 担任临时首席财务官，直到选出永久继任者为止。【原文：Gold miner Newmont Corp said on Monday its CFO Karyn Ovelmen has resigned and named insider Peter Wexler as interim CFO until a permanent successor is selected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/newmont-cfo-karyn-ovelmen-resigns-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKVRQARA2JMODPOVX24DBV7D5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰 6 月房价基本持平，买家期待更好的报价]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰房地产协会（REINZ）周二表示，6月份新西兰房价基本持平，因为在市场挂牌量增加的情况下，买家在等待更好的出价。【原文：New Zealand home prices were largely flat in June as buyers await better offers amid higher listings in the market, the Real Estate Institute of New Zealand (REINZ) said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealand-home-prices-largely-flat-june-buyers-eye-better-offers-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CB5BA2CBVN3FIW43NK3ZYIVVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：抵制关税紧张局势再起]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphics-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWWINOZMGFOGVHFTOCSMFWOE7E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>