<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:04:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:04:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[安普拉茨准备分拆上市，裁员节约成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[英美铂金公司（Amplats）周一表示，在计划与母公司分拆之前，该公司已裁员约3700人，以减少开支。【原文：Anglo American Platinum (Amplats) has cut about 3,700 jobs to reduce spending ahead of a planned demerger from its parent company, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/anglo-platinum-cuts-jobs-save-costs-it-readies-spinoff-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEN6JA52WZPCTMDBFR5KCTKSZY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:35:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利称明年石油市场可能过剩]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利表示，目前原油市场供应紧张，但明年可能会出现过剩，布伦特原油价格将跌至 70 美元中高价位。【原文：The crude oil market is currently tight but next year will likely be in surplus, with Brent prices declining into the mid-to-high $70s range, Morgan Stanley said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-market-likely-be-surplus-next-year-morgan-stanley-says-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJ5AAV6LV5JR3BP56UQVMIKVRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:34:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃达丰以 13 亿欧元进一步出售 Vantage Towers 10% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国沃达丰公司（Vodafone）以 13 亿欧元的价格再次出售了 Vantage Towers 公司 10% 的股份，从而使其在欧洲移动电话天线杆集团的持股比例达到了基础设施投资者的预期水平。【原文：Britain's Vodafone has sold a further 10% stake in Vantage Towers for 1.3 billion euros, bringing its shareholding in the European mobile phone mast group down to the intended level alongside infrastructure investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/vodafone-sells-further-10-stake-vantage-towers-13-bln-euros-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BE4IQ24MTNITNCGKTPDX6AHOQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:13:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：西方矿商推动金属价格上涨以抵御中国竞争对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国唯一的一座钴矿位于爱达荷州北部的森林中，是一座被废弃的钢铁和泥土堆砌而成的矿山，由于中国竞争对手以低廉的价格向全球市场大量供应用于电动汽车电池和电子产品的蓝色金属，矿主的运营成本太高。【原文：The only U.S. cobalt mine sits fallow in the northern Idaho woods, a mothballed hunk of steel and dirt that is too expensive for its owner to operate because Chinese rivals have flooded global markets with cheap supplies of the bluish metal used in electric vehicle batteries and electronics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/western-miners-push-higher-metals-prices-ward-off-chinese-rivals-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5IF6PA7PFP4PHJS7UBDUR5UIE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:08:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺首席执行官呼吁欧洲电动汽车过渡时间表具有灵活性]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷诺首席执行官卢卡-德-梅奥（Luca De Meo）在周一出版的商业日报《回声报》（Les Echos）上发表评论时，对欧洲过渡到电动汽车的时间表表示怀疑，并补充说汽车制造商要想实现电动汽车目标，就必须降低成本。【原文：Renault's CEO Luca De Meo expressed doubts over the timeline for transitioning to electric vehicles in Europe, adding the carmaker has to bring down costs if it wants to deliver on its EV goals, in comments to business daily Les Echos published on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-ceo-calls-flexibility-european-ev-transition-timeline-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGICXVATQVO4HGQKR7LLMTSC5A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:33:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股价大涨后欧洲银行盈利成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的银行将于本周公布第二季度财报，利率上调带来的收益是否已经耗尽，以及近期的政治风波是否会对市场情绪造成影响，都将成为各方关注的焦点。【原文：Europe's biggest banks report their second-quarter earnings this week, with all eyes on whether the gains from higher interest rates have run out of steam and if recent political drama is weighing on sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-banks-earnings-spotlight-after-big-share-price-gains-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZK6YU36YMNL3ZH6MHO3UFCN3CE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价拜登卸任，华尔街情绪低落]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2UXSCDNVFOTBLQVTKUSCY2R6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:41:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称英伟达正在为中国市场准备新版旗舰 AI 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，英伟达正在为中国市场开发一款符合美国现行出口管制的新旗舰人工智能芯片。【原文：Nvidia is working on a version of its new flagship AI chips for the China market that would be compatible with current U.S. export controls, three sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-preparing-version-new-flaghip-ai-chip-chinese-market-sources-say-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUY3U7EVDRPWZK3SFIGECDT7IM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与 StanChart 有关联的中国渤海寻求处置 40 亿美元不良贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国渤海银行（China Bohai Bank）周一表示，该行正寻求出售价值 290 亿元人民币（39.9 亿美元）的不良贷款，因为中国经济摇摇欲坠，房地产行业问题日益加深，这给贷款机构带来了处置不良资产的压力。【原文：China Bohai Bank said on Monday it is looking to sell 29 billion yuan ($3.99 billion) worth of non performing loans as the faltering Chinese economy and deepening property sector problems pressure lenders to dispose of bad assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stanchart-linked-china-bohai-seeks-dispose-4-bln-bad-loans-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYWBHWQRIVNCDOCXF4LLE774UQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国下调短期和长期利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行周一将短期和长期利率下调了 10 个基点，称其目的是支持经济增长。【原文：China cut short and long-term rates by 10 basis points on Monday, with the central bank saying it was aiming to support growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-cuts-short-long-term-rates-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2IG7AFTFNPY3HG3EBTUUWA7HI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:17:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新鹏与大众成立项目公司，推出全新电动汽车架构]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车（EV）制造商新鹏汽车周一表示，该公司已与德国大众汽车公司（Volkswagen AG）合作成立了一个工程师项目室，以加快电动汽车新架构的开发进程。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle (EV) maker Xpeng said on Monday it has established a project house in partnership with German automaker Volkswagen AG for engineers to accelerate the development process of new architecture for EVs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/xpeng-volkswagen-set-up-project-house-roll-out-new-ev-architecture-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YM5ZGSM7MRJUDMRESMZPHPEVTA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 01:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登结束竞选连任，美元走低；降息后人民币持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）决定结束竞选连任，为另一位民主党人挑战唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）扫清了道路。【原文：The dollar eased on Monday in the initial reaction to U.S. President Joe Biden's decision to end his reelection campaign, clearing the way for another Democrat to challenge Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-eases-biden-ends-reelection-bid-yuan-steady-after-rate-cut-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTDHDYY4HZOH7GEJMHF7PO3SIY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者寻找美国开始降息的迹象，油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一早盘，油价上涨，因为投资者在密切关注预计最快将于 9 月开始的降息周期的迹象。【原文：Oil prices rose in early trade on Monday as investors keep a lookout for signs of a rate-cut cycle expected to begin as soon as September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-rise-investors-look-signs-us-rate-cuts-begin-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RLJIS5T7ZPVDJOLXN725WV7YI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国意外下调关键利率支持经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，中国出人意料地降低了关键的短期政策利率和基准贷款利率，试图刺激世界第二大经济体的增长。【原文：China surprised markets by lowering a key short-term policy rate and its benchmark lending rates on Monday, in an attempt to boost growth in the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-central-bank-cuts-short-term-policy-rate-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BUWKKKHENLXJGEZ6FKT6OUDQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:26:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登退出，亚洲股市谨慎；华尔街未受影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周一表现谨慎，因为本周企业财报密集，将对科技股的高估值构成考验，而投资者希望美国通胀率的关键数据将缩小 9 月份降息的可能性。【原文：Asian shares tread cautiously on Monday ahead of a packed week of corporate earnings that should test the sky-high valuations of tech stocks, while investors hope a key reading in U.S. inflation will narrow the odds on a September rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BYC4FXZH5NZXIPNSYQQ3AC7NU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:22:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航空峰会在飞机短缺和供应链动荡中开幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，航空业领导人将在伦敦郊外举行的一次大型峰会上会面，因为航空业正与供应链中断、飞机延误和碳减排计划的失败作斗争。【原文：Aviation leaders will meet at a marque summit outside London on Monday as the industry struggles with supply chain disruptions, aircraft delays and floundering plans to reduce carbon emissions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aviation-summit-opens-amid-jet-shortages-supply-chain-turbulence-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OV37VQU6ARMRZMBNZOUY3HE5FE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 23:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国副总统哈里斯对商业问题的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国副总统卡马拉-哈里斯有可能在 11 月的大选中成为民主党总统候选人。以下是她对一些重要商业话题的看法和行动。【原文：U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris is potentially poised to become the Democratic presidential nominee in the November election. Here are her views and actions related to some key business topics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-vice-president-harris-views-business-issues-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IU4NMFQSKVNE3OFUOTKC7TML7E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 23:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治超越通胀，成为主权财富基金最担心的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Invesco）周一公布的一项调查显示，对于管理着约22万亿美元资产的主权财富基金和中央银行来说，地缘政治竞争，包括中美之间正在酝酿的贸易战，现在已经超越通货膨胀，成为它们最大的担忧。【原文：Geopolitical rivalries, including brewing trade battles between the United States and China, now trump inflation as the biggest worry for sovereign wealth funds and central banks managing some $22 trillion in assets, an Invesco survey published on Monday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/geopolitics-overtakes-inflation-top-sovereign-wealth-fund-worry-list-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6HG6JGCPFMZBNJ55MJ4CUX6FI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 23:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国交通部长就航班取消与达美航空首席执行官通话]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部长皮特-巴蒂吉格（Pete Buttigieg）周日与达美航空首席执行官进行了会谈，该航空公司自上周五以来因 IT 系统大面积故障取消了数千个航班，并在继续努力恢复运营。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg spoke on Sunday with the CEO of Delta Air Lines, following the carrier's cancellation of thousands of flights since Friday due to a widespread IT-systems outage and as it continued to try to restore operations, a department official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transportation-chief-speaks-with-delta-ceo-flight-cancellations-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27PYIFROAVJWFJFAOEHM3ZWGC4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登退出美国总统竞选后，标准普尔 500 指数电子盘上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统乔-拜登结束连任竞选，并支持副总统卡马拉-哈里斯接替他成为民主党候选人，与共和党人唐纳德-特朗普竞争之后，美国 500 指数小型股期货在周日尾盘小幅上涨。【原文：S&amp;P 500 e-mini futures were up slightly late on Sunday after U.S. President Joe Biden ended his reelection bid and endorsed Vice President Kamala Harris to replace him as the Democratic candidate against Republican Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sp-500-e-minis-edge-up-after-biden-pulls-out-us-presidential-race-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVSFCS57OVMQJKLYNA53EURS7Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:27:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CrowdStrike 称大量受停电影响的设备已恢复运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[网络安全公司 CrowdStrike 周日表示，因软件更新导致全球技术中断而受到影响的 850 万台微软设备中，有相当一部分已重新上线运行。【原文：Cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike said on Sunday that a significant number of the 8.5 million Microsoft devices that were impacted as a result of a global tech outage related to a software update were back online and operational.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/crowdstrike-says-significant-number-outage-affected-devices-back-up-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNHMT7N5CNLZJK5EXX3YR7GHS4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：流向俄罗斯的芯片非法交易有所放缓，但中国和香港仍是转运中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部此前未公开的数据显示，今年通过中国大陆和香港向俄罗斯运送的半导体和其他受限制商品减少了五分之一，但香港仍然是全球逃避制裁的热点地区。【原文：Semiconductors and other restricted goods shipped through China and Hong Kong to fuel Russia's war effort fell by a fifth this year previously undisclosed U.S. Commerce Department data shows, but Hong Kong remains a global sanctions evasion hotspot.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/illicit-chip-flows-russia-seen-slowing-china-hong-kong-remain-transshipment-hubs-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O36QVEOXQZK3ZGSKALYOOO2SOM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:05:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标处理拜登退出 11 月大选一事]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺埃尔-兰德维奇（Noel Randewich）对亚洲市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets by Noel Randewich.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3E2OYFI6NOJNPWFLJ5A4DGQQU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 21:53:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登退出可能刺激特朗普解除贸易协定，政府面临分裂]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）周日退出总统竞选可能会促使投资者平仓押注共和党获胜将增加美国财政和通胀压力的交易，而一些分析师表示，市场可能会从下届政府分裂的可能性增加中受益。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden's exit from the presidential race on Sunday could prompt investors to unwind trades betting that a Republican victory would increase U.S. fiscal and inflationary pressures, while some analysts said markets could benefit from an increased chance of divided government under the next administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bidens-exit-could-spur-trump-trade-unwind-divided-government-eyed-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TBDGGNN3NKFJDVXJZEPCO7DJ4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 20:51:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道：美国监管机构私下发现半数大型银行风险管理薄弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周日报道，美国一家顶级银行监管机构的机密评估发现，在其监管的 22 家大型银行中，有 11 家对从网络攻击到员工失误等一系列风险的管理 "不足 "或 "薄弱"。【原文：A top U.S. bank regulator's confidential assessments found 11 of the 22 large banks it supervises have "insufficient" or "weak" management of a broad swath of risks ranging from cyberattacks to employee blunders, Bloomberg News reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regulator-privately-finds-weak-risk-management-half-large-banks-bloomberg-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZWIWSYC6FOXNCFNAHFYRPMONA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:34:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对拜登退出总统竞选的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）周日结束了他的连任竞选活动，因为民主党同僚对他的心智和击败唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的能力失去了信心，这使得总统竞选陷入了未知领域。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden ended his reelection campaign on Sunday after fellow Democrats lost faith in his mental acuity and ability to beat Donald Trump, leaving the presidential race in uncharted territory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/view-investors-react-biden-pulling-out-presidential-race-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5T6UNVDWRMX5D4EIEYEE7PSTA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 18:53:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球网络中断后更多美国航班被取消]]></title><description><![CDATA[据数据跟踪机构 FlightAware.com 称，受周五全球网络中断事件影响，周日有 1200 多架次航班被取消，其中以达美航空（Delta Air Lines）和美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）为首。【原文：More than 1,200 flights have been canceled within, into or out of the U.S. on Sunday, led by cancellations in top carriers Delta Air Lines and United Airlines , according to data tracker FlightAware.com, in the wake of Friday's global cyber outage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/more-us-flights-cancelled-wake-global-cyber-outage-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7Q6Y3CUURIWZFUQS5RCJIFSYI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 18:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司寻求在太空和卫星领域创造规模的机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官纪尧姆-福瑞（Guillaume Faury）周日表示，空中客车公司正在寻找机会，在国防、太空，特别是卫星市场创造规模。【原文：Airbus is looking at opportunities to create scale in defence, space and particularly satellites markets, CEO Guillaume Faury said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-looking-opportunities-create-scale-space-satellites-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ICEP7DIBNNXLM75O5OMT2O3RU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 17:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司称航空公司收益率压力尚未影响喷气机需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司飞机制造主管克里斯蒂安-舍勒（Christian Scherer）周日表示，有迹象表明航空公司的收益率在下降，但这尚未影响到对新飞机的需求。【原文：There are some signs of a decline in airline yields but this is not yet affecting demand for new aircraft, Airbus's planemaking chief Christian Scherer said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-says-pressure-airline-yields-not-yet-impacting-jet-demand-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLCFMISMKFO6RHC4N77CTWXBEE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 17:39:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音高管称飞机制造商已确定解决 MAX 7 结冰问题的设计方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司的商用飞机主管表示，该飞机制造商已经确定了解决发动机防冰系统问题的设计方案，该问题已严重推迟了737 MAX 7的认证，并表示可能在明年完成修复。【原文：Boeing's commercial airplane chief said the planemaker has settled on the design to address an engine anti-ice system that has significantly delayed certification of the 737 MAX 7 and suggested a fix could be completed by next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-exec-says-planemaker-has-settled-design-max-7-icing-issue-2024-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DQ5TYWCG5NXLLVVMCBHEMSAUM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 15:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>