<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:28:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:28:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[韩国 SK On 与福特汽车将终止美国电池合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国电池制造商 SK On 周四表示，已决定终止与福特汽车在美国的两家合资电池厂。【原文：South Korean battery maker SK On said on Thursday that it has decided to end its joint venture with Ford Motor for their two joint battery factories in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-koreas-sk-ford-motor-end-us-battery-joint-venture-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25IVN37FO5NJLLLJXRG62OUDKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意法半导体与欧洲投资银行新开设 10 亿欧元信贷额度]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商意法半导体公司（STMicroelectronics）周四表示，已与欧洲投资银行（EIB）建立了 10 亿欧元（12 亿美元）的信贷额度。【原文：Chipmaker STMicroelectronics said on Thursday it had established a 1 billion euro ($1.2 billion) credit line with the European Investment Bank (EIB).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stmicroelectronics-announces-1-billion-euro-credit-line-with-eib-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EELELJPPCNOHBILMEYTJDSRB4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:18:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预测未达华尔街目标，甲骨文欧洲股价下跌 12]]></title><description><![CDATA[甲骨文公司在法兰克福的股价开盘下跌近 12%，追随美国股市盘后的跌势，此前该公司预测的销售额和利润不及分析师预期。【原文：Shares in Oracle opened almost 12% lower in Frankfurt, tracking U.S. afterhour losses after the company forecast sales and profit that missed analyst estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/oracle-shares-drop-12-europe-after-forecasts-miss-wall-st-targets-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HY2VIOI6HNMGPBBPJFFAOTOBAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:12:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察：Stellantis 首席执行官 "急诊室 "夺回市场份额的内幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，斯泰兰特新任首席执行官安东尼奥-菲罗萨（Antonio Filosa）将汽车销量增长置于利润之上，包括采用利润率较低的车队销售和投资经济型车型，以夺回北美和欧洲的市场份额，使这家全球第四大汽车制造商重回正轨。【原文：New Stellantis CEO Antonio Filosa is prioritising vehicle sales growth over profits including resorting to lower-margin fleet sales and investing in affordable models to recapture market share in North America and Europe and get the world's No. 4 automaker back on track, four sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/inside-stellantis-ceos-emergency-room-rush-recapture-market-share-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5PUQCBDWRJQLHQ7LBDXGDEQQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利 Bancomat 计划推出与欧元挂钩的稳定币，以促进数字支付发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利支付网络 Bancomat 首席执行官 Fabrizio Burlando 表示，Bancomat 正在与该国主要贷款机构和经济部合作，推出一种与欧元挂钩的稳定币，并将向其他发行商开放。【原文：Italian payment network Bancomat is working with the country's main lenders and the economy ministry to launch a euro-pegged stablecoin that will be open to other issuers, Chief Executive Fabrizio Burlando said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/italys-bancomat-plans-euro-pegged-stablecoin-boost-digital-payments-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFHWESETC5IBDMOBMKPKFXN7GU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚内容创作者因社交媒体禁令失去年轻粉丝而感到痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[在澳大利亚全面禁止青少年使用社交媒体一天之后，澳大利亚的内容创作者们报告说，他们的追随者和浏览量都在下降，这给收入带来了风险，并迫使他们重新思考内容策略。【原文：Australian content creators are reporting drops in followers and views a day after the country imposed a sweeping teen social media ban, posing risks for incomes and forcing rethinks of content strategies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australian-content-creators-feel-sting-losing-young-fans-social-media-ban-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNRF3CYVKZOXJHN2EPT466ISTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 06:27:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储发出暂停降息的信号，投资者正面临数据暗淡和领导层更迭的考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[在连续三次降息之后，投资者现在面临的是未来一年美国货币政策前景的不确定性，持续的通胀、数据缺口以及美联储即将发生的领导层变动都给这一前景蒙上了阴影。【原文：After three consecutive interest rate cuts, investors now confront an uncertain U.S. monetary policy outlook for the year ahead, clouded by persistent inflation, data gaps, and an impending leadership change at the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-signals-pause-rate-cuts-investors-navigate-data-darkness-leadership-change-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMVZQNBG2VLAJEQJ5PB645OCEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 06:01:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能忧虑削弱风险偏好，比特币跌破 90,000 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币周四暴跌，比特币跌回 9 万美元门槛以下，再次释放出市场恐慌的信号，因为对人工智能利润的新担忧拖累了科技股。【原文：Cryptocurrencies tumbled on Thursday and bitcoin fell back below the $90,000 threshold in a renewed signal of market jitters as fresh concerns about artificial intelligence profits weighed on technology stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-dips-below-90000-ai-worries-dent-risk-appetite-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONQYAR5YJNNP7MTL4GZMIGQZSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 05:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：甲骨文在美联储推动的反弹后带来现实检验]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDOOIT3O65KR7IEMXYKGQ5XMKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 05:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文冲击股市，美联储信息影响美元走势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国云计算巨头甲骨文公司（Oracle）令人失望的财报为人工智能的盈利能力敲响了警钟，周四亚洲股市震荡，而美联储下调美国利率后，债券坚挺，美元止跌回升。【原文：Stocks wobbled around Asia on Thursday after disappointing earnings at U.S. cloud computing giant Oracle sounded a warning for AI profitability, while bonds were firm and the dollar nursed losses after the Federal Reserve cut U.S. interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WE4KMZF33JOBVDYUW7O6TEEG54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 02:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储可能不会让特朗普降息，但对 2026 年经济持积极看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）可能不会给唐纳德-特朗普总统想要的所有降息措施，但决策者们周三在新的经济预测中对经济的看法应该会让政府感到振奋，因为在 2026 年中期选举之前，美国经济将保持较快的增长、较低的通胀和稳定的失业率。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve may not give President Donald Trump all the rate cuts he wants, but the view of the economy policymakers included in new economic projections on Wednesday should buoy the administration nonetheless with its outlook for faster growth, lower inflation and steady unemployment heading into the 2026 midterm elections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-may-not-give-trump-his-rate-cuts-has-set-out-positive-view-2026-economy-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FX72ATGXQRPQJJ6FICYOMUFF6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鹰派受挫，美元下滑，市场期待再降息两次]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周四下跌，因为美联储发表的展望不像一些人预期的那样鹰派，这给了投资者做空美元的信心，因为他们押注明年还会有两次降息。【原文：The dollar fell on Thursday after the Federal Reserve delivered an outlook that was not as hawkish as some had anticipated, giving investors confidence to short the currency as they bet on two more rate cuts next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-slides-fed-dents-hawks-markets-eye-two-more-rate-cuts-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWRLSXQY6JN6ZPVQTNSMKJSDEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在委内瑞拉附近扣押油轮后，石油涨势扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，石油连续第二个交易日上涨，此前美国在委内瑞拉沿海扣押了一艘受制裁的油轮，两国之间的紧张局势升级，并引发了对进一步供应中断的担忧。【原文：Oil rose for a second straight session on Thursday after the U.S. seized a sanctioned oil tanker off Venezuela’s coast, escalating tensions between the two countries and raising concern over further supply disruptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-extends-gains-after-us-seizure-tanker-off-venezuela-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBVJ4VZZ4FK2JE6BITH5Y42ROI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:22:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[媒体报道后，马斯克在 X 博文中暗示 SpaceX 可能进行 IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周三在社交媒体上与Ars Technica太空记者埃里克-伯杰（Eric Berger）交流时暗示，SpaceX可能进行首次公开募股，此前有报道称这家火箭制造商可能在2026年上市。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk on Wednesday hinted at a possible SpaceX initial public offering in a social media exchange with Ars Technica space journalist Eric Berger, following reports of a possible listing of the rocket maker in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musk-hints-possible-spacex-ipo-x-post-after-media-reports-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAR2Y6RFXJPIXCCEOYV4NFKTIA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚领导人为社交媒体禁令辩护，因为青少年吹嘘自己一直在上网]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞承认，在全球首次禁止 16 岁以下青少年使用社交媒体的禁令生效一天后，仍有一些年轻人在使用社交媒体，他说，这项禁令的推出总是磕磕绊绊，但最终会拯救生命。【原文：Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese acknowledged some young people were still on social media a day after a world-first ban on under-16s went live, saying the rollout was always going to be bumpy but would ultimately save lives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australia-leader-defends-social-media-ban-teens-brag-about-staying-online-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKVVLDV7XNPDJIF43INSVR7DMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司首席执行官以隐私问题为由，推动修改美国儿童网络安全法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司首席执行官蒂姆-库克（Tim Cook）周三会见了美国众议院议员，回击了可能要求这家 iPhone 制造商验证用户年龄并可能收集儿童敏感数据的联邦立法，转而游说将决定是否告知应用程序商店儿童年龄的责任推给父母。【原文：Apple CEO Tim Cook met U.S. House members on Wednesday to push back against federal legislation that could require the iPhone maker to authenticate users' ages and possibly collect sensitive data on children, lobbying instead to put the onus on parents to decide whether to tell app stores about a child's age.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/apple-ceo-pushes-changes-us-child-online-safety-bill-citing-privacy-concerns-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OX4EXHMT5J5JPQNUBU7FKHSAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:08:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国中兴通讯可能因外国贿赂指控向美国支付超过 10 亿美元的赔偿金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，中国电信设备制造商中兴通讯（ZTE Corp）可能向美国政府支付超过 10 亿美元，以解决多年来的外国贿赂指控。【原文：Chinese telecom equipment maker ZTE Corp may pay more than $1 billion to the U.S. government to resolve years-old allegations of foreign bribery, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/chinas-zte-may-pay-more-than-1-billion-us-over-foreign-bribery-allegations-2025-12-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FK7ZFP6CTVOO7DHZHKGOW2D62Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者反感西太平洋银行与澳大利亚证券交易所的关系后，西太平洋银行董事在代理投票中再次当选]]></title><description><![CDATA[西太平洋银行（Westpac Banking Corp）非执行董事彼得-纳什（Peter Nash）因与陷入困境的澳大利亚证券交易所（Australian Securities Exchange）的关系而受到投资者的反弹，根据该银行年会的代理投票显示，他似乎没有受到影响。【原文：Westpac Banking Corp non-executive director Peter Nash appeared to have survived an investor backlash due to his ties to the troubled Australian Securities Exchange , according to proxy votes shown at the bank's annual meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-westpac-urges-bigger-role-social-media-firms-scam-prevention-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3E4TBBCABMJHBFAXWMIT4SPFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:44:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威尔士卡森支持的 Lumexa Imaging 在美国首次公开募股中融资 4.63 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的诊断成像服务提供商之一 Lumexa Imaging 公司周三表示，该公司已在首次公开募股中筹集到 4.625 亿美元。【原文：Lumexa Imaging, one of the largest U.S. diagnostic imaging services providers, said on Wednesday it has raised $462.5 million in its initial public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/welsh-carson-backed-lumexa-imaging-raises-463-million-us-ipo-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DK3ILKVR5IVFKKZ546QX66GIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:26:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalFoundries 任命 Sam Franklin 担任临时首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[GlobalFoundries 周三任命 Sam Franklin 为首席财务官，接替今年早些时候卸任的 David Reeder。【原文：GlobalFoundries on Wednesday appointed Sam Franklin as its chief financial officer, succeeding David Reeder, who stepped down earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/globalfoundries-names-sam-franklin-cfo-after-interim-stint-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VU6BTRRAV5I5JC7MSGWUNR3DOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:25:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本企业称中日关系紧张是 2026 年首要关注问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项调查显示，日本企业表示，在进入 2026 年之际，与中国紧张的外交关系是他们最关心的问题，紧随其后的是美国的贸易政策。【原文：Japanese companies said strained diplomatic relations with China are their primary concern as they head into 2026, followed closely by U.S. trade policies, a Reuters survey showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-firms-say-strained-sino-japan-ties-top-concerns-2026-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGDUE3MTP5O4XBSLSKFWNRA75U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:06:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储恢复购买国债，投资者预期货币市场将有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储通过购买国库券再次扩大资产负债表的举措有望缓解货币市场的紧张局势，从而平息投资者对多年来债券投资组合流失导致金融体系流动性过剩的担忧。【原文：The Federal Reserve’s move to expand its balance sheet again by buying Treasury bills is expected to ease money-market strains, calming investor worries that years of bond-portfolio runoff had drained too much liquidity from the financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-expect-relief-money-markets-fed-resumes-t-bill-purchases-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Z5MSEID4JMLHB5E33J55NNPSU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片设计工具需求强劲，Synopsys 收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受芯片设计工具需求强劲的推动，芯片设计软件供应商 Synopsys 周三公布的第四季度营收超出分析师预期，股价在盘后交易中上涨 5%。【原文：Chip design software provider Synopsys beat analysts estimates for fourth-quarter revenue on Wednesday, driven by strong demand for its chip design tools, sending its shares up 5% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/synopsys-tops-revenue-estimates-strong-demand-chip-design-tools-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDMX3TD2ZFMVHAN5O5HZCIZVJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易主管称，如果最高法院裁定 IEEPA 关税无效，美国可复制收入模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周三表示，如果最高法院否决使用基于 1977 年法律的关税，美国可以采取其他措施重新获得约 2,000 亿美元的关税收入。【原文：The United States can use other measures to recreate the roughly $200 billion in revenues it is collecting under tariffs based on a 1977 law if the Supreme Court strikes down use of that law, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-can-replicate-revenues-if-supreme-court-rules-against-ieepa-tariffs-trade-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBTSGNNJGBOXDHR3JGTTKHNXG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:23:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可口可乐任命内部人士恩里克-布劳恩为新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[可口可乐公司周三任命内部人士亨里克-布劳恩（Henrique Braun）为新任首席执行官，接替詹姆斯-昆西（James Quincey），自 3 月 31 日起生效。【原文：Coca-Cola on Wednesday named insider Henrique Braun as its new CEO, replacing James Quincey, effective March 31.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/coca-cola-names-insider-henrique-braun-new-ceo-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDXWQUTRWVPL3IVYRAYEUW436E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:21:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易代表格里尔称，特朗普与巴西总统卢拉就贸易问题进行了多次建设性互动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周三表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统与巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）就贸易问题进行了几次建设性的互动，这个拉美国家似乎是一个愿意合作的伙伴。【原文：President Donald Trump has had several constructive interactions on trade with Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, and the Latin American country seems to be a willing partner, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-had-several-constructive-interactions-with-brazils-lula-trade-trade-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFQBPB2AUBLQRJH7A5G42VBHW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:10:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：市场为美联储欢呼]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储降息、美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔对经济增长和通胀前景作出积极展望后，美元下挫，华尔街周三反弹，小型股罗素 2000 指数飙升至新高。【原文：The dollar sank and Wall Street rallied on Wednesday, with the small-cap Russell 2000 index surging to new highs, after the Fed cut interest rates and Chair Jerome Powell offered a positive outlook on the path for growth and inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SARSLZSM5JOWPJV3TCGWZ7JQEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Semafor 报道，谷歌任命阿明-瓦哈达特（Amin Vahdat）为新任人工智能基础设施建设主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Semafor 周三援引一份内部备忘录报道，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌已任命长期高管阿明-瓦哈达特（Amin Vahdat）为人工智能基础设施首席技术专家。【原文：Alphabet's Google has appointed longtime executive Amin Vahdat as chief technologist for AI infrastructure, Semafor reported on Wednesday, citing an internal memo, as tech giants pour billions into the computing backbone needed to power artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-names-amin-vahdat-new-chief-ai-infrastructure-buildout-semafor-reports-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KZKLCLOKBJCXCN2SSZ6ONE644</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:59:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[温克艾沃斯双胞胎的双子座公司获得美国预测市场许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[由亿万富翁双胞胎泰勒-温克艾沃斯（Tyler Winklevoss）和卡梅隆-温克艾沃斯（Cameron Winklevoss）创办的加密货币平台双子座公司（Gemini）周三表示，它已获得商品期货交易委员会颁发的许可证，可以向美国客户提供预测市场服务。【原文：Gemini, the crypto platform founded by billionaire twins Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, said on Wednesday it had received a license from the Commodity Futures Trading Commission to offer prediction markets to U.S. customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/winklevoss-twins-gemini-bags-us-license-prediction-markets-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIAFC2BBARO4LMICLDCQXSGIFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 CNN 应作为华纳兄弟发现交易的一部分出售]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三表示，CNN 应作为其母公司华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）交易的一部分或单独出售。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Wednesday the news network CNN should be sold as part of a deal for its parent company Warner Bros Discovery or separately.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-says-cnn-should-be-sold-part-warner-bros-discovery-deal-2025-12-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AV4OXZK3RBL5TOJLXAB4ODD4OU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>