<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 21:07:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 21:07:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[供应链软件公司 Logility 收到主动出价，每股 15 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能驱动的软件制造商 Logility Supply Chain Solutions 周五表示，该公司收到了一份主动提议，以每股 15 美元的价格收购其全部流通股。【原文：AI-powered software maker Logility Supply Chain Solutions said on Friday it had received an unsolicited proposal to acquire all of its outstanding shares for $15 a piece.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/supply-chain-software-firm-logility-receives-unsolicited-bid-15-per-share-2025-03-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVKXLV4ZZNKV3JI6MGIUT2TXXE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 00:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国放弃要求谷歌在反垄断案中出售人工智能投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五放弃了迫使 Alphabet 旗下谷歌出售其在人工智能公司（包括 OpenAI 竞争对手 Anthropic）的投资，以促进在线搜索领域竞争的提议。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice on Friday dropped a proposal to force Alphabet's Google to sell its investments in artificial intelligence companies, including OpenAI competitor Anthropic, to boost competition in online search.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-drops-bid-make-google-sell-ai-investments-antitrust-case-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERD3XXGOFVKF7FNVHLTMRTXZJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国务院雇员被控共享敏感信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份刑事起诉书，美国司法部周五宣布对一名国务院雇员提出刑事指控，该雇员被控与他在网上认识的人共享敏感的政府信息。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department on Friday announced criminal charges against a State Department employee accused of sharing sensitive government information with people he met online, according to a criminal complaint.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-state-dept-employee-arrested-conspiracy-charges-related-defense-information-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRNED2RO7VPLVBV3RIHOWWOBD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:16:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，激进投资者 Mantle Ridge 持有 Cognizant 超过 10 亿美元的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，激进投资者 Mantle Ridge 已持有咨询公司 Cognizant Technology 价值超过 10 亿美元的股份，称其股价被低估。【原文：Activist investor Mantle Ridge has built a stake worth more than $1 billion in consultancy firm Cognizant Technology , saying its shares are undervalued, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/activist-investor-mantle-ridge-builds-over-1-billion-stake-cognizant-wsj-reports-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2IMJELN6FKTNKQTIJT5SI4QTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构为银行参与某些加密货币活动扫清障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国监管国家银行的监管机构周五澄清说，银行可以从事一些加密货币活动，并取消了企业在这样做之前应事先获得监管机构许可的预期。【原文：The U.S. regulator overseeing national banks clarified Friday that banks can engage in some crypto activities, and removed expectations firms should receive advance permission from regulators before doing so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-regulator-reaffirms-banks-can-engage-some-crypto-activities-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEJRJ3UUR5O5HHEEN5LJZO3RHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[超级计算机扩张之际，埃隆-马斯克的 xAI 公司在孟菲斯购置新房产]]></title><description><![CDATA[大孟菲斯商会（Greater Memphis Chamber）周五表示，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）旗下的人工智能公司xAI已在田纳西州孟菲斯西南部购买了一处100万平方英尺的房产，这家初创公司希望在行业竞争加剧的情况下扩大其人工智能基础设施。【原文：Elon Musk-owned artificial intelligence firm xAI has bought a 1-million-square-foot property in Southwest Memphis, Tennessee, the Greater Memphis Chamber said on Friday, as the startup looks to expand its AI infrastructure amid intensifying competition in the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/elon-musks-xai-buys-new-property-memphis-amid-supercomputer-expansion-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V2QGJ3D4AVO2THOKLBFLULKSSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 20:36:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼软件购买流程转向更多访问权限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防部正在改变购买软件的方式，希望更多地接触商业和非传统软件供应商，因为五角大楼希望迅速实现武器和业务系统的现代化。【原文：The U.S. Department of Defense is shifting how it buys software eyeing greater access to commercial and non-traditional software providers as the Pentagon hopes to rapidly modernize its weapons and business systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-software-buying-process-shifts-towards-more-access-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KETJZNJKRIPLDOIYGUZHVVASQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 20:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国不顾反对，批准为马斯克的 "星链 "提供更高功率的手机服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会周五表示，将允许埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX 旗下公司 Starlink 以更高的功率水平与 T-Mobile 运营直达蜂窝服务，尽管竞争对手公司提出了反对意见。【原文：The U.S. Federal Communications Commission on Friday said it would allow Starlink, a unit of Elon Musk's SpaceX, to operate a direct-to-cell service with T-Mobile at higher power levels despite objections by rival companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-okays-higher-power-cellphone-service-musks-starlink-despite-objections-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2OYT35D7FP3DIC2F2VCLQ2UQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空飞机与公务机险些相撞后，美国联邦航空局将加强对小型飞机的检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周五表示，在2月25日芝加哥发生一起严重的险些失事事件后，该局将采取措施解决涉及通用航空和公务喷气机的安全问题。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said Friday it taking steps to address safety issues involving general aviation and business jets after a serious Feb. 25 near-miss incident in Chicago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/faa-step-up-small-plane-scrutiny-after-close-call-between-southwest-plane-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GFJLHVXIRNONDNDHZ6KYUCD24I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发动贸易战，美国和加拿大农民面临化肥价格飙升问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[距离边境两侧的春播只有几周时间了，已经面临谷物价格低迷的加拿大和美国农民正准备迎接另一个经济打击：在北美贸易战的背景下，化肥账单将更加庞大。【原文：With only weeks until spring planting on both sides of the border gets underway, Canadian and U.S. farmers, already facing low grain prices, are bracing for another economic blow: even bigger fertilizer bills amid a North American trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-canadian-farmers-face-soaring-fertilizer-prices-amid-trump-trade-war-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56JNDV4S7VP55MS3PA5CQQIJVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西最高法院分庭多数法官维持隆隆停职令]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西最高法院五人合议庭周五形成多数，维持了一名法官之前做出的裁决，即暂停美国视频共享平台 Rumble 在巴西的业务，原因是该平台未遵守法院命令。【原文：The majority of a five-member panel of Brazil's Supreme Court formed a majority on Friday to uphold a justice's previous ruling to suspend U.S. video-sharing platform Rumble in the country for not complying with court orders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazils-supreme-court-chamber-forms-majority-uphold-rumble-suspension-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBSELXVUZ5IHVJCCD5BCGQGHOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:06:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒就经济面临的不确定性和关税风险发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周五表示，在此类政策可能导致通胀压力上升的情况下，要掌握特朗普关税制度的影响仍然是一项挑战。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said Friday it still remains challenging getting a handle on the impact of the Trump tariff regime, in a climate where these sorts of policies could lead to higher inflation pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-warns-uncertainty-tariff-risks-economy-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZMCA2VXIRVMZ7FKXDZXDVQDVQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷 SE 预计大众汽车股权减值税后亏损 217 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车的最大股东保时捷公司（Porsche SE）周五表示，预计 2024 年将出现约 200 亿欧元（约合 217 亿美元）的税后亏损，理由是此前披露的其在欧洲顶级汽车制造商所持股份的减值。【原文：Porsche SE , Volkswagen's largest shareholder, expects a 2024 loss after tax of around 20 billion euros ($21.7 billion), it said on Friday, citing previously disclosed impairments on its holding in Europe's top carmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-se-expects-217-bln-loss-after-tax-volkswagen-stake-impairment-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMX5MPAHOFO7JC3RFPC72EG2JE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FAA 称 SpaceX 星际飞船爆炸中断近 240 次飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）称，SpaceX 公司的 "星际飞船"（Starship）爆炸导致周四约 240 架航班中断，包括二十多架飞机因担心太空碎片而改道。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said the explosion of SpaceX's Starship spacecraft disrupted about 240 flights Thursday, including requiring more two dozen airplanes to divert over space debris concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-says-spacex-starship-explosion-disrupted-nearly-240-flights-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5COENNUWBVND7LUKH4XBDZG2KI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:58:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达飞轮船公司首席执行官告诉《回声报》，该公司正在与美国船厂谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国达飞海运集团首席执行官鲁道夫-萨德（Rodolphe Saade）告诉《回声报》，该集团正在与造船厂商谈在美国建造中型集装箱船的可能性。【原文：CMA CGM is in talks with shipyards about the possibility of having medium-sized container vessels built in the United States, the French shipping group's CEO Rodolphe Saade told Les Echos newspaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cma-cgm-talks-with-us-shipyards-ceo-tells-les-echos-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SEK2EDDOBMCVFKEXUMNJU4WVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIE 鲍威尔称美联储正等待观察特朗普政策对经济的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔周五在纽约市的一个经济论坛上表示，美国央行将不急于降息，同时等待特朗普新政府的政策对经济的影响更加明朗。【原文：The U.S. central bank will be in no rush to cut interest rates while it waits for more clarity on how the policies of the new Trump administration affect the economy, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said at an economic forum in New York City on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-powell-says-fed-marking-time-see-economic-impact-trump-policies-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HLSE2NTFBPOVMEQ2OZQQDLJSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:23:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将就中国推动半导体产业发展的努力举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室将于周二就中国制造的老式 "传统 "半导体举行听证会，美国可能会对来自中国的芯片征收更多关税，这些芯片为从汽车、洗衣机到电信设备等日常用品提供动力。【原文：The U.S. Trade Representative's Office will hold a hearing on Tuesday into older Chinese-made "legacy" semiconductors that could heap more U.S. tariffs on chips from China that power everyday goods from autos to washing machines to telecoms gear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-hold-hearing-chinas-efforts-boost-semiconductor-industry-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIDSIHNAVJIC3EEQFTVOL6FSFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利因关税担忧下调美国 2025 年经济增长预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利周五下调了对美国2025年经济增长的预期，理由是关税带来的影响更大，以及劳动力市场仍然紧张导致通胀率上升。【原文：Morgan Stanley lowered its 2025 economic growth forecast for the United States on Friday, citing greater impact from tariffs and a still-tight labor market resulting in higher inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/morgan-stanley-cuts-us-growth-forecast-2025-tariff-concerns-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJL24IV4MRPT3D6J5AZZU3EY44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 17:54:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司称 Siri 的部分人工智能改进将推迟到 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周五表示，对语音助手 Siri 的一些人工智能改进将推迟到 2026 年。【原文：Some artificial intelligence improvements to Apple's voice assistant Siri will be delayed until 2026, the company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-says-some-ai-improvements-siri-delayed-2026-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J32VZ2ZHLVNHJO6N5RMUCQS3GY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 17:36:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒称利率政策可能维持一段时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周五表示，不断上升的通胀风险表明，央行应在更长时期内采取稳定的利率政策。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said on Friday that rising inflation risks argue for an extended period of steady central bank interest rate policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-kugler-says-rate-policy-likely-hold-some-time-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMBMRLW7ZJMAVEAHAX6IZRWUNQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 17:26:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高级官员称特朗普政府将比特币储备视为 "数字诺克斯堡"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府的高级官员在周五的媒体吹风会上表示，随着白宫推进建立数字资产储备的计划，他们认为比特币值得 "特殊对待"。【原文：Senior officials of the administration of U.S. president Donald Trump said in a media briefing on Friday that they view bitcoin as deserving "special treatment" as the White House forges ahead with plans to create stockpiles of digital assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-administration-views-bitcoin-reserve-digital-fort-knox-senior-officials-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAHLWR3PXZJSRJV3UBEL4XJ2BU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，加拿大皇家银行因收购汇丰银行而解雇部分员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解裁员情况的消息人士告诉路透社，加拿大最大的贷款机构加拿大皇家银行在去年斥资 135 亿加元收购汇丰银行国内业务后，由于业务部门发生变化而裁减了一些员工。
这两位要求匿名的消息人士称，部分裁员是在技术和运营团队，裁员于本周早些时候开始。【原文：Canada's largest lender Royal Bank of Canada laid off some employees as a result of changes at its business segments following the C$13.5 billion acquisition of HSBC's domestic business last year, two sources with direct knowledge of the layoffs told Reuters.
Some of the layoffs were at the technology and operations teams and began earlier this week, the sources said, requesting anonymity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadas-rbc-lays-off-some-employees-related-hsbc-acquisition-sources-say-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAO2UN6VY5PW5MT7TP5NG4JCVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:36:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟否认挑衅美国科技巨头，称美国也在处理垄断问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断和技术部门负责人告诉美国国会议员，欧洲新的技术规则旨在保持数字市场的开放，并非针对美国科技巨头，并提醒他们美国执法人员近年来也对这些公司进行了打击。【原文：Europe's new tech rule aims to keep digital markets open and is not targeted at U.S. tech giants, EU antitrust and tech chiefs told U.S. congressmen, reminding them that U.S. enforcers have in recent years also cracked down on these companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-denies-picking-us-tech-giants-says-us-also-tackling-monopolisation-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCOJ6MIV5RNS5JW3W3S2Y2BGK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:36:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业数据亮起潜在红灯，美联储有望在 6 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储将于 3 月 18-19 日召开政策会议，届时劳动力市场总体强劲，但可能会出现一些疲软的早期迹象，如果通胀率居高不下，而特朗普政府的关税又增加了物价压力，那么美国央行可能会陷入困境。【原文：The Federal Reserve will head into its March 18-19 policy meeting with the labor market strong overall but showing some potential early signs of weakening, a development that could put the U.S. central bank in a tough spot if inflation remains high and the Trump administration's tariffs add to price pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-expected-cut-rates-june-jobs-data-raises-potential-red-flags-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZ73WUARZBOY3EKRTPRAG4KY2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:29:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员就与军方和政府的关系向中国电信施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院一个小组的领导人呼吁中国顶级电信公司详细说明与中国军方和政府的任何联系，理由是这些公司在美国的存在造成了国家安全问题。【原文：The leaders of a U.S. House of Representatives panel have called on top Chinese telecom companies to detail any links to the Chinese military and government, citing national security concerns posed by the companies' U.S. presence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-lawmakers-press-chinese-telecoms-over-ties-military-government-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJPXOR5WUZI55BW23CS3XMVJSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:18:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国正酝酿禁止政府设备使用中国应用程序 DeepSeek]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉此事的人士周五表示，出于国家安全考虑，特朗普政府正在权衡禁止中国人工智能聊天机器人 DeepSeek 在美国政府设备上使用。【原文：The Trump administration is weighing a ban on Chinese AI chatbot DeepSeek from U.S. government devices over national-security concerns, a person familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-likely-ban-chinese-app-deepseek-government-devices-wsj-reports-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEXTJMLR6NMOXHR5JGMV537IPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:48:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克计划 24 小时交易，全球对美股的兴趣与日俱增]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克公司（Nasdaq Inc）一位高级管理人员周五在社交媒体上发帖称，该公司计划在其旗舰美国交易所推出 24 小时交易，以利用全球对美国股票日益增长的需求。【原文：Nasdaq Inc plans to introduce 24-hour trading on its flagship U.S. exchange to capitalize on growing global demand for U.S. equities, a senior executive said in a social media post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-plans-24-hour-trading-tap-into-growing-international-demand-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYLPOY4KY5IGPBHHSGEMWUP5L4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[房地产行业复苏乏力，Blackstone 最新房地产债务基金融资 80 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的另类资产管理公司 Blackstone 周五表示，其最新的房地产债务基金已募集到 80 亿美元，这表明房地产行业在经历了几年的动荡后正在复苏。【原文：Blackstone has raised $8 billion in its most recent real estate debt fund, the world's largest alternative asset manager said on Friday, a sign that the property sector is seeing a recovery after a couple of tumultuous years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstone-raises-8-bln-latest-real-estate-debt-fund-amid-nascent-sector-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X62GZ6CVCJM55OI3GW6PY4ZMLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:37:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，微软正在开发人工智能推理模型，与 OpenAI 竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周五援引一位参与此计划的人士的话报道，微软正在开发内部人工智能推理模型，以与 OpenAI 竞争，并可能将其出售给开发者。【原文：Microsoft is developing in-house artificial intelligence reasoning models to compete with OpenAI and may sell them to developers, The Information reported on Friday, citing a person involved in this initiative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/microsoft-developing-ai-reasoning-models-compete-with-openai-information-reports-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKNDMDM3DVJ7BHDLXGFWI2MSPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:12:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政策不确定性考验美国劳动力市场韧性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国的就业增长在二月份有所回升，但在混乱的贸易政策和联邦政府大幅削减开支有可能扰乱今年经济增长的情况下，曾经充满活力的劳动力市场正在出现裂痕。【原文：U.S. job growth picked up in February, but cracks are emerging in the once-resilient labor market amid a chaotic trade policy and deep federal government spending cuts that threaten to disrupt economic growth this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-growth-picks-up-february-unemployment-rate-rises-41-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONE5ER5HBJOUFOJZ4NNAFU47B4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>