<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:42:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:42:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行员工对联合信贷银行说 "不"，工会担心可能裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[约 200 名德国商业银行员工周四早些时候举行抗议活动，反对联合信贷银行（UniCredit）可能收购这家德国银行。【原文：Some 200 Commerzbank employees protested early Thursday against a possible takeover of the German lender by UniCredit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/commerzbank-workers-say-no-unicredit-union-fears-possible-job-cuts-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMIVYQX4EFIBTHAGGFZONCEXSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:36:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在北京的人如何从贸易全球主义者摇身一变成为对华鹰派]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国新任驻华大使戴维-珀杜（David Perdue）本周抵达北京。【原文：David Perdue, the new U.S. envoy to China, arrives in Beijing this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/how-trumps-man-beijing-swung-trade-globalist-china-hawk-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VY4Z5TENFMCLB43V4F4Y5HMYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年初，英国经济增长速度超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国官方周四公布的数据显示，3 月份英国经济意外增长，推动 2025 年第一季度的产出创下一年来最大增幅，这将受到英国财政大臣雷切尔-里夫斯（Rachel Reeves）的欢迎。【原文：Britain's economy unexpectedly grew in March to push up output over the first quarter of 2025 by the most in a year, according to official data on Thursday that will be welcomed by finance minister Rachel Reeves.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/uk-economy-beats-forecast-grow-by-02-march-ons-says-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKXIPHWMJNMUTFOPTP3R44SWWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:06:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商急于拯救美国夏季购物季]]></title><description><![CDATA[在华盛顿和中国政府同意暂时削减关税后，包括沃尔玛和几家服装品牌在内的美国零售商正争先恐后地为五月下旬开始的夏季购物旺季采购中国制造的商品。【原文：U.S. retailers including Walmart and several clothing brands are racing to secure China-made merchandise for the busy summer shopping season starting in late May after Washington and Beijing agreed to temporarily slash tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retailers-rush-save-us-summer-shopping-season-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTWYXKL6WJKGPLRWDUHSSTNFBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本投资者因贸易乐观情绪将外资股买盘扩大至第八周]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本投资者连续第八周抢购外国股票，原因是美国贸易谈判取得进展，对贸易战对全球经济影响的担忧有所缓解，从而提振了投资者情绪。【原文：Japanese investors snapped up foreign stocks for an eighth straight week, as progress in U.S. trade negotiations and easing concerns over the global economic impact of a trade war lifted investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japanese-investors-extend-foreign-stock-buying-eighth-week-trade-optimism-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUOH2GSZRJPSRFHRLYVAV7IBRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:25:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一季度核心利润略超预期，德国电信上调指导原则]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国电信周四公布的第一季度核心利润略高于分析师预期，并小幅上调了全年业绩指引。【原文：Deutsche Telekom reported a first-quarter core profit slightly above analyst expectations on Thursday and marginally lifted its full-year guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/deutsche-telekom-raises-guidance-after-slightly-beating-q1-core-profit-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JF5OHDYUS5J35G7Y4MMCQRSWHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本财政困境考验日本央行缩减债券计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[有关大规模财政支出的言论以及随之而来的超长收益率飙升，正在引发人们对日本央行能够多快缩减债券购买规模的疑问，这也加剧了日本央行在消除大规模货币刺激政策残余方面所面临的挑战。【原文：Talk of big fiscal spending and a subsequent spike in super-long yields are raising questions over just how quickly the Bank of Japan can taper its bond purchases, adding to the challenges it faces in removing remnants of its massive monetary stimulus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-fiscal-woes-put-boj-bond-taper-plans-test-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDCLW6CNBJJX7DGDUMAR2LTQBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒂森克虏伯维持展望，预计下半年环境将更加稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[蒂森克虏伯公司周四表示，维持本财年的业绩展望，并预计 2025 年下半年的市场环境将更加稳定，此前，价格和需求下降以及与维护相关的停工导致季度利润骤降。【原文：Thyssenkrupp kept its outlook for the fiscal year and expects a more stable market environment in the second half of 2025, it said on Thursday, after lower prices and demand as well as maintenance-related shutdowns caused quarterly profit to plunge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/thyssenkrupp-keeps-outlook-expects-more-stable-environment-h2-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CXYHXONZZOHBCLI65OU5CGVFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一季度业绩强劲，特朗普关税迷雾为欧洲公司前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲公司（Europe Inc）经受住了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策引发的动荡，实现了弹性十足的第一季度盈利，但尽管新近达成了贸易休战，投资者仍面临着不确定性的迷雾。【原文：Europe Inc has weathered the turbulence sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff policies to deliver resilient first-quarter earnings, but in spite of the newly-minted trade truce, investors still face a fog of uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-tariff-fog-clouds-outlook-europe-inc-after-robust-first-quarter-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6AYECFNWNKYVFGS4KV3QG5SJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:04:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第二季度业绩超预期，西门子确认增长前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国工程集团西门子公司周四表示，"尽管不确定性增加"，该公司仍预计全年销售额将增长 3% 至 7%，该公司第二季度利润好于预期。【原文：Siemens still expects to increase its full-year sales by between 3 and 7% "despite increased uncertainty", the German engineering group said on Thursday, as it reported better-than-expected profit during its second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/siemens-confirms-growth-outlook-after-q2-figures-beat-forecasts-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQDMBGXU7NL7LM53F3OXKTVONE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 随着亢奋情绪消退，鲍威尔开始行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAYLONI7INILDBY6POWGGIITOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:33:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：美国准备削减银行资本要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，美国当局正准备宣布削减银行的资本要求。【原文：Authorities in the United States are preparing to announce cuts to banks' capital requirements, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-poised-cut-capital-requirements-banks-ft-reports-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YM2UYWYAHVLCFBJDGPUFUZMJ44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普的不确定性影响下，日本央行将在 9 月前暂停加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项调查显示，大多数经济学家目前预计日本央行将在9月份之前维持利率不变，因为日本央行将暂停评估美国关税的影响，但仍有略微多数的经济学家认为日本央行将在年底前至少加息25个基点。【原文：Most economists now expect the Bank of Japan will hold interest rates through September as it pauses to assess the effects of U.S. tariffs, a Reuters survey showed, although a slight majority still see at least a 25-basis-point hike by year-end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-pause-rate-hikes-through-september-amid-trump-uncertainty-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTFNIENPLJOIDGT2VMGAPYCUEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普访问阿联酋，阿联酋希望推进人工智能雄心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四将结束对卡塔尔的短暂访问，向美军发表讲话，然后飞往阿拉伯联合酋长国，该国领导人希望美国帮助这个富裕的海湾国家成为人工智能领域的全球领导者。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump was due to end a brief trip to Qatar with a speech to U.S. troops on Thursday then fly to the United Arab Emirates, where leaders hope for U.S. help to make the wealthy Gulf nation a global leader in artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/trump-heads-uae-it-hopes-advance-ai-ambitions-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5HDYJEG2BJ2DM43OPZW7BY2KI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产汽车正在进行大规模裁员。扭转销售局面将更加困难]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，日产汽车新任首席执行官伊万-埃斯皮诺萨（Ivan Espinosa）面临着一项艰巨的任务，他无法保证这家陷入困境的日本汽车制造商能够扭转一线销售下滑的局面，即使他在努力削减成本。【原文：Nissan's new chief executive Ivan Espinosa faces an uphill task turning around the troubled Japanese automaker with no guarantee it can reverse sliding top-line sales, analysts said, even as he moves to slash costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-is-rolling-out-big-cuts-turning-around-sales-will-prove-harder-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBFHUGTDRVOX7PDH7TZI5GRTFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称日本将于下周寻求第三轮贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士周四告诉路透社，日本最高贸易谈判代表赤泽亮世可能最快于下周前往华盛顿，与美国进行第三轮贸易谈判。【原文：Japan's top trade negotiator, Ryosei Akazawa, could travel to Washington as soon as next week for a third round of trade talks with the U.S., two sources with knowledge of the plans told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan-seek-3rd-round-trade-talks-next-week-sources-say-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZI4XSG4OVJGXLYS3WYTP4BR2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚太经合组织警告美国关税对贸易的影响，各成员正寻求与美国达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚太经济合作组织警告说，在美国关税的影响下，该地区今年的出口几乎不会增长。【原文：The Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation grouping warned that exports in the region will barely grow this year amid U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/apec-warns-us-tariff-impact-trade-members-seek-deals-with-us-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z2L5JNOSRFP7THLFBE6F6BNSZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电池回收商 Li-Cycle 在加拿大申请破产保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于多伦多的锂电池回收公司 Li-Cycle 周三表示，该公司已在加拿大申请破产保护，预计将开始正式出售其业务或资产。【原文：Toronto-based lithium battery recycling firm Li-Cycle said on Wednesday that it has filed for bankruptcy protection in Canada and expects to start a formal sale for its business or assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/battery-recycler-li-cycle-files-bankruptcy-protection-canada-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COEMA4OBEROY3BV2BGM3GLB3YQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:45:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，星巴克将开始出售中国业务股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，星巴克已与私募股权投资公司、科技公司和其他公司进行了接触，以考虑其中国业务的各种选择，包括可能的股权出售。【原文：Starbucks has reached out to private equity firms, technology companies and others as it mulls options for its China business, including a possible stake sale, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/starbucks-said-start-stake-sale-china-business-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3SZFI2T6BM53OABATC4OAGIUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:31:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场在美国数据公布前等待时机，股市漂移，美元震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，股市难以找到方向，而美元则跌跌不休，因为本周早些时候市场翘尾因素带来的欣喜情绪逐渐消退，交易员们期待着当天晚些时候的美国数据能带来进一步的催化剂。【原文：Stocks struggled for direction on Thursday while the dollar stumbled as the euphoria from market tailwinds earlier in the week fizzled out, with traders looking to U.S. data later in the day for further catalysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4MIJ2BIXVI75FH5N2H2R6VC7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:27:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部就波音刑事案件会见 737 MAX 遇难者家属]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社查阅的一封信，美国司法部周五计划在 6 月 23 日波音 737 MAX 飞机制造商面临审判日期之前，与 2018 年和 2019 年两起波音 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故的受害者会面，这两起事故共造成 346 人死亡。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department on Friday plans to meet with the victims of two Boeing 737 MAX crashes that killed 346 people in 2018 and 2019 ahead of a June 23 trial date the planemaker faces, according to a letter reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-justice-department-meet-with-737-max-victims-boeing-criminal-case-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5EVROMIIORM4JFIWY3AHDHDHE4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:22:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因贸易协议的不确定性而摇摆不定；韩元成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在动荡不安的一周里，投资者对中美关税休战的欣慰让位于对各种贸易协议形式不确定性的谨慎情绪，而韩元在大幅波动后趋于稳定。【原文：The dollar wobbled on Thursday in a turbulent week that saw investor relief at the U.S.-China tariff truce give way to a cautious mood amid uncertainty over the shape of various trade deals, while the South Korean won steadied after sharp moves.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-wavers-uncertainty-over-trade-deals-skorean-won-focus-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RA4FP4HFTZMOHK2FKGXBHEN5RA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国第一季度经济增长可能因投资和消费疲软而放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对经济学家进行的一项调查显示，受私人投资低迷、家庭消费疲软和旅游业下滑的影响，泰国第一季度的经济增长可能放缓。【原文：Economic growth in Thailand likely slowed in the first quarter, weighed down by subdued private investment, weaker household consumption and a drop in tourism, according to a Reuters poll of economists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thai-growth-likely-slowed-first-quarter-weak-investment-consumption-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIZHR2WZSRMALDKD6KRSSPMOBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾台北国际电脑展将展示人工智能进展，Nvidia 的黄晓明将成为中心人物]]></title><description><![CDATA[在下周举行的台湾年度电脑展上，人们将再次聚焦英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋和最新的人工智能技术，同时也会关注美国提高关税可能带来的破坏性影响。【原文：At Taiwan's annual Computex trade show next week, the spotlight is expected to fall, once again, on Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang and the latest in artificial intelligence, but also on the potential destablising impact of higher U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-computex-showcase-ai-advances-nvidias-huang-take-centre-stage-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXW2EFKOFVLLJLR5CP65NJVCSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[库存增加引发供应过剩担忧，美国油价下跌逾 1 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国原油期货周四早盘下跌超过 1 美元，因为上周美国原油库存意外增加，引发了投资者对供应过剩的担忧。【原文：U.S. crude futures declined more than $1 in early trade on Thursday after an unexpected build in U.S. crude oil inventories last week raised investor concerns about oversupply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-oil-prices-drop-more-than-1-inventory-build-raises-oversupply-fear-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LF44CUYFBKW7PJMEIHADAPNHM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:22:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，UnitedHealth 因可能存在医疗保险欺诈而受到刑事调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，美国司法部（DOJ）正在对联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）可能存在的医疗保险欺诈行为进行刑事调查。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) is carrying out a criminal investigation into UnitedHealth Group for possible Medicare fraud, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-under-criminal-probe-possible-medicare-fraud-wsj-reports-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBFYFEO3MVJN3OBKJQXIHQ6TIQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国要求反垄断监管机构关注经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国周四要求其反垄断监管机构在兼并控制、数字市场和消费者保护方面采取更加及时、透明和反应迅速的干预措施，从而推动经济增长，并最大限度地减少企业面临的不确定性。【原文：Britain on Thursday told its antitrust regulator to get behind its push for economic growth and minimise uncertainty for businesses by making more timely, transparent and responsive interventions in merger control, digital markets and consumer protection.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/britain-tells-antitrust-regulator-focus-economic-growth-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQEQVJV6NJLANMILE6MDJ32LJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈雷戴维森在旨在罢免首席执行官的董事会斗争中取得胜利]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈雷戴维森公司在一份声明中说，该公司周三击退了投资者 H Partners 提出的罢免包括首席执行官在内的三名董事的提议。【原文：Harley-Davidson on Wednesday beat back investor H Partners' proposal to remove three directors, including the CEO, the company said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/harley-davidson-scores-victory-board-battle-aimed-removing-ceo-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3AUTIEZAJKHLH5ZSWZDARU36U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vizion称，关税暂停后中国至美国海运货物预订量激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[集装箱跟踪软件供应商Vizion周三表示，在中美两国暂停针锋相对的惩罚性关税之后，美国从中国到美国的集装箱运输预订量激增了近300%。【原文：U.S. bookings for container transport from China to the United States spiked almost 300% in the wake of the United States and China pausing punishing tit-for-tat tariffs, container-tracking software provider Vizion said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-ocean-cargo-bookings-surge-after-tariff-pause-vizion-says-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6QPNDKHP5KFPI3TEYGVLPRPOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovery 的 Citrone 称美国移动是他最看好的股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[Discovery Capital 的创始人罗布-西特龙（Rob Citrone）周三表示，他目前最喜欢的股票是墨西哥的 America Movil，因为该公司的业务涉及拉丁美洲的许多不同国家。【原文：Discovery Capital's founder Rob Citrone said on Wednesday his favorite stock at this moment is Mexico's America Movil due to its exposure to many different countries in Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/discoverys-citrone-says-america-movil-is-his-top-stock-name-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAKWGAD2W5NHBPDGBUW23XGLOQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>