<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:46:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:46:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，福特要求供应商削减成本，以推动电动汽车业务实现盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份公司备忘录，福特汽车公司已要求其电动汽车供应商降低成本，以支持盈利能力，并称 "一切都摆在桌面上"。【原文：Ford Motor Co has asked its electric-vehicle suppliers to reduce costs in an attempt to support profitability, saying "everything is on the table," according to a company memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-asks-suppliers-cut-costs-push-turn-ev-business-profitable-memo-says-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVEGWY6WZRPZTAZ4RRPR5CTSTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约诉讼称人工智能配音公司盗用演员声音]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名配音演员周四在曼哈顿联邦法院起诉人工智能初创公司 Lovo，指控该公司非法复制他们的声音，并未经许可将其用于人工智能配音技术。【原文：Two voice actors sued artificial-intelligence startup Lovo in Manhattan federal court on Thursday, accusing the company of illegally copying their voices and using them without permission in its AI voiceover technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ai-voiceover-company-stole-voices-actors-new-york-lawsuit-claims-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3EFW2CU2GRJUXFGT46XZD52HIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部提议对大麻重新分类后，大麻股反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国司法部公布放宽大麻限制的历史性提案后，包括 Tilray 、Curaleaf 和 AdvisorShares Pure US Cannabis ETF 在内的大麻股票周四大涨。【原文：Cannabis stocks including Tilray , Curaleaf , and the AdvisorShares Pure US Cannabis ETF rallied on Thursday after the U.S. Department of Justice unveiled a historic proposal to ease restrictions on marijuana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/cannabis-stocks-rally-after-doj-proposal-reclassify-marijuana-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4AA55NG35RNIFHIETG5MVRHLQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道指突破 40,000 点，拜登在分屏视频中嘲讽特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，道琼斯指数首次突破 40,000 点，创下历史新高，这为美国总统乔-拜登提供了一个机会，证明他的共和党竞选对手对 2020 年的预测是错误的。【原文：The Dow topped 40,000 for the first time on Thursday in an all-time high, giving U.S. President Joe Biden an opening to prove his Republican election rival's 2020 predictions wrong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/dow-tops-40000-biden-trolls-trump-split-screen-video-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHHWECJFTNJOHOKUUMGAK3424M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:49:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通投资者在创纪录的一年后权衡首席执行官戴蒙的战略和继任问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通今年的利润创下历史新高，投资者迫切希望了解该公司的继任计划、人工智能投资以及传统银行业务以外的机遇。【原文：With JPMorgan Chase coming off a year of record profits, investors are eager to learn about the firm's succession plans, investments in artificial intelligence and opportunities beyond traditional banking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-investors-weigh-ceo-dimons-strategy-succession-after-record-year-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSWVFHAPSJNKVJBX4HXPWJVXCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:44:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国比亚迪推迟 2025 年智利锂电正极工厂计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商比亚迪公司美洲区负责人周二告诉路透社，该公司已推迟到2025年在智利生产电动汽车（EV）电池用锂电正极的计划。【原文：Chinese carmaker BYD Co has postponed plans to produce lithium cathodes for electric vehicle (EV) batteries in Chile by 2025, the firm's Americas head told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-byd-postpones-plans-2025-chile-lithium-cathode-plant-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUVETYW6X5I4LFGV5DXG5I7AGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:29:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛的强劲预测预示着消费者将保持活力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，零售业的风向标沃尔玛发布了一份积极的预测，表明美国消费者的购买力正在恢复，这与沃尔玛的一家主要供应商和一家零售业竞争对手早些时候的言论一致。【原文：A positive forecast from retail bellwether Walmart on Thursday signaled a resilient U.S. shopper, in line with earlier remarks by one of its key suppliers and one of its retail rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmarts-strong-forecast-signals-resilient-consumer-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LUZRDAWEVLYBKPBHPMKBTINJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音供应商 Spirit AeroSystems 发言人称将裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体周四援引内部文件报道，精神航空系统公司（Spirit AeroSystems）正在美国堪萨斯州威奇托市裁员数百人，原因是该公司正面临高额债务和主要客户波音公司生产放缓的问题。【原文：Spirit AeroSystems is laying off several hundred members of its workforce in Wichita, Kan., according to a media report Thursday citing internal documents, as the company deals with high debt and slowed production at Boeing, its key customer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-supplier-spirit-aerosystems-lay-off-employees-spokesman-says-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDEJ6IN7TRJYFBJDKN76AYXBHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉德国工厂扩建获当地议会批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国电动汽车制造商特斯拉的扩建计划遭到抗议，但特斯拉位于柏林附近的格鲁海德（Gruenheide）的德国工厂仍于周四获得了当地议会的批准。【原文：Tesla got the go-ahead for an expansion of its German factory in Gruenheide near Berlin from the local council on Thursday despite protests against the U.S. electric vehicle maker's plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-gets-local-council-go-ahead-german-factory-expansion-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2RLFMYB2ZKJZFOYLRPD3676A4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:01:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西政府上调 2024 年国内生产总值预测，预计通胀率将上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西财政部周四上调了对该国今年经济增长的预期，但同时也上调了对2024年和2025年通货膨胀的预期，强调了近期南里奥格兰德州洪灾对物价造成的影响。【原文：Brazil's Finance Ministry on Thursday hiked its projection for the country's economic growth this year but also raised inflation estimates for 2024 and 2025, underlining price impacts from recent floods in Rio Grande do Sul state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-government-hikes-2024-gdp-forecast-sees-higher-inflation-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTCWADDDWFIFFKNFQMGATEBJ4Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业投入销售情况良好，南美则不尽如人意]]></title><description><![CDATA[据农业投入品生产商称，尽管谷物价格下降，但化肥和作物护理产品等农业投入品在美国的销售已接近正常水平，而在南美，销售情况却不尽如人意。【原文：Sales of agricultural inputs such as fertilizers and crop care products have been near normal in the United States despite lower grain prices, while they are not as good in South America, according to agricultural input producers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ag-inputs-sales-seen-good-level-us-not-good-south-america-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWXALJIKKJJXTGM6PGYYLI3324</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据改善，美联储仍对减产持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周的数据为美国联邦储备委员会提供了两方面的好消息，但政策制定者尚未就投资者确信将于今年开始的降息时机公开转变观点。【原文：Data this week offered the U.S. Federal Reserve good news on two fronts but policymakers haven't openly shifted views yet about the timing of rate cuts investors are convinced will start this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-remains-cautious-cuts-even-data-improves-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXAG4KH3CFMGTCIAHJ3CRKCMIA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会更新华尔街客户数据黑客规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街最高监管机构周四表示，它已更新了相关规则，以确保投资公司和其他机构努力检测和应对黑客窃取客户数据的行为。【原文：Wall Street's top regulator on Thursday said it had updated rules to ensure investment companies and others work to detect and respond to hackers' theft of customer data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-sec-updates-customer-data-hacking-rules-wall-street-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KR25EEAAARPVLOY3EDVN76DNH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英美资源集团首席执行官表示，英美资源集团数月来一直在寻找化肥合作伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[英美资源集团（Anglo American）首席执行官邓肯-万布拉德（Duncan Wanblad）告诉路透社记者，英美资源集团为其在北约克郡的化肥厂项目寻找合作伙伴已经有大约六个月的时间，他重申，即使那里的工作停滞不前，化肥厂业务仍将是这家改组矿商的三大支柱之一。【原文：Anglo American has been looking for partners for its fertiliser project in North Yorkshire for around six months, Chief Executive Duncan Wanblad told Reuters, reiterating the business will be one of three pillars of the revamped miner, even as work there stalls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/anglo-american-has-sought-fertiliser-partners-months-says-ceo-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XJDBUQGENKW7KW67XYYM4IVQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储梅斯特寻求通胀压力缓解的更多证据]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长洛雷塔-梅斯特（Loretta Mester）周四表示，将美国央行政策维持在当前水平将有助于使仍然高企的通胀率回到2%的目标。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Loretta Mester said on Thursday holding U.S. central bank policy at current levels will help get still-high inflation back to the 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-mester-seeks-more-evidence-inflation-pressures-are-easing-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHVIY3SVSVISNEZRPUJRN25L5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉塔姆航空公司扩大巴西国际航班的频率；法国航空公司增加航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉塔姆航空公司（LATAM Airlines）周四表示，该公司将增加连接巴西与美国以及欧洲和非洲国家的七条国际航线的班次。【原文：LATAM Airlines will increase the frequency of seven of its international routes connecting Brazil to the United States and countries in Europe and Africa, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/latam-airlines-expands-frequency-brazil-international-flights-air-france-adds-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HVA7FLL3JJ57KUOF6TUK5GBXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫布雷纳德称中国出口可能损害对美投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫国家经济顾问莱尔-布雷纳德（Lael Brainard）周四表示，中国的工业产能和某些行业的出口量如此之大，可能会削弱在美国投资的可行性。【原文：White House National Economic Adviser Lael Brainard said on Thursday China's industrial capacity and exports in certain sectors are so large, they can undermine the viability of investments in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/white-houses-brainard-says-chinas-exports-can-undermine-investments-us-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQXAOJF4ZNONLEZGHLBFPHDW4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织美国应保持开放贸易，与中国合作解决争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）周四表示，美国最好维持其开放的贸易体系，而不是对中国商品征收新的惩罚性关税。【原文：The U.S. would be better served by maintaining its open trade system rather than imposing new punitive duties on Chinese goods, the International Monetary Fund said on Thursday, adding that Washington and Beijing should work together to resolve their trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-us-should-keep-open-trade-work-with-china-resolve-disputes-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6X23JBR4TFK57N7OAXJRJ526WY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:23:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼、福克斯、华纳兄弟发现名为 Venu Sports 的体育流媒体合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[该公司首席执行官皮特-迪斯塔德（Pete Distad）周四表示，华特迪士尼公司、华纳兄弟发现公司和福克斯公司将推出的体育流媒体服务将被命名为 Venu Sports，并有望于今年秋季推出。【原文：The sports-streaming service set to be launched by Walt Disney Co , Warner Bros Discovery and Fox Corp will be called Venu Sports and is on track for launch this fall, Pete Distad, the venture's CEO, said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/disney-fox-warner-bros-discovery-sports-streaming-venture-named-venu-sports-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHE2CNVXONJHLMHBVOIUS2Q2ZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:04:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安培计算公司与高通公司合作研发人工智能，并发布新芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[安培计算公司（Ampere Computing）周四表示，该公司正在将其芯片与高通公司（Qualcomm）的芯片进行配对，推出一款新产品，旨在降低人工智能芯片运行所产生的电费。【原文：Ampere Computing on Thursday said it was pairing its chips with those from Qualcomm in a new offering aimed at lowering the power bills from operating artificial intelligence chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ampere-computing-pairs-with-qualcomm-ai-unveils-new-chip-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTQKYOS5ZJKA7IMZTX5NMHT5MY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 道指触及 40,000 点，因盈利增长和降息押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，道琼斯工业平均指数首次突破 40,000 点，这是蓝筹股指数最快的一次 10,000 点攀升，强劲的季度业绩和对美联储降息的押注不断升温为其提供了动力。【原文：The Dow Jones Industrial Average surpassed 40,000 points for the first time on Thursday, the blue-chip index's fastest 10,000 point-climb, powered by strong quarterly results and rising bets of interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-dow-hits-40000-earnings-boost-rate-cut-bets-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SVSRYGKBIBOWHKIJAQVEAGPDGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:56:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受财报提振和降息押注影响，道指短暂冲破 40,000 点大关]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，道琼斯工业平均指数首次短暂突破 40,000 点水平，这是蓝筹股指数最快的一次 10,000 点攀升，强劲的季度业绩和对美联储降息的押注不断升温为其提供了动力。【原文：The Dow Jones Industrial Average briefly breached the 40,000-point level for the first time on Thursday, the blue-chip index's fastest 10,000-point climb, powered by strong quarterly results and rising bets of interest-rate cuts by the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/dow-briefly-sprints-past-40000-mark-earnings-boost-rate-cut-bets-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTHAB3HQY5PIPNUBDIJPX77WSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛达成管理 UPS 养老基金 434 亿美元资产的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛资产管理公司（Goldman Sachs Asset Management）被任命为包裹递送公司 UPS 旗下价值 434 亿美元北美养老基金资产的外包首席投资官。【原文：Goldman Sachs Asset Management has been appointed the outsourced chief investment officer for $43.4 billion North American pension fund assets belonging to parcel delivery firm UPS .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/goldman-sachs-secures-deal-manage-upss-434-bln-pension-fund-assets-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOFU5DKIJBJZHP67IETU4BH7YA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:35:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，今年计划购买电动汽车的美国人越来越少]]></title><description><![CDATA[J.D. Power的一项研究显示，由于经济型汽车短缺、充电基础设施不足以及对电动汽车好处的无知，考虑在2024年购买电动汽车的美国买家数量比一年前有所下降。【原文：The number of buyers in the U.S. considering an electric vehicle purchase in 2024 has fallen from a year ago due to a shortage of affordable cars, inadequate charging infrastructure and ignorance about EV benefits, a study by J.D. Power has shown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fewer-people-us-plan-buy-evs-this-year-study-shows-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODMIKGQZR5JZPMV6YDTI7GORUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院支持消费者金融监督机构的筹资机制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周四在发薪日贷款行业提出的质疑中维持了消费者金融保护局的拨款机制，这给乔-拜登总统的政府带来了胜利，也给该机构的保守派批评者带来了挫折。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court on Thursday upheld the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau's funding mechanism in a challenge brought by the payday loan industry, handing a victory to President Joe Biden's administration and a setback to the agency's conservative critics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-backs-consumer-finance-watchdog-agencys-funding-mechanism-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XL3CFBW5ZL67LAJGMTQLXRIJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:14:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管 "最后一英里 "的风险依然存在，但全球避免了工资价格螺旋式上升--研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位顶级经济学家得出结论认为，发达经济体迄今尚未因大流行病后爆发的通胀而出现破坏性的工资价格螺旋上升，一些国家有可能从这一事件中相对无痛地着陆，但尚未得到保证。【原文：Developed economies have so far skirted a damaging wage price spiral from the breakout of inflation that followed the pandemic, two top economists have concluded, with a relatively painless landing from the episode possible in some countries but not yet assured.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/world-skirted-wage-price-spiral-though-last-mile-risks-remain-research-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2FUJLDIONJSXE4KR7QHFVMY4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月制造业产出意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的数据显示，由于机动车产量下降，4月份美国工厂的产量意外下降。【原文：Production at U.S. factories unexpectedly fell in April amid a decline in motor vehicle output, data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-output-unexpectedly-falls-april-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4H6EPNJLFJC7LHQGSKBTHS7LM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称，美国将倾向于让现有投资者获得委内瑞拉石油许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位接近讨论的人士说，美国正准备优先向已有石油生产和资产的公司发放有限的在委内瑞拉运营的许可证，而不是那些寻求首次进入这个受到欧佩克制裁的国家的公司。【原文：The U.S. is preparing to prioritize issuing limited licenses to operate in Venezuela to companies with existing oil production and assets over those seeking to enter the sanctioned OPEC nation for the first time, two people close to the discussions said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-favor-existing-investors-venezuela-oil-licenses-say-sources-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3NIIID25ZIK3P6HG3JQX2HYSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯股东再次选举托马斯-拉贝为董事长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，阿迪达斯大多数股东支持董事长托马斯-拉贝连任，他的任期将再延长一年，直至 2025 年，届时这家德国运动品牌将任命一位新董事长。【原文：A majority of Adidas shareholders backed the re-election of chairman Thomas Rabe on Thursday, securing his role for another year, until 2025 when the German sportswear brand will appoint a new chair.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-shareholders-re-elect-chairman-thomas-rabe-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZHVGZE2BVM5LFDZBK6DKTRDO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:43:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局允许美国联合航空公司重新启动认证活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周四表示，美国联邦航空管理局已允许该公司重新启动认证活动，包括新飞机和新航线。【原文：United Airlines said on Thursday the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration has permitted the carrier to restart its certification activities, including new aircraft and routes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-allows-united-airlines-restart-certification-activities-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7I4GYRPOZPVRN7IMA56NAWNKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:40:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>