<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:40:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:40:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[梅赛德斯首席执行官呼吁 "现实检查"，抨击欧盟内燃机禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰（Mercedes-Benz）首席执行官周一在接受媒体采访时批评了欧盟从2035年起禁止二氧化碳排放车辆的计划，并加入了今年即将对该目标进行审查的质疑声浪。【原文：The CEO of Mercedes-Benz criticised the European Union's plan to ban CO2-emitting vehicles from 2035 in a media interview on Monday, joining a chorus of voices calling the target into question as it comes up for review this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/mercedes-ceo-calls-reality-check-slamming-eu-combustion-engine-ban-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTBOA4EYMFMTVG64BO5IJBUREM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:27:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，乌克兰 Kyivstar 公司将在具有里程碑意义的美国上市中融资最多 2 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，乌克兰最大的电信运营商 Kyivstar 预计通过今年在纽约具有里程碑意义的股市上市融资 5000 万至 2 亿美元。【原文：Ukraine's biggest telecoms operator Kyivstar expects to raise between $50 million and $200 million through a landmark stock market listing in New York this year, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/ukraines-kyivstar-raise-up-200-million-landmark-us-listing-sources-say-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CD7RO4IUTRLVFHKBKRAK2PZG2A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:06:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度估计约 55% 的输美商品将面临特朗普关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府周一表示，印度出口到美国的商品中约有 55% 将受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府征收关税的影响。【原文：About 55% of India's merchandise exports to the United States will be subject to the tariff imposed by President Donald Trump's administration, the Indian government said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-estimates-about-55-goods-exported-us-will-face-trump-tariff-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VX23KIZAFNPCHGHM4IPNO2RTXA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:58:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[内阁官员称台湾将继续与美国进行关税谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收 20% 的关税后，台湾内阁仍在谈判更优惠的关税税率，副总理郑丽群周一表示。【原文：Taiwan's cabinet is still negotiating for more favourable tariff rates after a 20% levy was imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump, Vice Premier Cheng Li-chiun said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-is-continuing-tariff-negotiations-with-us-cabinet-official-says-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4AK7F2ILJM6ZMAVCJ25GFJORA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在印度，特朗普关税引发抵制美国商品的呼声]]></title><description><![CDATA[从麦当劳（McDonald's）和可口可乐（Coca-Cola）到亚马逊（Amazon）和苹果（Apple），总部设在美国的跨国公司在印度正面临抵制的呼声，因为企业高管和印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪（Narendra Modi）的支持者煽动反美情绪，抗议美国加征关税。【原文：From McDonald's and Coca-Cola to Amazon and Apple, U.S.-based multinationals are facing calls for a boycott in India as business executives and Prime Minister Narendra Modi's supporters stoke anti-American sentiment to protest against U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/india-trumps-tariffs-spark-calls-boycott-american-goods-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POWYEOIGQJNX5OTOH3KRMVA74Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:52:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行调查发现，"漫长的华丽七日 "再次成为全球最拥挤的行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国银行（BofA）的月度基金经理调查，随着乐观的盈利和全球经济情绪的改善，投资者重回股市，持有美国大型科技股再次成为最受欢迎的交易。【原文：Owning big U.S. tech stocks is once again the most popular trade, according to BofA's monthly fund manager survey, as upbeat earnings and improved sentiment towards the global economy send investors back into stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/long-magnificent-7-once-again-worlds-most-crowded-trade-bofa-survey-finds-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVDKN5DEV5PXDOTWUYIBL233AU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本不断加深的政治困境为预算和加息时间蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，日本政治不确定性的加深有可能延长政策瘫痪的时间，这可能会影响明年预算的起草和央行下次加息的时机，给脆弱的经济前景蒙上阴影。【原文：Japan's deepening political uncertainty risks prolonging policy paralysis that could affect the drafting of next year's budget and the timing of the central bank's next interest rate hike, analysts say, clouding the outlook for the fragile economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-deepening-political-woes-cloud-budget-rate-hike-timing-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEB5ILPKJRMH5OMOACP2KCDTIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 06:38:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 M&S 在系统被黑 15 周后恢复点击取货服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国零售商玛莎百货（Marks & Spencer）在遭遇网络黑客攻击和数据失窃后，暂停了 15 周，现已恢复接受服装点击提货订单。【原文：British retailer Marks & Spencer has resumed taking click and collect orders for clothing after a 15-week hiatus following a cyber hack and data theft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-ms-restores-click-collect-services-15-weeks-after-systems-hacked-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OL7TXEZKERMYTKDDIPDMG4KLHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 06:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普希望中国迅速将美国大豆订单翻两番]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，他希望中国将从美国订购的大豆数量翻两番，并补充说这也是 "大幅减少 "北京对华盛顿贸易逆差的 "一种方式"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday that he hoped China would quadruple its soybean orders from the U.S, adding that it was also "a way of substantially reducing" Beijing's trade deficit with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-hopes-china-will-quickly-quadruple-its-us-soybean-orders-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S47STUTWHZM3VIARSYZLKARKTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:38:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丹麦 Orsted 公司计划通过供股融资 94 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦风电场开发商 Orsted 周一表示，计划在丹麦政府作为大股东的支持下，进行 600 亿丹麦克朗（约合 93.8 亿美元）的供股。【原文：Danish wind farm developer Orsted said on Monday it plans a 60 billion Danish crowns ($9.38 billion) rights issue with support from the Danish State as majority shareholder.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/denmarks-orsted-plans-raise-94-billion-rights-issue-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJ4DDBOD3JKC5CICO3COSCTJUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:36:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国邮政阻止非法烟草运输，助力大烟草公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的信件显示，美国邮政服务局已经打击了使用其服务进行商业运输的未受管制的吸食器经销商，这是对一个数十亿美元的行业的打击，该行业削弱了大烟草公司的销售额。【原文：The U.S. Postal Service has cracked down on distributors of unregulated vapes using its services for business shipments, letters reviewed by Reuters show, in a blow to a multi-billion dollar industry that has dented Big Tobacco's sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/usps-blocks-shipping-illicit-vapes-boost-big-tobacco-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXN52FGPVZILHOFDNQTKIIN4YQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：日经指数有望重返历史高点俱乐部]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4B26PBHQJOAPEU3TWEKJQX6NI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:34:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债市动荡预示着对高送转股票的警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者正在退出或积极押注高价企业信贷，他们预计，由于经济增长放缓的迹象，高价企业信贷将出现调整，最终可能对股市产生影响。【原文：Investors are backing out of or taking active bets against high-priced corporate credit, where they anticipate a correction in response to signs of slowing economic growth that could eventually impact stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-credit-analysis-pix-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TB6QR5PXAVPSTNDBRZCXFBVRIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西联汇款将以约 5 亿美元收购 Intermex]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇款公司西联汇款（Western Union）周日表示，将以约 5 亿美元的现金收购 Intermex，Intermex 是一家专注于向拉丁美洲和加勒比地区汇款的美国公司。【原文：Money transfer company Western Union said on Sunday it will acquire Intermex , a U.S. firm that focuses on payment transfers to Latin America and the Caribbean, for about $500 million in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/western-union-acquire-intermex-about-500-million-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMKE5CQNJZMHRJPLZYMJQTMOFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:30:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rumble 考虑以接近 12 亿美元的价格收购德国人工智能云计算集团 Northern Data]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据两家公司的声明和路透社的计算，在美国上市的视频平台 Rumble 正在考虑以约 11.7 亿美元（10 亿欧元）的价格收购德国人工智能云集团 Northern Data AG。【原文：U.S.-listed video platform Rumble is considering a potential offer of about $1.17 billion (1 billion euro) for German AI cloud group Northern Data AG , according to separate statements from the companies and Reuters calculations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rumble-considers-near-12-billion-offer-german-ai-cloud-group-northern-data-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQVQXR2KMRM2HDERUTKLG3YL7E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:23:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元在通胀报告和中美关税截止日期前持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元在上周下跌后于周一企稳，因为市场在等待周二关键的美国7月份CPI报告，并关注华盛顿与中国政府在避免征收更高关税的最后期限前的贸易谈判进展。【原文：The U.S. dollar stabilised on Monday after last week's losses, as markets await Tuesday's key U.S. CPI report for July and focus on developments in trade talks between Washington and Beijing ahead of a deadline to avoid the imposition of higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dollar-steady-before-inflation-report-us-china-tariff-deadline-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XA7N4AZGXNNXVIT7ZDXSNW37TA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 01:54:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场关注美俄乌克兰问题会谈，油价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一亚市早盘，油价下跌，延续了上周超过4%的跌势，原因是美国对其贸易伙伴提高关税、欧佩克（OPEC）提高产量，以及人们预期美国和俄罗斯将更接近达成乌克兰停火协议。【原文：Oil prices fell in early Asian trading on Monday, extending declines of more than 4% last week on higher U.S. tariffs on its trading partners, an OPEC output hike, and expectations the U.S. and Russia were moving closer to a Ukraine ceasefire pact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-fall-market-eyes-us-russia-talks-ukraine-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RQTYTCD5TBKUJLDHLKPCB4CBAU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 01:25:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：为越南农民提供大量美元和大米，特朗普高尔夫俱乐部耗资 15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南农民阮氏香（Nguyen Thi Huong）睡不好觉，因为当局让她腾出自己的农场，用于特朗普家族支持的高尔夫度假村，而作为回报，她只得到了 3,200 美元和大米。【原文：Vietnamese farmer Nguyen Thi Huong has slept poorly since authorities told her to vacate her farm for a Trump family-backed golf resort, offering just $3,200 and rice provisions in return.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fistful-dollars-rice-vietnam-farmers-displaced-15-billion-trump-golf-club-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5NV2NNDCJOKDF7EWQ4H3PVVFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 01:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市上扬，美国通胀数据隐忧重重]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲主要股指走高，原因是乐观的公司盈利支撑了科技行业的高估值，而一份至关重要的美国通胀报告可能将决定美元和债券的走势。【原文：Major share indexes crept higher in Asia on Monday as upbeat company earnings underpinned high valuations in the tech sector, while a crucial report on U.S. inflation would likely set the course of the dollar and bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBNV5WKFSBJPNONP5YGCKLAPLM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:59:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，软银为支付应用 PayPay 的美国 IPO 挑选银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟知内情的人士透露，软银已选定投资银行，帮助组织旗下日本支付应用运营商 PayPay 可能在美国进行的首次公开募股。【原文：SoftBank has selected investment banks to help organize a potential initial public offering in the United States for its Japanese payments app operator PayPay, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/softbank-selects-banks-us-ipo-payments-app-paypay-sources-say-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MOSMCAP6CVPTRCC7HHDIJGE7W4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行新政策委员会增加了不可预测性]]></title><description><![CDATA[在全球不确定性已经很高的情况下，澳大利亚央行的沟通出现了问题，这给利率政策注入了不可预测性因素，而事实证明，这让投资者付出了高昂的代价。【原文：Australia's central bank has a problem communicating that has injected an element of unpredictability into interest rate policy when global uncertainty is already high, and its proving costly for investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rbas-new-policy-board-comes-with-added-unpredictability-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFWJVX4GNZK3XNV2I32ZOW6JOM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道SK 海力士预计到 2030 年人工智能内存市场每年将增长 30]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国 SK 海力士公司（SK Hynix）的一位高管在接受路透社采访时预测，一种专为人工智能设计的专用存储芯片的市场将在 2030 年前每年增长 30%。【原文：South Korea's SK Hynix forecasts that the market for a specialized form of memory chip designed for artificial intelligence will grow 30% a year until 2030, a senior executive said in an interview with Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/sk-hynix-expects-ai-memory-market-grow-30-year-2030-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDKK3R3UA5IDVJJFSLXHP34BHA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 22:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，英特尔首席执行官将于周一访问白宫]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周日援引知情人士的话报道，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普上周要求解除英特尔公司首席执行官陈立武的职务后，他将于周一访问白宫。【原文：Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan is set to visit the White House on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump called for his removal last week, the Wall Street Journal reported on Sunday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/intel-ceo-visit-white-house-monday-wsj-reports-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPM67XZRLZON5PKBZLZAAH7DHM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 21:45:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，贝森特表示，新任美联储主席应是能够审视组织的人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据日本《日经新闻》报道，美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）说，美联储新任主席应该是一个 "能够审视整个组织 "的人，因为美联储的使命包括了货币政策之外的许多事情，使其独立性面临风险。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said the new Federal Reserve chair should be someone "who can examine the whole organization" as the Fed's mission has included so many things outside of monetary policy and has put its independence at risk, Japan's Nikkei newspaper reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-says-new-fed-chair-should-be-someone-who-can-examine-organization-nikkei-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBNF5SEN2RMPTC2J7MBCSVCBIY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 21:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，英伟达和 AMD 将向美国政府缴纳中国芯片销售收入的 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周日报道，英伟达（Nvidia）和 AMD 已同意向美国政府提供在中国销售芯片收入的 15%，作为与特朗普政府达成的半导体出口许可安排的一部分。【原文：Nvidia and AMD have agreed to give the U.S. government 15% of the revenues from chip sales in China, as part of an arrangement with the Trump administration to obtain export licenses for the semiconductors, the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-amd-pay-15-china-chip-sale-revenues-us-government-ft-reports-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZ3NOJRKPBJITFBYA2EGIICXPE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 20:55:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥设定新鲜番茄最低出口价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥经济部和农业部周日在一份联合声明中说，在与美国达成的双边协议到期后，墨西哥为新鲜番茄设定了最低出口价格，以保护其国内生产并确保国内供应。【原文：Mexico has set minimum export prices for fresh tomatoes to protect its domestic production and ensure internal supply after a bilateral agreement with the U.S. expired, Mexico's economy and agriculture ministries said in a joint statement on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-sets-minimum-export-prices-fresh-tomatoes-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHLWJG5TVJMNZKNMJN556FKLYU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 17:41:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加航空姐组织全国行动抗议工作条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大公共雇员工会（Canadian Union of Public Employees）在周日的一份声明中说，加航空乘人员将于周一在加拿大主要机场同时举行行动，抗议工作条件，并要求承认关键的谈判问题。【原文：Air Canada flight attendants will hold simultaneous actions at major Canadian airports on Monday to protest working conditions and demand recognition of key bargaining issues, the Canadian Union of Public Employees said in a statement on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/air-canada-flight-attendants-organize-national-action-protest-working-conditions-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZA654ZZBNIFVGAWOEXEJALMFA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:28:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者比尔-阿克曼提议合并房利美和房地美]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）在周日的 X 帖子中建议合并美国政府资助的企业房利美（Fannie Mae）和房地美（Freddie Mac），认为此举将有助于降低抵押贷款利率，并在运营和交易价格方面实现巨大的协同效应。【原文：Billionaire investor Bill Ackman in an X post on Sunday suggested merging U.S. government-sponsored enterprises Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, suggesting the move would help reduce mortgage rates and achieve huge synergies both in their operations and in the trading price.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investor-bill-ackman-proposes-combining-fannie-mae-freddie-mac-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2ZRDENPVZMBROGONGXY3MIVSY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 14:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的 401(k) 令为退休投资组合增加了新的风险层]]></title><description><![CDATA[虽然对私募股权、加密货币或私人控股公司的投资可以提供更高的回报，但批评者认为，与传统退休计划相比，这些投资缺乏同样的信息披露，费用也更高。【原文：While investments in private equity, crypto or privately held companies could offer higher returns, critics say they lack the same disclosures and carry higher fees than traditional retirement plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-401k-order-offers-retirement-savers-crypto-private-assets-also-higher-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7IPTE3EAJIAHGAIUS5F6OLRCE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 10:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国家媒体称英伟达 H20 芯片对中国不安全]]></title><description><![CDATA[隶属于中国国家媒体的一个社交媒体账户周日称，英伟达（Nvidia）的 H20 芯片给中国带来了安全隐患，此前中国政府对这些芯片的后门访问提出了担忧。【原文：Nvidia's H20 chips pose security concerns for China, a social media account affiliated with China's state media said on Sunday, after Beijing raised concerns over backdoor access in those chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-state-media-says-nvidia-h20-chips-not-safe-china-2025-08-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UM6N5FCJZRMKTBQOPFVGQUDE3U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:08:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>