<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:04:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:04:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[白宫称让联邦贸易委员会委员离职的 "时机已到]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普解雇联邦贸易委员会两位民主党委员的决定辩护，称让他们离职的 "时机已经成熟"。【原文：The White House on Wednesday defended U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to fire two Democratic commissioners at the Federal Trade Commission, saying the "time was right" to let them go.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-says-time-was-right-let-ftc-commissioners-go-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEE72XU4OBJMXM4MUM63R2KAVM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会起诉特朗普政府停止学生贷款偿还计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一个主要的教师工会对教育部提起诉讼，指控共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府非法关闭了数百万学生贷款者使用的收入驱动还款计划。【原文：A major U.S. teachers union has filed a lawsuit against the Department of Education accusing Republican President Donald Trump's administration of unlawfully shutting down access to income-driven repayment plans used by millions of student loan borrowers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/union-sues-trump-administration-halting-student-loan-repayment-plans-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFEJQ3XSRZNUVEDWHGLW2NKNBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:52:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府指责法官在委内瑞拉驱逐案中越权行事]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国首席大法官约翰-罗伯茨（John Roberts）斥责共和党总统要求弹劾一名联邦法官之后一天，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周三在一份文件中指责一名联邦法官越权要求提供有关委内瑞拉移民驱逐航班的更多细节。【原文：Donald Trump's administration accused a federal judge on Wednesday of overstepping his judicial authority in demanding more details about deportation flights of Venezuelan migrants in a filing made a day after U.S. Chief Justice John Roberts rebuked the Republican president for calling for the judge's impeachment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-accuses-judge-overstepping-venezuela-deportations-case-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7D6FQVFJ75L5NOH4INGRIPNUEE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将于 2026 年底前在 74 个机场安装跑道安全技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）表示，到 2026 年底，将在 74 个机场安装增强型安全技术，帮助检测跑道入侵。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said it will install enhanced safety technology to help detect runway incursions at 74 airports by the end of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-install-runway-safety-technology-74-airports-by-end-2026-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMCEUSKWG5KD3DUY44M36V7HN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:50:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发布州和地方备灾行政命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周三发布了一项行政命令，涉及州和地方基础设施应对野火和飓风等自然灾害以及网络攻击等其他威胁的准备工作。【原文：President Donald Trump issued an executive order on Wednesday related to state and local infrastructure preparedness for responding to natural disasters such as wildfires and hurricanes, along with other threats like cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-issues-state-local-preparedness-executive-order-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNWFEFRXDFJJRAXSDLEH5FO2GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:41:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁是特朗普政府移民诉讼案的法官詹姆斯-博斯伯格？]]></title><description><![CDATA[这位暂时阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府援引战时权力驱逐移民的美国法官多年来一直在处理涉及敏感安全或政治问题的高风险案件--有时会做出有利于特朗普的裁决。【原文：The U.S. judge who temporarily blocked President Donald Trump’s administration from invoking wartime powers to deport migrants has for years handled high-stakes cases involving sensitive security or political issues - sometimes ruling in Trump's favor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/who-is-james-boasberg-judge-trump-administration-immigration-fight-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBFELVG2FVMFJK5UQO5L3TWXWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 10:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战迫在眉睫，特朗普将宴请美国顶级石油公司总裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将于周三在白宫接待石油行业的高层管理人员，他将阐述在原油价格下跌和贸易战迫在眉睫的情况下促进国内能源生产的计划。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will host top oil executives at the White House on Wednesday as he charts plans to boost domestic energy production in the midst of falling crude prices and looming trade wars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-host-top-us-oil-chief-executives-trade-wars-loom-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJLGZRY5SBO4FFAXWADV45EFAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 10:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普向普京靠拢，美国暂停部分反俄破坏行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普政府推动俄罗斯结束乌克兰战争之际，美国多个国家安全机构停止了打击俄罗斯破坏、造谣和网络攻击的协调工作，从而减轻了对莫斯科的压力。【原文：Several U.S. national security agencies have halted work on a coordinated effort to counter Russian sabotage, disinformation and cyberattacks, easing pressure on Moscow as the Trump Administration pushes Russia to end its war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-suspends-some-efforts-counter-russian-sabotage-trump-moves-closer-putin-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJBFNQNGT5PRLAURW4XVBDLXYE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 06:06:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普渡制药公司为 74 亿美元阿片类药物和解申请新的破产计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[破产制药商普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）周二提交了一份新的破产计划，这是去年在美国最高法院受挫后，该公司朝着最终达成至少 74 亿美元的阿片类药物和解协议迈出的重要一步。【原文：Bankrupt drugmaker Purdue Pharma filed a new bankruptcy plan on Tuesday, a major step towards finalizing a proposed opioid settlement of at least $7.4 billion after a setback in the U.S. Supreme Court last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/purdue-pharma-files-new-bankruptcy-plan-74-billion-opioid-settlement-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DT334CAHWRLNLKSOOZFGGNJC5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 05:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普削减美国新闻机构被批向中国和对手让步]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国立法者和人权倡导者说，在中国政府急于扩大其势力范围之际，特朗普政府解散美国政府资助的新闻机构，包括美国之音和自由亚洲电台，是对华盛顿来之不易的全球软实力的重大打击。【原文：U.S. lawmakers and rights advocates say the Trump administration's drive to dismantle U.S. government-funded news outlets, including Voice of America and Radio Free Asia, is a major blow to Washington's hard-earned soft power globally at a time when Beijing is rushing to expand its sphere of influence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-cuts-us-news-outlets-criticized-ceding-ground-china-adversaries-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIQ3ISKTPNKY5IQ247SERLOG6M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 04:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止特朗普的环保局收回气候拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一名美国法官暂时阻止美国环境保护局收回作为 200 亿美元气候资助计划一部分发放的赠款，共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已采取行动终止该计划。【原文：A U.S. judge on Tuesday temporarily blocked the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency from recovering grant funds issued as part of a $20 billion climate funding program that Republican President Donald Trump's administration has moved to terminate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-trumps-epa-clawing-back-climate-grants-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR2XXCBJ4NP2PPLOLETVV2JHOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止特朗普的环保局收回气候拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一名美国法官暂时阻止美国环境保护局收回作为 200 亿美元气候资助计划一部分发放的赠款，共和党总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已采取行动终止该计划。【原文：A U.S. judge on Tuesday temporarily blocked the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency from recovering grant funds issued as part of a $20 billion climate funding program that Republican President Donald Trump's administration has moved to terminate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-trumps-epa-clawing-back-climate-grants-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR2XXCBJ4NP2PPLOLETVV2JHOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府取消对联邦合同中 "隔离设施 "的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总务管理局发布的一份备忘录显示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已经取消了对联邦承包商等候室、餐厅和饮水机等 "隔离设施 "的明确禁令。【原文：The administration of U.S. President Donald Trump has removed an explicit ban on "segregated facilities" like waiting rooms, restaurants and drinking fountains for federal contractors, a memo issued by the U.S. General Services Administration showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-removes-ban-segregated-facilities-federal-contracts-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KORKRBDCFKM7DJ2O3VVVN4MSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 02:20:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国指控海地黑帮头目伊佐劫持一名美国公民为人质]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国华盛顿检察官办公室周二发表声明称，美国检察官指控海地黑帮头目约翰逊-安德烈（Johnson Andre）（绰号 "伊佐 "Izo）在海地劫持一名美国公民为人质。【原文：Prosecutors in the United States have charged powerful Haitian gang leader Johnson Andre, known as Izo, with taking a U.S. citizen hostage in Haiti, according to a statement from the U.S. Attorney's Office in Washington released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-charges-haitian-gang-leader-izo-with-hostage-taking-us-citizen-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALLFXPR2ZBI5PBWTJBBJLHT7MY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 01:57:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被特朗普解雇的两位联邦贸易委员会民主党委员是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周二解雇了联邦贸易委员会的两位民主党委员。【原文：President Donald Trump fired the two Democratic commissioners at the Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/who-are-two-democratic-ftc-commissioners-fired-by-trump-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OFB7QKNM5L3DI434DGM5VP3CI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 01:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令，将联邦紧急事务管理局的备灾工作移交给各州和地方政府]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二签署了一项行政命令，试图将备灾责任转移给州政府和地方政府，从而深化他对联邦紧急事务管理局的改革。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday signed an executive order that seeks to shift responsibility for disaster preparations to state and local governments, deepening his drive to overhaul the Federal Emergency Management Agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-signs-order-shift-disaster-preparations-fema-states-local-governments-2025-03-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JHWGZVIQRPBJNK4OC4VUYPFUI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2022 年得克萨斯州 53 名移民因偷渡死亡，两人被判有罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[司法部表示，得克萨斯州圣安东尼奥的一个联邦陪审团周二判定两名墨西哥男子有罪，他们在 2022 年 6 月酷热难耐的天气中将 53 名移民挤在一辆卡车上偷运致死的事件中扮演了重要角色。【原文：A federal jury in San Antonio, Texas on Tuesday convicted two Mexican men for their roles in the smuggling death of 53 migrants packed into a truck during sweltering heat in June 2022, the Justice Department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/two-convicted-smuggling-death-53-migrants-texas-2022-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLRLP5HQTFMETNEOOQCCATKSOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 23:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府正在权衡疾病预防控制中心艾滋病预防部门的未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生部周二表示，正在审查疾病控制和预防中心的艾滋病预防部门是否与其他机构重叠，但尚未就该部门的未来做出最终决定。【原文：The U.S. health department said on Tuesday it is reviewing the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's HIV prevention division for overlap with other agencies but no final decision had been made about its future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-weighing-future-cdcs-hiv-prevention-division-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2G75PDUWFPJ7OPK4VQ4V7K67U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 23:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部长称针对特斯拉财产的袭击为 "国内恐怖主义]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部长帕姆-邦迪（Pam Bondi）周二谴责了最近对特斯拉财产的暴力袭击，并补充说司法部已经起诉了几名肇事者。【原文：U.S. Attorney General Pam Bondi on Tuesday condemned recent violent attacks on Tesla property, adding the Department of Justice has already charged several perpetrators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-attorney-general-calls-attacks-against-tesla-property-domestic-terrorism-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECQR565XRVK6ZHJPF3CEUVMKFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 23:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止特朗普的变性人军事禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二暂时阻止美国军方执行唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统禁止变性人服兵役的行政命令，与此同时，20 名现役和即将服役的变性人对该措施提出质疑的诉讼正在进行中。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday temporarily blocked the U.S. military from enforcing President Donald Trump's executive order barring transgender people from military service while a lawsuit by 20 current and would-be service members challenging the measure goes forward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-blocks-trumps-transgender-military-ban-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FILCIR6X5NDRHSCKIQKXZN5RE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 22:57:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国威胁因纽约地铁事件扣留公交资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）周二威胁说，将因一系列地铁安全事件和其他问题扣留纽约大都会运输局的联邦交通资金。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy on Tuesday threatened to withhold federal transit funds from New York's Metropolitan Transportation Authority over a series of security incidents on subways and other issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-threatens-withhold-transit-funds-over-new-york-subway-incidents-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5VKSALKCJJHDPDARYOLO5CSCQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 22:54:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：如果特朗普政府不遵守法院命令会怎样？]]></title><description><![CDATA[几位联邦法官声称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府未能遵守法院有关对外援助、联邦开支和解雇政府工作人员的命令，而政府对此提出了异议。【原文：Several federal judges have claimed the administration of U.S. President Donald Trump has failed to comply with court orders regarding foreign aid, federal spending and the firing of government workers, which the administration disputes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/what-happens-if-trump-administration-doesnt-comply-with-court-order-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Q3EWGXJYBJ7NDQTRVCRLCWFWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 22:31:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，白宫聘请卡利-米恩斯为政府特别顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道称，白宫已任命美国卫生与公众服务部部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪的盟友卡利-米恩斯（Calley Means）为白宫顾问和 "特殊政府雇员"。【原文：The White House has appointed Calley Means, an ally of U.S. Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., as a White House adviser and "special government employee," Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-hires-calley-means-special-government-adviser-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQ2P4Q4645NZBF4L4BIRIZNJXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 21:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一些美国律师谴责特朗普的命令，而他们的律师事务所却保持沉默]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）因多元化政策和政治客户问题将矛头对准了大型律师事务所，这招致了法学教授、律师协会和一位联邦法官的谴责，但到目前为止，其他律师事务所还没有这样做。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's targeting of major law firms over their diversity policies and political clients has earned condemnation from law professors, bar associations and a federal judge - but not, so far, from other law firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/some-us-lawyers-decry-trump-orders-their-law-firms-stay-silent-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLQFH23R35PRJLUPOOGOQJC4UM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 21:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JD Vance 将在 2026 年中期选举前领导共和党筹款工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[该党周二表示，副总统 JD Vance 将担任共和党全国委员会财务主席，这将为他在下届总统竞选中与保守派顶级捐赠者面对面交流提供宝贵的时间。【原文：Vice President JD Vance will serve as the finance chair of the Republican National Committee, the party said on Tuesday, a role that will give him valuable face time with top conservative donors heading into the next presidential campaign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/jd-vance-tapped-lead-republican-party-fundraising-ahead-2026-midterm-elections-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6YRI7IQUJIIRE5LBYNLZJGBAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 21:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称，特朗普解雇了联邦贸易委员会的两位民主党委员]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉情况的消息人士称，唐纳德-特朗普总统周二解雇了美国联邦贸易委员会的两位民主党委员，这是对监管机构独立性的又一次重大考验。【原文：President Donald Trump fired the two Democratic commissioners at the U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday, two sources familiar with the situation said, in another major test of the independence of regulatory agencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-fires-both-democratic-commissioners-ftc-sources-say-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAOWMGSVCFO7PN5I6VEETLGVC4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 21:06:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普能源贷款办公室主任本周离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部周二表示，美国政府能源贷款办公室负责人将于本周离职，该办公室曾为唐纳德-特朗普总统的共和党同僚之一支持的核电和可持续航空燃料工厂等项目提供融资。【原文：The head of the U.S. government's energy loans office that has provided financing to projects from nuclear power to a sustainable aviation fuel plant supported by one of President Donald Trump's fellow Republicans will depart the agency this week, the U.S. Department of Energy said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/head-trumps-energy-loan-office-departs-this-week-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANBZE554SZOL7LQRD5MKM3C4RA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉获得在加利福尼亚州运行机器人轴所需的一系列许可中的第一个许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[据加利福尼亚州监管机构称，特斯拉已获得加利福尼亚州一系列批准中的首批批准，这是这家电动汽车制造商最终在该州推出其承诺的机器人出租车服务所必需的。【原文：Tesla has been granted the first in a series of approvals from California that would be required for the electric car maker to eventually launch a promised robotaxi service in the state, according to a state regulator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-gets-first-series-permits-it-needs-run-robotaxis-california-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XHR5U3OCJI33N3QHIF4WYW5ME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄亥俄州上诉法院驳回对变性未成年人的一些医疗限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄亥俄州一家上诉法院周二阻止该州执行一项禁止未成年人使用青春期阻断药物和激素进行性别转换的法律，认为该法律侵犯了父母决定子女医疗的权利。【原文：An Ohio appeals court on Tuesday blocked the state from enforcing a law banning the use of puberty-blocking drugs and hormones for gender transition in minors, finding it violated parents' rights to decide their children's medical treatment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/ohio-appeals-court-strikes-down-some-healthcare-restrictions-transgender-minors-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUEUFN4XOZPVXOYHZHUHPUWNOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官禁止马斯克和能源与环境部进一步关闭美国国际开发署]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二阻止亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）及其政府效率部（Department of Government Efficiency）采取任何进一步措施关闭美国国际开发署（U.S. Agency for International Development），称他们关闭该机构的努力可能违反了美国宪法。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday blocked billionaire Elon Musk and his Department of Government Efficiency from taking any more steps to shut down the U.S. Agency for International Development, saying their efforts to close the agency likely violated the U.S. Constitution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-bars-musk-doge-further-efforts-shut-down-usaid-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYOCGY7VN5K5DLXT7MMRHQE2TY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:16:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>