<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:46:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[油气公司 EOG 通过 56 亿美元的恩西诺交易加强了在尤蒂卡的布局]]></title><description><![CDATA[EOG Resources 周五表示，该公司将以 56 亿美元（包括债务）收购美国油气生产商 Encino Acquisition Partners，以加强其在尤蒂卡页岩地区的布局。【原文：EOG Resources said on Friday it is acquiring U.S. oil and gas producer Encino Acquisition Partners for $5.6 billion, including debt, to strengthen its Utica shale footprint.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eog-resources-buy-encino-acquisition-partners-56-billion-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVJJI6GJMVOMBDFXFM2H4DADT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:13:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道矿商淡水河谷错过扩建巴西镍矿联合企业的最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西电网运营商 ONS 告诉路透社，该公司拒绝了矿商淡水河谷提出的增加其北部 Onca Puma 镍矿联合企业用电量的请求，因为该公司错过了确认竞标的最后期限。【原文：Brazilian power grid operator ONS told Reuters it denied miner Vale's request to increase power consumption at its northern Onca Puma nickel complex, after missing a deadline to confirm the bid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/miner-vale-misses-deadline-power-expand-brazil-nickel-complex-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U34J6K3LFBK73K7XCCNUSTBDX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受贸易紧张局势影响，美国股票基金迎来每周赎回潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至5月28日的一周内，美国股票基金连续第二周面临资金外流，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税威胁和对借贷成本上升的担忧促使投资者削减对美国资产的投资。【原文：U.S. equity funds faced a second successive weekly outflow in the week through May 28 as tariff threats from President Donald Trump and concerns over rising borrowing costs prompted investors to cut exposure to U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-weekly-redemptions-trade-tensions-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2B6F74XYZPOJANWAWZB22334Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+加息、贸易担忧挥之不去，油价前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于欧佩克+供应膨胀以及贸易争端对燃料需求影响的不确定性挥之不去，分析师连续第三个月下调了油价预测。【原文：Analysts have revised down their oil price forecasts for the third consecutive month as swelling OPEC+ supply and lingering uncertainty around the impact of trade disputes on fuel demand weigh on prices, a Reuters poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-price-outlook-weakens-opec-hikes-lingering-trade-concerns-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNH3NXDRRNMDHB4EV44IF6HVBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Zara 创始人奥特加以 2.83 亿美元买下巴塞罗那办公楼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，两位熟悉交易的消息人士称，Zara 创始人 Amancio Ortega 以 2.5 亿欧元（2.83 亿美元）的价格从 Blackstone 手中买下了巴塞罗那的一栋办公楼。【原文：Zara founder Amancio Ortega has bought an office building in Barcelona from Blackstone for 250 million euros ($283 million), two sources familiar with the transaction said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/zara-founder-ortega-buys-barcelona-office-building-283-million-sources-say-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KCU43NXBZIW7B4P5GQHXCCDVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税担忧导致全球股票基金第二周资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至5月28日，全球股票基金连续第二周出现资金外流，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁对欧盟进口商品和海外生产的苹果手机征收关税后，避险情绪升温，同时长期限债券收益率飙升。【原文：Global equity funds posted outflows for a second straight week through May 28, as risk aversion rose following U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats on EU imports and overseas-made iPhones, alongside a spike in long-tenor bond yields.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZ7GFF4G4ROIBAFIKFWY43R3WM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:20:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普以美国关税和中国市场竞争为由下调沃尔沃汽车评级展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P周五将沃尔沃汽车公司（Volvo Cars）的BB+信用评级展望从 "稳定 "下调至 "负面"，称美国关税和中国更激烈的竞争正在损害该公司的增长前景。【原文：S&amp;P on Friday lowered the outlook for its BB+ credit rating on Volvo Cars to "negative" from "stable", saying U.S. tariffs and tougher competition in China were hurting the company's growth prospects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/sp-lowers-outlook-volvo-cars-rating-citing-us-tariffs-competition-china-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZQISY52B5JFXMZ6W7AJZQNNUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:54:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管西芒杜供应迫在眉睫，但铁矿石悲观情绪有所减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和贸易商表示，由于今年全球过剩量低于预期，铁矿石价格前景正在改善，但几内亚西芒杜巨型项目的新供应量迫在眉睫，这仍是铁矿石价格长期下行的一个风险。【原文：The prospects for iron ore prices are improving thanks to a lower than expected global surplus this year, analysts and traders say, though looming new supply from the giant Simandou project in Guinea remains a long-term downside risk for prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/iron-ore-pessimism-subsides-despite-looming-simandou-supply-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJ7JEZCZMJICTPWCVM2BIJICCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：关税回归与资本税担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLG7CBLO2FOWZLZWOHLTYP6AT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吸烟者肺部用药的试验数据好坏参半，导致 Regeneron 股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Regeneron 公司治疗一种俗称 "吸烟肺 "的肺部疾病患者的实验性药物在一项后期试验中失败，但在另一项试验中获得成功，因此该公司股价在周五收盘前下跌了近 13%。【原文：Regeneron shares fell nearly 13% before the bell on Friday after its experimental drug for patients with a type of lung condition commonly called "smoker's lung" failed a late-stage trial, although it succeeded in another.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/regeneron-shares-slide-mixed-trial-data-smokers-lung-drug-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BKC5ID7FIJOFROMKGRXIY7D2GA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德债锚可防止欧元区曲线过度陡峭化]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对高债务和债券销售的担忧，全球政府债券大跌，欧元区也未能幸免，但德国日益增长的避险地位应能保护欧元区免受长期借贷成本过度上升的影响。【原文：A global selloff in government bonds due to concerns over high debt and bond sales has not left the euro zone unscathed, but Germany's growing safe-haven status should shield the bloc from an excessive rise in long-term borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/german-bund-anchor-can-shield-euro-area-excessive-curve-steepening-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B566QAZRPJLNHNCP5Q3UEUO6ZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:29:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院作出最新裁决后，特朗普的关税政策保持不变，华尔街期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街期货周五下滑，原因是投资者考虑到上诉法院决定撤销此前阻止美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收大部分关税的裁决。【原文：Wall Street futures slipped on Friday, as investors took stock of an appeals court decision to undo a prior ruling that had blocked most of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, heading into the last trading day of a solid month for equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-down-trumps-tariffs-stay-put-after-latest-court-ruling-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVL53ENS7VIWFFHAZRR5UKNBIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4 月份中国外资品牌手机销量上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家政府下属研究公司周五公布的数据显示，包括苹果公司 iPhone 手机在内的外国品牌手机 4 月份在中国的销量有所上升。【原文：Sales of foreign-branded mobile phones in China, including Apple Inc's iPhones, edged up in April, according to data released by a government-affiliated research company on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/foreign-branded-mobile-phone-sales-china-edge-up-april-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYPM6LPD3ZNQPPOLHBZK7MPSIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[税收法案包含特朗普报复外国数字税的 "大锤]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国国会正在审议的全面税收法案中的一项条款，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将有权对那些向亚马逊和 Alphabet 等美国大型科技公司征收特殊数字服务税的国家进行报复。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump would have the power to retaliate against countries that impose special digital service taxes on large U.S. technology companies like Amazon and Alphabet, under a provision in the sweeping tax bill that Congress is considering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/tax-bill-contains-sledgehammer-trump-retaliate-against-foreign-digital-taxes-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FE4FI254FRIYHPF64S5E54OIVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥希望尽早审议《美国与墨西哥关于建立更紧密经贸关系的协定》（USMCA）能够结束不确定性，重振投资信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资下降、经济增长放缓以及美国总统唐纳德-特朗普不断变化的奇思妙想促使墨西哥支持尽早审查美国-墨西哥-加拿大（USMCA）贸易协定，这与墨西哥之前打算尽可能拖延时间的计划大相径庭。【原文：Falling investment, slowing growth, and the changing whims of U.S. President Donald Trump have led Mexico to support an early review of the U.S.-Mexico-Canada (USMCA) trade agreement, a sharp U-turn on its previous plan to hold off for as long as possible.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-hopes-early-review-usmca-can-end-uncertainty-revive-flagging-investment-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YX5UYYOYBI4RCTW2KKOC5FOKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:09:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与司法部将在美国搜索反垄断案中展开最后一搏]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌和美国反垄断执法机构将就科技巨头是否应被迫出售其 Chrome 浏览器或采取其他措施以恢复在线搜索领域的竞争展开最后的辩论。【原文：Alphabet's Google and U.S. antitrust enforcers will make their final arguments on whether the tech giant should be forced to sell its Chrome browser or adopt other measures to restore competition in online search, as the blockbuster antitrust trial concludes on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-doj-make-final-push-us-search-antitrust-case-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXHODDDJEZOMBCMLIN35RZ5PWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 就业数据、税改法案和贸易问题将推动美股反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国股市逼近历史高点，关键的美国经济数据、联邦税收和支出立法的发展以及贸易问题的波折都将在未来一周影响股市。【原文：Key U.S. economic data, developments with federal tax-and-spending legislation and twists and turns on trade all are poised to influence equities in the coming week, with the U.S. market closing in on record highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-jobs-data-tax-bill-trade-tap-rebounding-us-stocks-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2OKAO3QVFPKFCQ7ZDYFMKSBE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在宾夕法尼亚州工厂集会庆祝新日铁 "交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五将前往宾夕法尼亚州匹兹堡，主持一场集会，庆祝新日铁与美国钢铁公司 "计划中的合作伙伴关系"，这意味着该交易可能即将获得最终批准。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump heads to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania on Friday to headline a rally to celebrate Nippon Steel's "planned partnership" with U.S. Steel , signaling final approval for the deal could be on the horizon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-celebrates-nippon-steel-deal-with-rally-pennsylvania-plant-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNGXFN4W2RLX3OUPU3S67TION4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克说他在用电锯锯政府开支。这更像是修剪]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）曾在舞台上挥舞电锯，以戏剧性的方式展示了他在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统领导下大幅削减美国联邦政府开支的努力。随着他离开政府，官方数据显示，他的成果更接近于用剪刀修剪。【原文：Elon Musk once famously wielded a chainsaw on stage in a theatrical demonstration of his effort to drastically cut U.S. federal spending under President Donald Trump. As he leaves government, official data shows he achieved something closer to a trim with scissors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/musk-said-he-was-chainsawing-government-spending-it-was-more-like-trim-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIHVLYUWDJJDLF7LDTK6VP2YVU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者认为美股涨势扩大，即使 "华丽七雄 "出现反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周，巨型科技股和成长股重新夺回了美国市场的领导地位，但投资者表示，目前存在的一些因素可能会让更多股票在今年余下的时间里跑赢大盘。【原文：Megacap technology and growth stocks have retaken U.S. market leadership in recent weeks, but investors say that factors are in place that could allow a broader group of stocks to outperform for the rest of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-see-us-stocks-rally-broadening-even-magnificent-seven-rebound-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCJOBNFZ5NKYPJIFUPALSPI45Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟官员称，美国法院对关税提出质疑，欧盟在贸易谈判中获得筹码]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟官员周五表示，在美国法院对华盛顿 "对等 "关税的合法性提出质疑后，欧盟在与美国的贸易谈判中获得了筹码。【原文：The European Union has gained leverage in trade talks with the United States after a U.S. court cast doubt on the legality of Washington's "reciprocal" tariffs, EU officials said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-gains-leverage-trade-talks-us-court-casts-doubt-tariffs-eu-officials-say-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RT72OAJ4F5OXBFHNGNFYYZNWEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:34:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长帕内塔警告称，加密货币损失会损害人们对银行的信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行决策者兼意大利银行行长法比奥-帕内塔（Fabio Panetta）周五呼吁密切关注银行在提供加密资产服务时面临的声誉风险，并警告说损失可能会损害客户的信任。【原文：European Central Bank policymaker and Bank of Italy Governor Fabio Panetta called on Friday for close monitoring of the reputational risks banks face in providing crypto-asset services, warning that losses could harm the trust of customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecbs-panetta-warns-crypto-losses-can-harm-confidence-banks-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W54D7KQ5YFJG5G6FGXDMLAQYQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在稀土出口限制方面的立场趋于缓和]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于稀土短缺导致欧洲和印度的汽车和半导体制造商面临倒闭风险，中国表示将就稀土出口管制问题与其他国家进一步合作。【原文：China said it would cooperate further with other countries over its rare earth export controls as shortages put auto and semiconductor makers in Europe and India at risk of closure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-signals-softer-stance-rare-earth-export-curbs-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLRVXYRORJJYNGCBPFEYJAAFHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:26:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪高管称中国主流汽车制造商无 "恒大 "风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国顶级电动汽车制造商比亚迪的一位高管周五表示，中国主流汽车制造商中不存在 "恒大 "风险。【原文：An executive at top Chinese electric vehicle manufacturer BYD said on Friday there was no "Evergrande" risk among mainstream Chinese automakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-executive-says-no-evergrande-risk-among-mainstream-chinese-automakers-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVE53H2XTNMR3OQKIZBLKRF7KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，Zeekr 投资者批评吉利 22 亿美元的私有化出价不足]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位直接了解此事的消息人士称，中国吉利提出的 22 亿美元私有化要约低估了其高端电动汽车部门 Zeekr 的价值，Zeekr 的五位早期投资者已致函董事会。【原文：China's Geely is undervaluing its premium electric car unit Zeekr with the $2.2 billion take-private offer it has made, five early investors in Zeekr have written to its board, according to three sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/zeekr-investors-criticise-geelys-22-billion-take-private-bid-inadequate-say-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45IKHEGMJVK2NMA5GYYOUBU6KA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院称，25 人因企图绑架加密货币被法国法官传讯]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴黎法院称，25 人将于周五被带见调查法官，罪名是企图绑架一名富有的加密货币商人的女儿，以及共谋犯罪。【原文：Twenty-five people will be brought before an investigating judge on Friday for attempting to kidnap the daughter of a wealthy crypto businessman and for criminal conspiracy, the Paris court said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/twenty-five-people-hauled-before-french-judge-crypto-kidnapping-attempt-court-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKBW3I2FWJOGXMHV6VBNNLHXCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷高价拍卖 10 亿美元债务，向金融秩序迈出第一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷七年来首次大规模出售债券，发行 10 亿美元，以比索支付，这清楚地表明，全球投资者正在重拾对这个最近深陷三位数通胀的国家的信心。【原文：Argentina's first major bond sale in seven years, a $1 billion offering with payments in pesos, is a clear sign that global investors are regaining their faith in a country recently mired in triple-digit inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-takes-baby-step-toward-financial-order-with-pricey-1-billion-debt-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRMQLQEBOJLNRJNGJH7CERBGIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦敦证券交易所集团任命施罗德主席伊丽莎白-科利为董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦证券交易所集团周五表示，英国基金管理公司施罗德（Schroders）董事长伊丽莎白-科利（Elizabeth Corley）将加入该公司董事会，担任非执行董事。【原文：London Stock Exchange Group said on Friday Elizabeth Corley, chair of British fund manager Schroders , will join its board of as a non-executive director.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/lseg-appoints-schroders-chair-elizabeth-corley-board-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AEXHMK24DVPKJMCRO5ANTTDHQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:58:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院认为有足够证据继续审理 Grifols 对高谭市的诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Grifols 周五在一份声明中说，纽约一家法院发现了足够的证据，可以继续审理西班牙制药公司 Grifols 对做空机构 Gotham City Research 提起的诽谤诉讼。【原文：A New York court found enough evidence to continue with the defamation lawsuit filed by Spanish pharmaceutical company Grifols against short seller Gotham City Research, Grifols said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-court-finds-enough-evidence-proceed-with-grifols-lawsuit-against-gotham-city-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUAXDIBG2VI7TBL4MZPITELUFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对华乙烷出口因许可证要求遭遇新障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[据贸易消息来源和航运数据显示，在美国商务部要求出口商申请对华出口许可证后，中国对美国乙烷（一种重要的石化原料）的采购面临新的不确定性。【原文：Chinese purchases of U.S. ethane, a key petrochemical feedstock, face fresh uncertainty after the Commerce Department told exporters to seek licences to export to China, according to trade sources and shipping data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-ethane-exports-china-hit-new-roadblock-with-licence-requirement-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZC2RL3D6HJM6PO3EMGB6RONJNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>