<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:04:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:04:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，德国经济研究所将 2025 年的经济增长预测下调至 0.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士周二告诉路透社，德国经济机构已将今年的经济增长预期从9月份的0.8%下调至0.1%，并补充说这一调整尚未包括美国最新宣布的关税。【原文：German economic institutes have cut their forecast for this year to 0.1% growth from the 0.8% growth expected in September, two sources told Reuters on Tuesday, adding that the revision does not include yet the latest tariffs announced by the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-economic-institutes-cut-forecast-2025-01-growth-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IA33KY3DB5MAFN6XFISYGVNCNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 X 公司达成协议，将 Twitch 从广告支出诉讼中撤诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 公司已达成一项协议，以解决关于直播流媒体服务公司 Twitch 与其他公司和一个广告行业组织合谋抵制该社交媒体平台，导致其广告收入减少的指控。【原文：Elon Musk’s X has reached an agreement to resolve claims that live streaming service Twitch conspired with other companies and an advertising industry group to boycott the social media platform, causing it to lose ad revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/musks-x-reaches-deal-drop-twitch-lawsuit-over-ad-spending-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TDVR5JIORJG3A752V3HHAWQTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:53:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行在特朗普表态后取消美国多元化目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）周二表示，该行将取消其在全美范围内的多元化和包容性目标，成为继美国总统反对其包容性目标之后，又一家放弃该目标的英国公司。【原文：Barclays is scrapping its diversity and inclusivity targets across the United States, the bank said on Tuesday, becoming the latest British company to abandon its inclusivity goals following the U.S. President's opposition to them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/barclays-scraps-diversity-targets-us-following-trumps-stance-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5DTFE3FZBKBXDMPTDDDN3L3UE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行业盈利可能因经济衰退担忧而蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国贷款机构本周开始公布财报，投资者的关注点可能会从利润转向银行老板们在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布征收巨额关税并引发市场大跌后对经济的言论。【原文：As U.S. lenders begin to report earnings this week, investors' focus will likely shift from profits to bank bosses' remarks on the economy after President Donald Trump unveiled steep tariffs and triggered a market selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-earnings-likely-be-overshadowed-by-recession-concerns-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYWGXHTSAZOPFHTOPAA2BYN5JY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:31:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球市场衰退令欧洲奢侈品牌前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[越来越多的人担心唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税闪电战将使全球陷入经济衰退，这使年收入 4000 亿美元的奢侈品行业希望美国富豪能帮助其走出多年来最大的低谷。【原文：Growing fears that Donald Trump's tariff blitz will plunge the world into recession are dashing hopes in the $400-billion-a-year luxury industry that wealthy Americans might help to pull it out of the biggest slump in years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-market-rout-darkens-outlook-european-luxury-labels-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RMO452HFQRLBDASJD3EA76P7LU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:26:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利安托法加斯塔公司预计铜需求将抵御关税动荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利安托法加斯塔公司（Antofagasta）负责人表示，美国关税引发的贸易战给金属需求带来了风险，不过他预测人工智能和其他技术可以抵消经济疲软造成的传统消费损失。【原文：The trade war stirred by U.S. tariffs raises a risk for metal demand, the head of Chile's Antofagasta said, although he predicted AI and other technology could offset any loss of traditional consumption caused by economic weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chiles-antofagasta-expects-copper-demand-defy-tariff-turmoil-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TE3J22DGVLJBCIBDEJK4K3SUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国暂停提供资金后，世贸组织旨在减少人事费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织周二表示，在美国暂停向该机构提供资金后，该组织正在审查员工成本。【原文：The World Trade Organization said on Tuesday it is reviewing staff costs after the United States paused funding to the institution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/wto-aims-reduce-staffing-costs-after-us-funding-pause-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNDAY2RWBBMOHFNA2SUQUYLWR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部解散加密货币执法部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，美国司法部正在解散其国家加密货币执法小组，并命令检察官将重点放在涉及利用数字货币为非法业务融资的卡特尔和恐怖组织的刑事调查上。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department is disbanding its National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team and ordering prosecutors to focus instead on criminal investigations involving cartels and terrorist groups that use digital currency to finance illicit business, according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-justice-dept-disbands-cryptocurrency-enforcement-unit-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROV5KPAAEJODNGAUHILSZH6S3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:12:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息称美光将从 4 月 9 日起对部分产品征收关税相关附加费]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟知内情的消息人士称，美国内存芯片制造商美光科技（Micron Technology）已告知美国客户，该公司计划从周三起对部分产品征收附加费，以应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的新关税。【原文：U.S. memory chipmaker Micron Technology has told U.S. customers it plans to impose a surcharge on some products from Wednesday to account for U.S. President Donald Trump's new tariffs, four sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/micron-impose-tariff-related-surcharge-some-products-april-9-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAW25MNISBMITFMYLNIND6FPJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财长称中国关税升级是个大错误]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，美国的关税谈判是其他国家呼吁的结果，而不是金融市场下滑的结果，中国的升级是一个大错误。【原文：U.S. tariff negotiations are the result of calls from other countries not sliding financial markets and China's escalation is a big mistake, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/china-tariff-escalation-big-mistake-us-treasury-secretary-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CGR2SYE7IRM3VB643VRYYTWDFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立陶宛对 Revolut 罚款 350 万欧元，因其未能防止洗钱]]></title><description><![CDATA[立陶宛中央银行周一表示，已对英国最有价值的初创公司 Revolut 罚款 350 万欧元（383 万美元），原因是该公司在防止洗钱方面存在失误。【原文：Lithuania's central bank has fined Britain's most valuable start-up Revolut 3.5 million euros ($3.83 million) for failures in money-laundering prevention, the bank said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/lithuania-fines-revolut-35-million-euros-money-laundering-prevention-failures-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXEDHLBSAZMCBOZY2SHZEXEOL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司瑞波将以 12.5 亿美元收购主要经纪商 Hidden Road]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞波公司（Ripple）周二表示，将以 12.5 亿美元的价格收购多资产主经纪商 Hidden Road，这也是该加密货币公司最大的收购交易之一。【原文：Ripple said on Tuesday it will buy multi-asset prime broker Hidden Road in a $1.25 billion deal, making it one of the largest acquisitions by the crypto company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/crypto-firm-ripple-buy-prime-broker-hidden-road-125-billion-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKFXIDBWQZMGZOKX3CLE5SRHXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈雷首席执行官蔡茨计划于 2025 年退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国摩托车制造商哈雷戴维森（Harley-Davidson）的约亨-蔡茨（Jochen Zeitz）周二表示，在担任首席执行官五年后，他计划于 2025 年退休。【原文：Harley-Davidson's Jochen Zeitz plans to retire as CEO in 2025 after five years in the role, the American motorcycle maker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/harley-davidson-says-ceo-plans-retire-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFOB3NW4CJJWPEU5ZLYTBIGOMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:55:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 停止在波兰生产 Leapmotor 电动车，转而寻求其他选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利汽车制造商 Stellantis 周二表示，已停止在波兰生产其中国合作伙伴 Leapmotor 的 T03 小型电动汽车，并正在评估替代生产方案。【原文：Stellantis has stopped making its Chinese partner Leapmotor's T03 small electric car in Poland and is assessing alternative production options, the Franco-Italian automaker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-says-it-stopped-making-small-ev-leapmotor-car-poland-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5VLHRB73NPLJBLYICEMSF2LNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:24:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税冲击下服装零售商推迟订单、冻结招聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周三对从越南和中国进口的产品加征关税生效之前，美国各地的服装和配饰零售商正在推迟订单并冻结招聘。【原文：Clothing and accessories retailers across the United States are delaying orders and freezing hiring ahead of tariff hikes that take effect Wednesday on products imported from Vietnam and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/clothing-retailers-delay-orders-freeze-hiring-tariffs-hit-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3TACSOV75MYJKJJ3UZEE3YVRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称第一季度意大利 Stellantis 产量进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[FIM Cisl 工会周二表示，Stellantis 意大利汽车产量在 2024 年降至近 70 年低点后，第一季度进一步下降，原因是新车型在明年之前不会支持汽车生产活动。【原文：Stellantis' Italian auto production dropped further in the first quarter after output in the country fell to an almost 70-year low in 2024, the FIM Cisl union said on Tuesday, as new models will not support activity before next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-output-italy-fell-further-first-quarter-union-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2D5L73F6ZIKJIDY3B3X4EKWOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普将签署行政命令促进煤炭行业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周二签署旨在促进美国煤炭工业发展的行政命令。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will sign executive orders on Tuesday aimed at boosting the nation's coal industry, sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-sign-executive-orders-boost-coal-industry-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THMIALX5BJPPJL2574ZI7K47QI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[断崖式下跌后，台湾启动 150 亿美元股票稳定基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾周二授权启动 150 亿美元的股票稳定基金，以支撑因美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收新进口关税而连续两天暴跌的市场。【原文：Taiwan authorised the activation of its $15 billion stock stabilisation fund on Tuesday to prop up the market after two days of sharp falls in reaction to U.S. President Donald Trump's new import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/taiwan-activates-15-billion-stock-stabilisation-fund-after-precipitous-falls-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7A5R4XDTNL3JB3XOTSCLEDTNI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RTX 的普惠公司开发增材制造技术，缩短发动机维修时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[RTX 公司周二表示，其发动机制造子公司普惠公司已为齿轮传动涡扇（GTF）发动机部件开发出一种增材制造维修工艺，可将加工时间缩短 60% 以上。【原文：RTX said on Tuesday its engine making subsidiary Pratt & Whitney has developed an additive manufacturing repair process for its geared turbofan (GTF) engine components, which would reduce process time by more than 60%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtxs-pratt-whitney-develops-additive-manufacturing-reduce-engine-repair-time-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKLVWGRMPZL4VA3FQG5KMK7EOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:13:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：股市喘息，人民币和国债震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFQWNH2QSRKLRBIEUL7C3WRP3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:09:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔格林在 Sycamore Partners 交易完成前实现季度盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔格林公司（Walgreens）正在被 Sycamore Partners 私有化，该公司的季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，因为这家连锁药店运营商受益于扭亏为盈的努力，包括关闭业绩不佳的门店。【原文：Walgreens , which is in the process of being taken private by Sycamore Partners, beat Wall Street estimates for quarterly profit as the pharmacy chain operator benefited from a turnaround effort that included closing underperforming stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/walgreens-second-quarter-profit-beats-ahead-sycamore-partners-deal-close-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A7CE3KHYFIJ3DVZSL6Z4M7QK4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国股市在巨额关税引发抛售后回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，英国主要股指从一年多来的最低水平回升，因为投资者正在寻找任何迹象，表明华盛顿在过去几天激怒全球市场的激进关税问题上立场有所软化。【原文：Britain's main indexes recovered from their lowest levels in more than a year on Tuesday, as investors look for any indication of Washington softening its stance on the aggressive tariffs that have roiled global markets over the last few days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/uk-stocks-recover-after-sell-off-triggered-by-hefty-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2VU6KHXTBIKBBRKB5USTBTEUQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:06:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国将增加美国进口并降低税率以应对关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国财政部长周二表示，泰国将增加美国进口，降低对美国商品征收的部分高额税款，并解决非关税壁垒问题，因为泰国政府正寻求通过谈判就美国新关税达成更好的协议。【原文：Thailand will increase U.S. imports, lower some of the higher taxes on American goods and address non-tariff barriers, the finance minister said on Tuesday, as the government seeks to negotiate a better deal on new U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thailand-increase-us-imports-lower-taxes-tariff-response-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UL6H7B6XSRNWFM7WSGNSCE2PQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:44:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CVS 任命 UPS 高管布莱恩-纽曼为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，CVS Health 任命联合包裹服务公司高管布莱恩-纽曼（Brian Newman）为新任首席财务官，这是这家医疗保险公司在首席执行官大卫-乔伊纳（David Joyner）领导下的首次高层管理变动。【原文：CVS Health named United Parcel Service executive Brian Newman its new chief financial officer on Tuesday, the first top management change for the health insurer under CEO David Joyner's leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-names-ups-executive-brian-newman-cfo-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75KU7XRYTZL5RAKUONT5XHZRJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:37:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，制药商警告欧盟美国关税将进一步削弱欧洲制药业]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位业内消息人士告诉路透社，欧洲制药公司在周二的一次会议上警告欧盟委员会主席，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税将加速该行业从欧洲转向美国。【原文：European pharma companies warned the European Commission president in a meeting on Tuesday that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs would expedite the industry's shift away from Europe and toward the United States, two industry sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drugmakers-warn-eu-that-us-tariffs-further-weaken-sector-europe-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZE63AYVZ5ZN6PDLBIYJFZPQL6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[有限选择将中国推向与特朗普的贸易 "消耗战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对中国和任何购买或组装中国商品的国家加紧征收关税，北京感到被逼入绝境，正准备迎接一场经济消耗战。【原文：Beijing, feeling boxed into a corner by the United States' intensifying tariff assault on China and any country that buys or assembles Chinese goods, is bracing for an economic war of attrition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/limited-options-push-china-into-trade-war-attrition-with-trump-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWIGWHAMI5KHPAJ54BFVFCVA3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:28:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，马斯克的 DOGE 使用人工智能窥探美国联邦政府工作人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士说，特朗普政府官员已告诉一些美国政府雇员，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 DOGE 技术专家团队正在利用人工智能监控至少一个联邦机构的通信，以寻找对唐纳德-特朗普总统及其议程的敌意。【原文：Trump administration officials have told some U.S. government employees that Elon Musk's DOGE team of technologists is using artificial intelligence to surveil at least one federal agency’s communications for hostility to President Donald Trump and his agenda, said two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/musks-doge-using-ai-snoop-us-federal-workers-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7EBDCBQQRLQZMKIKEOCGVXKLQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:19:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长斯托纳拉斯称美国关税带来的通胀上升可能推迟货币政策正常化进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）决策者亚尼斯-斯托纳拉斯（Yannis Stournaras）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税后可能出现的通胀走高和全球贸易战可能会推迟欧元区货币政策的正常化。【原文：European Central Bank policymaker Yannis Stournaras said on Tuesday that likely higher inflation and a global trade war following U.S. President Donald Trump's imposition of tariffs could delay normalization of euro zone monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecbs-stournaras-says-higher-inflation-us-tariffs-could-delay-monetary-policy-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFUFGP3UGVLVLH2BRR5AXSNNF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[反垄断负责人称，欧盟将在未来几周内对苹果和 Meta 做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断局长特雷莎-里贝拉（Teresa Ribera）周二告诉欧洲议会立法者，欧盟将在未来几周内就苹果和 Meta 公司是否违反了旨在遏制其市场力量的具有里程碑意义的技术规则做出决定。【原文：An EU decision on whether Apple and Meta have breached landmark tech rules aimed at curbing their market power will be issued in the coming weeks, antitrust chief Teresa Ribera told European Parliament lawmakers on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-decisions-apple-meta-due-coming-weeks-antitrust-chief-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKVRXFRGE5JHHP6TMNUOI2XFGE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗保险支付率 "最佳情况 "下，医疗保险股上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国医疗保险公司股价跳涨，原因是政府对 2026 年医疗保险优势计划的报销比例上调幅度大于预期，这为医疗成本高企的医疗行业带来了一些缓解。【原文：Shares of U.S. health insurers jumped on Tuesday after a bigger-than-expected increase in the government's reimbursement rates for Medicare Advantage plans in 2026, bringing some relief to a sector burdened with elevated medical costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/health-insurance-stocks-rise-best-case-scenario-medicare-payment-rates-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LP2VZJIAVLXHF4F6NOP6KPYWQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>