<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:37:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:37:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[受到特朗普关税威胁的美非贸易计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）已着手对进口到美国的大部分商品全面征收关税，其中包括受益于美国针对非洲大陆的旗舰贸易计划的非洲国家的商品。【原文：President Donald Trump has moved to impose sweeping tariffs on most goods imported to the United States, including from African countries that benefit from a U.S. flagship trade programme for the continent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/us-africa-trade-programme-under-threat-trump-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3FLBKHWGNNCNBMTFCPSFNVGDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:31:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能视频制造商 Runway 在 General Atlantic 领投的新一轮融资中获得 3.08 亿美元投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能视频初创公司Runway周四表示，它已在新一轮融资中筹集到3.08亿美元，由私募股权公司General Atlantic领投，用于扩展其新媒体生态系统。【原文：AI video startup Runway said on Thursday it had raised $308 million in a new funding round, led by private equity firm General Atlantic, to expand its new media ecosystem.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-video-maker-runway-raises-308-million-general-atlantic-led-funding-round-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQXZENSG6NOWNEKWJKG2KTPYEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司首席执行官誓言在美国生产更多汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在美国对全球汽车征收 25% 关税生效之际，沃尔沃汽车公司（Volvo Cars）新任高层周四表示，该公司将在美国生产更多汽车，同时加大区域化力度。【原文：Volvo Cars' new top executive said on Thursday the company would produce more cars in the United States while ramping up its regionalisation efforts, just as a 25% U.S. tariff on global autos takes effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-ceo-vows-produce-more-cars-us-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNSI5G5LNFLINBVT6WD3TT7Y5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西咖啡关税引发担忧，Lavazza 计划在美国扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利咖啡制造商拉瓦扎公司（Lavazza）周四表示，该公司计划继续扩大在美国市场的业务，并补充说，该公司将评估对巴西咖啡豆征收关税的潜在影响，然后再决定是否提高当地产量。【原文：Italian coffee maker Lavazza plans to press ahead with expansion in the U.S. market, it said on Thursday, adding it would assess the potential impact of tariffs on its Brazilian beans before making a decision on boosting local production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lavazza-plans-us-expansion-amid-brazil-coffee-tariff-concerns-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSRO55VR2BNW5FCYSYPMARPJWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲银行监管局称美国银行在欧洲衍生品市场 "占主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲银行管理局（European Banking Authority）周四表示，随着人们对欧洲金融业战略自主性的担忧与日俱增，非欧盟银行已经在欧洲的一些关键金融市场占据了 "主导 "地位，其中包括美国银行占主导地位的金融衍生品市场。【原文：Non-EU banks have carved out "dominant" roles in some of Europe's key financial markets, including derivatives where U.S. banks prevail, the European Banking Authority said on Thursday as concerns about the strategic autonomy of the European financial sector grow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-banks-are-dominant-european-derivatives-eba-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56GIFKZGZBOTBI2WIDQWLVAD64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联想与爱立信就国际专利纠纷达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[联想集团周四表示，它与爱立信已就全球专利交叉许可达成协议，并解决了所有未决诉讼，从而结束了一场全球范围的法律战。【原文：Lenovo said on Thursday it and Ericsson had reached an agreement on a global patent cross-licence and to settle all pending litigation, ending a worldwide legal battle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/lenovo-ericsson-settle-international-patent-dispute-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGTJKVJ3GRJJZE7GWG5UP3VASE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥宣布新关税后继续与美国对话]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普公布了不包括墨西哥在内的全面新关税之后，墨西哥与美国之间的对话与合作仍在继续。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Thursday that dialogue and cooperation remain ongoing with the United States, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled sweeping new tariffs that did not include Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-continues-dialogue-with-us-after-new-tariffs-announcement-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYW4TZQ6UFIQHE3G4RK4W4NIL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治紧张局势下汇丰银行上调金价预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行以地缘政治风险为由，将 2025 年和 2026 年的平均金价预测分别上调至每盎司 3015 美元和 2915 美元。【原文：HSBC raised its average 2025 and 2026 gold price forecast to $3,015 and $2,915 per ounce respectively, citing geopolitical risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/hsbc-raises-gold-price-forecasts-amid-geopolitical-tensions-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SE243DNEOBJZ7HJSIDCEL6WRAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢特尼克说，各国需要允许更多美国产品进入，以降低关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周四表示，特朗普政府正在与全球所有主要贸易伙伴商讨如何降低唐纳德-特朗普总统的新关税，并补充说，这些伙伴将不得不改变其规则，以允许更多美国产品进口。【原文：The Trump administration is talking to all major trading partners throughout the world about ways to bring down President Donald Trump's new tariffs, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said on Thursday, adding that they will have to change their rules to allow more imports of U.S. products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/countries-need-allow-more-us-products-bring-down-tariffs-lutnick-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LS7GA6ODWRIAZA7E5QJG6I24XQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月服务业增长几近刹车]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份，美国服务业增速放缓，创 9 个月新低、【原文：The U.S. services sector slowed to a nine-month low in March,】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-service-sector-growth-nearly-brakes-march-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSRQY43TIFNN7HIPNTO2ZBIJ5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉因贸易紧张局势下的债务风险下调中国信用评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构惠誉周四下调了中国的主权信用评级，理由是预计中国的公共财政将继续疲软，债务将迅速增加。【原文：Global ratings agency Fitch on Thursday downgraded China's sovereign credit rating, citing expectations of a continued weakening of public finances and rapidly rising debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/fitch-cuts-china-credit-rating-debt-risks-amid-trade-tensions-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CKPBLDTNFPHRPV6WHO2YIFLUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:50:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发需求担忧，咖啡和可可价格下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界可可和咖啡价格周三下跌，因为投资者担心唐纳德-特朗普总统对美国进口产品征收惩罚性关税的举动将损害世界第一大巧克力和咖啡消费国的巧克力和咖啡需求。【原文：World cocoa and coffee prices fell on Wednesday as investors fretted that President Donald Trump's move to slap punishing tariffs on U.S. imports would damage chocolate and coffee demand in the world's top consumer of the products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/coffee-cocoa-slide-trump-tariffs-spark-demand-worries-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQDSAGPLPVKXFDRPHJMXKZSCHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:49:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月贸易逆差收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 2 月份的贸易赤字有所收窄，但进口水平仍然较高，因为企业为避免关税导致价格上涨而提前采购商品，这使得贸易有望拖累第一季度的经济增长。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit narrowed in February, but the level of imports remained elevated after businesses front-loaded goods to avoid higher prices from tariffs, keeping trade on track to be a drag on economic growth in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-trade-deficit-narrows-february-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOF3EGIT3VJI5IWWR4MJZC45CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 表示将在关税宣布后临时裁员 900 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布加征关税后，公羊卡车和吉普车制造商 Stellantis NV 周四表示，将在美国五家工厂临时裁员 900 人，并暂时停止在墨西哥和加拿大一家装配厂的生产。【原文：Stellantis NV, maker of Ram trucks and Jeeps, said on Thursday it was temporarily laying off 900 workers at five U.S. facilities after President Donald Trump's tariffs were announced, and temporarily pausing production at an assembly plant in Mexico and in Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-says-will-temporarily-lay-off-900-us-workers-following-tariff-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBU3GFQA4BLYBCFOIC6ZJKSKN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:42:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国干邑行业组织呼吁缓和美国与欧盟的贸易争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[干邑行业游说团体干邑国家跨行业办公室（BNIC）主席弗洛伦特-莫里隆（Florent Morillon）说，欧盟和美国需要缓和贸易争端，而葡萄酒和烈酒则不应受到双方的影响。【原文：The European Union and the United States need to de-escalate their trade dispute and wine and spirits should be left untouched by both sides, said Florent Morillon, the president of the National Interprofessional Office of Cognac (BNIC), the cognac industry's lobby group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/french-cognac-industry-group-calls-de-escalation-us-eu-trade-dispute-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FX5MDDDCNMZRKRIURQJFCMFAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国钢铁制造商阿佩拉姆公司将寻求美国关税的潜在豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国钢铁生产商阿佩拉姆公司（Aperam）周四表示，它将与美国客户一起探索美国宣布的关税豁免可能。【原文：French steel producer Aperam said on Thursday it would explore potential exemptions from announced U.S. tariffs, along with its U.S. customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/french-steelmaker-aperam-seek-potential-exemptions-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOMXXMKS3ZLPTNVTPEDZBJTYQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对非洲小国莱索托征收最高关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[南部非洲小国莱索托被美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收 50%的互惠贸易关税，这是他一长串目标经济体名单中征税最高的一个国家。【原文：The tiny southern African kingdom of Lesotho has been hit with a 50% reciprocal trade tariff by U.S. President Donald Trump, the highest levy of any single state on his long list of target economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/trump-slaps-tiny-african-kingdom-lesotho-with-highest-tariff-all-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZFANTEUBJOTNNWZ3XH25T3APY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利预计美联储今年不会降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利周四表示，预计美国联邦储备委员会今年不会降息，原因是特朗普最新关税政策可能导致通胀水平上升。【原文：Morgan Stanley said on Thursday it expects the U.S Federal Reserve will not cut rates this year due to potential elevated inflation levels on the back of Trump's latest tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/morgan-stanley-expects-no-rate-cuts-fed-this-year-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFWQH64WEVLMBODQDPVKM2GKOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:53:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉下调中国评级至 "A]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构惠誉周四将中国的长期外币评级从 "A+"下调至 "A"，理由是预计公共财政将继续疲软，债务将迅速增加。【原文：Global ratings agency Fitch on Thursday downgraded China's long-term foreign currency rating to 'A' from 'A+', citing expectations of a continued weakening of public finances and rapidly rising debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/fitch-downgrades-chinas-rating-a-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3RDFHEDXNOZRGHMG5KB7WFT44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:51:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降，劳动力市场暂时保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数有所下降，表明在进口关税带来潜在波动之前，劳动力市场将继续保持稳定。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell last week, pointing to continued labor market stability ahead of potential volatility from import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-labor-market-stays-stable-now-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZS2CVJ5MZNNNG2MBX2MUUFX6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国副总统称 TikTok 协议 "进展顺利]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府副总统万斯（JD Vance）周四表示，随着竞标的增加，特朗普政府为短视频社交网站 TikTok 寻找美国买家的工作正在按部就班地进行，比 4 月 5 日达成非中国所有权交易的最后期限提前了。【原文：The Trump administration's work to find an American buyer for the short-video social media site TikTok is on track ahead of the April 5 deadline to reach a deal for non-Chinese ownership, Vice President JD Vance said on Thursday as bids mounted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/work-tiktok-deal-is-in-good-place-us-vice-president-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYKXJE2USFIYLBOCXITWWH3O7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:38:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国公布美国可能加征关税的商品清单]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普决定对英国征收10%的进口关税，英国周四公布了一份可能被列入任何报复性关税对策的商品清单。【原文：Britain on Thursday published a list of goods that could be included in any retaliatory tariff response to U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to impose import tariffs of 10% on the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-publishes-list-goods-potential-us-tariff-response-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCCVKTA3Z5PZTJJ3K77L7IV4AY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:35:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被特朗普关税震惊的投资者准备应对全球经济增长冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）巨额新关税的冲击，大型投资者们正拿出他们的全球衰退手册，急于分散投资，避开遭受重创的华尔街股票和美元。【原文：Big investors reeling from the shock of U.S. President Donald Trump's hefty new tariffs are pulling out their global recession playbooks and rushing to diversify away from battered Wall Street stocks and the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/investors-stunned-by-trump-tariffs-prepare-global-growth-shock-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQVKDVZFPVNVNOZ73KDEB5T664</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABB 预计将转嫁新关税带来的成本增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士工程集团ABB周四表示，该公司正在评估新进口关税的影响，并预计将转嫁由此导致的更高成本。【原文：Swiss engineering group ABB said on Thursday it is evaluating the implications of new import tariffs and expects to pass on higher costs that result from them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/abb-expects-pass-cost-increases-new-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZYFT34Y7NMGBHXMYOSYWYT3CM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，汽车关税第一年将使美国消费者损失超过 300 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[咨询公司安德森经济集团（Anderson Economic Group）周四在一份报告中称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对汽车进口征收 25% 的关税，可能会使美国消费者在第一个完整年度中因汽车价格上涨和汽车销量减少而损失超过 300 亿美元。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's 25% tariff on auto imports may cost American consumers more than $30 billion in higher vehicle prices and reduced car sales in the first full year, consultancy firm Anderson Economic Group said in a report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/auto-tariff-cost-us-consumers-more-than-30-bln-first-year-report-shows-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUUCH6NKIFLHRI75NLOWV4ASWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰总理称考虑支持受关税冲击的企业为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰总理米歇尔-马丁（Micheal Martin）周四表示，现在考虑支持受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收20%进口关税影响的企业还为时过早，但他期待与美国就征税的影响进行谈判。【原文：Irish Prime Minister Micheal Martin said on Thursday it was still too early to consider supporting businesses hit by President Donald Trump's import tariffs of 20% but that he expected talks with the U.S. on the impact of the levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/irish-pm-says-too-early-consider-supporting-businesses-hit-by-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZULOYSHBNZNGHA27IGKDUPO5LU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[约翰逊爸爸希望人工智能改变披萨订购方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[约翰爸爸国际公司（Papa John's International）周四表示，希望通过扩大与谷歌云（Google Cloud）的合作，将人工智能技术注入顾客订购披萨的方式中。【原文：Papa John's International wants to inject artificial intelligence technology into how its customers order pizza through an expanded partnership with Google Cloud, the chain said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/papa-johns-wants-ai-transform-pizza-ordering-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RM4NMU5YFJZLA4ZRYV2R45DPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国需求增长放缓，矿业整合将加速]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于制造业的放缓和工业金属需求的增长，尤其是在最大消费国中国，采矿业的整合时机已经成熟，预计合资企业和资产出售将加速发展。【原文：Joint ventures and asset sales are expected to accelerate in the mining industry, which is ripe for consolidation due to the slowdown in manufacturing and demand growth for industrial metals, particularly in top consumer China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/mining-consolidation-speed-up-chinese-demand-growth-slows-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZ7EZGQBV5PUFATVE6DDPZMTNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税冲击刺痛孟加拉国和斯里兰卡服装巨头，但可能有助于印度]]></title><description><![CDATA[孟加拉服装出口商沙希杜拉-阿齐姆（Shahidullah Azim）周四一觉醒来，就被美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对孟加拉出口产品征收 37% 的关税所震惊，这危及到这个已经因国内政治动荡而岌岌可危的服装中心。【原文：Bangladeshi garment exporter Shahidullah Azim woke up on Thursday to the shock of U.S. President Donald Trump slapping a 37% tariff on his country's exports, endangering an apparel hub already reeling from domestic political upheaval.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/trump-tariff-shock-stings-bangladesh-sri-lanka-garment-giants-may-help-india-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QVI2RT5AFFNKDOKRORFEIDQO7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，WTO负责人将回答成员有关美国关税的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封信称，世界贸易组织负责人周四告诉各成员国，该组织已收到 "许多 "有关美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税对贸易的影响的问题，并将对这些问题做出回应。【原文：The head of the World Trade Organization told member states on Thursday that it had received "many" questions about the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on trade and would respond to their questions, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/wto-chief-will-answer-members-questions-about-us-tariffs-document-shows-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNBYKKI7WJN43MUUN6TRMODCPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:54:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>