<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:05:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:05:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司在印度推出的 Mounjaro 引发减肥咨询热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项调查显示，礼来公司在印度推出的流行减肥药Mounjaro引发了患者对该药供应情况的大量咨询，一些印度医生接到了数百个有关该药的电话。【原文：The India launch of Eli Lilly's popular weight-loss drug Mounjaro has triggered a huge wave of patient enquiries about its availability, with some Indian doctors fielding hundreds of calls about the medicine, according to a Reuters survey.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eli-lillys-mounjaro-launch-india-ignites-wave-weight-loss-enquiries-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHQDSDCYUFNLBAOIE6CJOFSSCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 19:49:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税暂停后贝莱德上调美股展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德投资研究所（BlackRock Investment Institute）周一表示，在美国宣布暂停实施大部分关税 90 天后，该研究所对美股的看涨立场略有上升。【原文：The BlackRock Investment Institute said on Monday that it is taking a modestly more bullish stance on U.S. stocks following the announcement of a 90-day pause in implementing most U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackrock-boosts-outlook-us-stocks-after-tariffs-pause-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OJETJ45LZNKPIT44VDGL5MXMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 19:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，Atlas 控股公司以每股 130 便士的价格竞购英国央行货币印刷商 De La Rue]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻周一报道，总部位于美国的收购公司 Atlas Holdings 正在就以每股约 130 便士的价格收购纸币印刷商 De La Rue 进行深入谈判。【原文：U.S.-based buyout firm Atlas Holdings is in advanced talks to take over Banknote printer De La Rue for about 130 pence per share, Sky News reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/atlas-holdings-bids-boe-currency-printer-de-la-rue-130-pence-per-share-sky-news-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NESOZH7F4VMSLGTS3T3FRZUNYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 19:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟贸易负责人寻求与美国共同努力达成公平关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易委员马罗斯-塞夫科维奇（Maros Sefcovic）周一表示，欧盟正在寻求与美国达成一项公平的关税协议，并补充说这需要双方 "共同努力"。【原文：The European Union is seeking a fair deal on tariffs with the United States, European Trade Commissioner Maros Sefcovic said on Monday, adding that this would require a "significant joint effort" on both sides.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-trade-chief-seeks-joint-effort-with-us-fair-tariff-deal-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CF3OEAN4JZKA5NDHYBSAPIW2TY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:57:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场崩溃后，Systematica 基金下跌 19]]></title><description><![CDATA[Systematica Investments 旗舰对冲基金的上市版本今年下跌了约 19%，原因是一些趋势跟踪策略在美国新贸易政策引发的市场动荡中举步维艰。【原文：A listed version of Systematica Investments' flagship hedge fund is down roughly 19% this year, as some trend-following strategies have struggled to navigate the market turmoil caused by the new U.S. trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/systematica-fund-down-19-following-market-rout-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7426LA7GUBIQPBUHW7CIO543ZM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通因需求疲软、产量增加下调油价预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周一下调了 2025 年和明年的油价预期，理由是欧佩克+产量增加和需求疲软。【原文：JP Morgan on Monday lowered its oil price forecasts for 2025 and next year, citing higher production from OPEC+ and weaker demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/jp-morgan-cuts-oil-price-forecasts-weak-demand-higher-output-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7YFCY4PMNOSXPROS22X6CA3RM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，标普 500 指数迫在眉睫的 "死亡交叉 "可能并不像听起来那么不祥]]></title><description><![CDATA[关税引发的美国股市大跌还面临另一个隐忧--"死亡交叉 "形态，但历史表明，这种听起来不吉利的技术信号并不一定意味着股市将面临更大幅度的下跌。【原文：A tariff-induced selloff in the U.S. stock market faces another worry, the "death cross" pattern, but history shows the ominous sounding technical signal may not necessarily mean equities face more significant downside.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sp-500s-looming-death-cross-may-not-be-ominous-it-sounds-analysts-say-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5QNQDHVRVPTZFUYKVHDWGXIQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 推出新的 GPT-4.1 模型，改进了编码和长语境理解能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周一发布了新的人工智能模型 GPT-4.1，以及更小的版本 GPT-4.1 mini 和 GPT-4.1 nano，宣称在编码、指令遵循和长语境理解方面有重大改进。【原文：OpenAI on Monday launched its new AI model GPT-4.1, along with smaller versions GPT-4.1 mini and GPT-4.1 nano, touting major improvements in coding, instruction following, and long context comprehension.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-launches-new-gpt-41-models-with-improved-coding-long-context-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMXESNJ3XNL7LMBMUYKS5CEHXA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三藩市联储文件称，求职率下降、失业时间增加可能预示着经济衰退即将到来]]></title><description><![CDATA[据旧金山联邦储备银行周一发表的研究报告称，近年来美国失业率逐步且相对较小幅度上升的背后，是几个关注度较低的劳动力市场指标闪烁着经济衰退风险的黄灯。【原文：Behind the gradual and relatively small rise in the U.S. unemployment rate in recent years are a couple of less-closely followed labor market indicators that are flashing yellow for recession risk, according to research published on Monday by the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/drop-job-finding-rate-rise-time-out-work-could-signal-recession-ahead-sf-fed-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXJVKX355RLRXCXK7SYRDLMOAE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管货币升值，阿根廷农民仍注重收获而非销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家说，阿根廷谷物行业周一对汇率改革表示欢迎，但由于收成仍落后于计划，新措施可能不会立即转化为销售。【原文：Argentina's grain industry welcomed an exchange-rate overhaul on Monday, though the new measures will likely not translate into immediate sales as the harvest remains behind schedule, experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/argentina-farmers-focus-harvest-over-sales-despite-currency-boost-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWY4MZIQZBJBJCAGWQYEHQVYOU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将在欧盟使用公共帖子和人工智能互动来训练模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周一表示，它将利用用户与其人工智能的互动，以及成年人在其平台上分享的公开帖子和评论，在欧盟训练其人工智能模型。【原文：Meta Platforms said on Monday it would use interactions that users have with its AI, as well as public posts and comments shared by adults across its platforms, to train its artificial intelligence models in the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/meta-use-public-posts-ai-interactions-train-models-eu-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPSDAVEVFFN7ZFBYSA6ZK57ZJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:23:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃勒关税带来重大冲击，可能出现多种结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）周一表示，特朗普政府的关税政策是对美国经济的重大冲击，即使通胀率居高不下，也可能导致美联储降息以防止经济衰退；或者，如果关税政策被证明是一种谈判工具，也可能不会留下什么持久的影响。【原文：The Trump administration's tariff policies are a major shock to the U.S. economy that could lead the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates to head off recession even if inflation remains high, or alternately leave little lasting imprint if they turn out to be a negotiating tool, Fed Governor Christopher Waller said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/waller-tariffs-major-shock-with-wide-array-possible-outcomes-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4DEYU3T4FJ3LCJVFYQ2P7DZDE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约起诉 DailyPay 和 MoneyLion，指控其提供掠夺性发薪日贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约总检察长周一起诉了 DailyPay 和 MoneyLion，指控这两家基于应用程序的金融科技公司剥削工人，为更快地收取工资收取过高的费用，实际利率超过 200%，有时甚至高达 750%。【原文：New York's attorney general sued DailyPay and MoneyLion on Monday, accusing the app-based financial technology companies of exploiting workers by charging excessive fees to collect paychecks more quickly, with effective interest rates above 200% and sometimes topping 750%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/new-york-sues-dailypay-moneylion-alleging-predatory-payday-lending-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCE6PMBAO5ILPOGXN3DVBTLRHQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利数据公司 Cerved 任命前特工部门高管为董事长]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球金融数据和软件集团 ION 旗下的意大利信用数据公司 Cerved 已聘请一名前情报部门官员担任董事长，这是企业数据安全日益重要的最新迹象。【原文：Cerved, an Italian credit data firm owned by global financial data and software group ION, has hired a former intelligence services official as chairman, in the latest sign of the growing importance of corporate data safety.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italian-data-firm-cerved-names-former-secret-service-executive-chairman-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUMHPECSKRIFVJFCCDOBYOX3QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称特朗普政策削弱了对美国和美元资产的信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周一表示，她担心唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税和其他政策正在削弱盟国对美国承诺的信任，一些投资者开始回避美国资产。【原文：Former U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Monday she was concerned that President Donald Trump's tariffs and other policies were eroding allies' trust in U.S. commitments, and that some investors were starting to shun U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/yellen-says-trump-policies-eroding-trust-us-dollar-assets-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDQBLKDLZJNDRFAYJSNFXJHGIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:18:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[核心业务下滑，LVMH 销售额下降 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[路威酩轩集团
 全球最大的奢侈品集团路威酩轩集团（LVMH）周一表示，第一季度销售额下降了 3%，低于预期，这也证实了该行业的增长放缓，因为在动荡的经济环境下，购物者减少了对名牌时装的购买。【原文：LVMH 
 , the world's largest luxury group, said on Monday sales fell 3% over the first quarter, missing expectations and confirming a sector slowdown as shoppers held back on purchases of designer fashion in a choppy economic environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lvmh-posts-3-drop-first-quarter-sales-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2GHZAQBDZK6ZDVBKASM2F3R3M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金 Qube 公布 1.05 亿美元的特朗普媒体空头头寸]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据提交给德国联邦公报《Bundesanzeiger》的文件，对冲基金 Qube Research & Technologies 周一公布了针对特朗普媒体与科技集团股票的约 1.05 亿美元的空头头寸。【原文：Hedge fund Qube Research & Technologies unveiled a roughly $105 million short position against shares in Trump Media & Technology Group on Monday, according to a filing with Germany's federal Gazette Bundesanzeiger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/hedge-fund-qube-unveils-105-million-short-position-trump-media-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NI2YA2RVLNPDPHFMQX6BJNOYZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:42:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳音乐任命前动视暴雪高管为财务总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳音乐集团（Warner Music Group）是艾德-希兰（Ed Sheeran）和杜阿-利帕（Dua Lipa）等艺人背后的唱片公司，该音乐娱乐公司周一表示，已任命前动视暴雪（Activision Blizzard）高管阿明-泽尔扎（Armin Zerza）为财务总监。【原文：Warner Music Group , the label behind artists such as Ed Sheeran and Dua Lipa, has appointed former Activision Blizzard executive Armin Zerza as its finance chief, the music entertainment company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-music-appoints-former-activision-blizzard-executive-finance-chief-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3PVX52ACBLLBOUJR27TGZMVZY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:21:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储：纽约联储：3 月近期通胀预期将在情绪恶化的情况下跳升]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周一发布的一份报告称，在公众对个人财务状况和就业前景的评估变差的情况下，美国人对近期通胀的预期在3月份达到了2023年秋季以来的最高水平。【原文：Americans’ expectations for near-term inflation hit the highest level since the fall of 2023 in March, amid a souring in the public’s assessment of their personal finances and hiring prospects, a report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ny-fed-march-near-term-inflation-expects-jump-amid-souring-sentiment-levels-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYJOIYCQBVOTNHVRS442JAVJQQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:18:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国共和党参议员要求特朗普政府撤回限制全球使用人工智能芯片的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的信件副本显示，七名共和党参议员周五致信美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克，敦促政府撤回拜登政府在最后一刻通过的一项将控制全球人工智能芯片准入的规定，并警告称这些限制将损害美国在人工智能领域的领导地位。【原文：Seven Republican senators sent a letter to U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick on Friday, urging the administration to withdraw a last-minute Biden administration rule that would control global access to AI chips, warning the restrictions would damage U.S. leadership in artificial intelligence, according to a copy of the letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/gop-senators-ask-trump-admin-withdraw-rule-that-would-limit-global-access-ai-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARMUCSMAUFI6VKMWOXWAL3VA7U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:13:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果期权看涨交易收获颇丰，股价因关税豁免而跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位身份不明的期权交易商押注苹果公司股价短期反弹，押注金额高达数百万美元，结果获得了可观的利润，因为在特朗普政府周末批准对智能手机免征关税之后，这家 iPhone 制造商的股价周一飙升。【原文：An unidentified options trader's multi-million dollar bet on a short-term rebound in Apple Inc.'s shares was set to reap a sizable profit as the iPhone-maker's shares soared on Monday following the Trump administration's weekend move to grant tariff exclusions for smartphones.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bullish-trade-apple-options-reaps-gains-shares-jump-tariff-exemption-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLFQTHEKNNKTFDZRCMPG7OSPO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西家乐福销售总额增长 3.6]]></title><description><![CDATA[家乐福巴西公司在周日提交的一份证券文件中说，包括燃料在内，该公司第一季度的销售总额为288亿雷亚尔（约合49.3亿美元），比去年同期增长了3.6%。【原文：Carrefour Brasil's gross sales in the first quarter including fuel totaled 28.8 billion reais ($4.93 billion), a 3.6% increase from a year earlier, the retailer said in a securities filing on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/carrefour-brasil-posts-36-increase-gross-sales-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ66SXBWJ5JXRFWHDBO6VVCRJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界黄金协会称中国黄金ETF四月流入量超过第一季度总量]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界黄金协会（World Gold Council）的数据显示，本月迄今为止，流入中国实物黄金交易所交易基金的投资资金已超过第一季度全年，并超过了流入美国上市基金的资金。【原文：Investment flows into Chinese physically backed gold exchange-traded funds so far this month have exceeded those for the whole of the first quarter and overtaken inflows registered by U.S.-listed funds, World Gold Council data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinese-gold-etfs-april-inflows-surpass-first-quarter-total-wgc-says-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNE22RF4EBLVZP2GOG47EK24UI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛下调铝价预期，因增长前景疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普政府大幅提高关税之后，高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）的经济学家下调了包括美国和中国在内的全球经济增长预期，因此高盛周一下调了今年的铝价预期。【原文：Goldman Sachs on Monday reduced its forecast for aluminium prices this year after its economists downgraded global growth forecasts including for the U.S. and China following the Trump administration's move to sharply increase tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/goldman-sachs-cuts-aluminium-price-forecast-weaker-growth-outlook-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DR2QEFFOPFKGZFRO4E2DSFVCXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税导致成本上升，芭比乐园一片愁云惨淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 的影响者和收藏家 Noemi de Lama 在她位于西班牙北部港口希洪（Gijon）的家中被数百个芭比娃娃包围着，她与她的追随者们分享了一个消息：美国的关税很可能会推高他们喜爱的娃娃的价格。【原文：Surrounded by hundreds of Barbies at her home in the northern Spanish port of Gijon, TikTok influencer and collector Noemi de Lama has shared the news with her followers that U.S. tariffs are likely to drive up the price of their favourite dolls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/gloom-barbieland-trump-tariffs-drive-up-costs-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BGDTZ6FXFNIVH2KDBDUDYB3HM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科迪亚克机器人公司将通过 SPAC 交易上市，估值 25 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动驾驶卡车技术公司科迪亚克机器人公司（Kodiak Robotics）周一表示，该公司计划今年晚些时候通过与空白支票公司 Ares Acquisition Corp II 合并在美国上市，科迪亚克公司的估值为 25 亿美元。【原文：Autonomous truck technology firm Kodiak Robotics said on Monday it plans to go public in the U.S. later this year through a merger with blank-check company Ares Acquisition Corp II , valuing Kodiak at $2.5 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kodiak-robotics-go-public-spac-deal-valuing-firm-25-billion-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLDM5BO3BFKG3BFIGC7RSP7WQE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kraken 宣布推出免佣金交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Kraken 周一宣布在其平台上推出美国上市股票和 ETF 免佣金交易。【原文：Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken on Monday announced the rollout of commission-free trading for U.S.-listed stocks and ETFs on its platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kraken-announces-launch-commission-free-trading-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCEVYURTDNIPFEQ2EJ5PGMFAXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行称科技银行团队去年增长 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）周一表示，由于美国科技行业的增长，其技术银行部门的员工人数在过去一年中增加了 20%，2025 年还将有更多的招聘计划。【原文：Wells Fargo said on Monday its technology banking unit increased its headcount by 20% over the past year on the back of growth in the U.S tech sector, with additional hires in the pipeline for 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-says-tech-banking-team-grew-by-20-over-past-year-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5SNFHICIVMXZLRAXL2FF2QSVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达称与合作伙伴合作在美国制造人工智能超级计算机]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周一表示，它正在与合作伙伴合作，设计并建造完全在美国生产人工智能超级计算机的工厂。【原文：Nvidia said on Monday it was working with partners to design and build factories to produce AI supercomputers entirely in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/nvidia-says-working-with-partners-make-ai-supercomputers-us-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXHBVMIE2ZMQRHMPA32LBWTQH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商 Qorvo 任命两位行业资深人士进入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商 Qorvo 周一表示，在激进投资者 Starboard Value 推动公司提振疲软股价之际，公司任命业内资深人士 Richard Clemmer 和 Christopher Koopmans 为董事会独立董事。【原文：Chipmaker Qorvo appointed industry veterans Richard Clemmer and Christopher Koopmans as independent directors to its board, it said on Monday, amid activist investor Starboard Value's push to boost the company's weak share price.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmaker-qorvo-appoints-two-industry-veterans-board-2025-04-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRPSI76OD5LBHHSWG5HZBUHNRQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>