<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:10:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:10:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[关税政策主导之际，最高法院重申其制衡特朗普的权力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在过去一年里，美国最高法院在二十余起案件中支持唐纳德·特朗普总统，助其扩大权力并迅速改变美国在移民、兵役、联邦雇佣等领域的政策。如今，最高法院终于触及了其权力的边界。【原文：After siding with President Donald Trump in two dozen cases in the past year in ways that boosted his power and let him quickly transform U.S. policies on immigration, military service, federal employment and beyond, the U.S. Supreme Court finally reached its limit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/with-tariffs-ruling-supreme-court-reasserts-its-power-check-trump-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3QKRRGFH5LVVKEF37LWYLAKHY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行官员帕内塔表示，中国进口推动通胀降幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行一位高级政策制定者周六警告称，欧元区通胀风险在两个方向上都"相当大"，并补充说，廉价的中国进口商品对价格的影响值得密切关注。【原文：Risks to euro zone inflation are "significant" in either direction, a top European Central Bank policymaker warned on Saturday, adding that the impact on prices of cheap Chinese imports warranted close attention.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ecbs-panetta-says-chinese-imports-helped-drive-sharperthanforecast-inflation-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4C4573VX75P6FP6TAUJKXZZEQ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:34:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其审查六家在线平台的儿童数据处理实践]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其数据保护机构周五晚间表示，已对六家主要社交媒体平台启动审查，以评估其处理儿童个人数据的方式。【原文：Turkey's data protection authority said late on Friday that it has launched a review into six major social media platforms to assess how they handle children's personal data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/turkey-reviews-six-online-platforms-childrens-data-processing-practices-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPBMQ3FLRFPP3O57PULXPZ6ACM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲经济体权衡特朗普新关税举措的影响，市场陷入混乱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国在亚洲的贸易伙伴于周六开始权衡新的不确定性，此前数小时，美国总统特朗普誓言将对进口商品征收新关税，而最高法院刚刚推翻了他为发动全球贸易战而实施的许多广泛关税措施。【原文：U.S. trading partners in Asia started weighing fresh uncertainties on Saturday after President Donald Trump vowed to impose a new tariff on imports, hours after the Supreme Court struck down many of the sweeping levies he used to launch a global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asian-economies-weigh-impact-fresh-trump-tariff-moves-confusion-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDFJHBOAUNNYJLRJVTCXNNSDBI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对欧洲企业而言，美国关税减免背后暗藏玄机]]></title><description><![CDATA[从欧洲葡萄酒生产商到化工企业和蒸馏酒制造商，美国最高法院推翻特朗普总统大部分贸易关税的裁决带来了一记回马枪：贸易前景变得更加扑朔迷离。【原文：From European wine makers to chemical companies and distillers, the U.S. Supreme Court ruling knocking down a large part of President Donald Trump's trade tariffs comes with a sting in the tail: an even more uncertain trade outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/europe-inc-us-tariff-relief-comes-with-sting-tail-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PG3MC74OTNLCVAQ46PBAWZHAD4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室预计，新一轮301条款调查将覆盖大多数主要贸易伙伴。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔周五表示，其办公室将根据1974年《贸易法》第301条款启动多项新调查，涵盖多数主要贸易伙伴及药品定价等领域。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer on Friday said his office would initiate several new investigations under Section 301 of the Trade Act of 1974, covering most major trading partners and areas such as pharmaceutical product pricing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ustr-expects-new-section-301-probes-cover-most-major-trading-partners-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V2PHWFCNMZPSTJBYTOQDKJETDQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[玩具制造商评估在美国最高法院关税退税诉讼中的下一步行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过向投资者出售潜在关税退税索赔权来规避风险的企业，在周五美国最高法院推翻特朗普总统广泛的紧急关税措施后欢欣鼓舞。【原文：Companies that hedged their bets by selling potential tariff refund claims to investors celebrated on Friday after the U.S. Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping emergency tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/toymaker-assesses-next-steps-us-supreme-court-tariff-refund-battle-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFDKM4UPDFNHNJU3OAMMT73WXI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:03:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院裁决后，律所为关税退税之争严阵以待]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五裁定，总统特朗普无权依据一项旨在应对国家紧急状态的法律征收关税。此后，相关诉讼预计将转向美国国际贸易法院，多家企业已聘请大批律师团队，以期追回关税损失。【原文：After the U.S. Supreme Court ruled on Friday that President Donald Trump lacked authority to impose tariffs under a law meant for use in national emergencies, litigation is expected to turn to the U.S. Court of International Trade, where companies have already hired an army of lawyers to help them recoup their tariff losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/law-firms-gird-tariff-refund-fight-after-supreme-court-ruling-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKJ25VW35FKYZNYX4BMH6TQ3MY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TXNM能源公司115亿美元收购黑石集团交易获联邦能源监管委员会批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[TXNM能源公司周五宣布，美国联邦能源监管委员会（FERC）已批准该公司被黑石基础设施收购。【原文：TXNM Energy on Friday said the U.S. Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (FERC) had authorized the company's acquisition by Blackstone Infrastructure .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/txnm-energy-gets-ferc-approval-115-billion-blackstone-deal-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIQQBWMMYFO5BPI3X3ANGQ5QQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普因最高法院推翻其全球关税令而勃然大怒，誓言将征收10%新关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普对周五最高法院裁决其无权单方面对进口商品加征关税的判决作出激烈回应，在誓言继续这场已让世界紧张不安一年的全球贸易战时，他贬低了部分大法官。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump responded with fury to Friday's Supreme Court ruling that he did not have the power to unilaterally set tariffs on imports, denigrating individual justices as he vowed to continue a global trade war that has kept the world on edge for a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-furious-after-supreme-court-upends-his-global-tariffs-vows-new-10-levy-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NL64WZTSOZPCBL5NYBSHJUGOUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院关税裁决令美联储加息路径蒙上阴影，此前一年市场动荡不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[最高法院对特朗普政府一系列关税措施的裁决，给美联储决策者提出了新问题。过去一年间，这些决策者一直在努力理解总统大幅提高进口关税将如何影响通胀和经济走势。【原文：The Supreme Court's ruling against a broad set of the Trump administration's tariffs poses new questions for Federal Reserve policymakers who have spent the last year trying to understand how the president's sharply higher import taxes would affect inflation and the economic trajectory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/supreme-court-tariff-ruling-clouds-feds-rate-path-after-year-upheaval-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAJZCO2F7RITXAPTX7PIHCJY4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税政策逆转或将降低美国能源企业成本，但整体能源流向可能保持不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五裁定推翻特朗普总统去年实施的贸易关税，此举可能减轻部分石油生产商和钻井商的成本压力。但专家和分析师向路透社表示，目前能源流动格局整体上可能维持不变。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court's Friday decision to strike down trade tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump last year may ease costs for some oil producers and drillers, but experts and analysts told Reuters that broader energy flows would likely remain unchanged for now.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-tariff-reversal-could-cut-costs-us-energy-firms-will-likely-leave-broader-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZF6FXIJLA5KQTEYE3UB6ANTODI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据CNBC报道，OpenAI预计到2030年计算支出将达到约6000亿美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国全国广播公司财经频道周五报道，ChatGPT开发商OpenAI已向投资者透露，其目标是在2030年前实现约6000亿美元的总计算支出。【原文：ChatGPT-maker OpenAI has told investors that it is targeting roughly $600 billion in total compute spend by 2030, CNBC reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-sees-compute-spend-around-600-billion-by-2030-cnbc-reports-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OWKQA4LAVK5TMZ3SOW3ZNIHVA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软游戏部门负责人菲尔·斯宾塞退休，内部人士阿莎·夏尔马接任]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周五宣布，游戏业务负责人菲尔·斯宾塞在该公司任职38年后即将退休。此次重大领导层调整正值该行业竞争日益激烈、挑战不断加剧之际。【原文：Microsoft said on Friday gaming head Phil Spencer is retiring after 38 years at the software maker, in a major leadership shake-up amid growing challenges in a competitive industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-gaming-head-phil-spencer-retires-insider-asha-sharma-takes-over-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44OAJIB5QBIORDFZP4YFZPM2KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邮轮运营商嘉年华将实现双重上市统一]]></title><description><![CDATA[邮轮运营商嘉年华公司周五宣布，将整合其在纽约和伦敦的双重上市地位，并将注册地迁至百慕大。【原文：Carnival will unify its parallel listings in New York and London and redomicile to Bermuda, the cruise operator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cruise-operator-carnival-unify-dual-listing-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXBNODHRQZL2VNLTY4F2G5B6QQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:22:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空公司Azul退出第11章破产程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空公司Azul周五通过证券文件宣布，已正式结束在美国境内的破产程序。【原文：Brazilian airline Azul formally exited its bankruptcy proceedings in the United States on Friday, it said in a securities filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/brazils-airline-azul-exits-chapter-11-bankruptcy-proceedings-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCOTF3DDQRM5DJFF7JWZKT2TZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:08:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特向福克斯新闻表示，美国经济2026年至少可实现3.5%的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五在福克斯新闻《威尔·凯恩秀》节目中表示，他认为2026年美国经济增速至少可达3.5%。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told "The Will Cain Show" on Fox News on Friday that he believed the U.S. economy could grow by at least 3.5% in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economy-can-grow-least-35-2026-bessent-tells-fox-news-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4D7MIOYFAVKJRINZI573FKV3NI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西副总统阿尔克明称，美国最高法院关税裁决使巴西重获竞争力]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西副总统杰拉尔多·阿尔克明周五表示，美国最高法院推翻特朗普总统全面关税的裁决对南美国家至关重要，因为该裁决取消了针对巴西的特定关税，恢复了该国在美国市场的竞争力。【原文：Brazil's Vice-President Geraldo Alckmin said on Friday the U.S. Supreme Court ruling that struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs was really important for the South American country, as it removed levies specifically targeting the nation and restored its competitiveness in the U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-supreme-court-tariff-ruling-restores-competitiveness-brazil-says-vp-alckmin-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75WAZYKXQJPYJC6CQE4FF3GHEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:12:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大交通部已认证湾流G500和G600喷气机，文件显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大交通部已认证通用动力湾流公司的G500和G600公务机，政府文件显示。此前美国总统特朗普曾批评加拿大监管机构审批该机型耗时过长，引发双方近期争执。【原文：Transport Canada has certified General Dynamics Gulfstream's G500 and G600 business jets, according to a government document, following a recent spat in which U.S. President Donald Trump criticized the Canadian regulator for taking too long to approve the aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/transport-canada-has-certified-gulfstream-g500-g600-jets-document-says-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NFX53QT3FIDJEAF26KRZUYPHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部在农业经济面临挑战之际为120亿美元补贴辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国农业部准备在下周发放120亿美元政府补贴，该机构在华盛顿附近举行的年度论坛上，官员和经济学家们为这项援助措施辩护，称其是防止更多农民陷入财务困境的必要举措。【原文：As the U.S. Department of Agriculture prepares to dole out $12 billion in government subsidies next week, officials and economists at the agency's annual forum near Washington defended the assistance as a necessary measure to prevent more farmers from financial ruin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-defends-12-billion-subsidy-amid-farm-economy-challenges-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKLTY46QBNOFXIAJWPD3EHECNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔旗下太平洋电力公司支付5.75亿美元，以解决美国政府提出的野火索赔]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五表示，伯克希尔哈撒韦旗下公用事业公司太平洋电力公司已同意支付5.75亿美元，以解决美国政府就俄勒冈州和加利福尼亚州六起野火提出的损害赔偿索赔。这些野火烧毁了近29万英亩联邦土地。【原文：PacifiCorp, a utility owned by Berkshire Hathaway, , agreed to pay $575 million to resolve U.S. government damages claims related to six wildfires in Oregon and California that burned nearly 290,000 acres of federal land, the U.S. Department of Justice said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/berkshire-owned-pacificorp-pays-575-million-settle-us-governments-wildfire-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAXMHWDPGJNWNL375VWFB4DL3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院裁决对全球经济几乎没有缓解作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国最高法院周五对特朗普总统使用关税的裁决，标志着其将贸易关税作为经济武器的策略遭遇重大挫折，但分析人士指出，这对全球经济几乎没有带来立竿见影的缓解。【原文：While the U.S. Supreme Court's ruling on Friday against President Donald Trump's use of tariffs marks a clear setback for his use of trade levies as an economic weapon, analysts say it offers little immediate relief for the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-supreme-court-ruling-offers-little-respite-global-economy-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D33IGY63MJNDJL6E4BTG5HVNJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业对美国最高法院就特朗普全球关税案裁决的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业界和行业团体对美国最高法院推翻特朗普紧急关税的裁决表示欢迎。这一裁决虽带来解脱，但企业仍需为即将到来的复杂退税流程做好准备。【原文：Businesses and industry groups hailed the U.S. Supreme Court's move to overturn Donald Trump's emergency tariffs, a ruling that brings relief but leaves companies bracing for the complicated refund process ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/industry-reaction-us-supreme-court-ruling-trumps-global-tariffs-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IS36US7QTZKKDDQ7I5K5BJ2TNU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:26:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，美国证券交易委员会对AppLovin的调查仍在进行中]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻周五报道称，美国证券交易委员会对营销平台AppLovin的调查仍在继续。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's investigation into marketing platform AppLovin is continuing, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sec-probe-involving-applovin-still-active-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BA7EOIMYVVNE3IZFGSEW2FQGP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称最高法院裁决后中国购买美国大豆的可能性降低]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析人士称，在最高法院推翻特朗普全面加征关税的决定后，中国可能不太可能继续推进特朗普数周来大力宣传的又一笔美国大豆大宗采购。【原文：China may be less likely to follow through on another big purchase of U.S. soybeans that President Donald Trump has been touting for several weeks in the wake of the Supreme Court striking down Trump's sweeping tariffs, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/analysts-say-china-less-likely-buy-us-soy-after-supreme-court-decision-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BWIP2I22JPITHKDMJFOXVCKJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:25:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道，康菲石油公司正考虑出售价值20亿美元的二叠纪盆地资产。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周五报道，知情人士透露，康菲石油正考虑出售其部分二叠纪盆地资产，作为其资产组合更广泛精简计划的一部分。【原文：ConocoPhillips is exploring a sale of some of its Permian Basin assets as part of a broader streamlining of its portfolio, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/conocophillips-considers-selling-permian-assets-worth-2-billion-bloomberg-news-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUUYDNXRRZLHNKWMVK2KYPPWTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:20:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据备忘录显示，摩根大通正联合半导体行业协会（CHIPS）及国防官员，推动一项价值1.5万亿美元的安全计划。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五获得的一份备忘录显示，摩根大通已任命一批高级管理人员，以推进其在国家安全和经济韧性相关领域的业务拓展。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has appointed a group of senior leaders to advance its push into sectors tied to national security and economic resilience, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-taps-chips-defense-officials-15-trillion-security-initiative-push-memo-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">552RE2BPAVNY7MGPIFO5VJUSTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令实施临时性10%全球关税，以替代被美国最高法院否决的关税措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周五表示，他将实施为期150天的10%全球关税，以取代部分被美国最高法院否决的紧急关税措施。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday that he would impose a 10% global tariff for 150 days to replace some of his emergency duties that were struck down by the U.S. Supreme Court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-orders-temporary-10-global-tariff-replace-duties-struck-down-by-us-supreme-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKK55MQIHZKM7DXQRWLKYVBKQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:53:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将签署行政令，对全球商品加征10%关税。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周五在简报会上表示，他将签署一项命令，根据1974年《贸易法》第122条对全球商品征收10%的关税，同时还将启动多项其他调查。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday told a briefing he would sign an order to impose a 10% global tariff under Section 122 of the 1974 Trade Act and would initiate several other investigations as well.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-he-will-sign-order-imposing-10-global-tariff-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PKGEEAB3BP4TJNQBBYWTFMXF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:44:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分销商和零售商可能错失特朗普关税退税]]></title><description><![CDATA[缺乏进口商合法资质的分销商和零售商，可能因美国最高法院一项具有里程碑意义的裁决而错失高达1750亿美元的关税退税。【原文：Distributors and retailers that lack legal status as importers could miss out on as much as $175  billion in tariff refunds that may follow a landmark U.S. Supreme Court decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/distributors-retailers-risk-missing-out-trump-tariff-refunds-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJMBU5MBGNI6RNZSLRIZMPXBIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:39:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>