<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 07:35:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 07:35:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中东紧张局势令投资者提高警惕，权衡最坏情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果美国进一步卷入中东冲突，投资者正在考虑一系列不同的市场情景，如果能源价格暴涨，可能会产生连锁反应。【原文：Investors are mulling a host of different market scenarios should the U.S. deepen its involvement in the Middle East conflict, with the potential for ripple effects if energy prices skyrocket.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/middle-east-tensions-put-investors-alert-weighing-worst-case-scenarios-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UZI2C37ZFMUDMXZU4N4HUDJOQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 05:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾央行称美国债务增长过快可能影响对国债的信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾央行行长周六警告说，美国债务的快速上升可能对美国国债的前景 "不利"，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易政策也让投资者变得谨慎。【原文：Taiwan's central bank governor warned on Saturday that rapidly rising U.S. debt could be "unfavourable" to the outlook for U.S. Treasuries and that U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies have made investors cautious.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-central-bank-says-us-debt-rising-too-fast-may-impact-trust-treasuries-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAGZPPZQOZJDHHFDIJEY3DZRUQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:16:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国首席贸易特使计划于 6 月 22 日至 27 日访问美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国贸易部周六表示，韩国贸易部长杨汉九将于 6 月 22 日至 27 日访问美国。【原文：South Korea's trade minister Yeo Han-koo will visit the United States from June 22 to 27, the trade ministry said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-koreas-chief-trade-envoy-plans-us-visit-june-22-27-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75E6KNX6DJNJVM3OLJWTNJZJ3E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，丰田将从 7 月起将美国汽车价格上调 200 多美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，日本汽车制造商丰田汽车公司将从7月起把在美国销售的部分汽车价格提高200多美元。【原文：Japanese carmaker Toyota Motor Corp will raise prices of some vehicles it sells in the U.S. by more than $200 from July, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-raise-us-auto-prices-by-more-than-200-july-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBCJ3OUYEJKHFPXLFS3FE7DF3Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称马拉松公司正在评估得克萨斯州加尔维斯顿湾炼油厂的受损情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉工厂运营情况的人士称，马拉松石油公司周五继续评估其位于得克萨斯州得克萨斯城、日产 63.1 万桶的加尔维斯顿湾炼油厂（Galveston Bay Refinery）因 6 月 14 日火灾而关闭的残余加氢装置（RHU）所遭受的损失。【原文：Marathon Petroleum continued assessing damage on Friday to the shut residual hydrotreating unit (RHU) at its 631,000-barrel-per-day (bpd) Galveston Bay Refinery in Texas City, Texas, from a June 14 fire, said people familiar with plant operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/marathon-assessing-damage-galveston-bay-texas-refinery-sources-say-2025-06-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">77ZESKRYLVIYZNTIGASCLEEYN4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国之音母公司再解雇 600 多名员工，可能敲响丧钟]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国之音的母机构周五表示，已向超过 639 名员工发出解聘通知，自 3 月份以来人员减少了 85%，这实际上意味着一个为反纳粹宣传而成立的广播网络的终结。【原文：The parent agency of Voice of America said on Friday it had issued termination notices to over 639 more staff, completing an 85% decrease in personnel since March and effectively spelling the end of a broadcasting network founded to counter Nazi propaganda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/voice-america-parent-terminates-over-600-more-staff-likely-death-knell-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QECOUVU5FZITNNYPVCNAXNIFNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 23:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称可能不得不改变解雇美联储主席鲍威尔的主意]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他可能不得不改变解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的想法。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he may have to change his mind about firing Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-he-may-have-change-his-mind-about-firing-fed-chair-powell-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75F7I5BQKVLY5CBHLPZQOINRDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 22:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府表示暂停执行拜登时代的农民工规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周五表示，将暂停执行前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）政府的一项农民工规定，并称该规定 "负担沉重"。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration said on Friday it was suspending enforcement of a farmworker rule from former President Joe Biden's administration while labeling that rule as "burdensome."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trump-administration-says-it-is-suspending-enforcement-biden-era-farmworker-rule-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVUITCXSPFMPDBGVYMM54FORHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 22:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果公司高管就收购 Perplexity 举行了内部会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，苹果公司高管已经就竞购人工智能初创公司Perplexity的可能性举行了内部会谈。【原文：Apple executives have held internal talks about potentially bidding for artificial intelligence startup Perplexity, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-executives-held-internal-talks-about-buying-perplexity-bloomberg-news-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AT2PWCHU5NNTLNTEGSEHOC7ITQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:31:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国高速公路安全官员审查特斯拉的机器人出租车部署计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）上个月曾致函特斯拉，就其部署自动驾驶机器人出租车的计划提出问题，特斯拉已对此作出回应。【原文：Tesla has responded to a letter the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration sent last month asking questions about its plans to deploy its self driving robotaxi, the agency said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-highway-safety-officials-reviewing-teslas-robotaxi-deployment-plans-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FT4ZENA4NNRVPNRO26SZZDNGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛支付 1,000 万美元了结美国联邦贸易委员会有关汇款欺诈的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛已同意支付 1,000 万美元，以了结美国联邦贸易委员会的民事诉讼，该诉讼指控这家全球最大的零售商忽视了欺诈者利用其汇款服务骗取消费者数亿美元的警告信号。【原文：Walmart has agreed to pay $10 million to settle a U.S. Federal Trade Commission civil lawsuit accusing the world's largest retailer of ignoring warning signs that fraudsters used its money transfer services to fleece consumers out of hundreds of millions of dollars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/walmart-pay-10-million-settle-us-ftc-lawsuit-over-money-transfer-fraud-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMQTDHDNTNO4RIZKGLVR46YSYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会因与中国的关系下令审查 "网络信任标志 "计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会主席布兰登-卡尔（Brendan Carr）周五表示，他已下令对美国网络信任标识计划进行审查，因为 "可能与中国政府有关联"。【原文：Federal Communications Commission chair Brendan Carr said on Friday he had ordered a review of the U.S. Cyber Trust Mark program over "potentially concerning ties to the government of China."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/fcc-orders-review-cyber-trust-mark-program-over-china-ties-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FE3HFNLUNL3PKTRJQF44YV3ZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:38:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 周末再次观战]]></title><description><![CDATA[- 交易日【原文：- TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FS2S5NUHNFMUBK25SHGEIGD72E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:36:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席戴利称秋季降息可能合适]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周五表示，美国经济的基本面正在发生变化，可能有必要降息，但她同时表示 7 月份降息可能为时尚早。【原文：The fundamentals of the U.S. economy are moving to where an interest rate cut may be necessary, San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly said on Friday, though she signaled a July rate cut would probably be too early.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-says-rate-cut-fall-could-be-appropriate-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VH7J3NRXIFPXHOJQEKLMROZVJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰克资源公司着眼于提高芯片制造金属锗的产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大泰克资源公司（Teck Resources）通讯与政府事务副总裁道格-布朗（Doug Brown）表示，该公司正在权衡扩大锗生产的各种方案，锗是一种对芯片制造至关重要的战略金属，目前该公司正在与包括加拿大和美国在内的各国政府就可用资金问题进行商谈。【原文：Canada's Teck Resources is weighing options to expand production of germanium, a strategic metal key to chipmaking, and is currently talking with governments, including Canada and the United States, on available funding, said Doug Brown, VP communications & government affairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/teck-resources-eyes-output-boost-chipmaking-metal-germanium-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTCSCU5MBFKQXKADUPKZNSE3NE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普预测将与印度和巴基斯坦达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五预测，美国将能够与印度和巴基斯坦谈判达成贸易协议。【原文：President Donald Trump predicted on Friday that the United States will be able to negotiate trade deals with both India and Pakistan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-predicts-trade-deals-with-india-pakistan-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONI6A7HSE5IUNNVLLI3PYUYO44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TD Cowen 表示，到 2035 年，肌肉保护药物的销售额将超过 300 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[TD Cowen 公司的分析师周五表示，礼来公司和诺和诺德公司生产的流行肥胖症药物旨在帮助患者在减肥的同时保持肌肉，到 2035 年其销售额将超过 300 亿美元。【原文：Treatments designed to help patients preserve muscle while losing weight with popular obesity drugs by Eli Lilly and Novo Nordisk could generate more than $30 billion in sales by 2035, analysts at TD Cowen said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/muscle-preserving-drugs-could-generate-over-30-billion-sales-by-2035-td-cowen-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LDXDFL4N5K6RMQYK5VOHOGPXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国生产商急于锁定飙升的油价，石油套期保值量创下新纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列上周对伊朗的突然袭击导致油价飙升，美国生产商争相锁定价格涨幅，推动了创纪录的套期保值交易量，这将帮助他们抵御未来的价格波动。【原文：Israel's surprise attack on Iran last week had oil prices spiking which sent U.S. producers scrambling to lock in the price gain, driving record hedging volumes that will help shield them from future price swings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-hedging-volumes-hit-new-records-us-producers-rush-lock-soaring-prices-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3IQI7LVZVLTLMBOYXXXECU57A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥银行下周将把关键利率下调 50 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥央行预计将在下周发布的公告中再次将关键利率下调半个百分点，不过在通胀上升和经济增长疲软的情况下，墨西哥央行将放缓未来的货币紧缩步伐。【原文：Mexico's central bank is expected to cut its key interest rate by half a percentage point again in its announcement next week, although it would moderate the pace of monetary tightening going forward amid rising inflation and weak economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-mexico-seen-cutting-key-rate-by-50-basis-points-next-week-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6V53SJFKMVKJHC5FBQO72ZQIQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司因披露人工智能信息遭股东起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，苹果公司遭到股东集体起诉，指控苹果公司淡化了将先进的人工智能功能整合到其 Siri 助手中所需的时间，从而损害了 iPhone 的销量和股价。【原文：Apple was sued by shareholders in a proposed class action on Friday, accusing it of downplaying the time needed to integrate advanced artificial intelligence-based features into its Siri assistant, hurting iPhone sales and its stock price.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apple-sued-by-shareholders-over-ai-disclosures-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLMC227RFNO2LNJWEMQOBUPFUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉邀请少数人参加德克萨斯州机器人出租车试验，前座配备安全监控装置]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据社交媒体上的帖子和电子邮件截图，特斯拉已向一小部分人发出邀请，参加其在得克萨斯州奥斯汀的机器人出租车服务有限测试，测试暂定于周日开始。【原文：Tesla has sent out invitations to a small group of people to join the limited test of its robotaxi service in Austin, Texas, which is tentatively set to start on Sunday, according to posts and email screenshots on social media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-invites-select-few-texas-robotaxi-trial-with-front-seat-safety-monitors-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BGRXBUSWZI3PPODCANF53K3XE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谘商会称美国 5 月领先指标下滑，触发衰退信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[受消费者悲观情绪、制成品新订单疲软、申请失业救济人数上升和建筑许可申请量下降的影响，衡量美国未来经济活动的指标在 5 月份连续第六个月下降，并触发了衰退信号。【原文：A measure of future U.S. economic activity fell in May for the sixth straight month and triggered a recession signal, held down by consumer pessimism, weak new orders for manufactured goods, an uptick in jobless benefits claims and a drop in building permit applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-leading-indicators-slip-may-triggering-recession-signal-conference-board-says-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3R3QZS2HNI7NOA6HT4OPY62AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:08:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院拒绝加快决定是否受理特朗普关税之争]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五拒绝加快审议是否受理对唐纳德-特朗普总统的全面关税措施提出的质疑，甚至在下级法院对这一争端作出裁决之前就拒绝受理。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Friday to speed up its consideration of whether to take up a challenge to President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs even before lower courts have ruled in the dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-declines-speed-up-decision-taking-up-fight-over-trump-tariffs-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEA5KRHQ3FJOBGLJFTDLN4CJSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，谷歌提议调整搜索结果以促进竞争对手，避免欧盟反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的文件显示，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司已提议对其搜索结果进行更多改动，以更好地展示竞争对手，从而避免可能被欧盟处以巨额反垄断罚款。【原文：Alphabet's Google has proposed more changes to its search results to better showcase rivals in a bid to stave off a possible hefty EU antitrust fine, according to documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/google-offers-tweak-search-results-promote-rivals-stave-off-eu-antitrust-fine-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7Y4IICEOZN2LDY37C453YPJSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:32:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储主席巴金不急于降息，不能忽视关税带来的通胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周五表示，鉴于新进口税可能引发通胀的风险仍未解决，而且美国就业市场和消费支出保持良好，因此不急于降息。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said on Friday there's no rush to cut interest rates given the still-unresolved risk that new import taxes might raise inflation, and with the U.S. job market and consumer spending holding up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-barkin-no-rush-cut-cant-dismiss-inflation-risks-tariffs-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOHEJ4EQSZIKFKKKX6UY5Z77BI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业科技资金荒仍在持续，乳业和太阳能行业成为亮点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业科技行业正处于充满挑战的投资环境中。然而，在资金不景气的情况下，一些公司正在寻找增长机会，尤其是在乳制品和太阳能领域。【原文：The U.S. AgTech sector is navigating a challenging investment climate. Yet, amid the funding downturn, some companies are carving out growth opportunities, particularly in the dairy and solar sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-agtech-capital-drought-continues-dairy-solar-sectors-offer-bright-spots-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVLLFKQM4NK73E4IEXPJQIYS2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AT&T 1.77 亿美元数据泄露和解协议获美国法院批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一名美国法官初步批准了一项价值 1.77 亿美元的和解协议，该协议解决了针对 AT&amp;T 公司的数据安全诉讼，该诉讼涉及该电信巨头数千万客户的个人信息泄露。【原文：A U.S. judge granted preliminary approval on Friday to a $177 million settlement that resolves data security lawsuits against AT&amp;T over breaches that exposed personal information belonging to tens of millions of the telecom giant’s customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/177-million-att-data-breach-settlement-wins-us-court-approval-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4W4SYQGEABIRVHSRNYJMRIFTEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称花旗集团从摩根大通聘请德拉古-拉杰科维奇担任并购部门联席主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份备忘录，花旗集团从竞争对手摩根大通聘请德拉戈-拉杰科维奇（Drago Rajkovic）担任并购部门联席主管。【原文：Citigroup hired Drago Rajkovic as its co-head of mergers and acquisitions from rival JPMorgan Chase , according to a memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-hires-drago-rajkovic-co-head-ma-jpmorgan-memo-says-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7R3ETQIZHJI4ZAZMJVPAJF6YLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百胜中国推出人工智能工具以提高效率]]></title><description><![CDATA[百胜中国控股公司周五表示，已在部分肯德基门店推出新的人工智能免提助手工具，以提高效率。【原文：Yum China Holdings , said on Friday it has launched a new AI-enabled hands-free assistant tool at certain KFC stores in a bid to boost efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/yum-china-unveils-ai-tool-bid-boost-efficiency-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ2ZRUPFL5OVDAF4YHT42WFRCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:28:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国准备针对盟友在华芯片工厂采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，一名美国官员已通知全球领先的半导体公司，计划取消允许它们在中国使用美国技术的豁免。【原文：A U.S. official has informed leading global semiconductor companies of plans to cancel waivers allowing them to use American technology in China, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-prepares-action-targeting-allies-chip-plants-china-wsj-reports-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UG5U7ZQAZIPVLVQSTOAO4YOCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>