<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:35:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:35:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[看好人工智能前景提振第一季度盈利，软银股价飙升至创纪录水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五上午，软银集团（SoftBank Group）股价跳涨逾 13%，创下历史新高，表明投资者支持这家日本科技投资者在第一季度利润超出预期后推动人工智能发展。【原文：Shares in SoftBank Group jumped more than 13% to a record high on Friday morning in a show of investor support for the Japanese technology investor's AI push after first quarter profit beat expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-shares-surge-record-after-optimism-ai-prospects-boosted-q1-earnings-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLMB2H3DUBM3VNVWHGRE5ZSIAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国中芯国际称特朗普关税并未导致预期的 "硬着陆]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国顶级代工企业中芯国际的联席首席执行官周五表示，美国的关税政策并未导致该公司最初担心的 "硬着陆"，强劲的国内需求将使其产能在10月份之前一直处于紧张状态。【原文：China's top foundry SMIC's co-CEO said on Friday that U.S. tariff policy had not resulted in the "hard landing" that the company was initially worried about and that strong domestic demand will keep its production capacity tight until October.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-smic-says-trump-tariffs-did-not-cause-expected-hard-landing-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GG4ZDYDRGRIV3EXUALLXARM53Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财报提振日本股指创历史新高，亚洲其他市场有所缓和]]></title><description><![CDATA[在积极的盈利报告和美国将取消对日本商品征收重叠关税的预期之后，日本股市周五大涨。【原文：Japanese shares surged on Friday after positive earnings reports and expectations the U.S. would remove overlapping tariffs on the country's goods, while shares were down in other Asian markets after a late retreat on Wall Street during the previous session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJSAG47OS5PDDLXJCF6NUFNN5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美联储人选、英国央行的 "鹰派 "降息令美元承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普临时选择的美联储代理理事人选激起了人们对在杰罗姆-鲍威尔任期结束后由一个鸽派人选接替其职务的预期，美元周五承压，并有望每周下跌。【原文：The dollar was under pressure on Friday and was on course for a weekly fall as U.S. President Donald Trump's temporary choice for a fill-in Federal Reserve Governor stoked expectations for a dovish pick to replace chair Jerome Powell when his term ends.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/trumps-fed-pick-bank-englands-hawkish-cut-weigh-dollar-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTFGPIIS3FI2FDRN5GSIGLUALI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Meta 选择 Pimco 和 Blue Owl 为其数据中心融资 290 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，Meta 已选择投资管理公司 Pimco 和另类资产管理公司 Blue Owl Capital 为其路易斯安那州农村地区的数据中心项目提供 290 亿美元的融资。【原文：Meta has selected investment management firm Pimco and alternative asset manager Blue Owl Capital for a $29 billion financing deal related to its data center projects in rural Louisiana, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-selects-pimco-blue-owl-29-billion-data-center-financing-bloomberg-news-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGS7ZS4WUJIJHHKQIBM27AU4ZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税给需求前景蒙上阴影，石油将创六月以来最大单周跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚洲早盘，油价变化不大，但因投资者对周四生效的关税对全球经济的影响表示担忧，油价将创下自6月底以来的最大单周跌幅。【原文：Oil prices were little changed in early Asian hours on Friday, but were headed for their steepest weekly losses since late-June, as investors expressed concern over the impact to the global economy from tariffs that kicked into effect on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-set-steepest-weekly-losses-since-june-tariffs-cloud-demand-outlook-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BAKYNPCTBJ2RLMDIJQXQGDESQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:16:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7 月摘要显示，日本央行就恢复加息的可能性进行了辩论]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行 7 月份会议的意见摘要显示，一些日本央行决策者警告称通胀压力正在上升，其中一位决策者表示有可能在年底前恢复加息，从而保持了近期加息的可能性。【原文：Some Bank of Japan policymakers warned of mounting inflationary pressures and one signaled the chance of resuming interest rate increases by year-end, a summary of opinions at the July meeting showed, keeping alive the possibility of a near-term rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-debated-chance-resuming-rate-hike-july-summary-shows-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BPXNBWJBZMJHA6MZAHWKBXK5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官驳回美国消费者监督机构对益百利的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份法庭文件，消费者金融保护局针对信用评级巨头益百利公司（Experian）有关信用报告准确性的诉讼于周三被驳回。【原文：A lawsuit filed by the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau against credit rating giant Experian over credit report accuracy was dismissed on Wednesday, according to a court filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/judge-dismisses-us-consumer-watchdog-lawsuit-against-experian-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2QT2RD3PGFJCJMHMP6TGI3HYOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heartflow 在美国首次公开募股中融资 3.167 亿美元，医疗科技上市企业试图卷土重来]]></title><description><![CDATA[医疗技术公司 Heartflow 周四表示，该公司在美国首次公开募股中筹集了 3.167 亿美元，为其在纳斯达克的首次公开募股做好了准备，这是对投资者对医疗技术公司胃口的又一次考验。【原文：Medical technology firm Heartflow said on Thursday it had raised $316.7 million in its U.S. initial public offering, setting the stage for its Nasdaq debut in another test of investor appetite for medical tech companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/heartflow-raises-3167-million-us-ipo-medtech-listings-attempt-comeback-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGTCOPOIRBMXHIQZ76SKYCSKFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚隐私监管机构就 2022 年网络攻击事件起诉 Optus]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚隐私监管机构周五表示，已就新加坡电信旗下电信运营商 Optus 于 2022 年 9 月遭遇网络攻击一事对该公司提起法律诉讼。【原文：Australia's privacy regulator has initiated legal proceedings against Optus, the Singapore Telecommunications-owned telecom operator, over a cyber attack it faced in September 2022, the company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australias-privacy-regulator-sues-optus-over-2022-cyber-attack-2025-08-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LAVJNG4WNKIJMZSIQMSFVR4YQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁工人工会为下一份炼油厂工人合同提出建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁工人联合会（USW）全国石油谈判主席迈克-史密斯（Mike Smith）说，在匹兹堡举行的 300 多名炼油厂和化工厂工人会议周四批准了将于 2026 年初与能源公司开始的劳资谈判提案。【原文：More than 300 United Steelworkers union (USW) refinery and chemical plants workers meeting in Pittsburgh approved on Thursday proposals for labor negotiations set to begin early in 2026 with energy companies, said Mike Smith, chair of national oil bargaining for the union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/united-steelworkers-union-sets-proposals-next-refinery-worker-contract-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4A6ERGOTRK3TFNLJLNCBW6S7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:46:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Iress 确认与 Blackstone、Thoma Bravo 就潜在竞购进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Iress 公司周五证实，该公司正与 Blackstone 和 Thoma Bravo 就金融软件公司的潜在收购要约进行早期讨论。【原文：Australia's Iress confirmed on Friday that it was in early stages of discussion with Blackstone and Thoma Bravo for a potential offer for the financial software firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-iress-confirms-talks-potential-bid-blackstone-thoma-bravo-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQNC7WNPW5P2FDOSSA2NLBK6NI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保费增长、索赔减少，澳大利亚昆士保险公司中期利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，澳大利亚昆士兰保险公司（QBE）的中期盈利超出了市场预期，这主要得益于北美和国际业务保费的强劲增长，以及赔付率的限制。【原文：Australian insurer QBE beat market estimates for interim earnings on Friday, helped by strong premium growth in North America and international divisions coupled with claims being limited.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-insurer-qbe-beats-interim-profit-estimates-premium-growth-lower-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWC5FCIZJVNU3D2P6GEVXGH55I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[永利因澳门业务疲软未达季度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，赌场运营商永利度假村（Wynn Resorts）第二季度利润不及预期，原因是澳门业务低迷。【原文：Casino operator Wynn Resorts missed second-quarter profit expectations on Thursday, owing to sluggish Macau business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/wynn-misses-quarterly-estimates-weak-macau-business-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43VTBIQJ6RL2LPTYOPSDR7JUFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:59:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jack in the Box 首席执行官称西班牙裔消费者因 "不确定性 "而缩减开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jack in the Box 的首席执行官说，Jack in the Box 核心市场的西班牙裔消费者 "面临不确定性，已经缩减了开支"，这个问题对这家美国快餐连锁店的销售产生了巨大影响。【原文：Hispanic consumers in Jack in the Box's core markets "face uncertainty and have pulled back their spending," with the issue having an outsized impact on the U.S. fast-food chain's sales, its CEO said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/jack-box-ceo-says-hispanic-consumers-pulling-back-spending-over-uncertainty-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXLYE4JEN5OBVPORVQSNTPKNJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:53:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求稳定，摩托罗拉解决方案上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[安全和企业安全服务提供商摩托罗拉解决方案公司周四上调了年度收入预期，原因是安全和安全解决方案需求强劲。【原文：Safety and enterprise security services provider Motorola Solutions raised annual revenue forecast on Thursday, driven by robust demand for its safety and security solutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/motorola-solutions-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-steady-demand-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXQLOAVQJVJF3M7IKYR6CAN24E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:46:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚矿业公司 Fortescue 获得近 20 亿美元贷款以推进脱碳进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fortescue周五表示，它已获得价值142亿元人民币（19.8亿美元）的银团定期贷款，这家澳大利亚矿业公司希望以此支持其雄心勃勃的去碳化计划。【原文：Fortescue said on Friday it had secured a syndicated term loan facility worth 14.2 billion Chinese yuan ($1.98 billion) as the Australian miner looks to support its ambitious decarbonisation plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australian-miner-fortescue-lands-near-2-billion-loan-advance-decarbonisation-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NB4VSWA2I5PDZIQ5X2VKVROEGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:33:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本敦促修改美国总统关税令]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周五表示，日本最高关税谈判代表赤泽亮世在华盛顿与美国高级官员会晤时 "强烈 "敦促美国修改总统征税令。【原文：Japan's top tariff negotiator Ryosei Akazawa "strongly" urged the United States to revise the presidential order on the levies at his meetings with top U.S. officials in Washington, the Japanese government said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-urges-revision-us-presidential-order-tariffs-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUY6MCHGQVPNXOCFSQ42P2LGTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:25:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特斯拉解散 Dojo 超级计算机团队]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，特斯拉正在解散其 Dojo 超级计算机团队，该团队负责人彼得-班农（Peter Bannon）将离开公司。【原文：Tesla is disbanding its Dojo supercomputer team and its leader, Peter Bannon, will depart the company, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-disbands-dojo-supercomputer-team-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GYIC37HL5M4TMOLAU5M2PAW5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pemex 计划令等待数十亿美元逾期付款的供应商失望]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥一家代表全球油田服务公司的协会负责人周四表示，尽管官方承诺加快付款速度，但墨西哥国家石油公司（Pemex）的新业务计划缺乏解决其与供应商之间巨额债务的具体措施。
AMESPAC协会主席拉斐尔-埃斯皮诺（Rafael Espino）告诉路透社记者，在周二与财政部、能源部和Pemex公司官员举行的会议上，没有提到该公司将如何偿还2024年和2025年上半年已完成工作的债务。
埃斯皮诺说，截至 6 月底，AMESPAC 成员被拖欠了约 650 亿比索（约合 34.9 亿美元）的工程款，而这些工程款甚至尚未开具发票。
"埃斯皮诺在接受采访时说："这令人失望，因为没有具体提及 2024 年的债务。"如果我们不得不等待用未来的现金流来偿还......这笔债务将继续得不到偿还，直接影响的将是生产"。
不过，埃斯皮诺补充说，与会官员表示，墨西哥石油公司将加快付款速度，不会让发票账龄超过两个月，并预计手头将有更多现金。这些现金将来自较低的税负、最近发行的 120 亿美元债务以及新设立的用于 2025 年项目的 130 亿美元特别基金。
Pemex 欠下了约 230 亿美元的供应商债务和近 1000 亿美元的金融债务，尽管近年来政府为其履行债务提供了数十亿美元的支持。
虽然支付了一些款项并经常做出承诺，但债务仍在不断累积，给服务供应商造成了前所未有的支付危机。
埃斯皮诺说，AMESPAC 对该计划表示欢迎，但正在寻求与当局建立一个正式的工作组，以了解新的 2025 年投资工具及其相关服务付款的规则、时间表和资格。
该协会认为，偿还未偿债务对于重新启用闲置设备和帮助实现墨西哥原油日产量 180 万桶的目标是必要的，而这一目标在很大程度上依赖于墨西哥石油公司。
AMESPAC 的成员包括全球最大的四家能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）、哈里伯顿（Halliburton）、威德福（Weatherford）和 SLB，以及采矿和运输集团墨西哥集团（Grupo Mexico）。
最近，大亨卡洛斯-斯利姆（Carlos Slim）控制的卡索集团（Grupo Carso）报告称，Pemex 欠其各种服务费超过 7 亿美元，其中一些债务可追溯到两年前。
Grupo Mexico 的一家子公司报告称，由于拖欠款项，它已暂时停止了四个平台的开采，而哈里伯顿公司也表示，它与 Pemex 的付款问题仍未解决。
(1 美元 = 18.6360 墨西哥比索）【原文：The head of an association representing global oilfield service firms in Mexico said on Thursday that a new business plan for state oil company Pemex lacks concrete measures to address its massive debt with suppliers, despite official promises to speed up payments.
Rafael Espino, president of the AMESPAC association, told Reuters that in a Tuesday meeting with officials from the finance and energy ministries and Pemex, there was no mention of how the company would pay down debts for work already performed in 2024 and the first half of 2025.
As of the end of June, Espino said, AMESPAC members were owed about 65 billion pesos ($3.49 billion) for work that has not yet even been invoiced.
"It was a disappointment because there was no specific reference to the 2024 debts," Espino said in an interview. "If we have to wait for it to be paid with future cash flow... this debt will continue to go unpaid and the immediate effect will be on production."
However, Espino added that officials at the meeting said Pemex would speed up payments, not let invoices age beyond two months, and that it expects to have more cash on hand. This would come from a lower tax burden, a recent $12 billion debt issuance, and a new $13 billion special fund for 2025 projects.
Pemex is saddled with supplier debts of around $23 billion and financial debt of nearly $100 billion, despite receiving billions in government support in recent years to meet its obligations.
While making some payments and frequent promises, the debts have continued to accumulate, creating an unprecedented payment crisis for service providers.
Espino said AMESPAC welcomes the plan but is seeking to establish a formal working group with authorities to understand the rules, timeline and eligibility for the new 2025 investment vehicle and its associated service payments.
The association argues that paying off outstanding debts is necessary to reactivate idled equipment and help meet Mexico's national crude production target of 1.8 million barrels per day (bpd), a goal heavily reliant on Pemex.
AMESPAC members include four of the world's largest energy services firms Baker Hughes , Halliburton , Weatherford , and SLB , and mining and transportation conglomerate Grupo Mexico .
Recently, Grupo Carso - controlled by tycoon Carlos Slim - reported that Pemex owes it more than $700 million for various services, with some debts dating back two years.
A subsidiary of Grupo Mexico reported it had temporarily halted four platforms due to non-payment, and Halliburton has stated its payment issues with Pemex remain unresolved.
($1 = 18.6360 Mexican pesos)】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pemex-plan-disappoints-suppliers-awaiting-billions-overdue-payments-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMKRL72N3NOEHMKMRFTKCLM56I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GoDaddy 季度收入略超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受互联网托管服务需求稳定的影响，GoDaddy 周四公布的第二季度营收略高于华尔街预期。【原文：GoDaddy marginally beat Wall Street expectations for second quarter revenue on Thursday, aided by steady demand for its internet hosting services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/godaddy-marginally-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIQV6MUTCVOELPB67O4WD2ZDNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微芯科技第一季度净销售额和利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商微芯科技（Microchip Technology）周四公布的第一季度净销售额和利润超出分析师预期，主要得益于客户清理了过剩库存。【原文：Chipmaker Microchip Technology beat analysts' estimates for first-quarter net sales and profit on Thursday, helped by customers clearing excess inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microchip-tech-beats-q1-net-sales-profit-estimates-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEUNQA4URNNABGUFHR5WQOTOWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府将终止 70 亿美元的太阳能补助计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护署署长李-泽尔丁（Lee Zeldin）周四在 X 上发表文章称，美国环境保护署将终止拜登时代的一项耗资 70 亿美元的拨款计划，该计划旨在将太阳能推广到低收入社区。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency will end a $7 billion Biden-era grant program to expand solar energy to low-income communities, Administrator Lee Zeldin said in a post on X on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trump-administration-will-end-7-billion-solar-energy-grant-program-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OVVKLGGVTNJJNOBOENJZ6BTCYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:52:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Atlassian 预测季度收入下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于企业客户在严峻的经济形势下削减了云软件服务支出，Atlassian 周四预计第一季度营收低于预期。【原文：Atlassian projected first-quarter revenue below estimates on Thursday, as enterprise customers cut spending on cloud software services in a tough economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/atlassian-forecasts-downbeat-quarterly-revenue-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AS2FGHE7WFNCVN3KC7ZTXDJZKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:42:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MSCI 宣布调整股票指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利资本国际公司（MSCI）周四表示，将从其广受关注的 ACWI 股票指数中增加 42 种证券，删除 56 种证券。【原文：MSCI said on Thursday it will add 42 securities and delete 56 from its widely followed ACWI equity index .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/msci-announces-changes-equity-indexes-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NP4VQFNS2BJ7FLVZHKHWCRLIOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:33:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼解决与《曼达洛人》女演员吉娜-卡拉诺的法律纠纷]]></title><description><![CDATA[卢卡斯影业公司（Lucasfilm）发言人周四表示，迪士尼公司已经解决了与演员吉娜-卡拉诺（Gina Carano）之间关于她被 "星球大战 "流媒体电视剧《曼达洛人》（The Mandalorian）解雇的法律纠纷。【原文：Walt Disney has resolved a legal dispute with actor Gina Carano over her firing from the "Star Wars" streaming TV series "The Mandalorian," a spokesperson for Lucasfilm said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/disney-resolves-legal-dispute-with-mandalorian-actress-gina-carano-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORFTJQBQ3ZNIXGHXWLXMDDO4C4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:33:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诉讼指控苹果公司窃取商业机密创建 Apple Pay]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司被一家德克萨斯州公司起诉，该公司指控这家 iPhone 制造商窃取了其技术，用来创建利润丰厚的移动钱包 Apple Pay。【原文：Apple has been sued by a Texas company that accused the iPhone maker of stealing its technology to create its lucrative mobile wallet Apple Pay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/lawsuit-accuses-apple-stealing-trade-secrets-create-apple-pay-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YX52B6FOI5KO3CPEQMM2AC7LAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拟任美联储理事米兰建议加强对他将加入的中央银行的政治控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济顾问委员会主席斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）曾抨击行政部门与美国联邦储备局之间的 "旋转门"，在唐纳德-特朗普总统提名他进入米兰希望彻底改革的机构--美国联邦储备局理事会之后，他现在可能就要走进这扇 "旋转门 "了。【原文：Having railed against the "revolving door" between the executive branch and the U.S. Federal Reserve, Council of Economic Advisers chair Stephen Miran may now be walking through it after President Donald Trump nominated him to the Board of Governors of an institution Miran would like to radically overhaul.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/proposed-fed-governor-miran-recommended-tighter-political-control-central-bank-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T66PWIKV5BLJBCRIBFWVM3SN5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[永明金融第二季度利润增长，亚洲业务表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大永明金融公司（Sun Life Financial）周四公布的第二季度利润大幅增长，主要得益于其亚洲部门的强劲增长。【原文：Canada's Sun Life Financial reported a jump in second-quarter profit on Thursday, driven by strong growth in its Asia unit, where insurers are expanding to tap a growing, under-insured middle class and offset weakness in the U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/sun-lifes-second-quarter-profit-rises-strong-asia-unit-performance-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2LTMVIKD5PYJBOVQM5XWWMCMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:10:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：关税、美联储担忧与科技乐观情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量。【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCUWL3QJFRKQFAT2MYSNZIYADI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:04:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>