<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:35:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:35:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波音罢工、飓风海伦影响美国工业生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[受波音公司罢工和包括海伦在内的两次飓风影响，美国 9 月份工业生产下降。【原文：U.S. industrial production fell in September, weighed down by a strike at Boeing and two hurricanes, including Helene.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/boeing-strike-hurricane-helene-weigh-us-industrial-production-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIQXXDS24NM6JNCF4NNKQVZIEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:28:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国预算案的税收力度远超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据新的细分数据，法国勒紧裤腰带的预算案带来的税收打击比政府最初宣称的要大，这表明埃马纽埃尔-马克龙总统的亲商传统受到了更大的冲击。【原文：France's belt-tightening budget delivers a bigger tax hit than the government originally let on, according to new breakdowns that suggest a bigger dent in President Emmanuel Macron's pro-business legacy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/french-budget-packs-bigger-tax-punch-than-first-meets-eye-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V57N4DE5QJMJ7DBQVP2U57EVQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:23:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁预计中期增长乏力，敦促改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周四表示，国际货币基金组织的最新预测显示，全球经济的未来将面临困难，中期增长乏力、贸易紧张局势升级和债务高企将是其特点。【原文：New forecasts by the International Monetary Fund point to a difficult future for the global economy marked by lackluster medium-term growth, escalating trade tensions and high levels of debt, IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-chief-expects-lukewarm-growth-medium-term-urges-reforms-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQLCZZMRU5PKNIS35CEL5KB4GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国住宅建筑商信心连续第二个月上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国房屋建筑商的信心在 10 月份连续第二个月上升，但波动的抵押贷款利率和较低的住房负担能力继续构成阻力。【原文：U.S. home builder confidence rose in October for the second consecutive month but volatile mortgage rates and low housing affordability continued to pose headwinds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-home-builder-confidence-rises-second-straight-month-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLOT55UNRJPJBC75VKYQDVLHRE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大型央行坚定地进入降息模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社追踪的 10 大发达市场中央银行中，有 7 家现已开始放松政策，由于政策制定者强调数据依赖性，对各家央行将以多快的速度放宽政策的预期前后摇摆不定。【原文：Seven of the 10 big developed-market central banks tracked by Reuters have now started easing policy, with expectations of how quickly each will move swinging back and forth as policymakers stress data dependency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/big-central-banks-are-firmly-rate-cut-mode-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFG7NKWHRNNFTLHDWOMWQN2SN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢标榜美国大选前后购物者的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司周四表示，消费者对美国大选的 "担忧 "给其最大市场的需求带来了进一步的压力，因为这造成了消费者的不确定性。【原文：Nestle on Thursday said shopper "concerns around the election" in the United States are putting further pressure on demand in its biggest market by creating consumer uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nestle-flags-shopper-uncertainty-around-us-election-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDHO3G6V7BJARKB3GBLLOVCVWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Lucid 预计通过出售股票筹资 16.7 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[资金短缺的电动汽车制造商 Lucid 周四表示，公开发行超过 2.62 亿股股票可能会为公司带来 16.7 亿美元的收益。【原文：Cash-strapped electric vehicle maker Lucid said on Thursday a public offering of more than 262 million shares would likely fetch it $1.67 billion in proceeds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-lucid-expects-raise-167-bln-stock-sale-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIHHORIAHJMUJO5PUKKIMJWAHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:54:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点：欧洲央行再次下调关键利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行周四今年第三次下调利率，指出欧元区的通胀率目前正日益受到控制，经济前景有所恶化。【原文：The European Central Bank cut interest rates for the third time this year on Thursday, pointing out that inflation in the euro zone is now increasingly under control and the economic outlook has worsened.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/view-ecb-cuts-key-rates-again-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYOZL3ATLRJ2VKGHUPH44XJGJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:52:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，新申请失业救济的美国人数量意外下降，但在飓风海伦和米尔顿的影响下，短期内可能会继续上升，从而使劳动力市场的情况变得模糊不清。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment unexpectedly fell last week, but could remain elevated in the near-term amid the effects of Hurricanes Helene and Milton, obscuring the labor market picture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-unexpectedly-fall-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYONAGEQPVJA5IBVFNVNSJPSNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:47:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月零售额稳健增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 9 月份零售额增幅略高于预期，支持了第三季度经济保持强劲增长的观点。【原文：U.S. retail sales increased slightly more than expected in September, supporting views that the economy maintained a strong pace of growth in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-retail-sales-increase-solidly-september-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCY2RJEIMNIYVPPPKOJYUZVOTU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行一如预期下调利率，称有望抑制通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲中央银行今年第三次降息，以应对疲软的经济增长、原本稳如磐石的劳动力市场出现的一些疲软以及消费者价格压力的缓解。【原文：The European Central Bank cut interest rates for the third time this year on Thursday in a nod to sluggish economic growth, some softening in an otherwise rock-solid labour market and easing consumer price pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ecb-cuts-rates-expected-says-well-track-tame-inflation-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYU7FPB4PNOENH3E6JXLBGQXHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:20:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[为削减成本，PPG 将在美国和欧洲裁员 1800 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[油漆和涂料生产商PPG工业公司（PPG Industries）周四表示，作为其成本削减计划的一部分，该公司将在美国和欧洲裁员1800人，并关闭多家工厂。【原文：Paints and coatings maker PPG Industries said on Thursday it would lay off 1,800 employees in the United States and Europe and close various facilities as part of its cost-reduction program.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ppg-lay-off-1800-employees-us-europe-cost-cut-push-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNZMQFDVQNORHN6NPQ3KR2Q6DA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电的人工智能前景打动投资者，美国芯片股反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国芯片类股周四盘前上涨，原因是行业风向标台积电强劲的销售预期激发了投资者对人工智能应用处理器需求的乐观情绪。【原文：U.S. chip stocks rose before the bell on Thursday after industry bellwether TSMC's strong sales forecast fanned investor optimism about demand for processors used to power artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-chip-stocks-rally-tsmcs-ai-backed-outlook-impresses-investors-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JX5G7BANWJKNRHGQ353L542VCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:19:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 盈利超出预期，资产规模创历史新高，交易量回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，黑石集团（Blackstone）的关键季度盈利指标超出华尔街预期，这家全球最大的另类投资公司的管理资产（AUM）达到创纪录的 1.1 万亿美元，其基金价值也有所上升。【原文：Blackstone beat Wall Street's expectations on its key quarterly earnings metric on Thursday, as the world's largest alternative investment firm's assets under management (AUM) hit a record $1.1 trillion and the value of its funds rose.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstone-tops-profit-estimate-its-assets-hit-record-dealmaking-picks-up-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6Y3W3GOGFJYDIIDOZ4DWGNZX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飓风袭击佛罗里达州后房主保险公司的应对措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据分析师最新估计，飓风米尔顿上周横扫佛罗里达州，给整个阳光之州造成高达 550 亿美元的财产损失。米尔顿飓风是在 "海伦 "飓风两周后袭击佛罗里达州的，也是近年来扰乱佛罗里达州财产保险市场的一系列重大飓风中最新的一次。【原文：Hurricane Milton tore through Florida last week, causing as much as $55 billion in property damage throughout the Sunshine State, according to the latest analyst estimates. Hitting just two weeks after Hurricane Helene, Milton was the latest in a series of major hurricanes in recent years to disrupt Florida's property insurance market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/homeowner-insurers-responses-after-hurricane-hits-florida-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVCRSTUOEFIW3CJAU2OIPTEEWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称美国高关税墙 "被严重误导"，将抬高物价]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）将于周四表示，共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提出的为美国经济筑墙的建议将是 "严重的误导"，会抬高美国消费者的物价，降低美国公司的竞争力。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen will say on Thursday that walling off the U.S. economy as proposed by Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump would be "deeply misguided," raising prices for American consumers and making U.S. companies less competitive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/yellen-says-high-us-tariff-wall-deeply-misguided-would-raise-prices-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PI62L43HOBKAZLSYVQHQMO5YAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国检察官发现人工智能生成的儿童性虐待图像的威胁正在上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦检察官正在加紧追捕使用人工智能工具操纵或创建儿童性虐待图像的嫌疑人，因为执法部门担心这种技术可能会刺激非法材料的泛滥。【原文：U.S. federal prosecutors are stepping up their pursuit of suspects who use artificial intelligence tools to manipulate or create child sex abuse images, as law enforcement fears the technology could spur a flood of illicit material.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-prosecutors-see-rising-threat-ai-generated-child-sex-abuse-imagery-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7MOQMQ5R5I2DKV4VCVGKJHCNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达州房主担心飓风过后保险费用飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[32 年来，Jim Tynan 为他位于佛罗里达州 Ponte Vedra、面积为 1,200 平方英尺的公寓向 Allstate 投保了业主保险。【原文：For 32 years, Jim Tynan had a homeowners' policy with Allstate on his 1,200-square foot condo in Ponte Vedra, Florida.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/florida-homeowners-fear-soaring-insurance-cost-after-hurricanes-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QT6NCIJBNFJLHGJ3X6KXLXBOCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡莱尔支持的音乐企业购买兰迪-纽曼的唱片版权]]></title><description><![CDATA[由收购公司凯雷集团（Carlyle Group）支持的音乐合资企业 Litmus Music 周四表示，该公司已获得创作歌手兰迪-纽曼（Randy Newman）的歌曲版权，其中包括他为迪士尼《玩具总动员》（Toy Story）电影创作的歌曲。【原文：Litmus Music, a music venture backed by buyout firm Carlyle Group , has acquired the rights to singer-songwriter Randy Newman's song catalog, which includes his work for Disney's "Toy Story" films, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/carlyle-backed-music-venture-buys-rights-randy-newmans-recorded-catalog-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7WD4TPLRFOSPMUMWPPFL6SF6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间交易台积电稳住芯片大船，欧洲央行将放宽政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76TG7AREC5NJ5HB6QV6BR2ZLN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:03:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电业绩公布后芯片股反弹，期指上涨；经济数据受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周四上涨，台积电的乐观预测提振了半导体类股，而投资者则在等待关键经济数据，以寻找有关美国消费者财务健康状况的线索。【原文：U.S. stock index futures gained on Thursday, with an upbeat forecast from TSMC lifting semiconductor stocks, while investors awaited key economic data for clues on the financial health of the U.S. consumer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-rise-chip-stocks-rally-after-tsmc-results-economic-data-focus-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPOMRXANFZMJZPZMUNWFP2JTH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:51:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》报道：耶伦警告全面关税将引发通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周四报道，美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）计划在一次演讲中警告说，共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提出的经济政策将加剧通货膨胀并损害企业利益。【原文：The economic policies being proposed by Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump would fuel inflation and harm businesses, U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen plans to warn in a speech, according to a report in the New York Times on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/yellen-warn-sweeping-tariffs-would-ignite-inflation-nyt-reports-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MA6YTWUCDZKJBKJVT66C2RPWDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:48:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登额外免除 45 亿美元学生债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）周四又为6万多名借款人免除了45亿美元的学生债务，使被免除学生贷款的公务员人数超过了100万。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden on Thursday canceled another $4.5 billion in student debt for over 60,000 borrowers, bringing the number of public service workers who have had their student loans cancelled to over 1 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/biden-cancels-additional-45-billion-student-debt-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AK27EMSKDBMH5CXLCIRZD5J2CY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环境组织呼吁 Holcim 在分拆美国公司之前减少碳足迹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环保组织加大了对水泥生产商 Holcim 的宣传力度，要求其在明年分拆北美业务之前，减少碳足迹，并致信 Holcim 董事长和北美业务的潜在投资者。【原文：U.S. environmental groups have stepped up a campaign to get cement maker Holcim to curb its carbon footprint, writing to its chairman and potential investors in its North American business before it is spun off next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/environment-groups-call-holcim-cut-carbon-footprint-ahead-us-spinoff-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4EMLAG7UFNORALXQG76X4HSUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 08:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元走强，投资者看空大多数亚洲外汇市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师转而看跌大多数亚洲货币，对印度卢比的空头押注创下一年来的新高，原因是对美联储将减少降息力度的预期使美元走强，并使风险较高的亚洲资产黯然失色。【原文：Analysts turned bearish on most Asian currencies, with short bets on the Indian rupee at a one-year high, as expectations the Federal Reserve would cut rates less aggressively strengthened the dollar and took the shine off riskier Asian assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/investors-turn-short-most-asian-fx-dollar-strength-prevails-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJ6FI3HRAFJOHAHWJ6B5ISGPZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国困境拖累保乐力加第一季度销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国烈酒制造商保乐力加（Pernod Ricard）表示，尽管部分由于中国市场疲软导致第一季度销售额降幅超过预期，但该公司仍预计 2024/25 财年销售额将恢复增长。【原文：French spirits maker Pernod Ricard said it still expected to return to sales growth in the 2024/25 fiscal year, despite reporting a bigger-than-expected fall in first quarter sales, caused partly by weakness in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/china-woes-drag-down-pernod-ricard-first-quarter-sales-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBVEFSA5AZO6TKEJPMI36BTBXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:41:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，现代汽车印度公司将以最高股价定价，以筹集 33 亿美元资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位直接了解此事的消息人士透露，现代汽车印度公司将在首次公开募股中把股价定在 1960 卢比，以筹集 33 亿美元。【原文：Hyundai Motor India is set to price its shares at 1,960 rupees to raise $3.3 billion in its initial public offering, according to two sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-india-set-price-shares-top-range-raise-33-bln-sources-say-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBNKP56ZBBP2JLIP3H7RE2WK7I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 06:38:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲亚特停滞不前，意大利都灵努力避免衰落]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利城市都灵是欧洲最古老的汽车制造厂所在地，它是欧洲大陆部分地区工业衰退的典型代表，因为这些地区的汽车制造商正在与电气化成本、低需求和来自中国的竞争作斗争。【原文：The Italian city of Turin, home to Europe's oldest car factory, typifies the industrial decay that parts of the continent face as its automakers struggle with the cost of electrification, low demand, and competition from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fiat-stalls-italys-turin-struggles-stave-off-decline-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFLSNUIXCJL3DF3RJCGDA2O5ME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 06:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第三季度利润增长 54%，好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾芯片制造商台积电周四公布的第三季度净利润增长 54%，超出市场预期，该公司继续从人工智能应用半导体需求激增中获得回报。【原文：Taiwanese chipmaker TSMC posted a 54% rise in third-quarter net profit on Thursday that beat market expectations as it continues to reap the rewards of surging demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-q3-profit-rises-54-better-than-forecasts-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDOVXHQQ2RIFDO4FL2NDROSZPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:37:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国困境拖累保乐力加第一季度销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国烈酒制造商保乐力加（Pernod Ricard）表示，尽管第一季度销售额下降了 5.9%，部分原因是中国市场疲软，但该公司仍预计 2024/25 财年销售额将恢复增长。【原文：French spirits maker Pernod Ricard said it still expected to return to sales growth in the 2024/25 fiscal year despite reporting a worse-than-expected 5.9% fall in first quarter sales, caused partly by weakness in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/china-woes-drag-down-pernod-ricards-q1-sales-2024-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZML4PGLJKJJJXEKEPV5RRA3EDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>