<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:06:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:06:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[重大 "网络事件增加 50%，英国警告企业领导者]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国国家网络安全中心（NCSC）负责人将于本周二表示，被列为 "高度重大 "的英国网络事件比一年前增加了 50%。
最近几个月发生的一系列网络攻击已导致包括玛莎百货（Marks & Spencer）、Co-op 和捷豹路虎（JLR）在内的一些英国最大的品牌断网。
"NCSC首席执行官理查德-霍恩（Richard Horne）将在伦敦举行的年度审查发布会上说："每个领导者，无论你是厨房餐桌上的一个人，还是成千上万人的老板，你都必须有一个抵御犯罪网络攻击的计划。
在截至今年 8 月的 12 个月里，英国国家计算机安全委员会（NCSC）应邀协助处理了 429 起网络事件，其中一半被认为具有 "国家意义"。
霍恩说，其中 18 起被列为 "高度重大"，因为它们 "对中央政府、英国基本服务、英国大部分人口或英国经济造成了严重影响"。
英国科学、创新与技术新闻部在一份声明中说，部长们已经致函公司，包括富时指数最大的350家公司，敦促它们了解可以获得哪些支持，并将网络恢复能力作为董事会层面的责任。
英国国家计算机安全委员会称，截至2025年8月的一年中，该委员会共处理了204起最严重的三类攻击，比前一年的89起增加了一倍多。
这让人们看到了企业，尤其是供应链中的小企业的应变能力，如果客户无法运营，这些企业可能更容易突然失去订单和付款。
据分析师估计，JLR 因停产每周损失约 5000 万英镑，在停产近六周后，上周重新开始了部分生产。
这家豪华汽车制造商隶属于印度塔塔汽车公司（Tata Motors），英国政府在 9 月底为其提供了 15 亿英镑的贷款担保，以帮助其支持供应商。
"如果你的 IT 基础设施明天就瘫痪了，你的所有屏幕都变成了空白，你还能运行你的薪资系统，让你的机器继续运转，或者给你的货架上货吗？霍恩在演讲中说。
如果答案是 "不能"，或者更可能是 "不知道"，请立即行动起来。【原文：British cyber incidents classed as "highly significant" have risen by 50% over a year ago, the head of the country's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) will say on Tuesday.
A series of cyber attacks in recent months has knocked some of Britain's biggest brands, including Marks & Spencer , Co-op and Jaguar Land Rover (JLR), offline.
"Every leader, whether you're one person at your kitchen table  or the boss of thousands of people,  you must have a plan to defend against criminal cyberattacks," NCSC CEO Richard Horne is due to say at the launch of its annual review in London.
The NCSC, part of Britain's GCHQ spy agency, was asked to help with 429 cyber incidents in the 12 months to August, half of which were considered of "national significance".
Of those, Horne said, 18 were classed as "highly significant" because they had "serious impact on central government, UK essential services, a large proportion of the UK population, or the UK economy".
Ministers have written to companies, including the largest 350 on the FTSE Index, urging them to understand what support is available and to make cyber resilience a board-level responsibility, Britain's Department for Science, Innovation & Technology Press said in a statement.
The NCSC said it had dealt with 204 attacks in the three most serious categories in the year to August 2025, more than doubling from 89 the year before.
That has cast a light on the resilience of companies and particularly the smaller businesses in their supply chains, which may be more vulnerable to suddenly losing orders, and payments, if their clients are unable to operate.
JLR, which analysts estimated was losing around 50 million pounds per week from the shutdown, last week restarted some manufacturing after an almost six-week pause.
The luxury carmaker, owned by India's Tata Motors , was given a 1.5 billion pound loan guarantee by the British government in late September to help it support suppliers.
"If your IT infrastructure was crippled tomorrow  and all your screens went blank,  could you run your payroll systems, keep your machinery working, or stock your shelves? ," Horne said in his speech.
"If the answer is no, or more likely ‘don’t know’, act now".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-warns-business-leaders-highly-significant-cyber-incidents-rise-50-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEQ2TSTKHRPJTDK3G23PN4IRSQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西戈尔公司（Gol）计划提出重组方案，将其私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一公布的 11 月 4 日股东大会投票公告，巴西航空公司 Gol Linhas Aereas Inteligentes SA 计划私有化，作为公司重组进程的一部分。【原文：Brazilian airline Gol Linhas Aereas Inteligentes SA plans to go private as part of a corporate reorganization process, according to the voting bulletin for a November 4 shareholder meeting published on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-gol-plans-restructuring-proposal-that-would-take-it-private-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32SFAQA3IRLDZLKZ242HLE7KLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受人工智能芯片需求拉动，三星预计季度利润为三年多来最高]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子（Samsung Electronics）周二预计，由于传统存储芯片的需求帮助抵消了高带宽存储芯片销售的疲软，第三季度营业利润同比增长 32%，远高于分析师的预期。【原文：Samsung Electronics on Tuesday projected a 32% rise in third-quarter operating profit from a year earlier, well ahead of analysts' estimates, as demand for conventional memory chips helped offset weaker high bandwidth memory chip sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-elec-estimates-32-rise-q3-operating-profit-beating-expectations-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQFO5RZWGRPRRIXU3WRDDEU2WQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DHT 称其船队在中国收取新港口费后与美国没有联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[油轮运营商 DHT Holdings 周一表示，其船队不属于中国针对与美国有关联的船舶新征收的特别港口费的范围。【原文：Oil tanker operator DHT Holdings said on Monday that its fleet does not fall under the scope of China's new special port fees targeting U.S.-linked vessels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dht-says-its-fleet-has-no-us-links-after-chinas-new-port-fee-move-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVQJSNSUZ5PSHGCVA7HKVRUFJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓第三季度铁矿石发货量环比增长 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓（Rio Tinto）周二报告称，尽管计划中的大型维护活动和基础设施工程将在第四季度继续进行，但第三季度铁矿石发货量仍连续增长了 6%。【原文：Rio Tinto , reported a 6% sequential rise in third-quarter iron ore shipments on Tuesday, despite planned major maintenance activities and infrastructure works which will continue in the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rio-tintos-third-quarter-iron-ore-shipments-rise-6-sequentially-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAQPA5JS3NNXZKQE2BK3M4BU3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：鲍威尔访华，银行将开启盈利闸门]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSWBCTXSS5LDJOI3AZ5UUAQ2JM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能驱动升级，第三季度全球智能手机出货量上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际数据公司（International Data Corporation）周一发布的初步数据显示，受消费者对高端和人工智能设备强劲需求的推动，今年第三季度全球智能手机出货量增长了2.6%。【原文：Global smartphone shipments grew 2.6% in the third quarter this year, fueled by strong consumer demand for premium and AI-enabled devices, according to preliminary data from the International Data Corporation on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-smartphone-shipments-rise-third-quarter-ai-driven-upgrades-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAYGYEW4TFLOXCPKPYGZWN7BK4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛收购风险投资公司 Industry Ventures]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）周一表示，已同意收购管理着 70 亿美元资产的领先风险投资公司 Industry Ventures，以扩大对科技企业家的服务。【原文：Goldman Sachs has agreed to buy Industry Ventures, a leading venture capital firm that manages $7 billion of assets, in a bid to expand its services to technology entrepreneurs, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/goldman-sachs-buys-venture-capital-firm-industry-ventures-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7AGRQANMFLK5GRXFL44PVLKEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在创纪录的加密货币暴跌之后，人们急于对冲再次暴跌的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[继上周五发生史上最大规模的加密货币清算之后，期权市场投资者正在为比特币和以太坊的更大波动性和进一步下跌做好准备，积极进行交易定位，以防再次出现潜在的自由落体。【原文：Following the largest crypto liquidation in history last Friday, options market investors are bracing for more volatility and further declines in bitcoin and ether, aggressively positioning in trades that offer protection against another potential freefall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/after-record-crypto-crash-rush-hedge-against-another-freefall-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OR2SMEB6TVIXPCABGHX7SWQK2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对供应过剩的担忧加剧，美国石油期货后市跌幅收窄至 20 个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于欧佩克+增加供应，而美国炼油厂的季节性检修又对速冻原油桶的需求构成压力，美国前月原油期货周一以 2024 年 1 月以来对第七个月合约的最小溢价收盘。【原文：Front-month U.S. crude oil futures ended Monday's trading at their smallest premium since January 2024 over the seventh-month contract, as OPEC+ ramps up supply while seasonal refinery maintenance in the U.S. pressures demand for prompt barrels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-futures-backwardation-narrows-20-month-low-mounting-fears-glut-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CBWN7B3ABI2HP3E2A5FX6G2WE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织的格奥尔基耶娃说，各国缺乏人工智能的监管和道德基础]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周一表示，世界各国缺乏应对人工智能快速发展的监管和道德基础，她敦促民间社会团体 "敲响警钟"。【原文：Countries around the world lack the regulatory and ethical foundation to deal with the rapid advent of artificial intelligence, IMF chief Kristalina Georgieva said on Monday, urging civil society groups to "ring the alarm bells."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imfs-georgieva-says-countries-lack-regulatory-ethical-foundation-ai-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YF5YAQAVJRJPHHRIFMCHZAGBYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局喷气推进装置将裁员约 550 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局喷气推进实验室（NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory）周一表示，作为重组的一部分，该实验室将裁员近 550 人，这与美国政府目前的停摆无关。【原文：NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory said on Monday it will cut nearly 550 jobs as part of a restructuring, not related to the current U.S. government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/nasas-jet-propulsion-unit-lay-off-about-550-workers-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VOAMMJTMSRNXPPTBFRRRDYJ72A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[庞巴迪宣布 Comlux Aviation 成为环球 8000 商务喷气机的新客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大飞机制造商庞巴迪公司周一在美国国家公务航空协会年会上宣布，该公司的积压订单中又增加了一份来自Comlux Aviation公司的Global 8000公务机订单。【原文：Bombardier added a new order from Comlux Aviation for its Global 8000 business jet to its backlog, the Canadian planemaker announced on Monday during the National Business Aviation Association's annual conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/bombardier-announces-comlux-aviation-new-global-8000-business-jet-customer-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2LHD3RQFFPRDNU5X2UJIQO67I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪将克莱斯勒公司的信用评级展望定为负面]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评级机构穆迪评级公司（Moody's Ratings）周一将欧洲汽车制造商 Stellantis 的评级展望改为负面，但维持其目前的评级。【原文：Credit rating agency Moody's Ratings changed European automaker Stellantis' ratings outlook to negative on Monday, though maintained its current ratings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/moodys-puts-chrysler-owners-credit-ratings-negative-outlook-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZ5RSIZFVVOKJNSAZX42GP4RUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国贸易机构称关税不确定性可能抑制对小企业的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国贸易和发展会议秘书长周一告诉路透社记者，由于关税的不确定性，中小企业和发展中经济体可能面临投资放缓的特别风险。【原文：Small and medium-sized businesses and developing economies are likely to be at particular risk of a slowdown in investment due to ongoing tariff uncertainty, the Secretary-General of the UN Trade and Development Agency told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tariff-uncertainty-could-curb-investment-small-businesses-un-trade-agency-says-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4MGSOOY5NPY5NXPX4PLVGUPVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储保尔森称美联储将对通胀爆发做出反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联邦储备银行行长安娜-保尔森（Anna Paulson）周一表示，如果通胀压力没有如她所预期的那样缓和，央行应该愿意采取行动。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia President Anna Paulson said on Monday that if inflation pressures do not moderate as she expects the central bank should be willing to take action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-paulson-says-fed-would-react-burst-inflation-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAWWV5EOG5MRBC6AXDOVJL447E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood高管表示对交易持开放态度，以发展预测市场业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易平台 Robinhood Markets 的一位高管周一在接受路透社采访时表示，随着全球范围内对曾经的小众资产类别的兴趣激增，Robinhood Markets 对快速增长的预测市场领域的潜在收购持开放态度。【原文：Trading platform Robinhood Markets is open to potential acquisitions in the fast-growing prediction markets space, a top executive told Reuters in an interview on Monday, as interest in the once-niche asset class surges globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/robinhood-open-deals-grow-prediction-markets-business-exec-says-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IURIOX2URKINKTG6VJEBL7JRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:39:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Semafor 报道，约会应用 Grindr 正在探索私有化交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Semafor 周一援引知情人士的话报道，约会应用 Grindr 的内部人士正在讨论将其私有化，因为股价暴跌使该公司的主要所有者陷入了个人财务拮据的境地。【原文：Insiders at dating app Grindr are discussing taking it private after a share slump put its top owners in a tight personal financial position, Semafor reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dating-app-grindr-explores-go-private-deal-semafor-reports-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTGCFV2OJVIH5BA5HIJBTO2IAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席保尔森认为未来将有更多降息措施来刺激就业市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[安娜-保尔森（Anna Paulson）周一在作为费城联储负责人的首次演讲中表示，由于贸易关税不太可能像预期的那样推高通胀，就业市场面临的风险不断上升，因此美国央行有理由进行更多的降息。【原文：In her first speech as head of the Philadelphia Federal Reserve, Anna Paulson said on Monday that rising risks to the job market argue for more interest rate cuts by the U.S. central bank, as trade tariffs are unlikely to push up inflation as much as expected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-paulson-sees-more-rate-cuts-ahead-bolster-job-market-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33N6OQOUZFJKBLNRJDII2P5VVU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[米其林下调年度展望，原因是北美地区轮胎需求不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国轮胎制造商米其林周一下调了全年业绩展望，原因是北美市场的经营状况比预期的要差，削弱了销售量和利润率。【原文：French tire maker Michelin on Monday cut its full-year outlook citing worse-than-expected business conditions in the North American market that have eroded sales volumes and margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frances-michelin-cuts-annual-outlook-worse-than-expected-business-deterioration-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4TCP3YO5BJIRDGZVA3W2WSRKI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:14:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国表示对现代汽车美国投资计划表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国工业部长周一表示，在首尔与华盛顿进行微妙贸易谈判的同时，韩国政府对现代汽车宣布数十亿美元的美国投资计划表示担忧。【原文：South Korea's industry minister said on Monday that the government had expressed concerns over Hyundai announcing multi-billion dollar U.S. investment plans at the same time as Seoul was involved in delicate trade negotiations with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-korea-says-it-flagged-hyundai-us-investment-plan-concerns-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3EP2ZHD3JOOLPSOCWMMDLMQOY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Embargo 1100 EDT Power Integrations 与 Nvidia 携手推动电源发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[提供电源处理芯片的利基芯片制造商 Power Integrations 周一表示，它正与 Nvidia 合作，推动这家人工智能巨头让数据中心在更高电压下运行。【原文：Power Integrations, a niche chipmaker that provides chips for handling power, on Monday said it is working with Nvidia on the artificial intelligence giant's push to make data centers operate at higher voltages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/embargo-1100-edt-power-integrations-joins-work-with-nvidia-power-supply-push-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z7SFPIPSYJP7DP7GO5ASQCQJZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 15:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电信运营商批准 eSIM 服务后，iPhone Air 将在中国开始预购]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周一表示，随着中国主要电信运营商获得 eSIM 服务的监管批准，苹果的 iPhone Air 将于本周晚些时候在中国开始预购。【原文：Apple's iPhone Air would be available for pre-order in China later this week, as major Chinese telecom operators obtained regulatory approvals for eSIM services, the company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/iphone-air-begin-pre-order-china-after-telecom-operators-approved-esim-services-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5VLLA3ON5NRFL7N3OS3LV6IEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊连续第三年在假日季招聘 25 万名员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊表示，计划在假期期间为其在美国的履约和运输网络招聘 25 万名员工，这一数字与过去两年持平，因为这家电子商务巨头正在为订单激增做准备。【原文：Amazon said it plans to hire 250,000 workers for the holiday season across its fulfillment and transportation networks in the U.S., the same number as the last two years, as the e-commerce behemoth prepares for a surge in orders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/amazon-hire-250000-workers-during-holiday-season-third-straight-year-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AINZIOJKSNJ4RHU7RJZTDTJ43Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:24:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司在供应方面取得进展，Spirit 公司的交易将在第四季度完成]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司的一位高级官员周一表示，供应商的信心和表现都有明显改善，所有供应商都准备好支持该公司今年将交付量增加 7% 至约 820 架喷气机的目标。【原文：Airbus has seen a marked improvement in confidence and performance from its suppliers, all of whom are ready to support the company's target of increasing deliveries by 7% to some 820 jets this year, a senior company official said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-sees-supply-progress-spirit-deal-close-q4-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WM4MBUAZZP6DAR6UQTBTLYRKU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:10:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼亚议会通过加密资产法促进投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯尼亚一位资深议员周一表示，肯尼亚立法者已经通过了一项监管加密货币等数字资产的法案，旨在通过为这一新兴行业制定明确的规则来促进对该行业的投资。【原文：Kenyan lawmakers have passed a bill to regulate digital assets like cryptocurrencies, a senior parliamentarian said on Monday, as it seeks to boost investments into the sector by putting clear rules in place for the emerging industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/kenya-parliament-passes-crypto-asset-law-boost-investments-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHVLE76XE5PZ3FSD7AHSP5OPPI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[a16z 支持的数据公司 Fivetran 和 dbt Labs 将通过全股票交易合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据创业公司 Fivetran 和 dbt Labs 告诉路透社，两家公司将以全股票交易的方式合并，合并后将成为一家年收入近 6 亿美元的数据基础设施公司。【原文：Data startups Fivetran and dbt Labs will merge in an all-stock deal, creating a combined data infrastructure company with nearly $600 million in annual revenue, the two companies told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/a16z-backed-data-firms-fivetran-dbt-labs-merge-all-stock-deal-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJR3LEHFNBJTXKE5TIAFDCCI6Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LMEWEEK Codelco 提高了对埃尔特尼恩特损失的估计，铜产量目标不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[Codelco 因其 El Teniente 矿事故造成的铜矿损失可能比之前估计的高出 45%，但董事长 Maximo Pacheco 仍预计这家全球最大的铜矿商今年的产量将略有增加。【原文：Codelco's copper losses from the accident at its El Teniente mine are likely to be 45% higher than previously estimated, but Chairman Maximo Pacheco still expects the world's largest copper miner to slightly increase output this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/lmeweek-codelco-lifts-el-teniente-loss-estimate-copper-output-target-intact-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJ3SJPAVVBLZTOIVWTZSESQ7K4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salesforce 将在五年内在旧金山投资 150 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[云软件供应商 Salesforce 周一表示，未来五年将在旧金山投资 150 亿美元，以支持该市的人工智能创新和劳动力发展。【原文：Cloud software provider Salesforce said on Monday it would invest $15 billion in San Francisco over the next five years to support artificial intelligence innovation and workforce development in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/salesforce-invest-15-billion-san-francisco-over-five-years-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWCOTLKVYZI3TNQAD3Y5KCHLJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在最新的芯片交易中，OpenAI 借助博通打造其首款人工智能处理器]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 已与博通公司（Broadcom）合作生产其首款内部人工智能处理器，这是该 ChatGPT 制造商的最新芯片合作，因为它正在努力确保所需的计算能力，以满足对其服务的激增需求。【原文：OpenAI has partnered with Broadcom to produce its first in-house artificial intelligence processors, the latest chip tie-up for the ChatGPT maker as it races to secure the computing power needed to meet surging demand for its services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-taps-broadcom-build-its-first-ai-processor-latest-chip-deal-2025-10-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23I2KKDINBNNHLNIKWWGBOSF7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>