<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:09:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:09:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月财政赤字创纪录达1450亿美元，支出超过收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周二表示，12月联邦政府预算赤字达1450亿美元，较上年同期增长67%或580亿美元，主要原因是福利支付和收入因日历变动而膨胀，导致支出创下历史新高。【原文：The U.S. government posted a $145 billion budget deficit for December, up 67% or $58 billion from ​a year earlier due to record outlays that ‌were inflated by calendar shifts in benefit payments and receipts, the Treasury Department said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-posts-record-145-billion-december-deficit-outlays-outpace-receipts-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QCCSSUKXBLLLJPC5Q265WJVOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠廷炼油厂工人开始与英国石油公司进行合同谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁工人联合会周二表示，英国石油公司位于印第安纳州怀廷的炼油厂工人正与这家英国石油巨头进行合同谈判。该公司提议对日处理量44万桶的炼油厂进行改组，包括裁员。【原文：Workers at BP's refinery in Whiting, Indiana are in contract negotiations with the British oil major, which has proposed changes including job cuts at the 440,000-barrel-per-day facility, the United Steelworkers union said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/whiting-refinery-workers-begin-contract-negotiations-with-bp-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKYHQ47JFBIRLFDKIMUYBZF2WA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德警示国际市场短期面临逆风]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德首席执行官迈克·杜斯特达尔周二表示，随着公司在多个国家失去市场独占权，竞争日益激烈，这家制药商预计2026年其国际业务将面临逆风。【原文：Novo Nordisk CEO Mike Doustdar said on Tuesday the drugmaker expects headwinds in its international operations in 2026, as competition intensifies after losing market exclusivity in several countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-flags-near-term-headwinds-international-markets-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWEPLVTOA5NX3HWOHFB6RCRGKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:54:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球音乐任命汉娜·波弗尔担任首席数据官]]></title><description><![CDATA[环球音乐集团周二任命汉娜·波弗尔为首席数据官，负责运用数据和人工智能技术统筹全球受众拓展与互动策略。【原文：Universal Music Group on Tuesday named Hannah Poferl as chief data officer to oversee its global audience development and engagement strategy using data and artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/universal-music-taps-hannah-poferl-top-data-role-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDNIZLOHEZM55HWTF6TOGVPJHI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:35:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[知情人士称，力拓聘请三家银行就潜在收购嘉能可事宜提供咨询]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，力拓集团已聘请摩根大通及其他两家顾问机构，就其潜在收购嘉能可一事提供咨询。该交易可能缔造市值逾2000亿美元的全球最大矿业巨头。【原文：Rio Tinto , has engaged JPMorgan and two other advisers on its potential acquisition of Glencore , a deal that could create the world's largest miner worth over $200 billion, a source with knowledge of the situation told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rio-tinto-engages-three-banks-advise-potential-glencore-acquisition-source-says-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBKGGHGZERIJ3KMN24OT6TMVEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部分美联储官员确信，尽管特朗普发起攻击，下一任美联储主席仍将恪守使命]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管特朗普总统已就即将任命的美联储主席人选明确表态，但部分现任央行官员仍坚信，无论谁最终获任，都将恪守美联储的使命——部分原因在于，当新任领导者真正意识到这份职责的分量时，自然会回归正轨。【原文：Even as President Donald Trump has laid out clear markers as to what he expects for his upcoming selection as Federal Reserve chair, some current central bankers remain ​confident that whoever gets the job will stick to the Fed’s mission in part as the weight of responsibility becomes clear to the new leader.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/some-fed-officials-confident-next-fed-chair-will-uphold-mission-despite-trump-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCZIAS7CMRP3VD4REAUKO5AIYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛默飞世尔科技公司赢得新合同，因制药企业将生产转移至美国，首席执行官表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[赛默飞世尔科技公司首席执行官马克·卡斯珀周二表示，该医疗设备制造商的制药服务业务已赢得多项合同，将协助客户将生产从欧洲或亚洲转移至美国。【原文：Thermo Fisher Scientific's pharmaceutical services business has won a number of contracts to help its customers move production from Europe or Asia to the U.S., the medical equipment maker's CEO, Marc Casper, said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/thermo-fisher-wins-contracts-pharma-shifts-production-us-ceo-says-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35IHXTOO2BK3VNBMSJM2LIJVNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韦恩斯坦旗下的萨巴资本在交易困境中推动Workspace逐步退出市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[博阿兹·温斯坦旗下的萨巴资本持有伦敦灵活办公空间供应商Workspace约13.5%的股份，该公司周二致函敦促Workspace推进有序清盘。【原文：Boaz Weinstein's Saba Capital, which holds about a 13.5% stake in London-focused flexible office-space provider Workspace , sent a letter on Tuesday urging the company to pursue a managed wind-down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/weinsteins-saba-capital-pushes-workspace-wind-down-amid-trading-struggles-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NMLL5ZXBRNZ3HEFC4QOQRNO7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：加拿大石油大亨提议协助美国重振委内瑞拉石油产业]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位执掌北美发展最快的石油公司之一的加拿大商界巨头，正呼吁加拿大向美国提供重油技术支持，以协助美国重建委内瑞拉的石油产业。【原文：A Canadian tycoon who heads one of North America's fastest-growing oil companies is advocating for his country to lend its heavy oil expertise to the United States as it seeks to rebuild Venezuela's oil industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/canadian-oil-tycoon-proposes-aiding-us-venezuelas-oil-revival-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7AMLLPHTD5O5BHUFCRVXVUSI3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:25:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WTI原油相对于布伦特原油的价差扩大至八个月高位，因预计更多委内瑞拉原油将流入美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[自1月3日美国推翻委内瑞拉总统尼古拉斯·马杜罗并接管该国石油运输以来，美国原油期货相对于全球基准布伦特原油的折扣价已扩大约每桶1美元。交易员和分析师表示，此举将数百万桶原油转运至美国港口，预计未来数月将推升美国原油出口量。【原文：The discount on U.S. crude futures to the global benchmark Brent has grown by around $1 per ​barrel since the U.S. ousted Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro on January 3 and took control of the South American country's ‌oil flows, redirecting millions of those barrels to U.S. ports in a move likely to boost U.S. crude exports in the coming months, traders and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/wti-oil-discount-brent-largest-eight-months-more-venezuelan-crude-expected-us-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LETQMQSIAJINPDWKS3PWRP427U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独立性如何成为全球中央银行的标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府决定对美联储主席展开刑事调查，加剧了人们对美国央行独立性的担忧。作为全球最大经济体的最高决策机构，美联储的独立性备受关注。【原文：The Trump administration's decision to open a criminal investigation into the head of the Federal Reserve has intensified fears about the independence of the U.S. central bank, the top policymaking body for the world's biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-independence-came-be-standard-global-central-banks-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USZM75PHMFMPTG7RPIKYXKKUEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将英伟达芯片采购限制在特殊情况下，据《信息报》报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《信息报》周二援引两位知情人士的消息称，中国政府本周告知部分科技公司，仅在特殊情况下（如大学研究用途）才会批准其采购英伟达H200人工智能芯片。【原文：The Chinese government this week told some tech companies it would only approve their purchases of Nvidia's H200 AI chips under special circumstances, such as for university research, the Information reported on Tuesday, citing two people with direct knowledge of the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-limits-nvidia-chip-purchases-special-circumstances-information-reports-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWFLJSKYCRKQRPAQKPG5ZMY4VI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国寻求在人工智能与创作者的版权之争中实现"重置"]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国科技大臣利兹·肯德尔周二表示，政府正寻求对版权规则改革计划进行"重置"，以适应人工智能的发展，承诺在保护创作者权益的同时释放人工智能的经济潜力。【原文：British technology minister Liz Kendall said on Tuesday the government was seeking a "reset" on plans to overhaul copyright rules to accommodate artificial intelligence, pledging to protect creators while unlocking AI's economic potential.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/britain-seeks-reset-copyright-battle-between-ai-creators-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G73PP3WHLRN4LP4EOYN6BA37TE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯利康收购Modella AI以加速肿瘤药物研发]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康周二宣布已同意收购波士顿人工智能公司Modella AI。随着制药行业加速运用人工智能技术推进新药研发进程，此类收购正日益频繁。【原文：AstraZeneca has agreed to buy Boston-based Modella AI, the companies said on Tuesday, as the drug industry increases its use of artificial intelligence to accelerate the discovery of new drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/astrazeneca-acquire-modella-ai-speed-oncology-drug-research-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BB6K36JV3BJFZNIRSOX6WWOFVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国监管机构称，随着欧盟许可证申请截止日期临近，部分加密货币公司未予回应]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国金融市场管理局周二警告称，该国近三分之一未持有欧盟牌照的加密货币公司尚未告知监管机构，它们是打算在7月前获取欧盟新规要求的牌照，还是将停止运营。【原文：Nearly a third of crypto companies without an EU licence in France are still to tell the regulator whether they intend to get the licence required under new EU rules or will cease operating by July, the country's markets regulator warned on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/french-regulator-says-some-crypto-firms-unresponsive-eu-licence-deadline-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZPOQVLDKJNG3HYIHTETEL7AOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西捷航空在乘客强烈反对下加快审查不可调节座椅]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一份员工通知显示，西捷航空正加速推进对非可调节经济舱座椅的审查，最早将于本周完成。此前该航空公司因乘客抱怨腿部空间不足引发强烈抗议，此事已广受关注。【原文：WestJet Airlines is speeding up a review of its non-adjustable economy seats to as early as this week, following a highly publicized backlash by passengers lamenting a lack of leg space, according to a message to staff seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/westjet-speeds-review-non-reclinable-seats-amid-passenger-backlash-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJ5YB35Y5ZMJFKDROVZDHCS4PM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院议长约翰逊表示，国会应研究对信用卡利率设限问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院议长迈克·约翰逊周二表示，国会应探讨特朗普总统提出的对信用卡利率设限的建议，但同时警告此举可能产生"负面次生效应"。【原文：U.S. House Speaker Mike Johnson on Tuesday said Congress should explore President Donald Trump's idea of imposing a cap on credit card interest rates but warned of the possibility of "negative secondary effects."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-speaker-johnson-says-credit-card-rate-cap-should-be-looked-into-by-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWYNF57K7NNQ3GC2POLC7REDX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:04:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司扭亏为盈势头稳固，实现2018年以来最高年度喷气式飞机交付量]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司在2025年强势反弹，交付量创2018年以来新高，净订单量七年来首次超越欧洲竞争对手空客，标志着这家美国飞机制造商在经历一系列危机后实现转机。【原文：Boeing bounced back in 2025 to deliver the most planes since 2018 and to beat European rival Airbus in net orders for the first time in seven years in a sign of a turnaround at the U.S. planemaker after a series of crises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-turnaround-takes-hold-with-highest-annual-jet-deliveries-since-2018-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U23GMZCLFLNDISBASQ2HBSQY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道，Meta正考虑在年底前将雷朋眼镜产量翻倍。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周二报道，Meta与依视路陆逊梯卡正考虑将人工智能智能眼镜的年产能翻倍至2000万副，目标在年底前实现。【原文：Meta and EssilorLuxottica are considering doubling the production capacity of their artificial intelligence-powered smart glasses to 20 million units annually by the end of this year, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-mulls-doubling-output-ray-ban-glasses-by-year-end-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PTN7WQVXNOVPAE4T6FMV647FA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆萨莱姆称鲍威尔视频“非常清晰且直截了当”——MNI网络直播]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托·穆萨莱姆周二表示，美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔将特朗普政府对其展开刑事调查称为利率争端的"借口"，这一表态"非常明确且直截了当"。但他补充称，对于"法律问题"将不再置评。【原文：Fed chair Jerome Powell's statement calling a Trump administration criminal investigation of him a "pretext" for a dispute over interest rates was "very clear and very direct," St. Louis Fed president Alberto Musalem said on Tuesday, but added he would not comment further on a "legal matter."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-musalem-wont-bet-productivity-yet-ensure-inflation-control-mni-webcast-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KD2I3WSOZ5LCLATYEEUIUOMZZA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国10月新屋销售量小幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国10月新单户住宅销售量在连续两个月增长后小幅回落，但库存仍处于高位且房价持续走低，这可能为今年新房市场提供支撑。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell slightly in October after increasing for two straight months, though declining prices amid still-elevated inventory could support the new housing ​market this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-marginally-october-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGQGRV3ESBPOVOQ4XHPVIYQPDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国防科技公司Onebrief在最新融资轮中估值突破20亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[专注于军事领域的平台Onebrief周二宣布，已完成2亿美元融资，公司估值达到21.5亿美元，较六个月前翻了一番。【原文：Military-focused platform Onebrief said on Tuesday it has raised $200 million in a funding round that gave the company a post-money valuation of $2.15 billion, doubling it over six months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/defense-tech-firm-onebrief-valued-over-2-billion-latest-funding-round-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPGTZYQV4ZJWRLIGSVDV3V3OHA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ro与安进合作研究肥胖症治疗障碍及GLP-1药物获取问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国远程医疗公司Ro周二宣布，已与制药商安进达成研究合作，旨在探讨患者和医疗服务提供者在获取肥胖症治疗（包括GLP-1疗法）过程中面临的挑战。【原文：U.S. telehealth firm Ro said on Tuesday it has entered a research collaboration with drugmaker Amgen to examine challenges patients and providers face in accessing obesity treatments, including GLP-1 therapies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ro-partners-with-amgen-study-barriers-obesity-care-glp-1-access-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DT25PEHQ5IADJEZ5S32N7NAU4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:22:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街预计，在强劲的美国经济推动下，第四季度企业盈利将表现强劲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球券商预计，随着美国经济持续展现韧性，各行业利润增长范围不断扩大，美国企业将在第四季度交出亮眼的财报成绩单。【原文：Global brokerages expect Corporate America to deliver a strong fourth-quarter earnings season, driven by a broadening of profit growth across industries as the U.S. economy remains resilient.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-expects-strong-fourth-quarter-earnings-driven-by-robust-us-economy-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KODDO6VSNBI6NGATBIBLUEQFK4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:56:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称通胀数据表明美联储应降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普对周二公布的通胀数据表示欢迎，他援引美国消费者价格指数数据，再次敦促美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔"大幅"降息。【原文：President Donald Trump welcomed inflation figures released on Tuesday, using the U.S. consumer price data to reiterate his push for Federal Reserve chair Jerome Powell to cut interest rates "meaningfully."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-inflation-data-means-fed-should-cut-interest-rates-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GEBSXD7OLJJSDGORH37MGHGK3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道琼斯指数暴跌，全球数千用户无法访问，Downdetector数据显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Downdetector.com网站显示，社交媒体平台X于周二在全球范围内出现故障，数千名用户无法访问。【原文：Social media platform X was down for thousands of users globally on Tuesday, according to Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/x-down-thousands-users-downdetector-shows-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5M7KVSFNJM4JLQI3ZFJY6QYLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行预测2026年全球经济将保持韧性增长，尽管关税存在但增长动力正在减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行周二表示，全球经济展现出超出预期的韧性，2026年GDP增速预计将略高于去年六月的预测值。但该机构同时警告称，经济增长过于集中于发达国家，且整体增长力度不足以消除极端贫困。【原文：The global economy is proving more resilient than expected, with 2026 GDP growth expected ‌to improve slightly over forecasts from last June, the World Bank said on Tuesday while warning that growth is too concentrated in advanced countries and overall too weak to reduce extreme poverty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/world-bank-sees-resilient-global-growth-2026-despite-tariffs-fading-dynamism-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FVRNVJ5MS5MZVNWTUFUS3GSEZA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果推出创作者工作室助力服务业务，新增人工智能功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周二推出Apple Creator Studio专业创意软件订阅套件，月费12.99美元或年费129美元。这家iPhone制造商正加速向创作者、学生及专业人士提供付费服务。【原文：Apple on Tuesday unveiled Apple Creator Studio, a new subscription bundle of professional creative software priced at $12.99 a month or $129 a year, as the iPhone maker steps up its push into paid services for creators, students and professionals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-rolls-out-creator-studio-boost-services-push-adds-ai-features-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6WC6GZB7RI5PF2I23GEVD3ONA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软推出数据中心计划以控制电力成本和用水量]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周二推出一项以社区为中心的计划，旨在降低其美国数据中心的用水量，并确保这些耗电大户不会推高公众的电价。【原文：Microsoft on Tuesday unveiled a community-focused initiative aimed at lowering water usage at its U.S. data centers and ensuring that the power-hungry facilities do not drive up electricity prices for the public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-launches-data-center-initiative-limit-power-costs-water-use-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXNOFOO7EBPKRCXFU23YK62QB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:19:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，与伊朗的贸易使巴西成为更多美国关税的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西政府数据显示，去年巴西对伊朗实现29亿美元贸易顺差，这使得这个南美国家成为美国新关税的潜在目标。【原文：Brazil ran a $2.9 billion trade surplus with Iran last year, government data shows, making the South American nation a potential candidate for new U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trade-with-iran-makes-brazil-target-more-us-tariffs-data-shows-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAAN5FOS2NPCDPW2N5GSBKPPEQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:15:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>