<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:08:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:08:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[加州总检察长就深度伪造图像问题向xAI公司发出停止令]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州总检察长罗伯·邦塔周五向埃隆·马斯克的xAI公司发出停止令，要求其立即停止生成和传播未经同意的性影像。【原文：California's attorney general, Rob Bonta, on Friday sent a cease and desist letter to Elon Musk's xAI, demanding that it stop the generation and distribution of non-consensual sexual images.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/california-ag-sends-cease-desist-letter-xai-deepfake-images-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYHXFSNQZNOHPLDWO46MY6KPDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:37:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌请求美国法官推迟强制其共享数据的命令，以便进行上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[据法庭文件显示，谷歌母公司Alphabet周五请求法官推迟要求该公司向竞争对手共享数据的裁决，同时该公司正就一项认定其在在线搜索领域非法垄断的裁决提出上诉。【原文：Alphabet's Google asked a judge on Friday to postpone making the company share data with rivals while it challenges a ruling that the company holds an illegal monopoly in online search, according to court papers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-asks-us-judge-defer-order-forcing-it-share-data-while-it-appeals-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCI6KFEGGZPJBD3EOQYIFSLME4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州总检察长致函要求xAI停止生产深度伪造内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州总检察长罗伯特·邦塔周五向xAI公司发出停止令，要求该公司立即停止其Grok人工智能聊天机器人生成并传播未经同意的性化图像的行为。【原文：California Attorney General Robert Bonta on Friday sent a cease and desist letter to xAI demanding the company stop the creation and distribution of AI-generated non-consensual sexualized imagery by its Grok AI chatbot.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/california-ag-sends-letter-demanding-xai-stop-producing-deekfake-content-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBZFG6QFEVOURFR7QKH652BFZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:07:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020年美联储面临疫情冲击时，部门分歧与决策独立性成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在新冠疫情暴发之初，美国联邦储备委员会大幅降息并实施大规模债券购买计划，向金融市场注入流动性，试图抵消这场公共卫生危机对经济造成的实际和潜在破坏。【原文：At the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, the U.S. Federal Reserve slashed interest rates and used massive bond purchases to flood financial markets with liquidity to try to offset the actual and potential economic devastation from the health emergency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-2020-division-independence-were-concerns-face-pandemic-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4WZ6EURWJPY5NJYXPP5KXJSJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会将审查科技巨头的人才收购交易，彭博社报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周五援引美国联邦贸易委员会主席安德鲁·弗格森的话报道称，该机构正密切关注大型科技公司通过招聘初创企业员工而非直接收购公司来获取人才的行为。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is scrutinizing big tech firms that hire employees of a startup instead of buying the companies outright, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing the agency's Chairman Andrew Ferguson.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-ftc-scrutinize-big-techs-talent-acquisition-deals-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3UX37DJFBIRHGPUESX7U2PV3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:52:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰斐逊称当前政策立场"定位良好"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储副主席菲利普·杰斐逊周五似乎暗示，他支持在1月27日至28日的央行会议上维持短期借贷成本不变。他表示，鉴于美联储降息已使货币政策处于中性区间，他对未来一年的经济、劳动力市场和通胀持"谨慎乐观"态度。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson on Friday appeared to signal his support for leaving short-term borrowing costs unchanged at the central bank's January 27-28 ​meeting, saying he is "cautiously optimistic" about the economy, the labor market and inflation ‌in the coming year now that the Fed's rate cuts have put monetary policy in the range of neutral.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-jefferson-says-current-policy-stance-well-positioned-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLAA5U2IJRLOPK4LU2EYZGIYWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称巴西对Banco Master的调查可能长达六个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西联邦检察官预计将耗时四至六个月分析近期针对破产贷款机构Banco Master展开的调查行动所收集的证据，检察总长办公室一位知情人士周五透露。【原文：Brazil's federal prosecutors will likely take four to six months analyzing evidence gathered in the latest operation probing liquidated ​lender Banco Master, a person in the prosecutor general's office ‌with knowledge of the case said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/banco-master-probe-brazil-may-take-up-six-months-source-says-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHCPQCCC3VKF7EUL7UGHWTV4HE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:10:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫寻求为美国最大电网举行紧急电力拍卖]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周五敦促美国最大的电网系统启动紧急电力拍卖，以防范大面积轮流停电。由于数据中心对能源的需求增长速度超过了美国新建发电厂的能力，当前电力供应面临严峻挑战。【原文：The White House on Friday urged the largest U.S. electric grid to conduct an emergency power auction to protect against rolling blackouts as energy demand from data centers grows faster than the country can build new generation plants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/white-house-seeks-emergency-power-auction-largest-us-electric-grid-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KQEUTDTMZNKZPENXXDJ3SKOCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，委内瑞拉银行将获得3亿美元石油资金用于外汇市场交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，委内瑞拉政府通知该国四家银行，将分配存放在卡塔尔账户中的3亿美元石油收入，使这些银行能够向需要外汇支付材料费的委内瑞拉公司出售美元。两名金融消息人士和一名分析师透露了这一消息。【原文：Four Venezuelan banks were notified this week by the ​country's government that they will split $300 million of oil revenues deposited in an account in ‌Qatar, enabling them to sell dollars to Venezuelan companies that need foreign exchange to pay for materials, two financial sources and an analyst said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuelan-banks-will-get-300-million-oil-money-sell-exchange-market-sources-say-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJ7T6XNHYBJLVJYTVGRXUCN4XE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称壳牌、三菱正探讨出售其在LNG Canada股权的方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，石油巨头壳牌和日本综合企业三菱商事正就其在价值400亿加元（288亿美元）的加拿大液化天然气项目中的持股进行出售方案的探讨。【原文：Oil major Shell and Japanese conglomerate Mitsubishi Corp are exploring sale options for their respective stakes in the C$40 billion ($28.8 billion) LNG Canada project, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-mitsubishi-exploring-sale-options-their-stakes-lng-canada-sources-say-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPSFCPPZE5LHTHIIX7RQZQGFKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:30:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克与瑞安航空CEO就飞机上星链Wi-Fi费用问题发生争执]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克周五称瑞安航空首席执行官迈克尔·奥利里是"彻头彻尾的蠢货"，理应被解雇。此前这位航空公司老板拒绝在瑞安航空飞机上安装马斯克的星链互联网服务，由此引发的公开争执进一步升级。【原文：Elon Musk on Friday called Ryanair CEO Michael O'Leary an "utter idiot" who should be fired, escalating a public spat that began after the airline boss ruled out installing Musk's Starlink internet service on Ryanair aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/musk-ryanair-ceo-clash-over-cost-starlink-wi-fi-planes-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYCUFXKWDNIHBONFJEVTKVEVWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:41:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际石油公司敦促委内瑞拉加快改革步伐，以期掌控该国石油出口权。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据参与谈判的消息人士透露，国际石油公司的高管和律师正游说美国和委内瑞拉政府，要求修改这个欧佩克成员国的碳氢化合物法律，使他们有权自由出口在委内瑞拉生产的石油。【原文：Oil executives and lawyers for international oil companies are lobbying the U.S. and Venezuelan governments for changes in the OPEC member's hydrocarbon law that would give them the right to freely export the oil they produce in Venezuela, sources involved in the talks said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/international-oil-companies-push-quick-reforms-venezuela-give-them-control-over-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USC2K7SWGZP5HNNIHQQTYTMB3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI将开始在ChatGPT的免费和Go版本中测试广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI周五表示，计划在其聊天机器人ChatGPT的免费版和Go版中开始测试广告功能。【原文：OpenAI said on Friday it plans to start testing ads in its chatbot ChatGPT's free and Go tiers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-begin-testing-ads-chatgpts-free-go-tiers-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O446QTEKNZMVLJRXDC4BSJMGHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称美国正探讨以委内瑞拉重质原油换取美国中质原油的计划，以补充战略储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两名消息人士周五透露，美国能源部正探讨一项计划，拟用委内瑞拉重质原油交换美国中质酸性原油，以补充战略石油储备。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy is exploring a plan to exchange heavy Venezuelan oil for U.S. medium, sour crude to fill up the Strategic Petroleum Reserve, two sources said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-explores-plan-swap-heavy-venezuelan-oil-us-medium-crude-fill-emergency-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UL3MIDM5CBP7PNH2OKYH42C7C4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:15:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西捷航空因乘客强烈反对将取消不可调节靠背的经济舱座椅]]></title><description><![CDATA[西捷航空周五宣布，将在部分波音737客机上取消不可调节的经济舱座椅。此前社交媒体上涌现大量投诉和视频，显示旅客膝盖紧贴前排座椅。【原文：WestJet Airlines said on Friday it will scrap non-reclinable economy seating on certain Boeing 737 jets, following a slew of complaints and videos on social media showing travelers' knees pressed up against the seats ahead of them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/westjet-reverses-course-non-adjustable-economy-seats-following-backlash-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4G6NUYQFMZO6TGW7USEXJDIUCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:09:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据库管理公司ClickHouse在人工智能热潮中估值达150亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据库管理公司ClickHouse在最新融资轮中估值达150亿美元，首席执行官亚伦·卡茨周五表示，投资者正对乘势而上的AI企业进行新一轮押注。【原文：Database management company ClickHouse was valued at $15 billion in its latest funding round , Chief Executive Aaron ​Katz said on Friday, as investors placed ‌a fresh bet on companies riding the AI boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/database-management-firm-clickhouse-valued-15-billion-amid-ai-boom-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3K7RXYZSFRMY3GEGYW6IM2DMWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:49:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称加拿大允许进口中国电动汽车的决定"存在问题"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔表示，加拿大政府决定以低关税率允许最多49,000辆中国电动汽车进口的做法"存在问题"，并称加拿大最终可能会为这一决定感到后悔。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said the Canadian government's decision to allow in up to 49,000 Chinese electric vehicles at a low tariff rate is "problematic" and that Canada may come to regret the decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-says-canadas-decision-allow-imported-chinese-evs-is-problematic-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OO5C5IVWU5LJVEAHHQRCN4AQQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院计划于1月20日作出裁决，特朗普关税案仍悬而未决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院预计将于1月20日作出下一批裁决，目前仍有若干重大案件悬而未决，包括对特朗普总统实施全球性关税的合法性问题。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court is expected to issue its next rulings on January 20 as several major cases remain pending including the legality of President Donald Trump's sweeping global tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/supreme-court-plans-rulings-january-20-with-trumps-tariffs-still-undecided-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7ZDS44JUNI2TBWFZ7VVF4KXVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:39:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍曼称美联储应准备再次降息以应对就业市场风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储负责监管事务的副主席米歇尔·鲍曼周五表示，脆弱的就业市场可能迅速恶化，这意味着美国央行应随时准备在必要时再次降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair for Supervision Michelle Bowman said on ​Friday a fragile job market that could weaken quickly means the U.S. central bank should stand ready to cut interest ‌rates again if needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bowman-says-fed-should-be-ready-cut-rates-again-amid-job-market-risks-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WLHD2I3BJMWDH6DAVWW3M3K6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道琼斯检测器显示，埃隆·马斯克的X平台全球数万用户无法访问]]></title><description><![CDATA[据故障追踪网站Downdetector.com显示，周五全球数万用户遭遇X平台服务中断。【原文：X was down for tens of thousands of users worldwide on Friday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/elon-musks-x-down-tens-thousands-users-globally-downdetector-shows-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQCRTGQL4FNSBHHRUEUFENOKZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:47:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顾问称特朗普住房计划将允许动用401(k)资金支付首付]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文·哈塞特周五表示，特朗普政府计划允许投资者动用部分退休金支付购房首付，并称更多细节将于下周公布。【原文：The Trump administration plans to allow investors to use some of their retirement funds to make a down payment on a ​house, White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett said on Friday, adding that ‌more details will be released next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-housing-plan-allow-401k-money-down-payments-adviser-says-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFKKVYX74VIF5GLQC3EDRHSXJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普告诉哈塞特，他可能希望留他在白宫任职。]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，唐纳德·特朗普总统在白宫活动中称赞了经济顾问凯文·哈塞特，并表示可能希望他继续担任现职。目前总统正在考虑下一任美联储主席的提名人选。【原文：President Donald Trump on Friday praised economic adviser Kevin Hassett at a White House event and said he may want to keep him in his current role, as the president considers his nominee for the next Federal Reserve chair.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tells-hassett-he-may-want-keep-him-white-house-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3V75N3YKJNEXM43TNOUIWRYEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:39:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月制造业产出意外增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国12月工厂产量意外增长，主要金属产量激增抵消了汽车装配厂的下滑，但受进口关税挑战影响，第四季度整体活动出现收缩。【原文：U.S. factory production unexpectedly increased in December amid a surge in primary metals output that offset a decline at motor vehicle assembly ​plants, but activity contracted in the fourth quarter against the ‌backdrop of challenges from import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-manufacturing-output-unexpectedly-increases-december-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6N4NGLOXCVNSZAXGM6VDJLFHKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国住宅建筑商信心指数1月回落，购房负担能力受限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国住房建筑商信心指数1月份恶化，一项周五公布的调查显示，购房负担能力担忧使潜在买家望而却步，而成本上升则阻碍了建筑活动。【原文：U.S. homebuilder sentiment deteriorated in January as affordability worries sidelined potential buyers and rising costs hampered construction activity, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-home-builder-sentiment-eases-january-amid-affordability-constraints-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACXILOEKYBMABAIAHGIUI6TUOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISS建议股东批准金佰利·克拉克公司拟议的肯维尤交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[机构股东服务公司周五建议股东批准金佰利·克拉克公司收购泰诺制造商健威公司的计划，称此次合并有望改善财务指标。【原文：Institutional Shareholder Services on ​Friday recommended that ‌shareholders approve plans by Kleenex maker Kimberly-Clark ‌to buy Tylenol maker ​Kenvue, saying a tie-up ‍could improve financial metrics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/iss-recommends-shareholders-approve-kimberly-clarks-planned-kenvue-deal-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNSSAQMFTVNSRK5MPOHZG67RLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期权到期或为美股波动率上升扫清道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[期权市场专家指出，周五的月度期权到期日可能使美国股市在未来几天面临更大涨跌幅，或将推动市场波动率从历史低位回升。【原文：Friday's monthly options expiration is likely to exposeU.S. stocks to greater swings in either direction in coming days, potentially boosting market volatility from historically low levels, according to options market experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/options-expiration-could-clear-path-us-stock-market-volatility-rise-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CKXQIODMUFL7TPA76Y5QH7ACMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛任命内部人士大卫·古吉纳为美国首席执行官，领导层迎来人事变动]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛周五任命资深高管大卫·古吉纳执掌美国业务部门，接替约翰·弗纳的职位。弗纳将出任这家零售巨头的首席执行官。【原文：Walmart on Friday named long-time executive ​David Guggina to head its U.S. division, succeeding ‌John Furner, who would take over as the chief executive officer of the retail behemoth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/walmart-names-insider-david-guggina-us-ceo-amid-leadership-shuffle-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZWRHQE6PZIWNIRDS3QDYXCYWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易撮合者预计2026年零售业并购与IPO将增多，因关税因素去年抑制了并购活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易撮合者预测，今年零售商和消费品公司的并购及首次公开募股活动将有所回升。此前，美国对进口商品征收的惩罚性关税导致该行业在2025年上半年陷入停滞。【原文：Dealmakers predict an uptick in mergers and IPOs for retailers and consumer goods companies this year after punishing tariffs on imports to the U.S. had sidelined activity in the industry for the first half of 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/dealmakers-see-more-retail-mergers-ipos-2026-after-tariffs-sidelined-ma-last-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQQFWZWIQZKCBP2SNK472AM2PY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫顾问哈塞特淡化对美联储主席鲍威尔的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫顾问凯文·哈塞特周五淡化了针对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的联邦刑事调查，称他预计"此事不会有任何结果"。【原文：White House adviser Kevin Hassett played down the federal criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday, saying he expected there would be "nothing to see here".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-adviser-hassett-plays-down-probe-fed-chair-powell-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRDSWOVBTFJGRBDUCYOGZZ7GIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:50:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通组建新顾问团队，借势私募市场繁荣期]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周五宣布组建新的顾问团队，协助企业及发起人从私募市场筹集资金。作为美国最大贷款机构，该行正寻求在炙手可热的另类资产领域深化布局。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has formed a new advisory team to help companies and sponsors raise money from private markets, it said on Friday, as the largest U.S. lender looks to deepen its presence in the red-hot alternative asset class.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-forms-new-advisory-group-tap-boom-private-markets-2026-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UBJHC37ENLNLDSE6D6OCENZSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:46:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>