<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:40:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:40:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车第四季度利润下滑，为动荡的 2025 年做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于瑞典的沃尔沃汽车公司周四公布第四季度营业利润下降，并预测 2025 年市场环境将充满挑战。【原文：Sweden-based Volvo Cars reported a fall in fourth-quarter operating profit on Thursday and predicted a turbulent 2025 with challenging market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-operating-profit-falls-q4-automaker-braces-turbulent-2025-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSW4BSNUZFJOVPKOCM27XPTXCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:13:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行警告：欧洲可能成为中美贸易战的最大输家]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行董事会成员皮埃罗-西波隆（Piero Cipollone）表示，随着通胀放缓，欧洲央行的利率还有进一步下降的空间，他同时警告说，美国政府与中国的贸易战可能会对拥有 20 个成员国的欧元区造成不利影响。【原文：European Central Bank interest rates have room to fall further as inflation moderates, ECB board member Piero Cipollone said, warning that the U.S. administration's trade war with China could have a detrimental impact on the 20-member euro zone.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/europe-could-be-big-loser-us-china-trade-war-ecb-warns-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQJY4PQZLRPQ3NYOHR4UQWBVLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元飙升刺激企业外汇套期保值激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业财务主管们正在加大力度保护公司盈利，以防美元进一步走强，一些分析师表示，此举表明，他们更加相信唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税计划将有助于美元在更长时间内保持高位。【原文：Corporate treasurers are ramping up efforts to guard company earnings against more dollar strength, a move that some analysts said points to increased conviction that President Donald Trump's tariff plans will help keep the U.S. currency higher for longer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/surging-dollar-spurs-jump-corporate-fx-hedging-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAD2VK3GRNNRHB3JBTDGS62PX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行希望特朗普的加密货币计划能加速数字欧元的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行董事会成员皮埃罗-西波隆（Piero Cipollone）告诉路透社，欧洲央行希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普支持与美元挂钩的加密货币的计划能加快数字欧元的立法支持。【原文：The European Central Bank hopes U.S. President Donald Trump's plan to support cryptocurrencies pegged to the U.S. dollar will speed up legislative backing for the digital euro, ECB board member Piero Cipollone told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ecb-hopes-trumps-crypto-plan-will-speed-up-digital-euro-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SB2TZJ4QVOX7LW3OPU7MKN66Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对原油征收报复性关税可能导致美国 2025 年出口下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国对美国的报复性关税可能导致美国石油出口在 2025 年出现下降，这是自 COVID-19 大流行以来的首次下降，而去年的增长已趋于平稳。【原文：China's retaliatory tariffs on the United States may cause U.S. oil exports to decline in 2025 for the first time since the COVID-19 pandemic, after growth plateaued last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-retaliatory-tariffs-crude-likely-push-us-exports-lower-2025-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGE2ER3JBNKEPJLQFK7LDVRJEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 06:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：焦点重回利率走势和公司收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOYWLPL6OBL3TBFSHDG2RGWBTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 05:33:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本三菱公司 9 个月净利润同比增长 19]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本三菱公司周四公布，截至 12 月份的九个月净利润增长了 19%，达到 8274 亿日元（54.3 亿美元）。【原文：Japan's Mitsubishi Corp posted on Thursday a 19% increase in nine-month net profit to December to 827.4 billion yen ($5.43 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-mitsubishi-9-month-net-profit-up-19-yy-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWMGB5RYOJNPJJP24EWT5GHDRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 05:12:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大阿尔伯塔省部长称，在美国关税威胁下，该省将目光投向日本，寻求新的液化天然气交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大环境与保护区部长丽贝卡-舒尔茨（Rebecca Schulz）告诉路透社，面对美国的关税威胁，加拿大主要天然气生产地阿尔伯塔省需要寻找新的出口市场，而扩大在日本的出口是一个重要目标。【原文：Canada's Alberta province, a major gas producer, needs to find new export markets in face of a U.S. tariff threat, and expanding in Japan is an important target, its minister of environment and protected areas, Rebecca Schulz, told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/canadas-alberta-eyes-japan-new-lng-deals-amid-us-tariff-threat-minister-says-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NTV645KRNLT5MNW3YICVLNDFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 04:51:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[约翰-舒尔曼离开人工智能初创公司 Anthropic]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI联合创始人、去年加入Anthropic的约翰-舒尔曼（John Schulman）周三晚些时候表示，他已离开这家人工智能初创公司。【原文：John Schulman, an OpenAI co-founder who joined Anthropic last year, has left his role at the artificial intelligence startup, the company said late on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/john-schulman-leaves-ai-startup-anthropic-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWTPSIYF3FMGBOH354DYMBIK5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 03:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据朝日新闻报道，日产首席执行官内田告诉本田首席执行官三部希望终止合并谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《朝日新闻》周四在线报道，日产汽车公司首席执行官内田诚（Makoto Uchida）向本田汽车公司首席执行官三部俊博（Toshihiro Mibe）表示，他希望终止双方关于合并可能性的讨论。【原文：Nissan Motor CEO Makoto Uchida told his Honda counterpart Toshihiro Mibe that he wants to terminate their discussions over a possible merger, the Asahi newspaper reported online on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nissan-ceo-uchida-tells-honda-ceo-mibe-he-wants-terminate-merger-talks-asahi-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5G7YBM2VRIFVHL2R3MVMOUKEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 02:27:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特提价后石油收窄跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四亚市早盘，油价从前一天沙特阿拉伯国家石油公司大幅上调3月份油价后的抛售中企稳回升。【原文：Oil prices ticked up in early Asian trading on Thursday, steadying from a sell-off the previous day after Saudi Arabia's state oil company sharply raised March oil prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-pares-losses-after-saudi-price-increase-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAJ47LG2XZM45KX6XGLCBG3ZSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 02:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战风险消退，美元兑日元跌至 8 周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美元对日元汇率跌至八周低点，对英镑汇率则徘徊在一个月低点附近，原因是投资者对引发通胀的全球贸易战的紧张情绪有所缓解。【原文：The U.S. dollar slumped to an eight-week trough to the yen and lingered near a one-month low versus sterling on Thursday, as investor nerves about an inflation-stoking global trade war abated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-slumps-8-week-low-vs-yen-trade-war-risk-recedes-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZB7MIO7AZJQRKFFXPKBIRVZBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行鹰派决策者敦促将利率上调至至少 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行鹰派董事田村直树周四表示，日本央行必须在 4 月开始的本财年下半年将利率至少提高到 1%。【原文：The Bank of Japan must raise interest rates to at least 1% by the second half of the fiscal year beginning in April, hawkish board member Naoki Tamura said on Thursday, remarks that pushed up the yen as they reinforced bets of a near-term rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/boj-must-raise-rates-1-by-latter-half-fiscal-2025-board-member-tamura-says-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPKBG2KWAVN5VO5GABC77S2YAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:53:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰斐逊不急于降低政策约束水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会副主席菲利普-杰斐逊（Philip Jefferson）周三表示，在政策制定者更好地了解特朗普政府的关税、移民、放松管制和税收政策的净影响之前，他满足于将央行的政策利率维持在目前的水平。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson on Wednesday said he is content to keep the central bank's policy rate in its current position until policymakers get a better sense of the net effects of the Trump administration's policies on tariffs, immigration, deregulation and taxes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-jefferson-no-rush-reduce-level-policy-restraint-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KY6AA2EPV5NEHC6FX7EXQKHAXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:46:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，OpenAI 将首次进军广告界，推出超级碗广告片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三援引知情人士的话报道，聊天软件制造商 OpenAI 预计将在周日的 "超级碗 "比赛中播放其首个电视广告。【原文：ChatGPT maker OpenAI is expected to air its first TV commercial during Sunday's Super Bowl, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-set-make-first-ad-foray-with-super-bowl-spot-wall-street-journal-reports-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5XPIXZMAY5OV3JGZYDXZO6PM3M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国务院称美国政府船只现在可以免费通过巴拿马运河]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院周三表示，美国政府船只现在可以通过巴拿马运河，无需支付费用。【原文：The U.S. Department of State said on Wednesday American government vessels can now transit the Panama Canal without charge fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/state-dept-says-us-government-vessels-can-now-transit-panama-canal-without-fees-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNQWPLEHXJIA3CI57SPVIHJVJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 01:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在世贸组织挑战特朗普关税，包裹托运人警告将出现混乱]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周三向世界贸易组织提出申诉，反对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国进口商品征收10%的新关税以及取消对低价值包裹的免税豁免，认为这些行动是 "保护主义 "的，违反了世贸组织的规则。【原文：China filed a World Trade Organization complaint on Wednesday against U.S. President Donald Trump's new 10% tariff on Chinese imports and his cancellation of a duty-free exemption for low-value packages, arguing the actions are "protectionist" and break WTO rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-challenges-trump-tariffs-wto-package-shippers-warn-chaos-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWXBXPKS7BOMRBU3QV6DXVMEP4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:59:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，交易员认为关税和通胀是 2025 年最大的市场动因]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）周三对机构交易客户进行的年度调查显示，全球交易员预计关税和通胀将对2025年的全球市场产生最大影响，因为他们已经做好了应对波动的准备。【原文：Traders across the globe project that tariffs and inflation will have the biggest impact on global markets in 2025 as they brace for volatility, an annual survey of institutional trading clients by JPMorgan Chase showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/traders-see-tariffs-inflation-2025s-biggest-market-movers-survey-shows-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMQ4QIW2LJOGTDGRHZ2WWEJL2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔首席执行官称公司因缺乏信任而拒绝 Venture Global 成为液化天然气供应商]]></title><description><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）首席执行官帕特里克-普亚内（Patrick Pouyanné）周三告诉路透社，道达尔能源公司拒绝了成为 Venture Global LNG 美国终端长期客户的机会，因为道达尔能源公司不信任该公司。【原文：TotalEnergies rejected opportunities to become a long-term customer of Venture Global LNG's U.S. terminals because it did not trust the company, CEO Patrick Pouyanné told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/total-ceo-says-company-rejected-venture-global-lng-supplier-over-lack-trust-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHS5UMY6DVI2BB3STKQ4TGTEQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行准备降息，但通胀忧虑挥之不去]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行看来将在周四降息，这是自 2020 年 COVID-19 大流行刚刚开始以来的第三次降息，因为它既要帮助疲软的经济，又要应对仍然强劲的通胀压力。【原文：The Bank of England looks set to cut interest rates on Thursday for only the third time since just after the start of the COVID-19 pandemic in 2020, as it juggles the need to help the sluggish economy with still-strong inflation pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/bank-england-poised-cut-rates-inflation-worries-linger-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6UGY6QHUJPO3BZB35ZDFC2EZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚企业的高估值面临关键的盈利考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周，澳大利亚企业将全面公布半年财报，虽然预计会有小幅增长，但交易员们将仔细研究利润是否能证明拉伸的估值是合理的，尤其是在面临美国关税等挑战的情况下。【原文：Corporate Australia kicks off its half-year earnings in full swing next week, and while modest growth is expected, traders will scrutinise whether profits justify stretched valuations, particularly in the face of challenges including U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australian-companies-high-valuations-face-crucial-earnings-test-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBBL6F7EQVNH3KK73KEIKU6SJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年初，花旗集团晋升了 8500 多名员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周三在其网站上发表声明称，作为年终工作的一部分，截至 1 月 1 日，花旗集团晋升了 8500 多名员工。【原文：Citigroup promoted more than 8,500 workers as of January 1 as part of its year-end process, the bank said in a statement on its website on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-promoted-more-than-8500-employees-start-2025-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUASDSMR2RPOPHD6JGRORAM75Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业削减 IT 支出，Cognizant 预测 2025 年收入低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对未来降息路径的不确定性迫使企业减少在 IT 服务和咨询方面的支出，Cognizant Technology Solutions 周三预测的年度收入低于预期。【原文：Cognizant Technology Solutions forecast annual revenue below estimates on Wednesday, as uncertainty about the path of future interest rate cuts forces companies to temper spending on IT services and consultancy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cognizant-forecasts-2025-revenue-below-estimates-businesses-temper-it-spending-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWLDYI2E3JO5PB4UQK3ZZCJPKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:23:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[McKesson 第三季度营收不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[药品分销商麦可森公司周三公布的第三季度营收不及预期，原因是包括品牌药和特药在内的美国医药部门的销售额低于预期。【原文：Drug distributor McKesson missed estimates for third-quarter revenue on Wednesday, hurt by less-than-expected sales in its U.S. pharmaceutical segment, which includes branded and specialty drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/mckesson-misses-third-quarter-revenue-estimates-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWV3M37GUJKKFAU3DQY6IAYP3A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:05:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全州保险公司因承保实力和投资收益而实现季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[受惠于承保业务的强劲增长和投资回报率的提高，财产和意外事故保险公司全州保险（Allstate）周三公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Property and casualty insurer Allstate's fourth-quarter profit beat Wall Street expectations on Wednesday, helped by strong gains in its underwriting business and higher returns on its investments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/insurer-allstates-quarterly-profit-beats-underwriting-strength-investment-gains-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6XCQJC2P5KDRBVR54PGYTODRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新闻集团业绩超预期，得益于数字不动产业务的强劲增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[新闻集团周三公布的第二季度业绩超过了分析师的预期，原因是数字房地产、图书出版和道琼斯业务部门的增长帮助抵消了新闻媒体部门增长放缓的影响。【原文：News Corp reported second-quarter results that beat analysts' estimates on Wednesday, as growth in its digital real estate, book publishing and Dow Jones segments help offset its slowing news media segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/news-corp-beats-results-helped-by-robust-growth-digital-real-estate-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PLUFJAYZ5OHDIP2NSU2PXN4AY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:51:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保费和投资收益强劲，大都会人寿第四季度利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[大都会人寿保险公司（MetLife）周三公布，由于保费和投资收入增加，第四季度利润有所增长。【原文：MetLife on Wednesday reported a rise in its fourth-quarter profit as it earned more in premiums and investment income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/metlife-fourth-quarter-profit-jumps-strong-premiums-investment-income-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQP2HX6APNNC7JTWXDP3PAAWDI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥官员称墨西哥和美国同意进行经济对话]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥外贸部副部长路易斯-罗森多-古铁雷斯（Luis Rosendo Gutierrez）表示，他于周三在白宫会见了美国政府高级官员，双方同意就经济问题进行持续、公开的对话。【原文：Mexican Deputy Foreign Trade Minister Luis Rosendo Gutierrez said he met with senior U.S. government officials at the White House on Wednesday and both sides agreed to ongoing and open dialogue on economic issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-us-agree-economic-dialogue-mexican-official-says-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI6RZA4Q4JKNRJFET4GKLWHWEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司称 Arm 已撤回违约索赔，不打算终止许可协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[高通公司首席执行官克里斯蒂安诺-阿蒙（Cristiano Amon）周三表示，Arm 控股公司已撤回终止高通公司与该技术供应商许可协议的威胁。【原文：Qualcomm's Chief Executive Officer Cristiano Amon on Wednesday said Arm Holdings has withdrawn a threat to terminate Qualcomm's license agreement with the technology provider.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qualcomm-says-arm-has-withdrawn-breach-claims-has-no-plans-terminate-license-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WG55PCGECBKOVORM4HDMUHRYOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储发布 2025 年银行压力测试方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三宣布，作为美国中央银行年度压力测试的一部分，将对大银行进行商业和住宅房地产市场的压力测试。【原文：The Federal Reserve announced on Wednesday it would be testing big banks against heightened stress in commercial and residential real estate markets as part of the U.S. central bank's annual stress tests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-releases-2025-bank-stress-test-scenarios-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJHXBABUS5IJXBJXF47VTWZ3AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:59:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>