<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:34:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:34:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[AirTrunk 完成 104 亿美元再融资，以支持亚太地区和日本的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[超大规模约会中心公司 AirTrunk 周二表示，该公司已经完成了 160 亿澳元（104.0 亿美元）的再融资，希望借此加快在亚太和日本地区的发展。【原文：Hyperscale date centre firm AirTrunk said on Tuesday it has closed an A$16 billion ($10.40 billion) refinancing as its looks to accelerate growth in the Asia Pacific and Japan region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/airtrunk-closes-1040-billion-refinancing-support-growth-apac-japan-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXAXB6OUEZIIBA5VMADYJCMQSE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:26:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skyworks Solutions 任命 AMD 高管 Philip Carter 为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Skyworks Solutions 周一表示，Philip Carter 将从 9 月 8 日起重新加入这家芯片制造商，担任首席财务官。【原文：Skyworks Solutions said on Monday Philip Carter will rejoin the chipmaker as its chief financial officer, effective September 8.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/skyworks-solutions-names-amd-executive-philip-carter-cfo-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6HKNG7XPHNPRVKRILBJILMFFOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:11:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西称南方共同市场与加拿大将恢复自由贸易协定谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西外交部长毛罗-维埃拉（Mauro Vieira）周一表示，加拿大和南美洲南方共同市场集团将恢复自由贸易协定谈判。【原文：Brazil's Foreign Minister Mauro Vieira said on Monday that Canada and South America's Mercosur bloc will resume negotiations for a free trade agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mercosur-canada-resume-talks-free-trade-agreement-brazil-says-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOYZJMJHWZJAJBQKGDWFMC3R4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 鲍威尔的中枢政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Y6BCLZ77FPQHO7QDKCOEHAWTQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布朗-福曼公司财务总监莉安-坎宁安将于明年退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[布朗-福曼公司周一表示，其首席财务官莉安-坎宁安（Leanne Cunningham）将于明年 5 月退休。【原文：Brown-Forman said on Monday its Chief Financial Officer Leanne Cunningham is set to retire in May next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/brown-formans-finance-boss-leanne-cunningham-retire-next-year-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A25VABDSUJOLRHW3A5545K42IU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:57:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，智利监管机构提高了受铜矿坍塌影响地区的重启要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周一看到的一份 Sernageomin 文件显示，智利矿业监管机构 Sernageomin 增加了对 Codelco 公司的要求，要求该公司重新启动受 7 月份埃尔泰尼恩特铜矿致命坍塌事故影响的地区。【原文：Chile's mining regulator Sernageomin has added requirements for Codelco to restart areas affected by a deadly collapse at its El Teniente copper mine in July, according to a Sernageomin document seen by Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chile-regulator-ups-requirements-restart-areas-affected-by-copper-mine-collapse-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DW7IHS2AY5K5BPU72GY7XYMGQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威财富基金从卡特彼勒和五家以色列银行撤资]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威的 2 万亿美元财富基金是世界上最大的财富基金，该基金周一表示，出于道德原因，已从美国卡特彼勒集团和五家以色列银行集团撤资。【原文：Norway's $2 trillion wealth fund, the world's largest, said on Monday it has divested from U.S. group Caterpillar as well as five Israeli banking groups on ethics grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/norway-wealth-fund-divests-caterpillar-five-israeli-banks-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6LMZUZUFVK2FCVYSJHUL4PWJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:23:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国橄榄球联盟（NFL）邀请前球员帮助传播联盟博彩政策的信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家橄榄球联盟（NFL）利用其退役球员名册来帮助现役球员避免因违规赌博而丢掉职业生涯--招募前铁人老将来传递赌博和橄榄球不能混为一谈的信息。【原文：The NFL has tapped its roster of retired players to help keep the current crop from fumbling away their careers over gambling violations — enlisting former gridiron veterans to deliver the message that betting and football simply do not mix.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/nfl-enlists-ex-players-help-spread-message-leagues-betting-policies-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YXITHNCD5JMPOWRU5SS32ECGA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，大韩航空预计将宣布订购约 100 架波音飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，在韩国总统李在明访问华盛顿之际，大韩航空预计将于周一宣布订购约 100 架波音飞机。【原文：Korean Air is expected to announce an order on Monday for about 100 Boeing airplanes coinciding with the visit of South Korean President Lee Jae Myung to Washington, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/korean-air-expected-announce-order-about-100-boeing-airplanes-sources-say-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSNJJ5526FLFPE5LZFSW6PZQE4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，沙特 Humain 公司将于 2026 年初推出采用美国芯片的数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一报道，沙特阿拉伯新成立的人工智能公司 Humain 已开始在沙特王国建设首个数据中心，并计划使用从美国进口的半导体，于 2026 年初投入使用。【原文：Humain, Saudi Arabia's new artificial intelligence company, has begun construction of its first data centers in the kingdom, and plans to bring them online in early 2026 using semiconductors imported from the U.S., Bloomberg News reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudis-humain-launch-data-centers-with-us-chips-early-2026-bloomberg-news-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3U2O4TMR7JM5RGAYHW6W3N5JH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:11:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡夫等公司打赢超标加工食品检测官司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国宾夕法尼亚州联邦法官驳回了卡夫、蒙代尔、可口可乐和其他几家大型食品公司指控它们设计的 "超加工 "食品会让儿童上瘾并导致慢性疾病的诉讼。【原文：Kraft, Mondelez, Coca-Cola and several other major food companies have beaten a lawsuit accusing them of designing "ultra-processed" foods to be addictive to children, causing chronic disease, after a Pennsylvania federal judge dismissed the lawsuit, which was seen by legal experts to be a key test case of the claims.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/kraft-other-companies-beat-test-lawsuit-over-ultra-processed-foods-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3DJ5ZELUZOMZB4W662DWJDHPU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称美国停止风电项目有损新英格兰电网可靠性和就业机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源和劳工官员周一表示，特朗普政府下令停止罗德岛海岸正在建设的一个大型风电场的工作，这威胁到电网的可靠性和就业。【原文：The Trump administration's order to halt work on a major wind farm under construction off the coast of Rhode Island threatens grid reliability and jobs, energy and labor officials said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-halt-wind-project-hurts-new-england-grid-reliability-jobs-officials-say-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I35BWGIEVPSFCQBKPUQ4WSTQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:43:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根认为仍有下调储备金的空间，预计下月SRF使用量将上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-洛根周一表示，她认为美国央行有更多的空间来削减储备金，她预计银行下个月会求助于常备回购机制来缓解任何流动性压力。【原文：Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan on Monday said she feels the U.S. central bank has more room to reduce its reserves, and she expects banks to turn to its standing repo facility next month to alleviate any liquidity pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-sees-room-lower-reserves-expects-uptick-srf-use-next-month-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZOP2XRI2FIIVHMXQK4ZZAVQZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国内政部建议将铜列入重要矿产清单]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周一提议将铜和钾肥等矿产列入 2025 年关键矿产清单草案，因为它们对经济和国家安全具有重要意义。【原文：The U.S. on Monday proposed adding copper and potash among others to the draft critical minerals list for 2025, for their importance to the economy and national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-interior-department-proposes-adding-copper-critical-minerals-list-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFBISPSABFP3JJEAR7H7Y45YPM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院命令美国证券交易委员会审查卖空规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周一下令美国证券交易委员会评估乔-拜登总统时代旨在提高卖空交易透明度的规定对经济的影响，这是提起诉讼的对冲基金取得的部分胜利。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Monday ordered the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to assess the economic impact of President Joe Biden-era rules aimed at boosting transparency of short sell trades, in a partial victory for hedge funds that brought the case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-appeals-court-orders-sec-review-short-selling-rules-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7AFDKG4MVL53A2JFQI4JKRNAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中国必须向美国提供磁铁，否则将面临 200% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周一对记者说，在两国贸易争端中，中国必须给美国磁铁，否则 "我们必须向他们征收 200% 的关税或其他什么"。【原文：President Donald Trump told reporters on Monday that China has to give the United States magnets or "we have to charge them 200% tariff or something" amid a trade dispute between the two nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-china-has-give-us-magnets-or-face-200-tariff-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WHVX36K3ZIIXICVKD563L5IDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司无意收购一家火车公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）首席执行官沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）周一在接受 CNBC 采访时表示，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司并不打算收购一家火车公司。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway is not in the market to buy a train company, CEO Warren Buffett said to CNBC on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/berkshire-hathaway-not-looking-buy-train-company-cnbc-reports-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5II6ZMDIZIATFUFI3QOYAEPXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特朗普政府正权衡对执行欧盟科技法的官员实施制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑对欧盟或成员国负责执行该集团具有里程碑意义的《数字服务法案》的官员实施制裁，因为美国抱怨该法案审查美国人并给美国科技公司带来成本。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering imposing sanctions on European Union or member state officials responsible for implementing the bloc's landmark Digital Services Act, two sources familiar with the matter said, over U.S. complaints that the law censors Americans and imposes costs on U.S. tech companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-weighs-sanctions-officials-implementing-eu-tech-law-sources-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5Q6DZB465NSRIZ4XQOIBUH2L4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业组织称，巴西咖啡零售价格可能因美国加征关税而飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西咖啡行业协会周一表示，由于巴西烘焙商的生豆成本激增，巴西烘焙咖啡和研磨咖啡的零售价格可能会出现逆转，8月份迄今为止平均下跌了12%。【原文：Retail prices for roasted and ground coffee in Brazil, which have fallen an average of 12% so far in August, could reverse course as costs of raw beans surge for Brazilian roasters, the country's coffee industry association said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-retail-coffee-prices-could-surge-amid-us-tariffs-industry-group-says-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DORROF2TMJL3XFQWUALER5RJKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SpaceX 希望通过第十次飞行测试克服 "星际飞船 "的挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索公司（SpaceX）将于周一在得克萨斯州第十次发射巨型 "星际飞船"（Starship）火箭，以克服连续的研发挫折，实现几个长期追求的里程碑，这对火星火箭系统的可重复使用设计至关重要。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX will try to launch its giant Starship rocket for a tenth time from Texas on Monday to overcome a streak of development setbacks and achieve several long-sought milestones essential to the Mars rocket system's reusable design.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spacex-aims-overcome-starship-setbacks-with-tenth-flight-test-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5AENV3F3FJNDLBVBBMNQG5TYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次推动美国机构吊销 NBC 和 ABC 电视台执照]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统在批评美国两大广播公司的新闻节目时，重申了他长期以来推动联邦通信委员会吊销两家美国主要广播公司的电台执照并向它们收取使用公共电波费用的主张。【原文：President Donald Trump reiterated a long-running push for the Federal Communications Commission to revoke station licenses of two major U.S. broadcasters and charge them for using the public airwaves, as he criticized their news programming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-again-pushes-us-agency-revoke-nbc-abc-station-licenses-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NV2XG5FG3NN4ZB2S5QX6BVELGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部撤销拜登的 74 亿美元半导体研究资助协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，将废除乔-拜登总统时期与一家外部中心达成的协议，该中心将负责监管 74 亿美元的半导体研究基金。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Monday it was voiding an agreement finalized under President Joe Biden with an outside center to oversee $7.4 billion in semiconductor research funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-commerce-department-voids-bidens-74-billion-semiconductor-research-grant-deal-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QN2WWXH75BLNBFKACZG4JZYGTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Squishmallows 制造商与 Build-A-Bear 在毛绒玩具官司中休战]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据向洛杉矶联邦法院提交的一份文件，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的 Squishmallows 制造商 Jazwares 已同意结束对 Build-A-Bear Workshop 的诉讼，因为该公司涉嫌山寨流行的毛绒玩具。【原文：Jazwares, the Berkshire Hathaway-owned maker of Squishmallows, has agreed to end a lawsuit against Build-A-Bear Workshop over its alleged knockoffs of the popular plush toys, according to a filing in Los Angeles federal court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/squishmallows-maker-build-a-bear-call-truce-plush-toy-legal-battle-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XI7BVXEKZZMPDN7VZAPLXNSPUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的 xAI 就人工智能竞争和应用商店排名起诉苹果和 OpenAI]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁企业家埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的人工智能初创公司 xAI 周一在美国得克萨斯州联邦法院起诉苹果公司和 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI，指控它们非法合谋阻挠人工智能竞争。【原文：Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence startup xAI sued Apple and ChatGPT maker OpenAI in U.S. federal court in Texas on Monday, accusing them of illegally conspiring to thwart competition for artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/elon-musks-xai-sues-apple-openai-over-ai-competition-app-store-rankings-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DC6MCVW5MRNHFLK6ZWWZEPFLNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔将 Keurig Dr Pepper 列入负面信用观察名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国软饮料巨头 Keurig Dr Pepper 周一宣布将收购荷兰咖啡集团 JDE Peet's 之后，评级机构 S&amp;P Global 将该公司的信用展望定为负面。【原文：Ratings agency S&amp;P Global put a negative credit outlook on U.S. soft drinks giant Keurig Dr Pepper after the company announced Monday it will buy Dutch coffee group JDE Peet's .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/sp-puts-keurig-dr-pepper-negative-credit-watch-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOZA5MXZ55M4NNV3N7NAZW42KU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月新屋销售下降；6 月销售修正为上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[继上月销售速度大幅上调之后，7 月份美国新建独户住宅的销售量有所下降，总体趋势仍然是住房市场在高抵押贷款利率的环境中苦苦挣扎。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell in July following a sharp upward revision to the prior month's sales pace, and the overall trend remained consistent with a housing market struggling in an environment of high mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-july-june-sales-revised-higher-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LH6HTVIRFFPTJJBTLZMHRUZENU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将继续达成类似英特尔的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他将与其他公司达成类似于上周宣布的与英特尔公司（Intel）的交易。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he would make deals with other companies similar to the one he announced last week with Intel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-continue-make-deals-like-intel-one-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2R3AJ3OB2RJLVNBQFLRAEE4XX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇率飙升和特朗普关税影响欧洲业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国关税和美元疲软导致的欧洲货币升值削弱了企业在第二季度的业绩表现，增加了企业将业务迁往美国或将工作岗位迁往美国的压力。【原文：U.S. tariffs and an appreciation in European currencies caused by dollar weakness have eroded companies' top line performance in the second quarter, increasing pressure on them to relocate operations or put jobs into the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/currency-spikes-trump-tariffs-take-bite-out-european-results-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIQOIBDYNVKPBEE7O67QNXLIXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，皮纳尔家族正在探索出售彪马公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道称，Pinault 家族正在权衡 Puma SE 的各种选择，包括出售。【原文：The Pinault family is weighing options for Puma SE , including a sale, Bloomberg News reported on Monday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pinault-family-explores-sale-puma-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPLEWCTLMNLE3DHWUZTJFESFJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拥有优质信用的美国消费者在付款方面开始出现滑坡]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评分公司 VantageScore 在周一发布的一份报告中称，信用评分最高的美国消费者在偿还债务方面开始落后，这表明美国人的财务健康状况可能正在更广泛地恶化。【原文：U.S. consumers with the highest credit scores are starting to fall behind in debt repayments, credit scoring company VantageScore said in a report published on Monday, in a sign that Americans' financial health may be deteriorating more broadly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumers-with-prime-credit-are-starting-slip-payments-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APIJM3WJQRLSVGIPDTJQV764M4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>