<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:40:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:40:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[根据共和党税收法案，各州将难以管理食品券福利]]></title><description><![CDATA[据各州官员、地方政府协会和政策专家称，如果共和党税收法案中一项迫使各州承担数十亿美元新成本的提案签署成为法律，那么美国各州将无法全面管理为全国数百万穷人提供的食品券福利。【原文：U.S. states will not be able to fully administer food stamp benefits for millions of the nation's poor if a proposal in the Republican tax bill forcing them to shoulder billions of dollars in new costs is signed into law, according to state officials, local government associations and policy experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/states-would-struggle-administer-food-stamp-benefits-under-republican-tax-bill-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2REESHSI5OUPJ6NUC7BKWHHJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将恢复对瑞士投资顾问的认证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）和瑞士金融市场监管机构金融市场管理局（FINMA）周二分别发表声明称，美国将恢复处理瑞士实体提出的旨在成为美国注册投资顾问的申请。【原文：The U.S. will resume processing applications from Swiss entities aiming to become registered investment advisers in the U.S., the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission and Swiss financial market regulator FINMA said in separate statements on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-will-resume-accreditation-swiss-investment-advisers-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POZ5MAPXINMPBK7Y4WA23KQPLQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税挤压蓝莓出口，秘鲁转向中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着产量的增加，秘鲁的种植者们正在寻找新的市场，而他们最好的客户--美国，正在对世界各地的合作伙伴发动贸易关税战。【原文：Growers in Peru are looking for new markets as production rises and their best customer, the United States, is waging a trade tariff war on partners around the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/peru-usas-top-blueberry-supplier-looks-china-tariffs-hit-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZ7XVSZ7HVMLBLME7OB4MROHDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:08:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列数据安全公司 Cyera 融资 5.4 亿美元，估值 60 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列数据安全初创公司 Cyera 周三表示，它在一轮后期私募融资中筹集了 5.4 亿美元，使其估值达到 60 亿美元。【原文：Israeli data security startup Cyera said on Wednesday it raised $540 million in a late-stage private funding round to bring its valuation to $6 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-data-security-firm-cyera-raises-540-mln-valued-6-bln-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNQIC7RS2BIQVLEBSUZ7WNR5EI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国进口商求助于中间商来应对特朗普时代的关税，但代价不菲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国进口商越来越依赖报关行来跟上唐纳德-特朗普总统不断变化的贸易政策。但业内人士告诉路透社，对帮助处理外国货物的蓬勃需求使这些服务变得更加昂贵，为关税负担增加了另一项成本。【原文：U.S. importers are increasingly relying on customs brokers to keep up with President Donald Trump’s ever-changing trade policies. But booming demand for help in processing foreign goods has made these services more expensive, adding another cost to the tariff burden, industry players told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-importers-turn-brokers-navigate-trump-era-tariffs-cost-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZBSNNEUXFO2JIKWFK2SYH5LVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:05:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达首席执行官称量子计算正处于拐点]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋周三在巴黎举行的 VivaTech 会议上重申，量子计算技术正处于拐点。【原文：Quantum computing technology is at an inflection point, Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang reiterated on Wednesday at the VivaTech conference in Paris.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-ceo-says-quantum-computing-is-an-inflection-point-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCJHIRTJYZPAVLQF3WKZX5VKXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 09:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着美国贸易休战重回正轨，一些中国出口商正在 "慢慢死去]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jacky Ren是中国一家厨房电器工厂的老板，他说，他所在行业的出口商为了留住美国客户，现在都在亏本销售，对于面临更高关税的产品的降价要求，他们几乎没有能力说 "不"。【原文：Jacky Ren, who owns a kitchen appliance factory in China, says exporters in his industry are now selling at a loss to keep their U.S. clients, with little power to say "no" to requests for lower prices on products facing higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-trade-truce-gets-back-track-some-chinese-exporters-are-slowly-dying-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAK35IKH4FKSJGXQNJ7E54TVWA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 09:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为推出 Pura 80 智能手机系列，迈出重返中国的下一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国科技巨头华为公司（HWT.UL）周三推出了 Pura 80 系列智能手机，该公司力图巩固其在美国多年制裁后在中国高端智能手机市场的地位。【原文：Chinese tech giant Huawei (HWT.UL) launched its Pura 80 smartphone series on Wednesday, as the company seeks to cement its comeback in China's premium smartphone market following years of U.S. sanctions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/huawei-launches-pura-80-smartphone-series-next-step-china-comeback-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDIJJ6GWR5JKVJWWAG6XWJWTRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 09:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，摩洛哥皇家航空公司接近达成波音和空客喷气机交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内消息人士称，空中客车公司即将与摩洛哥皇家航空公司（Royal Air Maroc）达成约20架A220小型客机的交易，在这家北非航空公司准备与美国波音公司续签更广泛的喷气机订单之际站稳脚跟。【原文：Airbus is nearing a deal with Royal Air Maroc for around 20 of its small A220 passenger jets, gaining a foothold as the North African carrier also prepares to renew U.S. ties with a broader jet Boeing order, industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/royal-air-maroc-nearing-deals-boeing-airbus-jets-sources-say-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3TZ5J7DGJOGFDBRQFGGL7FR2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 08:59:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本在 6 月经济报告中对关税影响保持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府在周三的月度报告中重申了美国关税对经济增长所带来风险的警告，称需要关注美国关税对企业利润的潜在影响。【原文：Japan's government reiterated its warning on the risks from U.S. tariffs on economic growth, saying in a monthly report on Wednesday that the potential impact on corporate profits needed attention.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-remains-cautious-tariff-impact-june-econ-report-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKXJHT6K7VMJZKCZOIROL6V2BA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 08:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通因关税风险缓解和去美元化趋势上调人民币汇率预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）周三上调了中国在岸人民币即期价格的年末预期，理由是美国贸易战的风险有所缓和，以及所谓的去美元化这一更广泛的全球主题。【原文：JPMorgan lifted its end-of-year forecast for China's onshore yuan spot price on Wednesday, citing moderating risks around the U.S. trade war and a broader global theme of so-called de-dollarisation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/jpmorgan-lifts-yuan-forecast-easing-tariff-risks-de-dollarisation-trend-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBR5DSLS2RPMNFB62I6HMHEFRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 08:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，通用磨坊考虑出售中国哈根达斯门店]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，通用磨坊公司正在考虑出售其在中国的哈根达斯冰淇淋店。【原文：General Mills is considering selling its Haagen-Dazs ice-cream stores in China, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/general-mills-mulls-sale-china-haagen-dazs-stores-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W6MVFQ7Q3RMRVBPSJ2K2QKZY54</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 08:23:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，越航正在洽谈在巴黎航展前订购约 100 架空客喷气机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引熟知内情的消息人士的话报道，VietJet Aviation JSC 正在洽谈增购约 100 架空中客车公司窄体喷气式飞机，最早可能在下周的巴黎航展上达成交易。【原文：VietJet Aviation JSC is in talks to order around 100 additional Airbus SE narrowbody jets, with a potential deal as early as the Paris Air Show next week, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietjet-talks-order-about-100-airbus-jets-ahead-paris-air-show-bloomberg-news-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFHKFOFTPRNSBJKU52XHWHYTNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 08:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元不断失去市场份额，但欧元也不是赢家：欧洲央行研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行的一份报告显示，去年美元作为世界主要货币的市场份额继续下降，但主要受益的是较小的竞争对手和黄金，而不是欧元，后者希望填补因对美元信心下降而留下的空白。【原文：The dollar continued to lose market share last year as the world's dominant currency but mostly smaller rivals and gold benefited rather than the euro, which aspires to fill any void left by receding confidence in the greenback, an ECB report showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dollar-keeps-losing-market-share-euro-is-no-winner-either-ecb-study-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXGVK45G2BPARJGVKNRQGG4VOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 08:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克首席执行官告诉英国《金融时报》，星巴克对入股中国业务 "兴趣浓厚"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克首席执行官周三在接受英国《金融时报》采访时表示，星巴克对出售其中国业务的股份 "兴趣浓厚"，因为这家美国咖啡连锁店希望重振其第二大市场的销售业绩。【原文：Starbucks has received "a lot of interest" in the sale of a stake in its China business, its chief executive told the Financial Times in an interview published on Wednesday, as the U.S. coffee chain looks to revive sales in its second-largest market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/starbucks-has-received-a-lot-interest-china-business-stake-ceo-tells-ft-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNVDPRRNPBLWJPBCL4KA7OLKQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:51:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[校园刺伤事件发生后，马克龙将推动禁止 15 岁以下青少年使用社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国东部一所学校发生致命刺伤事件后，法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙表示，他将推动欧盟制定法规，禁止 15 岁以下儿童使用社交媒体。【原文：French President Emmanuel Macron said he would push for European Union regulation to ban social media for children under the age of 15 after a fatal stabbing at a school in eastern France, the latest such violent attack that left the country reeling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/macron-push-ban-social-media-under-15s-after-school-stabbing-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWBYNVIU25LMBAVOU54C5JBFMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:47:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利联合信贷银行首席执行官称达成 BPM 银行交易的可能性不超过 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合信贷银行首席执行官 Andrea Orcel 周三表示，联合信贷银行通过收购较小同行 Banco BPM 的可能性最多只有 20%。【原文：The chances that UniCredit can see through its takeover bid for smaller peer Banco BPM are at best 20%, CEO Andrea Orcel said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-ceo-says-chances-pursuing-banco-bpm-deal-no-more-than-20-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LADXJ2E4DVO2TIJW7QD2GT3NBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产供应商马瑞利申请破产保护，获得 11 亿美元新融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车零部件供应商马瑞利公司（Marelli Corp）周三在一份声明中说，在与债权人的谈判出现几个月的不确定性之后，该公司在美国申请了破产保护。【原文：Nissan supplier Marelli Corp filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the United States on Wednesday, the Japanese auto parts company said in a statement, after months of uncertainty about its talks with creditors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nissan-supplier-marelli-files-chapter-11-secures-11-billion-new-financing-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETOANMIMZJMVFE2ZUJIEDJV3LI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:22:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克说他对自己发表的一些关于特朗普的帖子感到后悔]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周三在其社交媒体平台 X 上留言说，他对上周发表的一些关于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的帖子感到遗憾。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk said on Wednesday that he regrets some of the posts he made last week about U.S President Donald Trump, in a message on his social media platform X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/musk-says-he-regrets-some-posts-he-made-about-trump-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHAI5PV3DBIQTAGP2ZKQLNRSZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Polestar 重启法国市场扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典高端汽车制造商 Polestar 的高层告诉路透社，该公司将于今年开始在法国交付电动汽车，目标是将法国打造成其三大欧洲市场之一。【原文：Swedish premium carmaker Polestar will start delivering its electric vehicles in France this year with the goal of making it one of its three main European markets, its top executive for the country told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/polestar-restarts-market-expansion-with-france-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPMHE6IQSZN7TBZTXZ47EE5INE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯德集团将于今年夏天推出人工智能招聘服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[与政府、军队和公司合作的英国外包公司 Capita 表示，它正在利用人工智能将招聘工作从数周缩短到数小时，并将在今年夏天推出与 Salesforce Inc 合作开发的这项服务。【原文：Capita , a British outsourcer that works with government, armed forces and companies, said it was using AI to cut recruitment from weeks to just hours, and it would roll out the service, developed with Salesforce Inc , this summer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/capita-roll-out-ai-powered-recruitment-this-summer-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFG6DWHLCBK57ASOVWY3O5ZBCA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:04:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国与美国的最新贸易休战令投资者不知所措]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美之间最新达成的贸易休战协议为投资者带来了希望，使这对不和的超级大国能够最终达成一项协议，尽管再次爆发关税冲突的可能性仍是市场面临的一个风险。【原文：The latest trade truce between China and the United States offered investors the hope of an eventual deal that the feuding superpowers can live with, though the possibility of another tariff flare-up remained a risk for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-latest-trade-truce-with-us-leaves-investors-none-wiser-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22X24UQQRBO3ZEPKGYP2FTXG3Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，亚航接近购买至少 100 架空客飞机，以转向 A220 飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士透露，亚航正在深入讨论在下周的巴黎航展上订购至少100架空客喷气机的事宜，这笔交易很可能标志着亚航机队将引进空客最小的喷气机A220。【原文：AirAsia is in advanced discussions to place an order for at least 100 Airbus jets at next week's Paris Airshow, a deal likely to mark the introduction to its fleet of the planemaker's smallest jet, the A220, industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airasia-close-buying-least-100-airbus-jets-shift-a220-sources-say-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2T46NSTIVIUFFGSPABWF3PDYU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 提出 23 亿美元 "最佳和最终 "收购英国 Assura 公司的报价]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权公司 KKR 和 Assura 周三表示，双方已就出售这家英国医疗保健房地产投资商的 "最佳和最终 "报价条款达成一致，估值近 17 亿英镑（22.9 亿美元）。【原文：U.S. private equity firm KKR and Assura have agreed on the terms of a "best and final" offer for the British healthcare real estate investor's sale, valuing it at nearly 1.7 billion pounds ($2.29 billion), the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kkr-tables-best-final-23-billion-offer-buy-uks-assura-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVJBVZHPEVOEJAGEGHGXBNGC5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨博和赫尔辛让人工智能驾驶战机与真正的战斗机飞行员对决]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典萨博公司（Saab）和德国防务初创公司赫尔辛（Helsing）周三表示，他们已经对一架由人工智能驾驶的鹰狮 E 战机与一名真正的战斗机飞行员进行了实战测试，这标志着欧洲在防务自主化竞争方面向前迈出了一步。【原文：Sweden's Saab and German defence startup Helsing have conducted combat testing of a Gripen E warplane flown by AI against a real fighter pilot, they said on Wednesday, in a step forward in European efforts to compete on autonomy in defence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/saab-helsing-pit-ai-piloted-warplane-against-real-fighter-pilot-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4RNDP37BRNIJI7TXUSDJT4NCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:04:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本向无现金社会的转变促使日本央行呼吁支付创新]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行官员正在加紧呼吁跟上数字货币的快速发展步伐，因为数字货币可能会加速这个以 "现金为王 "的国家向无现金支付的转变。【原文：Bank of Japan officials are ramping up calls to keep pace with rapid developments around digital currencies that may accelerate a shift to cashless payments in a country better known for its belief that "cash is king."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/japans-shift-cashless-society-prods-boj-call-payment-innovation-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXZEHOGBVZJKRNBEF6MAI3VRMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zara 所有者 Inditex 公布的第一季度销售额低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，Zara 所有者 Inditex 第一季度销售额未达预期，使人们更加怀疑这家快速时尚零售商在不确定的经济环境中保持强劲销售增长的能力。【原文：Zara owner Inditex missed expectations for its first-quarter sales on Wednesday, adding to doubts about the ability of the fast-fashion retailer to keep delivering strong sales growth in an uncertain economic environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/zara-owner-inditex-reports-weaker-than-expected-first-quarter-sales-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3LKFIPFH5OCNPU4ZZX4TL55CA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 05:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[任天堂 Switch 2 刷新纪录，成为公司销量最快的游戏机]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本任天堂公司周三表示，Switch 2 上市后的前四天销量已超过 350 万台，成为该公司迄今为止销量最快的游戏设备。【原文：Japan's Nintendo said on Wednesday it had sold more than 3.5 million Switch 2 units in the first four days after its launch, making the console the company's fastest-selling gaming device to date.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nintendo-switch-2-smashes-record-companys-fastest-selling-console-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AEQFULH4AJP4ZFMU4ARK4HGVCM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:38:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：所以，这可能是一个交易框架？]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMITNMRJHBMCBJHRNGBCXZS32Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:33:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民意调查 绝大多数经济学家认为日本央行将推迟至明年第一季度加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社的一项民意调查中，略占多数的经济学家预计，日本央行将在 2026 年初加息 25 个基点，由于美国关税政策的不确定性，日本央行今年将放弃再次加息。【原文：The Bank of Japan will forego another interest rate hike this year due to uncertainty over U.S. tariff policy, according to a slight majority of economists in a Reuters poll who expect the next 25-basis-point increase in early 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/boj-postpone-rate-hike-q1-next-year-tiny-majority-economists-say-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BVBIC2X2JMS3O3HPUDX64E7FA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:10:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>