<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:33:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:33:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[PNC Financial 第一季度利润因利息收入增加而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 PNC Financial 银行周二公布第一季度利润增长，主要得益于利息收入的增加。【原文：U.S. bank PNC Financial reported a rise in first-quarter profit on Tuesday, helped by a boost in interest income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/pnc-financial-first-quarter-profit-rises-higher-interest-income-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WP6GY5G4VBKRNFFCBU42DQ675E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:26:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利称英国未共享战斗机项目技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[国防部长吉多-克罗塞托（Guido Crosetto）表示，英国在开发新型战斗机的重大项目中没有与意大利和日本充分共享技术，并敦促伦敦拆除 "自私的壁垒"。【原文：Defence Minister Guido Crosetto has said Britain is not fully sharing technologies with Italy and Japan in a major project to develop a new fighter jet and urged London to bring down the "barriers of selfishness".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/italy-says-britain-is-not-sharing-technology-fighter-project-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSRAYLNRNBNPHGB26DVDQNAPBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Stellantis 即将确定新任首席执行官人选，候选名单上有五位候选人]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国-意大利汽车制造商 Stellantis 已将其首席执行官候选人的候选名单缩减至五位，两位熟悉此事的人士表示，该公司即将决定由谁来领导公司渡过该行业最动荡的时期之一。【原文：French-Italian carmaker Stellantis has reduced its shortlist of CEO candidates to five, said two people familiar with the matter, as it nears a decision on who will lead the company through one of the industry's most tumultuous periods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-closing-new-ceo-with-shortlist-five-candidates-sources-say-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ4XNKCJAZPSFF6WOHFWH455AU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:14:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关税威胁下，爱尔兰制药业对美出口激增至 105 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的数据显示，爱尔兰2月份对美国的药品和医疗产品出口同比激增了450%以上，这是爱尔兰对美国的药品和医疗产品出口的第二次月度增长，表明美国制药商可能会在潜在关税之前囤积药品。【原文：Irish exports of pharmaceutical and medical products to the U.S. surged by more than 450% year-on-year in February, data showed on Tuesday, a second monthly hike that suggested U.S. drugmakers may be stockpiling medicines in advance of potential tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/irish-pharma-exports-us-surge-105-billion-euros-amid-tariff-threat-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZUX2PCFVBNHPOYXSNL5GO4ZQ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院委员会要求 23andMe 联合创始人在破产后作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院一个委员会周二要求 23andMe 的联合创始人在下个月作证，因为该委员会正在对这家 DNA 检测公司破产之际基因数据被转移给潜在买家的风险展开调查。【原文：A U.S. House committee on Tuesday asked 23andMe's co-founder to testify next month as it launched an investigation into the risk of genetic data being transferred to potential buyers amid the DNA testing company's bankruptcy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-house-committee-seeks-testimony-23andme-co-founder-after-bankruptcy-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RYDBY635ZLTLD6C3NYQJ4LJ6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:07:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利部长：美国对稳定币的政策比关税更危险]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利经济部长周二表示，美国对稳定币的政策为欧洲公民的跨境交易提供了一种有吸引力的支付方式，这应该比贸易关税引发更多关注。【原文：U.S. policy on stablecoins offers European citizens an attractive payment method for cross-border transactions which should trigger more concern than trade tariffs, Italy's economy minister said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-policy-stablecoins-more-dangerous-than-tariffs-italian-minister-says-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGUQ5OD2CVK2RLEMFIRCODD6E4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡特彼勒任命内部人士约瑟夫-克里德（Joseph E Creed）为首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡特彼勒周二表示，首席运营官约瑟夫-克里德（Joseph E. Creed）将接替詹姆斯-昂普尔比三世（James Umpleby III）出任首席执行官，5 月 1 日起生效。【原文：Caterpillar said on Tuesday Chief Operating Officer Joseph E. Creed will succeed James Umpleby III as CEO, effective May 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/caterpillar-names-insider-joseph-e-creed-ceo-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XFD4SWKXNPF5F2TFQNJ6DAC3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:55:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行第一季度利润因交易强劲而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场波动提高了交易费用，美国银行第一季度利润上升，开盘前股价上涨了 1.9%。【原文：Bank of America's profit rose in the first quarter, as market volatility boosted its trading fees, lifting the shares of the bank up 1.9% before the open.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-profit-rises-trading-strength-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJFVDQUA2RM7VOVKLK5RRW7G3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储让市场喘口气]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X53HKRQE3VMKFI3DE43TVZXQHU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:43:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因抗癌药物销售，J&J 公司季度销售额和利润超出华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司周二公布的第一季度营收和利润高于华尔街预期，其癌症治疗药物包括多发性骨髓瘤药物 Darzalex 的强劲销售再次推动了这一增长。【原文：Johnson & Johnson on Tuesday reported first-quarter revenue and profit above Wall Street estimates, driven again by strong sales of its cancer treatments including multiple myeloma medicine Darzalex.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/jj-beats-wall-street-quarterly-sales-profit-estimates-cancer-drug-sales-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOOX4XQYAJIIFPJTQO2K5LEGSA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:23:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司明年开始提供免费机上 Wi-Fi 服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司（American Airlines）周二表示，将与 AT&amp;T 合作，从 2026 年 1 月起提供免费的高速机上互联网服务。【原文：American Airlines said on Tuesday it will provide free high-speed in-flight internet services beginning in January 2026 in partnership with AT&amp;T .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-start-offering-free-in-flight-wi-fi-next-year-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CF2HCGKZD5MC3PQGJ6S6HMBKHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国律师称英国情报公司为针对他的黑客行动买单]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位纽约律师指控一家英国私人情报公司付钱给雇佣兵黑客，称这些黑客在一场法庭战中向他的对手倾斜。【原文：A New York attorney has accused a British private intelligence firm of paying mercenary hackers who he says tipped a court battle in his opponents' favor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-lawyer-says-uk-intel-firm-paid-hack-operation-against-him-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RF4DOVZYC5NOZLIXXD6KMYL6MQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:14:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票期货因更多关税豁免希望而上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周二小幅走高，因为在唐纳德-特朗普总统提出更多豁免的想法后，投资者评估了汽车行业关税减免的可能性。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were slightly higher on Tuesday, as investors assessed the possibility of tariff relief for the auto sector after President Donald Trump floated the idea of more exemptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-stock-futures-edge-up-hopes-more-tariff-exemptions-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JX25A6YSMFNA7PYCDTN23A5ZIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究人员发现，3 月份全球电动汽车销量增长 29]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的数据显示，3月份全球电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车销量同比增长29%，这主要得益于中国和欧洲的增长，而北美电动汽车的增长则受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对排放标准的立场以及关税不确定性的影响。【原文：Global sales of electric and plug-in hybrid vehicles rose 29% year-on-year in March, helped by growth in China and Europe, while EV growth in North America was hampered by U.S. President Donald Trump's stance towards emissions standards and uncertainties around tariffs, data showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-electric-vehicle-sales-up-29-march-researchers-find-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKTLHHTBZVL7PIS2EO5UTX7UDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度官员表示将寻求与美国实现贸易自由化]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度贸易部长周二表示，印度已决定与美国走贸易自由化的道路，两国签署了双边贸易协议第一部分的职权范围。【原文：India has decided to pursue a path of trade liberalisation with the United States, India's trade secretary said on Tuesday, with the two countries signing the terms of reference for the first part of a bilateral trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-pursue-trade-liberalisation-with-us-official-says-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6QBLLRRABME3N2SC6VW7UAW7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:57:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管机构数据显示，关税战将打击中国市场上流行的美国产药品]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对中国监管机构数据的审查显示，治疗癌症和糖尿病等疾病的流行西药已被卷入不断升级的中美贸易战，并有可能增加制药商的成本。【原文：Popular Western medicines for diseases including cancer and diabetes have been caught in the escalating U.S.-China trade war, a Reuters review of Chinese regulator data showed, and threaten to add to drugmakers' costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/tariff-wars-hit-popular-us-made-drugs-china-regulator-data-shows-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HO4QUCM5MJKDJOXH4QKUTTO7L4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:40:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼提议将美国石油和液化石油气进口额提高约 100 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼能源部长巴赫利尔-拉哈达里亚（Bahlil Lahadalia）周二告诉当地媒体，作为关税谈判的一部分，印尼将提议增加从美国进口约100亿美元的原油和液化石油气。【原文：Indonesia will propose increasing its imports of crude oil and liquefied petroleum gas from the United States by around $10 billion as part of its tariff negotiations, energy minister Bahlil Lahadalia told local media on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/indonesia-propose-lifting-us-oil-lpg-imports-by-around-10-billion-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FM4KE2O5AVI5JOMLWMYZIF6JFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国金融监管机构在美国和亚洲设立分支机构，吸引企业到英国发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融行为监管局周二表示，该局首次在美国和亚太地区任命了工作人员，以帮助海外公司进入英国市场，促进英国金融服务的出口。【原文：Britain's Financial Conduct Authority has appointed staff in the United States and the Asia-Pacific region for the first time, to help overseas firms to enter the British market and boost exports of UK financial services, the watchdog said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/britains-financial-watchdog-sets-up-us-asia-attract-firms-uk-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7WE6BCDK5KTHMIYKTULU22RW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，本田将通过迁移墨西哥和加拿大的生产基地，实现 90% 的美国本土销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周二报道，本田汽车公司计划将部分汽车生产从墨西哥和加拿大转移到美国，目标是在美国销售的汽车中 90% 由本地生产。【原文：Honda Motor plans to switch some car production from Mexico and Canada to the United States, aiming for 90% of cars sold in the country to be made locally, the Nikkei newspaper reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-make-90-us-sales-locally-by-relocating-mexico-canada-production-nikkei-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UCZFTQD7NKXXBQZUINZBN3M4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:15:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软签署大额碳清除协议，支持 AtmosClear 的路易斯安那项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司周二表示，它与路易斯安那州的一个项目签订了合同，该项目将在 15 年内清除 675 万公吨二氧化碳，微软称这是迄今为止世界上最大的永久性碳清除项目。【原文：Microsoft said on Tuesday it signed a contract for a project in Louisiana that would remove 6.75 million metric tons of carbon dioxide over 15 years, which it says is the world's biggest permanent carbon removal project to date.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/microsoft-signs-large-carbon-removal-deal-backing-atmosclears-louisiana-project-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AX5JGS6KENLUXCDN3M6LPH3BXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普贸易战导致对华高粱销售减少，但美国农民计划种植更多高粱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）与中国的贸易战对堪萨斯州丹-阿特金森（Dan Atkisson）这样的高粱种植者来说恰逢其时，尽管如此，他仍准备在今年春季将种植面积增加 25%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war with China comes at a bad time for sorghum growers like Dan Atkisson in Kansas, who is nevertheless preparing to increase plantings by 25% this spring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-trade-war-dries-up-sorghum-sales-china-us-farmers-plan-plant-more-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VN6XCSYNGZPP5GR6XAQGNFWBMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将收紧电动汽车电池规定以降低起火和爆炸风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国正在加强对电池动力汽车的监管，并将要求汽车制造商遵守更高的电池安全标准，旨在降低这一快速增长行业的火灾和爆炸风险。【原文：China is tightening regulations on battery-powered vehicles and will require its automakers to comply with higher battery safety standards, aiming to reduce risks of fire and explosions in the fast-growing sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-tighten-ev-battery-rules-reduce-fire-explosion-risks-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3Y6IFTTIVL27LHMXZ7NUTSWUY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称巴基斯坦考虑进口美国石油以缓解贸易不平衡]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位直接参与该提案的政府消息人士和一位炼油厂高管透露，巴基斯坦正在考虑首次从美国进口原油，以抵消因美国提高关税而导致的贸易不平衡。【原文：Pakistan is considering importing crude oil from the United States for the first time to offset a trade imbalance that triggered higher U.S. tariffs, according to a government source directly involved with the proposal and a refinery executive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pakistan-mulls-us-oil-imports-ease-trade-imbalance-sources-say-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMCE3LCAXBKWDIQC4YE7N66OR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[妮维雅生产商拜尔斯道夫第一季度销售额小幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国消费品制造商拜尔斯道夫（Beiersdorf）周二公布的集团销售额略高于市场预期。【原文：German consumer goods maker Beiersdorf , the first European large-cap global health and personal care company to report first-quarter results, on Tuesday posted group sales marginally ahead of market expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nivea-maker-beiersdorf-posts-marginal-first-quarter-sales-beat-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUDUASWQQFMRJNVQKOBKUCSJFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络中断后，Binance 服务开始恢复]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Binance 在 X 上发文称，亚马逊网络服务数据中心的一个临时问题暂时中断了该平台的订单和取款服务，此后，Binance 的服务已开始恢复和复原。【原文：Crypto exchange Binance's services have started to resume and recover after a temporary issue involving a Amazon Web Services data center temporarily disrupted the platform servicing orders and withdrawals, it said in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/binance-services-start-recover-after-network-interruption-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V46GYLYYIJORJGT4FFKOC77UX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:27:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，中国下令停止波音飞机的交付]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周二援引知情人士的话称，中国已下令其航空公司不再接收任何波音喷气式飞机，以回应美国对中国商品征收 145% 关税的决定。【原文：China has ordered its airlines not to take any further deliveries of Boeing jets in response to the U.S. decision to impose 145% tariffs on Chinese goods, Bloomberg News said on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/china-orders-halts-boeing-jet-deliveries-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYCRTHR4HRJW5CSQQIWNK6U3OQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国最大的贸易博览会上，出口商称美国市场被 "冻结 "了]]></title><description><![CDATA[Candice Li 说，华盛顿对中国商品加征 145% 的关税后，她的公司生产的医疗器械在美国的订单消失了。【原文：Candice Li says that after Washington raised tariffs on Chinese goods by 145%, U.S. orders for the medical devices her firm is making have vanished.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-largest-trade-fair-exporters-say-us-markets-are-frozen-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAIOKK6DORKAPJRRO45B2APUNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:14:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本竞争监督机构向谷歌发出停止令]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本竞争监督机构周二向 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司发出了停止和终止反竞争行为的命令，这是首次对美国科技巨头采取此类行动。【原文：Japan's competition watchdog issued a cease and desist order to Alphabet's Google on Tuesday for anticompetitive practices in the first such action against a U.S. tech giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/japan-competition-watchdog-issues-cease-desist-order-google-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPEPBURS25IUHAHEMWLB674NR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:24:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奢侈品巨头路威酩轩集团第一季度销售额不及预期，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的奢侈品集团路威酩轩集团（LVMH）公布的第一季度收入低于预期，该集团股价周二下滑。【原文：LVMH shares slid lower on Tuesday after the world's largest luxury group posted first quarter revenues that undershot expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lvmh-shares-slump-after-luxury-giants-q1-sales-miss-forecast-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMTFT3XRBZOVZKP6Z5HIPKSB64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行调查显示，全球投资者抛售美股的速度创下纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美银全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）周二表示，全球投资者在过去两个月中减持美股的数量创下历史新高，并认为引发全球经济衰退的贸易战是市场面临的最大风险、【原文：Global investors have slashed their holdings of U.S. stocks by a record amount in the past two months, and think a trade war that triggers global recession is the biggest risk for markets, BofA Global Research said on Tuesday,】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-investors-dump-holdings-us-stocks-record-pace-bofa-survey-says-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFR54KS2ZJMGDFHVYWAYHTDI4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>