<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:46:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:46:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司预测 2024 年夏季旅行人数将创历史新高，比 2023 年增长 6.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个代表美国主要航空公司的组织预测，夏季旅行人数将创历史新高，预计将运送 2.71 亿人次，同比增长 6.3%。【原文：A group representing major U.S. airlines forecast record summer travel with carriers expected to transport 271 million passengers, up 6.3%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-forecast-record-2024-summer-travel-up-63-over-2023-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J52Y3IHADNPDVCAGJAKLJRV6CI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席鲍威尔PPI "好坏参半"，下一步不太可能是加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周二表示，最新的美国生产者价格报告 "喜忧参半"，而非 "热火朝天"，因为即使4月份的数据高于预期，此前的数据也被下调了。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Tuesday said the latest report on U.S. producer prices was more "mixed" than "hot" given that prior data was revised lower even as the figures for April came in higher than expected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-ppi-mixed-next-move-unlikely-be-rate-hike-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4Y7U7UN4FMP5FPVZ5ORGX2PLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:32:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓总裁敦促盎格鲁投资者考虑收购利益]]></title><description><![CDATA[必和必拓首席执行官迈克-亨利（Mike Henry）说，英美资源集团的投资者需要考虑必和必拓收购其在伦敦上市的较小竞争对手的利弊，他试图为这项已被拒绝两次的提议争取支持。【原文：BHP Chief Executive Mike Henry said that Anglo American investors need to consider the merits of his company's bid for its smaller London-listed rival, seeking to drum up support for a proposal that has been rejected twice.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bhp-chief-urges-anglo-investors-consider-takeover-benefits-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWONFMB6NNKOBI3LRYI4Y4OKCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:21:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉因加州工厂排放废气被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉被一家非营利性环保组织起诉，该组织指控埃隆-马斯克的电动汽车公司数百次违反联邦《清洁空气法》，让其位于加利福尼亚州弗里蒙特的工厂排放有害污染物。【原文：Tesla has been sued by an environmental nonprofit that accused Elon Musk's electric car company of violating the federal Clean Air Act hundreds of times by letting its Fremont, California, plant emit harmful pollutants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tesla-is-sued-over-emissions-california-plant-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ECY5WGS7VIAFH3FIHHW4ACIR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊云计算部门首席执行官亚当-塞利普斯基将卸任，马特-加曼将接替其职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）云计算部门亚马逊网络服务公司（Amazon Web Services）首席执行官亚当-塞利普斯基（Adam Selipsky）周二表示，他即将卸任。【原文：The chief executive of Amazon.com's cloud unit Amazon Web Services, Adam Selipsky, is stepping down, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazons-cloud-unit-ceo-step-down-firm-says-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTJZDSDQE5OU7MCZXNR3X7EVMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中美需要对其他车辆和产品征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前总统唐纳德-特朗普说，拜登政府对中国电动汽车、半导体和医疗产品征收的新关税应适用于其他类型的汽车和产品。【原文：Former U.S. President Donald Trump said the Biden administration's new tariffs on Chinese electric vehicles, semiconductors and medical products should be applied to other types of vehicles and products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-us-china-tariffs-needed-other-vehicles-products-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTYECDTFV5KDVOVY4CHOQDN5KQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[七国集团讨论美国对华加征关税后的全球贸易风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利经济部长吉安卡洛-乔盖蒂（Giancarlo Giorgetti）表示，下周在意大利举行的七国集团（G7）主要民主国家会议将讨论在美国对中国征收 "非常严厉 "的关税之后全球贸易出现分裂的风险。【原文：The Group of Seven (G7) major democracies meeting in Italy next week will discuss the risk of fragmentation in global trade after "very tough" tariffs imposed by the United States against China, Italian Economy Minister Giancarlo Giorgetti said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/g7-discuss-global-trade-risks-after-us-tariffs-china-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPEVZV7ASJN2RC2JZ7MB4CZY3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司第一季度出现净亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司周二报告称，第一季度经常性净亏损为 1.302 亿雷亚尔（约合 2539 万美元），在去年同期净利润为 1.364 亿雷亚尔之后，该公司再次陷入亏损。【原文：Brazilian airline Gol reported on Tuesday a first-quarter recurring net loss of 130.2 million reais ($25.39 million), swinging into the red after a 136.4 million-real net profit a year ago, mainly hit by financial expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazil-airline-gol-swings-net-loss-first-quarter-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHXBOFOR4VPRVNZCW4GP2FNPLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:55:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，英美资源集团探讨将戴比尔斯公司首次公开募股作为分拆的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士周二告诉路透社，英美资源集团正在探讨旗下钻石业务戴比尔斯公司的首次公开募股，其中一位人士说，伦敦是首选地点。【原文：Anglo American is exploring an initial public offering of its diamond business De Beers, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Tuesday, with London the preferred venue, one of them said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/anglo-american-explores-de-beers-ipo-part-break-up-sources-say-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYTSBYEDQVIPFKUHVG3QY3MWQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员减少对美联储 9 月开始降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在一份政府报告显示 4 月份批发价格涨幅超过预期后，交易员们减少了对美联储将在 9 月份首次降息的押注。【原文：Traders on Tuesday pared bets the Federal Reserve will deliver a first interest-rate cut in September after a government report showed wholesale prices rose more than expected in April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/traders-pare-bets-sept-start-fed-rate-cuts-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEC57UNBAJLJPKZ3GSNGJQPMME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月份生产者价格增幅高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于服务和商品成本涨势强劲，4 月份美国生产者价格涨幅超过预期，表明第二季度初期通胀依然高企。【原文：U.S. producer prices increased more than expected in April amid strong gains in the costs of services and goods, indicating that inflation remained elevated early in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-producer-prices-increase-more-than-expected-april-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKICRA5ELRMW5LKI3HHP67NEGM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:42:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[跑步鞋需求强劲，On Holding 上调年度销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[On Holding 周二上调了全年销售预期，此前该公司第一季度的销售额超出预期，原因是这家运动服装生产商专注于销售高价产品，并引入了新产品，这有助于吸引顾客。【原文：On Holding raised its annual sales forecast on Tuesday, after beating expectations for the first quarter, as the sportswear maker's focus on selling premium-priced products and bringing in newer items helped attract customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/holding-raises-annual-sales-forecast-strong-running-shoes-demand-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KINQYWXOTZJFFAREXIWZFN53VU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国强烈反对美国提高关税，承诺采取维权措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周二表示，中国坚决反对美国加征关税，并誓言将采取果断措施捍卫自身权益。【原文：China strongly opposed the United States' tariff hikes, its commerce ministry said on Tuesday, vowing it will take resolute measures to defend its rights and interests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-strongly-opposes-us-tariff-hikes-pledging-measures-defend-rights-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSN53G5D7RPLFHSL4ERU27367E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝洁公司计划在巴黎奥运会期间的广告中淡化公司名称]]></title><description><![CDATA[2024 年巴黎奥运会缺少了什么？宝洁公司向运动员母亲致敬的催人泪下的企业广告。【原文：What is missing from the Paris 2024 Olympics? A tear-jerking corporate advertising campaign from Procter &amp; Gamble saluting the mothers of athletes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pg-plans-downplay-its-corporate-name-ads-during-paris-olympics-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X7YRCPPGANKXXKHQOWSKGPPUG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典特斯拉罢工升温，全国最大工会加入战局]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典最大的工会周二表示支持特斯拉机械师长达六个月的罢工，这使得这家声名狼藉、对工会避之唯恐不及的公司与致力于集体谈判的北欧劳动力之间的冲突升级。【原文：Sweden's biggest union on Tuesday threw its weight behind a six-month-old strike by mechanics at Tesla , escalating a conflict the notoriously union-shy company is facing with a Nordic labour force committed to collective bargaining.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-strike-sweden-heats-up-nations-largest-union-joins-fray-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAAU7X6X6JNWRG7B5ZXRFLIUZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息押注减弱，提振美国国债收益率预期：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，在通胀持续走高以及金融市场更加确信美联储今年将减少降息次数的情况下，债券策略师们将未来几个月的美国国债收益率预期上调至至少11月以来的最高水平。【原文：Bond strategists upgraded their U.S. Treasury yield forecasts for coming months to their highest since at least November amid sticky inflation and greater conviction in financial markets of fewer Federal Reserve rate cuts this year, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/waning-fed-rate-cut-bets-boost-us-treasury-yield-forecasts-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIP6DD4HFVNRZO3O4M6JRQVQPI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hazeltree 称雪佛龙是四月份被抛售最多的股票，超过了特斯拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据和技术公司 Hazeltree 的月度报告显示，由于做空者加大了对能源价格疲软的押注，石油公司雪佛龙成为 4 月份被做空最多的美股，超过了长期以来的头号目标特斯拉。【原文：Oil company Chevron was the most shorted U.S. stock in April, overtaking long-standing top target Tesla as short-sellers up their bets on weaker energy prices, according to a monthly report by data and tech firm Hazeltree.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/chevron-tops-tesla-most-shorted-stock-april-says-hazeltree-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMGRF4MPN5JBXHLBT6GAKAMSSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:40:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷通胀率接近 300%，物价上涨略有放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管有积极的减速迹象，但阿根廷的物价仍在攀升，当阿根廷政府周二公布最新数据时，这个饱受困扰的南美国家的年通货膨胀率将逼近 300%。【原文：Prices in Argentina are climbing, despite positive signs of a deceleration, with the embattled South American country's annual inflation rate set to edge closer to 300% when the government reveals the latest data on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-inflation-nears-300-climb-prices-slows-bit-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2VR2VHG7FLCPN7ACIQVFBZU54</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alphabet 将在开发者大会上展示人工智能创新成果]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 预计将在本周二宣布如何在其各项业务中发展人工智能，而在此前一天，OpenAI 展示了一个新的人工智能模型，该模型除文本外还能处理声音和图像。【原文：Alphabet is expected to announce on Tuesday how it is building on artificial intelligence across its businesses, a day after OpenAI demonstrated a new AI model that can work with sound and images in addition to text.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alphabet-spotlight-ai-innovations-developer-conference-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOOGOKZDAJPWPIN7PW6UUO6WLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:04:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美电动汽车贸易战威胁拜登的清洁汽车议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府计划对中国电动汽车和电池征收新的高额关税，这将暂时保护美国汽车业的就业，但有可能牺牲白宫通过加快美国电动汽车的采用来应对气候变化的努力。【原文：The Biden administration's plan to slap heavy new tariffs on Chinese electric vehicles and batteries would provide temporary protection for U.S. auto jobs, potentially at the expense of White House efforts to fight climate change by accelerating U.S. EV adoption.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-china-ev-trade-war-threatens-bidens-clean-car-agenda-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FKTAVXU7BJDTPXKQBCGVVMWKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蚂蚁金服集团利润下降 19% 至 78.7 亿元人民币]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社根据阿里巴巴集团控股公司周二发布的财报计算显示，在截至12月31日的三个月里，中国蚂蚁金服集团的净利润下降了19%，为78.7亿元人民币（合10.9亿美元）。【原文：China's Ant Group posted a 19% fall in net profit of 7.87 billion yuan ($1.09 billion) in the three months to Dec. 31, according to Reuters calculations based on Alibaba Group Holding's earnings released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ant-group-profit-down-19-787-bln-yuan-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3PYP67V6FKFJOAVRKPFFNXRSA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:55:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西化妆品制造商 Natura 第一季度净亏损扩大，但利润率上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西化妆品生产商 Natura &amp;Co 周一晚些时候公布，公司第一季度净亏损 9.349 亿雷亚尔（1.8129 亿美元），大于去年同期的 6.52 亿雷亚尔亏损额。【原文：Brazilian cosmetics maker Natura &amp;Co reported late on Monday a net loss of 934.9 million reais ($181.29 million) for the first quarter, larger than the 652 million-real loss it had posted a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/brazil-cosmetics-maker-natura-widens-net-loss-q1-margins-rise-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZH4TPPAHZJI5NYPKXZPPMD55Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国阿里巴巴季度收入超预期，利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国阿里巴巴集团周二公布的第四季度营收超出分析师预期，原因是该公司为应对谨慎的消费支出而专注于低价商品，这有助于提高三个月的国内电子商务销售额。【原文：China's Alibaba Group Holding beat analysts' estimates for fourth-quarter revenue on Tuesday, as a focus on low-cost goods in response to cautious consumer spending helped boost domestic e-commerce sales in the three-month period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinas-alibaba-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCIZHQT5BFPMRONXZFRM5XEYZM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:33:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 通胀警戒下的单边行情]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHXNNC3XYZOULHQHOA26FVFMFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:11:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克坚持石油需求观点，认为经济有潜在上升空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克周二坚持其对2024年全球石油需求相对强劲增长的预测，并表示今年世界经济有可能好于预期。【原文：OPEC stuck to its forecast for relatively strong growth in global oil demand in 2024 on Tuesday and said there was a chance the world economy could do better than expected this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-sticks-oil-demand-view-sees-potential-economic-upside-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7AX2FL5C5NOBFRWH4VAKLKCU4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得宝季度可比销售额降幅大于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，家得宝公布的季度同店销售额降幅大于预期，原因是谨慎的房主减少了大件商品的购买，而将重点放在了小规模维修上。【原文：Home Depot posted a bigger-than-expected drop in quarterly same-store sales on Tuesday as cautious homeowners shelled out less for big-ticket purchases while focusing on small-scale repairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/home-depot-posts-bigger-than-expected-quarterly-comparable-sales-drop-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZIDC4MEBBO5BNJSUP65LV5BYM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表建议提高关税以应对中国的 "不公平 "做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表凯瑟琳-戴周二建议提高对一系列中国商品的关税，称需要采取更多行动来解决中国的技术转让政策和做法对美国工人和公司造成的损害。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Katherine Tai on Tuesday recommended raising tariffs on a range of Chinese goods, saying additional actions were needed to address China's technology transfer policies and practices that harmed U.S. workers and companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-trade-chief-recommends-higher-tariffs-address-chinas-unfair-practices-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVPEXG3HTRMCZLYED3BWJXQMDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月小型企业景气指数回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项调查显示，4月份美国小企业信心增强，计划提价的企业主比例为一年来最小，但持续的劳动力短缺继续给企业主带来成本压力。【原文：U.S. small-business confidence increased in April and the share of owners planning to raise prices was the smallest in a year, but persistent labor shortages continued to exert cost pressures for owners, a survey showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-small-business-sentiment-rebounds-april-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIXYFIGI6FM6LNMWF4ST6AGPT4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登对中国商品征收的新关税是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[乔-拜登总统将对 180 亿美元的中国商品加征关税，包括电动汽车、电池、半导体、钢铁、铝、关键矿产、太阳能电池、船岸起重机和医疗产品，同时保留特朗普时代对超过 3000 亿美元商品加征的关税。【原文：President Joe Biden is hiking tariffs on $18 billion in Chinese goods including electric vehicles, batteries, semiconductors, steel, aluminum, critical minerals, solar cells, ship-to-shore cranes, and medical products, while retaining Trump-era tariffs on over $300 billion in goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/what-are-bidens-new-tariffs-china-goods-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5L7RUGDPL5IBBL4ABQSJ3A7Z6A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 09:57:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 和 AMC 大涨唤起了 2021 年备忘录股票传奇]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 和 AMC 的股价在周二的盘前交易中分别大涨近 40%，有望延续一天前的涨势，当时 "咆哮的凯蒂猫 "发布的一系列帖子重新点燃了涨势，让人联想起漫画股的交易狂潮。【原文：Shares of GameStop and AMC jumped nearly 40% each in premarket trading on Tuesday, and are on track to extend gains from a day earlier when a series of posts from "Roaring Kitty" rekindled a rally reminiscent of the meme stocks trading frenzy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestop-amc-surge-evokes-2021-meme-stocks-saga-2024-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JH7I7MEKQVOAZBDX4GRW7RVE5I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 09:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>