<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:05:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:05:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货上涨，焦点转向主要财报和美联储会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货走高，因为投资者在等待多家公司的财报以及当天晚些时候开始的美联储政策会议。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Tuesday as investors awaited earnings reports from a number of companies and the Federal Reserve's policy meeting that starts later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-rise-focus-shifts-major-earnings-fed-meeting-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA4EJDZRKFKJTLUCD7FAPEUJNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，波音/萨博正在与 BAE 就英国喷气教练机竞标进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的人士透露，波音和瑞典萨博公司正在与英国 BAE 系统公司谈判，商讨未来联手研制英国鹰式教练机的替代品，以填补快速喷气机行业日益增长的空白。【原文：Boeing and Sweden's Saab are in talks with Britain's BAE Systems about teaming up on a future replacement of Britain's Hawk trainer in a growing niche of the fast jet industry, three people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeingsaab-talks-with-bae-uk-jet-trainer-bid-sources-say-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54I2U2UYLVOA3HEYND5LUDUTKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:45:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯国际航空公司取消更多航班，但称网络攻击后航班计划已 "稳定 "下来]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯航空公司周二又取消了数十个航班，但表示在一天前遭受重大网络攻击后，该公司现已稳定了航班计划。【原文：Russian airline Aeroflot cancelled dozens more flights on Tuesday but said it had now stabilised its schedule after a major cyberattack a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russias-aeroflot-cancels-more-flights-says-schedule-is-now-stabilised-after-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UONU5PN7Q5ODTLFQNK6KFQLBXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰总理称美国关税可能导致波兰损失超过 20 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰总理唐纳德-图斯克周二表示，据初步估计，美国对欧洲产品征收的新关税可能使波兰损失约80亿兹罗提（合21.6亿美元）。【原文：The new U.S. tariffs on European products could cost Poland around 8 billion zlotys ($2.16 billion), according to preliminary estimates, Polish Prime Minister Donald Tusk said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/poland-could-lose-over-2-billion-due-us-tariffs-pm-says-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DZ5G22QJNNTJMVTQGFOQUUPUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:12:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者组织称，美国联邦消费者保护委员会超过 3.6 亿美元的消费者赔款 "面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[据支持消费者的组织周二发布的一份分析报告称，美国消费者金融保护局推翻了数十项执法行动，导致据称受到金融公司伤害的消费者损失超过 3.6 亿美元的赔偿金。【原文：The reversal of dozens of enforcement actions by the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau has jeopardized more than $360 million in compensation to consumers allegedly harmed by financial companies, according to an analysis released Tuesday by pro-consumer organizations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/more-than-360-mln-cfpb-consumer-payouts-at-risk-consumer-groups-say-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JD4Z46LUVNOK7G3MN6UMGPQ4JM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月旅游预订量反弹，企业收入前景看好]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司和西南航空公司等航空公司以及希尔顿全球酒店集团和温德姆酒店集团等酒店运营商集体松了一口气，因为在今年早些时候许多人暂停度假计划后，有预算意识的美国人又开始预订旅行了。【原文：U.S. travel companies including air carriers United Airlines and Southwest Airlines and hotel operators Hilton Worldwide and Wyndham Hotels have issued a collective sigh of relief as budget-conscious Americans have started booking travel again after many put vacation plans on pause earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-travel-bookings-rebound-august-boosting-companies-revenue-outlook-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2KHZUMDKRKFFM4UVCBYC6JQOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:08:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 Telegram 群组中分享中国妇女的剥削性图片的报道在中国引起愤怒]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国媒体报道，中国女性的性剥削图片在加密的 Telegram 聊天群组中被数十万用户分享，在网上引发了广泛的愤怒。【原文：Sexually exploitative images of Chinese women were shared in encrypted Telegram chat groups with hundreds of thousands of users, Chinese media reported, triggering widespread outrage online.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/outrage-china-after-reports-exploitative-images-chinese-women-shared-telegram-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDM3PHOCA5K3TKL2KPH5MZL6BA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:42:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美在斯德哥尔摩恢复谈判以缓解关税敌对状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国官员周二在斯德哥尔摩开始了第二天的会谈，以解决长期存在的经济纠纷，从世界两大经济体之间不断升级的贸易战中后退。【原文：U.S. and Chinese officials began a second day of talks in Stockholm on Tuesday to resolve longstanding economic disputes and step back from an escalating trade war between the world's two biggest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-resume-talks-stockholm-ease-tariff-hostilities-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODMYJWOGTVKJBFW7OEJWLTTTEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能需求强劲，Advantest 将全年营业利润预期上调 24]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本芯片测试设备制造商 Advantest 周二将全年营业利润预期上调了 24%，原因是人工智能所用半导体的需求强劲。【原文：Japanese chip testing equipment maker Advantest raised on Tuesday its full-year operating profit forecast by 24% due to robust demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/advantest-raises-full-year-operating-profit-forecast-by-24-strong-ai-demand-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKHLFW6IEBNGLBVUFDS6IZOCTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:12:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称美国贸易协议缓解了关税不确定性，但风险依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本周二表示，它与美国达成的贸易协议消除了美国贸易政策的不确定性，但需要继续关注这些政策给日本经济带来下行压力的风险。【原文：Japan said on Tuesday the trade agreement it struck with the U.S. cleared uncertainties on U.S. trade policies but continued attention needs to be given to risks of those policies putting downward pressure on the Japanese economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-says-us-trade-deal-eases-tariff-uncertainties-risks-remain-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ6R4TGLPJPJDMJ4QMNKKVEL6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉称仅美国关税不会引发欧盟评级下调]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉（Fitch）周二表示，美国大幅提高对欧盟成员国的贸易关税不会立即引发主权评级下调，但会加剧现有压力。【原文：The sharp increase in U.S. trade tariffs on European Union member countries won't trigger immediate sovereign rating cut, but could compound existing pressures, Fitch said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fitch-says-us-tariffs-alone-wont-trigger-eu-rating-downgrades-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODI3EI5SVRKXPNFWPGMNQ4EA3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:01:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙黑橄榄出口商在美国新关税下举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[自美国总统唐纳德-特朗普上任以来，西班牙的黑橄榄出口商一直被征收苛刻的关税，他们警告说，根据欧盟与美国达成的最新贸易协议，他们现在将面临额外 15%的关税，这将使他们难以生存。【原文：Spain's black olive exporters, subject to harsh tariffs since U.S. President Donald Trump's first term, are warning it will be difficult to survive an extra 15% they now face under the European Union's latest trade deal with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spains-black-olive-exporters-struggle-under-fresh-us-tariffs-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RVGAKW3ARZKWXKQ2I2MSYRNXIU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 新任首席执行官认为，要修复公司还需做出更多 "艰难决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 周二表示，尽管面临越来越多的不利因素，但该公司预计下半年净营收将有所增长，营业收入利润率也将达到较低的个位数。【原文：Stellantis said on Tuesday it expected higher net revenue and a low-single digit operating income margin in the second half despite increasing headwinds, as the automaker aimed for a gradual recovery after a tough first half.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-new-ceo-sees-more-tough-decisions-fix-company-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXKYADDXQFIHVPRM4TYS32HLIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:14:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩联社：三星电子总裁前往华盛顿支持美国贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据韩联社报道，三星电子董事长李在镕周二登上了飞往华盛顿的航班。【原文：The chairman of Samsung Electronics , Jay Y. Lee, boarded a flight to Washington on Tuesday, the Yonhap News Agency reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-electronics-chief-heads-washington-support-us-trade-talks-yonhap-says-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACB7LRSDBRMTPGWLL452BY36LI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于 iGaming 和体育博彩业增长强劲，BetMGM 上调了 2025 年业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国体育博彩服务公司 BetMGM 是 Entain 和美高梅国际酒店集团（MGM Resorts）的合资企业，受惠于在线体育博彩和 iGaming 部门的强劲需求，该公司上调了 2025 年全年收入和核心盈利预期，上半年收入增长了 35%。【原文：U.S. sports-betting service BetMGM, a joint venture between Entain and MGM Resorts , has raised its full-year 2025 revenue and core earnings forecast after posting a 35% rise in first-half revenue, helped by strong demand in online sports betting and its iGaming division.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/betmgm-raises-2025-forecast-strong-igaming-sports-betting-growth-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36JFWWURKFKVFC76BKF3YQBA3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:58:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[野村录得首季最高利润，增幅达 52]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本野村控股公司（Nomura Holdings）表示，第一季度利润激增 52%，其交易和投资银行部门在全球市场动荡的情况下表现稳健，同时还受益于房地产销售的一次性收益。【原文：Japan's Nomura Holdings said first-quarter profit surged 52% with its trading and investment banking divisions putting in a solid showing amid volatile global markets, while it also benefited from a one-off gain on a property sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/nomura-logs-highest-profit-first-quarter-with-52-jump-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJQWJ6SO3JMRPCNM3NNZ3SIOW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:39:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国豆粕供应过剩引发美国大豆出口季节前的需求疑虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易消息人士称，在今年晚些时候的美国销售旺季期间，中国对大豆的需求可能会减弱，因为2025年早些时候创纪录的进口量和动物饲料生产商不温不火的需求已经推高了国内的豆粕库存。【原文：China's appetite for soybeans is likely to weaken during the peak U.S. marketing season later this year, as record imports earlier in 2025 and tepid demand from animal feed producers have pushed up soymeal inventories at home, trade sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-soymeal-glut-raises-demand-doubts-ahead-us-soybean-export-season-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LA5Y3JENZZJWHHXQ46Z7PBF2KE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:35:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯 Yandex 公司摆脱亏损，实现第二季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯互联网巨头 Yandex 公司周二表示，该公司从第一季度的净亏损中反弹，第二季度调整后净利润同比增长 34%，达到 304 亿卢布（约合 3.7461 亿美元）。【原文：Russian internet giant Yandex bounced back from a first-quarter net loss to report a 34% year-on-year rise in second-quarter adjusted net profit to 30.4 billion roubles ($374.61 million), the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russias-yandex-rebounds-loss-post-q2-profit-growth-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBFDKXYB2VLYLHRGBRA5WFGNME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱利润增长 23%，特朗普关税动荡提振交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国巴克莱银行周二表示，上半年利润增长了 23%，好于预期，其市场业务从美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易关税引发的疯狂交易活动中获得了丰厚的回报。【原文：Barclays first-half profit rose by a better-than-expected 23%, the British bank said on Tuesday, with its markets business reaping bumper returns from the frenzied trading activity sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump's trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-profit-up-23-trump-tariff-turmoil-lifts-trading-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TT7EVQ4S2BPURHCUWCBAOX5XQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯利康第二季度利润超出预期，维持业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康周二公布的第二季度财报超出预期，主要癌症、心脏病和肾病药物销售强劲，但由于定价压力和全球贸易风险仍是挑战，阿斯利康维持全年业绩预期。【原文：AstraZeneca beat second-quarter earnings expectations on Tuesday, helped by strong sales of key cancer, heart and kidney disease drugs, but maintained its full-year forecast as pricing pressures and global trade risks remain challenges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-beats-second-quarter-profit-expectations-maintains-outlook-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBANH7MDJFPN5EY6SZWYISKC6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 预计下半年将逐步复苏并做出更多 "艰难决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 周二表示，尽管面临越来越多的不利因素，该公司下半年的净收入仍将增加，营业收入利润率也将达到较低的个位数。【原文：Stellantis guided on Tuesday for increased net revenues and a low-single digit operating income margin in the second half despite increasing headwinds, as the automaker aims for a gradual recovery after a tough first half.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-expects-gradual-recovery-h2-more-tough-decisions-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMXV3WSOTNPARAXMDYJUZU6VKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:03:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世创电子材料下调全年业绩指导]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国半导体材料供应商世创电子材料（Siltronic）周二下调了年度销售指导，原因是其半导体业务持续疲软，客户库存居高不下。【原文：German semiconductor materials supplier Siltronic on Tuesday cut its annual sales guidance, amid continued weakness in its semiconductor business and high customer inventories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siltronic-lowers-full-year-guidance-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJIBB27XGJJGRO3JYLQDYXABKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标牢记关税的弊端]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3INILKKLTNPHNGNO24V7APHWXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 04:37:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，瑞银命令银行家减少复杂货币产品的销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周二报道，在客户因美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的 "解放日 "关税声明而遭受重大损失后，瑞银已下令银行家缩减复杂货币衍生品的销售。【原文：UBS has ordered bankers to scale back sales of complex currency derivatives after its clients suffered heavy losses due to U.S. President Donald Trump's "Liberation day" tariff announcements, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ubs-orders-bankers-scale-back-sale-complex-currency-products-ft-reports-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ID5LVAYFWFK6FE4GCSSDFRLLJQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 04:15:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长称泰美贸易谈判应在 8 月 1 日前结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国财政部长周二表示，泰国与美国的贸易谈判有望在 8 月 1 日前结束，美国对泰国征收的关税预计不会高达 36%。【原文：Thailand's trade talks with the United States are expected to be concluded before August 1, and U.S. tariffs on the country are not expected to be as high as 36%, its finance minister said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thailand-us-trade-talks-should-be-concluded-before-august-1-minister-says-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOXMQ4YC5JOVPN6ZJ7DW4CMPLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:58:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗宣布将研究领域扩展至私营企业，主要是科技公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团（Citigroup）周二表示，它正在扩大其研究覆盖范围，将私营公司纳入其中，重点关注快速增长的科技公司，这与摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）的类似策略如出一辙，据报道，摩根大通已开始覆盖非上市公司。【原文：Citigroup said on Tuesday it is expanding its research coverage to include private companies, with a focus on rapidly growing tech firms, mirroring a similar strategy by JPMorgan Chase, which has reportedly begun covering non-listed firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-announces-research-expansion-into-private-industry-mostly-tech-firms-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6G5DA7WRVFIJ5HUMRATNPYBQ6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:49:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前日本央行副行长中佐认为美元霸权存在 "裂痕]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行前副行长中曾宏（Hiroshi Nakaso）表示，美元将继续保持其作为全球主要货币的霸主地位，但美元地位出现的 "裂痕 "将促使投资者继续分散投资其他货币。【原文：The dollar will retain its supremacy as a key global currency but "cracks" appearing in its status will prod investors to continue diversifying into other currencies, said former Bank of Japan Deputy Governor Hiroshi Nakaso.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ex-boj-deputy-chief-nakaso-sees-cracks-dollars-supremacy-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RQN57HYZFNNAZDTDFP2M4IC2JI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:04:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息称因中国需求强劲，英伟达向台积电订购 30 万颗 H20 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，Nvidia 上周向合约制造商台积电下达了 30 万套 H20 芯片组的订单。【原文：Nvidia placed orders for 300,000 H20 chipsets with contract manufacturer TSMC last week, two sources said, with one of them adding that strong Chinese demand had led the U.S. firm to change its mind about just relying on its existing stockpile.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-orders-300000-h20-chips-tsmc-due-robust-china-demand-sources-say-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LU6RMLBXV5P5ZAL4EEUKPEBWIA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中央电视台报道：中国长安汽车重组为独立的国有汽车制造商]]></title><description><![CDATA[据国家电视台 CCTV 周二报道，长安汽车已开始作为一家由中国中央政府控制的独立汽车制造商运营。【原文：Changan Automobile has begun operating as an independent automaker controlled by China's central government, state television CCTV reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-changan-restructured-independent-state-owned-automaker-cctv-reports-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOBNKEUGWJN6PHTMQXQWFYRYM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:03:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：本周日本脆弱债券市场的利害关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本债券市场本周面临严峻考验，既有国内政治动荡和央行可能的鹰派转变，也有美联储带来的全球风险。【原文：Japan's bond market faces stern tests this week, from domestic political ructions and a possible hawkish shift at the central bank to global risks stemming from the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/whats-stake-japans-fragile-bond-market-this-week-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7OZBETRAZIVFMYWOAGSY33QG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:58:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>