<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:40:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:40:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与YouTube儿童隐私诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌将支付 3,000 万美元来解决一起诉讼，该诉讼称谷歌未经家长同意收集儿童的个人信息，并利用这些信息发送有针对性的广告，从而侵犯了使用 YouTube 的儿童的隐私权。【原文：Google will pay $30 million to settle a lawsuit claiming it violated the privacy of children using YouTube by collecting their personal information without parental consent, and using it to send targeted ads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-settles-youtube-childrens-privacy-lawsuit-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLDK6YR2XVLRJCNW4VM4EDDPMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西银行准备在美国制裁辩论中处理 "复杂 "问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西银行（Banco do Brasil）周二表示，该行已准备好处理涉及全球法规的 "复杂、敏感 "问题，因为最高法院的一位法官裁定，外国法律不能自动适用于巴西。【原文：Banco do Brasil said on Tuesday it is prepared to deal with "complex, sensitive" issues involving global regulations after a top court justice ruled foreign laws cannot be automatically applied in Brazil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/banco-do-brasil-ready-handle-complex-issues-amid-debate-over-us-sanctions-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVNJK5UJWZKUZOMNK5STCLIFXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国豆农敦促特朗普与中国达成采购协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国大豆种植农在周二的一封信中敦促唐纳德-特朗普总统与中国达成一项贸易协议，以确保重要的大豆采购协议，并警告说如果中国继续回避美国大豆作物，长期的经济后果将不堪设想。【原文：U.S. soybean farmers urged President Donald Trump in a Tuesday letter to reach a trade deal with China that secures significant soybean purchase agreements, warning of dire long-term economic outcomes if the country continues to shun the U.S. crop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-soybean-farmers-urge-trump-make-purchase-deal-with-china-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDEF65KKTZPXNAR6HIR7CCMO2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称去年美国石油天然气并购活动增加两倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二发布的一份报告显示，尽管大宗商品价格走软，但由于能源公司增加支出以提高效率和利润，去年美国石油和天然气行业的并购活动增加了两倍。【原文：Mergers and acquisitions in the U.S. oil and gas sector tripled last year despite softer commodity prices as energy companies boosted spending to improve efficiency and profits, according to a report released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-oil-gas-ma-activity-tripled-last-year-report-says-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKDRB2IDMNJV7N6X7J73UOCX2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在钢铝关税清单中增加 407 个产品类别]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周二宣布，在征收关税的 "衍生 "钢铁和铝产品清单中增加 407 个产品类别。【原文：The U.S. Department of Commerce on Tuesday announced the addition of 407 product categories to its list of "derivative" steel and aluminum products subject to tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-adds-407-product-categories-steel-aluminum-tariffs-list-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAC7CZE4QFPBHLKVX3A53FJIKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:43:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，Toms Capital 在收购 CSX 股份后寻求与 CSX 会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士透露，对冲基金汤姆士资本投资管理公司（Toms Capital Investment Management）最近买入美国铁路运营商 CSX 的股份后，已要求与该公司董事会会面，这引发了该公司可能推动合并的猜测。【原文：Hedge fund Toms Capital Investment Management has requested to meet with the board at U.S. railroad operator CSX after recently buying a stake, people familiar with the matter said, raising speculation the firm may push for a possible merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/toms-capital-seeks-csx-meeting-after-acquiring-stake-sources-say-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOWCV4RDTRKG5HZGASB6NQM2MI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Booking.com 母公司与得克萨斯州达成 950 万美元 "垃圾费 "和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Booking.com和其他旅游网站的母公司将支付950万美元，以了结德克萨斯州的诉讼。德克萨斯州的诉讼称，Booking.com通过省略强制性费用，以不存在的虚假低价诱骗消费者，从而对酒店客房进行欺骗性营销。【原文：The parent of Booking.com and other travel websites will pay $9.5 million to settle Texas' lawsuit claiming it deceptively marketed hotel rooms by omitting mandatory fees, enticing consumers with artificially low prices that didn't exist.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/bookingcom-parent-enters-95-million-junk-fee-settlement-with-texas-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6J7Y6TWTRMQPNBHEZNL5M6QM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管有特朗普的命令，但仅有 35 起关于去职的投诉涉及政治偏见]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局的数据显示，在过去 13 年里，向该局详细投诉支票或储蓄账户被关闭的客户中，只有不到百分之一的人指责银行出于政治或宗教原因行事，尽管白宫正在发起一场运动，以杜绝金融系统中的 "系统性滥用 "行为，并称这些行为损害了保守派的利益。【原文：Less than one percent of customers who filed detailed complaints about checking or savings account closures with the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau over the last 13 years accused banks of acting for political or religious reasons, even as the White House mounts a campaign to stamp out "systemic abuses" in the financial system that it says have wronged conservatives, a review of the agency's data shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/just-35-complaints-debanking-cite-political-bias-despite-trump-order-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WI3HEPIF65MDFN2YY6M2UQ54FQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定：特斯拉司机可就自动驾驶索赔提起集体诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉必须面对加州司机提出的经认证的集体诉讼，这些司机称伊隆-马斯克在其公司电动汽车的自动驾驶功能方面误导他们长达八年之久。【原文：Tesla must face a certified class action by California drivers who said Elon Musk misled them for eight years about the self-driving capabilities of his company's electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tesla-drivers-can-pursue-class-action-over-self-driving-claims-judge-rules-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDGMWHJO5VJ7BIZROE62GEVVIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：美国对英特尔的投资旨在帮助公司稳定发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，美国对英特尔的任何投资都将旨在帮助这家陷入困境的芯片制造商稳定下来，商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）也表示，政府希望通过参股来换取对半导体制造商的支持。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Tuesday said any U.S. investment in Intel would be aimed at helping the troubled chipmaker stabilize, as Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said the government wanted equity stakes in exchange for its support of semiconductor manufacturers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-investment-intel-would-be-aimed-helping-company-stabilize-bessent-says-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5II6ENAIVPTPBGZ4C6SWLUY7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帕利哈皮蒂亚重返 SPAC 市场，为美国例外论提交 IPO 申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[风险投资者查马特-帕利哈皮蒂亚（Chamath Palihapitiya）因其高调的空头支票交易而被誉为华尔街的 "SPAC之王"，他即将把自己最新的特殊目的收购工具上市，这标志着他时隔多年后重返市场。【原文：Venture investor Chamath Palihapitiya, dubbed Wall Street's "SPAC king" for his high-profile blank-check deals, is set to take his latest special purpose acquisition vehicle public, marking his return to the market after several years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/palihapitiya-returns-spac-market-with-american-exceptionalisms-ipo-filing-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROZTQMVNRNI5TIQWLJ7BQDYC6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长表示，土耳其计划在 10 月举行 5G 频率招标]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其交通和基础设施部长周二表示，土耳其计划于 10 月份启动期待已久的 5G 频率招标，预计将于 2026 年提供初始服务。【原文：Turkey plans to launch a long-awaited 5G frequency tender in October with initial service expected to be available in 2026, its transport and infrastructure minister said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/turkey-aims-hold-5g-frequency-tender-october-minister-says-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N22XZQVWYBO7RDT32NDHZAWBDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月独户住宅开工和许可均有增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管高抵押贷款利率和经济不确定性继续阻碍购房，但 7 月份美国新建独栋住宅的破土动工率和未来建筑许可仍有所上升。【原文：Groundbreaking for new U.S. single-family homes and permits for future construction rose in July even as high mortgage rates and economic uncertainty continued to hamper home purchases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-single-family-starts-permits-rise-july-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVDEKHDYQFMBFBJZBYEH55SPXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司 Tether 聘请前白宫加密货币顾问 Bo Hines]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币公司 Tether 周二表示，该公司已任命前白宫加密货币政策执行官博-海因斯（Bo Hines）为战略顾问，帮助指导其在美国的扩张。【原文：Cryptocurrency firm Tether has appointed former White House crypto policy executive Bo Hines as a strategic adviser to help steer its expansion in the United States, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/crypto-firm-tether-hires-ex-white-house-crypto-adviser-bo-hines-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRQIBWYYHVK6JEIADKMOSFC5SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nexstar 将以 35.4 亿美元收购规模较小的竞争对手 Tegna，这是一项大型地方电视台交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nexstar Media 已同意以 35.4 亿美元的价格收购规模较小的竞争对手 Tegna，从而打造出一家地方电视台巨头，力图更好地与大型科技公司和全国性媒体争夺广告资金。【原文：Nexstar Media has agreed to buy smaller rival Tegna for $3.54 billion, creating a local-TV powerhouse that seeks to compete better with Big Tech and national media for advertising dollars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/nexstar-buy-smaller-rival-tegna-354-billion-big-local-tv-deal-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZIWXEZ6WJIXHHESAA6PEFDF7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟称已将贸易和关税联合声明草案发回美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人在周二举行的每日新闻发布会上说，欧盟委员会上周收到了美国政府发来的一份文本，其中就贸易和关税问题联合声明的定稿提出了建议。【原文：The European Commission, which last week received a text from the U.S. administration with suggestions about finalising a joint statement on trade and tariffs, has sent back the draft to the US, a European Commission spokesman said during a daily press conference on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-says-draft-joint-statement-trade-tariffs-sent-back-us-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJJOJCJXWZKK3O53J7ZQDKWL4E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:16:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑山公司将以 36 亿美元收购公用事业公司西北能源公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[公用事业公司布莱克希尔斯周二表示，将以 36 亿美元的价格收购同行西北能源集团。【原文：Utility company Black Hills said on Tuesday it would buy peer NorthWestern Energy Group for $3.6 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/black-hills-buy-utility-firm-northwestern-energy-36-billion-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2C4NBOZZGVOFBLRX5WFMHL2HBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百威啤酒制造商安海斯-布希公司将向美国啤酒厂投资 1,500 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[安海斯-布希-英博（Anheuser-Busch InBev）周二表示，在唐纳德-特朗普总统推动提高国内产量之际，该公司将向其美国啤酒厂投资 1,500 万美元。【原文：Anheuser-Busch InBev , said on Tuesday that it would invest $15 million in its U.S. brewery, at a time when President Donald Trump is pushing to boost domestic production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/budweiser-maker-anheuser-busch-invest-15-million-us-brewery-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWCCMPXAA5IVLCICWY2ZJAUVTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲第二季度企业利润前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，最新的盈利预测显示，欧洲企业的健康前景略有恶化，这标志着在连续几周的改善之后，欧洲企业的发展方向发生了改变。【原文：The outlook for European corporate health has slightly deteriorated, the latest earnings forecasts showed on Tuesday, marking a change of direction after several weeks of improvement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-second-quarter-corporate-profit-outlook-dips-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXP5DQUYTJLKJCLSWVSE55SWKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻谨慎对待乌克兰，关注杰克逊霍尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2CNLOREEZPFTOHAPU4QIG6XFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车需求强劲，中国新鹏预计季度收入翻番]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商新鹏汽车周二预测，尽管经济形势严峻，但该公司第三季度的收入将翻一番，并押注于汽车交付量的激增。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle maker Xpeng on Tuesday forecast third-quarter revenue would double, betting on surging deliveries of its cars despite challenging economic conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-xpeng-expects-quarterly-revenue-double-strong-demand-its-evs-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3UXZUCHSNMELHE5Y426C3IPFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:37:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士刀具制造商考虑转移生产以缓解美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士军刀制造商 Victorinox 公司首席执行官告诉《Wirtschaftswoche》商业杂志，该公司正在考虑将部分生产转移到美国，以减少进口关税对其业务的影响。【原文：Victorinox, maker of Swiss army knives, is considering moving part of its production to the United States to lessen the impact of import tariffs on its business, the company's CEO told the Wirtschaftswoche business magazine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swiss-knife-maker-considers-production-shift-ease-us-tariffs-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WFBA7RDPZP2FG4SC22JRERA44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税让黑人美容企业岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年夏初，34 岁的达吉亚-布莱克谢尔-卡洛维开始注意到，她的老客户不再像以前那样经常光顾她的美发沙龙了。【原文：Earlier this summer, Dajiah Blackshear-Calloway, 34, started to notice that her regular clients weren't visiting her hair salon as often as they used to.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-tariffs-are-leaving-black-beauty-businesses-peril-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REYDIE4NKRLN3E4ILB333MW6G4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:17:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，中国爱奇艺为在香港二次上市向银行申请高达 3 亿美元的资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，中国视频流媒体平台爱奇艺已邀请美国银行、中金公司和摩根大通为其在香港的第二次上市工作提供服务，这次上市可能会融资 2 亿至 3 亿美元。【原文：Chinese video streaming platform iQIYI has tapped Bank of America, CICC and JPMorgan to work on its Hong Kong second listing that could raise between $200 million and $300 million, said two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinas-iqiyi-taps-banks-up-300-million-hong-kong-second-listing-sources-say-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UP5YFWAYRII7DYWRX7VF3OZ6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:14:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的利率要求让 "财政主导权 "成为市场焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国债务的膨胀和白宫对美联储降息的倚重，投资者正在权衡 "财政主导 "的风险。【原文：As U.S. debt swells and the White House leans on the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates, investors are weighing the risk of "fiscal dominance," a scenario where keeping government financing cheap eclipses the fight against inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-interest-rate-demands-put-fiscal-dominance-market-spotlight-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JESEBDWUZZISZOBLCT6K3YBI4Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:13:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在人工智能热潮中，Databricks 最新融资估值超过 1000 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Databricks 周二表示，它正在筹集新的资金，这将使这家数据分析公司的估值超过 1,000 亿美元，这距离上一轮融资不到一年时间，因为投资者对人工智能公司的胃口依然强劲。【原文：Databricks said on Tuesday it was raising new funds that would value the data analytics firm at more than $100 billion, less than a year after its previous round, as investor appetite for artificial intelligence companies remains strong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/databricks-valued-over-100-billion-latest-fundraising-amid-ai-rush-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAMFFSDRDFPBXPRW6653FBYYGE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售业盈利和美联储评论公布前，华尔街期货低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货走势低迷，投资者在等待主要零售商的财报，以了解美国消费者的健康状况，同时也在等待美联储定于本周晚些时候召开的重要会议。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were muted on Tuesday as investors awaited earnings reports from major retailers for insights on the health of the American consumer, and a key Federal Reserve conference scheduled later in the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-subdued-ahead-retail-earnings-fed-commentary-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSJ6ESAYUJP5DAPZTNXDFXVCME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:12:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大项目需求低迷，家得宝季度业绩不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，家得宝公司（Home Depot）第二季度销售额和利润均未达到分析师预期，原因是注重价格的房主减少了大规模装修支出，转而专注于自己动手项目。【原文：Home Depot missed analysts' estimates for second-quarter sales and profit on Tuesday, as price-conscious homeowners reined in spending on large-scale renovations and focused on do-it-yourself projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/home-depot-misses-quarterly-estimates-muted-demand-big-ticket-projects-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LS2BFWDO2ZMCHBLWYRTK3YKSC4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:06:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社/益普索民意调查发现，美国人担心人工智能会永久取代工人的工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社/益普索（Reuters/Ipsos）的一项最新民意调查显示，美国人对人工智能的进步可能导致全国大部分地区永久性失业的前景深感忧虑。【原文：Americans are deeply concerned over the prospect that advances in artificial intelligence could put swaths of the country out of work permanently, according to a new Reuters/Ipsos poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/americans-fear-ai-permanently-displacing-workers-reutersipsos-poll-finds-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHT66JUHHNML3PL3ZS2APJKNCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面对特朗普关税，印度虾农考虑转行]]></title><description><![CDATA[在印度南部海岸，V. Srinivas 靠养殖对虾茁壮成长了二十年，印度也因此成为美国的顶级美食供应国。现在，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）50%的关税威胁正迫使许多人考虑其他赚钱方式。【原文：On India's southern coast, V. Srinivas thrived for two decades by farming shrimp, as the country became the top supplier of the delicacy to the United States. Now, Donald Trump's 50% tariff threat is forcing many to consider other ways of making money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/facing-trump-tariffs-indias-shrimp-farmers-consider-switching-other-businesses-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTDKWA2NZFMUNOF24RZWXJOQOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>