<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:19:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:19:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔首席执行官称公司因缺乏信任而拒绝 Venture Global 成为液化天然气供应商]]></title><description><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）首席执行官帕特里克-普亚内（Patrick Pouyanné）周三告诉路透社，道达尔能源公司拒绝了成为 Venture Global LNG 美国终端长期客户的机会，因为道达尔能源公司不信任该公司。【原文：TotalEnergies rejected opportunities to become a long-term customer of Venture Global LNG's U.S. terminals because it did not trust the company, CEO Patrick Pouyanné told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/total-ceo-says-company-rejected-venture-global-lng-supplier-over-lack-trust-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHS5UMY6DVI2BB3STKQ4TGTEQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行准备降息，但通胀忧虑挥之不去]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行看来将在周四降息，这是自 2020 年 COVID-19 大流行刚刚开始以来的第三次降息，因为它既要帮助疲软的经济，又要应对仍然强劲的通胀压力。【原文：The Bank of England looks set to cut interest rates on Thursday for only the third time since just after the start of the COVID-19 pandemic in 2020, as it juggles the need to help the sluggish economy with still-strong inflation pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/bank-england-poised-cut-rates-inflation-worries-linger-2025-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6UGY6QHUJPO3BZB35ZDFC2EZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚企业的高估值面临关键的盈利考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周，澳大利亚企业将全面公布半年财报，虽然预计会有小幅增长，但交易员们将仔细研究利润是否能证明拉伸的估值是合理的，尤其是在面临美国关税等挑战的情况下。【原文：Corporate Australia kicks off its half-year earnings in full swing next week, and while modest growth is expected, traders will scrutinise whether profits justify stretched valuations, particularly in the face of challenges including U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australian-companies-high-valuations-face-crucial-earnings-test-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBBL6F7EQVNH3KK73KEIKU6SJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年初，花旗集团晋升了 8500 多名员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周三在其网站上发表声明称，作为年终工作的一部分，截至 1 月 1 日，花旗集团晋升了 8500 多名员工。【原文：Citigroup promoted more than 8,500 workers as of January 1 as part of its year-end process, the bank said in a statement on its website on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-promoted-more-than-8500-employees-start-2025-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUASDSMR2RPOPHD6JGRORAM75Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业削减 IT 支出，Cognizant 预测 2025 年收入低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对未来降息路径的不确定性迫使企业减少在 IT 服务和咨询方面的支出，Cognizant Technology Solutions 周三预测的年度收入低于预期。【原文：Cognizant Technology Solutions forecast annual revenue below estimates on Wednesday, as uncertainty about the path of future interest rate cuts forces companies to temper spending on IT services and consultancy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cognizant-forecasts-2025-revenue-below-estimates-businesses-temper-it-spending-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWLDYI2E3JO5PB4UQK3ZZCJPKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:23:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[McKesson 第三季度营收不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[药品分销商麦可森公司周三公布的第三季度营收不及预期，原因是包括品牌药和特药在内的美国医药部门的销售额低于预期。【原文：Drug distributor McKesson missed estimates for third-quarter revenue on Wednesday, hurt by less-than-expected sales in its U.S. pharmaceutical segment, which includes branded and specialty drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/mckesson-misses-third-quarter-revenue-estimates-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWV3M37GUJKKFAU3DQY6IAYP3A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:05:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全州保险公司因承保实力和投资收益而实现季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[受惠于承保业务的强劲增长和投资回报率的提高，财产和意外事故保险公司全州保险（Allstate）周三公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Property and casualty insurer Allstate's fourth-quarter profit beat Wall Street expectations on Wednesday, helped by strong gains in its underwriting business and higher returns on its investments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/insurer-allstates-quarterly-profit-beats-underwriting-strength-investment-gains-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6XCQJC2P5KDRBVR54PGYTODRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新闻集团业绩超预期，得益于数字不动产业务的强劲增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[新闻集团周三公布的第二季度业绩超过了分析师的预期，原因是数字房地产、图书出版和道琼斯业务部门的增长帮助抵消了新闻媒体部门增长放缓的影响。【原文：News Corp reported second-quarter results that beat analysts' estimates on Wednesday, as growth in its digital real estate, book publishing and Dow Jones segments help offset its slowing news media segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/news-corp-beats-results-helped-by-robust-growth-digital-real-estate-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PLUFJAYZ5OHDIP2NSU2PXN4AY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:51:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保费和投资收益强劲，大都会人寿第四季度利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[大都会人寿保险公司（MetLife）周三公布，由于保费和投资收入增加，第四季度利润有所增长。【原文：MetLife on Wednesday reported a rise in its fourth-quarter profit as it earned more in premiums and investment income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/metlife-fourth-quarter-profit-jumps-strong-premiums-investment-income-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQP2HX6APNNC7JTWXDP3PAAWDI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥官员称墨西哥和美国同意进行经济对话]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥外贸部副部长路易斯-罗森多-古铁雷斯（Luis Rosendo Gutierrez）表示，他于周三在白宫会见了美国政府高级官员，双方同意就经济问题进行持续、公开的对话。【原文：Mexican Deputy Foreign Trade Minister Luis Rosendo Gutierrez said he met with senior U.S. government officials at the White House on Wednesday and both sides agreed to ongoing and open dialogue on economic issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-us-agree-economic-dialogue-mexican-official-says-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI6RZA4Q4JKNRJFET4GKLWHWEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司称 Arm 已撤回违约索赔，不打算终止许可协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[高通公司首席执行官克里斯蒂安诺-阿蒙（Cristiano Amon）周三表示，Arm 控股公司已撤回终止高通公司与该技术供应商许可协议的威胁。【原文：Qualcomm's Chief Executive Officer Cristiano Amon on Wednesday said Arm Holdings has withdrawn a threat to terminate Qualcomm's license agreement with the technology provider.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qualcomm-says-arm-has-withdrawn-breach-claims-has-no-plans-terminate-license-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WG55PCGECBKOVORM4HDMUHRYOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 22:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储发布 2025 年银行压力测试方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三宣布，作为美国中央银行年度压力测试的一部分，将对大银行进行商业和住宅房地产市场的压力测试。【原文：The Federal Reserve announced on Wednesday it would be testing big banks against heightened stress in commercial and residential real estate markets as part of the U.S. central bank's annual stress tests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-releases-2025-bank-stress-test-scenarios-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJHXBABUS5IJXBJXF47VTWZ3AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:59:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔能源首席执行官加倍看好美国液化天然气市场，淡化特朗普关税担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）首席执行官周三对路透社表示，未来十年该公司将扩大在美国液化天然气领域的投资，以巩固其作为美国液化天然气主要出口商的地位。【原文：TotalEnergies will expand its investment in U.S. liquefied natural gas over the next decade as the French company seeks to cement its position as a major exporter of U.S. LNG, its CEO told Reuters on Wednesday, dismissing fears by American market watchers that more exports could boost U.S. gas prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/totalenergies-ceo-doubles-down-us-lng-downplays-trump-tariff-fears-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBLDFK6C5NOIRCC32WLNGV2YXY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标在不确定的迷雾中看到积极因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphics-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LZEVX2KARLODOUUJRZ7VIG5MI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长贝森特表示，征收关税旨在让制造业回归美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三告诉《福克斯商业》（Fox Business），美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税计划主要是为了让制造业回归美国，他特别指出医疗用品和造船业是目标行业。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff plans are largely aimed at bringing manufacturing back to the United States, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Fox Business on Wednesday, singling out medical supplies and shipbuilding as targeted sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/treasury-secretary-bessent-says-tariffs-aimed-bringing-manufacturing-back-us-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DO7ZVPPBFFMMTNNLXQN5U2J6AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Corteva 公布第四季度亏损减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农用化学品公司 Corteva 周三公布，由于销售量强劲，第四季度亏损有所减少。【原文：U.S. agrichemicals firm Corteva posted a smaller fourth-quarter loss on Wednesday, helped by strong sales volumes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/corteva-reports-smaller-fourth-quarter-loss-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBWKAZFVPRJMLNWDSQYAVH4C7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特预计 2025 年电动汽车亏损将增加，第四季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司周三预计，其电动汽车和软件业务今年将出现高达 55 亿美元的亏损，亏损额与去年相近，这表明削减电池动力车型的成本面临严重困难。【原文：Ford Motor on Wednesday projected up to $5.5 billion in losses on its electric vehicle and software operations this year, a loss similar to last year and a sign of the severe difficulties in cutting costs on battery-powered models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-projects-mounting-ev-losses-2025-q4-profit-up-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SH7K5EOBGNLSBCAJMZ5SODZDKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片技术供应商 Arm 收窄全年业绩预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片技术提供商 Arm Holdings 周三表示，该公司将不再达到此前全年指导目标的上限，但第四季度业绩略高于华尔街预期。【原文：Chip tech provider Arm Holdings , said on Wednesday it will no longer meet the top end of its previous full-year guidance, but slightly topped Wall Street's fourth-quarter expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chip-tech-provider-arm-forecasts-quarterly-revenue-above-expectations-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECTFJBVVMRONRIOKJYK4TWGBBA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能推动智能手机销量增长，高通公司业绩和预测超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[高通公司（Qualcomm）周三预测销售额和利润将超过分析师预期，因为人工智能功能有助于推动采用其芯片的智能手机、笔记本电脑和其他终端的销售。【原文：Qualcomm on Wednesday forecast sales and profits above analyst expectations as artificial intelligence features helped drive sales of the smartphones, laptops and other devices powered by its chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qualcomm-results-forecast-top-expectations-ai-drives-smartphone-sales-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ON5N67WERKFHBBUN4TDAYHYY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对中国的关注增加了中国特殊贸易地位终结的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易专家说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国贸易行为的抱怨增加了美国废除与中国自由贸易的一项已有25年历史的法律的可能性，此举可能会将关税平均提高到61%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's complaints about China's trade practices have increased the odds that a 25-year-old U.S. law that established free trade with Beijing is repealed, trade experts said, a move that could raise tariffs to 61% on average.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trumps-china-focus-increases-odds-its-special-trading-status-could-end-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCMTMLAFLRLXLGG6DTE43WGTT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：谷歌取消多元化招聘目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司正在取消从历史上代表性不足的群体中雇佣更多员工的目标，并正在重新审视其部分多元化、公平和包容性举措。【原文：Alphabet's Google is scrapping its goal to hire more employees from historically underrepresented groups and is reviewing some of its diversity, equity and inclusion initiatives, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-scraps-diversity-based-hiring-targets-wsj-reports-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNS2T2KT2FOPRODMVB47M2C6E4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:28:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康向美国证券交易委员会提出对比尔-阿克曼在 X 公司任职的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资人比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）在社交媒体平台 X 上发布了一篇现已删除的帖子，称他将做空这家医疗保健集团，联合健康已就此事联系了美国证券交易委员会。【原文：UnitedHealth has reached out to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission about billionaire investor Bill Ackman's now-deleted post on social media platform X that said he would take a short position in the healthcare conglomerate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-raises-concerns-over-bill-ackmans-post-x-with-sec-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJDUXIQTR5PUNAVYJ5ZLKBJ5VE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比警告关税对通胀的潜在影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周三警告说，忽视关税对通胀的潜在影响将是一个错误，他引用了 COVID-19 大流行病的经验，即供应链中断导致通胀上升。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee warned on Wednesday that ignoring the potential inflationary impact of tariffs would be a mistake, citing the COVID-19 pandemic experience where supply chain disruptions drove up inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-warns-potential-inflationary-impact-tariffs-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CN5GVMDRQNP2LCSA7O3Z7ICJYI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 19:32:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士：银行向投资者出售马斯克 55 亿美元的 X 债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士透露，以摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）为首的银行已经出售了约 130 亿美元债务中的 55 亿美元，这些债务是为了支持埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）在 2022 年以 440 亿美元收购 Twitter（现名 X）。【原文：Banks led by Morgan Stanley have sold $5.5 billion of some $13 billion of debt they lent to support Elon Musk's $44 billion acquisition of Twitter, now called X, in 2022, said a source with knowledge of the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/banks-sell-down-55-bln-musks-x-debt-investors-source-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2N2AFYOCBPVHDFCM34OTECHTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 19:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，马斯克将回避任何冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫发言人卡罗琳-利维特（Karoline Leavitt）周三表示，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）将回避他的各种商业利益与他为联邦政府削减成本所做努力之间的任何利益冲突。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk will excuse himself from any conflicts of interest between his various business interests and his efforts to cut costs for the federal government, White House spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/musk-will-excuse-himself-any-conflicts-white-house-says-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGCSJZ6UXNMEVDBPYHXDLSSOEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道亚马逊将发布拖延已久的 Alexa 生成式人工智能改进版]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士表示，亚马逊将发布其期待已久但迟迟未推出的人工智能语音服务 Alexa，并已安排在本月晚些时候举行新闻发布会，对其进行预览。【原文：Amazon is set to release its long-awaited - and delayed - Alexa generative artificial intelligence voice service, said three people familiar with the matter, and has scheduled a press event for later this month to preview it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-set-release-long-delayed-alexa-generative-ai-revamp-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TUTUA2ASJICJNBOMUBYFUDXRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微策略公司通过品牌重塑加深对比特币的关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币最大的企业持有者微策略公司（MicroStrategy）周三表示，该公司现在将以 "策略 "的名义运营，并公布了一个新的标识，以强调其对加密货币领域的承诺。【原文：MicroStrategy , the biggest corporate holder of bitcoin , said on Wednesday it would now operate as "Strategy" and unveiled a new logo to emphasize its commitment to the cryptocurrency space.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microstrategy-deepens-bitcoin-focus-with-rebrand-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6CCDOPFQVPCXHX4OJQY7OI67I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:35:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，LME场内经纪商Sigma寻求出售金属部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，Sigma Broking 是伦敦金属交易所允许在公开市场交易的八家会员之一，该公司在加入三年后正试图出售其基本金属业务。【原文：Sigma Broking, one of eight members of the London Metal Exchange allowed to trade on the open-outcry floor, is trying to sell its base metals business three years after joining, two sources with knowledge of the situation said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/lme-floor-broker-sigma-seeking-sell-metals-unit-sources-say-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYT44SWXD5N6RFPZD3HWASUF7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:26:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称贝莱德准备在欧洲推出比特币交易所交易产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，贝莱德正准备在几周内在欧洲推出一款比特币交易所交易产品，因为资金经理和消费者对加密货币的需求都在不断增长。【原文：BlackRock is gearing up to launch a bitcoin exchange-traded product in Europe within weeks, a source familiar with the matter told Reuters, amid growing demand for exposure to cryptocurrencies from both money managers and consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/blackrock-prepares-launch-bitcoin-exchange-traded-product-europe-source-says-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYUFS2JILVMDFK4E22NOCZ5OIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国就特朗普关税发起世贸组织争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于日内瓦的世界贸易组织（WTO）周三表示，中国已就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国商品征收关税一事向该组织发起争端。【原文：China has launched a dispute at the World Trade Organization (WTO) over tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump on Chinese goods, the Geneva-based body said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-launches-wto-dispute-over-trump-tariffs-2025-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTZDT6P3KNPMPHYL3OCOA3F6CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:20:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>