<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:04:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:04:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[全球股市因收益率下降和中国经济增长而跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于债券收益率下降、中国经济增长数据强于预期以及乐观的盈利支撑了风险资产，周五全球股市上涨，扩大了周涨幅。【原文：Global equities rose on Friday, adding to weekly gains, as declining bond yields, stronger than expected Chinese growth figures and upbeat earnings supported riskier assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6XWIFFNVFLJVKFT7FANZHIMHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:57:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者保护局就 Equifax 处理消费者纠纷问题罚款 1500 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局周五宣布对信用报告局 Equifax 罚款 1500 万美元，原因是该局未能充分调查消费者对其信用报告的争议。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau announced on Friday it had fined credit reporting bureau Equifax $15 million for failing to sufficiently investigate consumer disputes of its credit reports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumer-bureau-fines-equifax-15-million-issues-fixing-consumer-disputes-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HFVLFCT4FOU7JFJL6WTHZIFGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行和美林证券将支付 6000 万美元和解美国证券交易委员会的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）周五表示，富国银行的两家咨询公司和美林证券已同意支付合计 6000 万美元的民事罚款，以了结对合规失误的指控。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday said a pair of Wells Fargo Advisory firms and Merrill Lynch have agreed to pay a combined $60 million in civil penalties to settle charges over compliance failures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-firms-merrill-lynch-pay-60-mln-settle-sec-charges-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOKXCUDOGNNQPDA5OSGVXQFMTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[健身饮料公司 Celsius 将支付 300 万美元罚款，以了结美国证券交易委员会的会计案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周五表示，健身饮料公司 Celsius Holdings 将支付 300 万美元的民事罚款，以解决对其不当核算股票奖励的指控。【原文：Celsius Holdings , the fitness beverage company, will pay a $3 million civil fine to resolve charges it accounted improperly for stock-based awards, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/fitness-beverage-company-celsius-pay-3-million-fine-settle-us-sec-accounting-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQ4GQUUEJFMIBIOZSZCJSYEIYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:26:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国中型银行凭借强劲的手续费收入乘势而上]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国多家银行公布第四季度利润增长，延续了该行业的连胜势头，原因是资本市场的上扬缓解了贷款需求疲软带来的冲击。【原文：A raft of U.S. banks reported higher fourth-quarter profits on Friday, extending a winning streak for the industry as an upswing in capital markets alleviated a hit from weaker loan demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-mid-sized-banks-ride-industry-upswing-robust-fee-income-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3OLHJFGDVIDFD3PCMZMX2MZBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛将首席执行官薪酬提高至 3,900 万美元，准备再执掌高盛五年]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份文件显示，高盛去年将首席执行官大卫-所罗门的薪酬提高了 26%，达到 3900 万美元，董事会还为他准备了 8000 万美元的股票留用奖金，这预示着他将继续执掌高盛 5 年。【原文：Goldman Sachs raised CEO David Solomon's compensation 26% to $39 million for last year, according to a filing, and its board lined up an $80 million stock retention bonus that signals he will stay at the helm for another 5 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-boosts-ceo-pay-39-million-lines-up-five-more-years-helm-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQGSNB4PENIZJNBUPCU5B4XH5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）上调美国经济展望，警告各国反对保护主义和补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五将其对2025年全球经济增长的预测上调了十分之一个百分点，其中美国的增长强于预期，抵消了德国、法国和其他主要经济体下调的预测。【原文：The International Monetary Fund on Friday raised its forecast for global growth in 2025 by one-tenth of a percentage point, with stronger-than-expected growth in the U.S. offsetting downward revisions in Germany, France and other major economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/imf-lifts-us-outlook-warns-countries-against-protectionism-subsidies-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUKBTA7YLZMBLAKH4LEG4YO2J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国的 TikTok 禁令可能与印度的混乱相呼应，因为用户正在寻求各种选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 即将关闭，美国的 TikTok 粉丝们正争先恐后地寻找替代品，保护自己的数字王国，这让人想起印度 2020 年的禁令，一夜之间，该应用从 2 亿用户的生活中消失。【原文：TikTok fans in the U.S. are racing to secure alternatives and safeguard their digital empires ahead of a looming shutdown, evoking the chaos of India's 2020 ban that erased the app from the lives of 200 million users overnight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-tiktok-ban-could-echo-india-chaos-users-seek-options-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4Q2Q2WKVVJT7JJW3ZEASDDIRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月独户住宅新开工面积增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[12 月份，美国单户住宅建设稳健增长，但由于抵押贷款利率上升和市场上新房供应过剩，进一步增长受到限制。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding increased solidly in December, but further gains were seen limited by rising mortgage rates and a glut of new homes on the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-single-family-housing-starts-increase-december-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72WUSUMKZVJ3PCIUDDQP3LIN7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亨廷顿银行因资本市场强劲和利息收入增长而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[亨廷顿银行（Huntington Bancshares）周五公布的第四季度利润增长了两倍多，主要得益于资本市场部门的强劲表现和更高的利息收入。【原文：Huntington Bancshares on Friday reported a more than two-fold rise in its fourth-quarter profit, helped by robust performance in its capital markets unit and a higher interest income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/huntington-bancshares-profit-surges-strong-capital-markets-interest-income-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDRGRP44YFPQDJFKM2WCCJ5M4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bumble 首席执行官莉迪亚妮-琼斯辞职，创始人将担任首席执行官一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[约会应用运营商 Bumble 周五表示，在利迪亚娜-琼斯（Lidiane Jones）辞去首席执行官一职后，其创始人兼执行主席惠特尼-沃尔夫-赫德（Whitney Wolfe Herd）将从 3 月中旬起担任公司首席执行官。【原文：Dating app operator Bumble said on Friday its founder and executive chair, Whitney Wolfe Herd, will become the chief executive of the company from mid-March after Lidiane Jones resigned as CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bumble-ceo-lidiane-jones-resigns-executive-chair-fill-role-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YSIEMCBYJJPPCUKIXYU3NPLJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:38:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私募股权 "二次 "销售创纪录，Ardian 完成 300 亿美元基金募集]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，私募股权基金二级市场的交易量创下历史新高，因为在交易低迷的情况下，收购公司的老板和他们的投资者都在想方设法获取现金。【原文：The secondary market for private equity funds saw record transaction volumes last year as buyout bosses and their investors looked for ways to generate cash amid a downturn in dealmaking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/private-equity-secondary-sales-hit-record-ardian-closes-30-bln-fund-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7BGPXF635J75DZKOL3MQLQ35M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:36:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美 RedNote 用户找到难得的坦诚交流空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[从经济悲观主义到对马克思主义的愤世嫉俗，再到对潜在战争的恐惧，红笔记的中美用户本周进行了罕见的坦诚交流，测试了中国社交媒体平台审查制度的极限。【原文：From economic pessimism to cynicism about Marxism and fears over the potential for war, Chinese and American users of RedNote took part this week in rare candid exchanges that tested the limits of censorship on the Chinese social media platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-us-users-rednote-find-rare-space-candid-exchanges-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIT7MTIBCNIM7JJG7SC5S6OPCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈里王子将与默多克报社对簿公堂]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈里王子对鲁珀特-默多克（Rupert Murdoch）的英国报业集团提起的诉讼于本周二在伦敦高等法院正式开庭，查尔斯国王的小儿子将在下个月的庭审中亲自出庭作证。【原文：Prince Harry's lawsuit against Rupert Murdoch's British newspaper group officially begins at the High Court in London on Tuesday, with King Charles' younger son set to appear as a witness himself at the trial next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/prince-harry-set-court-battle-with-murdoch-papers-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQON62FJ7RNGTMKXDBPGFCRWXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工业安全产品需求低迷，Fastenal业绩未达预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Fastenal 公布的第四季度利润低于分析师预期，原因是建筑行业的持续放缓抑制了对其紧固件和其他安全产品的需求。【原文：Fastenal posted fourth-quarter profit below analysts' estimates on Friday, as a sustained slowdown in construction sector dented demand for its fasteners and other safety products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fastenal-misses-estimates-amid-sluggish-demand-industrial-safety-products-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFGUJ5E3T5IIZF7TUPL3VLSKRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场押注特朗普上台后中国会让人民币贬值，但幅度不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融市场押注，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）第二任总统任期内，中国将不会把人民币作为抵消美国关税预期的政策工具，因为有人认为，像第一任总统任期内那样的大幅贬值对陷入困境的经济弊大于利。【原文：Financial markets are betting China will not use the yuan as a policy tool to offset expected U.S. tariffs in a second Donald Trump presidency, based on a view that sharp depreciation like that seen in his first term will be more harmful than helpful to the struggling economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/markets-are-betting-china-will-let-yuan-fall-trump-takes-power-not-much-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLBUKQSIQRKBXOTGI72YO3B5TQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Truist 因投资银行业务收益而实现超预期的季度利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于资本市场走强，投资银行和交易活动更加活跃，特里斯特金融公司周五公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Truist Financial on Friday exceeded Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit, helped by stronger investment banking and trading activity as capital markets strengthened.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/truist-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-investment-banking-gains-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APKSSZ4YSRJRJONSDMANHGJ4IA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:32:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗证券申请中国证券牌照]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citadel Securities 是全球最大的做市商之一，在其全球首席执行官表示有意进入中国市场约一年后，该公司于周五提交了在中国的证券牌照申请。【原文：Citadel Securities, one of the world's largest market makers, on Friday filed an application for a securities licence in China, about a year after its global CEO expressed interest in entering the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citadel-securities-applies-securities-licence-china-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLN2XXA6YZJJTFENCLF2AC2JMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政策引发通胀忧虑，美联储 1 月将维持利率不变：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社调查，绝大多数经济学家认为，美国联邦储备委员会将在1月29日维持利率稳定，并在3月恢复降息，因为决策者们正在消化华盛顿方面预计将出台的一系列新经济政策。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve will hold interest rates steady on Jan. 29 and resume cutting in March, according to a slim majority of economists polled by Reuters, as policymakers digest an expected barrage of new economic policies from Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-hold-rates-jan-trumps-policies-stir-inflation-worries-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7LBSUIF3ZLYNBHC24RMXCTABY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:16:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟加强对马斯克 X 的调查，提出新要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五表示，正在加紧调查埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体网络 X 是否违反了欧盟关于内容节制的规定，要求该公司提供信息，并命令其保留相关文件。【原文：The European Commission said on Friday it was stepping up its investigation into whether Elon Musk's social media network X breached EU rules on content moderation with requests for information and an order for it to retain relevant documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-steps-up-probe-into-musks-x-with-new-demands-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJ5ICYKQKFPYZMKFCOKWDAH33E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际业务强劲，SLB 季度利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于北美和国际市场对钻井设备和技术的需求增加，这家油田服务供应商的第四季度利润超过了分析师的预期。【原文：SLB beat analysts' estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Friday as the oilfield services provider benefited from higher demand for its drilling equipment and technology in North America and international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/slbs-quarterly-profit-beats-international-business-strength-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOYAOBONBZNXDE42S6SAU6TMOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:57:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典萨博 2024 年有机销售增长高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典防务设备制造商萨博公司周五表示，预计2024年全年的有机销售额将增长23.4%，高于此前预期的15%至20%之间的上限。【原文：Swedish defence equipment maker Saab said on Friday it expected an organic sales growth of 23.4% for the full year of 2024, above its previously expected outlook at the upper end of the range between 15% and 20%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/swedens-saab-posts-higher-than-expected-organic-sales-growth-2024-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4PCRDQ74FL7PPM2TLTS2COTKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:44:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构结束对近 7000 辆菲斯科电动 SUV 的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构周五结束了对 6971 辆菲斯科 Ocean SUV 因不慎启动自动紧急制动系统的调查，因为它预计不会从这家破产的电动汽车制造商那里获得更多信息。【原文：The U.S. auto safety regulator closed its probe into 6,971 Fisker Ocean SUVs on Friday over inadvertent activation of the automatic emergency braking system, as it does not expect to get further information from the bankrupt EV maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-auto-safety-regulator-closes-probe-into-nearly-7000-fisker-electric-suvs-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BM62Y6B52BPT3AQ5LYKXPIA3E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达首席执行官表示不会出席特朗普就职典礼]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋周五表示，他不会出席美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的就职典礼，而是将 "在路上 "与员工及其家人一起庆祝农历新年。【原文：Nvidia's chief executive Jensen Huang said on Friday he will not be attending U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's inauguration, but will instead be "on the road" celebrating the Lunar New Year with employees and their families.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/nvidia-ceo-says-not-attending-trumps-inauguration-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEOR4VHYSVMKDJSEYKDC32BNEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息疑虑重重，美国股票基金资金外流激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月15日的一周内，美国股票基金的资金流出量激增，原因是美联储今年降息的前景黯淡，而投资者对正在进行的季度财报季持谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw a spike in outflows for the week ending Jan. 15, as the outlook for Federal Reserve rate cuts this year had dimmed while investors were cautious about the ongoing quarterly earnings season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-fund-outflows-surged-doubts-over-fed-rate-cuts-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5CVW3I5TRIKNG6FS2KSWC2RIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:35:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局对超过 87 万辆通用汽车展开初步调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，在收到有关通用汽车公司生产的877,710辆汽车发动机故障的报告后，正在对这些汽车展开初步调查。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday it was opening a preliminary probe into 877,710 vehicles manufactured by General Motors , after receiving reports alleging engine failure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-opens-preliminary-probe-into-more-than-870000-gm-vehicles-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QXIZ6BN5JJBPNRWNS7RM6QVLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:25:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 利率上行削弱小盘股力量，小盘股失去特朗普的支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在投资者寻找能在唐纳德-特朗普担任总统期间大放异彩的资产之际，美国股市有望从共和党政策中受益的一个角落却步履蹒跚。【原文：As investors seek assets that will shine under a Donald Trump presidency, one corner of the U.S. stock market expected to benefit from the Republican's policies has been stumbling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-small-caps-lose-trump-bump-rising-rates-sap-strength-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYLDWBOKBRJ6BJR3IAXZJTJZ74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标沃勒和贝森特帮助国债收益率回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7KZW72TOZIRNL2WTYVTEGALWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:16:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关注特朗普就职典礼，期货走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货上扬，S&amp;P 500指数和道指有望创下11月以来的最大单周涨幅，而投资者则在等待即将上任的特朗普政府的一系列政策变化。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged up on Friday, with the S&amp;P 500 and the Dow looking set to log their biggest weekly advances since November, while investors awaited a wave of policy changes under the incoming Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-higher-with-all-eyes-trump-inauguration-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDOSYHZR4ZJSVAQOCKKCT2I7H4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业为节省债务成本而进行的对冲可能加剧了 10 年期债券的抛售]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家和分析师们说，最近几周美国国债市场的抛售很可能因企业计划本月在债券市场上借入近1900亿美元而变得更加严重，这凸显了今年可能持续存在的市场风险。【原文：A sell-off in U.S. Treasury markets in recent weeks was likely made worse by corporate plans to borrow nearly $190 billion in the bond market this month, bankers and analysts said, highlighting a risk for markets that is likely to persist this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/corporate-hedging-save-debt-costs-may-have-worsened-10yr-sell-off-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3C7ZP7GZD5NGVJHB5THELD5UCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>