<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:24:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:24:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油厂努力消化委内瑞拉原油进口的突然激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[据交易员和航运数据显示，自上月委内瑞拉与美国达成20亿美元的旗舰供应协议以来，美国墨西哥湾沿岸的炼油商正努力消化委内瑞拉原油运量的激增，这给油价带来压力，并导致部分原油滞销。【原文：Oil refiners on the U.S. Gulf Coast are struggling to absorb a rapid surge in Venezuelan crude shipments since last month's flagship $2 billion supply deal between Caracas and Washington, pressuring prices and leaving some volumes unsold, according to traders and shipping data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refiners-struggle-absorb-sudden-surge-venezuelan-oil-imports-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMUJ2NSJ7ZPJRIL7XUTMSYN4GY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁激进投资者佩尔茨对更多收购持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者纳尔逊·佩尔茨周二表示，他正寻求回归其创立的Trian基金管理公司的初衷，未来可能直接收购更多公司。【原文：Nelson Peltz is looking to go back to his roots with Trian Fund Management and could buy more companies outright in the future, the billionaire investor said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/billionaire-activist-investor-peltz-open-more-buyouts-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPNIC5LQ35IEZP47SQZOBLW5B4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员称欧洲必须掌控关键技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟金融服务专员周二表示，欧洲必须掌控支撑该地区经济的关键技术，此言呼应了日益高涨的呼声——要求欧盟减少对美国科技巨头的依赖。【原文：Europe must keep control over key technologies that underpin the region's economies, the European Union's Financial Services Commissioner said on Tuesday, adding to growing calls for the bloc to be less reliant on U.S.-based technology giants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/europe-must-keep-control-key-technologies-says-eu-commissioner-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQ6NCMBF5VKIPHYJNECE3SSONU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑石集团的格雷表示，人工智能带来的颠覆性风险是我们最优先考虑的事项。]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大另类资产管理公司黑石集团总裁兼首席运营官乔恩·格雷周二表示，人工智能发展对企业的颠覆性影响是该集团"首要关注事项"。【原文：Disruption to businesses from artificial intelligence development is "top of the page" for Blackstone , the world's largest alternative asset manager, its president and chief operating officer Jon Gray said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackstones-gray-says-ai-disruption-risk-is-top-page-us-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AS4AR7WKCNLHVFUNCCWQLYIGOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帕兰蒂尔股价反弹，此前美国国防开支推动其创纪录季度业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘交易中，Palantir Technologies股价飙升6.9%，投资者押注该公司军用级人工智能工具与服务。此前该公司报告季度销售额激增，得益于美国国防开支的增长。【原文：Shares of Palantir Technologies jumped 6.9% in early trading on Tuesday as investors bet on the company's military-grade AI tools and services after it reported a surge in quarterly sales, boosted by rising U.S. defense spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/palantir-rallies-after-bumper-quarter-fueled-by-us-defense-spending-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7BVST33N5N2RDTVPHM4NCKIY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威盛上海公告称首席财务官因个人原因辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电子公司胜华科技在向上海证券交易所提交的文件中表示，其首席财务官张艳茹因个人原因辞职。【原文：Chinese electronics company Wingtech said in a Shanghai Stock Exchange filing that its chief financial officer Zhang Yanru had resigned, citing personal reasons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/wingtech-shanghai-filing-says-cfo-resigns-personal-reasons-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4G6B43P6RM6DKNDTJZZ7Z3FAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:44:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫会议未能打破美国加密货币立法僵局]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周一召开会议，旨在打破美国主要银行与加密货币公司之间长达数月的僵局，但最终未达成任何协议。这凸显出行业分歧持续威胁着具有里程碑意义的数字资产立法进程。【原文：A White House meeting aimed at breaking a months‑long stalemate between major U.S. banks and cryptocurrency firms ended Monday without any agreement, underscoring industry divisions that continue to threaten progress on landmark digital‑asset legislation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/white-house-meeting-fails-resolve-us-crypto-legislation-stalemate-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTORMPL3ABPQJPONJBEZXS3RF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国配音演员因担忧人工智能训练问题抵制网飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国配音演员协会发言人向路透社透露，德国配音演员已发起一场草根抵制活动，反对网飞平台的一项合同条款——该条款允许流媒体平台将他们的录音用于人工智能训练。【原文：German voice actors have launched a grassroots boycott against Netflix over a contract clause that allows the streaming platform to use their recordings for AI training, a spokesperson for the VDS voice actors' association told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/german-voice-actors-boycott-netflix-over-ai-training-concerns-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCHN2SCYVJLHLAMHOZODCO67GU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，美国住宅建筑商正着手制定计划，拟开发多达100万套"特朗普住宅"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周二报道，住宅开发商正着手制定一项开发近百万套"特朗普住宅"的提案，以应对美国的住房负担能力危机。【原文：Homebuilders are working on a proposal to develop nearly a million "Trump Homes" that would address the U.S. affordability crisis, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-homebuilders-working-plan-develop-many-1-million-trump-homes-bloomberg-news-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K3JLBR22NRIP7LQTKESDS6FWIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院委员会将就致命空中相撞事件举行听证会，国家运输安全委员会主席将出席]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商业委员会宣布，该机构发现美国联邦航空管理局存在一系列系统性失误，导致去年造成67人死亡的空难。为此，委员会计划于2月12日就此事举行听证会，国家运输安全委员会负责人将出席作证。【原文：The U.S. Senate Commerce Committee plans to hold a Feb. 12 hearing with the head of the National Transportation Safety Board after the agency found a series of systemic failures by the Federal Aviation Administration led to a devastating mid-air collision that killed 67 people last year, the committee said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-committee-hold-hearing-with-ntsb-chair-deadly-mid-air-collision-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYTWNOKKEZPJ5HRRUPFYNJIGZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:30:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SpaceX因二级火箭问题暂停猎鹰9号发射任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克的SpaceX公司表示，其主力火箭猎鹰9号因二级火箭出现不明故障而暂停飞行。此前该火箭于周一成功将星链卫星送入轨道。
这枚双级猎鹰9号火箭从南加州执行例行任务，将25颗星链卫星送入太空后，其第二级在按计划准备脱离轨道时"出现异常状态"。SpaceX在X平台发文称，该火箭级在事故后按设计排空了所有剩余燃料。SpaceX表示："团队正在分析数据以确定根本原因和纠正措施，随后将恢复飞行。"
猎鹰9号是全球最活跃的运载火箭——2025年累计执行165次发射任务，其中多数为SpaceX自主实施的星链卫星星座扩容任务。2024年一次导致整批星链卫星损毁的任务失败，是该型号火箭自2016年以来首次遭遇此类事故。
周一的任务虽未失败，但若火箭二级存在的问题得不到解决，可能危及未来卫星的轨道运输，或因飞行器无法正常处置残骸而威胁人口密集区。
猎鹰9号二级火箭主体设计为在将有效载荷送入轨道后重返地球大气层，其发动机可引导残骸落入远离人口密集区的预定区域。SpaceX未透露事故调查将持续多久。负责监管火箭发射活动及其公共安全影响的联邦航空管理局发言人因政府停摆处于强制休假状态，未回应置评请求。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX has paused flights of its workhorse Falcon 9 rocket over an unspecified issue that its second stage experienced after successfully deploying Starlink satellites into orbit on Monday, the company said.
After the two-stage Falcon 9 delivered 25 Starlink satellites to space in a routine mission from southern California, the rocket's second stage "experienced an off-nominal condition" as it prepared to deorbit itself as planned, SpaceX wrote on X, adding the rocket stage emptied all its remaining fuel as designed following a mishap.
"Teams are reviewing data to determine root cause and corrective actions before returning to flight," SpaceX said.
Falcon 9 is the world's most active rocket - it launched 165 times in 2025, most of them in-house SpaceX missions to expand its Starlink constellation. A mission failure in 2024 that doomed a batch of Starlink satellites was SpaceX's first such failure with the rocket since 2016.
Monday's mission was not a mission failure. But a problem with the rocket's second stage, if unchecked, could risk future satellite deliveries to orbit or endanger populated areas if the vehicle fails to properly dispose of itself.
Falcon 9's second stage body is designed to reenter Earth's atmosphere after boosting payloads into orbit, using its engines to target a reentry zone away from populated areas should any components survive deorbit.
SpaceX did not indicate how long its mishap investigation will take. A spokesman for the Federal Aviation Administration, which oversees rocket launch activities and their impact on public safety, was furloughed amid the government shutdown and did not return a request for comment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spacex-grounds-falcon-9-flights-after-second-stage-issue-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDZHQHLGEBJURE6AMR4D4PLQNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元动荡如何成为全球投资者的警钟]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为全球头号储备货币，美元正经历动荡时期。白宫政策举措难以预测，加之市场对美联储独立性的担忧，重新点燃了"抛售美国资产"的交易浪潮。【原文：The dollar, the world's No.1 reserve currency, is having a rocky ride as unpredictable White House policy moves and Federal Reserve independence concerns revive "Sell America" trades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/how-dollar-disorder-could-be-wake-up-call-global-investors-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHMDLOQ27JOCNMP4AMKQLLFZ5E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛市值首次突破万亿美元大关]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛周二成为史上首家市值突破万亿美元的零售企业，其股价在持续一年的上涨行情中累计涨幅近26%。【原文：Walmart became the first retailer ever to hit $1 trillion in market valuation on Tuesday, riding on a year-long rally that has seen its shares rise nearly 26%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-hits-1-trillion-market-value-first-time-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDPU7APUORJK5GTH6GFCNBBEII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:58:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[认识乔希·达马罗——美国主街市长兼迪士尼新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[在乔希·达马罗的世界里，没有谁微不足道。这位华特迪士尼公司的新任首席执行官，既是魔法王国休闲爱好者心中的偶像，也是员工们敬重的领袖。然而，这位54岁的前主题公园负责人接掌大权之际，这家媒体娱乐巨头正面临着堪比太空山过山车般惊险的商业挑战。【原文：No person is too small in Josh D'Amaro's world. The new chief executive of Walt Disney is a celebrity among the Magic Kingdom's recreational devotees and employees alike. Yet the 54-year-old former head of theme parks is stepping into the role as the media and entertainment conglomerate navigates challenges that are the business equivalent of a ride on Space Mountain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/meet-josh-damaro-mayor-main-street-usa-new-disney-ceo-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOSIBAVNGRKR7OCDC6VMA5VK4M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易主管称印度将在与特朗普的协议中保留部分农业保护措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府正着手将周一宣布的印美贸易协议细节落实为书面文件。美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔周二表示，该协议将使印度对美国工业产品的关税从13.5%降至零，同时取消关税，但允许印度维持部分农产品进口保护措施。【原文：The Trump administration is working to put the details of its trade deal with India announced on Monday on paper, but it will reduce India's tariffs on American industrial goods to zero from 13.5% and eliminate duties but allow India to maintain some agricultural import protections, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-trade-chief-says-india-maintain-some-agriculture-protections-deal-with-trump-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQO2EW3WNVJVVPWLBNWWTV7DAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SpaceX收购xAI：关于马斯克旗下初创企业的关键事实]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克周一宣布，SpaceX已通过创纪录的交易收购其人工智能初创公司xAI。此次将火箭卫星公司与Grok聊天机器人的制造商合并，实现了这位亿万富翁在人工智能与太空领域的双重雄心。【原文：Elon Musk said on Monday SpaceX has acquired his artificial intelligence startup xAI in a record-setting deal, unifying the billionaire's AI and space ambitions by combining the rocket-and-satellite company with the maker of the Grok chatbot.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/spacex-acquires-xai-key-facts-about-musk-owned-startups-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSOHF5736FOXFKJZ4BAFROGDSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易谈判代表称最高法院理解关税案的重大利害关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔周二表示，鉴于案件涉及的"巨大"利害关系，最高法院正谨慎处理一起质疑特朗普总统大规模关税合法性的案件。【原文：The Supreme Court is taking its time to rule on a case challenging the legality of President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs given the "enormous" stakes involved, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-trade-negotiator-says-supreme-court-understands-enormous-stakes-tariff-case-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4HUYPVDXJLN7KRNZGFQPYAJVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SLB赢得穆特里巴油田开发下一阶段15亿美元合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[油田服务供应商斯伦贝谢公司周二宣布，科威特石油公司已授予其一份为期五年、价值15亿美元的综合合同，负责科威特穆特里巴油田的生产设计、开发及管理。【原文：Oilfield services provider SLB said on Tuesday that Kuwait Oil Company has awarded it a five-year, $1.5 billion integrated contract to design, develop and manage production at the Mutriba field in Kuwait.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/slb-wins-15-billion-contract-next-phase-mutriba-field-development-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6AS4K3KPROWDP4IGPSAV6JQ2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博罗瑞吉上调年度盈利预期，得益于投资者沟通业务表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融科技公司布罗德里奇金融周二上调全年盈利预期，并公布第二季度利润增长，其投资者通讯业务的强劲表现为公司业绩提供了支撑。【原文：Fintech firm Broadridge Financial raised its full-year earnings forecast and posted a higher second-quarter profit on Tuesday, buoyed by strength in its investor communications business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/broadridge-raises-annual-profit-forecast-investor-communications-strength-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7TFT2WTP5PBFKKFSS6NPXBDV4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于迪士尼新任首席执行官乔希·达马罗的五个关键信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼公司周二任命主题公园业务负责人乔什·达马罗为首席执行官，接替长期掌舵的鲍勃·艾格。在此媒体整合时代，这家娱乐巨头正经历从传统电视向流媒体的转型。【原文：Walt Disney tapped theme-parks chief Josh D'Amaro as CEO on Tuesday, succeeding long-time head Bob Iger as the entertainment giant navigates the shift from linear television to streaming in an era of media consolidation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/five-facts-know-about-disneys-new-ceo-josh-damaro-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIRK4HXI35LJXEOXOFSDPVU3GM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称摩根大通即将推出新兴市场本地货币债券新指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通正敲定一项新指数计划，该指数将追踪前沿市场本地货币债券。知情投资者向路透社透露，该行此举旨在满足投资者对风险更高、更具多样性的高收益债券日益增长的需求。【原文：JPMorgan is finalising plans for a new index to track frontier market local currency bonds, investors consulted on the details told Reuters, as the bank looks to satisfy a growing appetite for riskier and more diversified high-yield debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-closing-new-frontier-market-local-currency-debt-index-sources-say-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOVB57YVWBIH7KQSMQ2ER7WMSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西部数据增持40亿美元回购计划，人工智能推动内存芯片销量增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[西部数据周二表示，其董事会已批准额外40亿美元用于股票回购，因其用于人工智能服务器的内存芯片需求激增。【原文：Western Digital said on Tuesday its board has approved $4 billion more for share repurchases, as demand for its memory chips used in artificial intelligence servers surges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/western-digital-adds-4-billion-buyback-plan-ai-boosts-memory-chip-sales-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMZCRQAU3RI3PNWBW7R4ULELZU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼任命主题公园负责人乔希·达马罗为首席执行官，引领后艾格时代]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼公司周二任命主题公园业务负责人乔希·达马罗为首席执行官，结束了长达数年的继任不确定性。在人工智能浪潮与行业整合浪潮颠覆媒体产业之际，这家老牌娱乐巨头将掌舵权交给了资深内部人士。【原文：Walt Disney on Tuesday named theme parks head Josh D'Amaro as CEO, ending years of succession uncertainty and placing a longtime insider at the helm as artificial intelligence and a wave of consolidation upend the media industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/disney-taps-parks-head-josh-damaro-ceo-lead-post-iger-era-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPI2IEXYPBOWLPHC7KVLLIUAYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基、赫伯罗特将恢复部分红海航线，由海军护航]]></title><description><![CDATA[马士基周二表示，航运集团赫伯罗特和马士基将通过其共享服务网络，于本月恢复部分经红海和苏伊士运河的运输航线。【原文：Shipping groups Hapag-Lloyd and Maersk will resume some transit routes through the Red Sea and the Suez Canal this month under their shared services network, Maersk said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/maersk-hapag-lloyd-transit-red-sea-with-one-their-shared-services-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GG4KUONEOBIQ5GDORUSO45BE4U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:23:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希腊政府消息人士称，该国即将宣布禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊政府高级消息人士周二向路透社透露，该国即将宣布禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体。【原文：Greece is "very close" to announcing a social media ban for children aged under 15, a senior government source told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/greece-soon-announce-social-media-ban-children-under-15-government-source-says-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUF5M4LB75NJNOWUB6YCVHIMOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:22:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hubbell季度利润因数据中心产品需求强劲而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二公布的财报显示，得益于数据中心对其电气设备的需求强劲，Hubbell公司第四季度利润实现增长。【原文：Hubbell posted a rise in fourth-quarter profit on Tuesday, helped by strong demand for its electrical equipment from data centers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/hubbells-quarterly-profit-rises-strong-data-center-product-demand-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDBOPKTFF5K5ZMFCJRLYFOCMQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KCC将冬季风暴造成的保险损失定为67亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[灾难风险建模公司凯伦·克拉克公司周二表示，近期冬季风暴造成的私人保险损失估计为67亿美元。【原文：Privately insured losses from the recent winter storm are estimated to be $6.7 billion, catastrophe risk modeling firm Karen Clark and Company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/kcc-pegs-insured-losses-winter-storm-67-billion-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5HB6RT5K5IQFGBXXDKDBFVZOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高德纳预测咨询部门因需求放缓将出现低迷年度业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[IT研究公司高德纳周二预测，其年度营收和利润将低于华尔街预期，因企业缩减开支导致对该公司咨询服务的需求减弱。【原文：IT research firm Gartner on Tuesday forecast annual revenue and earnings below Wall Street expectations, as enterprises scaling back their spending dampened demand for its consulting services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gartner-forecasts-downbeat-annual-results-slowing-demand-consulting-unit-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPYZ4T25OVPKVLKTJATOQUSIVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储巴金：降息措施迄今支撑就业市场，静待通胀"最后一公里"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会迄今的降息举措，在帮助保障就业市场健康的同时，也助力美联储完成将通胀率回归至央行2%目标的"最后一公里"。里士满联储主席汤姆·巴金周二如是表示。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve's interest rate cuts so far have helped insure the health of the job market while the Fed tries to complete "the last mile" in returning inflation to the central bank's 2% target, Richmond Fed President Tom Barkin said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-barkin-cuts-so-far-helped-support-job-market-while-waiting-inflations-last-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SCRM3NIJNIHRODQ2R2LAJHD6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：伊朗加密货币活动激增引发美国关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国调查人员正在审查特定加密货币平台是否曾协助伊朗官员规避制裁，一位区块链研究员向路透社透露。当前，加密货币活动在伊朗伊斯兰共和国呈现蓬勃发展态势。【原文：U.S. investigators are examining whether specific crypto platforms have facilitated sanctions evasion by Iranian officials, a blockchain researcher told Reuters, as cryptocurrency activity booms in the Islamic Republic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/irans-surging-crypto-activity-draws-us-scrutiny-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIQ4RAFZLBKFFHR5PUYASGRBRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:03:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>