<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 03:30:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 03:30:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[-全球市场对特朗普的关税变化变得麻木不仁]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CGS International Securities Group 首席执行官 Carol Fong 称，全球金融市场正在对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税方案 "麻木不仁"。【原文：Global financial markets are becoming 'desensitised' to U.S President Donald Trump's tariffs package, according to CGS International Securities Group chief executive Carol Fong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-becoming-desensitised-trumps-tariff-shifts-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37TMNHO2OJLWFAVURDEBUJEXSY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 03:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元坚挺，亚洲股市涨跌不一，交易商思考关税前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑主要货币汇率周三接近两周半高位，而铜价则在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普扩大全球贸易战，威胁对金属征收 50%关税后，在隔夜创下历史新高。【原文：The dollar traded close to a 2-1/2-week high versus major peers on Wednesday while copper hit an all-time peak overnight after U.S. President Donald Trump broadened his global trade war by threatening a 50% tariff on the metal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M45VCKI7GNPOBLT2F7DZFKACVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 03:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌人工智能支出主要用于技术基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌亚太区人工智能和新兴技术政策负责人黄颖（Eunice Huang）周三表示，谷歌的人工智能投资主要集中在技术基础设施方面。【原文：Google's AI investments are primarily in technical infrastructure, Google APAC head of AI and emerging tech policy Eunice Huang said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/google-ai-spending-primarily-technical-infrastructure-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62XI3BCANNMFHAJUUOFCK7MSQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 02:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳航确认逾百万客户个人信息遭泄露]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚澳航（Qantas Airways）周三表示，在该国多年来最大的一次网络泄露事件中，超过一百万名客户的电话号码、出生日期或家庭住址被泄露。【原文：Australia's Qantas Airways said on Wednesday more than a million customers had their phone number, birth date or home address accessed in one of the country's biggest cyber breaches in years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/qantas-confirms-over-million-customers-personal-information-leaked-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VAKUIDZLVVPCFLQVHGPUJESB64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 02:25:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行将现金利率维持在 3.25]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰中央银行周三将基准利率维持在 3.25%，但表示如果中期通胀压力继续如预测的那样缓解，预计将放松货币政策。【原文：New Zealand's central bank held the benchmark interest rate at 3.25% on Wednesday, but said it expected to loosen monetary policy if medium-term inflation pressures continued to ease as forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/new-zealand-central-bank-holds-cash-rate-325-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWLHX7XYFZL4HCMHT7TE2JATG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 02:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：美国重要矿产买家如何绕过中国出口禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[自中国去年禁止锑从泰国和墨西哥运往美国以来，大量锑--一种用于电池、芯片和阻燃剂的金属--异常地涌入美国。【原文：Unusually large quantities of antimony - a metal used in batteries, chips and flame retardants - have poured into the United States from Thailand and Mexico since China barred U.S. shipments last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/how-us-buyers-critical-minerals-bypass-chinas-export-ban-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7FX7FWQM5MXFHHES2BJ7IDDUI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 02:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国工厂门通缩为两年来最严重，原因是需求疲软和贸易风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[6 月份，中国生产商通货紧缩加深至近两年来最严重的水平，因为中国经济正努力应对全球贸易战的不确定性和国内需求的低迷，这给政策制定者带来了推出更多支持措施的压力。【原文：China's producer deflation deepened to its worst level in almost two years in June as the economy grapples with uncertainty over a global trade war and subdued demand at home, piling pressure on policymakers to roll out more support measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-consumer-prices-rise-first-time-five-months-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXQI6JQPFRKWPPVI74LIJSVURI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 01:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：白宫顾问哈塞特成为下任美联储主席的有力竞争者]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周二援引知情人士的话报道，白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）正在成为下一任美国联邦储备委员会主席的有力竞争者。【原文：White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett is emerging as a serious contender to be the next chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-adviser-hassett-emerging-serious-contender-next-fed-chair-wsj-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPQ2UJRZ6FPABKE2YSJTEBQGPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 01:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待关税明朗化，油价从两周高点回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在上一交易日升至两周高点后，周三小幅走低，原因是投资者正在关注美国关税的新动向，并试图判断其影响。【原文：Oil prices edged slightly lower on Wednesday after rising to two-week highs in the previous session, as investors were watching new developments on U.S. tariffs and trying to gauge their impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-ease-two-week-highs-investors-await-tariff-clarity-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNJZQVELGFKTFAGU46FN7OJLAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 01:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国以军民两用技术为由对八家台湾企业实施出口管制]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周三表示，它已将八家台湾公司列入出口管制名单，理由是对来自这个北京视其为自己领土的民主治理岛国的军民两用技术货物的担忧。【原文：China's commerce ministry on Wednesday said it has added eight Taiwanese firms to an export controls list, citing concerns over shipments of dual-use technologies from the democratically governed island that Beijing views as its own territory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/china-places-export-controls-eight-taiwanese-firms-citing-dual-use-tech-concerns-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7YXK6NL6ZMYNHL3AJ23B76LBI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 01:26:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普贸易战加剧，美元兑日元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在宣布对日本和其他贸易伙伴征收 25% 的关税后，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺推出更多与贸易有关的公告，美元兑日元汇率在周三连续第三天上涨。【原文：The dollar rose for a third day against the yen on Wednesday as U.S. President Donald Trump pledged more trade-related proclamations after announcing 25% tariffs on Japan and other trade partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-gains-against-yen-trumps-trade-war-intensifies-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIEN2LLVQFLLTM3BGG4YXAN55I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 01:14:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行关注美国关税动态]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行副行长安德鲁-豪瑟（Andrew Hauser）周三表示，澳大利亚央行非常关注美国关税的发展，并称全球经济存在巨大的不确定性。【原文：Australia's central bank is very focused on U.S. tariff developments, Deputy Governor Andrew Hauser said on Wednesday, adding that there is an enormous amount of uncertainty in the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-central-bank-focused-us-tariff-developments-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JHCET4VCBOUDEMZEI5PRQAKW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经》报道：日产汽车停止在美国两家工厂为加拿大生产三款车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周三报道，在美国和加拿大相互征收汽车关税的背景下，日产汽车将暂停在田纳西州和密西西比州工厂为加拿大生产三种车型。【原文：Nissan Motor is suspending production of three vehicle models for Canada at its Tennessee and Mississippi plants amid mutual auto tariffs between the U.S. and Canada, the Nikkei reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-halts-production-three-models-canada-two-us-plants-nikkei-reports-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFF2CJTMZVKJFE63BSIUQ7UJ6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发市场波动，美国二手车价格飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国二手车批发拍卖价格的一项指标在 COVID 大流行后通胀飙升之前被证明是具有预测性的，但现在该指标再次攀升，上个月创下了近三年来最大的年度涨幅。【原文：A gauge of U.S. used vehicle prices sold at wholesale auctions that proved predictive ahead of the inflation surge following the COVID pandemic is climbing again, last month notching its largest annual increase in nearly three years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-used-car-prices-surge-tariffs-drive-market-volatility-2025-07-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2RVRNBZFROAPIXB5PHVN6N5OM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长称美国今年可征收 3,000 亿美元关税收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，今年到目前为止，美国已获得约1000亿美元的关税收入，随着唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易运动加速收税，到2025年底，这一数字可能会增长到3000亿美元。【原文：Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Tuesday said the U.S. has taken in about $100 billion in tariff income so far this year, and this could grow to $300 billion by the end of 2025 as collections accelerate from President Donald Trump's trade campaign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-could-collect-300-billion-tariff-revenue-this-year-treasury-chief-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MA4MQZ6RABO4DP2VSZNSJHBBHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 23:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北卡罗来纳州州长表示花旗集团将在夏洛特增加 500 多个工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[北卡罗来纳州州长乔希-斯坦恩（Josh Stein）周二表示，花旗集团计划在夏洛特新增 510 个工作岗位。【原文：Citigroup plans to create 510 new jobs in Charlotte, Josh Stein, governor of North Carolina said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-add-over-500-jobs-charlotte-north-carolina-governor-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62CFCASZBNJAVM7FCFZSB3OG3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 22:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：关税不明朗，市场无波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KCTGAESO5I4FPGYRY6HPOTMVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:41:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国议员再次关注 GenScript 与中国的关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院中国问题委员会周二致函联邦调查局局长和国家情报局局长，鉴于 GenScript 生物技术公司与中国的关系，再次对该公司与美国公司的合作表示担忧。【原文：The U.S. House of Representatives committee on China on Tuesday sent a letter to the directors of the FBI and national intelligence, renewing its concerns about GenScript Biotechnology's work with U.S. companies, given its ties to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-lawmakers-renew-concerns-about-genscripts-ties-china-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4FXQBJ5EBJH3CR5MWHPG2SBPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商受亚洲国家关税影响的程度]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示将对十多个向美国公司供应大量纺织品的国家征收关税，其中包括越南和印度尼西亚等几个亚洲国家，美国服装零售商和鞋类公司正面临着更高的关税风险。这些征税大致从 25% 到 40% 不等。【原文：U.S. clothing retailers and footwear companies are facing heightened tariff exposure after the White House said it would put levies on more than a dozen nations, including several Asian countries like Vietnam and Indonesia, that supply large volumes of textiles to U.S. companies. Those levies range roughly from 25% to 40%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retailers-exposure-tariffs-asian-countries-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSZVL6BXUJML7IFIF4RIUOC5RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 "点击取消 "规则被上诉法院驳回]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国上诉法院阻止了一项要求企业像注册一样方便取消订阅和会员资格的规定，称制定该规定的机构没有遵守协议。【原文：A U.S. appeals court blocked a rule that would have required businesses to make it as easy to cancel subscriptions and memberships as it is to sign up, saying the agency that created it did not follow protocol.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/us-click-cancel-rule-blocked-by-appeals-court-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BH3VCN66URIZNDCUIYUPQLCTQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:19:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称金砖国家 "很快 "将被征收 10%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，美国将 "很快 "对从金砖国家进口的商品征收10%的关税，这引起了刚刚主办了金砖国家年度峰会的巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）的不满。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday the U.S. would "pretty soon" charge a 10% tariff on imports from BRICS countries, drawing another complaint from Brazil President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, who just hosted the bloc's annual summit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-brics-nations-get-10-tariff-pretty-soon-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMMFUC3CHBOV5NH3J5Q7SQKJYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球最大铜生产国智利在特朗普关税重磅炸弹之后陷入观望状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）出人意料地宣布对进口的红色金属征收 50%的关税后，世界第一大铜生产国智利正处于观望状态。【原文：Chile, the world's No. 1 copper producer, is in wait-and-see mode after U.S. President Donald Trump announced a surprise 50% tariff on imports of the red metal, with the Andean nation blindsided while its top miner held out hope of exemptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/worlds-top-copper-producer-chile-wait-and-see-mode-after-trump-tariff-bombshell-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJCPLDHC4FO5FEQ3B7G36URTVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果任命内部人士萨比汗为首席运营官]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周二任命内部人士萨比-汗（Sabih Khan）接替杰夫-威廉姆斯（Jeff Williams）担任首席运营官。【原文：Apple on Tuesday named insider Sabih Khan as its chief operating officer, succeeding Jeff Williams.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-names-insider-sabih-khan-coo-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDL5JZDRMZMXLHXZE5Z2CSMLTQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:42:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Meta 持有雷朋母公司 EssilorLuxottica 约 3% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周二告诉路透社，Meta Platforms 收购了眼镜制造商 EssilorLuxottica 近 3% 的股份。【原文：Meta Platforms has acquired a nearly 3% stake in eyewear maker EssilorLuxottica , a source told Reuters on Tuesday, amid growing consumer interest in AI-powered wearable devices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/meta-takes-around-3-stake-ray-ban-parent-essilorluxottica-source-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSSUCQ6DJJPEJO46LSNJR4B7QA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:20:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会要求加强对 "美国制造 "在线销售声明的监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周二呼吁亚马逊公司和沃尔玛公司打击在这两家零售巨头的在线市场上宣称 "美国制造 "的第三方卖家。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday called on Amazon.com and Walmart to crack down on third-party sellers that make deceptive "Made in USA" claims on the retailing giants' online marketplaces.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-ftc-demands-better-policing-made-usa-online-sales-claims-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GVXFWC4HJIJRCXULZTLBVR724</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院解除阻止特朗普大规模裁员的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周二为唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府恢复大规模裁员和机构重组扫清了道路，这是他缩减和重塑联邦政府的运动的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court cleared the way on Tuesday for President Donald Trump's administration to resume carrying out mass job cuts and the restructuring of agencies, elements of his campaign to downsize and reshape the federal government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-supreme-court-lifts-order-that-blocked-trumps-mass-federal-layoffs-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZNN4WDDNBLDFOGFSHBLKMRHP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国的铜从哪里来？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，他计划在当天晚些时候宣布对进口铜征收 50%的关税，这让全球铜产业大吃一惊，因为铜的产量对电动汽车、军事硬件、半导体和各种消费品至关重要。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday said he planned to announce a 50% tariff on copper imports later in the day, surprising a global industry whose output is critical to electric vehicles, military hardware, semiconductors and a wide range of consumer goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/where-does-us-get-its-copper-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6L6VMABLZNN5MWT6HK7W77K2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:40:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥 6 月总体通胀有所缓解，核心通胀率攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二的一项民意调查显示，墨西哥6月份的总体通胀率在连续四个月上升后可能有所回落，但核心通胀率预计仍将继续攀升，这加剧了市场对墨西哥央行将放缓降息步伐的押注。【原文：Mexican headline inflation likely eased in June after rising for four straight months, though core inflation is expected to have kept climbing, fueling bets the central bank will slow the pace of interest rate cuts, a Reuters poll showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-headline-inflation-seen-easing-june-with-core-rate-climbing-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5JBXLODKVNC7HTSYGAUTVVYI4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[衍生品转换后，联合信贷银行获得德国商业银行 20% 的股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利第二大银行意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）持有德国商业银行约 20% 的股份，并拥有相应的投票权。【原文：Italy's second biggest bank UniCredit owns an equity stake of around 20%, with corresponding voting rights, in Commerzbank after converting into shares derivatives which gives it an overall 29% holding in its German rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-gets-20-equity-stake-commerzbank-after-derivatives-conversion-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTT3WKTDUBPUXKIOPGQOBALHAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普推迟关税期限给贸易伙伴和企业带来希望和困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最近推迟关税的做法给主要贸易伙伴日本、韩国和欧盟带来了一些希望，即仍有可能达成放宽关税的协议，但同时也让南非等一些较小的出口国感到困惑，并让企业对未来的道路感到迷茫。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's latest tariff delay provided some hope to major trade partners Japan, South Korea and the European Union that deals to ease duties could still be reached, while bewildering some smaller exporters such as South Africa and leaving companies with no clarity on the path forward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trumps-tariff-deadline-delay-brings-hope-confusion-trade-partners-businesses-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YUQ6QQFW5MGJDTKEG2GQMYEQQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 18:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>