<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:09:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:09:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼仍支持降息，尽管在最近会议上支持暂停降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会负责监管事务的副主席米歇尔·鲍曼周五表示，她仍认为利率应下调，但本周投票支持维持货币政策不变，仅为在下一次降低借贷成本前收集更多数据。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Vice Chair for Supervision Michelle Bowman said on Friday she still feels interest rates should fall, but voted to hold monetary policy steady this week ​only to gather more data before the next reduction in borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bowman-still-supports-rate-cuts-despite-backing-pause-recent-meeting-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKGR77TTJZOXNN65BZ7ZUCSCYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，迪士尼首席执行官鲍勃·伊格尔计划在合同到期前卸任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，知情人士透露，媒体巨头华特迪士尼公司首席执行官鲍勃·艾格已向同事表示，计划在12月31日合同到期前卸任首席执行官职务，并退出日常管理。【原文：Media conglomerate Walt Disney's Chief Executive Bob Iger has told associates he plans to step down as CEO and pull back from daily management before the December 31 end of his contract, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/disney-ceo-bob-iger-plans-leave-role-before-contract-expires-wsj-reports-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MS5SFU5ZMNM3FMKRHVHPIO3N24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，Thoma Bravo正考虑出售身份管理软件公司Imprivata]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位知情人士透露，私募股权公司托马斯·布拉沃正考虑出售医疗行业数字身份软件供应商Imprivata。【原文：Thoma Bravo is exploring a sale of Imprivata, a digital identity software provider for the healthcare industry, according to three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/thoma-bravo-explores-sale-identity-software-firm-imprivata-sources-say-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6JPFTCKRVPIJN6HPCKJO66S7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森美孚、雪佛龙看到委内瑞拉的潜力曙光，但前路漫漫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油巨头埃克森美孚和雪佛龙周五向投资者透露了其对委内瑞拉问题的若干新见解。尽管特朗普总统持续敦促美国石油企业重建这个南美国家的能源产业，但两家公司均未宣布长期投资承诺。【原文：U.S. oil majors Exxon Mobil and Chevron offered investors a few pieces of new insight into their thinking about Venezuela on Friday, even though neither company announced long-term investment commitments despite President Donald Trump's continued push to convince American oil firms to rebuild the South American country's energy sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-chevron-see-glimmer-venezuelas-potential-with-long-road-ahead-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SPLKHTRYVIHVMD4SYXFDLYKV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称SpaceX去年在首次公开募股前盈利约80亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，SpaceX去年在150亿至160亿美元营收基础上创造了约80亿美元利润，这为埃隆·马斯克旗下这家预计将于今年晚些时候上市的航天公司财务状况提供了最新洞见。【原文：SpaceX generated about $8 billion in profit on $15 billion to $16 billion of revenue ​last year, two people familiar with the company's results said, providing fresh insight ‌into the financial health of Elon Musk’s space company that is expected to go public later this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/spacex-generated-about-8-billion-profit-last-year-ahead-ipo-sources-say-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHFD434AMBJ7FM4DLVMPDMFI4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道，Peloton裁员11%，包括工程团队人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士消息报道称，Peloton Interactive公司已裁减11%的员工，旨在通过重组努力削减成本。【原文：Peloton Interactive has cut 11% of its employees as it aims to reduce costs amid turnaround efforts, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing a person with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/peloton-cuts-11-staff-including-engineering-teams-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLB2Y43RINNP3J7IKLASC32O3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:34:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会重组美国会计监管机构董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周五任命了新董事会成员来领导该国的审计监管机构，其中包括一位新任主席，他曾在大型审计公司安永工作了四十年。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday tapped new board members to lead the country's audit watchdog, including a new chairman who spent four decades at large audit firm Ernst and Young.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-sec-taps-new-board-members-accounting-watchdog-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BTLA5KFD5KWTAFDUB4IXGUA2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:19:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，凯雷正就卢克石油资产与阿联酋潜在合作伙伴进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，美国私募股权公司凯雷集团已开始与阿联酋投资者进行初步接洽，若其收购俄罗斯卢克石油公司国际资产的初步协议得以推进，将引入合作伙伴。【原文：U.S. private equity firm Carlyle has begun exploratory talks with UAE investors to ‌bring in partners should its initial agreement to buy Russian firm Lukoil's international assets proceed, three sources with knowledge of the process said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/carlyle-talks-with-potential-uae-partners-lukoil-assets-sources-say-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXJJUNX7KRMOLC7VH2C7HUJFQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:57:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[密歇根州总检察长要求中国电池制造商国轩高科归还2370万美元，因其未能履行美国工厂的债务义务]]></title><description><![CDATA[密歇根州总检察长达娜·内塞尔周五要求中国电池企业国轩高科归还2370万美元州政府资金。该公司去年放弃在密歇根州投资24亿美元建设生产电动汽车电池关键材料的工厂计划后，获得了这笔资金。【原文：Michigan Attorney General Dana Nessel on Friday asked Chinese battery company Gotion Inc to return $23.7 million in state funds the company received after the company last year abandoned a plan to build a $2.4 billion plant in Michigan to produce key materials for electric vehicle batteries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/michigan-ag-asks-chinese-battery-maker-gotion-return-237-million-after-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBYWRQDCP5K4DA6422K64LQS2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰官员指责俄罗斯国内情报机构策划12月29日网络攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰官员周五表示，上月底针对该国30家可再生能源设施、一家制造企业以及为近50万用户供热的工厂的网络攻击，很可能是由俄罗斯国内情报机构所为。【原文：Russia's domestic spy agency was likely responsible for cyberattacks late last month on 30 Polish renewable energy facilities, a manufacturing firm and a plant supplying heat for nearly 500,000 customers, Polish officials said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/polish-officials-blame-russian-domestic-spy-agency-dec-29-cyberattacks-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDVMM262ORNFBJHRQUTSMFRGPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在争夺破产的萨克斯百货公司提前付款的斗争中，大型奢侈品牌占据优势。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据七位知情人士透露，全球多家顶级奢侈品牌正悄然施加影响力，在与破产的萨克斯百货全球公司（Saks Global）的谈判中，因该零售商高度依赖其高端商品，这些品牌正推动获得优先债权人待遇。【原文：Some of the world’s biggest luxury ​brands are quietly exerting their influence in talks with bankrupt Saks Global, pushing the retailer for favorable creditor treatment due ‌to Saks' reliance on their high-end merchandise, according to seven people familiar with the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/fight-early-payouts-bankrupt-saks-big-luxury-brands-have-edge-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4D6URCUFTBLWFJ4EH5VNZD5VUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗认为黄金价格受到风险因素支撑，但预计2026年下半年支撑力度将有所减弱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗周五表示，黄金投资配置正受到多重地缘政治与经济风险的支撑，但其中约半数风险可能在今年晚些时候消退。【原文：Gold investment allocations are being underpinned by a broad mix of overlapping geopolitical and economic risks, but around half of the risk may fade later this year, Citi said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-sees-gold-supported-by-risks-with-some-fading-expected-later-2026-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJZ7YMWC4JKTJJH4BOAU4RM6EE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员穆萨莱姆表示，当前政策已处于中性水平，无需进一步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托·穆萨莱姆周五表示，除非就业市场开始恶化或通胀率下降，否则美国央行无需进一步降息。【原文：St. Louis Federal Reserve President Alberto Musalem said on Friday ​the U.S. central bank does not ‌need to cut interest rates further unless the job market starts to deteriorate or inflation falls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-musalem-says-no-more-rate-cuts-needed-with-policy-now-neutral-level-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EASSHVPHA5KFHLJ7YFP3JEDLVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚央行意外加息100个基点，利率升至10.25%]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚央行周五将基准利率上调100个基点至10.25%，这是近三年来首次加息，幅度超出多数分析师预期。政策制定者指出，此举是基于通胀压力上升、通胀预期急剧攀升以及财政和外部风险加剧的考量。【原文：Colombia's central bank raised its benchmark interest rate by 100 basis points to 10.25% on Friday, its ​first hike in nearly three years and a larger move than most ‌analysts had expected, as policymakers pointed to rising inflation pressures, a sharp jump in inflation expectations and mounting fiscal and external risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombias-central-bank-shocks-with-100-bp-rate-hike-1025-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKXPUM42Z5OY5J2TFX5SF4V3UU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:25:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于特朗普"中央选角"美联储主席人选凯文·沃什的五件事]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周五表示，他将提名前美联储理事凯文·沃什于五月重返美联储主席职位，此举延续了总统推动美国降息的政策主张。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday said he will nominate former Federal Reserve governor Kevin Warsh to return as Fed Chair in May, as the president continues his campaign for lower U.S. interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/five-things-know-about-kevin-warsh-trumps-central-casting-fed-chair-pick-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5ERP5HFH5LW3DNAOMBKUPE7CI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称对美联储提名人沃什的利率问题提问不恰当，对降息充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统周五表示，询问其提名的下任美联储主席人选凯文·沃什是否会降息并不恰当，但他补充说，他相信沃什倾向于降低借贷成本。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday it would be inappropriate to ask Kevin Warsh, his nominee to be the next chair of the Federal Reserve, whether he would cut interest rates, but added he was confident Warsh was inclined to lower borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-calls-rate-questions-fed-nominee-warsh-inappropriate-confident-cuts-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCOKB3LNZFK2RKT2QTUF4GSNJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:09:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国称美韩需就贸易协定进行更多磋商]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国产业部长表示，在特朗普总统宣布提高关税后，韩国需要就去年达成的贸易协议与美国进行更多磋商。此前，韩美双方产业部长经过为期两天的会谈，于周五结束磋商。【原文：South Korea needs more discussion with the U.S. on a trade deal they reached last year, the industry minister said after two days of talks through Friday with his counterpart, following U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement to raise tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-south-korea-need-more-discussion-trade-deal-seoul-says-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWFWXBZLDFOMVH5XJBD5FX2FLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:06:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌推出能将指令转化为可玩世界的AI模型，游戏股应声下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五午盘交易时段，视频游戏公司股价大幅下挫。此前谷歌母公司Alphabet推出了一款人工智能模型，该模型仅需简单指令即可创建交互式数字世界。【原文：Shares of videogame companies fell sharply in afternoon trading on Friday after Alphabet's Google rolled out its artificial intelligence model capable of creating ​interactive digital worlds with simple prompts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/videogame-stocks-slide-googles-ai-model-that-turns-prompts-into-playable-worlds-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW36ZYA42RMCBHOXBZ6NICAXHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉股价飙升，因SpaceX合并谈判点燃市场对马斯克帝国整合的期待]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉股价周五飙升逾5%，此前有报道称SpaceX正与埃隆·马斯克旗下的其他公司进行交易谈判，这点燃了投资者对这位亿万富翁科技帝国可能进一步整合的期待。【原文：Shares of Tesla jumped more than 5% on Friday, after reports that SpaceX was in deal talks with Elon Musk's other companies stoked investor ​hopes that the billionaire's tech empire could be unified further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/tesla-jumps-spacex-merger-talks-fuel-musk-empire-consolidation-hopes-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFA6YJ5GJNI6JLVNIO6TFJTJKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局最终确定25小时驾驶舱语音记录器规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周五最终敲定一项规定，要求2027年所有新客机驾驶舱语音记录器必须保留25小时数据，而现行规定仅要求循环记录两小时。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration on Friday finalized a rule to require cockpit voice recorders to retain 25 hours of data for all new passenger airplanes in 2027 compared with the current two-hour loop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-finalizes-25-hour-cockpit-voice-recorder-rule-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBF5EWA56ZPMNLTERQLWEBF5CI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:28:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名的美联储主席人选遭遇共和党参议员的早期阻挠]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普总统提名的凯文·沃什出任美联储主席一事，正遭遇来自国会本党内部的阻力。至少一名共和党参议员周五证实，若司法部对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的调查持续进行，他将反对该提名获得确认。【原文：President Donald Trump's pick of Kevin Warsh to lead the Federal Reserve is running into opposition from within his own ​party in Congress, as at least one Republican senator confirmed on Friday he will oppose the confirmation if the Justice Department's investigation of U.S. ‌central bank chief Jerome Powell continues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-pick-lead-fed-faces-early-hurdle-republican-senator-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVU44Z6GAVNXDPWSU3ZIQ6447U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:17:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员米兰预计沃什将接替其在央行理事职位 - CNBC]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬·米兰周五在电视采访中表示，他预计被提名为美联储现任主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔继任者的凯文·沃什，很可能会接替他在美联储即将届满的任期。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran said in a television interview Friday that he assumes Kevin Warsh, nominated to succeed current Fed chair Jerome Powell, will likely fill his expiring term at the central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-miran-assumes-warsh-will-fill-his-governor-slot-central-bank-cnbc-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUL2RK2HCZKJVKNHGGUVBA5TBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名沃什出任美联储主席，料将推动华尔街监管放松]]></title><description><![CDATA[监管专家表示，美国总统特朗普提名的美联储主席人选凯文·沃什很可能推动美联储放宽对华尔街银行的监管，并让政府在监管和监督事务上拥有更大话语权。【原文：Kevin Warsh, U.S. President Donald Trump's pick to chair the Federal Reserve, will likely boost the central bank's effort to ease Wall Street bank rules, ​and allow the administration a bigger say on regulation and supervision matters, said regulatory experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trumps-fed-chair-pick-warsh-likely-boost-wall-st-rule-easing-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKHD74OYUZMZ3B32XJ7G2XPD5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:51:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1月份美国在欧洲液化天然气进口中的份额增至60%]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据显示，本月美国供应了欧盟60%的液化天然气，这证实了其作为欧洲主要液化天然气供应商的地位。与此同时，一些欧洲官员对日益依赖美国能源感到警惕。【原文：The United States supplied 60% of the European Union's liquefied natural gas this month, data showed on Friday, confirming its role as Europe's dominant LNG supplier as some European officials become wary of growing reliance on U.S. energy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-share-europes-lng-imports-increased-60-january-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4TDE3WDTRJ6TPY4AYUVEVKJDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普顾问哈塞特告诉CNBC，沃什是执掌央行的好人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫首席经济顾问凯文·哈塞特周五表示，美联储本周未降息实属失策，同时呼吁迅速批准凯文·沃什出任美联储主席。【原文：Top White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett on Friday said the Federal Reserve blundered in ​not cutting rates this week, in comments that also called for ‌a swift approval of Kevin Warsh to be Fed Chair.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-advisor-hassett-tells-cnbc-warsh-good-pick-run-central-bank-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RQNTK62SJNVJCYFV7QSHMMCKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:22:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前班杰瑞董事质疑Magnum试图操控独立董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[被撤职的本杰瑞独立董事会成员在美国法院提起诉讼，质疑麦格纳冰淇淋公司任命新董事的计划，指控其存在公司越权行为。【原文：Directors removed from Ben & Jerry's independent board have challenged in a U.S. court filing The Magnum Ice Cream Company's plans to appoint new directors, accusing it of corporate overreach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/former-ben-jerrys-directors-challenge-magnum-efforts-shape-independent-board-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USIAQD2NIRLWBHNXLDOMKRPKJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金在巨型股财报发布前吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至1月28日当周，美国股票基金资金再度涌入，尽管市场对特朗普总统最新关税威胁感到不安，但大型股财报季前乐观预期仍为其提供了支撑。【原文：U.S. equity funds experienced renewed inflows in the week to January 28, supported ​by upbeat expectations ahead of mega-cap ‌earnings despite jitters over President Donald Trump's latest tariff threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-attract-inflows-ahead-mega-cap-earnings-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VB6EXIGFDNJODJOMMWHIW7FUC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司斥资35亿美元在宾夕法尼亚州建厂，推动美国制造业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周五宣布将在宾夕法尼亚州新建一家制药工厂，这是该公司为扩大美国本土产能、强化医疗供应链而设立的第四个新生产基地。【原文：Eli Lilly announced on Friday that it will build a pharmaceutical manufacturing facility in Pennsylvania, its fourth new site in an effort to expand U.S. production and bolster medical supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eli-lilly-build-35-billion-pennsylvania-plant-us-manufacturing-push-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5KLH7V7HFJFXHHFFSWJOSOLEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:04:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森美孚表示拥有开采委内瑞拉高成本原油所需技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚首席执行官达伦·伍兹周五向分析师表示，该公司拥有从委内瑞拉开采高成本原油所需的技术。【原文：Exxon Mobil CEO Darren Woods told analysts on Friday that the company has the technology that would be needed to produce higher cost barrels from Venezuela.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-says-it-has-technology-needed-venezuelas-high-cost-crude-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2LL24OVUNLBVJJBRPBGVFSQYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[闪迪股价飙升，强劲的人工智能需求推动业绩预期大幅上调]]></title><description><![CDATA[闪迪公司股价周五大幅上涨，此前这家数据存储企业公布的第三季度利润和营收远超分析师预期，并延长了一项重大供应协议。此轮上涨主要得益于人工智能驱动的数据存储需求激增。【原文：Sandisk shares rallied on Friday, after the data storage firm projected third-quarter profit and revenue well above analysts' estimates and extended a major supply ​deal, powered by a surge in AI-driven demand for data storage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sandisk-surges-robust-ai-demand-powers-blowout-forecast-2026-01-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRW2SY2WNFNGNGWTTYUGYEIMGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:55:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>