<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:34:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:34:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示美国与中国就关税问题进行了非常良好的谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二告诉福克斯新闻（Fox News），美国与中国就关税问题进行了非常良好的会谈，两国试图在关税实施暂停的90天内达成贸易协议。【原文：Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Fox News on Tuesday that the United States has had very good talks with China regarding tariffs as the countries attempt to reach a trade deal during a 90-day pause in tariff implementation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-us-has-had-very-good-talks-with-china-tariffs-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZPUWYZPXVMQHMLOD7IFIBRXOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着贸易蜜月期的结束，日本日经指数将从历史最高点回落：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，日本日经平均指数可能会在年底前从近期的历史高点回落，尽管这在很大程度上取决于与美国达成的脆弱贸易协议。【原文：Japan's Nikkei share average will likely ease off recent record highs toward year-end, according to strategists in a Reuters poll, though much depends on a fragile trade agreement with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-nikkei-ease-off-record-peak-trade-honeymoon-fades-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CGYFMJO7OZO75FNERQQXR6TEI4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在对美联储主席的最新攻击中，特朗普称鲍威尔 "伤害 "了房地产业]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔 "非常严重地伤害了 "房地产业，并称他应该降息。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell is "hurting" the housing industry "very badly" and said he should cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-claims-powell-hurting-housing-industry-latest-attack-fed-chair-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSHHNIPNMVLSDFCPYBZF5L3KDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 22:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普希望美国政府参股其他获得《CHIPS 法案》基金的芯片制造商]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）正在研究联邦政府入股那些获得《CHIPS 法案》资助在美国建厂的计算机芯片制造商。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick is looking into the federal government taking equity stakes in computer chip manufacturers that receive CHIPS Act funding to build factories in the country, two sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-eyes-us-government-stakes-other-chip-makers-that-received-chips-act-funds-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z65JQ6YLCVJETKM3Z4GYPMPDSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 22:20:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vantage 数据中心计划在得克萨斯州建造价值 250 亿美元的人工智能园区]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vantage Data Centers 公司周二表示，它将斥资 250 多亿美元在得克萨斯州沙克尔福德县建造一个占地 1200 英亩的数据中心园区，因为人工智能基础设施的需求激增推动了超大规模的开发。【原文：Vantage Data Centers said on Tuesday it would spend more than $25 billion to build a 1,200-acre data center campus in Shackelford County, Texas, as surging demand for artificial intelligence infrastructure fuels mega-scale developments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/vantage-data-centers-plans-25-billion-ai-campus-texas-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CY6OR3NKK5JTHN32A5FAB6F5SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:57:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道白宫推出官方 TikTok 账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周二推出了一个官方 TikTok 账户，利用其超过 1.5 亿美国用户的优势传播唐纳德-特朗普总统的信息。【原文：The White House launched an official TikTok account on Tuesday, taking advantage of its more than 150 million U.S. users to spread the messages of President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-launches-official-tiktok-account-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BIAEWN7KJLLLI5CEBRC7F6QFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国接受巴西就关税问题向世贸组织提出的磋商请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据世界贸易组织网站上公布的一份文件，美国已经接受了巴西就其对其商品征收关税一事向世界贸易组织提出的磋商请求，尽管美国辩称征收关税事关国家安全。【原文：The United States has accepted a request for consultations from Brazil at the World Trade Organization regarding tariffs it imposed on its goods, even as it argued the levies are a matter of national security, according to a document posted on the WTO website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-accepts-brazils-wto-consultation-request-over-tariffs-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJRGKHHVX5NITP7MPMOVPPMJKM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空和美联航因出售无窗 "靠窗座位 "遭起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）和美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周二遭到乘客的起诉，他们声称自己花了额外的钱坐在 "靠窗 "的座位上，却发现自己的座位紧挨着一堵白墙。【原文：Delta Air Lines and United Airlines were sued on Tuesday by passengers who claimed they paid extra money to sit in "window" seats, only to find themselves placed in seats next to a blank wall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/delta-united-sued-selling-windowless-window-seats-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STJNTD3FJBOS5PWBU7NBALWGGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:13:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 降低技术含量]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MF6D6PUPSNNQPC637DMET5WUG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉威科技公布乐观的季度业绩，并上调 2025 年业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子设备制造商 Keysight Technologies 周二公布的第三季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，凸显出其通信、汽车和半导体终端市场对产品的强劲需求。【原文：Electronic equipment maker Keysight Technologies beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue and profit on Tuesday, highlighting robust product demand across its communications, automotive and semiconductor end-markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/keysight-technologies-reports-upbeat-quarterly-results-lifts-2025-forecast-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUHJIGBUIRJUPJZCCJ5WZIYGW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:54:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰克-亨利公司季度利润因银行技术需求强劲而大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰克-亨利（Jack Henry）周二公布，受银行业技术产品需求强劲的推动，公司第四季度利润猛增 26%。【原文：Jack Henry reported a 26% jump in fourth-quarter profit on Tuesday, buoyed by robust demand for its banking technology offerings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/jack-henrys-quarterly-profit-jumps-robust-bank-tech-demand-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBNP56U6O5KNZALMKQB57S2JZM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加航劳资协议或将重塑北美航空公司机组人员的薪酬待遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司（Air Canada）空乘人员因工资和拖欠劳动报酬问题举行瘫痪性罢工，导致数千个航班停飞，这是对航空业补偿制度的最新打击，因为该制度没有为机舱乘务员的工作时间支付全额工资。【原文：A crippling strike by Air Canada flight attendants that grounded thousands of flights over wages and unpaid labor is the latest blow to the airline industry's compensation system that does not fully pay cabin crews for their hours at work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/air-canada-labor-deal-may-reshape-pay-north-american-airline-crews-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V73ECR5KD5KIJEWLO3FDYMX5RY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:40:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在铁路行业动荡之际，Ancora 敦促 CSX 寻求合并或更换首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[激进投资者 Ancora Holdings 周一致信 CSX 董事会，敦促该公司寻求近期合并方案或更换首席执行官 Joe Hinrichs。【原文：Activist investor Ancora Holdings, in a letter to CSX board disclosed on Monday, urged the railroad to pursue near-term merger options or replace CEO Joe Hinrichs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/ancora-urges-csx-pursue-merger-or-replace-ceo-amid-rail-industry-shakeup-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMGL56PRS5LRPHCTCYHRAOUHQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普抨击上诉法院停止决议铜矿土地转让]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二抨击了上诉法院暂时阻止联邦官员完成力拓和必和必拓开发亚利桑那州 Resolution Copper 项目所需的土地转让的决定。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday blasted an appeal court's decision to temporarily block federal officials from completing a land transfer needed for Rio Tinto and BHP to develop Arizona's Resolution Copper project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-blasts-appeals-court-halting-resolution-copper-land-transfer-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAENFHUUH5JCDPL5DA5XAIMK24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 SpaceX 和其他公司赢得美国法院对劳工委员会结构的挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周二同意埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）和其他两家公司的观点，认为美国国家劳工关系委员会的结构可能不合法，并阻止该机构对它们提起诉讼。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Tuesday agreed with Elon Musk's SpaceX and two other companies that the U.S. National Labor Relations Board's structure is likely unlawful and blocked the agency from pursuing cases against them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/musks-spacex-others-win-us-court-challenge-labor-boards-structure-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWZRHIMEENOXTPNTKOHNY3SMTA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:48:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼建议允许央行员工持有少量加密货币产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储最高监管官员周二建议，应允许央行工作人员拥有少量加密产品，认为经验将更好地指导他们在这些金融市场上的监管活动。【原文：The Federal Reserve's top regulatory official suggested on Tuesday that central bank staff should be permitted to own small amounts of crypto products, arguing experience would better inform their work policing activities in those financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-bowman-suggests-allowing-central-bank-staff-own-small-amounts-crypto-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJV5ONZ675KX3DHC75OSIWVDCA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛财报将考验投资者对美国市场的信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者预计，随着美国劳动力市场的降温和通胀率的上升，沃尔玛管理层将对顾客需求采取谨慎的基调，尽管该公司在过去一年中的表现优于同行，这是因为它依赖于食品杂货销售，而且富裕的顾客更经常到沃尔玛购物。【原文：Investors expect Walmart's management to strike a cautious tone on customer demand as the U.S. labor market cools and inflation ticks up, though the company has outperformed its peers over the last year due to its reliance on grocery sales and wealthier customers shopping there more often.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/walmarts-earnings-report-will-test-investor-confidence-us-market-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWOJS37NJNO53L5CR74YZHBRBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[反垄断裁决受挫，巴西 "大豆暂停 "网站下线]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，在巴西反垄断机构下令暂停执行巴西 "大豆暂停令 "之后，一个包含巴西 "大豆暂停令 "相关信息的网站被下线。"大豆暂停令 "是一项由全球谷物贸易商执行的私人协议，旨在保护亚马逊雨林免遭大豆砍伐。【原文：A website containing information about Brazil's "soy moratorium," a private agreement enforced by global grain traders to protect the Amazon rainforest from soy-driven deforestation, was taken offline on Tuesday after Brazil's antitrust authority ordered suspension of the pact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/brazils-soy-moratorium-site-offline-after-antitrust-ruling-setback-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDOHSGJVRRPQRPSK7JLU7DEBJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:12:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析显示，美联储杰克逊霍尔夏季会议前后美股往往上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 DataTrek Research 的历史分析，美股在美联储 8 月杰克逊霍尔会议前后往往表现良好，尽管近年来市场出现了双向的大幅波动。【原文：U.S. stocks have tended to fare well around the Federal Reserve's Jackson Hole gathering in August, according to a historical analysis from DataTrek Research, although the market has seen sizable moves in both directions in recent years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stocks-tend-gain-around-feds-jackson-hole-summer-conference-analysis-shows-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFAYGSLDRBM2HE3JPTM5OUSQAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示美国关税收入将 "大幅增长"，重点是减少债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）表示，他预计唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统征收的全面关税将带来收入的大幅跃升，并表示这笔钱将首先用于开始偿还联邦债务，而不是向美国人发放退税支票。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said he expects a big jump in revenues from sweeping tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump, and said the money would be used first to start paying down the federal debt, not to give rebate checks to Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bessent-says-us-tariff-revenues-rise-substantially-focus-reducing-debt-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW3CY6XMPZKMRN32XK5D2VKC2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌在欧盟压力下调整 Google Play 条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[在欧盟竞争监督机构指控谷歌违反欧盟法规后，Alphabet 旗下公司谷歌周二表示，将让应用开发者更容易将客户引导到谷歌以外的渠道。【原文：Alphabet unit Google said on Tuesday it will make it easier for app developers to steer customers to channels other than Google after the European Union competition watchdog charged it with breaching EU regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/google-tweaks-google-play-conditions-following-eu-pressure-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RR42A72FZVKK7JTHGPRZQMAAUY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:27:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融业机构呼吁修改银行加密货币规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群金融业机构呼吁重新思考迫在眉睫的监管标准，他们认为这些标准将使银行难以参与加密货币市场。【原文：A group of finance industry bodies is calling for a rethink on looming regulatory standards that they say will make it difficult for banks to participate in crypto markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/finance-industry-bodies-call-changes-crypto-rules-banks-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGAD27OBMJOVJDKQVTBT2RX2YY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:23:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔 500 指数因人工智能反弹遭遇关税忧虑而停滞不前：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社最新民调显示，2025 年年底，S&amp;P 500 指数将略低于目前接近历史最高水平的水平，反映出人们在持续担忧唐纳德-特朗普总统的全球关税对经济的影响以及美联储降息的不确定性的情况下，乐观情绪有所缓和。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 benchmark U.S. stock index will end 2025 just below current near-record levels, reflecting tempered optimism amid ongoing concerns over the economic impact of President Donald Trump's global tariffs and uncertainty surrounding Federal Reserve rate cuts, according to a new Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sp-500-seen-stalling-ai-rally-meets-tariff-jitters-reuters-poll-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KUELWSXU5MOPNQGBM32BXC6M4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度计划禁止用钱玩网络游戏，理由是有上瘾风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，一份拟议法案显示，印度政府计划禁止用钱玩网络游戏，这对吸引了数十亿美元外商投资的网络游戏产业来说将是一个沉重的打击。【原文：India's government plans to ban online games played with money, a proposed bill showed on Tuesday, in what would be a heavy blow for an industry that has attracted billions of dollars of foreign investment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-plans-ban-online-games-played-with-money-citing-addiction-risks-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GX7DICFIUNLU7GAS7XR2PB3X3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:46:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与YouTube儿童隐私诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌将支付 3,000 万美元来解决一起诉讼，该诉讼称谷歌未经家长同意收集儿童的个人信息，并利用这些信息发送有针对性的广告，从而侵犯了使用 YouTube 的儿童的隐私权。【原文：Google will pay $30 million to settle a lawsuit claiming it violated the privacy of children using YouTube by collecting their personal information without parental consent, and using it to send targeted ads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-settles-youtube-childrens-privacy-lawsuit-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLDK6YR2XVLRJCNW4VM4EDDPMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西银行准备在美国制裁辩论中处理 "复杂 "问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西银行（Banco do Brasil）周二表示，该行已准备好处理涉及全球法规的 "复杂、敏感 "问题，因为最高法院的一位法官裁定，外国法律不能自动适用于巴西。【原文：Banco do Brasil said on Tuesday it is prepared to deal with "complex, sensitive" issues involving global regulations after a top court justice ruled foreign laws cannot be automatically applied in Brazil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/banco-do-brasil-ready-handle-complex-issues-amid-debate-over-us-sanctions-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVNJK5UJWZKUZOMNK5STCLIFXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国豆农敦促特朗普与中国达成采购协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国大豆种植农在周二的一封信中敦促唐纳德-特朗普总统与中国达成一项贸易协议，以确保重要的大豆采购协议，并警告说如果中国继续回避美国大豆作物，长期的经济后果将不堪设想。【原文：U.S. soybean farmers urged President Donald Trump in a Tuesday letter to reach a trade deal with China that secures significant soybean purchase agreements, warning of dire long-term economic outcomes if the country continues to shun the U.S. crop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-soybean-farmers-urge-trump-make-purchase-deal-with-china-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDEF65KKTZPXNAR6HIR7CCMO2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称去年美国石油天然气并购活动增加两倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二发布的一份报告显示，尽管大宗商品价格走软，但由于能源公司增加支出以提高效率和利润，去年美国石油和天然气行业的并购活动增加了两倍。【原文：Mergers and acquisitions in the U.S. oil and gas sector tripled last year despite softer commodity prices as energy companies boosted spending to improve efficiency and profits, according to a report released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-oil-gas-ma-activity-tripled-last-year-report-says-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKDRB2IDMNJV7N6X7J73UOCX2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在钢铝关税清单中增加 407 个产品类别]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周二宣布，在征收关税的 "衍生 "钢铁和铝产品清单中增加 407 个产品类别。【原文：The U.S. Department of Commerce on Tuesday announced the addition of 407 product categories to its list of "derivative" steel and aluminum products subject to tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-adds-407-product-categories-steel-aluminum-tariffs-list-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAC7CZE4QFPBHLKVX3A53FJIKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:43:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，Toms Capital 在收购 CSX 股份后寻求与 CSX 会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士透露，对冲基金汤姆士资本投资管理公司（Toms Capital Investment Management）最近买入美国铁路运营商 CSX 的股份后，已要求与该公司董事会会面，这引发了该公司可能推动合并的猜测。【原文：Hedge fund Toms Capital Investment Management has requested to meet with the board at U.S. railroad operator CSX after recently buying a stake, people familiar with the matter said, raising speculation the firm may push for a possible merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/toms-capital-seeks-csx-meeting-after-acquiring-stake-sources-say-2025-08-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOWCV4RDTRKG5HZGASB6NQM2MI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>