<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:38:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:38:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国称美国限制性措施破坏贸易谈判气氛]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部长王文涛表示，9 月马德里会谈后美国推出的 "密集限制措施 "严重损害了中国的利益，破坏了双边贸易磋商的气氛。【原文：China's commerce minister, Wang Wentao, said "intensive U.S. restrictive measures" rolled out after talks in Madrid in September seriously harmed China's interests and undermined the atmosphere for bilateral trade consultations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/china-says-us-restrictive-measures-undermine-trade-talk-atmosphere-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHV4T5RG7ZMBLDH56F43726AXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:08:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[酸奶制造商乔巴尼在最新一轮融资中募集 6.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chobani 周四表示，该公司在最新一轮融资中筹集了 6.5 亿美元，这家酸奶生产商希望为其在美国的工厂扩张计划提供资金。【原文：Chobani has raised $650 million in its latest funding round, the company said on Thursday, as the yogurt maker looks to fund its plant expansion plans in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/yogurt-maker-chobani-raises-650-million-latest-funding-round-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH2XXQW5VBOJRDOQTFXK4W3LLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABB 首席执行官对人工智能数据中心的需求充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士 ABB 公司首席执行官莫滕-维罗德（Morten Wierod）告诉路透社记者，该公司对为人工智能提供动力的数据中心的未来需求 "非常有信心"。【原文：Switzerland's ABB is "very confident" about future demand from data centers that power artificial intelligence, its CEO Morten Wierod told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/abb-ceo-very-confident-demand-data-centers-powering-ai-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5WSZGOJ7RKC3IL5K7FC3ZZPNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CNN 的全方位订阅层级将于 10 月 28 日推出，每月 6.99 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）将于 10 月 28 日推出每月 6.99 美元的流媒体订阅服务，这是在其母公司华纳兄弟探索公司（Warner Bros Discovery）推出成本高昂的 CNN+ 平台 30 天后的第三年。【原文：CNN is taking another shot at streaming with a $6.99-a-month subscription service that will launch on October 28, three years after its parent Warner Bros Discovery pulled the plug on the costly CNN+ platform within 30 days of debut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cnns-all-access-subscription-tier-will-launch-october-28-699-per-month-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAFP4NJ4OZJIFCO43GMNOWPEOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[腾讯支持的乌兹别克斯坦初创企业 Uzum 考虑在伦敦上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合创始人尼古拉-塞列兹涅夫（Nikolay Seleznev）告诉路透社，由腾讯支持的金融科技和电子商务服务提供商、乌兹别克斯坦最有价值的初创公司--乌兹别姆公司（Uzbekum）已将伦敦列入其股票市场上市的可能地点名单。【原文：Tencent-backed fintech and e-commerce provider Uzum, Uzbekistan's most valuable start-up, has added London to its list of possible locations for a stockmarket listing, co-founder Nikolay Seleznev told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tencent-backed-uzbek-start-up-uzum-considers-london-listing-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQRYRPICHFLHXCH5HSEZAMN7MQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储主席米兰称在推动降息过程中不关注资产价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周四表示，他并不担心放宽货币政策会进一步推高历史上、在某些情况下甚至是创纪录的资产价格。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran on Thursday said he's not concerned that easing monetary policy risks further inflating historically and in some cases record-high asset prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-miran-says-not-focused-asset-price-boom-push-lower-rates-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3TKHU7Y6BK4NJZDFCF4ZDR3QI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:20:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月住宅建筑商信心指数升至 6 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于人们希望抵押贷款利率的下降将刺激住房需求，并有助于减少阻碍新住房建设的库存过剩，美国住房建筑商的情绪在 10 月份跃升至六个月来的最高点。【原文：U.S. homebuilder sentiment jumped to a six-month high in October amid hopes that declining mortgage rates would stimulate demand for housing and help reduce an inventory overhang that has hampered new housing construction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-homebuilder-sentiment-vaults-6-month-high-october-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSWUERLIEJLGZABW2KKY55HGMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:03:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称，到 2029 年，北美的液化天然气出口能力将增加一倍多]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（U.S. Energy Information Administration）周四表示，美国的液化天然气出口商已宣布计划将美国的液化能力提高一倍以上，预计到2029年将增加139亿立方英尺/天（Bcf/d）。【原文：Liquefied natural gas exporters in the U.S. have announced plans to more than double U.S. liquefaction capacity, adding an estimated 13.9 billion cubic feet per day (Bcf/d) by 2029, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/north-americas-lng-export-capacity-could-more-than-double-by-2029-eia-says-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AE4KX2CC7BNZ3OS6OWRXE5PK2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[七国集团同意在中国出口管制问题上保持统一战线，实现供应商多元化]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲经济专员瓦尔蒂斯-东布罗夫斯基斯（Valdis Dombrovskis）周四表示，七国集团财长同意保持统一战线，协调对中国稀土出口管制的短期应对措施，并实现供应商多样化。【原文：Group of Seven finance ministers agreed to keep a united front and coordinate their short-term response to China's export controls on rare earths and to diversify suppliers, European Economic Commissioner Valdis Dombrovskis said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/g7-agrees-keep-united-front-china-export-controls-diversify-suppliers-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KI6E47FJ4NK2XBMN2WEHOLV5IA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储决策者对关税的关注使央行显得政治化：米兰]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周四表示，为了维护其极其重要的货币政策独立性，美联储决策者在谈论特朗普政府的政策时必须采取 "要么全盘接受，要么全盘否定 "的态度，这是他对其他决策者担心关税对经济影响的尖锐批评。【原文：To safeguard their critically important monetary policy independence, Federal Reserve policymakers must take an "all-or-nothing" approach to talking about the Trump administration's policies, Fed Governor Stephen Miran said on Thursday, a pointed critique of his fellow policymakers' concern about the impact of tariffs on the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-policymakers-focus-tariffs-makes-central-bank-seem-political-miran-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6G37R6AL5NNIVOSD5DDPLWWTTE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电展望人工智能需求强劲，芯片股上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周整个半导体行业数十亿美元的交易中，顶级合约芯片制造商台积电发布了一份乐观的预测，激发了人们对人工智能基础设施需求的乐观情绪，半导体类股周四走高。【原文：Semiconductor stocks advanced on Thursday after top contract chipmaker TSMC issued a rosy forecast, fanning optimism about demand for artificial intelligence infrastructure in a week of multi-billion-dollar deals across the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chip-stocks-rise-after-tsmcs-rosy-outlook-strong-ai-demand-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJQGDVAKWNLGFJSHZCJVAUY5CU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道明银行聘请业内资深人士担任总法律顾问和财务主管，以加强美国团队的实力]]></title><description><![CDATA[多伦多道明银行（Toronto Dominion Bank）周四任命业内资深人士布莱恩-卡莱纳（Brian Callanan）为美国总法律顾问，安德烈-拉莫斯（Andre Ramos）为美国财务主管。【原文：Toronto Dominion Bank on Thursday named industry veterans Brian Callanan as U.S. general counsel and Andre Ramos as U.S. finance head in the Canadian lender's latest push for a stronger footprint south of the border.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/td-bank-taps-industry-veterans-general-counsel-finance-head-roles-bolster-us-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3RHMKSJPNIDNCVINBMOQHL2NU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国间谍头目警告人工智能的危险，但并非灾难片中的厄运]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国军情五处（MI5）间谍机构负责人周四表示，不受人类控制的人工智能系统有朝一日可能会对安全构成威胁，但他并不是在预测科幻电影中描述的末日场景。【原文：AI systems acting without human control could one day pose a security threat, the head of Britain's MI5 spy agency said on Thursday, although he said he was not predicting doom scenarios as depicted in sci-fi movies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-spy-chief-warns-ai-danger-though-not-disaster-movie-doom-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJO53HC6PVNYBBZ7SOC2O4QOSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经纪商施瓦布凭借客户资产和交易实力实现创纪录利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经纪公司嘉信理财（Charles Schwab）周四公布的第三季度利润超出预期，原因是客户资产创下新纪录，交易收入飙升。【原文：U.S. brokerage firm Charles Schwab beat third-quarter profit expectations on Thursday as client assets hit a new record and trading revenue soared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-broker-schwab-clinches-record-profit-client-assets-trading-strength-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5Y6TBWN45JHNJSPJRMYPHHLEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）上调亚洲经济增长预期并警告风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周四上调了亚洲经济增长预期，但警告称贸易政策不确定性和地缘政治紧张局势将给亚洲经济前景带来风险。【原文：The International Monetary Fund revised up Asia's economic growth forecast on Thursday, but warned of risks to the outlook from trade policy uncertainty and geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/imf-upgrades-asias-growth-forecast-warns-risks-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFEJVXUDCJLCXGEEV7J4F7SETM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:19:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大西洋沿岸中部地区 10 月份制造业收缩；价格措施增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，美国大西洋中部地区的工厂活动出人意料地萎缩，更多的制造商报告称，他们支付和收到的投入品和货物价格上涨，这表明通胀仍有可能进一步上升。【原文：Factory activity in the U.S. mid-Atlantic region unexpectedly contracted in October, and more manufacturers reported paying and receiving higher prices for inputs and their goods, suggesting inflation could still rise further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-mid-atlantic-manufacturing-contracts-october-price-measures-increase-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I762CT4YV5JF5BXVL6CMWKXZGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:16:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰银行上调 2025 年和 2026 年黄金均价预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于地缘政治紧张局势、经济不确定性和美元走软所带来的避险需求，汇丰银行将 2025 年黄金平均价格预测从每盎司 3215 美元上调至 3355 美元。【原文：HSBC has raised its 2025 average gold price forecast to $3,355 per ounce from $3,215 due to safe-haven demand driven by geopolitical tensions, economic uncertainty, and a weakening U.S. dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/hsbc-raises-average-gold-price-forecasts-2025-2026-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5CEKGXKLNJFDBAJDC3PJZBQQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:16:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席沃勒尔赞成在就业市场担忧的情况下于 10 月降息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）周四表示，由于就业市场状况喜忧参半，他同意在本月晚些时候举行的美国央行政策会议上再次降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Christopher Waller said on Thursday he's on board with another interest rate cut at the U.S. central bank's policy meeting later this month because of the mixed readings on the state of the job market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-waller-favors-25-basis-point-rate-cut-october-amid-job-market-worries-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZJEQGAJIRPVZAZSAVYH3C3V7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软为 Windows 11 推出新的人工智能升级，增强 Copilot 功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周四为 Windows 11 推出了一系列人工智能升级，使其 Copilot 人工智能助手更容易自动执行任务和跨设备连接服务，从而对用户更具吸引力。【原文：Microsoft on Thursday rolled out a series of artificial intelligence upgrades to Windows 11 that would make its Copilot AI assistant more appealing to users by making it easier to automate tasks and connect with services across devices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-launches-new-ai-upgrades-windows-11-boosting-copilot-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64AQO7C74BPD5LL6HX3F3NLYVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft 将在多伦多开设技术中心，进一步拓展美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[打车公司 Lyft 周四表示，计划明年下半年在多伦多市中心开设一个新的技术中心，使多伦多成为仅次于旧金山的第二大技术中心。【原文：Lyft plans to open a new technology hub in downtown Toronto in the second half of next year, making the city its second-largest tech center after San Francisco, the ride-hailing firm said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lyft-open-toronto-tech-hub-deepening-push-beyond-us-market-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q546VNNGVVIIXHA5JEKTCSI3EY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IAM 对波音公司提出不公平劳动行为指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际机械师和航空航天工人协会周四表示，它已向美国全国劳工关系委员会（National Labor Relations Board）提出对波音公司不公平劳动行为的指控。【原文：The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers said on Thursday it has filed an unfair labor practice charge against Boeing with the National Labor Relations Board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/iam-files-unfair-labor-practice-charge-against-boeing-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFGJX4437ZJXDFGYN2BI4VWVJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:55:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[老挝计划在 2026 年初之前关闭加密货币矿机]]></title><description><![CDATA[老挝能源部副部长告诉路透社，老挝正在考虑到 2026 年第一季度停止向加密货币矿工供电，因为老挝希望将国内电力转向对经济增长贡献更大的行业。【原文：Laos is considering halting electricity supply to cryptocurrency miners by the first quarter of 2026, as it seeks to redirect domestic power to industries that contribute more to economic growth, the country's deputy energy minister told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/laos-plans-pull-plug-crypto-miners-by-early-2026-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7OE4GS3JVI4NJAINDVZZTKJVQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴金消费者正在消费，但不像大流行病时期那么旺盛]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周四表示，在低失业率和工资增长的情况下，消费者仍在继续消费，但与大流行病时期相比，他们的消费受到了更多限制。【原文：Consumers continue to spend given low unemployment and wage gains, but are more constrained than during the pandemic years, Richmond Fed president Thomas Barkin said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-barkin-consumers-are-spending-not-flush-pandemic-years-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGK2WTRM5NJFHK4RGAXFHKJJEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 8 月经济活动增幅低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行周四公布的数据显示，8月份巴西经济活动增幅低于预期，越来越多的经济学家预计，在紧缩货币政策的影响下，巴西经济将出现更大幅度的放缓。【原文：Brazil's economic activity increased less than expected in August, central bank data showed on Thursday, as a growing chorus of economists anticipate a sharper slowdown ahead amid tight monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-economic-activity-rises-less-than-expected-august-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2YVVMWN2NLY7K2VA5ZDJRWGBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁格奥尔基耶娃敦促各国继续将贸易作为增长引擎]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周四敦促各成员国在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收新关税的情况下，继续将贸易作为世界经济增长的引擎。【原文：International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva on Thursday urged member countries to keep trade as an engine of growth for the world economy despite President Donald Trump's steep new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/imfs-georgieva-urges-countries-keep-trade-engine-growth-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVVHEL5YNRKGFCTIXETX23UGGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:25:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的沃勒：现有数据显示劳动力持续疲软，为降息提供支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）周四表示，即使在美国政府就业报告未及时公布的情况下，现有数据也始终显示出招聘疲软的情况，这增强了美联储降息的必要性，即使其他数据显示经济增长稳健。【原文：Data available even in the absence of delayed U.S. government employment reports tells a consistent story of weak hiring, bolstering the need for the Federal Reserve to cut rates even as other data points to solid economic growth, Fed Governor Christopher Waller said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-waller-available-data-show-ongoing-labor-weakness-bolstering-rate-cut-case-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CBSDXFLFBL47NM4OYKH2T3NAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[StanChart 称，外汇储备管理者对美元走势作出反应，而非推动美元走势]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行（Standard Chartered）在周四的一份报告中称，储备经理们倾向于在美元走弱时买入美元，而在美元上涨时卖出美元，这表明他们在推动美元走强方面所起的作用可能不如私人投资者。【原文：Reserve managers tend to buy the dollar when it weakens and sell when it rises, suggesting they might play a lesser role in driving the greenback than private investors, Standard Chartered said in a note on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/fx-reserve-managers-react-not-drive-dollar-moves-stanchart-says-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVZ46FCJ65L3VB7FXWQ5FNNMIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席米兰：明年经济增长取决于中美紧张局势如何解决 - Fox Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）表示，未来一年的经济增长可能取决于围绕中美贸易不断升级的风险是实现了还是化解了。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran said economic growth for the coming year could turn on whether the escalating risks around U.S.-China trade are realized or defused.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/feds-miran-growth-next-year-could-hinge-how-us-china-tensions-are-resolved-fox-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZRROXEJBZNPBAFYXYPQEB4CHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其电信、土耳其电信和沃达丰在土耳其 29.5 亿美元的 5G 招标中赢得频率]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其 5G 频谱招标周四吸引了总计 29.5 亿美元的中标，土耳其主要运营商 Turkcell、沃达丰和土耳其电信获得了 700 MHz 和 3.5 GHz 频率范围内的关键频段。【原文：Turkey's 5G spectrum tender drew a total of $2.95 billion in winning bids on Thursday, with the country's major operators Turkcell, Vodafone and Turk Telekom securing key blocks across the 700 MHz and 3.5 GHz frequency ranges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/turkcell-turk-telekom-vodafone-win-frequencies-turkeys-295-billion-5g-tender-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EA46WPRKRKFRNNKOZAMB6Q6BA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工具制造商斯纳普-昂（Snap-On）季度业绩超出预期，因维修需求增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，由于汽车零部件公司和维修店的需求复苏促进了公司工具制造产品的销售，斯耐普公司第三季度的收入和利润均超出预期。【原文：Snap-On beat third-quarter revenue and profit estimates on Thursday as recovering demand from auto parts companies and repair shops boosted sales for the company's tool-making products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/toolmaker-snap-on-tops-quarterly-estimates-repair-demand-revs-up-2025-10-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROH5YDVNQ5LJDLGLQTJGCQ73CU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:23:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>