<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:23:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:23:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德首席财务官表示，iShares 的年度流入量有望创下历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德（BlackRock）首席财务官马丁-斯莫尔（Martin Small）周二表示，贝莱德的 iShares 产品今年有望实现创纪录的年流入量，并成为有机基础费用增长最强劲的年份之一。【原文：BlackRock is on track for record annual inflows into its iShares products this year and for one of its strongest years for organic base-fee growth, Chief Financial Officer Martin Small said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackrock-track-record-annual-flows-into-ishares-says-cfo-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5RCWGW6BVM2LNZRAEDJH4HZBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府免除美国航空公司因轮椅问题被罚的 1,670 万美元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部周二表示，将在 2024 年免除对时任总统乔-拜登领导下的美国航空公司开出的 1670 万美元罚单，作为该航空公司对待残疾乘客的和解协议的一部分，其中包括未能为一些残疾乘客提供足够的帮助以及对轮椅处理不当。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department said Tuesday it will waive $16.7 million in fines issued to American Airlines under then President Joe Biden in 2024 as part of a settlement over the air carrier's treatment of disabled passengers, including failing to provide some with adequate assistance and mishandling wheelchairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-waives-167-million-fines-american-airlines-over-wheelchair-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYEMBXIAYJIOBHWXVXJPIEIA7A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者局以资金短缺为由发布 "临时最终 "开放银行规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护最高监督机构周二表示，它将发布有关 "开放银行 "和消费者数据权利的临时法规，因为它预计在完成目前正在进行的重写拜登时代法规的程序之前，资金将耗尽。【原文：The top U.S. watchdog agency for consumer financial protection said Tuesday it will issue interim regulations for "open banking" and consumer data rights because it expects to run out of money before completing a process now underway to rewrite Biden-era regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-consumer-bureau-issue-interim-final-open-banking-rule-cites-funding-shortfall-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYZQOOBUWFI2HI2LFT4CE6MMFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团首席财务官梅森预计第四季度投资银行业务增长率在 20%左右]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团首席财务官马克-梅森（Mark Mason）周二表示，预计第四季度投资银行业务费用将比去年同期增长 20%左右。【原文：Citigroup Chief Financial Officer Mark Mason said on Tuesday that fourth-quarter investment banking fees are expected to be increase by a percentage in the mid 20s compared with a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-cfo-mason-expects-investment-banking-climb-mid-20s-fourth-quarter-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDZTH2JM7BJMTGXZRLICPL3YMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:55:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，SpaceX 将于 2026 年进行首次公开募股，融资额将超过 300 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）正在推进首次公开募股计划，该计划将寻求大幅融资300多亿美元，目标估值约为1.5万亿美元。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX is moving ahead with plans for an initial public offering that would seek to raise significantly more than $30 billion and target a valuation of about $1.5 trillion, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spacex-pursue-2026-ipo-raising-above-30-billion-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIV3XNWDFVMONA4X7PWAGLU5UA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来拟斥资 60 亿美元在阿拉巴马州建厂，推动美国制造业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周二表示，将投资 60 多亿美元在阿拉巴马州亨茨维尔新建一座活性药物成分生产厂，以扩大美国的生产规模并加强药品供应链。【原文：Eli Lilly said on Tuesday it will invest more than $6 billion in a new active drug ingredient manufacturing facility in Huntsville, Alabama, to expand U.S. production and bolster medicine supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eli-lilly-build-6-billion-alabama-plant-part-us-manufacturing-push-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42G7ECAVFNOL3MHR4AJNC725PM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:34:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 聘用 Slack 首席执行官 Denise Dresser 担任首席营收官]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周二任命 Slack 首席执行官 Denise Dresser 为其首席营收官，因为这家 ChatGPT 制造商希望扩大其企业业务。【原文：OpenAI on Tuesday appointed Slack CEO Denise Dresser as its chief revenue officer, as the ChatGPT maker looks to expand its enterprise business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-taps-slack-ceo-denise-dresser-chief-revenue-officer-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABM46DYY3BLKJE53DPANO2DXYM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:26:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文对 OpenAI 的依赖面临审查，债务推动的人工智能建设引发担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在甲骨文公司 4000 多亿美元的合同积压点燃股市狂潮几个月后，人们对其依赖 OpenAI 和债务推动的数据中心建设的热情已经让位给了质疑，而这将是甲骨文公司周三财报的主要内容。【原文：Months after Oracle's $400 billion-plus contract backlog ignited a stock-market frenzy, the enthusiasm has given way to doubts about its reliance on OpenAI and debt-fueled datacenter buildout, which will dominate its earnings on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/oracles-openai-reliance-faces-scrutiny-debt-fueled-ai-buildout-raises-worries-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGSRKJNQ7RIN7MKZH3OT7TCKO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行监管机构称银行可充当加密货币中介机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家银行监管机构周二表示，将允许银行充当加密货币交易的中介机构，这是特朗普政府为缩小传统金融部门与加密货币活动之间的差距而采取的最新举措。【原文：Banks will be allowed to act as intermediaries on crypto transactions, a national U.S. bank regulator said on Tuesday, in the latest step by the Trump administration to narrow the gap between the traditional financial sector and crypto activities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-bank-regulator-says-banks-can-act-crypto-intermediaries-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5IXGFRZW5K6BLEAUVPRTNPGVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通预计第四季度投资银行业务收入增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通消费者和社区银行业务首席执行官玛丽安-莱克（Marianne Lake）周二表示，摩根大通预计第四季度投资银行业务收入将以较低的个位数百分比增长，同时预计第四季度市场业务收入将以较低的十位数百分比增长。【原文：JPMorgan Chase expects investment banking revenue to be up by the low-single digit percentages in the fourth quarter, while it expects markets revenue to be up in the low-teens percentages in the fourth quarter, its consumer and community banking CEO Marianne Lake said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-chase-expects-fourth-quarter-investment-banking-revenue-rise-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAP7KEI5SNKMVD7I2MM3BSSLXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为美联储长期不和预热]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计本周将举行的美联储政策会议将是多年来最富争议性的会议之一，这很可能成为金融市场对 2026 年美国货币政策辩论将如何发展的路演测试。【原文：What is expected to be one of the most ructious Federal Reserve policy meetings in years this week could well prove to be the road test for financial markets on how U.S. monetary policy debates will shape up in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-warm-up-long-spell-discordant-fed-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VI7WOMHGIBMS3MZUUAZQO2SKJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:45:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，壳牌正在就以 30 多亿美元收购 LLOG 勘探公司进行深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，壳牌正在就收购 LLOG Exploration Offshore 进行深入谈判，交易价值超过 30 亿美元。【原文：Shell is in advanced talks to buy LLOG Exploration Offshore in a deal worth more than $3 billion, two sources familiar with the matter said, a move that would boost the oil major's upstream portfolio through one of the largest privately held oil and gas producers in the U.S. Gulf.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/shell-advanced-talks-buy-llog-exploration-more-than-3-billion-sources-say-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMBK46NNHROPRHVKZBIBOWSN6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:30:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[恢复对华销售后，美国农业部维持美国大豆出口前景不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部在周二发布的月度报告中维持美国大豆出口预期不变，原因是在与华盛顿的贸易战陷入僵局数月之后，美国大豆恢复了对中国的销售，而中国是美国大豆的最大进口国。【原文：The U.S. Department of Agriculture left its U.S. soybean export forecast unchanged in a monthly report on Tuesday as sales to China have resumed after the top importer shunned purchases for months amid a bruising trade war with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/usda-leaves-us-soybean-export-outlook-unchanged-after-china-sales-resume-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7D4AUZ2HC5LDPKRE3E463PJTZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:06:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国机构称，今年全球贸易将增长 7%，超过创纪录的 35 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国贸易与发展署周二表示，今年全球贸易将增长约7%，有望超过创纪录的35万亿美元。【原文：Global trade is set to grow by about 7% this year and is on track to exceed a record $35 trillion, the UN Trade and Development Agency said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-trade-set-grow-7-pass-record-35-trillion-this-year-un-agency-says-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXHL7CE6AFJLXAVXUS2DURRPEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国的 Merz 就 X 罚款问题：在这里运营要遵守我们的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理周二回应美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对社交媒体平台 X 的罚款的批评时说，包括美国公司在内的外国公司在德国运营时必须遵守德国和欧盟的规定。【原文：Foreign companies, including those from the United States, must obey German and EU rules when they operate there, Germany's chancellor said on Tuesday, responding to U.S. President Donald Trump's criticism of a fine imposed on social media platform X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/germanys-merz-x-fine-obey-our-laws-if-you-operate-here-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSLBVALN7RLFHMFG4JMDBW5N6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:52:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛首席财务官预计并购势头将持续到 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）财务总监丹尼斯-科尔曼（Denis Coleman）表示，今年有望成为全行业历史上宣布并购规模第二大的一年，这对 2026 年来说是一个令人鼓舞的信号。【原文：Goldman Sachs says this year is on track to become the second-biggest in history for announced mergers and acquisitions industrywide, an encouraging sign for 2026, according to its finance chief Denis Coleman.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-cfo-expects-ma-momentum-continue-into-2026-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PRNXJOYPJORJOW54VZEXO7EVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[渴望好莱坞的海湾国家为派拉蒙竞购华纳兄弟提供资金支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙天舞公司（Paramount Skydance）以 1,080 亿美元恶意竞购华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery），并将三家海湾地区主权财富基金纳入其竞购阵营，这标志着各州在建立自己的娱乐产业时结成了相对罕见的联盟。【原文：Paramount Skydance's addition of three Gulf sovereign wealth funds to the cast of its $108 billion hostile bid for Warner Bros Discovery marks a relatively rare alliance among the states as they build their own entertainment industries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hollywood-hungry-gulf-states-bankroll-paramounts-warner-bros-bid-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULZGYWAN3NNXBDTCYCVUXP3AEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷朋 Meta 眼镜起飞，但面临隐私和竞争考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[依视路公司（EssilorLuxottica）在智能眼镜领域下了大赌注，而这场豪赌即将面临考验。该公司的雷朋 Meta 眼镜采用人工智能技术，今年首次实现了有意义的收入增长，但分析师警告说，隐私问题和新竞争对手的涌入可能会限制其增长。【原文：EssilorLuxottica is betting big on smart eyewear and the gamble is about to be tested. Its Ray-Ban Meta glasses, powered by artificial intelligence, have delivered their first meaningful revenue boost this year, but analysts warn that privacy concerns and a wave of new rivals could limit their growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ray-ban-meta-glasses-take-off-face-privacy-competition-test-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOBWM2U7PJMZHK3KPPNQQGXACA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美对华鹰派称特朗普批准向中国出售英伟达芯片将为中国军力增效]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿的中国强硬派抨击特朗普政府允许英伟达（Nvidia）向中国运送其第二款最先进的人工智能芯片的决定，理由是担心中国政府可能利用这项技术来加强其军事力量。【原文：China hardliners in Washington slammed the Trump administration for its decision to allow Nvidia to ship its second most advanced AI chip to China, citing fears Beijing could harness the technology to supercharge its military.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-hawks-say-trump-approved-nvidia-chip-sales-china-will-supercharge-its-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6FM7AEUFRL6DFNFG5NC6EWGHA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:11:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音 11 月交付量下降 17%，落后于空客]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二表示，11月份交付了44架新喷气式飞机，低于上个月的53架，落后于欧洲竞争对手空中客车公司（Airbus），后者交付了72架飞机。【原文：Boeing delivered 44 new jets in November, down from 53 the prior month, the company said on Tuesday, lagging behind European rival Airbus which delivered 72 planes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-deliveries-fall-17-november-trail-airbus-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJUUKRINGZLZPGLOL5AWQGVFKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫顾问哈塞特：降息的 "空间很大" - 华尔街日报]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）也被认为是美联储下一任主席的热门人选，他周二表示，进一步降息的 "空间很大"，但如果通胀上升，降息的计算方法可能会改变。【原文：White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett, also presumed front-runner to be the Federal Reserve's next chair, said Tuesday that there is "plenty of room" to cut interest rates further, though if inflation rises the calculation may change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/white-house-advisor-hassett-plenty-room-cut-rates-wsj-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQVESW7XGNPD5PGTYNBVB3WHAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空客获中国批准交付喷气机，但仍在等待新订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司表示，该公司已获得中方同意，继续交付之前订购的120架喷气式飞机，但在北京签署的协议让这家欧洲飞机制造商仍在等待数百架喷气式飞机新订单的进展。【原文：Airbus has secured Chinese agreement to go ahead with the delivery of 120 previously ordered jets, the company said, but the deal signed in Beijing leaves the European planemaker still waiting for progress on a new order for hundreds of jets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-gets-china-nod-jet-deliveries-still-awaiting-new-order-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PBYWDUDZFO7JGVIUNLD56ZFKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:45:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KeyCorp 首席执行官加倍重视股票回购，排除收购可能]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国地区性贷款机构 KeyCorp 首席执行官 Chris Gorman 周二表示，尽管行业出现整合，但 KeyCorp 不会寻求收购，并将把多余的资金用于股票回购。【原文：U.S. regional lender KeyCorp is not looking to pursue acquisitions despite consolidation in the industry and will use its excess capital for share buybacks, CEO Chris Gorman said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/keycorp-ceo-doubles-down-share-buybacks-rules-out-acquisitions-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADYGRD3OJJLZNCCXWWGYTDQCEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份职位空缺小幅增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 10 月份的职位空缺略有增加，但由于雇主们在不确定的经济环境中艰难前行，招聘工作依然低迷。【原文：U.S. job openings increased marginally in October, but hiring remained subdued as employers navigated an uncertain economic environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-job-openings-increase-modestly-october-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2WPPPBBKZOKJCJ7HCDTY2EUQE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合利华首席执行官表示，联合利华每年拨款 17 亿美元用于并购，重点是美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华首席执行官费尔南多-费尔南德斯（Fernando Fernandez）周二表示，联合利华每年将拨出约 15 亿欧元（17.4 亿美元）用于并购，重点是在美国的交易。【原文：Unilever is allocating about 1.5 billion euros ($1.74 billion) a year for mergers and acquisitions, focusing heavily on deals in the United States, CEO Fernando Fernandez said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/unilever-allocates-17-billion-year-ma-with-us-focus-says-ceo-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWHQF7VGFRO33G7YGE57UT4KNM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:11:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify 向美国和加拿大的高级用户扩展音乐视频访问权限，以对抗 YouTube]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify 周二表示，将向美国和加拿大的高级订户提供音乐视频，这家瑞典流媒体巨头将在市场份额上向 YouTube 发起挑战。【原文：Spotify said on Tuesday it is making music videos available to premium subscribers in the U.S. and Canada, as the Swedish streaming giant challenges YouTube for market share.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/spotify-expands-music-videos-access-premium-users-us-canada-take-youtube-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HZWH4PSM5OLHELKZVKI2JAFB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：维基百科运营商任命前美国驻智利大使为首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[维基百科运营商维基媒体基金会周二任命伯纳黛特-米汉（Bernadette Meehan）为首席执行官，选拔一位具有深厚政策专业知识和联邦政府工作经验的管理者来领导这本在线百科全书。【原文：Wikimedia Foundation, the operator of Wikipedia, on Tuesday named Bernadette Meehan its chief executive officer, tapping an administrator with deep policy expertise and federal government experience to lead the online encyclopedia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/wikipedia-operator-taps-former-us-ambassador-chile-ceo-role-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5RBKCHTLFMDVLSDL6FPHN4SXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:35:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国运输部称，因 A320 软件更新而中断航班的乘客无权获得航空公司赔偿]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部周二表示，上个月因政府紧急指令更新空客A320飞机软件而延误或取消美国航班的航空公司无需为受影响的乘客提供酒店、餐饮或其他福利。【原文：Airlines that delayed or cancelled U.S. flights last month due to an emergency government directive to update the software on Airbus A320 planes were not required to provide hotels, meals or other benefits to impacted passengers, the U.S. Transportation Department said Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/passengers-disrupted-by-a320-software-update-not-entitled-airline-compensation-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6XOKNR6DVIKLAR56KIYZAUZ74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利制定个人数据保护苛刻条款，为中国 JD.com 收购 Ceconomy 案扫清障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二看到的一份政府法令显示，意大利在个人数据保护方面制定了严格的条款，以批准中国电子商务巨头京东商城对德国电子产品零售商 Ceconomy 的收购。【原文：Italy has set tough terms on personal data protection to clear Chinese e-commerce giant JD.com's takeover of German electronics retailer Ceconomy , a government decree seen by Reuters showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/italy-sets-tough-terms-personal-data-protection-clear-chinese-jdcoms-takeover-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5YFXJGHVFI6ZCWOIXR4QFXXTQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃森哲与 Anthropic 建立多年合作关系，促进人工智能的应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃森哲和 Anthropic 周二宣布通过一个新的业务集团扩大双方的合作关系，该咨询巨头的约 30,000 名员工将接受这家人工智能初创公司 Claude 模型的培训。【原文：Accenture and Anthropic on Tuesday announced an expansion of their partnership through a new business group where around 30,000 of the consulting giant's employees will be trained on the AI startup's Claude model.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/accenture-anthropic-strike-multi-year-partnership-boost-ai-adoption-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6UKYXNP4JNQ3CYMGMXYKZDXFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:20:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>