<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 09:09:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 09:09:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行称，有美元敞口的欧元区银行需要更多缓冲资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）周三表示，拥有大型美元业务的欧元区贷款机构应增加其流动性和资本缓冲，以抵御美国货币的任何紧缩。【原文：Euro zone lenders with big dollar businesses should bulk up their liquidity and capital cushions to withstand any squeeze in the U.S. currency, the European Central Bank said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/euro-zone-banks-with-dollar-exposure-need-more-buffers-ecb-says-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLJBMQUS2NJL7I47QJC4P6Q2CM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 09:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称现代汽车将因后视镜图像问题召回 143,472 辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，现代汽车美国公司（Hyundai Motor America）将在美国召回143472辆圣达菲（Santa Fe）和圣达菲混合动力车（Santa Fe Hybrid），原因是后视摄像头可能安装不当。【原文：Hyundai Motor America is recalling 143,472 Santa Fe and Santa Fe Hybrid vehicles in the U.S. over rearview cameras which may not have been installed properly, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-recall-143472-us-vehicles-over-rearview-image-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MR74JR265JIHFMW6N5XWZN5HE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称消费者信心改善，维持经济 "温和 "复苏的观点]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府在周三公布的月度报告中称，尽管通货膨胀持续存在，但消费者对经济的信心正在恢复。【原文：Japan's government said consumer sentiment on the economy was recovering despite persistent inflation in a monthly report published on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-says-consumer-sentiment-improving-keeping-its-view-moderate-economic-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2RFN25F6FPEDFM2EUNEHHMWDI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特朗普团队正在与台湾商谈贸易协议，这将有助于培训美国工人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据五位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府正在就一项协议进行谈判，该协议可能使台湾承诺在半导体制造和其他先进产业领域进行新的投资并培训美国工人。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is negotiating a deal that could commit Taiwan to fresh investment and training of U.S. workers in semiconductor manufacturing and other advanced industries, according to five people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-team-negotiating-trade-deal-with-taiwan-that-could-help-train-us-workers-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBFVBDNDSBJM5J2IZSKWCDX3GE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IQM Quantum Computers 将投资 4000 多万欧元扩建芬兰生产基地]]></title><description><![CDATA[IQM 量子计算机公司（IQM Quantum Computers）表示，该公司将投资 4000 多万欧元（4600 万美元）扩建位于芬兰的生产基地。【原文：IQM Quantum Computers - seen as a key player in Europe's attempts to compete globally in the quantum computer sector - will invest more than 40 million euros ($46 million) to expand a production site in Finland, said the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/iqm-quantum-computers-invest-more-than-40-million-euros-expanding-finland-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWU74MDQPRNYVN5IA3IX6TS2LM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:01:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步和 WeRide 在阿布扎比推出无人驾驶机器人出租车]]></title><description><![CDATA[继去年宣布与中国自动驾驶公司 WeRide 合作之后，优步科技公司周三在阿布扎比推出了无人驾驶机器人出租车。【原文：Uber Technologies rolled out driverless robotaxis in Abu Dhabi in partnership with Chinese autonomous-driving firm WeRide on Wednesday, following the tie-up they announced last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/uber-weride-launch-driverless-robotaxis-abu-dhabi-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSSHPHEY5BLDDJSZH5KAFCOSMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 07:57:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉表示重视中国供应商，不排除任何原产地供应商]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉中国公司的一位高管周三表示，这家美国汽车制造商非常重视中国供应商的作用，不会因为原产国或地理位置而排斥任何中国供应商。【原文：A top Tesla China executive said on Wednesday the U.S. automaker values the role of China-based suppliers and does not exclude any on the basis of country of origin or geographical location.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-says-it-values-china-suppliers-does-not-exclude-any-by-origin-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANNE4BFBFZN4XGZOCGGD7JXEKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 07:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利就 WhatsApp 中的人工智能工具扩大对 Meta 的反垄断调查范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利反垄断机构周三表示，已扩大了对 Meta Platforms 公司的调查范围，因为该公司被指控通过在信息服务 WhatsApp 上使用人工智能工具滥用其支配地位。【原文：Italy's antitrust authority said on Wednesday it had broadened the scope of its investigation into Meta Platforms over allegations the company abused its dominant position through the use of its artificial intelligence tools on messaging service WhatsApp.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/italy-competition-watchdog-broadens-probe-into-meta-over-ai-tools-whatsapp-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAYHHPFY2RNSRLMA7563GPZP6M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 07:22:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚青少年请求高等法院阻止社交媒体禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[针对澳大利亚禁止 16 岁以下儿童使用社交媒体的规定，澳大利亚最高法院收到了一份宪法挑战书，距离这项世界首例法律生效还有两周时间。【原文：A constitutional challenge against Australia’s social media ban on children younger than 16 has been filed in the nation’s highest court, two weeks before the world-first law is set to take effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-teenagers-ask-high-court-block-social-media-ban-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SOIWWNB5VVMJRB5JBEY7VAKPBY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 07:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能打开了中世纪犹太记录的巨大宝库]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列的研究人员希望通过将一千年前的手稿数字数据库加载到一个使用人工智能的新转录工具中，从而对犹太历史有新的发现。【原文：Researchers in Israel are hoping to make new discoveries about Jewish history by loading a digital database of manuscripts stretching back a thousand years into a new transcription tool that uses artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/vast-trove-medieval-jewish-records-opened-up-by-ai-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4FNALXPPNICPDODURFITLJRGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 07:04:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官马斯克称下个月奥斯汀机器人出租车队将增加一倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周二表示，继 6 月份在德克萨斯州奥斯汀市推出自动驾驶服务后，12 月份该市的机器人出租车数量将翻一番。【原文：Tesla Chief Executive Elon Musk said on Tuesday that the number of robotaxis in Austin, Texas, will double in December, following the rollout of its self-driving service in the city in June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-ceo-musk-says-austin-robotaxi-fleet-double-next-month-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G66OC4LDOBOIVEQE7AZHAF7HDA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 06:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：特斯拉努力从销量滑坡中修正航向]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）今年大部分时间都在专注于这家汽车制造商对机器人技术的追求，以及为其新近推出的 1 万亿美元薪酬方案赢得股东批准。与此同时，特斯拉的主营业务--汽车销售--的前景却越来越暗淡。【原文：Tesla CEO Elon Musk has spent much of this year focused on the carmaker’s robotics pursuits and winning shareholder approval for his freshly minted $1 trillion pay package. In the meantime, the outlook for Tesla's main business – selling cars – is darkening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-struggles-course-correct-sales-skid-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73HAXZC2BRPABDOJ77SGZDSSF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 06:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标里夫斯占据中心舞台]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔-斯图尔特-亨特（Gregor Stuart Hunter）展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天：【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNYUKCII5NOFHKOPNRB6CO6Z6E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 05:33:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对国家支持的担忧加剧，中国万科债券下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国有房地产开发商万科的债券周三暴跌，再次引发了市场对中央政府可能在多大程度上支持受危机冲击的房地产行业的担忧。【原文：Chinese state-backed property developer Vanke's bonds tumbled on Wednesday, reigniting market concerns about the extent of potential central government support for the crisis-hit sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-vanke-bonds-slump-concerns-mount-over-state-support-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6WTOY3PVVJWHNFWTXNUSVL7TU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 04:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡封杀与激进主义有关的澳大利亚人的 TikTok 和 Meta 账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡内政部周二表示，新加坡已下令 TikTok 和 Meta 屏蔽一名澳大利亚男子的账户在新加坡的访问，当局称该男子导致了两名新加坡公民的激进化。【原文：Singapore has ordered TikTok and Meta to block access in Singapore to the accounts of an Australian man authorities say has contributed to the radicalisation of two of its citizens, the ministry of home affairs said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/singapore-blocks-tiktok-meta-accounts-australian-linked-radicalisation-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFJBIB7BPRIEHLTJ7X6NHXZYHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 04:53:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood和Susquehanna收购交易所LedgerX，推动预测市场发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood Markets 和苏斯克汉纳国际集团周二达成了一项协议，将接管迈阿密国际控股公司运营的一家受监管交易所，从而大大推动了这两家公司在预测市场建立据点的进程。【原文：Robinhood Markets and Susquehanna International Group on Tuesday struck a deal to take over a regulated exchange run by Miami International Holdings , giving the companies a major boost in their push to establish a stronghold in prediction markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/robinhood-susquehanna-take-over-exchange-ledgerx-prediction-markets-push-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZAYRP6YF5KOPCO7OHIJH7OPOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 03:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，无人机在得克萨斯州抢断网线后，美国联邦航空局（FAA）对亚马逊进行调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周二援引美国联邦航空管理局（FAA）发言人的话报道，美国联邦航空管理局正在对亚马逊进行调查，因为上周亚马逊的一架送货无人机在德克萨斯州中部击落了一根网线。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration is probing Amazon after one of its delivery drones downed an internet cable in central Texas last week, CNBC reported on Tuesday, citing a Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) spokesperson.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/faa-probes-amazon-after-delivery-drone-snaps-internet-cable-texas-cnbc-reports-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSEH2JZ25FLC7MG5FESWVCB3OM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:39:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国在新交易中购买了至少 10 批美国大豆货物]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情交易商称，中国在周二以来签署的合同中购买了至少10船美国大豆，延续了近期中美贸易关系解冻后的购买热潮。【原文：China bought at least 10 cargoes of U.S. soybeans in contracts signed since Tuesday, two traders with knowledge of the deals said, extending a surge in buying after the recent thaw in U.S.-China trade relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-buys-least-10-us-soybean-cargoes-new-deals-sources-say-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLZ3N6V2CRN27FHMWOVVF6W5IM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰和谈将油价推至一个月低点后油价回稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，油价小幅回升，前一交易日曾跌至一个月低点，原因是有迹象表明乌克兰正接近与俄罗斯达成和平协议，这很可能导致国际社会结束对俄罗斯供应的制裁。【原文：Oil prices recovered slightly on Wednesday, after dipping to one-month lows in the previous session amid signs that Ukraine is nearing a peace deal with Russia that would likely lead to the end of international sanctions on Russian supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-stabilises-after-ukraine-peace-talks-push-prices-one-month-lows-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CBOF6OPLZPVHE7JFQ4URHXPQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:21:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[央行行长称澳大利亚金融状况受全球因素影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚一位高级央行官员周三表示，澳大利亚的金融状况受到全球因素的影响，低股票风险溢价和信贷息差表明该国的金融状况可能比其他国家要宽松。【原文：A senior Australian central banker said on Wednesday the country's financial conditions were influenced by global factors, with low equity risk premia and credit spreads suggesting conditions may be easier than otherwise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-financial-conditions-influenced-by-global-factors-central-banker-says-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUM6H7E3JZJB5J5OF5WEHWMUV4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国广汽传祺欧洲首家汽车厂目标年产量 30 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国长城汽车一位高管表示，该公司的目标是到2029年在欧洲年产30万辆汽车，目前正在为其首家汽车厂选址，以重振该地区疲软的销售业绩。【原文：China's Great Wall Motor is targeting annual production of 300,000 vehicles by 2029 in Europe where it is scouting locations for its first car plant in a battle to revive flagging regional sales, a company executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-gwm-targets-300000-annual-production-with-first-europe-car-plant-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67SUY4GVRJPZFBNO57N4D6J6YE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国数据疲软提振美联储降息押注，亚洲股市上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周三上涨，追随华尔街的涨势，因为弱于预期的经济数据刺激了对美联储将在下月政策会议上降息的预期。【原文：Asian stocks rose on Wednesday, chasing gains on Wall Street as weaker-than-expected economic data spurred expectations that the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates at its policy meeting next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELPJVDKM4VNEVEWDO7DJMROCMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注美国降息，美元下滑；新西兰央行决议公布后，新西兰元跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元汇率有所回落，因为良性的美国经济数据增强了12月降息的预期，而且投资者押注下一任美联储主席的主要候选人可能会将政策引向更加鸽派的方向。【原文：The dollar eased on Wednesday after benign U.S. economic data reinforced expectations of a December rate cut, and as investors wagered that the leading candidate for the next Federal Reserve chair may guide policy in a more dovish direction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-slips-investors-bet-us-rate-cuts-kiwi-jumps-after-rbnz-decision-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQP77NCFWNNX7DF65EW7FAAD2M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道日元疲软为政治蒙上阴影，日本央行为近期加息做准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着对日元暴跌的担忧重现，以及要求日本央行维持低利率的政治压力减弱，日本央行正在为最快下个月可能加息做准备，重拾此前的鹰派措辞。【原文：The Bank of Japan is preparing markets for a possible interest rate hike as soon as next month, sources say, reviving previous hawkish language as worries about sharp yen declines return and political pressure for the bank to keep rates low fades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-preps-markets-near-term-hike-weak-yen-overshadows-politics-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPNSGQV7XVJPLKNXI7ZK5JPOQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康获批在威斯康星州投资 5.69 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾富士康周三表示，该公司已获得监管部门批准在美国威斯康星州追加 5.69 亿美元的投资。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn said on Wednesday that it has won regulatory approval for an additional $569 million investment in the U.S. state of Wisconsin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/foxconn-wins-approval-new-569-million-investment-wisconsin-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLKXTUKC6FIQ5M76XQCIUCW3EQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:27:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《信息》报道，OpenAI 预计，到 2030 年，至少有 2.2 亿人将为 ChatGPT 付费]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能公司 OpenAI 预计，ChatGPT 每周至少有 2.2 亿用户会付费订阅。【原文：Artificial intelligence firm OpenAI has projected at least 220 million of ChatGPT weekly users will pay for a subscription, the Information reported on Tuesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-projected-least-220-million-people-will-pay-chatgpt-by-2030-information-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5DJFYD6YVIENASTYHTFLVITPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:20:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司获得价值 24.7 亿美元的合同，为美国空军增购 15 架 KC-46A 加油机]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国空军授予波音公司一份价值 24.7 亿美元的合同，增购 15 架 KC-46A 天马座空中加油机。【原文：The U.S. Air Force awarded Boeing a $2.47 billion contract for 15 additional KC-46A Pegasus aerial refueling tankers, the company announced on Tuesday in a release.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-wins-247-bln-contract-15-additional-us-air-force-kc-46a-tankers-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SHFVRTYEJKBHMOGCAPNYFHLFM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中国国家主席习近平 "或多或少同意 "加快购买美国商品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，他在周一的电话中向中国国家主席习近平施压，要求中国政府加快和增加对美国商品的购买，而中国领导人 "或多或少地同意了"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that he pressed Chinese President Xi Jinping to accelerate and increase Beijing's purchases of U.S. goods during a phone call on Monday, and the Chinese leader had "more or less agreed."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-chinas-xi-more-or-less-agreed-accelerate-purchases-us-goods-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7D2YRLPVS5JF7A7YJMUXN7XL2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:42:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Venture Global 与东京燃气签署 20 年液化天然气供应协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Global 公司周二表示，该公司已与日本首都天然气供应商东京燃气公司签署了一份为期 20 年的销售和采购协议（SPA），从 2030 年起每年向其供应 100 万公吨液化天然气。【原文：Venture Global said on Tuesday it has signed a 20-year sales and purchase agreement, or SPA, with Japan's capital city gas supplier, Tokyo Gas , to supply it with 1 million metric tonnes per annum of liquefied natural gas, starting in 2030.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venture-global-tokyo-gas-sign-20-year-lng-supply-deal-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFZ36EAWGJPZ3LDTWXBFCEYCIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Workday 季度订阅收入冷淡，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Workday 周二公布的第三季度订阅收入与华尔街预期一致，表明需求疲软，股价在盘后交易中下跌近 7%。【原文：Workday reported third-quarter subscription revenue in line with Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, signaling softer demand and sending its shares down nearly 7% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/workday-posts-lukewarm-quarterly-subscription-revenue-shares-fall-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGM7OG3JGRIBXGJMURE3GKJPEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>