<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:42:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:42:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，李维斯限制假日购物季的选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 应对美国关税的策略很简单：在节假日购物季停止发售不那么受欢迎的款式，这样就可以避免通过打折来转移库存。【原文：Levi Strauss has a simple strategy to deal with U.S. tariffs: stop offering less-popular styles during the holiday shopping season so they can avoid having to offer discounts to move inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/levi-strauss-limits-selection-holiday-shopping-season-due-tariffs-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN2KQB24EJLIJCDIWYSRYYMBGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:23:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部就发行国债的市场容量征求交易商意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五就提高债务上限后如何重建现金余额，以及在不扰乱市场的情况下可以发行多少国库券等问题向一级交易商征求意见。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department on Friday asked primary dealers for input regarding how it should rebuild its cash balance following the increase in the debt ceiling, and how many Treasury bills it could issue without disrupting the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/treasury-seeks-dealer-input-market-capacity-t-bill-issuance-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJSNSDYOA5JWJEEGXNPBXYDOP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:14:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的铜关税给美国汽车业带来更多金属灾难]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁对进口铜征收50%的关税，这引起了美国汽车行业的警觉，因为这可能会使汽车制造商和供应商更加难以承受边境税和不断上涨的成本。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's threat of a 50% tariff on copper imports is raising alarm in the U.S. auto sector, as it could make it even harder for carmakers and suppliers to absorb border taxes and rising costs, executives and industry experts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trumps-copper-tariffs-pile-more-metal-misery-us-auto-industry-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQPS4NKVGRNXZOXWSJ6PH6V7V4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:03:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道受美国关税威胁影响，沃尔玛部分孟加拉国服装订单被搁置]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的三位工厂主和一位供应商的信件称，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁要对孟加拉国这个纺织中心征收 35% 的关税，沃尔玛的供应商已经推迟或搁置了孟加拉国服装制造商的一些订单。【原文：Suppliers to Walmart have delayed or put on hold some orders from garment manufacturers in Bangladesh, according to three factory owners and correspondence from a supplier seen by Reuters, as U.S. President Donald Trump's threat of a 35% tariff on the textile hub disrupts business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/some-walmart-garment-orders-bangladesh-hold-due-us-tariff-threat-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHQUO6AEXJNBRO5KBCJN62IBDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，卡夫亨氏正计划解体]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，包装食品制造商卡夫亨氏正准备自我解体。【原文：Packaged food maker Kraft Heinz is preparing to break itself up, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/kraft-heinz-prepares-spinoff-wsj-reports-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRKONM7JVZOBRNEO2GKVYFLFZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:56:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西监管机构再次推迟 Marfrig-BRF 股东大会]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西证券监管机构 CVM 周五在一份证券文件中说，巴西家禽和猪肉加工商 BRF 第二次推迟了对牛肉加工商 Marfrig 收购该公司的股东投票。【原文：Brazilian securities regulator CVM postponed for the second time a shareholder vote on the takeover of poultry and pork processor BRF by beef processor Marfrig , BRF said in a securities filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-regulator-again-postpones-shareholder-meeting-marfrig-brf-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNPJNDZUNBJ2NDZWCTVZAEIEEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:35:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉国家石油公司（PDVSA）石油出口猛增，2024 年海外销售额达 175 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份业绩文件，委内瑞拉国营石油公司（PDVSA）2024 年的海外石油销售额为 175.2 亿美元，由于美国允许外国合作伙伴在这个受制裁的欧佩克成员国开展业务，石油出口大幅增长。【原文：Venezuelan state-run PDVSA's oil sales abroad in 2024 stood at $17.52 billion, according to a results document seen by Reuters on Friday, as exports jumped due to U.S. licenses allowing foreign partners to operate in the sanctioned OPEC member.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuelas-pdvsa-oil-sales-abroad-hit-175-billion-2024-exports-jump-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36QVXC2HQVI3XIMG3PGEW5U6AU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:27:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自由港麦克莫兰公司有望从特朗普的铜关税中获益，而同行的选择不多]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果唐纳德-特朗普总统的铜关税政策得以实现，自由港麦克莫兰公司（Freeport-McMoRan）的年利润将增加 16 亿美元。【原文：Freeport-McMoRan could see a $1.6-billion boost to annual profit if President Donald Trump's copper tariff materializes, a benefit driven by the firm's role as the largest U.S. producer with more expansion options than rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/land-use-biodiversity/freeport-mcmoran-poised-gain-trumps-copper-tariff-against-peers-with-few-options-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHNNG4RQRRN5RPBPEBAPQHJCSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:54:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月预算数据显示特朗普关税征收额有望增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五将在其六月份的预算数据中披露唐纳德-特朗普总统关税收入的力度，因为多波新进口关税的征收开始成为政府的一个重要收入来源。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department on Friday will reveal the strength of President Donald Trump's tariff revenues in its June budget data, as collections from multiple waves of new import duties start to build into a substantial government revenue source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-tariff-collections-expected-grow-june-us-budget-data-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F76N32NP3ZK57AMXJLUNULQNJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资者回避气候和社会改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[晨星公司（Morningstar）的数据显示，在截至 6 月 30 日的 12 个月里，要求美国公司进行环境和社会改革的股东决议的支持率平均下降到 16%，只有三年前的一半。【原文：Support for shareholder resolutions pressing U.S. companies for environmental and social reforms fell to 16% on average for the 12 months ended June 30, half the rate of three years ago, data from Morningstar shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-investors-back-away-climate-social-reforms-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H772EZPHZZNMZNG22QJR26PM7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国月神人工智能公司发布开源模型，以夺回市场地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创企业月神人工智能公司（Moonshot AI）周五发布了一个新的开源人工智能模型，加入了本土竞争对手发布类似模型的浪潮，试图在竞争激烈的国内市场上夺回一席之地。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence startup Moonshot AI released a new open-source AI model on Friday, joining a wave of similar releases from local rivals, as it seeks to reclaim its position in the competitive domestic market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinas-moonshot-ai-releases-open-source-model-reclaim-market-position-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GY3HABX63VJD7AXZWGD267VDGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员称美联航和捷蓝航空的合作可能会损害竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员理查德-布卢门撒尔（Richard Blumenthal）说，美国联合航空公司和较小的捷蓝航空公司之间拟议的合作可能会损害竞争，导致消费者的选择更少、更贵。【原文：Democratic Senator Richard Blumenthal said a proposed partnership between United Airlines and smaller JetBlue Airways could harm competition and lead to fewer and more expensive options for consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-senator-says-united-jetblue-partnership-could-harm-competition-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6XH52RSVJPTXPCKZGU2UJBDYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:22:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西淡化美国关税对 2025 年经济增长的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西政府周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普本周早些时候宣布对来自南美国家的所有商品征收50%的关税，预计这对巴西今年的经济增长影响不大。【原文：Brazil's government expects the 50% tariff U.S. President Donald Trump announced earlier this week on all goods from the South American country to have little impact on its economic growth this year, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-downplays-impact-us-tariffs-2025-growth-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPY7LE2WQFI37JFBUBPETJWWCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:17:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球商业团体称，最新一轮关税后美国关税税率可能超过 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）本周宣布征收进口关税后，国际商会（International Chamber of Commerce）估计，美国消费者将面临超过20%的有效关税率，这是自20世纪初以来的最高水平。【原文：U.S. consumers face an effective U.S. tariff rate of more than 20%, the highest since the early 1900s, the International Chamber of Commerce has estimated following President Donald Trump's import levy announcements this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-tariff-rate-may-be-more-than-20-after-latest-round-global-business-group-says-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAEVWTFUM5L2XOOJKGPQGWYKFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游说团体称欧洲葡萄酒可能被排除在与美国的贸易协议之外]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲葡萄酒业的主要游说团体周五表示，在欧盟与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府之间达成的任何贸易协定中，欧洲葡萄酒都可能无法享受优惠待遇。【原文：European wines may not benefit from preferential treatment in any trade agreement between the EU and the administration of U.S. President Donald Trump, the industry's main lobby group said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/wine-lobby-group-urges-eu-keep-wine-us-trade-talks-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DVSRKKMVJPITBNADBOJVF7RBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴黎检察官联系警方，调查社交媒体平台 X]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴黎检察院周五表示，在推进今年早些时候启动的针对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 社交媒体平台（涉嫌算法偏见）的调查时，已与警方取得联系。【原文：The Paris public prosecutor's office said on Friday it had contacted police as it advanced its probe launched earlier in the year against Elon Musk's X social media platform over alleged algorithmic bias.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/paris-prosecutor-contacts-police-probe-into-social-media-platform-x-advances-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKPZJDAGPFKB7DP2JLNIPLG4SE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:48:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国报告敦促采取更有力的措施检测人工智能驱动的深度伪造行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国国际电信联盟（International Telecommunications Union）周五在一份报告中敦促各公司必须使用先进的工具来检测和消除错误信息和深度伪造内容，以帮助应对日益增长的选举干扰和金融欺诈风险。【原文：Companies must use advanced tools to detect and stamp out misinformation and deepfake content to help counter growing risks of election interference and financial fraud, the United Nations’ International Telecommunication Union urged in a report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/un-report-urges-stronger-measures-detect-ai-driven-deepfakes-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFPTWSMVOZKCZCIOMXUZML3DHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:32:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰与美国同行一道退出银行气候联盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国贷方汇丰银行周五表示，已决定退出银行业的主要气候联盟，但仍 "坚定地 "致力于到本世纪中叶实现整个业务的净零排放目标。【原文：British lender HSBC said on Friday it had decided to leave the banking sector's main climate coalition but remained "resolute" in targeting net-zero emissions across its business by mid-century.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/hsbc-joins-us-peers-leaving-bank-climate-coalition-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AD4AU2TJWNLWPA5KQ3AAGECW6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼集团与迪拜 Khazna 公司合作在意大利建设数据中心园区]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利能源集团埃尼公司（Eni）和迪拜的卡兹纳公司（Khazna）周五表示，双方已签署初步协议，将在意大利北部联合开发一个 500 兆瓦（MW）的数据中心园区。【原文：Italian energy group Eni and Dubai-based Khazna have signed a preliminary agreement to jointly develop a 500-megawatt (MW) data centre campus in northern Italy, the two companies said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/eni-dubai-based-khazna-team-up-build-data-center-campus-italy-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV7GYTRMP5NNLP33KI3W4F5UGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，尽管面临欧盟罚款风险，Meta 不会进一步调整 "付费或同意 "模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的人士周五表示，Meta Platforms 不太可能对其付费或同意模式做出更多改变，这意味着它几乎肯定会受到欧盟新的反垄断指控和每日巨额罚款的打击。【原文：Meta Platforms is very unlikely to offer more changes to its pay-or-consent model, meaning it is almost certain to be hit by fresh EU antitrust charges and hefty daily fines, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-wont-tweak-pay-or-consent-model-further-despite-risk-eu-fines-sources-say-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7SNJ2ETLBIFVIWTUSTCMEV5VU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:16:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马首席执行官希望就美国汽车进口关税达成 "可控 "协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝马公司首席执行官周五表示，他对欧盟和美国将很快就汽车进口关税达成一项 "可管理的 "协议感到乐观，该协议可能包括一个以出口抵消进口的机制。【原文：BMW's CEO said on Friday he was optimistic that the European Union and the United States would soon reach a "manageable" agreement on auto import tariffs, potentially including a mechanism to offset imports with exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-ceo-hopeful-manageable-deal-us-auto-import-tariffs-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SO72N2ITU5ILXAJPVGJYRTNWAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税威胁引发谨慎情绪，美国股票基金流入减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至7月9日的一周里，尽管股市因人工智能领域需求上升而创下新纪录，但由于对唐纳德-特朗普总统威胁对贸易伙伴征收新关税持谨慎态度，美国股票基金的净投资额大幅下降。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw a significant drop in net investments in the week through July 9 on caution over President Donald Trump's threats of fresh tariffs on trading partners, even though stocks surged to new records on rising demand in the artificial intelligence sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-fund-inflows-ease-caution-over-tariff-threats-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONKJYGBUWROEFGPNFXBGMUXEUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受人工智能反弹和关税延迟影响，全球股票基金迎来第二周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至7月9日的七天里，全球股票基金连续第二周吸引资金流入，这主要是受到与人工智能相关的股票反弹，以及美国将关税推出时间推迟到8月份可能会对正在进行的贸易谈判产生积极影响的预期的推动。【原文：Global equity funds drew inflows for a second consecutive week in the seven days to July 9, boosted by a rally in AI-linked stocks and expectations that pushing the U.S. tariff rollout to August could positively affect ongoing trade talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXJAWN2BERIATLWSH7NRNT4AJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币创新高，监管乐观情绪再起，加密货币股受提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在美国上市的加密货币股票在盘前交易中上涨，比特币飙升至历史新高，原因是越来越多的人乐观地认为监管障碍将很快开始缓解。【原文：U.S.-listed cryptocurrency stocks rose in premarket trading on Friday as bitcoin surged to a record high on growing optimism that regulatory hurdles would soon begin to ease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoins-record-high-lifts-crypto-stocks-renewed-regulatory-optimism-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I43IHFRAERNETP3CUYPMF3OSME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标加拿大重回关税漩涡]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTZ5WZHXIRJZDBOWK7EK4ZZRVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：特朗普的 1 亿美元加密货币神秘人]]></title><description><![CDATA[在向唐纳德-特朗普总统的世界自由金融公司（World Liberty Financial）加密货币业务发送资金的数字钱包中，一个鲜为人知的实体上个月成为了最大的谜团。【原文：Of all the riddles wrapped in the digital wallets sending funds to President Donald Trump’s World Liberty Financial crypto business, a little-known entity last month became the biggest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-100-million-crypto-mystery-man-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLZQXJEZUVJDFPE3VANQD2VEJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高价股和债券给市场带来关税威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[关于美国关税对经济增长可能产生的长期影响，全球市场的说法不一，投资者认为，这种分歧意味着，一旦孰是孰非明朗化，股票或债券都可能出现大幅回调。【原文：Global markets are telling conflicting stories about the possible longer-term impact of U.S. tariffs on growth, a schism that investors say means either stocks or bonds could see a steep correction once it's clear which is right.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/high-priced-stocks-bonds-raise-tariff-threat-markets-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZJ6VVOMIWBN7LMHHY2ZUDEU46I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟等待特朗普来信，市场消化最新关税炮弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟周五收到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的一封信，信中概述了美国在最近几天扩大关税战后对其最大贸易和投资伙伴征收关税的计划。【原文：The European Union braced on Friday to receive a letter from U.S. President Donald Trump, outlining planned duties on his largest trade and investment partner after a broadening of his tariff war in recent days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-waits-trump-letter-markets-digest-latest-tariff-salvo-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DE4ZI3WLQFLALBBQXBKPRRXOLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球牛仔布需求强劲，李维斯上调业绩预期，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[李维斯（Levi Strauss）周五在盘前交易中股价大涨超过 7%，此前这家牛仔布生产商上调了年度营收和利润预期，指望其门店和网站的强劲需求能抵消美国关税对利润率的冲击。【原文：Levi Strauss shares surged more than 7% in premarket trading on Friday after the denim maker raised its annual revenue and profit forecasts, counting on robust demand at its stores and website to offset a margin hit from U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/levi-strauss-shares-jump-after-raising-forecasts-strong-global-denim-demand-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCSLGNRVANMDJKRIEHEHE5DCSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:49:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 拒绝批准细胞疗法，Capricor 股价下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周五表示，已拒绝批准 Capricor Therapeutics 公司治疗心脏病的细胞疗法，导致该公司股价在早盘交易中暴跌 30%。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has declined to approve Capricor Therapeutics' cell therapy for a heart condition, the company said on Friday, sending its shares tumbling 30% in early trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-declines-approve-capricors-muscle-disorder-therapy-2025-07-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLOEX4VK5NII7E6LMYNSLKTVCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>