<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:35:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:35:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司延续涨势，股票市值再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[** 苹果公司股价上涨 2.1%，iPhone 制造商的市值有望达到 3.33 万亿美元，超过历史上任何一家公司，微软和 Nvidia 紧随其后。【原文：** Shares of Apple Inc climbs 2.1% with the iPhone maker on track to close with a market cap of $3.33 trln, more than any company in history, with Microsoft and Nvidia both close behind】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-extends-rally-with-record-breaking-stock-market-value-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGQUDBFXB5MEDL3LS5UQXV6JRQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:31:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈克：我的基本情况是今年降息一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联储主席帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）周一表示，如果他的经济预测奏效，美国联邦储备委员会今年将能够下调一次基准利率。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve would be able to cut its benchmark interest rate once this year, Philadelphia Fed President Patrick Harker said on Monday, if his economic forecast plays out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-harker-one-interest-rate-cut-this-year-my-base-case-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUTN3RE7YNKNRLR2G35VZSNULY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:05:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CFTC 命令 Trafigura 就欺诈行为支付 5500 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会（Commodity Futures Trading Commission）周一表示，将责令全球大宗商品交易商 Trafigura 就欺诈、操纵和阻碍与政府机构的沟通支付 5500 万美元。【原文：The Commodity Futures Trading Commission said on Monday it was ordering global commodities trader Trafigura to pay $55 million over fraud, manipulation and impeding communications with the government agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/cftc-orders-trafigura-pay-55-million-over-fraud-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5A4KXXUQRIGLDPEE5RDI4NQBA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 16:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着 Citgo 股份拍卖进入最后阶段，金融联盟不断建立]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，本月至少有五组投资者在美国法院下令进行的 Citgo 石油公司母公司股份拍卖中提交了具有约束力的出价，其中三组投资者已经获得了对委内瑞拉这颗外国皇冠上的明珠的融资承诺。【原文：At least five groups of investors submitted binding bids this month in a U.S. court-ordered auction of shares in Citgo Petroleum's parent, and three have secured financing commitments for Venezuela's foreign crown jewel, people close to the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/financial-alliances-build-citgo-share-auction-enters-last-mile-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YS3Y7H7JTVOOVBEEFS44654A5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 16:43:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各州起诉美国阻止要求石油业支付拆除旧油井费用的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州、路易斯安那州和密西西比州周一起诉美国政府，要求阻止拜登政府提出的要求近海石油和天然气行业提供近 70 亿美元资金以支付拆除旧基础设施费用的规则。【原文：Texas, Louisiana and Mississippi on Monday sued the U.S. government to block the Biden administration's proposed rule that would require the offshore oil and gas industry to provide nearly $7 billion in funds to cover costs of dismantling old infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/states-sue-us-block-rule-requiring-oil-industry-pay-dismantling-old-wells-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSE35DJ3AVIRHEBTP5QXQWOKIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉 Adobe 披露订阅计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周一起诉 Adobe 公司，指控这家 Photoshop 和 Acrobat 的制造商在没有明确披露重要条款的情况下，让消费者加入其最赚钱的订阅计划，从而损害了消费者的利益。【原文：The U.S. government on Monday sued Adobe , accusing the maker of Photoshop and Acrobat of harming consumers by enrolling them in its most lucrative subscription plans without clearly disclosing important terms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-sues-adobe-over-subscription-plan-disclosures-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPYSP5ZKXJPCPJAGTYDUYC2C4Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉就电动汽车电池商业机密起诉前供应商马修斯]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉在加州联邦法院起诉其前供应商马修斯国际公司（Matthews International），指控其窃取与特斯拉电池制造工艺有关的商业机密，并与这家电动汽车巨头的竞争对手分享。【原文：Tesla has sued its former supplier Matthews International in California federal court for allegedly stealing trade secrets related to Tesla's battery-manufacturing process and sharing them with the electric-vehicle giant's competitors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-sues-ex-supplier-matthews-over-ev-battery-trade-secrets-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNEJAJKMSFPX3N2BCR3U6BPK3A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉启动恢复马斯克薪酬的法律斗争]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一公开的一封信，特斯拉开始争取法律承认支持埃隆-马斯克创纪录薪酬的股东投票，并告诉特拉华州法官，这 "极大地影响 "了她宣布薪酬无效的裁决。【原文：Tesla began its fight for legal recognition of a shareholder vote favoring Elon Musk's record compensation, telling a Delaware judge that it "significantly impacts" her ruling voiding the pay, according to a letter made public on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tesla-kicks-off-legal-fight-reinstate-musks-pay-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXMWXRWF2FJ3FNY2UAD6HPRGTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上诉法院将于 9 月 16 日审理对美国 TikTok 潜在禁令的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周一表示，将于 9 月 16 日就一项新法律的法律挑战进行口头辩论，该法律要求总部位于中国的字节跳动公司在 1 月 19 日前剥离 TikTok 在美国的资产，否则将面临禁令。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Monday said it will hold oral arguments on Sept. 16 on legal challenges to a new law requiring China-based ByteDance to divest TikTok's U.S. assets by Jan. 19 or face a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/appeals-court-hear-challenges-potential-us-tiktok-ban-sept-16-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B24GZBEEJJPZZBBYU64DFZXVKE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银开始大规模股票回购计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行周一表示，瑞银已开始实施今年早些时候宣布的股票回购计划，上周回购了价值4480万瑞士法郎（5021万美元）的股票。【原文：UBS has begun a share buyback program announced earlier this year, and repurchased 44.8 million Swiss francs ($50.21 million) worth of shares last week, the Swiss bank said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ubs-begins-major-share-buy-back-programme-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHM3IRMKMVLM3C7A2EQMRJUKVI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将审理 Nvidia 撤销股东诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一同意听取英伟达公司（Nvidia）的诉讼请求，以阻止一起证券欺诈诉讼，该诉讼指控这家人工智能芯片制造商在其销售额中有多少用于动荡的加密货币行业方面误导投资者。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court agreed on Monday to hear a bid by Nvidia to scuttle a securities fraud lawsuit accusing the artificial intelligence chipmaker of misleading investors about how much of its sales went to the volatile cryptocurrency industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-hear-nvidia-bid-scuttle-shareholder-lawsuit-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5MVYW7FWRM3JIAGFZI4QMVIDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:41:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利锂矿开采商 SQM 与现代、起亚达成供应协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利锂矿商 SQM 周一表示，已与现代和起亚达成长期供应协议，将向这两家汽车制造商提供生产电动汽车电池所需的白色金属。【原文：Chilean lithium miner SQM said on Monday that it had reached a long-term supply deal with Hyundai and Kia to provide the carmakers with the white metal, key for the production of electric vehicle batteries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chile-lithium-miner-sqm-reaches-supply-deal-with-hyundai-kia-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIYA3FMPSNMLBPOP6AVL25WJNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:40:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部和国税局将堵住 500 亿美元的合伙企业税收漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部和国内税收署周一表示，他们将堵住一个被大型复杂合伙企业利用的税收漏洞，据他们估计，这一行动可在 10 年内增加 500 亿美元的新税收。【原文：The U.S. Treasury and Internal Revenue Service said on Monday they will close a tax loophole exploited by large, complex partnerships, an action that they estimated could raise $50 billion in new revenue over 10 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-treasury-irs-close-50-bln-tax-loophole-partnerships-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNGVHAAO6NJODIKYKFTASQIDK4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金流动 高盛称，5 月份以并购为重点的对冲基金独占鳌头]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）在一份致客户的说明中说，随着交易量的回升，对冲基金经理在 2024 年前五个月押注并购的回报率为 7.7%，超过了那些部署其他策略的对冲基金经理。【原文：Hedge fund managers making bets on mergers and acquisitions outperformed those deploying other strategies with a return of 7.7% in the first five months of 2024, Goldman Sachs said in a note to clients, as deal-making rebounded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/hedge-flow-ma-focused-hedge-funds-lead-pack-may-goldman-sachs-says-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QSLWKGZFNJKTN6IR77BSRUMAI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:23:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，You.com 初创公司正筹资 5000 万美元，瞄准人工智能助手市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[You.com背后的初创公司正在筹集5000万美元的新资金，一位熟知内情的人士透露，该公司正在寻求在日益增长的人工智能助手市场中占据一席之地。【原文：The startup behind You.com is raising $50 million in fresh capital, a person familiar with the effort said, as it seeks a foothold in the growing market for assistants with artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/youcom-startup-is-raising-50-mln-it-targets-ai-assistant-market-says-source-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CKEJSY66VJ4HFDPDKPRAWOLLE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:05:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Naver 旗下 Webtoon Entertainment 在美国 IPO 的目标估值高达 26.7 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线漫画平台 Webtoon Entertainment 周一表示，其在美国首次公开募股的目标估值高达 26.7 亿美元。【原文：Online comics platform Webtoon Entertainment said on Monday it is targeting a valuation of up to $2.67 billion in its initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/navers-webtoon-entertainment-targets-up-267-bln-valuation-us-ipo-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6623S2DN4ZPXTLQSQS2I37FVTA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 12:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯股价因中国腐败指控调查而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿迪达斯股价周一下跌 4%，这家德国运动品牌称，在收到一封匿名信后，正在对中国的腐败指控进行调查。【原文：Adidas shares dropped 4% on Monday after the German sportswear brand said it was investigating allegations of corruption in China after receiving an anonymous letter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-shares-fall-investigation-into-china-corruption-allegation-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKRHPN3GSVPBXL3HAOW4RXTLS4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:40:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡特彼勒的俄罗斯资产转入亚美尼亚基金拥有的公司名下]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯公司文件显示，美国机械制造商卡特彼勒公司的前俄罗斯资产已被转移到亚美尼亚投资基金巴尔楚格资本（Balchug Capital）旗下的一家公司。【原文：U.S. machinery maker Caterpillar's former Russian assets have been transferred to a company owned by Armenian investment fund Balchug Capital, Russian company filings showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/caterpillars-russian-assets-transferred-firm-owned-by-armenian-fund-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TC4CMBOVWZOFHDCE2LUU7FFYSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:36:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟监管机构将于 7 月 18 日前就 Bunge 和 Viterra 340 亿美元的交易做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周一提交的一份文件显示，美国谷物商邦吉（Bunge）和嘉能可（Glencore）支持的维泰拉公司（Viterra）创建一家价值 340 亿美元的农产品贸易巨头的计划，将由欧盟反垄断监管机构在 7 月 18 日前作出决定。【原文：U.S. grains merchant Bunge and Glencore-backed Viterra's plan to create a $34 billion agricultural trading giant will be decided by EU antitrust regulators by July 18, a European Commission filing showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/eu-regulators-decide-bunge-viterras-34-bln-deal-by-july-18-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZX7INQGXFICNBPF5NNWSN5PCQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:13:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[StanChart 要求从英国诉讼中删除违反美国制裁的索赔，但遭到拒绝]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行（Standard Chartered）周一在伦敦一宗诉讼中败诉，该公司被指控违反了美国对伊朗的制裁，而且违反制裁的范围比它之前承认的还要广泛。【原文：Standard Chartered on Monday lost a bid to cut from a London lawsuit allegations that it broke U.S. sanctions against Iran in a more widespread way than it has previously admitted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stanchart-loses-bid-cut-us-sanctions-breach-claims-uk-lawsuit-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R76A5BWKNNNDFLCBGGORY2UPUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待数据和美联储评论，期指回调]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在等待新的经济数据和美联储官员的言论，以进一步明确货币政策，周一美国股指期货在低迷的交投中涨跌互现。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were mixed in muted trading on Monday as investors awaited fresh economic data and comments from Federal Reserve officials for more clarity on monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-pull-back-investors-await-data-fed-comments-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6SSRCMBKNIWJCL5UXO3DML2VI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西部稀土供应链启动]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球稀土供应链正在重新调整，从最大的稀土生产国中国向多元化发展，以生产用于电动汽车、风力涡轮机和无人机等产品的永久磁铁。【原文：Global supply chains for rare earths are realigning to diversify away from top producer China to make permanent magnets used in products from electric vehicles to wind turbines and drones.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/western-rare-earths-supply-chain-springs-into-gear-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPME3PTAA5N3PEWWF34DU2FKFI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国：法国的焦虑、中国的住房问题、美国的活力]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-graphics-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6B4WZODNZ5LWTO2ELZ7FCTTESI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:09:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[价格暴跌，美国农民回避买家，紧握未售出的玉米]]></title><description><![CDATA[上个月，当玉米价格接近 4 个半月的峰值时，南达科他州农民 Eric Kroupa 接到了大量来自谷物经销商和乙醇厂的电话，要求购买锁在粮仓里的玉米。【原文：South Dakota farmer Eric Kroupa received a flurry of calls from grain dealers and ethanol plants asking to buy the corn locked away in his bins when prices neared 4-1/2-month peaks last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-farmers-shun-buyers-cling-unsold-corn-prices-slump-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74MCVISTARLHLHIOC33JEXQ2YU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:07:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 的粉丝们在等待股东大会的召开，此前的高需求使首次尝试脱轨]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 的年会定于周一举行，在该公司众多狂热的零售投资者粉丝中，社交媒体上的讨论日益热烈。【原文：GameStop's annual meeting, scheduled for Monday, is creating a growing buzz on social media among the company's host of avid retail investor fans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestops-fans-await-shareholder-meeting-after-high-demand-derailed-first-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4WULQA6RFPRZIJJ77ULAQRP3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[夏季驾驶淡季导致全球汽油炼制利润下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于夏季驾车旺季的需求低于许多炼油厂提高产量时的预期，炼油厂销售汽油的利润正在减少。【原文：Oil refiners are making less money selling their gasoline as demand during the peak summer driving season has fallen short of what they expected when many of them boosted production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/global-gasoline-refining-margins-slump-slow-summer-driving-season-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3Z4VDUPDJOTHMI2DGB5SSIIWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司 398 亿美元出售中国比亚迪股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一份证券交易所文件显示，沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）旗下的投资公司伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）以 3.105 亿港元（合 3,980 万美元）的价格出售了 130 万股在香港上市的电动汽车制造商比亚迪的股票。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway, the investment company owned by Warren Buffett, has sold 1.3 million Hong Kong-listed shares of electric vehicle maker BYD for HK$310.5 million ($39.8 million), a stock exchange filing showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/berkshire-hathaway-sells-398-mln-shares-chinas-byd-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXPDI23DJJLQFGRU25VVL5EDYQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 09:43:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西加入放松中国对稀土产业控制的竞争行列]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着西方经济体努力确保绿色能源和国防所用磁铁所需的金属，并打破中国在供应链中的主导地位，矿业巨头巴西雄心勃勃地要建立稀土产业。【原文：Mining giant Brazil has big ambitions to build a rare earths industry as Western economies push to secure the metals needed for magnets used in green energy and defence and break China's dominance of the supply chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazil-joins-race-loosen-chinas-grip-rare-earths-industry-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4K4AF5MQAFNJFGJ6PYQGY5YU7A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 08:57:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对欧洲猪肉发起针锋相对的反倾销调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国已对从欧盟进口的猪肉及其副产品展开反倾销调查，这一举措似乎主要针对西班牙、荷兰、法国和丹麦，以回应中国对其电动汽车出口的限制。【原文：China has opened an anti-dumping investigation into imported pork and its by-products from the European Union, a step that appears mainly targetted at Spain, the Netherlands, France and Denmark in response to curbs on its electric vehicle exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-opens-anti-dumping-probe-into-imported-pork-by-products-eu-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO4WEACPOVO3RNGIRFVUB5C6YA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银将计提与继承格林希尔基金相关的 9 亿美元拨备]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行周一表示，瑞士信贷与倒闭的供应链融资公司格林希尔资本（Greensill Capital）有关联，该行预计将为此拨备约 9 亿美元。【原文：UBS expects to record a provision of around $0.9 billion, the Swiss bank said on Monday, in connection to Credit Suisse's funds linked to collapsed supply chain financing firm Greensill Capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-book-09-bln-provision-linked-inherited-greensill-funds-2024-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5MQ252NEVIL5M4S4IBKNBFLKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 06:37:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>