<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:34:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:34:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[前先锋公司首席执行官起诉美国联邦贸易委员会禁止他进入埃克森董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[先锋自然资源公司（Pioneer Natural Resources）前首席执行官斯科特-谢菲尔德（Scott Sheffield）周二起诉美国联邦贸易委员会，称该委员会在埃克森美孚公司以价值 595 亿美元的交易收购先锋公司时，禁止他加入埃克森美孚董事会的做法违反了法律。【原文：Former Pioneer Natural Resources CEO Scott Sheffield sued the U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday, saying it violated the law by barring his inclusion on Exxon Mobil's board when the company acquired Pioneer in a deal worth $59.5 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ex-pioneer-ceo-sues-ftc-banning-him-exxon-board-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2OEEF3YVFKCHEHT4EAYOEAYUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称，在 SpaceX 游说之后，特朗普可能会废除太空委员会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉该计划的人士透露，唐纳德-特朗普总统的新政府很可能取消白宫的国家太空委员会，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）的说客们一直在推动取消这个内阁政策小组。【原文：President Donald Trump's new administration is likely to do away with the White House's National Space Council, a cabinet policy panel that lobbyists at Elon Musk's SpaceX have been pushing to axe, according to three people familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-likely-axe-space-council-after-spacex-lobbying-sources-say-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2X24FA7CIROPTO4T7VLF543PD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普试图给墨西哥卡特尔贴上 "外国恐怖分子 "标签，给公司和移民带来风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一晚间，唐纳德-特朗普总统呼吁美国国务院将墨西哥贩毒集团贴上 "外国恐怖组织 "的标签，分析人士称，此举扩大了美国执法部门对犯罪集团的打击范围，但有可能使国际商业活动复杂化，限制庇护申请，并使美国与墨西哥的关系紧张。【原文：On Monday night, President Donald Trump called for the State Department to label Mexican cartels as "foreign terrorist organizations," a move that increases the reach of U.S. law enforcement over the criminal groups but risks complicating international business, restricting asylum claims, and straining relations with Mexico, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trumps-bid-label-mexican-cartels-foreign-terrorists-poses-risks-companies-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HN342MKOZ5PKDF23B4HEWTAA6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:58:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲 美元大幅波动，不确定性迷雾重重？习惯就好]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BZG6OK2TVKDXJRSSANA5ALCYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Capital One 第四季度利润因利息收入增加而大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Capital One Financial 周二报告称，由于利息收入增加，这家消费贷款公司第四季度利润增长了 60%。【原文：Capital One Financial reported a 60% rise in fourth-quarter profit on Tuesday, as a higher income from interests helped the consumer lender.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/capital-ones-fourth-quarter-profit-jumps-interest-income-boost-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXBIGB75MNLTRJE3U2LJABUUTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:44:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币金融公司在联邦调查局调查后认罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一家加密货币金融服务公司同意对美国的指控认罪，该公司在联邦调查局的授意下帮助操纵一种数字代币的市场，以帮助揭露加密货币领域的欺诈行为。【原文：A cryptocurrency financial services firm agreed on Tuesday to plead guilty to U.S. charges that it offered to help manipulate the market for a digital token created at the FBI's behest to help uncover fraud in the crypto sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cryptocurrency-financial-firm-plead-guilty-after-novel-fbi-probe-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUYWVPH46RMELHFUT4J3W2LHGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周二预计本季度利润将高于预期，此前该公司第四季度的盈利因强劲的旅行需求和定价能力的提高而超过了华尔街的预期。【原文：United Airlines on Tuesday forecast a stronger-than-expected profit in the current quarter, after its earnings topped Wall Street estimates in the fourth quarter on robust travel demand and improved pricing power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-sees-stronger-quarterly-profit-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R453NDPTNJO5NJG3QKCPFRQA64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 节假日季度新增 1900 万订户，创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 周二发布报告称，该公司假日季度新增用户 1890 万，超过了华尔街的预期，其中体育赛事直播和韩国热门剧集《乌贼游戏》的回归吸引了创纪录数量的新用户。【原文：Netflix added 18.9 million subscribers in its holiday quarter, blowing past Wall Street's forecasts, with live sporting events and the return of its popular South Korean series "Squid Game" attracting a record number of new customers, the company reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-added-record-19-million-subscribers-holiday-quarter-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUE6D4NBTFP4ROGMNT7NZMJJTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德克萨斯州港口在寒冷天气中限制活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗里波特港周二表示，预计船只活动有限，而休斯顿港则表示，由于冬季风暴恩佐席卷得克萨斯州，该港所有公共设施将在周三前继续关闭。【原文：Port Freeport on Tuesday said it expects limited vessel activity while Port Houston said all of its public facilities will remain closed through Wednesday as winter storm Enzo sweeps through Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ports-texas-limit-activity-amid-cold-weather-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANN533PFMNMHRBVAFMJ3UEC3ME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，道明银行希望出售 90 亿美元抵押贷款以达到资产上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，多伦多道明银行（Toronto-Dominion Bank）正计划出售约 90 亿美元的住宅抵押贷款，以调整其资产负债表，遵守美国监管机构规定的新上限。【原文：Toronto-Dominion Bank is aiming to sell about $9 billion of residential mortgage loans in order to modify its balance sheet to comply with a new cap imposed by the U.S. regulators, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/td-bank-looking-sell-9-bln-mortgages-meet-asset-cap-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QG2MGFAQORKA5MINMFNBADH2OQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，作为破产退出的一部分，全球航空公司正在与巴西 Gol 航空公司进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地报纸《Valor Economico》周二援引消息人士的话报道，全球航空公司正在与 Gol 洽谈投资巴西航空公司的事宜，该公司正在美国进行破产保护程序。【原文：Global airlines are in talks with Gol to invest in the Brazilian airline, which is undergoing Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings in the U.S., local newspaper Valor Economico reported on Tuesday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/global-airlines-talks-with-brazils-gol-part-bankruptcy-exit-reports-local-media-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDQCR7SAP5P2FE4UU2C6OGX6LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:38:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普行政令让 TikTok 暂时陷入法律困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发布行政命令恢复对 TikTok 的访问，这给短视频平台带来了大量新的法律问题，白宫、希望禁止该平台的国会议员和夹在中间的科技公司之间也出现了新的紧张关系。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's executive order to restore access to TikTok has created a thicket of new legal questions for the short-video platform, along with new tensions between the White House, members of Congress who want the platform banned, and tech companies caught in the middle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-executive-order-leaves-tiktok-legal-limbo-now-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZQJ4J4ERBID3FN2YPT4O73F3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普重启出口许可推动美国液化天然气项目发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）已于 2024 年 1 月结束了其前任乔-拜登（Joe Biden）实施的暂停新液化天然气出口许可的禁令。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has ended the moratorium on new liquefied natural gas export permits imposed by his predecessor Joe Biden in January 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-lng-projects-boosted-by-trumps-export-permit-restart-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSFY6J4APNI5VNZHEHVR3MQW2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:45:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的电动汽车退税政策预计不会抑制对关键矿产的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和行业领袖表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普撤销电动汽车目标可能会暂时减缓对锂和其他关键矿物的需求，但不太可能在全球电动汽车需求激增的情况下阻碍采矿业的发展。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's rollback of electric vehicle targets may temporarily slow demand for lithium and other critical minerals, but is unlikely to hamper the mining industry amid surging global EV demand, analysts and industry leaders said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-ev-rollback-not-expected-suppress-appetite-critical-minerals-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPG3TXQYXRORPMUNLSSI5FWXLI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:19:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团必须面对纽约的欺诈诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二驳回了花旗集团要求驳回纽约总检察长莱蒂娅-詹姆斯（Letitia James）指控花旗集团旗下花旗银行未能向遭受网络诈骗的客户提供补偿的诉讼请求。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday rejected Citigroup's bid to dismiss a lawsuit by New York Attorney General Letitia James accusing its Citibank unit of failing to reimburse customers who fall victim to online scammers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/citigroup-must-face-new-york-lawsuit-over-fraud-scams-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJR3QO7IKVKOVAD42LKNHGRIHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师报告称，保时捷在投资者电话会议上确认了 2024 年的盈利前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯恩斯坦研究公司（Bernstein Research）分析师在周二与投资者的电话会议上确认了保时捷 2024 年的盈利前景，即 14-15% 的利润率，并表示预计 2025 年仍将面临挑战。【原文：Porsche confirmed its earnings outlook for 2024 of a 14-15% profit margin in a call with investors on Tuesday and said it expected 2025 to remain challenging, according to a note by Bernstein Research analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-confirms-2024-earnings-outlook-investor-call-analysts-note-says-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZ3JP4JJTRNQTNDPR6S2VYMFIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:37:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在达沃斯，马来西亚哈撒那集团（Khazanah）寻求发达市场投资，抑制特朗普风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚主权财富基金（Khazanah Nasional Bhd）的高级官员表示，该基金正在重新平衡其投资组合，以更多地投资于发达市场，同时着眼于管理唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）新一届美国总统任期的预期风险。【原文：Malaysia's sovereign wealth fund Khazanah Nasional Bhd is rebalancing its portfolio to invest more in developed markets, with an eye on managing expected risks from the new Donald Trump presidency in the U.S., its top official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/davos-malaysias-khazanah-looks-developed-market-investments-tame-trump-risks-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RUZF5KBBBJRTI7TCZHXJVOKNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:25:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会成立加密货币工作组]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周二表示，它正在组建一个新的加密货币特别工作组，"致力于为加密资产制定一个全面、清晰的监管框架"。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Tuesday it was forming a new cryptocurrency task force "dedicated to developing a comprehensive and clear regulatory framework for crypto assets."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-sec-forms-cryptocurrency-task-force-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAT5DXA7JNPNPJPI4SQULSK73U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:58:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据哥伦比亚广播公司报道，特朗普将宣布私营部门的人工智能基础设施投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[据哥伦比亚广播公司新闻（CBS News）周二报道，唐纳德-特朗普总统将宣布由私营部门投资，在美国建设总额达数十亿美元的人工智能基础设施。【原文：President Donald Trump is due to announce private sector investment to build artificial intelligence infrastructure in the United States totaling billions of dollars, CBS News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/trump-announce-private-sector-ai-infrastructure-investment-cbs-reports-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F6BWJMHQAJOWHOS2FPYIYIK72E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABB 首席财务官称将增加美国投资以提高本地产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[ABB首席财务官蒂莫-伊哈穆奥蒂拉（Timo Ihamuotila）周二表示，ABB正在增加在美国的投资，以应对特朗普新政府预期的关税上调，并从美国的经济增长中获益。【原文：ABB is increasing its investments in the United States as a way to deal with tariff hikes expected from the new Trump administration and to benefit from the country's economic growth, Chief Financial Officer Timo Ihamuotila said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/abb-increasing-us-investment-raise-local-production-cfo-says-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLT7JFSKSVII3LSZHV2GJ3Z74U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:57:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯公布第四季度销售额和利润率增长情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿迪达斯周二公布的第四季度初步业绩好于预期，在重要的假日购物期实现了强劲的销售和盈利。【原文：Adidas reported what it said were better than expected preliminary fourth-quarter results on Tuesday, with strong sales and profitability for the important holiday shopping period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-reports-fourth-quarter-sales-profitability-gains-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTHG4K2HVZLPPLUHIDYGR4XGNE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文推出面向销售人员的人工智能代理]]></title><description><![CDATA[甲骨文公司周二发布了一套新的人工智能代理，帮助销售人员完成一系列与客户打交道的任务。【原文：Oracle on Tuesday released a new set of artificial intelligence agents to help salespeople with a range of tasks around dealing with customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/oracle-rolls-out-ai-agents-sales-professionals-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADFQXT5YC5PHNGTITY357FMCR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:59:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄牙呼吁深化欧盟与美国对话以避免有害关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[葡萄牙财政部长周二表示，欧洲应与美国新政府建立并加强对话，以避免关税升级损害消费者，尤其是最不富裕的消费者。【原文：Europe should establish and strengthen dialogue with the new U.S. administration to avoid an escalation of tariffs that would harm consumers, especially the least wealthy, Portugal's finance minister said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/portugal-calls-deeper-eu-us-dialogue-avoid-harmful-tariffs-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRNCP372F5OVJFEHHBVTX5JWZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:52:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上任首日美股褒贬不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉、监狱运营商和其他著名的 "特朗普交易 "在周二出现波动，因为投资者对唐纳德-特朗普总统在宣誓就职后数小时内发布的一系列行政命令进行了评估。【原文：Tesla, prison operators and other notable "Trump trades" were volatile on Tuesday as investors assessed a blitz of executive orders by President Donald Trump within hours of taking the oath of office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-first-day-office-gets-mixed-reception-us-stocks-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCZE5WLEAJPVJEB6ELD3WB6NPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:27:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行聘请摩根大通高管担任银行卡和商户服务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国富国银行周二任命摩根大通高管 Ed Olebe 为其新任银行卡和商户服务主管，立即生效。【原文：U.S. bank Wells Fargo named JPMorgan Chase executive Ed Olebe as its new head of cards and merchant services on Tuesday, effective immediately.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-hires-jpmorgan-executive-head-cards-merchant-services-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCDZ4G4SZJII5POEQU5WBU7BFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特出任美国财政部部长的提名获得参议院财政委员会通过]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院财政委员会周二投票决定将亿万富翁、对冲基金经理斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）担任唐纳德-特朗普总统财政部长的提名提交参议院全会批准。【原文：The U.S. Senate Finance Committee on Tuesday voted to send the nomination of billionaire hedge fund manager Scott Bessent as President Donald Trump's Treasury secretary on to the full Senate for approval.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-nomination-us-treasury-clears-senate-finance-committee-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J3QYI7O5JRLD7PKN72DMOJG6WI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济学家将巴西利率预测上调至 15%以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家对巴西今年的利率预测进行了新一轮的上调，理由是通胀预期恶化、货币疲软以及对拉美最大经济体财政前景的担忧挥之不去。【原文：Economists have launched a fresh wave of upward revisions to projections for Brazil's interest rate this year, citing deteriorating inflation expectations, a weaker currency and lingering concerns over the fiscal outlook of Latin America's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/economists-ramp-up-projections-brazils-interest-rates-above-15-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6HB7TVGAFL7PG7MJ572KFU74M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[仓库需求改善，Prologis 核心财务和利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产投资信托公司（REIT）Prologis 第四季度核心运营资金（FFO）超出华尔街预期，主要得益于仓储空间需求的增长和一个数据中心的出售。【原文：Real estate investment trust (REIT) Prologis beat Wall Street expectations for fourth-quarter core funds from operations (FFO), helped by improving demand for its warehousing spaces and sale of a data center.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/prologis-beats-core-ffo-estimates-improving-warehouse-demand-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7E7GDRKMROPXI3FWRWSPCMOQQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：特朗普对欧盟贸易逆差的抱怨以及接下来可能发生的事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普
 他承诺要解决与欧盟长期存在的贸易逆差问题，并表示将通过征收关税或让欧盟购买更多美国石油和天然气来扭转这一局面。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump
 has promised to address a longstanding trade deficit with the European Union, saying he will reverse that by imposing tariffs or making the EU buy more U.S. oil and gas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-complaints-about-trade-deficit-with-eu-what-may-come-next-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EN3PZEX5CFPZXK4L45GQZCRWII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威银行在空气产品公司董事会之争中投票支持激进分子的四名候选人]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威主权财富基金是空气化工产品公司的 10 大投资者之一，该基金表示将投票支持激进投资者 Mantle Ridge 的所有四名董事候选人加入这家工业气体公司的董事会。【原文：Norway's sovereign wealth fund, one of Air Products and Chemicals' 10 biggest investors, said it will vote for all four of activist investor Mantle Ridge's director candidates to join the industrial gases company's board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/norges-bank-votes-activists-four-candidates-air-products-board-fight-2025-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R33CWGXTKVMEJFJATOBYQOP5TE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>