<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 05:34:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 05:34:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[宇航员机组与空间站对接，取代 "布奇和苏尼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Crew-10任务是让威尔莫尔和威廉姆斯返回地球的期待已久的第一步。两人计划于美国东部时间周三凌晨4点（格林尼治标准时间8点）离开国际空间站，同行的还有美国国家航空航天局宇航员尼克-黑格和俄罗斯宇航员亚历山大-戈尔布诺夫。【原文：The Crew-10 mission is a long-awaited first step to bring Wilmore and Williams back to Earth. The duo are scheduled to depart the ISS on Wednesday as early as 4 a.m. ET (0800 GMT), along with NASA astronaut Nick Hague and Russian cosmonaut Aleksandr Gorbunov.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/astronaut-crew-docks-with-space-station-replace-butch-suni-2025-03-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KC3RXPWUWVP6DODODDCG6P5ZJE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 04:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在俄罗斯提出抱怨后，特朗普将凯洛格的角色限定为乌克兰特使]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些俄罗斯前高级官员抱怨说，在他们看来，凯洛格过于同情基辅。【原文：Some high-ranking former Russian officials have complained that Kellogg was, in their view, too sympathetic to Kyiv.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-limits-kelloggs-role-ukraine-envoy-after-russian-complaints-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJ4BKUARUBILZFIMKLXCCHSYPQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 20:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被拘留的哥伦比亚大学学生的律师要求保释]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学一名学生因支持巴勒斯坦激进主义而被拘留，他的律师在周六的保释动议中辩称，他没有潜逃风险，应获准回家生第一个孩子。【原文：A Columbia University student detained over his pro-Palestinian activism is not a flight risk and should be allowed to return home for the birth of his first child, his lawyers argued in a motion for bail on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/lawyers-detained-columbia-student-ask-his-release-bail-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMJCBRJAH5M3RF2DPARRCO6LIU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 19:14:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官以担心战时法律为由提起诉讼，阻止部分驱逐行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在两个非营利组织起诉称唐纳德-特朗普总统可以援引战时法律加速驱逐无证移民后，一名联邦法官周六暂时阻止了美国政府驱逐一些委内瑞拉人。【原文：A federal judge on Saturday temporarily blocked the U.S. government from deporting some Venezuelans after two non-profit groups sued saying President Donald Trump could invoke a wartime law to accelerate deportations of undocumented migrants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-some-deportations-after-lawsuit-cites-fears-wartime-law-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K3LTDHTQJVITJM64UPEL6U5AT4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:25:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫：特朗普签署预算拨款法案使其成为法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫在一份声明中说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六签署了国会本周通过的一项临时支出法案，避免了政府部分停摆。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Saturday signed a stopgap spending bill, passed by Congress this week, that averts a partial government shutdown, the White House said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-signs-budget-appropriations-bill-into-law-says-white-house-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKVTYKA2NJOYJDLEGZRCFRARAE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫撤回人质问题特使提名]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周六表示，特朗普政府已撤回对亚当-博勒（Adam Boehler）担任人质事务总统特使的提名。【原文：The Trump administration has withdrawn the nomination of Adam Boehler to serve as special presidential envoy for hostage affairs, the White House said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/white-house-withdraws-nomination-hostage-envoy-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDEDRHZB3RNUJECAFXWZXDBNOQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:21:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[龙卷风袭击美国南部造成三人死亡，风险不断上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[密苏里州警方表示，一系列龙卷风一夜之间袭击了美国中西部和东南部地区，造成三人死亡。【原文：Three people were killed in Missouri as a series of tornadoes hit the U.S. Midwest and southeast overnight, raking a path of destruction that was still being assessed early on Saturday, police said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/tornadoes-strike-us-south-leaving-three-dead-amid-rising-risk-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMNVSU7MQFM7HJSO5XB2FJMH7U</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 13:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令撤消美国之音和其他机构的职能]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五签署了一项行政命令，旨在削减美国政府资助的媒体机构美国之音的母公司和其他六个联邦机构，这是他的政府为缩减官僚机构而采取的最新举措。【原文：President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Friday aimed at gutting the parent of U.S. government-funded media outlet Voice of America and six other federal agencies, his administration's latest step to shrink bureaucracy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-signs-order-gut-voice-america-other-agencies-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBL3SKPDIJMGVDVQX2YBDH5XFI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 10:59:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普暂停保罗-魏斯律师事务所人员的安全许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五签署了一项行政命令，暂停纽约律师事务所 Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison 员工的安全许可。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Friday suspending security clearances held by people at New York law firm Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-suspends-security-clearance-people-paul-weiss-law-firm-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ED3PU52JFZP6HO2TVJ24WILLH4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:45:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，特朗普政府正在权衡对数十个国家的旅行禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的消息人士和路透社看到的一份内部备忘录称，作为新禁令的一部分，特朗普政府正在考虑对数十个国家的公民实施全面的旅行限制。【原文：The Trump administration is considering issuing sweeping travel restrictions for the citizens of dozens of countries as part of a new ban, according to sources familiar with the matter and an internal memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-weighs-travel-ban-dozens-countries-memo-says-2025-03-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4P6FTJBPNOOLHE76FHZE6HHRE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将提出允许扩大无人机使用范围的规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）周五表示，联邦航空管理局计划提出扩大使用无人机送货和提供其他服务的规则。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said on Friday that the Federal Aviation Administration plans to propose rules to expand use of drones for deliveries and other services.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-faa-propose-rule-allowing-expanded-drone-use-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IJBKALGHNMDPJ6NEKEPDI52E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[实时更新：美国国家航空航天局（NASA）和太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）将发射火箭将被困宇航员送回家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航天局和 SpaceX 公司正在执行一项任务，将宇航员布奇-威尔莫尔和苏尼-威廉姆斯带回家。他们已经被困在国际空间站九个月了。【原文：The U.S. space agency and SpaceX are on a mission to bring home astronauts Butch Wilmore and Suni Williams. They have been stuck on the International Space Station for nine months.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/live-updates-nasa-spacex-launch-rocket-bring-stuck-astronauts-home-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUNO6FMPUJAF3GY43F6IYTZUJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 22:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院允许特朗普暂时执行对可持续发展教育项目的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周五暂时中止了法官的一项裁决，该裁决曾阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府在联邦机构和与联邦政府签订合同的企业中实施有关多元化、公平和包容计划的禁令。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Friday temporarily paused a judge's ruling that had blocked the administration of President Donald Trump from implementing bans on diversity, equity and inclusion programs at federal agencies and businesses that contract with the federal government.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-court-allows-trump-enforce-ban-dei-programs-now-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPEU7YFBJBMJJJKAY7X6JXQUSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 22:41:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院政府支出法案获得通过]]></title><description><![CDATA[在足够多的少数派民主党人与多数派共和党人联合支持之后，美国参议院周五似乎将推进一项法案，以防止政府部分关门。【原文：The U.S. Senate on Friday looked set to advance a bill that would prevent a partial government shutdown, after a sufficient number of minority Democrats joined with the majority Republicans in support.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-government-spending-bill-advances-toward-passage-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVWN2IKRXNL7NG6HUGUFGFDBEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:03:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国副总统万斯告诉 NBC 新闻，他希望在 4 月 5 日前达成 "高水平 "的 TikTok 协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国副总统 JD Vance 周五表示，他希望在 4 月 5 日最后期限之前达成 "高水平 "的 TikTok 协议。【原文：U.S. Vice President JD Vance said on Friday he expects a "high level" TikTok deal by the April 5 deadline.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/us-vice-president-vance-tells-nbc-news-he-expects-high-level-tiktok-deal-by-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKUFXI5HFZLY7BAUW37I6HAE5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 20:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在司法部讲话中要求对追捕他的人 "问责]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周五在美国司法部发表讲话，誓言要追究那些在他下台后的几年里对他穷追猛打的人的责任。【原文：President Donald Trump on Friday vowed to seek accountability for those who pursued him during his years out of power, speaking at the U.S. Justice Department whose prosecutors had brought some of those cases.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-demands-accountability-his-pursuers-justice-department-speech-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFORPJDHSNNZNPPTATPS3JHYHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 19:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鉴于任务繁忙，NASA获得额外一周时间提交大规模裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）周五表示，鉴于该机构本月要处理的高度优先太空任务数量众多，该机构向美国最高人事机构提交大规模裁员计划的截止日期被延长了一周。【原文：NASA on Friday said it received a one-week deadline extension to submit its plans for mass layoffs to the top U.S. personnel agency, given the number of high-priority space missions the agency is grappling with this month.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/nasa-gets-extra-week-submit-mass-layoff-plan-given-busy-mission-workload-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIM7U5MPHRJ33NE2XOHVW3CIFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 19:31:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部官员称哥伦比亚战争抗议活动违反恐怖主义规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部副部长托德-布兰奇（Todd Blanche）周五表示，司法部正在审查哥伦比亚大学学生就加沙战争举行的抗议活动是否违反了联邦恐怖主义法。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department is examining whether student protests at Columbia University over the Gaza war violated federal terrorism laws, Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche said on Friday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-justice-dept-probes-columbia-war-protests-terrorism-violations-official-says-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IXP2PDSVNOF5EOBSCVSCYP55A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加巴德承诺 "积极追究 "美国情报机构的泄密行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家情报总监图尔西-加巴德（Tulsi Gabbard）承诺将严厉打击情报界向记者泄露信息的行为。【原文：U.S. Director of National Intelligence Tulsi Gabbard has pledged to crack down on people within the intelligence community who leak information to journalists.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/gabbard-pledges-aggressively-pursue-leaks-us-intelligence-agencies-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZNGI47MDNJDJARCC6KKFPDZOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:20:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴尔的摩市要求停止美国联邦储蓄委员会资金冻结的申请被法官驳回]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴尔的摩市的一名联邦法官周五驳回了该市要求暂时阻止消费者金融保护局清空其储备金并将资金返还给美国联邦储备局或财政部的努力。【原文：A federal judge in Baltimore on Friday rejected the city's effort to temporarily block the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau from emptying its reserves and returning the money to the U.S. Federal Reserve or Department of the Treasury.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/baltimore-bid-halt-us-cfpb-defunding-rejected-by-judge-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVQOEICJDRNK5G5LE6UUIHZD2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:49:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢比奥称美国将在未来几天撤销更多学生签证]]></title><description><![CDATA[继哥伦比亚大学学生马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil）被捕并被拘留之后，美国国务卿马可-鲁比奥（Marco Rubio）周五表示，美国很可能在未来几天撤销更多学生的签证。【原文：The United States will likely revoke visas of more students in the coming days, U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio said on Friday, following the arrest and detention of Columbia University student Mahmoud Khalil, whom the Trump administration aims to deport over his pro-Palestinian activism.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/rubio-says-us-revoke-more-student-visas-coming-days-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64DZ7F4IXBLC3M7QT4O5ZWKYOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:42:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党人针对共和党选区开展反对特朗普削减开支的市政厅活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党人计划在目前由共和党人把持的竞争激烈的美国众议院选区举行一系列市民大会，旨在利用人们对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统大力削减联邦政府的愤怒情绪。【原文：Democrats plan a series of town hall meetings in highly competitive U.S. House of Representatives districts currently held by Republicans, aiming to tap into anger over President Donald Trump's campaign to aggressively slash the federal government.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/democrats-target-republican-districts-with-town-hall-campaign-against-trump-cuts-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOSCX53B7VLC3BTITER2SIP2KI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:52:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国前参议员、和蔼可亲的老派共和党人艾伦-辛普森逝世，享年 93 岁]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伦-辛普森（Alan Simpson）是一位老派温和的共和党参议员，曾在 1986 年帮助制定了美国重大移民改革方案，并结交了许多跨党派的朋友，他的家人在一份声明中说，他于周五在怀俄明州科迪市去世。享年 93 岁。【原文：Alan Simpson, an old school moderate Republican senator who helped craft major U.S. immigration reform in 1986 and made friends across the aisle, died on Friday in Cody, Wyoming, his family said in a statement. He was 93.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/former-us-senator-alan-simpson-affable-old-school-republican-dies-aged-93-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPSW7KJEKJJLZDS7SL3QFJDYJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:39:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州卫生部门称麻疹病例增至 259 例]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州卫生部门周五报告了该州的 259 例麻疹病例，比 3 月 11 日的上一次统计增加了 36 例，这也是美国近十年来爆发的最大规模的麻疹疫情之一。【原文：The Texas health department reported 259 measles cases in the state on Friday, an increase of 36 cases from its previous count on March 11, as one of the largest outbreaks the U.S. has seen in the last decade spreads.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/measles-cases-rise-259-texas-state-health-department-says-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5B5B4RW5VOF5E5KQMJ7JKQUNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈利勒的律师称，特朗普驱逐活动人士的政策违宪]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名被拘留的哥伦比亚大学学生的律师说，特朗普政府驱逐一些参加亲巴勒斯坦抗议活动的外国公民的政策是违宪的。【原文：The Trump administration’s policy of deporting some foreign nationals who participate in pro-Palestinian protests is unconstitutional, lawyers for a detained Columbia University student said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-policy-deport-activists-is-unconstitutional-khalils-lawyers-say-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQ7WONJ35BJRNAVBLWX4BSII34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院阻止加州关于儿童网络安全的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官称，加利福尼亚州不能执行一项旨在保护儿童免受可能对其身心造成伤害的在线内容影响的州法律。【原文：A federal judge said California cannot enforce a state law meant to shield children from online content that could harm them mentally or physically.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/court-blocks-california-law-childrens-online-safety-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EL43G73SGZIMHB6PKRJOZLECDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:27:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦特工搜查哥伦比亚大学两处学生宿舍]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦特工搜查了哥伦比亚大学的两处学生宿舍，该校临时校长说，一周前移民特工拘留了去年校园抗议活动的领导人马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil），特朗普政府希望将其驱逐出境。【原文：Federal agents searched two student residences at Columbia University, its interim president said, a week after immigration agents detained Mahmoud Khalil, a leader of last year's campus protests, who the Trump administration wants to deport.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/federal-agents-search-two-student-residences-columbia-university-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISWT4UGXSJM43H2ZN362CXQTXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[作为特朗普提名的医疗保险候选人，电视主持人奥兹医生将回答冲突问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[被唐纳德-特朗普总统提名负责监督医疗保险和医疗补助计划的名医、前共和党美国参议院候选人麦赫麦特-奥兹博士（Dr. Mehmet Oz）预计将在周五接受有关可能造成利益冲突的行业关系的提问。【原文：Dr. Mehmet Oz, the celebrity physician and former Republican U.S. Senate candidate nominated by President Donald Trump to oversee Medicare and Medicaid, is expected to field questions on Friday on industry ties that could create conflicts of interest.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/tvs-dr-oz-field-conflict-questions-trumps-medicare-nominee-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TVHX3KAR6RJTLIXUS2ZX6HQUDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[致命碰撞事故发生后，美国联邦航空局（FAA）对华盛顿州直升机交通发布永久性限制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周五表示，将对华盛顿里根国家机场周边的非必要直升机作业实施永久性限制，并取消直升机与客机的混合飞行。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said Friday it is imposing permanently restrictions on non-essential helicopter operations around Washington Reagan National Airport and eliminating helicopter and passenger jet mixed traffic.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/faa-issues-permanent-restrictions-washington-helicopter-traffic-after-fatal-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HWWKKFFTFVO3PB5N5V6ZEFCQYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国教育部称正在调查 45 所大学]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国教育部周五表示，其民权办公室正在对 45 所大学进行调查。【原文：The U.S. Department of Education on Friday said its office for civil rights is investigating 45 universities.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-education-department-says-it-is-probing-45-universities-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MOVYZZPS2RPVZKXLXGHPOXIFLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:17:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>