<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:33:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:33:31 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[路透社报道 Meta 的人工智能政策后，美国参议员呼吁对 Meta 进行调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社独家报道了一份允许该公司的聊天机器人 "与儿童进行浪漫或感性的对话 "的内部政策文件后，两位美国共和党参议员周四呼吁国会对 Meta Platforms 展开调查。【原文：Two Republican U.S. senators called for a congressional investigation into Meta Platforms on Thursday after Reuters exclusively reported on an internal policy document that permitted the company’s chatbots to “engage a child in conversations that are romantic or sensual.”】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-senators-call-meta-probe-after-reuters-report-its-ai-policies-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSPDLR4CQBNRFCXRFPL7SEWXUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:28:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称巴拿马运河将就两个港口的建设和运营进行招标]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位参与筹备工作的消息人士周四表示，巴拿马运河将很快开始与可能感兴趣的公司进行磋商，以便在明年第一季度启动竞争性招标，在其区域内建设和运营两个新港口。【原文：The Panama Canal will soon begin consults with potentially interested companies to launch in the first quarter next year a competitive tender offering two new ports for construction and operation within its zone, a source involved in the preparations said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/panama-canal-launch-tender-construction-operation-two-ports-source-says-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5QLKH77PJONFHAUC4ZGLRJJGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国批准可能以 5 亿美元的价格向巴林出售火箭系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[五角大楼周四表示，美国国务院已批准可能向巴林出售M142高机动性火炮火箭系统及相关设备，估计费用为5亿美元。【原文：The U.S. State Department has approved a potential sale of the M142 High Mobility Artillery Rocket System and related equipment to Bahrain for an estimated cost of $500 million, the Pentagon said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-approves-potential-sale-rocket-system-bahrain-500-million-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRK63JF3FBIHXI2B2CXLOWEA3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道巴西立法者爱德华多-博尔索纳罗警告美国将采取更多制裁措施，甚至可能征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西众议员爱德华多-博尔索纳罗（Eduardo Bolsonaro）是前总统雅伊尔-博尔索纳罗（Jair Bolsonaro）的儿子，他周四告诉路透社记者，由于美国对他父亲的法律打击，他预计美国将对巴西官员实施更多制裁，并可能征收更多关税。【原文：Brazilian Congressman Eduardo Bolsonaro, the son of former President Jair Bolsonaro, told Reuters on Thursday that he expects additional U.S. sanctions against Brazilian officials and possibly more tariffs due to a legal crackdown on his father.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-lawmaker-eduardo-bolsonaro-warns-more-us-sanctions-maybe-tariffs-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SCKEDLGUFONNHZIAL6YPTWXAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：加拿大统计机构提前发布数据，然后又将其撤下]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大统计局网站周四显示，该局在周五原定发布日期之前，在其网站上公布了有关 6 月份制造业数据的市场敏感信息。【原文：Statistics Canada posted market-sensitive information about June manufacturing data on its website ahead of the scheduled release date on Friday, the agency's website showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/canadas-statistics-agency-publishes-data-early-then-takes-it-down-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCIOYXIUVJJELCQMXXFLWQBKRI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:35:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院暂时拒绝阻止密西西比州社交媒体年龄检查法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周四拒绝搁置密西西比州要求社交媒体平台用户核实年龄并征得未成年人父母同意的法律，该法律是由一个贸易团体提出的，该团体成员包括 Meta 的 Facebook、Alphabet 的 YouTube 和 Snapchat。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Thursday to put on hold Mississippi law requiring that users of social media platforms verify their age and that minors have parental consent in a challenge by a trade group whose members include Meta's Facebook, Alphabet's YouTube and Snapchat .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-declines-now-block-mississippi-social-media-age-check-law-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2TUZX24SRJNDFGUY5A3JD6XHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:22:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴里克公司和山东黄金公司计划向阿根廷矿山投资 4 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷 Veladero 金矿的联合运营商巴里克黄金公司（Barrick Gold）和山东黄金公司（Shandong Gold）正在寻求将一个价值 4 亿美元的项目纳入政府旨在吸引大型投资的新制度。【原文：The joint operators of Argentina's Veladero gold mine, Barrick Gold and Shandong Gold , are seeking to add a $400 million project to a new government regime designed to attract large investments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/barrick-shandong-gold-aim-400-million-investment-argentine-mine-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSESEZSYQZO35D632SJ3GSZNB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富裕的购物者暂时抵挡住了 Birkenstocks 和 Bugaboo 婴儿车的涨价潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管受到贸易关税和其他方面勒紧裤腰带的影响，但至少到目前为止，美国各地的富裕购物者似乎愿意忍受从时髦的 Birkenstock 凉鞋到 Bugaboo 婴儿车等令人向往的产品的价格上涨。【原文：Well-heeled shoppers around the United States seem - so far at least - willing to soak up price hikes for aspirational products from trendy Birkenstock sandals to Bugaboo prams, despite the impact of trade tariffs and belt-tightening elsewhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/well-heeled-shoppers-shrug-off-price-hikes-birkenstocks-bugaboo-strollers-now-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XA7723DFVVNVXB5WBZLS5KJH6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:56:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团考虑为稳定币和加密 ETF 提供托管和支付服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团的一位高管告诉路透社，花旗集团正在探索提供稳定币托管和其他服务，这进一步表明华盛顿全面的政策变化正在刺激大型金融公司拓展加密货币业务。【原文：Citigroup is exploring providing stablecoin custody and other services, a top executive told Reuters, in a further sign sweeping policy changes in Washington are spurring major financial firms to expand into the cryptocurrency business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-considers-custody-payment-services-stablecoins-crypto-etfs-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6ANEVJN7FK5TBZ7KSPXYE554Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:53:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国卫生部网站显示，UnitedHealth 技术部门遭黑客攻击，1.927 亿人受到影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生部网站周四显示，联合健康集团技术部门去年遭受的网络攻击影响了 1.927 亿人。【原文：The cyberattack at UnitedHealth Group's tech unit last year impacted 192.7 million people, the U.S. health department's website showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hack-unitedhealths-tech-unit-impacted-1927-million-people-us-health-dept-website-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DGTRXMTBRKGJKROGCDMUX2SEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:50:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院将重新安排花旗集团母公司拍卖的最终听证会时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份文件显示，美国联邦法院周四批准重新安排原定于下周举行的期待已久的出售听证会，以决定委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份拍卖的最终获胜者。【原文：A U.S. federal court on Thursday approved the rescheduling of a long-awaited sale hearing originally planned for next week to decide the final winner of an auction of shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum, according to a filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-court-reschedule-final-sale-hearing-auction-citgo-parent-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KP5LGFTD4JN2JF36T6PFV7I46Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:31:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Toyota to enter South Africa's EV market with three models in 2026]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田公司一位高管周四表示，丰田计划于2026年在南非推出三款全电动车型，进军电动车新兴市场，比亚迪等中国竞争对手已在该市场与欧洲汽车制造商展开竞争。【原文：Toyota plans to introduce three fully-electric models in South Africa in 2026, a senior executive said on Thursday, entering a nascent EV market where Chinese rivals such as BYD are already competing with European carmakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-enter-south-africas-ev-market-with-three-models-2026-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZUQCXTXJFPTTJ5564RPSXAR3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者在特朗普与普京峰会前缓和对乌克兰的希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管有一些充满希望的迹象，但投资者对周五唐纳德-特朗普和弗拉基米尔-普京之间的峰会将在乌克兰战争问题上取得重大突破的预期有所减弱。【原文：Investors are tempering expectations that Friday's summit between Donald Trump and Vladimir Putin will deliver a significant breakthrough on the war in Ukraine despite some hopeful signs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-temper-ukraine-hopes-ahead-trump-putin-summit-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHJZGTIHRBK4NKVALZNDFYKAVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司 Cohere 最新融资估值 68 亿美元，任命新高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[在最新一轮 5 亿美元的融资后，Cohere 的估值达到 68 亿美元，这家人工智能初创公司正努力在竞争激烈的行业中扩大市场份额。【原文：Cohere was valued at $6.8 billion after its latest $500 million funding round, as the artificial intelligence startup moves to expand its market share in a highly competitive industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-startup-cohere-valued-68-billion-latest-fundraise-appoints-new-executives-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UJGYHRRGZN2LGHHMYUIB66ZCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫纳瓦罗称232条款调查可能涉及制药关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫贸易顾问彼得-纳瓦罗（Peter Navarro）周四表示，特朗普政府很可能根据 "232条款 "贸易调查对药品进口征收关税，因为 "很明显，由于美国在该行业对外国生产商的依赖，我们面临着国家安全危机"。【原文：White House trade adviser Peter Navarro said on Thursday that the Trump administration is likely to levy tariffs on pharmaceutical imports under a "Section 232" trade investigation because it's "very clear that we have a national security crisis" due to U.S. reliance on foreign producers in the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/white-houses-navarro-says-pharma-tariffs-likely-under-section-232-probe-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEDEABE6QVO33LDLYBZ2H7T2RI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JD.com 面临着在中国即时配送市场的争夺战]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电子商务巨头京东正在全力打造即时配送业务，以实现收入多元化，但事实证明，要打入这个竞争激烈的行业并不容易。【原文：Chinese e-commerce giant JD.com , is going all out to build its instant-delivery business to diversify revenue, but breaking into the competitive industry is proving difficult.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/jdcom-faces-battle-gain-ground-chinas-instant-delivery-market-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUUYYJEC55KYBFNAHBTNFPZJEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普的 "去银行化令 "可能给银行带来麻烦]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普要求银行不得以政治或宗教为由歧视客户的行政命令可能会给银行业带来不确定性和行政方面的麻烦。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's executive order requiring banks not to discriminate against clients on political or religious grounds could create uncertainty and administrative headaches for the industry, sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/trumps-debanking-order-could-create-headaches-banks-sources-say-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNEMWQ3JYRMM7G53A6DLVRZY5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：文件显示，汇丰计划在全球范围内大规模扩建办公室，加强人员监控]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的内部文件显示，汇丰银行计划在全球范围内增加摄像头和生物识别门禁，从而加强对员工和建筑物的监控。【原文：HSBC plans to step up surveillance of staff and buildings by adding more cameras and biometric access to its premises globally, internal documents seen by Reuters show, a move that comes amid growing concerns about companies' extensive monitoring of workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-plans-major-global-expansion-office-staff-surveillance-documents-show-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X35R6VWNO5IOZEF2X2DEXS4WUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JBS 认为美国养牛周期将从 2027 年底开始改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[JBS公司经理周四表示，美国牛肉包装商将在大约三到四个季度内继续受到牛肉供应量低的影响，美国牛群将从2027年下半年开始逐步改善。【原文：U.S.-based beef-packers will continue to reel from low cattle availability for about three or four quarters, with gradual improvements of the U.S. cattle herd happening gradually from late 2027, JBS managers said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/jbs-sees-us-cattle-cycle-improving-late-2027-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGPBHTXSPZLSXGTO5MZ2KJIZGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 公司湾威炼油厂汽油装置在火灾后降价销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，两位熟悉内情的人士称，菲利普斯 66 公司位于新泽西州林登的日产量 25.8 万桶的 Bayway 炼油厂汽油生产装置附近发生火灾后，该厂减少了汽油产量。【原文：Phillips 66 has reduced gasoline output at its 258,000 barrel-per-day Bayway refinery in Linden, New Jersey after a fire near the plant's gasoline producing unit, two people familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/phillips-66s-bayway-refinerys-gasoline-unit-reduced-rates-after-fire-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VR547F6CPFIUDJPASYNJOZLSJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示，数以千计的美国用户无法使用马斯克的 X 系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[据停电跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 称，埃隆-马斯克的 X 系统周四在美国有数千用户停机。【原文：Elon Musk's X was down for thousands of users in the U.S. on Thursday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-x-down-thousands-us-users-downdetector-shows-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYQJFMCFJVO75PXN4FN7DN5CNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 WWD 报道，华伦天奴首席执行官卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《女装日报》（Women's Wear Daily）周四报道，华伦天奴首席执行官雅各布-文图里尼（Jacopo Venturini）已从这家意大利奢侈品牌卸任。【原文：Valentino CEO Jacopo Venturini has stepped down from the Italian luxury house, Women's Wear Daily reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/valentino-ceo-steps-down-wwd-reports-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBPPYGG6JZKPVF7WSW6KLWSVPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司计划在迫在眉睫的罢工前取消 500 个航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司周四表示，在工会空乘人员计划于周六举行罢工之前，该公司预计将在当天结束前取消几十个航班，并在周五结束前取消约 500 个航班，影响 10 万名乘客。【原文：Air Canada said on Thursday it expects to cancel several dozen flights by day's end and around 500 flights by the end of Friday affecting 100,0000 passengers, ahead of a planned Saturday strike by its unionized flight attendants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-canada-plans-cancel-500-flights-by-friday-ahead-looming-strike-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSU2RFGUNVKCFEI4X3MTZXET6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:31:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储在通胀数据爆表后被认为将坚持常规规模降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[上个月美国批发价格的飙升似乎几乎抹杀了美联储在 9 月份大幅降息半个百分点的可能性，但下个月降息四分之一个百分点、10 月份再降息一个百分点的预期依然未变。【原文：A jump in U.S. wholesale prices last month looks to have all but erased the possibility that the Federal Reserve will deliver a jumbo-sized half-point interest-rate cut in September, though expectations for a quarter-point cut next month, followed by another in October, remain intact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-seen-sticking-regular-sized-rate-cuts-after-inflation-data-pops-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQMOBEGUPRKOJPGCQMU35TY4HY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果将通过软件更新为部分美国手表提供血氧功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四表示，在有关血氧测量技术的旷日持久的法律纠纷中，苹果公司在获得美国政府批准后，将通过软件更新为其部分手表型号提供血氧测量功能。【原文：Apple will bring a blood oxygen measurement feature to some of its watch models via a software update after receiving approval from the U.S. government amid a protracted legal dispute over the technology, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/apple-bring-blood-oxygen-feature-some-us-watches-with-software-update-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNAMK3AQHVNTXM2JI6RM6RDQMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:26:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 和 Target 计划于 2026 年结束合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 和 Target 周四表示，双方已同意在 2026 年结束合作关系。【原文：Ulta Beauty and Target on Thursday said they have mutually agreed to end their partnership in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ulta-beauty-target-plan-conclude-partnership-2026-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJW57VJN3FJPRHR2UD6YI75F74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国生产者价格飙升超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在服务和商品成本激增的情况下，7 月份美国生产者价格的增幅超过预期，这表明未来几个月通胀将出现更广泛的回升。【原文：U.S. producer prices increased more than expected in July amid a surge in the costs of services and goods, suggesting a broader pickup in inflation in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-us-producer-prices-surge-more-than-expected-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMYDYTGMY5NJ3JDSXA6EP3BNYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月生产者价格加速上涨，服务和商品成本激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[在服务和商品成本激增的情况下，7 月份美国生产者价格的增幅超过预期，这表明未来几个月通胀将出现更广泛的回升。【原文：U.S. producer prices increased more than expected in July amid a surge in the costs of services and goods, suggesting a broader pickup in inflation in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-producer-prices-accelerate-july-costs-services-goods-surge-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2DCV4TPONMPNILCAYIPG3FJWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融科技公司 Klarna 第二季度收入同比增长 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典金融科技公司 Klarna 于 4 月份暂停了在美国首次公开募股的计划，该公司周四表示，其第二季度收入比去年同期增长了 20%，调整后利润略有增长。【原文：Swedish fintech Klarna, which in April paused plans for an initial public offering in the United States, said on Thursday its second-quarter revenue grew 20% from a year ago on a like-for-like basis while adjusted profits increased slightly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fintech-klarnas-second-quarter-revenue-up-20-year-on-year-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSNQS7WGYFOBHD4KCQKHAWSR4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:52:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降，裁员人数减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于裁员人数较少，上周新申请失业救济的美国人数有所下降，但由于国内需求疲软，企业不愿增加招聘，这可能会使 8 月份的失业率升至 4.3%。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for jobless benefits fell last week amid low layoffs, but a reluctance by businesses to boost hiring because of softening domestic demand could drive the unemployment rate to 4.3% in August.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-amid-low-layoffs-2025-08-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DISWWJ3BMFLNDHM43JYDFNJKYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>