<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:06:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:05:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达市长试图驱逐放映以色列-巴勒斯坦电影的电影院]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈阿密海滩市市长史蒂文-迈纳（Steven Meiner）试图将一家艺术影院驱逐出城市地产，因为这家艺术影院放映了奥斯卡获奖影片《没有别的土地》（No Other Land），这部影片讲述了以色列在以色列占领的约旦河西岸驱赶一个巴勒斯坦社区的故事。【原文：Miami Beach Mayor Steven Meiner has sought to evict an art house cinema from city property for screening Oscar-winning "No Other Land," a film about the Israeli displacement of a Palestinian community in the Israeli-occupied West Bank.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/florida-mayor-seeks-evict-cinema-screening-israeli-palestinian-film-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UXDYQB6FRLLXI36ZQGT5RWZ7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:40:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达市长试图驱逐放映以色列-巴勒斯坦电影的电影院]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈阿密海滩市市长史蒂文-迈纳（Steven Meiner）试图将一家艺术影院驱逐出城市地产，因为这家艺术影院放映了奥斯卡获奖影片《没有别的土地》（No Other Land），这部影片讲述了以色列在以色列占领的约旦河西岸驱赶一个巴勒斯坦社区的故事。【原文：Miami Beach Mayor Steven Meiner has sought to evict an art house cinema from city property for screening Oscar-winning "No Other Land," a film about the Israeli displacement of a Palestinian community in the Israeli-occupied West Bank.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/florida-mayor-seeks-evict-cinema-screening-israeli-palestinian-film-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UXDYQB6FRLLXI36ZQGT5RWZ7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:40:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[No injuries reported after American Airlines plane fire in Denver, Fox affiliate says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Passengers were evacuated Thursday evening from an American Airlines plane on the ground in Denver after a fire was reported, a Fox affiliate said, adding no injuries were reported.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/no-injuries-reported-after-american-airlines-plane-fire-denver-fox-affiliate-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q62ST5YY7BNDFAYXOKVFJQBJ7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:54:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vance says you never can predict future, when asked to rule out recession -Fox News]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Vice President JD Vance on Thursday told Fox News' "The Ingraham Angle" that you can never predict the future, when asked during an interview if he could rule out a recession.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/vance-says-you-never-can-predict-future-when-asked-rule-out-recession-fox-news-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNO3U2UUXZMUHA3XLXLMSQ4BGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump administration is defying court order over anti-DEI policy, groups say]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. agencies are defying a court order blocking President Donald Trump's ban on diversity, equity and inclusion programs at businesses and organizations that contract with the federal government, groups suing over the ban said in a court filing on Thursday.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-is-defying-court-order-over-anti-dei-policy-groups-say-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKE2IXNLX5PYBK7MKFCL5HBOQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:28:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Newsmax agreed to pay $40 million to settle defamation suit over 2020 false election claims]]></title><description><![CDATA[Newsmax Media has agreed to pay $40 million to settle allegations it defamed Smartmatic by reporting false claims that the voting machine company helped rig the 2020 U.S. election for Joe Biden over Donald Trump, according to a filing.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/newsmax-agreed-pay-40-million-settle-defamation-suit-over-2020-false-election-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YQL7UYYLBJZXOVGERSO3DHXQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:27:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Columbia University punishes pro-Palestinian protesters who occupied building]]></title><description><![CDATA[Columbia University on Thursday said it had doled out a range of punishments to students who occupied a campus building last spring during pro-Palestinian protests.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/columbia-university-punishes-pro-palestinian-protesters-who-occupied-building-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFSDI5CCIVMEDEGGYLMVHDX35M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:16:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins University slashes 2,000 jobs after Trump administration grant cut]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Johns Hopkins University said on Thursday it will slash over 2,000 jobs in the U.S. and abroad after the administration of President Donald Trump terminated $800 million in grants to the renowned academic institution.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/johns-hopkins-university-slashes-2000-jobs-after-trump-administration-grant-cut-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPV5O5KK7RJMXAXQDZ2M2VRT5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:07:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Senate Democrats to clear way for stopgap bill, avert shutdown, Punchbowl News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Top U.S. Senate Democrat Chuck Schumer told colleagues behind closed doors on Thursday that he would vote to advance a stopgap funding bill, signaling that his party would provide the votes to avert a government shutdown, Punchbowl News reported, citing Democratic aides and lawmakers.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-democrats-clear-way-stopgap-bill-avert-shutdown-punchbowl-news-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBNX44A7LROUDOHZU4MLQSXVME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elon Musk visits US National Security Agency amid ongoing DOGE cuts]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elon Musk, who is leading the Trump administration's effort to cut and streamline the federal government's workforce, visited the National Security Agency on Wednesday to meet with the NSA's head, a spokesperson for the agency told Reuters.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/elon-musk-visits-us-national-security-agency-amid-ongoing-doge-cuts-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMHZ6WTENNJITF6MN6BVOXIRUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK Next round of inspections in Eaton Fire expected next week, Edison Intl CEO]]></title><description><![CDATA[Southern California Edison will begin its first close-up physical inspections of certain power equipment under investigation for possible links to the start of the Eaton Fire in Los Angeles early this year, Edison International CEO Pedro Pizarro told Reuters at the CERAWeek conference in Houston on Thursday.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ceraweek-next-round-inspections-eaton-fire-expected-next-week-edison-intl-ceo-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GFQI4NHAJLA5IV2RVQT5F7IGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US public broadcasting entity sues FEMA over emergency alert funding freeze]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Corporation for Public Broadcasting, which provides funding to PBS and NPR stations, sued the U.S. Federal Emergency Management Agency on Thursday to lift a freeze on funds meant to support the country's emergency alert system.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-public-broadcasting-entity-sues-fema-over-emergency-alert-funding-freeze-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQJFQDUQKZN6HE5QHERZF4JCFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democratic congressman Raúl Grijalva of Arizona dead at 77]]></title><description><![CDATA[Democratic U.S. Representative Raúl Grijalva, who represented Arizona for more than 20 years, died on Thursday at the age of 77 due to complications from cancer treatments, his office said in a statement.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-congressman-ral-grijalva-arizona-dead-77-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XG724RBDTVILFGRLLW6I422CEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 ABC 新闻报道，白宫将联邦调查局高级职员的背景调查移交给五角大楼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国广播公司（ABC）周四援引知情人士的话报道称，白宫已指示联邦调查局停止对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的数十名高级幕僚进行背景调查，并将这一程序移交给五角大楼。【原文：The White House has directed the FBI to stop conducting background checks into dozens of U.S. President Donald Trump's top staffers, and to transfer the process to the Pentagon, ABC News reported Thursday, citing sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-transfers-fbi-senior-staff-background-checks-pentagon-abc-news-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBJQRF5YZRJYZKSVH3BIF7ARNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼泄密者杰克-特谢拉承认犯有妨碍军事行动罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰克-特谢拉（Jack Teixeira）是马萨诸塞州空军国民警卫队的一名成员，因在网上泄露美国国家安全机密文件而被判 15 年监禁。【原文：Jack Teixeira, a member of the Massachusetts Air National Guard who is serving a 15-year prison sentence for leaking classified U.S. national security documents online, on Thursday pleaded guilty to military charges of obstructing justice.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-leaker-jack-teixeira-pleads-guilty-military-obstruction-charges-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4EEO4LXEZMZBNI2HO5UQFRV6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼泄密者杰克-特谢拉承认犯有妨碍军事行动罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰克-特谢拉（Jack Teixeira）是马萨诸塞州空军国民警卫队的一名成员，因在网上泄露美国国家安全机密文件而被判 15 年监禁。【原文：Jack Teixeira, a member of the Massachusetts Air National Guard who is serving a 15-year prison sentence for leaking classified U.S. national security documents online, on Thursday pleaded guilty to military charges of obstructing justice.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-leaker-jack-teixeira-pleads-guilty-military-obstruction-charges-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4EEO4LXEZMZBNI2HO5UQFRV6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢特尼克称特朗普希望在预算平衡时免除收入低于 15 万美元者的税收--福克斯新闻]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周四告诉福克斯新闻（Fox News），美国总统唐纳德-特朗普希望在平衡预算后免除收入低于15万美元的美国人的税收。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump would like to waive taxes for Americans earning under $150,000 once he balances the budget, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick told Fox News on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/lutnick-says-trump-wants-waive-taxes-those-earning-under-150000-when-budget-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75UPF5B4PRJFHAL7NRMBCQFFVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:16:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国批准扩建蒙大拿州煤矿]]></title><description><![CDATA[内政部周四在一份声明中说，特朗普政府批准了一项扩建蒙大拿州煤矿并将其寿命延长16年的计划。【原文：The Trump administration approved a plan to expand a Montana coal mine and extend its life by 16 years, the Interior Department said in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-approves-expansion-montana-coal-mine-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGTLFY6T6ROFHC73RKXUBOMPCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[食品与药物管理局警告说，周一返回办公室时将出现争抢工作和停车位的情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局（U.S. Food and Drug Administration）本周告诉员工，该局无法保证他们在周一按要求集体返回办公室时将面临的工作空间或停车位等障碍，这引发了对该机构进一步混乱的担忧。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration told staff this week it cannot guarantee work space or parking spots among the hurdles they will face on Monday when they return to their offices en mass as required, raising concerns of further disruption at the agency.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/fda-warns-scramble-work-parking-space-monday-return-office-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPQEZO7NZFJQPJQTJZ3P27UWPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:46:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫撤回疫苗批评家韦尔登的疾控中心主任候选人提名]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫撤回了唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统对前共和党国会议员、疫苗问题批评家戴夫-韦尔登（Dave Weldon）担任美国疾病控制和预防中心主任的提名，这一举动出人意料地发生在他原定于周四举行的参议院确认听证会前不久。【原文：The White House withdrew President Donald Trump's nomination of former Republican congressman and vaccine critic Dave Weldon to serve as director of the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, a surprise move that came shortly before his scheduled Senate confirmation hearing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/white-house-withdraws-vaccine-critic-weldon-cdc-director-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4OFHVACOFJ5LI2YQYHORZLFLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:48:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求美国最高法院干预遏制出生公民权的努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四将他试图限制美国与生俱来的公民权的斗争推向了最高法院，这位共和党总统的政府要求大法官们缩小对他强硬移民政策中这一关键因素的司法阻挠。【原文：Donald Trump took the fight over his attempt to restrict automatic U.S. birthright citizenship to the Supreme Court on Thursday as the Republican president's administration asked the justices to narrow a judicial block imposed on this key element of his hardline approach toward immigration.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-asks-us-supreme-court-intervene-bid-curb-birthright-citizenship-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5EQW2RXJKJML3DC56IH2WIHZDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普政府做出保证后，工会撤回阻止美国国际开发署（USAID）粉碎文件的动议]]></title><description><![CDATA[在得到特朗普政府律师关于没有人事档案被销毁的保证后，政府工作人员工会周四放弃了阻止美国国际开发署粉碎该机构现已关闭的办公室内文件的动议。【原文：Government worker unions on Thursday dropped their motion to block the U.S. Agency for International Development from shredding documents in the agency's now-shuttered offices after being assured by Trump administration lawyers that no personnel records had been destroyed.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/unions-retract-motion-block-usaid-document-shredding-after-trump-administration-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCJF5OL6KRKZ5P6MHL7L4LYYHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府因终止运输安全管理局官员的工会谈判而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[工会周四提起诉讼，要求阻止特朗普政府终止为美国机场和其他交通枢纽检查站的约 5 万名运输安全管理局官员进行集体谈判。【原文：Unions filed a lawsuit on Thursday seeking to block the Trump administration from ending collective bargaining for about 50,000 Transportation Security Administration officers that staff checkpoints at U.S. airports and other transportation hubs.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-sued-ending-union-bargaining-tsa-officers-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGNPO5Y6NRJBBKVRHOM6XFFEBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院批准 Pulte 担任房利美和房地美监管机构职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院周四投票确认威廉-普尔特（William Pulte）担任负责监管房利美和房地美的监管机构的下一任主管。【原文：The U.S. Senate voted Thursday to confirm William Pulte to serve as the next director of the regulator charged with overseeing housing giants Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/senate-approves-pulte-fannie-freddie-regulator-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6QCF2ZLTJOIJDV7N6FRLFOPTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学学生被捕后，抗议者占领特朗普大厦]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，数十人涌入纽约市特朗普大厦大厅，抗议逮捕和拘留哥伦比亚大学学生马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil）。【原文：Scores of people poured into the lobby of Trump Tower in New York City on Thursday to protest the arrest and detention of Columbia University student Mahmoud Khalil, whom the Trump administration aims to deport over his pro-Palestinian activism.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/protesters-occupy-trump-tower-following-arrest-columbia-student-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGEVV6SOYFI7JPLSWBTAOTD2HE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:15:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称白宫指示各机构避免解雇网络安全人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封电子邮件称，白宫正在敦促联邦机构不要裁减其网络安全团队，因为他们正在争分夺秒地遵守周四提交大规模裁员计划以削减预算的最后期限。【原文：The White House is urging federal agencies to refrain from laying off their cybersecurity teams, as they scramble to comply with a Thursday deadline to submit mass layoff plans to slash their budgets, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-instructs-agencies-avoid-firing-cybersecurity-staff-email-says-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TM52ZPNLNFJKXIATQSATFU2HVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国邮政与埃隆-马斯克的 DOGE 团队签署援助协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国邮政总局局长路易斯-德乔伊（Louis DeJoy）告诉国会，他与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 DOGE 政府改革团队签署了一项协议，在这个亏损的机构努力解决 "大问题 "的过程中，为其提供援助。【原文：U.S. Postmaster General Louis DeJoy told Congress he signed an agreement with Elon Musk's DOGE government reform team to provide assistance to the money-losing agency as it works to address "big problems."】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usps-signs-agreement-with-elon-musks-doge-team-assistance-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFFPABDOLBISDOP5VQWRKHQGXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称纽约州州长霍邱尔将于周五与特朗普会晤]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普周四告诉记者，纽约州州长凯西-霍楚尔（Kathy Hochul）将于周五上午来华盛顿与唐纳德-特朗普总统会面。【原文：New York Governor Kathy Hochul will come to Washington to meet with President Donald Trump on Friday morning, Trump told reporters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ny-governor-hochul-meet-with-trump-friday-trump-says-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZAQZNG4YBJAXFJ5JV3H437TAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院备忘录显示，特朗普医疗保险提名人近年来可能 "严重 "少缴医疗保险税款]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据参议院财政委员会民主党工作人员起草的一份备忘录，被唐纳德-特朗普总统提名监督医疗保险和医疗补助计划的名医麦赫麦特-奥兹博士近年来似乎少缴了社会保险和医疗保险税。【原文：Dr. Mehmet Oz, the celebrity physician nominated by President Donald Trump to oversee Medicare and Medicaid, appears to have underpaid his social security and Medicare taxes in recent years, according to a memo drafted by Democratic staffers on the Senate Finance Committee.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-medicare-nominee-may-have-significantly-underpaid-his-medicare-taxes-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIWZNYZY4ZI63EEL7ZH55PCSXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:14:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农民起诉特朗普政府扣留 IRA 资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，几位美国农民和非营利组织对特朗普政府提起诉讼，称其非法扣留农业部通过《通货膨胀削减法》（Inflation Reduction Act）资助的拨款。【原文：Several U.S. farmers and nonprofits filed a lawsuit against the Trump administration on Thursday, arguing it is illegally withholding Department of Agriculture grants funded by the Inflation Reduction Act.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-farmers-sue-trump-administration-withheld-ira-funds-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLOZIDKL5VNVPANVBAXD6Q4T4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>