<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:21:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:21:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官取消巴黎航展之旅，通用电气公司在致命坠机事故后推迟投资者日活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度航空公司一架喷气式客机坠毁后，波音公司和通用电气宇航公司正在缩减其公开活动，波音公司首席执行官取消了下周的巴黎航展之旅，通用电气公司则推迟了投资者日活动。【原文：Boeing and GE Aerospace are scaling back their public activities following the fatal crash of an Air India jetliner, with the planemaker's CEO canceling his trip to the Paris Airshow next week and GE postponing an investor day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-ceo-cancels-trip-paris-airshow-ge-postpones-investor-day-after-fatal-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XO56XFH7LJNJRGX7AI67OXES3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，赛默飞世尔计划以 40 亿美元的价格出售诊断部门的部分资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引知情人士的话报道称，赛默飞世尔科技公司计划以约 40 亿美元的价格出售其诊断部门，以求卸下部分低增长资产。【原文：Thermo Fisher Scientific plans to sell its diagnostics unit for about $4 billion in an attempt to offload some of its low-growth assets, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/thermo-fisher-plans-sell-parts-diagnostics-unit-4-billion-ft-reports-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFRJ72GOQVM4HLRAINY4F4XJUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 23:54:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在生物燃料混合新规出台前，ADM 在美国大豆市场掀起 "狂潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿彻-丹尼尔斯-米德兰公司（Archer-Daniels-Midland）是美国一家主要的大豆压榨商和生物燃料生产商，本周在特朗普政府宣布生物燃料掺混要求（豆油需求的主要驱动力）之前，该公司削减了购买油籽的出价。【原文：Archer-Daniels-Midland , a major U.S. soybean crusher and biofuel producer, slashed its bids to buy the oilseed this week ahead of an expected Trump administration announcement on biofuel blending requirements, a primary driver of demand for soybean oil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/adm-sets-off-frenzy-us-soybean-market-ahead-new-biofuel-blend-rule-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXU76WE54JLRXK7YDTXKHZHVBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 23:42:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NextEra 员工出售公司股票净赚 4500 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[NextEra Energy 公司周四披露，该公司员工在 2024 年期间通过出售退休计划中的公司股票实现了 4500 万美元的收益，扭转了前两年的严重亏损局面。【原文：NextEra Energy employees realized $45 million in gains from selling company stock in their retirement plan during 2024, reversing heavy losses from the previous two years, the utility disclosed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nextera-workers-net-45-million-sales-company-stock-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">US6J7YFHCJPHVAW2YV5QHFRUJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 23:09:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[5 月份全球电动汽车销量上升，中国达到 2025 年峰值 -Rho Motion]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场研究公司 Rho Motion 的数据显示，5 月份全球电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车的销量与去年同期相比增长了 24%，原因是中国市场的强劲表现抵消了北美市场的增长放缓。【原文：Global sales of electric and plug-in hybrid vehicles rose 24% in May compared with the same period a year ago, as strength in China offset slower growth in North America, according to market research firm Rho Motion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-ev-sales-rise-may-china-hits-2025-peak-rho-motion-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PJNLUZUNVO2ZAYGSWUOT7YAHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 23:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将出席匹兹堡人工智能与能源峰会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国宾夕法尼亚州参议员戴夫-麦考密克（Dave McCormick）办公室周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和来自科技与能源行业的高管将出席7月15日在宾夕法尼亚州匹兹堡举行的人工智能与能源峰会。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump and executives from the tech and energy sectors will appear at an artificial intelligence and energy summit in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, on July 15, the office of the state's U.S. Senator Dave McCormick said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-attend-ai-energy-summit-pittsburgh-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CD7K5J4SRND3CMDXE64GRDXXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 23:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 公司与新墨西哥州签署先进地热发电协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 公司与 XGS Energy 公司周四表示，双方签署了一项协议，帮助在新墨西哥州开发 150 兆瓦的先进地热电力，为 Facebook 母公司的人工智能扩张提供电力。【原文：Meta signed an agreement with XGS Energy to help develop 150 megawatts of advanced geothermal electricity in New Mexico to power the Facebook parent company's artificial intelligence expansion, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-signs-deal-advanced-geothermal-power-new-mexico-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RGYU7CRGBOYZBHKYMSR3HZO64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家电产品卷入特朗普钢铁关税扩围]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周四发布的通知，从本月晚些时候开始，包括洗碗机、洗衣机、冰箱等在内的一系列进口家用电器将受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普扩大钢铁关税的影响。【原文：A range of imported household appliances including dishwashers, washing machines, refrigerators and more will be subject to President Donald Trump's expanded steel tariffs starting later this month, according to a notice posted on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/home-appliances-swept-up-expansion-trump-steel-tariffs-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4S45UM4EJLFVKV5HVCPUOGO5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[剥夺美联储付息权的努力可能给市场带来动荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位共和党参议员计划剥夺美联储向银行支付其存放在央行账簿上的现金利息的权力，市场人士表示，如果该计划得以实施，可能会给货币政策的实施带来混乱。【原文：A Republican senator’s plan to take away the Federal Reserve’s power to pay banks interest on cash they park on central bank books could cause chaos for monetary policy implementation if it were implemented, market participants said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/effort-strip-fed-interest-paying-power-seen-likely-bring-upheaval-markets-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OG5T424YZMCPBQWHBMUM5N5ZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:15:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe上调年度预测，原因是人工智能工具的稳步采用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Adobe周四上调了全年业绩预期，这主要得益于市场对其人工智能软件工具（用于生成图像和视频内容）的持续需求。【原文：Adobe raised its full-year results forecast on Thursday, helped by continued demand for its AI-powered software tools that generate images and video content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/adobe-raises-annual-forecasts-steady-adoption-ai-powered-tools-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57KHLQ5OTNJJFIQMH6QJRZXTSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:06:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：美元绝望情绪加深]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCVQ3O47ERKNZIQ5UWLKQXOR5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普与马斯克不和后，马斯克的 SpaceX 公司在金顶导弹防御系统中的作用受到质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉该项目的人士透露，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX 公司在雄心勃勃的美国新型导弹防御系统中的作用受到质疑，因为这位亿万富翁企业家与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）上周发生了戏剧性的争吵。【原文：The role of Elon Musk's SpaceX in an ambitious new U.S. missile defense system is in question following the dramatic feud last week between the billionaire entrepreneur and President Donald Trump, according to three people familiar with the project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/after-trump-feud-role-musks-spacex-golden-dome-missile-shield-question-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFJPADHWP5L5DOGVQALWLSCV2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌就巴西 YouTube 视频纠纷在美国起诉拉达姆航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周四在加利福尼亚州圣何塞的美国联邦法院起诉总部位于智利的拉美航空，要求法院宣布巴西法院不能强迫这家科技巨头在美国撤下一段指控拉美航空一名员工性虐待儿童的 YouTube 视频。【原文：Alphabet's Google sued Chile-based LATAM Airlines in U.S. federal court in San Jose, California on Thursday, seeking a declaration that Brazilian courts cannot force the tech giant to take down a YouTube video in the United States that accused a LATAM employee of sexually abusing a child.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/google-sues-latam-airlines-us-over-brazilian-youtube-video-dispute-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5OBJG3BG5JCZLNVBFNJTUD5AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:56:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约州公共服务委员会批准 29 个电力项目，价值 6.362 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州公共服务委员会周四表示，该委员会批准了价值 6.362 亿美元的 29 个基础设施项目，实现了 642 兆瓦的电气化升级。【原文：The New York State Public Service Commission approved 29 infrastructure projects worth $636.2 million, enabling 642 megawatts of electrification upgrades, the commission said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ny-state-public-service-commission-approves-29-power-projects-valued-6362-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FT6R35LGQZLH3GZFR2TXYSF46I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行提升美国投资银行家查汉和蒙加为部门主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行资本市场（RBC Capital Markets）发言人周四证实，该行已提拔了两名金融服务投资银行家，负责管理为美国保险和特殊金融公司提供咨询服务的部门。【原文：RBC Capital Markets has promoted two of its financial services investment bankers to run units advising insurance and specialty finance companies in the U.S., a spokesperson for the bank confirmed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rbc-elevates-us-investment-bankers-chawhan-monga-unit-heads-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AX27O2QSEVMIDBOXET5N6SWWFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:45:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 将在美国推出符合 CFTC 标准的永续期货交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所的一位高管周四表示，Coinbase 计划在美国推出永续期货交易，该交易将符合美国商品期货交易委员会（Commodity Futures Trading Commission）制定的监管标准。【原文：Coinbase plans to launch perpetual futures trading in the United States, with the offering set to comply with regulatory standards outlined by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, a top executive at the crypto exchange said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coinbase-launch-cftc-compliant-perpetual-futures-trading-us-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F35NAQKIYFIMBAQ3K5LL2QKWDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:35:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，特斯拉将在全国范围内开展日本虚拟电厂业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周五报道，特斯拉将在日本扩大其虚拟发电厂业务，向企业免费提供蓄电池，并对其进行远程管理，以帮助平衡能源供需。【原文：Tesla will expand its virtual power plant business in Japan by providing free storage batteries to companies and remotely managing them to help balance energy supply and demand, Nikkei reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-take-japan-virtual-power-plant-business-nationwide-nikkei-reports-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRAJZUGAS5NVTNSUBU7DLU6H64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:21:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Kenvue 考虑出售部分皮肤健康和美容品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，四位熟悉内情的人士透露，Kenvue 正在探索出售其部分皮肤健康和美容品牌，因为这家消费保健公司正在裁减表现不佳的业务部门，以专注于核心产品。【原文：Kenvue is exploring the sale of some of its skin health and beauty brands, four people familiar with the matter said on Thursday, as the consumer health firm prunes an underperforming business segment to focus on core products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/kenvue-mulls-sale-some-skin-health-beauty-brands-sources-say-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSBNNJ2CB5IIVHQVQ73KENEOJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:09:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卖空者查诺斯质疑比特币持有先驱战略公司的估值溢价]]></title><description><![CDATA[著名做空者吉姆-查诺斯（Jim Chanos）对战略公司持有比特币的估值溢价提出质疑，称董事长迈克尔-赛勒（Michael Saylor）提高公司收益的策略是 "金融胡言乱语"。【原文：Prominent short-seller Jim Chanos has questioned Strategy's valuation premium over its bitcoin holdings, saying Chairman Michael Saylor's tactics to boost the company's returns are "financial gibberish."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/short-seller-chanos-questions-bitcoin-holding-pioneer-strategys-valuation-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">II46TCWUYVKDNCMWLCV2UXMZ7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称中国华为 2025 年不能生产超过 20 万个人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国出口管制部门的一位高级官员周四对立法者说，中国华为技术公司[RIC:RIC:HWT.UL]在2025年能够生产不超过20万个先进的人工智能芯片，并警告说，尽管这个数字低于该公司的需求，但中国正在迅速赶上美国的能力。【原文：China's Huawei Technologies [RIC:RIC:HWT.UL] is capable of producing no more than 200,000 advanced artificial intelligence chips in 2025, a top U.S. exports controls official told lawmakers on Thursday, warning that though the number is below the company's demand, China is quickly catching up to U.S. capabilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-says-chinas-huawei-cant-make-more-than-200000-ai-chips-2025-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZAE73ULNFJ53KT47LYJGKELKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示谷歌云、Spotify 有数万用户宕机]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 的数据，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌云和音乐流媒体平台 Spotify 周四有数万用户出现故障。【原文：Alphabet's Google Cloud and music streaming platform Spotify were down for tens of thousands of users on Thursday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-cloud-down-thousands-users-downdetector-shows-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEXTSOWTURO3XB3WYHKJ7LY2JU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:41:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家："Neocloud "克鲁索将为人工智能数据中心购买价值 4 亿美元的 AMD 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[Crusoe 首席执行官蔡斯-洛赫米勒（Chase Lochmiller）周四表示，这家人工智能数据中心构建商计划从先进微设备公司（Advanced Micro Devices）购买价值约 4 亿美元的人工智能芯片，以增加其计算能力组合。【原文：Crusoe CEO Chase Lochmiller said on Thursday the artificial intelligence data center builder planned to purchase roughly $400 million worth of AI chips from Advanced Micro Devices to add to its portfolio of computing power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/neocloud-crusoe-buy-400-million-worth-amd-chips-ai-data-centers-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZ2DCFGL4FMSJAOMZFXSZ26SB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）报道：因美国芯片出口管制，英伟达将停止把中国纳入预测范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）周四告诉美国有线电视新闻网（CNN），在美国对向中国销售芯片实施严厉限制后，英伟达将把中国市场排除在收入和利润预测之外。【原文：Nvidia will exclude the Chinese market from its revenue and profit forecasts following the imposition of tough U.S. restrictions on chip sales to China, CEO Jensen Huang told CNN on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-stop-including-china-forecasts-amid-us-chip-export-controls-cnn-reports-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKU4HUSFPJMTRBBBRBOYDQ2NWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:31:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[农业部长表示，特朗普将研究农场工人的所有选项]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部长布鲁克-罗林斯（Brooke Rollins）周四表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统将利用一切可用的工具来解决他正在进行的打击移民行动中的农场工人问题，但国会需要做出大部分改变。【原文：U.S. Agriculture Secretary Brooke Rollins on Thursday said President Donald Trump would look at every available tool to address farm workers amid his ongoing immigration crackdown, but that Congress would need to make most of the changes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trump-examine-all-options-farm-workers-agriculture-secretary-says-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOX6Z33XCRKCLPFOXLGRVRQII4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:25:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD 首席执行官发布新款人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[先进微设备公司首席执行官苏丽莎展示了新一批人工智能芯片，这些芯片将与英伟达公司设计的旗舰处理器展开竞争。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices CEO Lisa Su showed off a new crop of artificial intelligence chips that will compete with the flagship processors designed by Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/amd-ceo-unveils-new-ai-chips-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TG52CJBBGRMQNHXRHQQPGN5SHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 IPO 市场复兴扎根，Chime 首次公开募股便一飞冲天]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周，美国的新上市房源大幅反弹，一些令人瞠目的首次上市房源激起了人们的希望，在经历了 4 月份以来的枯竭期后，美国房市有望持续复苏。【原文：New listings in the U.S. have bounced back sharply in recent weeks, with some eye-popping debuts stoking hopes of a sustained revival after a dry spell since April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-ipo-market-revival-takes-root-chime-soars-debut-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVIDAD2ZNNOU7IGMNYKU4SQ7K4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢公司经理说，巴西塞拉多米内罗地区的阿拉比卡种植者正在测试 Conilon 植物]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司的农业咖啡经理说，巴西的塞拉多米内罗（Cerrado Mineiro）是种植阿拉比卡咖啡豆的大本营，巴西的咖啡生产商正在测试 Conilon 品种，以应对气候变化和其他问题。【原文：Brazilian coffee producers in the country's Cerrado Mineiro, a stronghold for growing Arabica beans, are testing Conilon varieties amid climate change and other concerns, Nestle's agricultural coffee manager said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/arabica-growers-brazils-cerrado-mineiro-testing-conilon-plants-nestle-manager-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWPU5KBPSZLA7NEIK4NMB35KYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飞机初创企业 JetZero 将在十年内投资 47 亿美元建设北卡罗来纳州总部]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国飞机初创公司 JetZero 已获得美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）和阿拉斯加航空公司（Alaska Airlines）的投资，该公司周四表示，将在十年内投资 47 亿美元，在北卡罗来纳州建造生产设施和总部。【原文：U.S. aircraft startup JetZero, which has secured investments from United Airlines and Alaska Airlines, will invest $4.7 billion over a decade on a production facility and headquarters in North Carolina, the state said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/aircraft-startup-jetzero-invest-47-bln-over-decade-north-carolina-hq-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGLOEXMT6BINRMMP66KMSVFG4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德计划明年开始肥胖症药物淀粉样蛋白的后期试验]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）周四表示，该公司计划在2026年第一季度开始对超重或肥胖的成年人进行实验性减肥药淀粉样蛋白（amycretin）的注射和口服后期试验。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Thursday it plans to start late-stage trials of its experimental weight-loss drug amycretin in injection and oral forms during the first quarter of 2026 for adults who are overweight or obese.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-plans-start-late-stage-trials-experimental-obesity-drug-amycretin-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RXFSUFST5I3TATXU6YJWTOYEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:22:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称可能很快提高汽车关税以增加美国产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四警告说，他可能很快会提高汽车关税，认为这可能会促使汽车制造商加快在美国的投资。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday warned he may soon hike auto tariffs, arguing that could prod automakers to speed U.S. investments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-he-may-soon-hike-auto-tariffs-get-more-us-production-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">656X4BVTEZOJLALWB67YE42MBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:17:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>