<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:26:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:26:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Novo Nordisk rolls out $349 Wegovy cash price ahead of plan]]></title><description><![CDATA[Novo Nordisk said on Monday it has begun selling its popular weight-loss drug Wegovy for $349 a month to cash payers, months ahead of the timeline set out with the Trump administration.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-rolls-out-349-wegovy-cash-price-ahead-plan-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJNFXWYEFZL4JOEJFSPSJ4CDTA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:55:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China's C919, rival to Boeing and Airbus, makes debut display outside Asia]]></title><description><![CDATA[China staged a Middle East debut for its C919 jetliner with a flying display at the Dubai Airshow on Monday, its first outside East Asia, as it showcases plans to compete with Airbus and Boeing.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-c919-rival-boeing-airbus-makes-debut-display-outside-asia-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56TAIFOSQVKDDNIFNAHI3RQ3VQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，杰夫-贝索斯将共同领导人工智能初创公司，这是他自亚马逊之后首次担任运营职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周一报道，杰夫-贝索斯（Jeff Bezos）将担任一家新成立的人工智能初创公司的联合首席执行官，该公司专注于人工智能在计算机、汽车和航天器的工程和制造领域的应用。【原文：Jeff Bezos will serve as co-chief executive officer of a new artificial intelligence startup that focuses on AI for engineering and manufacturing of computers, automobiles and spacecraft, the New York Times reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/jeff-bezos-co-lead-ai-startup-first-operational-role-since-amazon-nyt-reports-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJSQSFA35BPUFFYZROANC63MB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:49:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商新鹏汽车预计第四季度收入疲软 竞争激烈]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商新鹏汽车周一预计第四季度营收将低于预期，因为在全球最大的汽车市场上，旷日持久的价格战和愈演愈烈的竞争有可能导致其增长放缓。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle maker XPeng forecast fourth-quarter revenue below estimates on Monday, as a prolonged price war and intensifying competition in the world's largest auto market threaten to slow its growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-ev-maker-xpeng-forecasts-weak-fourth-quarter-revenue-amid-fierce-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Y6TCZYUMRLZLLFW4VTBTSTHGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：英伟达和数据下滑前恢复平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOTZOU6Z2NIZZG3HMAOG43XYBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:45:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利投票结果显示极右翼势力强劲，为市场谨慎反弹奠定基础]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师周一表示，智利总统选举的第一轮投票结果应该会对比索、股票和债券产生积极影响，预计这有可能为更多有利于市场的举措铺平道路。【原文：The outcome of the first-round vote in Chile's presidential election should be positive for the peso, stocks and bonds, analysts said on Monday, expecting this could potentially pave the way for more market-friendly initiatives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chile-vote-sets-stage-cautious-market-rally-strong-far-right-showing-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPXWLXXMC5LTHBLNQ2CNUNNO2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:44:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院将考虑恢复泰诺与自闭症案件的审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院预计将于周一听取寻求重启泰诺诉讼的家庭的辩论，此前特朗普政府公开宣传他们的主张，即这种流行的止痛药与儿童自闭症有关。【原文：A U.S. appeals court is expected to hear arguments on Monday from families seeking to revive their lawsuits over Tylenol, after the Trump administration publicly promoted their claims that the popular painkiller is linked to autism in children.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-appeals-court-weigh-reviving-cases-over-tylenol-autism-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMTXQHMDCJPD5MVGZN4CCUCSSM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[散户投资者购买美国股市下跌股票的信念减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[散户投资者对美国股市反弹能力的信心有减弱的迹象，市场数据和分析师的观察都表明，他们逢低买入的热情正在减退。【原文：Retail investors are showing signs of waning confidence in the U.S. stock market's ability to rebound, with market data and analysts' observations both indicating an ebb in their enthusiasm about buying dips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retail-investors-show-less-conviction-buying-us-stock-market-dips-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OULHORXKRN63EMH4WWP5EMU3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GMI Cloud 将在台湾建造价值 5 亿美元的人工智能数据中心，采用 Nvidia 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国云服务提供商 GMI Cloud 周一表示，在美国芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）的支持下，该公司将在台湾建立一个价值 5 亿美元的人工智能数据中心。【原文：U.S.-based cloud services provider GMI Cloud said on Monday it will build a $500 million artificial intelligence data centre in Taiwan with the support of U.S. chipmaker Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/gmi-cloud-build-500-million-ai-data-centre-in-taiwan-with-nvidia-chips-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K3ODPJIC7VJPZEEGZ7YGGXP6P4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场等待英伟达财报和政府数据，美股期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街主要股指期货周一走高，为包括人工智能巨头英伟达（Nvidia）财报和政府数据发布在内的密集一周拉开了序幕，而在伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）披露持有该公司股份后，Alphabet跳涨。【原文：Futures for Wall Street's main indexes were higher on Monday, kicking off a packed week that includes AI giant Nvidia's earnings and resumption of government data releases, while Alphabet jumped after Berkshire Hathaway disclosed a stake in the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-rise-markets-await-nvidia-earnings-government-data-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PDSKZNLFVPNXEO2LT5V3CHOWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国电力集团与 OpCore 公司将在法国开发价值 40 亿欧元的数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国公用事业公司 EDF 和电信集团 Iliad 与 InfraVia Capital Partners 的合资企业 OpCore 周一表示，双方已就开发一个超大规模数据中心进行了独家谈判。【原文：French utility EDF and OpCore, a joint venture between telecoms group Iliad and InfraVia Capital Partners, have entered into exclusive negotiations to develop a hyperscale data centre, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/edf-opcore-develop-4-billion-euros-data-centre-france-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QOCCUC2CVOGHN6KGNIES3LYXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度监管机构将在法庭上拒绝简街的数据请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解此事的消息人士称，印度市场监管机构本周将向法院表示，在美国公司就一项证券交易禁令提起上诉后，该机构认为没有理由向简街公司公布更多数据和文件。【原文：India's markets regulator will tell a court this week that it sees no reason to release additional data and documents to Jane Street, two sources with direct knowledge of the matter said, after the U.S. firm appealed a securities trading ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-regulator-decline-jane-street-data-request-court-sources-say-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ6Z525SCVLW5BWWFRYOXZ66ZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔披露 49 亿美元持股后，谷歌母公司 Alphabet 股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）披露持有这家科技巨头的股份后，Alphabet 的股价在周一盘前交易中上涨了 5.5%，这可能是巴菲特领导下的这家企业集团最后的重大举措之一。【原文：Alphabet's shares rose 5.5% in premarket trading on Monday after Berkshire Hathaway disclosed a stake in the tech giant, marking what could be one of the final major moves by the conglomerate under the leadership of Warren Buffett.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-parent-alphabets-shares-rally-after-berkshire-reveals-49-billion-stake-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOTND6LALVI3DDKRHN6THW4KJQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 09:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[入侵奥巴马账户的英国推特黑客被勒令偿还 540 万美元比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国检察官周一表示，一名因 2020 年推特（Twitter）黑客攻击事件而被定罪的男子已被勒令偿还价值 410 万英镑（约合 540 万美元）的比特币。【原文：A man convicted over a 2020 Twitter hack that compromised accounts of high-profile figures including former U.S. President Barack Obama has been ordered to repay 4.1 million pounds ($5.40 million) worth of Bitcoin, British prosecutors said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-twitter-hacker-who-breached-obama-accounts-ordered-repay-41-million-pounds-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWRKLHFJSNNEBF5L7OC7XLMDEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 09:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡交易所将推出比特币和以太币永续期货]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡交易所（SGX）衍生品部门周一表示，将在其平台上推出比特币和以太币加密货币永续期货交易。【原文：The derivatives arm of Singapore Exchange (SGX) said on Monday that it would launch bitcoin and ether cryptocurrency perpetual futures trading on its platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-exchange-launch-bitcoin-ether-perpetual-futures-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTN5W3FN5VKJXADFOZFFPDULIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 09:23:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：电动汽车销售在南美蓬勃发展--没有特斯拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[当秘鲁绿色能源企业家路易斯-兹维巴赫（Luis Zwiebach）想在 2019 年购买一辆电动汽车时，他飞了 4000 英里到加利福尼亚试驾特斯拉的 Model 3 轿车。但特斯拉没有官方进口商，他也无法绕过秘鲁复杂的汽车进口程序。【原文：When Peruvian green energy entrepreneur Luis Zwiebach wanted to buy an electric vehicle in 2019, he flew 4,000 miles to California to test drive Tesla’s Model 3 sedan. But Tesla lacked an official importer and he couldn’t find a way around Peru’s complex vehicle import procedures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/electric-vehicle-sales-are-booming-south-america-without-tesla-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZF7DP6FZJNM2PJIZYV4OYMX65M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 09:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音研究更大型喷气机之际，阿联酋航空再订购 65 架 777X]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于迪拜的阿联酋航空公司周一表示，它将再订购 65 架波音 777-9 喷气式飞机，从而巩固其作为全球最大宽体喷气式飞机买家的地位，因为这家美国飞机制造商同意对更大型的波音 777-9 喷气式飞机进行可行性研究。【原文：Dubai-based airline Emirates said on Monday it was ordering another 65 Boeing 777-9 jets, cementing its position as the world's biggest buyer of wide-body jets as the U.S. planemaker agreed to carry out a feasibility study for a larger version.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/emirates-says-it-orders-65-more-boeing-777-9-jets-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMPRDI3Y7FI2DMEGIU73EG7764</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 08:42:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利看好 2026 年美股而非全球股票，上调标普 500 指数年底目标值]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）在周一发布的一系列全球经济展望报告中表示，与全球同行相比，摩根士丹利更看好美国股市，并将2026年的S&amp;P 500指数年末目标上调至7,800点，理由是盈利增长强劲、人工智能驱动的效率提升以及支持性的政策背景。【原文：In a series of global economic outlook notes published on Monday, Morgan Stanley said it favors U.S. stocks over global peers and raised its 2026 year-end target for the S&amp;P 500 index to 7,800, citing robust earnings growth, AI-driven efficiency gains and a supportive policy backdrop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/morgan-stanley-prefers-us-stocks-over-global-peers-2026-raises-sp-500-year-end-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6BO4QVQNBPB7ANZCTMLSMDZ74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 07:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅收购第二笔中国护肤品股份，C-Beauty 品牌抢占市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[化妆品巨头欧莱雅周一表示，它已持有中国大众护肤品牌兰蔻的少数股份，这是它近几个月来在中国的第二笔投资。【原文：Cosmetics giant L'Oreal said on Monday it has taken a minority stake in mass-market Chinese skincare brand Lan, marking its second investment in recent months in China, where local brands have grown rapidly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/loral-buys-second-chinese-skincare-stake-c-beauty-brands-snare-market-share-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAHEQC2QL5IU3KD5FZULXPZQRY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 06:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行董事会改组暴露出可能影响政策的多元化缺陷]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元区官员已经开始了为期两年的更换欧洲中央银行执行董事会大部分成员的进程，其中包括行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德。【原文：Euro zone officials have embarked on a two-year process to replace most of the European Central Bank's executive board, including President Christine Lagarde, raising questions along the way about how well the institution represents the people it serves.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ecb-board-revamp-exposes-diversity-failings-that-could-impact-policy-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EYUV27HKBI7ZEDDFRD4AUFS3A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价英伟达财报可能盖过美国数据延迟的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFPM3PYCANMMLLOH3P7G3DYXYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:33:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰最高法院裁定优步司机为雇员]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，新西兰最高法院支持下级法院的裁决，即优步（Uber）司机在起诉共享出行公司时应被视为雇员，这一裁决可能为集体谈判铺平道路。【原文：New Zealand’s highest court sided on Monday with a lower court’s ruling that drivers of Uber who brought a case against the rideshare company should be treated as employees, a decision that could pave the way for collective bargaining.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/new-zealands-top-court-rules-that-uber-drivers-are-employees-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2SQAU2OUFNDJLMHCEOREFSR7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 05:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[朝日新闻》报道：日本考虑制定新的网络货币规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[据日本《朝日新闻》周日报道，日本金融厅（FSA）正在考虑制定相关法规，将加密货币定义为受内幕交易规则约束的金融产品，并降低利润税率。【原文：Japan's Financial Services Agency (FSA) is considering regulations that would define cryptocurrency as financial products subject to insider trading rules and reduce the tax rate on profits, the Asahi newspaper reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/japan-considers-new-cyptocurrency-rules-asahi-newspaper-reports-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3H7YN4YVNRPENI2OBBKSL45Q6M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 02:17:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元持稳，投资者关注美国公布的积压数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周一小幅走强，因为投资者在等待政府关门结束后公布的一系列美国经济数据，希望这些数据能为美联储 12 月份的利率前景增添清晰度。【原文：The dollar firmed slightly on Monday as investors braced for the release of a slew of U.S. economic data following the ending of the government's shutdown, hoping it will add clarity to the Federal Reserve's rate outlook in December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-steady-investors-eye-release-us-data-backlog-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3E4OETXDFPAXGWCYDMDBRCCCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:47:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达财报大考在即，股市保持谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市基调谨慎，交易员们展望了本周的企业财报和美国补涨数据，重点关注利率前景和人工智能类股泡沫化涨势的命运。【原文：Asia's stock markets struck a cautious tone on Monday as traders looked ahead to a week of corporate earnings and catch-up U.S. data, with the focus on the interest rate outlook and the fate of a frothy rally in artificial intelligence stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-markets-global-markets-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIAO7W3VBFPKJNOFKMNSK5A6MQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯重要出口枢纽恢复装载后石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一亚市早盘，油价下跌，抹去了上周的涨幅，原因是俄罗斯重要的出口枢纽新罗西斯克港在遭受乌克兰袭击的黑海港口停航两天后恢复了装货。【原文：Oil prices fell in early Asian trade on Monday, erasing last week's gains, as loadings resumed at the key Russian export hub of Novorossiysk after a two-day suspension at the Black Sea port that had been hit by a Ukrainian attack.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-falls-after-loadings-resume-key-russian-export-hub-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEHAWM2F6JNJXFIWUMLMTIDLGM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资承诺后，三星电子股价上涨逾 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子承诺在韩国投资 450 万亿韩元（约合 3101.4 亿美元），并在平泽市增加一条芯片生产线，三星电子股价在周一开盘时上涨超过 3%。【原文：Shares of Samsung Electronics gained more than 3% at the market opening on Monday after the company pledged to invest 450 trillion won ($310.14 billion) in the country and add a chip production line in city of Pyeongtaek.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/samsung-elec-shares-rise-more-than-3-after-investment-pledge-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WTJ62AX6JNFBCL67BIOGEZ44Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，航空公司预计美国联邦航空局将结束在美国主要机场削减 3% 航班的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，航空公司预计美国联邦航空管理局将于周一早些时候结束在美国40个主要机场削减3%的国内航班，从而放宽因空中交通管制安全问题而实施的限制。【原文：Airlines anticipate the Federal Aviation Administration will end 3% domestic flight reductions at 40 major U.S. airports early Monday, easing restrictions imposed over air traffic control safety concerns, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/airlines-expect-faa-end-3-flight-cuts-major-us-airports-sources-say-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HS4JFNR3KVOT7KBUHNV5TURRFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本经济六个季度以来首次出现萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周一公布的数据显示，由于美国关税对出口的打击，日本经济在 7-9 月份按年率计算萎缩了 1.8%，这是六个季度以来的首次下滑。【原文：Japan's economy contracted an annualised 1.8% in the July-September quarter, the first fall in six quarters, due to a hit to exports from U.S. tariffs, government data showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-economy-contracts-first-time-six-quarters-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVVGODDDFFLAFEF5H7ZLKYSLNA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚西拉资源公司与特斯拉将进一步延长石墨供应协议的最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚西拉资源公司（Syrah Resources）周一表示，该公司已与特斯拉公司达成一致，在两个月内第二次延长处理其石墨供应协议违约指控的最后期限，因为该公司正努力保持其美国业务的活力。【原文：Australia's Syrah Resources said on Monday that it had agreed with Tesla to extend the deadline to tackle an alleged default of their graphite supply agreement for the second time in two months as the miner works to keep its U.S. operations buoyant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/australias-syrah-resources-tesla-further-extend-graphite-supply-deal-deadline-2025-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POCW4IVKLBJY5CBCSLGBXBIEL4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>