<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:33:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:32:20 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Hershey sees strong 2026 even as cocoa costs weigh]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hershey forecast annual sales and profit above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, supported by resilient demand for its confectionery and salty snacks and continued benefits of earlier price hikes implemented to absorb rising costs.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hershey-sees-strong-2026-even-cocoa-costs-weigh-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXIXT4HBAFKRDCR5UFD5OOOGLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:11:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IQVIA forecasts weak annual profit on higher interest expenses]]></title><description><![CDATA[Healthcare data and clinical research provider IQVIA Holdings on Thursday forecast annual profit below Wall Street expectations, weighed down by higher interest costs, even as strong fourth-quarter results underscored improving demand from pharmaceutical clients.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/iqvia-forecasts-weak-annual-profit-higher-interest-expenses-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNJGFMGETBOFZKU3APPPAZEH2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI unveils AI agent service as part of push to attract businesses]]></title><description><![CDATA[Your next coworker might be generated by AI.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/openai-unveils-ai-agent-service-part-push-attract-businesses-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXXP6N76KFJSXLXSJ7A6XIXYAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[India monitoring evolving crypto trading to ensure tax compliance, top tax official says]]></title><description><![CDATA[India is talking to cryptocurrency exchanges to assess evolving trading activity as it seeks oversight over newer crypto products, according to a top tax official.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-monitoring-evolving-crypto-trading-ensure-tax-compliance-top-tax-official-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIYBV7SCPZMEDO6KISJGPQI6IU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US weekly jobless claims increase more than expected]]></title><description><![CDATA[The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased more than expected last week, likely boosted by snowstorms across much of the country, but labor market conditions remain stable.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-more-than-expected-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AF6IYLJDCRMONDTAHN6LZOIYPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Hims and Hers Health launches compounded copy of Wegovy pill at $49]]></title><description><![CDATA[Online telehealth company Hims and Hers Health will begin offering compounded copies of Novo Nordisk's new Wegovy pill at an introductory price of $49 per month, the company said Thursday, about $100 less than the brand name.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hims-hers-health-launches-copy-wegovy-pill-49-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOOFLPU2XNIF3BGG7M33WXOYBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球非美国股票基金吸引资金流入，投资者避开估值过高的美国科技股]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球非美国股票基金正吸引强劲资金流入，投资者正从估值过高的美国科技股转向更具多样性、估值较低的海外市场，这一趋势由美国宏观经济风险和美元走弱所驱动。【原文：Global ex-U.S. equity funds are attracting strong inflows as investors shift away from high-valuation U.S. tech stocks toward more diversified, lower-valued markets abroad, driven by U.S. macro risks and a weaker dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-funds-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXNJL5QKYNJ6LDT5D4GBAFVMV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙任命新任战略、交易及业务发展负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司周四公布了将于2026年生效的高层领导层变动计划，多名资深高管即将退休，内部候选人将接任战略、贸易及业务发展等关键岗位。【原文：Chevron Corp on Thursday outlined senior leadership changes that will take effect in 2026, with several long-serving executives retiring and internal candidates stepping into key roles across strategy, trading and business development.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-names-new-heads-strategy-trading-business-development-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LT3BQCJMAJLB5NOM6WJEHI7MSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:22:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉夫·劳伦对利润率的警示盖过了强于预期的季度销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉夫·劳伦周四公布的第三季度销售额超出华尔街预期，但这家奢侈品零售商警告称美国关税将导致利润率承压，其股价在盘前交易中下跌6.6%。【原文：Ralph Lauren posted third-quarter sales that topped Wall Street estimates on Thursday, but the luxury retailer's warning of margin pressure tied to U.S. tariffs sent its shares down 6.6% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ralph-lauren-posts-third-quarter-sales-beat-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAPMOCXUBRKS3JOGFLOWARBRBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蓝猫基金盈利超预期，资产管理规模突破3000亿美元里程碑]]></title><description><![CDATA[蓝猫公司周四公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，其管理资产规模激增22%，突破3000亿美元大关，推动其股价在盘前交易中上涨2%。【原文：Blue Owl beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Thursday and posted a 22% surge in assets under management that crossed the $300 billion milestone, sending its shares up 2% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blue-owl-beats-profit-estimates-aum-crosses-300-billion-milestone-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THKKDINVIFIMFKWLFA5C6732HA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:57:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡迪纳尔健康公司上调年度利润预期，押注专科药品需求激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡迪纳尔健康公司周四上调了全年利润预期，此前其季度业绩超出华尔街预期。该公司押注于专业药品的强劲需求及其各业务板块的优异表现。【原文：Cardinal Health on Thursday raised its expectations for annual profit after surpassing Wall Street estimates for quarterly results, as it bets on robust demand for specialty medicines and strong performance across its segments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cardinal-health-boosts-annual-profit-forecast-banking-surging-demand-specialty-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLE3PROG3NLLHEAQXSZOE52X5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:55:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金遭人工智能抛售冲击，高盛称]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛在周三收盘后向客户发布的报告中指出，随着科技股抛售潮导致热门交易价值缩水，股票交易类大型对冲基金遭遇近一年来最惨淡的一天。【原文：Big hedge funds that trade in stocks had their worst day in almost a year on Wednesday as crowded trades lost value in the tech-driven selloff, Goldman Sachs said in a note to clients released after the market closed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-hit-by-ai-sell-off-goldman-sachs-says-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RB6MR6XAHVLSTLPAO6D4PXD2VU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:50:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约证券交易所母公司洲际交易所集团因交易量增长而利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[洲际交易所周四公布第四季度利润增长，这家纽约证券交易所母公司受益于波动市场中交易量的提升。【原文：Intercontinental Exchange posted a rise in fourth-quarter profit on Thursday, as the New York Stock Exchange parent benefited from stronger trading volumes in a volatile market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nyse-parent-ices-profit-rises-stronger-trading-volumes-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5XXOTLNQRNAFNCAD4IEU6QGQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国软件股在因人工智能颠覆担忧遭遇重挫后趋于稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[软件与数据服务类股周四在经历重挫后企稳，投资者正密切关注快速发展的人工智能工具是否开始冲击传统软件及订阅业务的需求。【原文：Software and data services stocks stabilized on Thursday after a bruising selloff, as investors looked for clues on whether fast-advancing artificial intelligence tools are starting to dent demand for traditional software and subscription businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-software-stocks-stabilize-after-bruising-selloff-ai-disruption-fears-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4M55GWM65JBTBWZDW74EFRVOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普拉达旗下品牌范思哲任命艾莱亚设计师彼得·穆利尔为创意总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利时尚品牌范思哲（Versace）去年被竞争对手普拉达（Prada）收购，该公司宣布任命历峰集团旗下品牌Alaïa的离任设计师彼得·穆利尔（Pieter Mulier）为新任创意总监。【原文：Versace, the Italian fashion brand which last year was acquired by rival Prada , said it had appointed as its new creative director Pieter Mulier, the outgoing designer of Richemont-owned Alaia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/prada-owned-versace-appoints-alaias-pieter-mulier-creative-director-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7BE423BJNLCLO4TUXXPPJDOOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:06:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着房主补贴到期，美国屋顶太阳能安装商裁员重组]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国住宅太阳能企业正为今年业务量大幅下滑做准备。此前推动该行业十余年快速增长的联邦税收抵免政策已到期，这将引发裁员、重组及部分企业倒闭。【原文：U.S. residential solar companies are preparing for a steep drop in business this year after the expiration of a federal tax credit that helped drive more than a decade of rapid growth, prompting layoffs, restructurings and some company failures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-rooftop-solar-installers-cut-jobs-restructure-homeowner-subsidy-expires-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FH3SEYCBVBNJ7PNMHGTMOKCMFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康菲石油因油价疲软未达季度盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[康菲石油公司周四公布的第四季度利润低于华尔街预期，原因是原油价格下跌抵消了石油产量增长和成本节约措施带来的积极影响。【原文：ConocoPhillips missed Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Thursday, as lower crude prices countered a rise in oil production and cost-saving efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/conocophillips-misses-quarterly-profit-estimates-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXWNQVU33ZLQFHHSYTA4IGPW3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车在2025年超越特斯拉，成为欧洲电动汽车销量冠军。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据JATO Dynamics周四发布的数据显示，2025年大众汽车在欧洲纯电动汽车销量超越特斯拉。此前中国比亚迪已于去年取代特斯拉成为全球最大电动汽车制造商，此次又使这家美国车企遭遇新的挫折。【原文：Volkswagen overtook Tesla in sales of fully-electric cars in Europe in 2025, data from JATO Dynamics showed on Thursday, another setback for the U.S. automaker after China's BYD dethroned it as the world's top EV maker last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-overtook-tesla-europes-top-ev-seller-2025-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVZFF73GUVNWDPBFD5QZDBD5FY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼要求调查SpaceX公司潜在的中国所有权问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一封信函显示，美国民主党参议员敦促五角大楼立即对SpaceX展开审查。信中援引潜在国家安全风险为由，指控中国投资者已秘密收购这家私营火箭制造商的股权。【原文：Democratic U.S. senators urged the Pentagon to conduct an immediate review of SpaceX amid allegations that Chinese investors have secretly acquired stakes in the closely held rocket maker, citing potential national security risks, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/pentagon-asked-probe-spacex-potential-chinese-ownership-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JRWBS6WSJZIPHN7LJTDYFCMG5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私募巨头KKR报告管理费上升，交易费下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司KKR周四报告称，第四季度管理新资本所获的费用收入有所增长，但交易产生的费用收入下降，同时一项一次性费用拖累了关键盈利指标。【原文：Investment firm KKR reported a rise in fourth-quarter income from fees it earns on managing new capital on Thursday, but booked lower fees earned from transactions, while a one-off charge weighed on a key profit metric.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/buyout-giant-kkr-reports-rising-management-fees-lower-transaction-fees-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOYYICLQHJIH3PICRPNXLUOBDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汤森路透报告显示第四季度营收增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[汤森路透周四公布第四季度营收增长，得益于其法律、税务与会计以及企业业务板块的业绩表现。与此同时，投资者正评估人工智能企业进军其核心市场的潜在影响。【原文：Thomson Reuters reported higher fourth quarter revenue on Thursday, boosted by results from its legal, tax and accounting and corporates businesses, as investors weigh the impact of artificial intelligence companies moving into its key markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/thomson-reuters-reports-higher-fourth-quarter-revenue-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAMU3CMZEBNX7AYITU47RZXYTU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify将通过与Bookshop.org的合作，允许用户在应用内购买实体书籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify周四宣布，将通过与在线零售商Bookshop.org的合作，在其流媒体平台上开始销售实体书籍，标志着其业务意外地扩展到有声读物领域之外。【原文：Spotify said on Thursday it will begin selling physical books on its streaming platform through a partnership with online retailer Bookshop.org, marking an unexpected expansion beyond its audiobooks business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spotify-let-users-buy-physical-books-app-through-bookshoporg-partnership-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BK2V47YNZVLWPNJ6CEZ36LJ56Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挂毯公司上调年度预测，Tabby手袋热潮助推假日季度销售暴涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[塔佩斯特里公司周四再次上调年度盈利目标，此前其Tabby手袋需求强劲，助力这家平价奢侈品零售商轻松超越假日季度预期。【原文：Tapestry raised its annual earnings targets on Thursday for a second time after strong demand for its Tabby handbags helped the affordable luxury retailer comfortably beat holiday-quarter estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tapestry-lifts-annual-forecasts-tabby-handbag-craze-fuels-blowout-holiday-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CROOPW7JJKMDDJU6NGTZRFMC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:48:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙首相桑切斯：我们不会在社交媒体禁令问题上被科技寡头左右]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙首相佩德罗·桑切斯周四表示，科技公司无法动摇西班牙政府的决心，政府计划禁止年轻人使用社交媒体平台。他指责"科技寡头"散布关于西班牙的谎言。【原文：Tech companies will not sway the will of the Spanish government as it intends to ban young people from social media platforms, Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez said on Thursday, accusing "tech oligarchs" of spreading lies about Spain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/spains-sanchez-we-wont-be-swayed-by-tech-oligarchs-social-media-ban-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAZ7I34S65KCJJY5EDRZCLP23Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：卖出催生卖出]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3NB2DEXIFNAXAFFGOR3ZD6XKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:40:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[水泥制造商Cemex季度盈利因削减成本和提高价格而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥水泥制造商Cemex周四报告称，受成本削减措施和产品价格上涨推动，其第四季度核心利润增长16%，但业绩仍低于分析师预期。【原文：Mexican cement maker Cemex reported on Thursday a 16% climb in fourth-quarter core earnings, supported by cost-cutting measures and higher product prices, though results fell short of analysts' estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/cement-maker-cemexs-quarter-earnings-rise-cost-cuts-higher-prices-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXBD55YO5NIYRNKRA3ENFGZEF4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴里克将推进北美黄金资产IPO，任命希尔为首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴里克黄金公司周四宣布，将推进其北美黄金资产首次公开募股的筹备工作，并任命临时负责人马克·希尔为公司首席执行官兼总裁。【原文：Barrick Mining said on Thursday it would move forward with preparations for an initial public offering of its North American gold assets and named interim head Mark Hill as its chief executive and president.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/barrick-mining-names-mark-hill-ceo-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLOQSDJ4QRMPFMZRW5VNRYRFJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大型银行在政策之争加剧之际，正加强在华盛顿的游说力量。]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对披露数据和行业游说者的分析显示，去年美国大型银行的游说支出激增12%，创十余年来最大增幅。随着特朗普政府执政期间华盛顿重大政策动荡加剧，这些银行正加紧努力应对政策变化。【原文：Big U.S. banks' lobbying spend jumped 12% last year, the most in more than a decade, as they intensified efforts to navigate major policy flux in Washington under President Donald Trump's administration, according to a Reuters analysis of disclosure data and industry lobbyists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/big-us-banks-boost-washington-lobbying-muscle-policy-fights-heat-up-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQQTD6KJTNIYPCNBANUB3TQLWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR将以14亿美元收购Arctos]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司KKR周四宣布，将以14亿美元收购Arctos。【原文：Investment firm KKR said on Thursday that it would buy Arctos in a deal valued at $1.4 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/kkr-buy-arctos-14-billion-deal-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOPP24UESZKMBJ7YFKCMY7ESRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛上调全年盈利预期，因中国市场销售改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[化妆品制造商雅诗兰黛周四上调了年度利润预期，押注中国市场销售改善及首席执行官斯蒂芬·德拉法维里实施的转型计划将带来收益。【原文：Cosmetics maker Estee Lauder raised its annual profit forecast on Thursday, betting on improving China sales and benefits from CEO Stephane de La Faverie's turnaround plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/estee-lauder-raises-annual-sales-forecast-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFGFKBNT4NMTLMYSERRBXB75XI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>