<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 04:06:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 04:06:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[得益于外国投资回报，日本 2024 年经常账户盈余创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财政部周一公布的数据显示，日本去年的经常账户盈余跃升至创纪录水平，原因是日元走软提高了外国投资回报，从而帮助抵消了贸易逆差。【原文：Japan's current account surplus jumped to a record last year, data from the finance ministry showed on Monday, as a weaker yen boosted returns on foreign investments that helped to comfortably offset a trade deficit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-runs-record-current-account-surplus-2024-foreign-investment-returns-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KC5VZUXTRJNGPDC3WCE3WIUF7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:43:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾希望购买阿拉斯加天然气，以抵御美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾经济部周一表示，台湾对阿拉斯加的天然气 "相当感兴趣"，并将继续评估购买的可行性，因为台湾政府希望缩小与美国的贸易顺差并避免关税。【原文：Taiwan is "quite interested" in natural gas from Alaska and will continue to assess the feasibility of purchases, the economy ministry said on Monday, as the government looks to narrow the trade surplus with the United States and head off tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/taiwan-looks-buy-alaskan-natural-gas-seeks-head-off-us-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URZHI65EABKXBETTILVEZI3MR4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁特朗普称美国低等分币的时机已到]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周日在其社交媒体 "真相"（Truth）账户上发帖称，美国财政部已下令停止生产被称为 "便士 "的一美分硬币。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent has been ordered to cease production of the one-cent coin known as the penny, President Donald Trump said in a posting on his Truth Social media account on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/billionaire-trump-says-times-up-lowly-us-penny-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6EQK5WANJKB5JKCFWPYOB7C4A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚全球锂业公司寻求政府帮助，指控中国企图控制该公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚全球锂资源公司（Global Lithium Resources）正在向政府施压，要求在本周召开股东大会之前，制止中国投资者对其基础资产的收购企图。【原文：Australia's Global Lithium Resources is pressing the government to halt what it calls a takeover attempt by Chinese investors of its cornerstone asset ahead of a shareholder meeting this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australias-global-lithium-seeks-government-help-alleging-chinese-control-attempt-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRCMYK4OQNOTJM4OGTGA7UBPNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 02:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场对特朗普征收钢铝进口关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，他将在现有金属关税的基础上，对所有进口到美国的钢铁和铝征收25%的新关税。他还表示将在周二或周三宣布对等关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday he will introduce new 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminum imports into the U.S., on top of existing metals duties. He also said he will announce reciprocal tariffs on Tuesday or Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/markets-react-trumps-tariffs-steel-aluminium-imports-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIAIKEHXFNN6HHGYOWRJEPKAXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 02:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[控股股东结构可能发生变化，东风汽车股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商东风汽车表示，在重组过程中，公司控股股东结构可能会发生变化，随后东风汽车股价最高飙升 85.8%。【原文：Shares of Dongfeng Motor soared as much as 85.8% after the Chinese automaker flagged a possible change in the company's controlling shareholder structure amid a restructuring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shares-dongfeng-motor-jump-possible-change-controlling-shareholder-structure-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWGQK7C37ROMLP2R3MFJGX5VSU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:53:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因特朗普关税威胁而上涨，欧元接近两年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将对所有进口钢铁和铝征收25%的新关税后，美元周一走强，给欧元以及以大宗商品为主的澳元和新西兰元带来压力。【原文：The dollar firmed on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he was set to impose new 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminium imports, putting pressure on the euro and the commodity-focused Australian and New Zealand dollars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-gains-trump-tariff-threats-euro-near-2-year-low-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSYYRJRWFNP3TBMAOSNMWU6YVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:50:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚称其钢铁和铝出口为美国创造就业机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚贸易部长表示，澳大利亚对美国的钢铁和铝出口创造了 "高薪的美国工作"，并且是共同国防利益的关键。【原文：Australia's trade minister said its steel and aluminium exports to the U.S. create "good paying American jobs" and are key to shared defence interests, as Canberra presses Washington for an exemption to President Donald Trump's planned tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australia-says-its-steel-aluminium-exports-create-american-jobs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6377QCMSYRIHRFXOVJNNIW3HCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:49:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者权衡美国新关税措施，石油走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周一走高，尽管投资者正在权衡美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的最新关税威胁，这次是对所有进口钢铁和铝征收关税，这可能会抑制全球经济增长和能源需求。【原文：Oil prices ticked higher on Monday even as investors weighed U.S. President Donald Trump's latest tariff threat, this time on all steel and aluminium imports, which could dampen global economic growth and energy demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-ticks-higher-investors-weigh-new-us-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PN3J2N66VMQZDJCGK7TZ3AHDA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:41:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税有望促进澳大利亚博思格钢铁公司美国业务增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将宣布对所有进口钢铁和铝征收 25% 的关税后，博思格钢铁公司的股价在周一创下了两个月来的新高，这可能有利于这家澳大利亚钢铁制造商在美国的业务。【原文：Shares of BlueScope Steel hit a two-month high on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he will announce 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminum imports, which could benefit the Australian steelmaker's U.S operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australias-bluescope-steel-rises-hopes-trump-tariffs-boosting-its-us-ops-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MKBBQ23DBKM3ANXYCJE3NQIXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国出口中心义乌，贸易商对特朗普的关税避之唯恐不及]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日，中国出口制造业中心义乌的贸易商们对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国征收关税和采取的举措不以为然，一些贸易商表示，他们已做好准备来缓解这一打击。【原文：Traders in China's export manufacturing hub of Yiwu shrugged off U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs and moves against China on Sunday, with some saying they made preparations to soften the blow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-export-hub-yiwu-traders-shrug-off-trumps-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTGKBJJSTZKZ5IRDJTRW2OUNBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:09:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普谈关税，韩国钢铁企业股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将征收新关税后，韩国钢铁制造商的股票周一下跌。【原文：Shares of South Korean steelmakers dropped on Monday, after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would introduce new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/shares-south-korean-steelmakers-drop-trump-talks-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWR47WKRJFPHZORZ7SDRYR6J2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[T-Mobile 与 Starlink 开始大规模卫星连接测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[T-Mobile周日表示，该公司已开始大规模测试由SpaceX的Starlink提供的卫星对手机服务，这家美国无线运营商的目标是消除移动死角，并将连接扩展到偏远地区。【原文：T-Mobile said on Sunday it has started wide-scale testing of its satellite-to-cell service, powered by SpaceX's Starlink, as the U.S. wireless carrier aims to eliminate mobile dead zones and extend connectivity to remote areas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/t-mobile-starlink-start-wide-scale-testing-satellite-based-connectivity-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MMZJGJRTFMPBAGMKJBLW7GUBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国大陆蚕食份额，台湾传统芯片业思考未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[2015 年，台湾力晶科技公司与中国东部城市合肥达成协议，建立新的芯片代工厂，希望此举有助于更好地进入前景广阔的中国市场。【原文：When Taiwan's Powerchip Technology entered a deal with the eastern Chinese city of Hefei in 2015 to set up a new chip foundry, it hoped the move would help provide better access the promising Chinese market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-legacy-chip-industry-contemplates-future-china-eats-into-share-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKA3IG3YUZO7JGVGN2OPFXOO3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁拒绝就特朗普反对持有美国钢铁多数股权的声明发表评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新日铁公司周一拒绝就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于任何人不得拥有美国钢铁公司多数股权的声明发表评论。【原文：Japan's Nippon Steel on Monday declined to comment on U.S. President Donald Trump's statement that no one can have a majority stake in U.S. Steel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steel-declines-comment-trump-statement-opposing-majority-stake-us-steel-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5QQ7MTETVMSTOWXCTWCD3IXWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下滑，美元因关税威胁而攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）再次警告即将对包括钢铁和铝在内的产品征收关税，这一通胀举措可能会限制降息的空间，随后华尔街股票期货下跌，美元广泛上涨。【原文：Wall Street share futures fell and the dollar rose broadly on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump repeated warnings of imminent tariffs including on steel and aluminium, an inflationary move that could limit the scope for rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7KIW2BOEVKMDH3QBWAHSKGEKE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡星展银行第四季度净利润同比增长 10%，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡最大的银行星展集团周一向证券交易所提交的文件显示，由于商业账目和市场交易双双增长，该集团第四季度的净利润比去年同期增长了10%。【原文：DBS Group , Singapore's biggest bank, posted a 10% rise in net profit in the fourth quarter from a year earlier on the back of growth in both commercial book and markets trading, according to stock exchange filing on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/singapore-bank-dbs-fourth-quarter-net-profit-rises-10-year-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZMHTH7EABOOZF3AFK5UX7A2PE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 22:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国的债务可能比想象的要少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，美国的债务可能比想象的要少，并称这可能是因为与债务支付有关的欺诈行为。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Sunday said the United States may carry less debt than thought and said it could be because of fraud related to debt payments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-says-us-might-have-less-debt-than-thought-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDUM6T5FG5JSDLSODE57GUO45U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 22:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价驾驭美国利率和全球关税紧张局势]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphics-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZX4UJAKTBM3VCFAJUYKOFCEOY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 21:50:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将于周一宣布征收 25% 的钢铝关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，他将于周一宣布对所有进口到美国的钢铁和铝征收25%的关税，这是他贸易政策改革的又一次重大升级。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday that he will announce on Monday 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminum imports into the U.S., another major escalation in his trade policy overhaul.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-says-he-will-announce-25-steel-aluminum-tariffs-monday-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNB4Q7CNGNP4HNIXRDJZS3CL4E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 21:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马克龙表示私营部门将向法国人工智能领域投资 1,090 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙说，在周一开幕的巴黎人工智能峰会上，法国将宣布私营部门在人工智能领域的投资总额约为1090亿欧元（合1125亿美元）。【原文：France will announce private sector investments totalling some 109 billion euros ($112.5 billion) in its artificial intelligence sector during the Paris AI summit which opens on Monday, President Emmanuel Macron said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/france-invest-109-billion-euros-ai-macron-announces-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUFYA6PIBVOFJGVABWDG43Y5FE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 20:18:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球停电后，索尼将为 PlayStation Plus 用户提供五天延期服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼公司周日表示，在上周五和周六PlayStation Network（PSN）全球中断约18小时后，所有PlayStation Plus会员将自动获得额外五天的服务。【原文：Sony said on Sunday that all PlayStation Plus members would automatically receive an additional five days of service, after a global outage disrupted the PlayStation Network (PSN) for about 18 hours on Friday and Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sony-offer-playstation-plus-users-five-day-extension-after-global-outage-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPUWOC6KQNIALCX64DID7BR3OU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 13:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 DeepSeek 的热潮中，中国公司详细介绍了人工智能的使用情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商长城汽车和中国领先的电信供应商正在将 DeepSeek 发布的人工智能模型整合到他们的产品中，这些中国公司都希望利用这家初创公司的突破和关注度。【原文：Chinese automaker Great Wall Motor and China's leading telecoms providers are integrating the AI model released by DeepSeek into their offerings, the latest Chinese companies looking to capitalize on the start-up's breakthrough and attention.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amid-deepseek-frenzy-chinese-companies-detail-use-ai-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSMM6AYWDJKQHA73VSZBBRY5WQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 11:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[心境、怀旧和人工智能：超级碗广告商挖掘美国的过去和未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年的比赛中，广告商们又回到了安全、怀旧的赛场--大量的克莱德驯鹿，却看不到一个有影响力的变性人，这体现了广告商们的趋势：倚重名人、幽默和美国人的真性情。【原文：The return to the safe, nostalgic ground of Clydesdales in abundance and nary a transgender influencer in sight embodies the trend for advertisers at this year's game: lean on celebrities, humor and American true grit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/heartland-nostalgia-ai-super-bowl-advertisers-mine-americas-past-future-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WLS42TDEVPLRKTIUBKWFG4LPQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 11:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[热潮过后，中国将削减清洁电力补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最高经济规划机构周日表示，在太阳能和风能发电装机蓬勃发展之后，中国正在采取措施减少对可再生能源项目的补贴。【原文：China's top economic planning agency said on Sunday it was taking steps to scale back subsidies for renewable energy projects after a boom in solar and wind power installations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/china-roll-back-clean-power-subsidies-after-boom-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWKS3H2QSZLW7PNXMVKMHSHEKM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 07:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焕然一新的中东开始吸引投资者......然后特朗普来了]]></title><description><![CDATA[中东地区的历史性动荡开始吸引国际投资者的目光，在经历了如此多的动荡之后，他们对相对和平和经济复苏的前景充满热情。【原文：A historic shake-up of the Middle East is starting to draw international investors, warming to the prospects of relative peace and economic recovery after so much turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/new-look-middle-east-had-started-draw-investors-then-came-trump-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5JLASLOXVJCNLESD3MB4MCVEI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 06:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰将放宽签证规定吸引外国投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰中右翼政府周日表示，为刺激经济增长，新西兰将放宽签证规定以吸引更多外国投资者。【原文：New Zealand will relax visa rules to attract more foreign investors, in efforts to stimulate economic growth, its centre-right government said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/new-zealand-loosen-visa-rules-lure-foreign-investors-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDQ4EIHH6RLRJAH7KJNPQILEDY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 03:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 1 月份消费通胀加快，生产通缩持续]]></title><description><![CDATA[1 月份，中国居民消费价格指数创下 5 个月来最快增速，而生产者价格通缩仍在持续，因为在政府推出各种激励措施后，假日消费令人鼓舞。【原文：China's consumer price index grew at the fastest pace in five months in January, while producer price deflation persisted, as holiday spending looked encouraging in the wake of various government incentives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-consumer-inflation-quickens-january-producer-deflation-persists-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFG36UEIYROUTID357UPFXL3RY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 01:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克称无意收购 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）表示，他对收购 TikTok 没有兴趣。TikTok 是一款广受欢迎的短视频应用程序，美国出于国家安全考虑一直试图禁止其中国所有者字节跳动（ByteDance）使用该应用程序。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk said that he was not interested in purchasing TikTok, the popular short-video app that the United States has been trying to ban over national security concerns with its Chinese owner ByteDance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/billionaire-musk-says-not-interested-acquiring-tiktok-2025-02-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4KOX7CDCJN5HOK3WUDIAXAHLM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，激进分子埃利奥特持有英国石油公司大量股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周六援引消息人士的话报道，激进投资者埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）已持有石油巨头英国石油公司（BP）的大量股份。【原文：Activist investor Elliott Investment Management has built a significant stake in oil major BP, Bloomberg News reported on Saturday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/activist-elliott-builds-significant-stake-bp-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-02-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLUME33ZFNIEVEOZP27XJREUII</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:17:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>