<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 17:04:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 17:04:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国总统贝森特称赞与中国的贸易谈判取得 "实质性进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周日表示，他的团队与中国副总理何立峰的团队在日内瓦就化解世界两大经济体之间的贸易战举行的会谈取得了 "实质性进展"。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Sunday that there had been "substantial progress" in talks between his team and that of Chinese Vice Premier He Lifeng in Geneva on defusing a trade war between the world's two largest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-bessent-hails-substantial-progress-trade-talks-with-china-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MORKHTA7IFOF3LRS2JZPNRAEVI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 16:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长卢特尼克称中美谈判旨在缓和贸易紧张局势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周日表示，目前正在日内瓦举行的与中国的双边会谈旨在 "缓和 "两个超级大国之间的紧张局势，他预测未来几个月将达成多项贸易协议，但没有点名具体国家。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick on Sunday said bilateral talks with China now underway in Geneva are intended to "de-escalate" tensions between the two superpowers, as he predicted multiple trade deals over the next few months without naming specific countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-says-china-talks-aimed-lowering-trade-tensions-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7EDOZA36NOM7IADKANFINDI6E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：OpenAI 与微软谈判，以获得新资金并在未来上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周日报道，OpenAI 和微软正在重写双方价值数十亿美元的合作条款，这是一场高风险谈判，目的是让这家 ChatGPT 制造商能够在未来进行首次公开募股，同时保护这家软件巨头对尖端人工智能模型的使用权。【原文：OpenAI and Microsoft are rewriting the terms of their multibillion-dollar partnership in a high-stakes negotiation designed to allow the ChatGPT maker to launch a future IPO, while protecting the software giant's access to cutting-edge AI models, the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-negotiates-with-microsoft-unlock-new-funding-future-ipo-ft-reports-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53I7IOJSB5KUBHT6UWPF7C7F5A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 12:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[化解贸易争端的中美会谈在日内瓦重启]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，中美两国高级官员周日在日内瓦再次会晤，重启周末会谈，旨在为有可能严重损害全球经济的贸易战降温。【原文：Senior U.S. and Chinese officials met again on Sunday in Geneva, two sources familiar with the situation told Reuters, to resume weekend talks aimed at cooling the trade war that threatens to seriously damage the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-talks-defuse-trade-row-resume-geneva-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVVBAWO2LRMKVI4WXNHOPXPUHA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 09:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂再次呼吁取消与美国的所有关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂周日重申，他将致力于在与美国的贸易谈判中取消所有关税。【原文：Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba reiterated on Sunday that he will aim for the elimination of all tariffs in trade negotiations with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japan-pm-ishiba-reiterates-call-eliminate-all-tariffs-with-us-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AAWYTEMKJK5ND2ZOMSQV463QQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 4 月汽车销量增长 14.8]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于政府补贴的汽车以旧换新减轻了美国关税对消费者情绪的影响，中国 4 月份的汽车销量同比增长 14.8%。【原文：China's car sales rose 14.8% in April from a year earlier, as government-subsidised auto trade-ins mitigate the impact of U.S. tariffs on consumer sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-car-sales-rise-148-april-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCNEWFUT7BLRHFDPYQSQP6L5OI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 02:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谨慎的投资者希望中美谈判为高风险的贸易战降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者希望本周末举行的中美贸易谈判将为世界两大经济体之间的贸易战降温，并消除笼罩在金融市场上的一些不确定性，尽管几乎没有人预计谈判会取得重大突破。【原文：Investors are hopeful that U.S.-China trade talks this weekend will cool a trade war between the world's two largest economies and dispel some of the uncertainty clouding financial markets, though few expect a major breakthrough just yet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/wary-investors-hope-us-china-talks-cool-high-stakes-trade-war-2025-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7OVQBR4BRKF5DDROC3EFHVJNU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 18:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保健公司渴望避免 WeightWatchers 的命运，拥抱减肥药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，WeightWatchers 宣布破产，原因是新的大片药物的使用量大幅增加。【原文：Health and wellness companies are embracing weight-loss drugs and building offerings around them in an effort to avoid the fate of WeightWatchers, which declared bankruptcy this week, citing vastly increased use of the new blockbuster medicines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/wellness-companies-eager-avoid-weightwatchers-fate-embrace-weight-loss-drugs-2025-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSTRMSK7ABPMNKZ3B4LXPT5HJ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 10:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易谈判在日内瓦开始]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国有通讯社新华社报道，中国国务院副总理何立峰周六早些时候在日内瓦与美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特举行了会谈。【原文：China's vice premier He Lipeng held talks with U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent early on Saturday in Geneva, China's state-owned news agency Xinhua reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-trade-talks-begin-geneva-2025-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRTNIKFD6JK5NECQRLY3X262DA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 09:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 4 月份居民消费价格连续第三个月下降，PPI 再次下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于决策者正在努力应对与美国的贸易战对经济的影响，中国 4 月份的居民消费价格连续第三个月下降，而工厂出厂价格则创下了六个月来的最大降幅。【原文：China's consumer prices fell for the third consecutive month in April, while factory-gate prices recorded their steepest drop in six months, as policymakers grapple with the economic impact of a trade war with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-consumer-prices-fall-third-straight-month-april-2025-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LPD2AHESFJ35CPWZAYEGDMSPU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将就纽瓦克临时航班削减事宜与航空公司会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周五晚些时候表示，计划于周三与各大航空公司会面，商讨新泽西纽瓦克自由国际机场可能临时削减航班的事宜，以应对近期发生的重大航班中断事件。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said late on Friday it plans to meet with major airlines on Wednesday about potential temporary cuts in flights at New Jersey's Newark Liberty International Airport to address recent major disruptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-faa-meet-with-airlines-about-temporary-newark-flight-cuts-2025-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPPD2NCZK5OMZFO3C35MHZLO4U</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 01:31:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨莱姆：在关税影响确定之前不应承诺降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆周五表示，在明确特朗普政府的关税政策会导致持续性通胀还是不太严重的一次性价格调整之前，美联储不应承诺进一步降息。【原文：The Fed should not commit to further interest rate cuts until it is clear whether the Trump administration's tariff policies lead to persistent inflation or a less serious, one-time adjustment in prices, St. Louis Fed President Alberto Musalem said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-musalem-should-not-commit-rate-cuts-until-tariff-impact-becomes-certain-2025-05-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN5IEKOIBFMMRPK7BECNWNMNHY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[施纳贝尔：欧洲央行应保持稳健，将利率维持在当前水平附近]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行（ECB）董事会成员伊莎贝尔-施纳贝尔（Isabel Schnabel）周五表示，欧洲央行应停止削减借贷成本，因为全球经济动荡加剧了物价压力，通胀率有可能在中期内超过该行2%的目标。【原文：The European Central Bank should stop cutting borrowing costs as turmoil in the global economy is fuelling price pressures and inflation was at risk of exceeding the bank's 2% target in the medium term, ECB board member Isabel Schnabel said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ecb-should-keep-steady-hand-hold-rates-close-current-levels-schnabel-says-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K73OQ3YU4BI23GQLUZENM444F4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 23:53:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储库克警告说，关税可能会降低生产力，助长通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）正在实施的贸易政策可能会抑制美国的生产率，在经济效率较低的情况下，可能需要提高利率来抑制通胀。【原文：President Donald Trump's unfolding trade policy may curb U.S. productivity and possibly require higher interest rates to contain inflation in a less efficient economy, Federal Reserve governor Lisa Cook said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-cook-warns-tariffs-could-lower-productivity-feed-inflation-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TN7OLZNSLRIXXCTVNBM66FBSHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 23:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易战停火而非和平谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美两国将于本周六开始其首次重要的贸易战二次会议，以摆脱被分析人士描述为两国经济双输的局面，但双方都不太清楚赢的结果是什么。【原文：China and the United States start their first major Trade War Two meeting on Saturday to pull back from what analysts describe as a lose-lose situation for their economies, without much clarity on what a win would look like for either side.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-talk-trade-war-ceasefire-not-peace-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSI5IEE5VZKRJIKONNXMCYGPDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 23:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官暂时阻止美国原住民反对的力拓、必和必拓铜矿换地计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一名美国联邦法官暂时阻止了特朗普政府将亚利桑那州的土地转让给力拓集团和必和必拓公司（BHP），以建造一座遭到美国原住民反对的大型铜矿。【原文：A U.S. federal judge on Friday temporarily blocked the Trump administration from transferring Arizona land to Rio Tinto and BHP to build a major copper mine that is opposed by Native Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-temporarily-blocks-land-exchange-rio-tinto-bhp-copper-mine-opposed-by-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BMHZDQ4YVOJJIU6NIKLQI7PJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:54:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州称就数据隐私问题与谷歌达成 13.8 亿美元和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州总检察长肯-帕克斯顿（Ken Paxton）在周五的一份声明中说，他的办公室已就数据隐私权问题与谷歌原则上达成了 13.75 亿美元的和解协议。【原文：Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton has reached a $1.375 billion settlement in principle with Google over data privacy rights, his office said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/texas-says-it-secures-138-billion-settlement-with-google-over-data-privacy-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4QHSYJIWFONTDBU6DXFF7A5KQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:49:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会暂停执行 "点击取消 "规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五表示，该机构将推迟实施一项定于下周生效的规定，该规定要求企业在取消订阅和会员资格时必须像注册一样方便，以便给企业更多的时间来遵守这一规定。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is delaying implementation of a rule set to take effect next week that would require businesses to make it as easy to cancel subscriptions and memberships as it is to sign up, to give companies more time to comply, the agency said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ftc-hits-pause-click-cancel-rule-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFZO3FHBHNLD7GDAAQ5APVB4LM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CSX 与 BLET 达成为期 5 年的临时协议，涵盖 3,400 名工人]]></title><description><![CDATA[铁路运营商 CSX 周五表示，它已与机车工程师和列车员兄弟会 (BLET) 签署了一份为期五年的新合同临时协议。【原文：Railroad operator CSX said on Friday it has signed a tentative agreement for a new five-year contract with the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Trainmen (BLET).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/csx-reaches-tentative-5-year-deal-with-blet-covering-3400-workers-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKTSY6BP7ZMXXAQ2GOKCPXOWJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普传媒寻求并购活动以实现多元化发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的社交媒体公司特朗普媒体与科技集团（Trump Media & Technology Group）周五表示，该公司正计划寻求潜在的兼并与收购，因为它希望多元化发展，进入金融服务等领域。【原文：Trump Media & Technology Group is planning to pursue potential mergers and acquisitions, U.S. President Donald Trump's social media firm said on Friday, as it looks to diversify into sectors such as financial services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-media-seeking-ma-activity-diversification-bid-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HDLXHZWUFLL7H36YYKSCKJ6WE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称美国普拉特发动机罢工者要求就业承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[约 3000 名美国普惠公司工人为在康涅狄格州保留喷气发动机工作而举行了长达近一周的罢工，这是航空航天供应链中最新的不确定因素，该供应链本已在努力满足全球对新客机的需求。【原文：A nearly week-long strike by around 3,000 U.S. Pratt & Whitney workers to keep jet engine work in Connecticut is the latest source of uncertainty in an aerospace supply chain already struggling to meet global demand for new airliners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-pratt-engine-strikers-press-jobs-commitment-union-says-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJXJE6WALNPEJOUJ5YOBKRTSB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[领导裁员的美国联邦人力资源机构取消 Workday 独家采购合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦人力资源机构是亿万富翁特朗普顾问埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）削减联邦雇员的核心机构，该机构周五取消了与 Workday 公司的合同。【原文：The U.S. federal human resources agency at the heart of billionaire Trump adviser Elon Musk's efforts to slash the federal workforce on Friday canceled a contract it had awarded to Workday .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-federal-hr-agency-leading-doge-job-cuts-cancels-sole-source-workday-award-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YQHMJUJMRPIHAHBGDM3QUJXBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数字医疗公司 Omada 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[虚拟慢性病护理提供商 Omada Health 已申请在美国上市，这是今年预计将有的一连串医疗保健公司上市中的最新一家。【原文：Virtual chronic care provider Omada Health has filed to go public in the United States, the latest in a string of healthcare listings expected this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/digital-health-company-omada-files-us-ipo-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5APZPWSXJJTBNYW6PUYPEWQY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:51:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美联储鲍曼从高盛、戴维斯-波尔克和 BPI 挑选员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美国联邦储备局局长米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）已从银行界挑选了三名工作人员。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman has picked three staffers from the banking world, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bowman-picks-staff-goldman-davis-polk-bpi-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZU33R4UMQRPD7AL4WWI4DBJVZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道贸易商称中国购买加拿大和澳大利亚小麦，因高温影响作物生长]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商说，最近几周，中国买家从澳大利亚和加拿大购买了 40 万至 50 万吨小麦，因为高温有可能损害中国农业中心地带的作物。【原文：Chinese buyers bought between 400,000 and 500,000 metric tons of wheat from Australia and Canada in recent weeks, traders said, as heat threatens to damage crops in China’s agricultural heartlands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-buys-canadian-australian-wheat-heat-hits-crop-traders-say-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVTVTKXYI5KQJCOMNIKA4TADXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长敦促国会在七月中旬前提高债务限额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五敦促国会在七月中旬之前提高联邦政府的债务限额，以避免出现将颠覆全球市场的违约事件。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Friday urged Congress to raise the federal government's debt limit by mid-July to avoid a default that would upend global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-treasury-secretary-urges-congress-raise-debt-limit-by-mid-july-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ME2FIZQMBIVDLEWMVB2T3C7UU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:32:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示，即使达成贸易协议，美国仍将维持 10%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五表示，即使在达成贸易协议后，美国仍将维持对进口商品征收 10%关税的基准，并补充说，如果有国家提供重要的贸易条件，则可能会有豁免。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday that the U.S. will maintain a baseline 10% tariff on imports even after trade deals are struck, adding there could be exemptions when countries offer significant trade terms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-us-will-maintain-10-tariffs-even-after-trade-deals-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWXWH74OERIIXJR7GRBIJ4DARE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对进口商用喷气机和发动机展开国家安全调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五表示，已对商用飞机、喷气发动机和零部件的进口展开国家安全调查。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Friday it has opened a national security investigation into the import of commercial aircraft, jet engines and parts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-opens-national-security-probe-into-imported-commercial-jets-engines-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QYYZFFZPNORJGCOLAMYNQBERY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:06:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，贝恩资本将以 100 亿美元的估值收购 PCI 制药公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，贝恩资本正在洽谈以 100 亿美元的估值收购合同药品制造商 PCI Pharma Services。【原文：Bain Capital is in talks to buy contract drug manufacturer PCI Pharma Services at a valuation of $10 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bain-capital-buy-pci-pharma-10-billion-valuation-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YMS3GH3ZNPO5K4QVJGIBWSWUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储主席哈马克希望在确定利率前获得明确数据，6 月前数据不会太多]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联储主席贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周五表示，美联储需要更多的时间来观察经济对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税和其他政策的反应，然后才能找出正确的应对措施。【原文：The Federal Reserve needs more time to see how the economy responds to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff and other policies before figuring out the right response, Cleveland Federal Reserve President Beth Hammack said on Friday, noting that much of the administration's sweeping agenda remains unclear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-hammack-wants-clear-data-before-moving-rates-not-much-data-by-june-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y3HLG7B7ZKRZISDE7IKG4PYTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>