<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:10:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:10:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[道明银行从摩根大通、高盛等竞争对手处挖角银行家，以扩大其债务与股权资本市场团队。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，TD银行高管透露，该行已从北美多家顶级银行挖角六名资深银行家至纽约，以推动其债务与股权资本市场业务发展。【原文：TD Bank has recruited half a dozen senior bankers in New York from top North American banks to boost its debt and equity capital market businesses, senior executives told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/td-hires-bankers-rivals-including-jpmorgan-goldman-expand-debt-equity-capital-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGT2QUQKZZL4TE7AHQ7JOMLTWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的攻击目标——美联储的库克，是位身经百战的斗士，身上的伤痕便是明证。]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德·特朗普总统解雇美联储理事丽莎·库克的争议性决定，已成为其试图掌控美国央行及不断挑战总统权力边界行动的试金石。【原文：President Donald Trump's contested firing of Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook has become a test case in his ​bid to assert control over the U.S. central bank and his ongoing efforts to push the limits of presidential power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/targeted-by-trump-feds-cook-is-fighter-with-scars-prove-it-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YINDNCSPMFKE5JQA6DUB52SW2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院审议特朗普解雇美联储委员丽莎·库克的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院即将审理唐纳德·特朗普总统解雇美联储理事丽莎·库克的史无前例之举。此案将考验大法官们为维护央行独立性愿意走多远。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court is set to consider President Donald Trump's unprecedented attempt to fire Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook in a case that tests how far the justices may be willing to ​go to preserve the central bank's independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-considers-trumps-bid-fire-feds-lisa-cook-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COJ3D4KVJBLSTNTUVTLNGCCLZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称德意志银行首席执行官致电要求银行与分析师的格陵兰报告保持距离]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，德意志银行首席执行官致电告知，该行不再支持其分析师报告中关于欧洲投资者可能抛售美国资产的观点。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that Deutsche Bank's chief executive had called him to say the bank does not stand by one of its analyst reports suggesting European investors may dump U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/bessent-says-deutsche-bank-ceo-called-distance-bank-analysts-greenland-report-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZ2YYI3V4BLNXEDXUW5W7KHM3E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度塔塔通信季度利润因强劲需求激增；任命候任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度塔塔通信公司周三公布，受云服务和连接解决方案需求强劲推动，该公司实现三个季度以来的首次利润增长。【原文：India's Tata Communications reported its first profit rise in three quarters on Wednesday, on strong demand for its cloud services and connectivity solutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/indias-tata-communications-quarterly-profit-jumps-robust-demand-names-ceo-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZCMTHUTM5IPDPZPZ27LMJJK5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:14:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奈飞为收购华纳兄弟计划辩护，股价因业绩疲软下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA["YouTube已不再只是用户生成内容和猫咪视频的聚集地，"网飞首席执行官泰德·萨兰多斯周二表示。【原文："YouTube is not just user-generated content and cat videos anymore," Netflix CEO Ted Sarandos said on ​Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-shares-drop-tepid-results-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRFBADKONNJJBKE7BHJTATPA3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子能源首席执行官将出席特朗普与商界领袖的会议，董事长表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子能源公司监事会主席乔·凯泽表示，该公司首席执行官克里斯蒂安·布鲁赫将出席定于周三晚些时候在瑞士达沃斯举行的企业领袖与美国总统唐纳德·特朗普的会晤。【原文：Siemens Energy CEO Christian Bruch will attend a meeting of business leaders with U.S. President Donald Trump scheduled later on Wednesday in Davos, Switzerland, the company's Supervisory Board Chairman Joe Kaeser said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/siemens-energy-ceo-attend-trump-meeting-with-business-leaders-chairman-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FP7TQIH46ZP7FKT52MWMTRWOWI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[无论华纳兄弟被谁收购，摩根大通和艾伦公司都将凭借1.8亿美元的并购佣金获利。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在奈飞与派拉蒙天空舞影业争夺华纳兄弟探索公司的竞购战中，摩根大通和艾伦公司正成为明显的赢家。【原文：Some clear winners are emerging in the bidding war between Netflix and Paramount Skydance for Warner Bros Discovery: JPMorgan and Allen & Company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/no-matter-who-buys-warner-bros-jpmorgan-allen-co-win-with-180-million-ma-fees-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTO3EOFFVJPQNBJKSWKUFLV5L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优必选与空客达成协议，将扩大机器人在航空制造领域的应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国机器人企业优必选周三宣布，已与全球最大飞机制造商空客签署协议，为其航空制造领域提供机器人设备。【原文：Chinese robotics firm UBTech said on Wednesday it had signed a deal with the world's largest planemaker, Airbus , to supply robots for use in aviation manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/ubtech-agrees-airbus-deal-expand-robot-use-aviation-manufacturing-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4GB6ANC4BIFFJCRMA2KNCCZ5E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:55:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉预计日本将把赤字控制在可控范围内，尽管实施了减税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉评级的日本主权分析师周三向路透社表示，该机构预计日本政府在下月众议院选举后将继续将财政赤字控制在可控范围内，因东京方面正面临债券市场对其减税政策的压力。【原文：Fitch Ratings expects Japan's government to continue to keep deficits within manageable levels after a lower house election next month as Tokyo faces pressure from the bond market over tax cuts, its sovereign analyst told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fitch-expects-japan-keep-deficits-within-manageable-levels-despite-tax-cut-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KLYOTZ27JPKHGUGWBSYB6PV4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：Meta新成立的人工智能团队本月已向内部交付首批关键模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms公司首席技术官周三表示，该公司新成立的人工智能实验室本月已向内部交付了首批备受瞩目的人工智能模型。【原文：Meta Platforms' new artificial intelligence lab has delivered its first high-profile AI models internally this month, the company's chief technology officer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/metas-new-ai-team-has-delivered-first-key-models-internally-this-month-cto-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVKV7DDC7FO4DPHUCLHISVFCXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟草案拟赋予欧洲电信运营商无限无线电频谱使用权]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周三公布的一项提案将为欧洲电信运营商提供重大助力，允许其无限期使用无线电频谱。但运营商要求科技巨头分担宽带部署成本的诉求未获采纳。【原文：Europe's telecoms operators will get a major boost under a European Commission proposal announced on Wednesday, allowing them to use radio spectrum for an unlimited duration, but their demand that Big Tech be required to help fund the cost of rolling out broadband went unheeded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/european-telcos-get-unlimited-radio-spectrum-under-eu-draft-law-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGW4HFRNZVKCDD2OBBFK7Y62AI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长贝森特对国债抛售潮不感到担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周三表示，他不担心因特朗普政府威胁对反对美国收购格陵兰岛的欧洲盟友加征关税而引发的美国国债抛售潮。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday he ​was not concerned about any sell-off in U.S. Treasuries related to the ‌Trump administration's threats to impose tariffs on European allies opposing U.S. efforts to acquire Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/us-treasury-secretary-bessent-not-concerned-about-any-treasuries-sell-off-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5HDRHBY5BKZNARSEDYMJ5C6OI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI致力于推动人工智能在全球日常生活中的广泛应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI正扩大其努力，旨在说服全球各国政府建设更多数据中心，并鼓励在教育、医疗和防灾等领域更广泛地应用人工智能。【原文：OpenAI is expanding its efforts to convince global governments to build more data centers and encourage greater usage of artificial intelligence in areas such as education, health and disaster preparedness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/openai-seeks-increase-global-ai-use-everyday-life-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCS6XVGODBLUTFBBLVGAK2T2O4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解读：特朗普对六个欧盟国家加征关税可能给美国海关带来麻烦]]></title><description><![CDATA[若美国总统特朗普兑现其对六个欧盟国家（而非整个欧盟）加征关税的威胁，鉴于欧盟成员国间货物流通的便利性，美国海关当局将面临真正的挑战。【原文：U.S. customs authorities will face a real challenge if President Donald Trump goes through with his threat to place tariffs on six EU countries - rather than the whole European Union - given the ease of movement of goods between EU members.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-six-eu-nations-could-create-us-customs-headache-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAGVHX7FWBMEZGAW43MFFVH73Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，福特因发动机缸体加热器存在起火风险召回逾11.9万辆美国本土车辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周三表示，福特汽车公司正在美国召回119,075辆汽车，原因是发动机缸体加热器可能出现裂纹并泄漏冷却液，当加热器插电时可能导致短路，从而增加起火风险。【原文：Ford Motor is recalling 119,075 vehicles in the U.S. as the engine block heater may crack and leak coolant, potentially causing a short circuit and increasing the risk of a fire when the heater is plugged in, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recalls-over-119000-vehicles-over-engine-block-heater-fire-risk-nhtsa-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2Q7I26R3FLSBMPBCDFMCMSXNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:20:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奈飞股价在欧洲暴跌7%，此前公布第四季度财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管Netflix第四季度营收和盈利超出预期，但该公司周三在法兰克福上市的股票早盘仍出现下跌，原因是其仍在与华纳兄弟探索公司展开激烈的收购竞标战。【原文：Netflix , shares listed in Frankfurt fell in early trade on Wednesday despite beating expectations for fourth quarter revenue and earnings, as the company remains locked in a fierce bidding war for Warner Bros Discovery .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-shares-drop-7-europe-after-q4-results-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5G3KHXOPN5LFTNYYPMOPC5SMIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalWafers董事长表示，该公司正为德克萨斯州工厂的第二阶段扩建做准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾硅晶圆制造商华晶科技董事长徐丽珍周三向记者透露，该公司正筹备其位于美国得克萨斯州工厂的二期扩建计划，具体实施将取决于客户订单承诺。【原文：Taiwanese silicon wafer manufacturer GlobalWafers is preparing for the phase two expansion of its plant in the U.S. state of Texas, subject to customer commitments, Chairperson Doris Hsu told reporters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/globalwafers-is-preparing-phase-two-expansion-texas-plant-chairperson-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFCTDORMYBOO5IWJVN3NSZCUIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球液化天然气供应量将于2026年大幅增长，这将抑制价格上涨并刺激需求增长。]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师指出，全球液化天然气（LNG）产量今年将大幅攀升，这将缓解自2022年乌克兰战争以来出现的供应紧张局面，并抑制价格上涨。此举可能刺激包括中国和印度在内的主要进口国的需求。【原文：Global liquefied natural gas (LNG) output is set to jump this year, easing constraints seen since the 2022 Ukraine war and dampening prices, which could spur demand including from top importers China and India, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/global-lng-supply-set-jump-2026-limiting-prices-spurring-demand-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UETJ5TMLPJJ3JKK7M4XR3W2PWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国安托斯公司警告2025年营收将大幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国IT集团埃托斯周三表示，预计将报告年度收入大幅下滑，但符合其自身预期，因截至12月31日的季度中合同流失持续存在。【原文：French IT group Atos said on Wednesday it expected to report a sharp drop in annual revenue, but in line with its own guidance, as contract losses persisted through the quarter that ended on December 31.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frances-atos-flags-steep-revenue-decline-2025-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LHEDYPCAROX3CU5QWONJL3Y4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治与关税风险强势回归市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着唐纳德·特朗普总统开启其第二个任期的第二年，标志着他重掌大权的地缘政治与关税相关动荡再度浮现，撼动市场。那些习惯于资产价格迅速反弹的投资者担忧，此次冲击可能造成更持久的损害。【原文：As President Donald Trump kicks off the second year of his second term in office, the geopolitical- and tariff-related volatility that characterized his return to power has resurfaced to shake markets. Investors who ​have been conditioned to asset prices swiftly rebounding are worried that this time, there could be more lasting damage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/geopolitical-tariff-risk-back-with-bang-markets-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GPQ3LF4L5I43I7PTKUERBP5XI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本最大工会组织敦促政府稳定外汇市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大工会联合组织"总联"的负责人周三敦促政府将经济政策转向稳定汇率，称日元疲软正通过推高进口成本加速通胀。【原文：The chief of Japan's largest trade union umbrella group Rengo on Wednesday pressed the government to steer economic policy toward stabilising foreign exchange rates, saying that the weak yen is accelerating inflation through higher import costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/japans-top-labour-union-group-urges-government-stabilise-forex-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHHMA7VZ35NOTJ7GAPDNWRZVEE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 05:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早盘行情：市场仍寄望达沃斯论坛能缓和紧张局势]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲及全球市场今日展望——由邱思妤为您解读【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIFB2ZKRHFKCNNZQ524372KZYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 05:32:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[盖茨与OpenAI携手推动非洲国家人工智能医疗发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[比尔及梅琳达·盖茨基金会与OpenAI正建立一项5000万美元的合作关系，旨在帮助非洲国家利用人工智能改善其卫生系统。【原文：The Gates Foundation and OpenAI are setting up a $50 million partnership to help African countries use artificial intelligence to improve their health systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/gates-openai-team-up-ai-health-push-african-countries-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QVVIBXO74JNU3ALAPBDPKXGFNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 05:02:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《信息》报道，OpenAI将开始向广告商提供聊天机器人广告服务。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《The Information》周二报道，知情人士透露，OpenAI已开始向数十家广告商提供其新型聊天机器人广告服务。【原文：OpenAI has started offering its new chatbot ads to dozens of advertisers, The Information reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/openai-start-offering-chatbot-ads-advertisers-information-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQO3GLRR5RL6FL6QLGVCMMB2WQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅将向印度美妆科技中心投资3.83亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国化妆品巨头欧莱雅周三宣布，将在印度南部城市海得拉巴建立一个美容科技中心，初期投资额超过350亿卢比（约合3.834亿美元）。【原文：French cosmetics giant L'oreal said on Wednesday it will set up a beauty tech hub in the south Indian city of Hyderabad with an initial investment of over 35 billion rupees ($383.4 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/loreal-invest-383-million-indian-tech-hub-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVJOR62GPNM4XLTPBX366BH4X4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:36:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《信息》报道，OpenAI将向广告主展示聊天机器人广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《信息报》周二报道，知情人士透露，OpenAI计划于2月向数十家广告客户展示其聊天机器人广告。【原文：OpenAI plans to unveil its chatbot ads in February to dozens of its advertisers, The Information reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/openai-unveil-chatbot-ads-its-advertisers-information-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QP33LCH4PVNBLHXHTA6NH5PXFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲律宾将恢复Grok访问权限，此前该应用开发者承诺进行安全修复]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲律宾网络犯罪调查部门周三表示，在开发者承诺移除此前引发儿童安全担忧的图像处理工具后，该国将恢复对埃隆·马斯克旗下人工智能聊天机器人Grok的访问权限。【原文：The Philippines will restore access to Elon Musk's AI chatbot Grok following commitments from its developer to remove image-manipulation tools that previously raised child safety concerns, its cybercrime investigation unit said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/philippines-restore-access-grok-after-developer-commits-safety-fixes-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGXRTCNFRZJ3LGG2ILSI6E72RY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国李明博淡化美国拟征芯片关税影响，警告价格可能上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统李在明周三表示，若华盛顿对半导体进口提高关税，可能推高美国国内价格，他同时淡化了对拟议100%关税的担忧。【原文：South Korean President Lee Jae Myung said on Wednesday if Washington introduced higher U.S. tariffs on semiconductor imports, it would likely boost U.S. prices, playing down concerns about the proposed 100% duty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-koreas-lee-plays-down-proposed-us-chip-tariffs-warns-higher-prices-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3D2ZHUZGMRJLHD2VW5VRAA7TYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，英伟达首席执行官黄仁勋计划访问中国，以寻求重启市场。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻周二报道，英伟达首席执行官黄仁勋计划于1月下旬访问中国，旨在重启该公司人工智能芯片的关键市场。该报道援引知情人士消息称。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang plans to travel to China in late January as he seeks to reopen a critical market for the company's artificial intelligence chips, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-ceo-huang-plans-visit-china-he-seeks-reopen-market-bloomberg-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FGSBYLDKFBKBLIV57GJ5RRXCMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>