<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 16:37:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 16:37:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院命令间谍软件公司 NSO 停止针对 WhatsApp 的间谍活动，并降低了赔偿金额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法院已下令以色列 NSO 集团停止针对 Meta Platforms 公司的 WhatsApp 消息服务，这家间谍软件公司警告说，这一事态发展可能会使其破产。【原文：A U.S. court has ordered Israel's NSO Group to stop targeting Meta Platforms' WhatsApp messaging service, a development the spyware company warned could put it out of business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-court-orders-spyware-company-nso-stop-targeting-whatsapp-reduces-damages-2025-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKDOSSY7ARJKJEM5HQTDZIREMQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Kering 接近以 40 亿美元将美容部门出售给欧莱雅]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周六援引知情人士的话报道，法国奢侈品集团开云集团（Kering）正就以约 40 亿美元的价格将其美容部门出售给美容集团欧莱雅（L'Oreal）一事进行深入谈判。【原文：French luxury group Kering is in advanced talks to sell its beauty division to beauty group L’Oreal for about $4 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on Saturday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kering-nears-4-billion-sale-beauty-unit-loreal-wsj-reports-2025-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYP4B3DPT5IWPMX6OHUSHRMMEU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 13:48:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Variety 报道，派拉蒙 Skydance 将于 10 月 27 日开始的一周内在美国裁员 2000 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Variety 周六援引公司消息来源报道，派拉蒙天舞公司将于 10 月 27 日开始大规模裁员，裁掉约 2000 个美国工作岗位，作为新任首席执行官大卫-埃里森（David Ellison）20 亿美元成本削减计划的一部分。【原文：Paramount Skydance will begin mass layoffs the week of October 27, eliminating around 2,000 U.S. jobs as part of a $2 billion cost-cutting plan under new CEO David Ellison, Variety reported on Saturday, citing company sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-skydance-cut-2000-us-jobs-starting-week-october-27-variety-reports-2025-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6EFFW46VVPPZMEO7BGF57NXSE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与荷兰关系紧张，Nexperia 中国部门坚持独立自主]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nexperia 中国公司周六表示，该公司一直遵守中国法律，并有权独立运营，此前一天，荷兰表示已开始会谈，试图缓解出口管制方面的紧张关系。【原文：Nexperia’s China unit has respected Chinese laws and has the right to operate independently, it said on Saturday, a day after the Netherlands said talks had begun to try to ease tensions over export controls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nexperia-china-unit-asserts-its-independence-tensions-with-netherlands-run-high-2025-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDUK276KXVPI7KNNUJUJRZFHWE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:50:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球电影业摆脱特朗普再次发出的电影关税威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA["尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）再次威胁要对美国境外制作的电影征收关税，但全球电影业仍在继续发展。【原文："Star Wars: Starfighter" is filming in Britain, soundstages in Hungary are packed and post-production houses in Australia are humming, as the global film industry keeps rolling despite U.S. President Donald Trump's renewed threats to impose tariffs on movies made outside of the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/global-film-industry-shrugs-off-renewed-trump-movie-tariff-threat-2025-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHBLU4FTS5MQLDUBJYLBIQLCB4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子家族在股价上涨之际出售 12 亿美元股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子在一份监管文件中表示，三星电子董事长李在镕的母亲和两个姐妹计划出售这家韩国科技公司价值约 1.73 万亿韩元（约合 12.2 亿美元）的股份。【原文：The mother and two sisters of Samsung Electronics Chairman Jay Y. Lee plan to sell some 1.73 trillion won ($1.22 billion) worth of shares in the South Korean tech firm, the company said in a regulatory filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-electronics-family-sell-12-bln-stake-amid-share-rally-2025-10-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SK4FAHUE6JMUDK5HO7WG4G4KP4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 01:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲁比奥与利比里亚部长讨论促进美国参与利比里亚关键矿产部门的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院周五表示，美国国务卿马尔科-鲁比奥（Marco Rubio）在本周与利比里亚外交部长萨拉-贝索洛-尼安蒂（Sara Beysolow Nyanti）的会晤中讨论了美国扩大参与利比里亚关键矿产部门的途径。【原文：U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio discussed avenues for expanding U.S. participation in Liberia's critical minerals sector in a meeting this week with Liberian Foreign Minister Sara Beysolow Nyanti, the State Department said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/rubio-liberian-minister-discuss-boosting-us-participation-liberias-critical-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42CFVDJB7FLV7HWWSZFPCO7WUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 23:39:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称电动汽车供应链数据公司 Benchmark Mineral 裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[Benchmark Mineral Intelligence 是一家总部位于英国的能源转型矿物定价和数据研究公司，该公司的三位熟知内情的人士表示，最近几周该公司至少裁减了五分之一的员工。【原文：Benchmark Mineral Intelligence, a UK-based pricing and data research firm for energy transition minerals, has cut at least a fifth of its workforce in recent weeks, said three people familiar with the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ev-supply-chain-data-firm-benchmark-mineral-trims-workforce-sources-say-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IM4DD6VZXFPUVM5NYY4P6IYWEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 23:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普批准减免美国汽车生产关税，发布新的卡车关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五签署命令，批准大幅减免美国汽车和发动机生产的关税，并从11月1日起对进口中型和重型卡车及零部件征收25%的新关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday signed orders approving significant tariff relief for U.S. auto and engine production and setting new 25% tariffs on imported medium- and heavy-duty trucks and parts starting November 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-approves-tariff-relief-us-auto-production-issues-new-truck-duties-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TL6Z6MFS3FLXTA26HU6YQJVE4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:31:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿波罗支持的墨西哥航空公司在美国首次公开募股中寻求最高 29 亿美元的估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥航空公司集团（Grupo Aeroméxico）周五表示，其美国首次公开募股的目标估值高达 29.2 亿美元，这家墨西哥航空公司希望在两年多后再次上市。【原文：Grupo Aeroméxico said on Friday it was targeting a valuation of up to $2.92 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, as the Mexican carrier looks to go public again after over two years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aeromxico-backers-aim-raise-235-million-us-ipo-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYAVMCMWABLKROBDXUQQG5FXTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小特朗普和奥米德-马利克支持的 SPAC 申请 2.6 亿美元的美国 IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥米德-马利克（Omeed Malik）支持的空白支票公司 Colombier Acquisition Corp.奥米德-马利克（Omeed Malik）支持的空头支票公司哥伦比亚收购公司三期（Colombier Acquisition Corp. III）周五在美国提交了首次公开募股申请。【原文：Colombier Acquisition Corp. III, a blank-check firm backed by Omeed Malik, filed for an initial public offering in the United States on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spac-backed-by-trump-jr-omeed-malik-files-260-million-us-ipo-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5L7AJOQFBNETADB3T7WEOEVFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局称波音公司可将 737 MAX 的月产量提高到 42 架]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）和波音公司周五表示，该局取消了自2024年1月起实施的每月生产38架飞机的上限，波音公司可以将737 MAX的月产量提高到42架。【原文：Boeing can hike 737 MAX production to 42 planes per month after the Federal Aviation Administration lifted a 38 plane-per-month cap that had been in place since January 2024, the agency and planemaker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-can-hike-737-max-production-42-planes-per-month-faa-says-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQEJHMGFOFI7BGFL3UPEYUWCEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Axios 报道，Nvidia 和台积电推出首款美国制造的 Blackwell 芯片晶圆]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Axios报道，英伟达（Nvidia）和台积电（TSMC）将于本周五宣布其首个完成的美国制造晶圆，这些晶圆最终将成为用于人工智能的Blackwell芯片。【原文：Nvidia and TSMC will announce on Friday their first completed U.S.-made wafer that will eventually become Blackwell chips for AI purposes, Axios reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-tsmc-unveil-first-blackwell-chip-wafer-made-us-axios-reports-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APGVF2GFJZIEHENSDCCESWJPR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州对声称可回收利用的塑料袋制造商采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州周五宣布对三家主要塑料袋生产商提起诉讼，并与另外四家生产商达成和解，在此之前，加利福尼亚州已经完成了对这些生产商谎称塑料袋可回收的调查。【原文：The state of California announced a lawsuit against three major plastic bag producers and reached a settlement with four other manufacturers on Friday after concluding an investigation into their false claims that these bags were recyclable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/california-takes-action-against-plastic-bag-makers-over-recycling-claims-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OVBVJZKBRN5DIVJAYM6G77DRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:35:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，KKR 支持的 FiberCop 就意大利援助竞争对手的指控向欧盟提出申诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士透露，KKR 支持的电信网络公司 FiberCop 已向欧盟委员会提出申诉，指控意大利违反欧盟竞争规则，向竞争对手 Open Fiber 提供国家援助。【原文：KKR-backed telecom network firm FiberCop has filed a complaint with the European Commission, alleging that Italy provided state aid to rival Open Fiber in breach of EU competition rules, three sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/kkr-backed-fibercop-files-complaint-with-eu-over-alleged-italys-aid-rival-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5DFXAIERZL25ODT4MWDGQRGD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美港口收费扰乱货流，推高费率]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内高管表示，中国和美国对靠港征收的新费用正在减少可用于运输货物的货轮数量，并有可能增加两国的消费成本。【原文：New fees imposed on port calls by China and the U.S. are reducing the number of cargo vessels available for moving goods and threatening to increase consumer costs in both countries, industry executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-port-fees-disrupt-cargo-flows-push-up-rates-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VL4IB7Y3ABMILDXLRPZYCXTVBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司罢工工会将于周一恢复合同谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表 3,200 多名波音公司罢工工人的工会周五表示，已同意下周恢复与美国飞机制造商的合同讨论。【原文：A union representing more than 3,200 striking Boeing workers said on Friday it had agreed to resume contract discussions with the U.S. planemaker next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/iam-boeing-resume-contract-talks-monday-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKI67N4LHZJYDDVX3SVBX3SR6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁希望中美稀土交易避免对全球经济造成 "实质性影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周五表示，她希望美国和中国能达成协议，避免全球经济中的稀土供应断流，并补充说这种限制将对经济增长产生 "实质性影响"。【原文：International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said on Friday she was hoping for an agreement between the U.S. and China that avoids a cutoff in the flow of rare earths to the global economy, adding that such restrictions would have a "material impact" on growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/imf-chief-hopes-us-china-rare-earths-deal-avoid-material-impact-global-economy-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JI7M2GNNJNLRPKJWZJ3Y2DO67U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:51:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储穆萨莱姆倾向于支持 10 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆周五表示，他将支持央行在本月底降息，同时警告说，在通胀风险仍不稳定的情况下，美联储在放宽信贷成本方面不能走得太远。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis President Alberto Musalem suggested Friday he will support a central bank interest rate cut at the end of the month, while warning it's important for the Fed not to go too far with easing the cost of credit amid still unsettled inflation risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-musalem-leans-toward-supporting-october-interest-rate-cut-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5PF6LSZNZLQLFCB5YKFWSMQUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:25:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉薪酬计划面临反弹，ISS敦促投票反对马斯克的 1 万亿美元方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，代理咨询公司机构股东服务公司（Institutional Shareholder Services）敦促特斯拉股东投票反对首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）提议的 1 万亿美元业绩奖励，理由是担心薪酬过高和治理风险。【原文：Proxy advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services on Friday urged Tesla shareholders to vote against CEO Elon Musk's proposed $1 trillion performance award, citing concerns over excessive compensation and governance risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/proxy-advisory-firm-iss-recommends-voting-against-tesla-ceo-1-trillion-pay-plan-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7DHGZNPOVKXFIKQUOO35A6WIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士部长在美国与贝森特会谈，未透露关税问题取得进展的迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士经济部长居伊-帕梅林（Guy Parmelin）周五表示，他已就美国对瑞士征收39%的关税一事与美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）进行了简短的交谈，但他没有表示在减少征税方面取得了进展。【原文：Swiss Economy Minister Guy Parmelin said on Friday he had spoken briefly to U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent about the United States' 39% tariffs on Switzerland, but he gave no indication of progress on reducing the levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swiss-minister-speaks-bessent-us-gives-no-sign-progress-tariffs-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGHCSWH2FFO5FEMQ5ZO2C5WQSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[与甲骨文有关的黑客攻击活动针对特使航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司最大的地区性航空公司 Envoy Air 周五证实，该公司最近几天遭到黑客攻击，这是黑客利用甲骨文电子商务套件应用程序进行勒索的一部分。【原文：Envoy Air, American Airlines' largest regional carrier, suffered a hack in recent days as part of the wave of extortion attempts from hackers exploiting Oracle E-Business Suite applications, the company confirmed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/envoy-air-targeted-oracle-linked-hacking-campaign-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OE477JYCE5KINBVEFBAIGDXTJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:47:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷期待 SUV 老板莱特斯回归，接过 "毒杯]]></title><description><![CDATA[保时捷邀请前迈凯轮老板迈克尔-莱特斯（Michael Leiters）重振这家德国豪华汽车制造商的举动受到了投资者的欢迎，尽管他们对新老板面临的挑战并不抱幻想。【原文：Porsche's moves to bring in ex-McLaren boss Michael Leiters to revive the luxury German carmaker were welcomed by investors, although they have no illusions about the challenge in store for the new boss.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-eyes-return-suv-boss-leiters-assume-poisoned-chalice-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7J53H7Q7J5KRXNOOLO3RTV3YPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:20:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，高盛对新成立的资本解决方案集团管理层进行了调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份内部备忘录称，高盛已对其负责大型交易融资和为企业客户提供贷款的部门进行了多项组织调整和任命。【原文：Goldman Sachs has made several organizational changes and appointments in its unit that focuses on financing large deals and providing loans to corporate clients, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-rejigs-management-recently-created-capital-solutions-group-memo-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQNP4IWIFJN3RMQWKT27FSZC5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:14:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A2A 首席执行官称，米兰数据中心的容量将在五年内激增十倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源集团 A2A 首席执行官周五表示，意大利金融之都米兰周边的数据中心预计将在未来五年内增加约两千兆瓦的发电能力，比目前的水平增加十倍。【原文：Data centres around Italy's financial capital Milan are expected to add around two gigawatts of capacity over the next five years, a tenfold increase from current levels, the Chief Executive of energy group A2A said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/milans-data-centre-capacity-set-surge-tenfold-five-years-a2a-ceo-says-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQLPOMY5FVM2TIUPJADGWHKVII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称美国再次购买比索，比索汇率下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五表示，美国财政部周四在 "蓝筹掉期 "和现货市场上买入了阿根廷比索，并将继续监控所有市场。【原文：The U.S. Treasury bought Argentine pesos in the "Blue Chip Swap" and spot markets on Thursday and it continues to monitor all markets, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bessent-says-us-bought-pesos-again-currency-dips-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIHB7OYPBZJY3ENR2DEACFMPZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德聘请美国制药业资深人士，应对特朗普施加的定价压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）已任命美国制药业高管格雷格-麦利（Greg Miley）为其新任企业事务主管，因为这家肥胖症制药商在药品定价方面面临着来自美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）越来越大的压力。【原文：Novo Nordisk has appointed U.S. pharmaceutical executive Greg Miley as its new head of corporate affairs, as the obesity drugmaker faces growing pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump on drug pricing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-hires-us-pharma-veteran-trump-pricing-pressure-mounts-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SI22NLWKFLSJINQ3FVOVY52MA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:51:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行的班加呼吁提高债务重组过程的透明度]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行行长阿贾伊-班加（Ajay Banga）周五强调，有必要提高债务重组过程的透明度，使有关各方更加清楚地了解情况，包括将债务人报告制度扩大到 20 国集团的所有主要经济体。【原文：World Bank President Ajay Banga on Friday stressed the need to increase transparency in debt restructuring processes to give greater clarity to all parties involved, including by expanding the debtor reporting system to all Group of 20 major economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/world-banks-banga-calls-more-transparency-debt-restructuring-process-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6UO2IRRXZL2PNGGAQ3BLU7YQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受人工智能提振，瑞银将全球股市观点上调至 "有吸引力 "评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银全球财富管理公司（UBS Global Wealth Management）将其对全球股市的评级上调至 "有吸引力"，理由是人工智能支出有望提高生产率，且政策背景具有支持性。
"结构性趋势依然稳固。领先的人工智能企业之间的战略合作浪潮增强了我们对持续的资本支出周期和更高收入能见度的信心"，瑞银在周四的一份说明中说。
最近几周，人工智能热潮引发了一波涉及大型科技公司和硅谷初创企业的备受瞩目的交易。
受美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）提前开始降息以避免经济衰退的乐观情绪推动，全球股市攀升至历史新高。【原文：UBS Global Wealth Management upgraded its stance on global equities to "attractive", citing expected productivity gains from AI spending and a supportive policy backdrop.
"Structural trends remain firmly in place. The wave of strategic partnerships among leading AI players reinforces our confidence in a sustained capex cycle and greater revenue visibility", UBS said in a note on Thursday.
The AI boom has spurred a wave of high-profile deals involving Big Tech and Silicon Valley startups in recent weeks.
Global equities have climbed to record highs, driven by optimism that the U.S. Federal Reserve began cutting interest rates early enough to avoid a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/ubs-lifts-global-equities-view-attractive-ai-boost-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDT524KLLFKFDGPU3ZIFHWYEWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特敦促国际货币基金组织和世界银行对中国采取更强硬立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五向国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）和世界银行（World Bank）下达了具体指令，要求它们对中国以国家为主导的经济行为采取更强硬的立场，这是他推动全球贷款机构重新专注于其核心使命的一部分。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Friday gave specific marching orders for the International Monetary Fund and World Bank to take tougher stances on China's state-driven economic practices as part of his push to get the global lenders to refocus on their core missions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bessent-urges-imf-world-bank-take-tougher-line-china-2025-10-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5HKIU7HG2VIQXEN4YL6735ING4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>