<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:20:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:20:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[必胜客美国销售额超预期，优惠活动吸引精打细算的顾客]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美乐披萨周一公布的美国第四季度同店销售额超出华尔街预期，这家快餐连锁企业以价值驱动的促销活动和新菜品推动了需求增长。【原文：Domino's Pizza beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter U.S. same-store sales on Monday, as the fast-food chain's value-driven promotions and new menu items fueled demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dominos-beats-us-sales-estimates-deals-attract-budget-conscious-customers-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4B6M2YD4FLF5BCNY4SK3PST3A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德以78亿美元收购Arcellx]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司周一宣布将收购癌症疗法开发商Arcellx，交易隐含股权价值达78亿美元，推动Arcellx股价在盘前交易中飙升77.8%至113.99美元。【原文：Gilead Sciences said on Monday it will buy cancer therapy developer Arcellx for an implied equity value of $7.8 billion, sending shares of Arcellx climbing 77.8% to $113.99 in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/gilead-acquire-arcellx-78-billion-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SONFG3J7AFLSBHL47CB3UJ6CEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：人工智能威胁企业生存，软件公司面临更高借贷成本和更严格审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业消息人士称，软件公司正推迟债务融资交易，因借贷成本上升及贷款方审查趋严给该行业带来压力，而人工智能带来的日益增长的压力则威胁着其商业模式。【原文：Software companies are delaying debt deals as higher borrowing costs and tougher scrutiny from lenders weigh on the sector, at a time when mounting pressure from artificial intelligence threatens their business models, industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/software-companies-face-higher-borrowing-costs-tougher-scrutiny-ai-threatens-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSWKHZIQLVM23F7KI7M4LDG7CA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商正推动实现"无需注视"的驾驶技术，引发安全与责任归属的争议]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商正朝着实现完全无人驾驶汽车的漫长征程中一个关键里程碑全力冲刺：开发出允许驾驶员将视线移离道路——无论是发短信还是敲击笔记本电脑——的系统，除非车辆发出警报要求其重新接管控制权。【原文：Automakers are racing toward a key milestone on the long road to fully driverless cars: systems that let drivers take their eyes off the road – to shoot a text or peck away on a laptop – unless the car alerts them to retake control.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carmakers-push-toward-eyes-off-driving-raising-questions-safety-liability-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7BFKMSR3BKUJJF7N3LHF3YX3M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将审理埃克森公司向古巴索赔案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院将于周一审议一项法律的适用范围，该法律允许美国企业就古巴没收财产寻求赔偿。此案涉及埃克森美孚公司和邮轮运营商，正值特朗普政府加大对古巴政府施压之际。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court will consider on Monday the scope of a law that lets American companies seek compensation for property seized by Cuba in cases involving ExxonMobil and cruise operators being argued at a time when President Donald Trump's administration is ramping up pressure on the Cuban government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-supreme-court-hear-exxon-bid-compensation-cuba-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTS4SCHUGJM3TAL3RI6YLKHFSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下跌，关税疑虑打击风险偏好]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周一走低，因关税不确定性再度升温令投资者感到不安。此前尽管最高法院裁定推翻了特朗普总统更广泛的关税措施，但特朗普仍宣布将对部分商品加征15%的关税。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Monday as renewed tariff uncertainty unnerved investors after President Donald Trump announced a new 15% duty despite a Supreme Court ruling that struck down his broader levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-dip-tariff-doubts-hit-risk-appetite-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JT7JFICHZLU5OONVXDRY3SWLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威普罗首席技术官表示人工智能是机遇而非威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度威普罗公司高管表示，人工智能的快速普及将推动软件服务供应商需求增长而非萎缩，此言反驳了该技术将威胁行业外包模式的担忧。【原文：India's Wipro expects rapid AI adoption to boost rather than shrink demand for software service providers, a top executive said, countering concerns that the technology threatens the industry's outsourcing model.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/wipros-cto-says-ai-is-an-opportunity-not-threat-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSQE7JVTENOLPADQXTY24WOXII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士工业团体称特朗普最新关税上调加剧混乱局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普上周末宣布将所有国家对美出口商品的临时关税从10%提高至15%，此举引发了更多混乱。瑞士工业协会Swissmem周一表示，全球不确定性正在抑制投资活动。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's weekend announcement that he would increase a temporary tariff on U.S. imports from all countries to 15% from 10% has created more chaos, and the global uncertainty is dampening investment activity, Swiss industry association Swissmem said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/swiss-industry-group-says-trumps-latest-us-tariff-hike-creates-more-chaos-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJLMBQHQ7FLFNIJVON6DF3LPMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德减肥药CagriSema在临床试验中逊于礼来公司产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德周一表示，其新一代减肥药CagriSema在直接对比试验中效果逊于礼来公司的tirzepatide，这标志着在减肥药市场主导权争夺战中遭遇挫折。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Monday its next-generation obesity drug CagriSema was less effective than Eli Lilly's tirzepatide in a head-to-head trial, a setback in the race for dominance in the weight-loss drug market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisks-obesity-drug-falls-short-against-eli-lillys-copenhagen-trial-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INUR3NIW45P7FG5HKCOVF2GYFI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛上调第四季度油价预期，因经合组织国家库存下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛将2026年第四季度布伦特原油和西德克萨斯中质原油价格预期分别上调6美元至60美元和56美元，理由是经合组织国家库存下降。不过该机构仍维持伊朗供应不会中断的假设，并坚持今年市场将出现过剩的观点。【原文：Goldman Sachs raised its Brent and West Texas Intermediate crude forecasts for the fourth quarter of 2026 by $6 to $60 and $56 respectively, citing lower OECD stocks, even as it continued to assume no Iran-related supply disruption and maintained its view of a surplus this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-raises-q4-oil-price-outlook-lower-oecd-stocks-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPFKK2JHAVNPRPKWJLEHXWV2II</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，沙特阿美首次向美国企业及印度出售贾富拉凝析油货运]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位贸易消息人士透露，沙特国家能源巨头沙特阿美公司已向美国大型企业及印度炼油商出售了数批来自其价值1000亿美元贾富拉天然气厂的超轻质原油，该公司正准备在本月下旬出口首批货物。【原文：State energy major Saudi Aramco has sold several cargoes of ultra light crude oil from its $100 billion Jafurah gas plant to U.S. majors and an Indian refiner as it prepares to export its first cargo later this month, four trade sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/saudi-aramco-sells-first-jafurah-condensate-cargoes-us-firms-india-sources-say-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74JB4NSIBRKB3OHK2ZVZMKA3CI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:18:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着美国关税税率悬而未决，经济迷雾再度浓重]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国及外国官员、企业高管、分析师和投资者曾开始期待，去年动荡的美国贸易政策反复已告终结。如今，他们却面临着因美国最高法院上周裁决而重燃的不确定性——该裁决推翻了特朗普总统关税计划的关键部分，而特朗普随后又暗示将实施大幅加征关税作为规避措施。【原文：U.S. and foreign officials, corporate executives, analysts and investors had begun to hope the tumultuous U.S. trade policy reversals of last year were finished. Now they face rekindled uncertainty from a U.S. Supreme Court ruling last week that struck down key parts of President Donald Trump's tariff plans and his ensuing suggestion of substantial levies coming in an attempted workaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/with-us-tariff-rates-up-air-economic-fog-again-thickens-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHJ6FWKTTBILJOYOJRW66RYKWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税风波令国债市场陷入迷茫]]></title><description><![CDATA[最高法院推翻特朗普总统关税的裁决非但未能缓解市场担忧，反而为贸易政策、美国债务和美元注入了新的风险与不确定性。【原文：Far from being a source of relief, the Supreme Court's takedown of President Donald Trump's tariffs has infused new risks and uncertainties into trade policy, U.S. debt and the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-tariff-turmoil-leaves-treasury-markets-dazed-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNYNGGM2P5PWVPXLR72R5X6RGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:49:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国与巴西同意扩大关键矿产及贸易领域合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统李在明周一在首尔与巴西总统路易斯·伊纳西奥·卢拉·达席尔瓦举行峰会会谈，双方同意在贸易、关键矿产、科技和文化等领域扩大合作。【原文：South Korean President Lee Jae Myung held summit talks in Seoul on Monday with Brazilian President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, where they agreed to expand cooperation in sectors including trade, key minerals, technology and culture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-brazil-agree-expand-cooperation-key-minerals-trade-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWVZYVKYOFOUXMVBJEX47AS63A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税混乱的代价]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩·科尔为您解析欧洲及全球市场今日展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZCV4CHET5LH3DFOIW4BVUDHQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚Lendlease集团上半年转亏，股价跌至近40年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚联盛集团周一公布上半年转亏，受投资物业重估及减值影响，其股价跌至近四十年低点。【原文：Australia's Lendlease Group swung to a first-half loss on Monday, hurt by investment property revaluations and impairments, sending its shares to a near four-decade low.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-lendlease-hits-near-4decade-low-after-swinging-to-firsthalf-loss-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7LNGZDMPNL6LKWUTGJGE44NSY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国海关机构将停止征收最高法院周二裁定为非法的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国海关与边境保护局表示，将于周二东部时间凌晨12点01分（格林尼治时间0501）停止征收依据《国际紧急经济权力法》实施的关税。此前美国最高法院裁定该关税非法，距裁决已逾三日。【原文：The U.S. Customs and Border Protection agency said it will halt collections of tariffs imposed under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act at 12:01 a.m. EST (0501 GMT) on Tuesday, more than three days after the U.S. Supreme Court declared the duties illegal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-customs-agency-stop-collecting-tariffs-deemed-illegal-by-supreme-court-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LC3HL3KEFNNXPLST22E42SG6NY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对美国最高法院裁决及特朗普新关税威胁的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普表示，在最高法院推翻其大部分关税决定后，他将把对所有国家进口商品征收的临时关税从10%提高至15%。新关税依据的是另一项尚未实施的法律条款，即第122条。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said he will raise a temporary tariff on U.S. imports from all countries to 15% from 10%, following a Supreme Court decision striking down a large swath of his tariffs. The new levies are grounded in a separate but untested law, known as Section 122.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/reaction-us-supreme-court-ruling-trumps-new-tariff-threat-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZA5J4Z4U4FLZTH26KI3X22ZZZY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行前政策制定者称若日元再度走弱或于三月加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行前理事樱井诚向路透社表示，若日元在预计将于本月举行的美日首脑会晤前再度走弱，日本央行最早可能在3月加息。【原文：The Bank of Japan may raise interest rates as soon as March if the yen renews its slide ahead of a U.S.-Japan summit expected to be held during the month, former central bank board member Makoto Sakurai told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-may-raise-rates-march-if-yen-resumes-slide-says-ex-policymaker-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XSSZDTBSBLN3CPUSN36PRWXDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:35:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元走低，特朗普关税壁垒松动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周一走低，因交易员将美国最高法院推翻特朗普总统大部分关税的裁决视为对全球经济增长的利好，但中东地区的混乱局势和冲突风险使汇率波动幅度相对有限。【原文：The dollar fell on Monday as traders took the U.S. Supreme Court's decision to strike down most of President Donald Trump's tariffs as supportive for global growth, though confusion and risk of conflict in the Middle East kept moves relatively small.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-dips-trumps-tariff-wall-slips-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCYS4UF3QNIL3AARZFOFF437Z4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市犹豫不决，美元因关税混乱而走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周一表现犹豫，美元汇率走低，投资者正等待美国关税政策出现亟需的明确信号。与此同时，科技巨头英伟达本周将公布的财报，将考验市场对整个人工智能板块的信心。【原文：Share markets were hesitant and the dollar slid in Asia on Monday as investors waited for some much-needed clarity on U.S. tariffs, while confidence in the entire AI trade was set to be tested by results from tech-diva Nvidia this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTAOHD4IYFJ4BFPMPRIT7QFXF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价下跌，因美国提高关税引发对全球经济的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一油价下跌，此前美国总统特朗普表示将提高美国对全球进口商品的关税，这给全球经济增长和燃料消费带来了不确定性。【原文：Oil prices slipped on Monday after President Donald Trump said he would raise U.S. tariffs on global imports, creating uncertainty for world economic growth and fuel consumption.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-slides-us-tariff-hike-raise-jitters-over-global-economy-2026-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73AULJ6R65O3XGZKC3IKWEN6PU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，DAE Capital即将达成收购飞机租赁公司麦格理航空金融的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位行业消息人士透露，总部位于迪拜的飞机租赁公司DAE Capital即将达成协议，收购租赁平台麦格理航空金融的控股权。【原文：Dubai-based aircraft lessor DAE Capital is closing in on a deal to buy control of leasing platform Macquarie AirFinance, two industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/dae-capital-nears-deal-buy-aircraft-leasing-firm-macquarie-airfinance-sources-2026-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6LTTH54YRORDD5HV5VGXOBJII</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 18:28:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，劳斯莱斯将通过股票回购向股东返还高达20亿美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻周日报道，劳斯莱斯控股公司预计将在本周公布年度业绩时宣布，将向投资者启动新一轮股票回购计划，回购规模高达15亿英镑（约合20.2亿美元）。【原文：Rolls-Royce Holdings is expected to announce alongside its annual results this week that it will launch a fresh share buyback worth as much as 1.5 billion pounds ($2.02 billion) to investors, Sky News reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rolls-royce-return-more-than-1-billion-pounds-shareholders-buyback-sky-news-2026-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JASU3SP5INJNPH3ILXVAZTUB2M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 18:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示在最高法院裁决后不会接受美国加征关税："协议就是协议"]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周日要求美国遵守去年达成的欧盟-美国贸易协定条款。此前美国最高法院推翻了特朗普政府实施的全球性关税政策，特朗普随即以全面加征新关税作为回应。【原文：The European Commission demanded on Sunday that the United States stick to the terms of an EU-U.S. trade deal reached last year, after the U.S. Supreme Court struck down Donald Trump's global tariffs and he responded with new levies across the board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-says-it-will-accept-no-increase-us-tariffs-after-supreme-court-ruling-a-deal-2026-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJINCXFUCRKBFDTL3G6P7SKL74</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税裁决无法消除贸易伙伴的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[最高法院推翻特朗普大部分关税的裁决削弱了他的影响力，但他仍可通过频频转向和政策变动让各国保持警惕。【原文：The Supreme Court's decision to strike down a large swath of Donald Trump's tariffs clips his wings, but he can still leverage rapid-fire pivots and changes to keep countries on their toes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/tariff-ruling-limits-trumps-leverage-wont-end-uncertainty-trade-partners-2026-02-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKAMVP4OMNPTHNPQ34FM7KTPKQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通称在1月6日袭击事件发生一个月后关闭了特朗普的银行账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通银行于2021年2月通知唐纳德·特朗普总统及其酒店业务，将关闭他们在该行的账户。这一消息源于周五披露的新文件，该文件是特朗普对该银行及其首席执行官杰米·戴蒙提起的50亿美元诉讼的一部分。【原文：JPMorgan Chase told President Donald Trump and his hospitality business in February 2021 it was closing their accounts at the bank, according to new documents released Friday as part of a $5 billion lawsuit Trump has filed against the bank and CEO Jamie Dimon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-says-it-closed-trumps-bank-accounts-month-after-jan-6-attack-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72CUIOO6TRPMZB7BKXSIV2DB7Y</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:30:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿联酋挫败网络攻击，国家通讯社称]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿联酋国家通讯社周六报道称，该国已挫败针对其数字基础设施和关键部门的有组织网络攻击。【原文：The United Arab Emirates has thwarted organised cyber attacks targeting the country's digital infrastructure and vital sectors, the state news agency said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/uae-foils-cyber-attacks-state-news-agency-says-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2MO27SAVFPELP5OXIF67ZOS5Y</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:07:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将把美国全球关税税率从10%提高至15%]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统因最高法院裁定其动用紧急法案推进关税议程的举动无效而勃然大怒，随即对所有国家的进口商品征收临时关税。【原文：President Trump, infuriated by the Supreme Court's ruling against his use of an emergency law to push through his tariff agenda, imposed the temporary rate on imports from all countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-raise-global-tariff-rate-10-15-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIKY5DZEVNOOFDIUCUUKHUGTBI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国的梅尔茨预计，在特朗普关税案美国法院作出裁决后，关税负担将减轻。]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希·梅尔茨周六表示，在特朗普总统大部分贸易关税被美国最高法院裁定无效后，他预计德国经济的关税负担将减轻。【原文：German Chancellor Friedrich Merz said on Saturday he expected the tariff burden on the German economy to be lower after a U.S. Supreme Court ruling knocking down a large part of President Donald Trump's trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/germanys-merz-expects-lower-tariff-burden-after-us-court-verdict-trump-tariffs-2026-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4U4XZ7YXVO4ZHLCGGV6FBBZZE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>