<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 14:34:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 14:34:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国上周原油和产品库存可能下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二进行的一项调查显示，上周美国原油和燃料库存预计将下降。【原文：U.S. crude oil and fuel stockpiles are expected to have fallen last week, an extended Reuters poll showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-product-inventories-likely-fell-last-week-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5E3IUS36RM4ZMHCH7XPY4QPV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 提出向新营利结构转型的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周五制定了一项计划，将于明年对其公司结构进行改革，并表示将成立一家公益公司来管理其不断增长的业务，并放宽其当前非盈利母公司施加的限制。【原文：OpenAI on Friday laid out a plan to revamp its corporate structure next year, saying it would create a public benefit corporation to manage its growing business and ease the restrictions imposed by its current non-profit parent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-lays-out-plan-shift-new-for-profit-structure-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWYLRI3WQBIW7M332ELNFQQJLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:47:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，Jana Partners 在推动兰姆-威斯顿公司变革的过程中签下了第六位高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的一份监管文件显示，Jana Partners 正与第六位高管合作推动兰姆-韦斯顿公司（Lamb Weston）的变革，这表明这位激进投资者可能会寻求更换这家薯条生产商的大部分董事会成员。【原文：Jana Partners is working with a sixth executive to push for changes at Lamb Weston, signaling the activist investor may seek to replace the majority of the french fry maker's board, according to a regulatory filing made on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jana-partners-signs-up-sixth-executive-it-pushes-changes-lamb-weston-filing-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HDYGOBQS5LHNFT7PMDINZWALI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:45:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HomeStreet 银行将向美国银行出售 9.9 亿美元的多户住宅贷款组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[HomeStreet 银行周五表示，已同意向美国银行出售近 9.9 亿美元的多户商业房地产贷款。【原文：HomeStreet Bank said on Friday it has agreed to sell nearly $990 million of its multifamily commercial real estate loans to Bank of America .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/homestreet-bank-sell-990-mln-multifamily-loan-portfolio-bofa-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYFFL4JHJJJVBLQG5M4PRVBVLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:35:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院停止执行反洗钱法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院已停止执行一项反洗钱法，该法要求公司实体在大多数公司向美国财政部披露其真实受益所有人身份的最后期限之前披露。【原文：A U.S. appeals court has halted enforcement of an anti-money laundering law that requires corporate entities to disclose the identities of their real beneficial owners to the U.S. Treasury Department ahead of a deadline for most companies to do so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-appeals-court-halts-enforcement-anti-money-laundering-law-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAE2OWPTKJJ5DDVIMOFJTGMJ5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 13:35:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BioNTech 就 COVID 疫苗特许权使用费问题与美国代理机构和宾夕法尼亚大学达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[BioNTech 公司在周五提交的文件中表示，该公司已与美国国立卫生研究院和宾夕法尼亚大学就其 COVID-19 疫苗的版税支付问题分别达成了两项和解协议。【原文：BioNTech has entered into two separate settlement agreements with the U.S. National Institutes of Health and the University of Pennyslvania over the payment of royalties related to its COVID-19 vaccine, the company said in filings on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/biontech-enters-settlement-with-us-agency-upenn-over-covid-vaccine-royalties-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VH37I2SQNLLJHZ6FOXIER33DI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司向未披露的客户出售两架 C-390 军用飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周五表示，该公司已经签署了一份合同，向一家未公开的客户出售两架 C-390 千禧型军用货机。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer has signed a contract to sell two C-390 Millennium military cargo aircraft to an undisclosed client, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/embraer-sells-two-c-390-military-aircraft-undisclosed-client-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YAWU2LE3BML7N6O57NE3YPFTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:25:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾科学部警告说，削减开支可能会影响芯片和人工智能的资金投入]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾科学部周五警告说，在反对党通过要求削减经济和技术支出的法律后，明年用于半导体、人工智能和航空航天等领域的资金可能会减少200亿新台币（约合6.0911亿美元）。
在议会中占多数的台湾反对党上周通过立法，要求将中央政府的支出转到地方政府。【原文：Taiwan’s science ministry warned on Friday that funding for areas such as semiconductors, AI and aerospace could be reduced by T$20 billion ($609.11 million) for next year after opposition parties passed laws requiring cuts to economic and technology spending.
Taiwan’s opposition parties, which hold a majority in parliament, passed legislation last week to redirect spending from the central govern】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-science-ministry-warns-spending-cuts-could-hit-chips-ai-funding-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANBJ3PXEKZIJ7K5MNWQLKPAQYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:33:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 和 Amedisys 放弃终止合并协议的权利]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五提交的一份文件显示，UnitedHealth 和 Amedisys 放弃了在特定日期前终止合并协议的权利。【原文：UnitedHealth and Amedisys waived the right to terminate their merger agreement until a certain date, a filing showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/unitedhealth-amedisys-waive-right-terminate-merger-agreement-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FRYQX3AKBPPNB7I524XEG7UGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡港务局称壳牌关闭石油加工厂调查泄漏事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡海事与港务管理局（MPA）和国家环境局（NEA）周五表示，壳牌已关闭了其位于布干礁（Pulau Bukom）设施的一个石油加工装置，以调查一起疑似泄漏事件。【原文：Shell has shut down an oil processing unit at its Pulau Bukom facility to investigate a suspected leak, Singapore's Maritime and Port Authority (MPA) and National Environment Agency (NEA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-shuts-down-oil-processing-unit-investigate-leak-singapores-port-authority-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDGW26ZTXJIETHCNLHKYIX253Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[方舟的凯茜-伍德（Cathie Wood）在 "特朗普冲击 "中呼吁明确税制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技投资者凯茜-伍德（Cathie Wood）告诉路透社记者，她呼吁唐纳德-特朗普即将上任的政府通过将承诺的企业和个人减税政策追溯到2025年1月1日来促进经济增长和政策确定性。【原文：U.S. tech investor Cathie Wood is calling on Donald Trump's incoming administration to boost economic growth and policy certainty by backdating promised corporate and personal tax cuts to Jan. 1, 2025, she told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/arks-cathie-wood-calls-tax-clarity-she-rides-trump-bump-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OQM3D7EFBKT7M3NBO7IU3B4WE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 特朗普的首次行动和就业数据将在一月考验市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国股市今年的辉煌业绩收官之后，投资者预计将乘着季节性的势头进入 1 月中旬，届时一系列经济数据和华盛顿的权力交接可能会让市场蠢蠢欲动。【原文：After closing the books on a banner year for U.S. stocks, investors expect to ride seasonal momentum into mid-January when a slew of economic data and a transition of power in Washington could send markets moving.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-trumps-first-actions-job-data-test-market-january-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRSRRXEZDBLN3HQW563Z73ASTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 11:04:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货走软，假期缩短的一周强势收官]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货下跌，华尔街主要股指在节假日缩短的一周结束时表现乐观，市场对传统强势期的预期推动了股指的上涨。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Friday at the end of an upbeat holiday-shortened week for Wall Street's main indexes that was driven by expectations around a traditionally strong period for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-futures-ease-strong-holiday-shortened-week-draws-close-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSXA273TGRM2ND6WDTHVMV5QO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 10:41:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金因通胀降温、融资法案和假日反弹而获得大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 12 月 25 日的一周内，美国股票基金吸引了大量资金流入，从前一周的抛售中恢复过来，这主要是受到冷淡的通胀报告、避免政府停摆的临时拨款法案以及所谓的 "圣诞老人 "反弹的推动。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted significant inflows in the week to Dec. 25, recovering from a prior-week sell-off, buoyed by a cooler inflation report, a stopgap funding bill averting a government shutdown and a so-called "Santa Claus" rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-receive-big-inflows-cool-inflation-funding-bill-holiday-rally-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5K2TNSGR7RPF7BXUXRMC7NHYSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 10:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀缓解，全球股票基金重获资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至12月25日的一周内，全球股票基金资金大幅流入，从上一周的大量净卖出中反弹，这主要是受到美国通胀报告向好以及华盛顿避免了政府关门的影响，这恢复了投资者对风险资产的信心。【原文：Global equity funds witnessed sharp inflows in the week through Dec. 25, rebounding from significant net sales the previous week, buoyed by a benign U.S. inflation report and relief that Washington had averted a government shutdown, which restored investor confidence in risk assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGAE25T455J7TENCEQIRND2BVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 09:57:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 SMFG 预计 2025 财年净利润将超过 76.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[三井住友金融集团（Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group）首席执行官表示，随着日本银行业在利率正常化的同时努力实现海外收入来源多元化，该公司从明年 4 月起的一年内可能会获得超过 1.2 万亿日元（76.5 亿美元）的净利润。【原文：Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group's CEO said the firm may make more than 1.2 trillion yen ($7.65 billion) net profit in the year from next April, as a resurgent Japanese banking sector cashes in on efforts to diversify income sources abroad alongside interest rate normalisation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japans-smfg-expects-more-than-765-billion-net-profit-fy-2025-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SUVJI2GUFNIFPBTV267XQ7TFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 09:09:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在巴西受到抨击的比亚迪承包商--中国锦江是一家什么样的公司？]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西劳工部门称，中国晋江集团为电动汽车制造商比亚迪建造的一家工厂的工人是在 "类似奴役的条件下 "工作的人口贩运受害者，晋江集团因此成为焦点。【原文：China's Jinjiang Group is in the spotlight after Brazil's labour authorities said workers at a factory it is building for electric vehicle maker BYD were victims of human trafficking working in "slavery-like conditions".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/what-is-chinas-jinjiang-byd-contractor-under-fire-brazil-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAMMYQZKA5KZNDGKYRGO2VK4D4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 08:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[带领日本汽车制造商进军印度的铃木治去世，享年 94 岁]]></title><description><![CDATA[这位领导日本铃木汽车公司长达四十多年，并在印度汽车市场蓬勃发展的过程中发挥了关键作用的聪明人已经去世。【原文：The ingenious pennypincher who led Japan's Suzuki Motor for more than four decades and played a key role in turning India into a flourishing auto market has died.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/obituary-osamu-suzuki-who-led-japanese-automaker-into-india-dies-94-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGCLC5BZNNPS7E3GTNEXDYJ5LY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 08:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高昂的食品价格抑制了俄罗斯的节日气氛]]></title><description><![CDATA[这个假期，许多俄罗斯人都勒紧了裤腰带。【原文：This holiday season, many Russians are tightening their belts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/high-food-prices-dampen-festive-spirits-russia-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74EOC7DYGRLKDERL3LIGEB6CQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 08:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国快速发展的商业航天领域发生罕见火箭故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国领先的商业火箭公司之一中国航天科技集团公司（CAS Space）称，其 "利剑一号 "火箭周五意外失灵，这标志着该公司的主力运载火箭自2022年首飞以来首次遭遇挫折。【原文：CAS Space, one of China's leading commercial rocket firms, said its Lijian-1 rocket unexpectedly failed on Friday, marking the first setback for the company's main launch vehicle since its inaugural flight in 2022.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-fast-expanding-commercial-space-sector-logs-rare-rocket-failure-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFL5BYJPSJLWRBS6QOXSWQYXQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 06:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国 12 月出口连续第 15 个月增长，但增长势头放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，韩国12月份的出口增长预计将连续第15个月上升，但分析人士认为，随着对美国可能加征关税的担忧升温，未来一年的出口增长势头可能会有所放缓。【原文：South Korea's export growth is expected to have risen in December for a 15th straight month, but analysts feel momentum could moderate in the year ahead as concerns about possible U.S. tariffs heat up, a Reuters poll showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/south-korea-dec-exports-seen-up-15th-month-row-momentum-slowing-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YM5XJP6RCBPH5KGVLPVO7XGHXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 05:14:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行就未来加息对收益的影响做出估计]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行首次公布了对未来利率上调可能对其盈利产生的影响的估计，结果显示，如果短期借贷成本上升到 2%，日本央行将短暂蒙受高达 130 亿美元的亏损。【原文：The Bank of Japan released for the first time estimates on how future interest rate hikes could affect its earnings, which showed it will briefly suffer red ink of up to $13 billion if short-term borrowing costs were to go up to 2%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-produces-estimates-how-future-rate-hikes-affect-earnings-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26I2MHQOQNIM5KSNQFMVZOIDPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 03:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国比亚迪提供最高 11.5% 的年终折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪公司网站称，该公司的两款混合动力车和电动车将在1月26日前打折促销。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle giant BYD is offering discounts until Jan. 26 on two of its hybrid and EV models, according to its website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-byd-offers-year-end-discounts-up-115-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJ7ZWCW26BL5NGM4SRKGVRZW64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对中国刺激政策持乐观态度，油价将迎来周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，油价变化不大，但由于人们乐观地认为经济刺激措施将促使全球最大的石油进口国中国经济复苏，油价本周将上涨。【原文：Oil prices were little changed on Friday but were set for a weekly rise amid optimism economic stimulus efforts will prompt a recovery in China, the world's biggest oil importer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-set-weekly-gain-china-stimulus-optimism-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R325YSVAVZPW5I6KIY5QIRIIGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[年末交易清淡，亚洲股市漂移，日元创 5 个月新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市震荡，美元持稳，在清淡的年末交易中，日元维持在五个月低点附近，因为投资者展望2025年，预计美联储将有节制地降息。【原文：Asian stocks wobbled on Friday while the dollar was steady, keeping the yen rooted near five-month lows in thin year-end trading as investors looked ahead to 2025, when the Federal Reserve is expected to be measured in its interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XHUXURB7VLN7IVFG4YBO2SG2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:01:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 11 月工业利润降幅放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的官方数据显示，中国 11 月份工业利润降幅放缓，政策制定者承诺加大支持力度，以支撑摇摇欲坠的经济复苏。【原文：China's industrial profits fell at a slower clip in November, official data showed on Friday, as policymakers pledged stronger support to prop up a faltering economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-industrial-profits-decline-slower-pace-nov-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVQQDKVM5NIZTMBN7RBOVN3JCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 01:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元徘徊在 5 个月低点附近，日本央行的谨慎立场造成影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元兑美元汇率徘徊在五个月低点附近，因为美国联邦储备委员会的鹰派信息与日本央行对进一步收紧政策的谨慎态度形成了鲜明对比。【原文：The yen hovered near a five-month low to the dollar on Friday as the U.S. Federal Reserve's hawkish messaging contrasted with the Bank of Japan's cautious approach to further policy tightening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yen-hovers-near-5-month-low-bojs-cautious-stance-weighs-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SZFSKE6ZFPZHFI2NCKKQ3425Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 01:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[气候议程步履维艰，大石油公司在推动可再生能源方面出尔反尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲主要能源公司在 2024 年加倍努力开采石油和天然气，专注于近期利润，放缓--有时甚至逆转--气候承诺，这种转变在 2025 年很可能会坚持下去。【原文：Major European energy companies doubled down on oil and gas in 2024 to focus on near-term profits, slowing down - and at times reversing - climate commitments in a shift that they are likely to stick with in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/big-oil-backtracks-renewables-push-climate-agenda-falters-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBVIPMHKRNIGRKND34BE3SM4KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 01:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西法院暂缓执行为承诺砍伐森林的大豆企业减税的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，巴西最高法院的一名法官暂停执行巴西最大的大豆生产州的一项法律，该法律将终止为那些同意不购买亚马逊雨林砍伐区大豆的企业提供税收减免。【原文：A justice on Brazil's top court on Thursday suspended a law from the country's top soy-producing state that would end tax breaks for firms following an agreement to not purchase soy from deforested areas of the Amazon rainforest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-court-suspends-law-cutting-tax-breaks-firms-with-deforestation-soy-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5C6Q42CKZKGHAW43WTC5OUA3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首都通胀加速，加息前景不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，随着物价压力的扩大，日本首都的核心通胀率在12月份加速上升，这使市场对近期加息的预期保持了活力。【原文：Core inflation in Japan's capital accelerated in December as price pressures broadened, data showed on Friday, keeping alive market expectations for a near-term interest rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/inflation-japans-capital-accelerates-keeps-rate-hike-prospects-intact-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOIDPOF6JBOG3OMUXMPHA44LYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 23:50:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>