<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:12:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:12:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）非洲部负责人：撒哈拉以南非洲地区必须提高收入以渡过全球动荡期]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织非洲局局长阿贝贝-艾姆罗-塞拉西（Abebe Aemro Selassie）说，撒哈拉以南非洲经济体应努力增加国内税收，以避免在 "动荡的全球形势 "下不得不举债。【原文：Sub-Saharan African economies should work to increase their domestic revenue collection to avoid having to take on debt amid "turbulent global conditions", International Monetary Fund Africa Director Abebe Aemro Selassie said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/sub-saharan-africa-must-lift-revenue-ride-out-global-turbulence-imf-africa-head-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TN6E4RD7YJPD5EZYYH3Y5U3MRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美关税紧张局势缓解，全球股票基金第二周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至4月23日，全球股票基金连续第二周吸引资金流入，原因是有迹象表明中美之间的关税战可能降级，这刺激了对高风险资产的需求。【原文：Global equity funds attracted inflows for a second straight week through April 23, supported by signs of a potential de-escalation in the tariff war between the U.S. and China, which boosted demand for riskier assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BFQKT5YGJLRVID2LPD2TB7RTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债券基金六周来首次每周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至4月23日当周，美国债券基金六周来首次录得资金净流入，原因是美国债券市场的抛售有所缓解，投资者对中美贸易战可能缓和抱有希望。【原文：U.S. bond funds recorded net inflows in the week through April 23 for the first time in six weeks, as a selloff in U.S. bond markets eased and investors grew hopeful about a potential de-escalation in the trade war between the U.S. and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-bond-funds-attract-first-weekly-inflow-six-weeks-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4IAER7TXNMKTHMTAOXM6MFAKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:42:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院将对 Citgo 母公司的股份展开为期 30 天的竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周四晚些时候提交的一份法院文件显示，负责监督委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份拍卖的一名美国法院官员提议于 4 月 28 日开始为期 30 天的竞标期，并于 6 月 11 日选出出售过程的最终获胜者。【原文：A U.S. court officer overseeing an auction of shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum has proposed to open a 30-day competition period on April 28 to receive bids, with a final winner of the sale process to be selected on June 11, according to a court filing late on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-court-launch-30-day-competition-citgo-parents-shares-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNMQYTVU7ZMDLCC5AWM2WJAJI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:40:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高露洁棕榄公司季度业绩超预期，上调全年销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[高露洁-棕榄公司周五公布的季度业绩超过了华尔街的预期，并上调了全年销售预期，该公司希望通过适度提价和增加广告支出来刺激对其口腔和个人护理产品的需求。【原文：Colgate-Palmolive reported quarterly results that beat Wall Street estimates and raised its annual sales forecast on Friday, banking on moderate price hikes and higher advertising spending to boost demand for its oral and personal care products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/colgate-palmolives-quarterly-results-beat-raises-annual-sales-forecast-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAR7TKJOJJPZTIFEGFGLAP5VFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车需求放缓，印度塔塔科技公司收入不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受全球电动汽车需求放缓的影响，印度塔塔技术公司公布的第四季度收入低于预期。【原文：India's Tata Technologies reported a smaller-than-expected revenue for the fourth quarter, hurt by slowing global demand for electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-tata-technologies-misses-revenue-expectations-ev-demand-slows-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGYKDCQYPNLLRJP5ZNMCBQYF2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:33:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 2 月零售销售下降 0.4%；3 月预计增长 0.7]]></title><description><![CDATA[4月25日（路透社）--加拿大统计局周五称，由于汽车和零部件经销商的销售额下降，加拿大2月份零售销售额为693.3亿加元（499.5亿美元），比1月份下降0.4%。该机构在一份速报估计中说，3月份的销售额可能增长了0.7%。【原文：April 25 (Reuters) - Canadian retail sales fell by 0.4% in February from January at C$69.33 billion ($49.95 billion), on lower sales at motor vehicle and parts dealers, Statistics Canada said on Friday. Sales likely increased 0.7% in March, the agency said in a flash estimate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-february-retail-sales-fall-04-seen-up-07-march-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXVP5C7ETNKXBOLA754EBC7FDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行主席拒绝将比特币作为储备资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行行长周五表示，加密货币不符合该机构的货币储备标准，驳斥了加密货币倡导者要求瑞士国家银行持有比特币以对冲日益增长的全球经济风险的呼吁。【原文：The head of the Swiss National Bank said on Friday that cryptocurrencies failed to meet the institution's currency reserve standards, rebuffing calls by crypto advocates that it hold bitcoin as a hedge against growing global economic risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swiss-national-bank-chairman-rebuffs-bitcoin-reserve-asset-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWN5TZMU7RP5LIXP6YME6LVSSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:28:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[化工生产商利安德巴塞尔（LyondellBasell）因销量疲软，季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[利安德巴塞尔公司（LyondellBasell）周五未能达到华尔街的季度利润预期，原因是为汽车、建筑和电子行业提供原材料的最大业务部门进行了维护活动，且产量下降。【原文：LyondellBasell on Friday missed Wall Street's quarterly profit expectations, due to maintenance activity and lower volumes in its largest segment supplying raw materials to the automotive, construction and electronics industries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chemical-maker-lyondellbasell-misses-quarterly-profit-estimate-weak-volumes-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TD6HYGV5IFO2RNX5WLMZEK7MPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[移动服务强劲，Charter Communications 营收超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Charter Communications 周五公布的第一季度营收超出华尔街预期，其移动服务的新增用户数也超过预期，这主要得益于捆绑计划的强劲需求。【原文：Charter Communications on Friday topped Wall Street estimate for first-quarter revenue and added more subscribers than expected for its mobile services, thanks to strong demand for its bundled plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/charter-communications-beats-revenue-estimate-strength-mobile-services-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLW4DJPT3FOANF2ROM64Q334WQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HCA 医疗保健公司因医疗保健需求强劲而利润增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[医院运营商 HCA Healthcare 周五表示，由于流感病例增加，更多的人接受了选择性手术和就医，其第一季度利润增长了近 9%。【原文：Hospital operator HCA Healthcare said on Friday its first-quarter profit rose nearly 9%, as more people underwent elective procedures and sought medical care due to a rise in flu cases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hca-healthcare-posts-higher-profit-strong-demand-medical-care-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INY2KZDTQNIIBNXCZTSWHKRP2U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:51:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾伯维因新型免疫药物销售强劲而上调盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯维周五上调了 2025 年的利润预期，此前其较新的免疫学药物 Skyrizi 和 Rinvoq 的强劲销售帮助该公司第一季度盈利超过了华尔街的预期。【原文：AbbVie raised its 2025 profit forecast on Friday after strong sales of its newer immunology drugs Skyrizi and Rinvoq helped the company beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/abbvie-lifts-profit-forecast-strong-sales-newer-immunology-drugs-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVBBF6NGKNMJ5LVIXWNXAZNW64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，腾讯音乐正洽谈以 24 亿美元收购中国喜马拉雅]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，腾讯音乐娱乐集团正在就以 24 亿美元收购中国最大的在线音频平台喜马拉雅公司进行深入谈判。【原文：Tencent Music Entertainment Group is in advanced talks to buy China's largest online audio platform Ximalaya Inc for $2.4 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tencent-music-talks-buy-chinas-ximalaya-24-billion-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RL7L6WWSQFMCFPUY23SOB6JVHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:42:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于成本增加，保险经纪公司 Aon 季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受支出增加的影响，保险经纪公司怡安周五未能达到华尔街对其第一季度利润的预期。【原文：Insurance brokerage firm Aon missed Wall Street estimates for first-quarter profit on Friday, hurt by higher expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/insurance-broker-aon-misses-quarterly-profit-estimates-higher-cost-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGRSXGG3SJMVVEVDULC75KIULE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:34:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称习近平给他打过电话，并在《时代》周刊采访中阐述了贸易和其他交易计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[迄今为止，北京一直对美国对会谈的描述提出异议。【原文：Beijing has so far disputed the U.S. characterization of talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-xi-called-him-lays-out-trade-other-deal-plans-time-interview-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6LBUQLXTNKPDKRVWBSGEGQVSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油田服务提供商 SLB 盈利不及预期，原因是国际市场疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于拉丁美洲对其油田设备和服务的需求放缓，拖累了其国际业务，SLB 周五公布的第一季度利润不及分析师预期。【原文：SLB missed analysts' estimates for first-quarter profit on Friday, as a slowdown in demand in Latin America for its oilfield equipment and services dragged its international business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oilfield-services-provider-slb-misses-profit-estimates-international-weakness-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDZZEQ2YOBLJPDJCG2DBMBVGRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油商菲利普斯 66 季度亏损超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 周五公布的第一季度财报显示，由于美国炼油行业普遍进行检修和周转活动，炼油利润率下降，影响了公司业绩，导致亏损超过预期。【原文：Phillips 66 reported a bigger-than-expected loss in the first quarter on Friday, as lower refining margins amid a widespread maintenance and turnaround activity across the U.S. refining sector weighed on its performance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-refiner-phillips-66-posts-bigger-than-expected-quarterly-loss-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5RXG2IQTRKDJALKAKHSNUBOCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥扩建最大港口，不惧特朗普关税押注全球贸易]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的贸易战引发了黯淡的前景，但墨西哥当局仍将赌注押在积极的经济增长和全球贸易的力量上，墨西哥最大海港的大规模扩建工程正在进行中。【原文：A massive expansion of Mexico's largest seaport is under way as Mexican authorities bet on positive economic growth and the strength of global trade despite the gloomy outlook sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump's trade wars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-expands-its-largest-port-it-bets-global-trade-despite-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPLJ2CFTFBLSVBLLDBA4A6DOJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本是特朗普关税协议的一个试验案例。但谈判可能会很曲折。]]></title><description><![CDATA[本月早些时候，东京最高贸易谈判代表在白宫与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普举行关税谈判时，向他赠送了一个金色的储蓄罐。【原文：When Tokyo's top trade negotiator met U.S. President Donald Trump for tariff talks at the White House earlier this month, he presented him with a gold-coloured piggy bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/japan-is-test-case-trumps-tariff-deals-talks-may-be-tortuous-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AULJT4TGKRODTIRHRUGO4IUHVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易放缓，拉扎德第一季度利润下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资银行拉扎德（Lazard）周五公布，其第一季度调整后利润下降了9%，原因是关税和贸易战的可能性导致经济动荡，企业不愿进行交易。【原文：Investment bank Lazard reported a 9% drop in its first-quarter adjusted profit on Friday, as companies steered away from making deals amid economic turmoil due to tariffs and likelihood of a trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lazard-first-quarter-profit-dives-dealmaking-slows-down-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K55CZ6TEVJINFJNDS6COKAA2JY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《时代》报道，特朗普称中国国家主席习近平给他打电话，美中正在进行贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五接受《时代》杂志采访时表示，他的政府正在与中国谈判以达成关税协议，而且中国国家主席习近平已经给他打过电话。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said his administration is talking with China to strike a tariff deal and that Chinese President Xi Jinping has called him, according to a Time magazine interview published on Friday as Beijing continues to dispute U.S. characterization of talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-chinas-xi-has-called-him-that-us-china-are-trade-talks-time-reports-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFQC3SSOUJJTXFECRHGEPKKR6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，丰田董事长提议可能以 420 亿美元收购丰田工业公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，丰田汽车董事长丰田章男已提议收购供应商丰田工业，交易金额可能达到 6 万亿日元（418 亿美元）。【原文：Toyota Motor Chairman Akio Toyoda has proposed the acquisition of supplier Toyota Industries in a possible 6 trillion yen ($41.8 billion) deal, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-chairman-proposes-possible-42-billion-acquisition-toyota-industries-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKYREI7CGFPOXKILWXRLT3A23Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早安哇，我们已经成功一半了]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天美国和全球市场的重要事件，作者：Alun John，欧洲、中东和非洲地区即时新闻通讯员，金融与市场【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today, by Alun John, EMEA Breaking News Correspondent, finance and markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJRFYLJWHBJYZDYZ7JR3CEXYFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪第一季度利润翻番]]></title><description><![CDATA[比亚迪第一季度利润同比增长 100.4%，创下近两年来的最快增速，这家中国电动汽车巨头通过发起一场聪明的电动汽车价格战，扩大了其在竞争激烈的国内市场的领先优势。【原文：BYD's first-quarter profit leapt 100.4% from a year earlier, the fastest pace in nearly two years, as the Chinese electric vehicle giant extends its lead in its competitive home market by launching a smart EV price war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byds-first-quarter-profit-doubles-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MK7UHKP56ZJMXCDCTUO3NJEFCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:15:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街因中国关税减免迹象和乐观的 Alphabet 财报而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货跳涨，此前有迹象表明中国准备软化其关税立场，而重磅股Alphabet好于预期的季度业绩也提振了其股价，并为其他科技股提供了支撑。【原文：U.S. stock index futures jumped on Friday after signs China was prepared to soften its stance on tariffs, while better-than-expected quarterly results from heavyweight Alphabet lifted its shares and supported other technology stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/wall-street-rises-signs-chinas-tariff-relief-upbeat-alphabet-results-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NYS2A4YCZI5HORDDKFEC7ZQWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴拉圭豆农乘坐关税战 "雪橇]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于巴拉圭的大豆种植者和出口商来说，全球贸易关税战是一场不可预测的旅程，让他们担心波动的影响，同时也希望中国对南美豆粕和豆油有更多的需求。【原文：For Paraguay's soy farmers and exporters, the global trade tariff war is an unpredictable ride that makes them fear the effects of volatility and also hope for more Chinese demand for South American soy meal and oil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/paraguays-soy-farmers-ride-tariff-war-toboggan-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7C6YFOHEZNOOHDNSYCABQEBXKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价下挫，美国页岩补丁放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于原油价格跌至多年来的低点，加上高额关税导致建筑成本上升，美国一些小型页岩油生产商正在为石油钻探踩刹车。【原文：Some small U.S. shale producers are putting the brakes on oil drilling as crude prices sink to multi-year lows and steep tariffs drive construction costs higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-shale-patch-slows-down-oil-prices-sink-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADVUXP263ZKT3IDFQTAM4WZEV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国美国商会主席称制药公司已报告中国进口产品关税豁免情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部设在北京的美国商会周五表示，制药行业的公司报告称，在过去的一周里，他们能够以免征关税的方式向中国进口药品。【原文：The Beijing-based American Chamber of Commerce said on Friday that companies in the pharmaceutical sector had reported that they had been able to import drugs to China over the past week with tariff exemptions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/amcham-china-president-says-pharma-companies-have-reported-tariff-exemptions-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GASMPLMZ4NKYLMVFLO4ELQBFDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 09:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国平安保险第一季度利润下降 26.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国平安保险（集团）股份有限公司周五公布第一季度净利润下降 26.4%。【原文：Ping An Insurance (Group) Co of China Ltd reported a 26.4% decline in first-quarter net profit on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/chinas-ping-an-insurance-posts-264-fall-first-quarter-profit-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMD2FAM6SNKIXN6JJWMJC6ZO4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 09:26:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国寻求与印度就电子商务、农作物和数据存储达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，正在讨论的美印贸易协定将涵盖 19 个类别，包括扩大农产品、电子商务、数据存储和关键矿产的市场准入。【原文：A U.S.-India trade agreement under discussion will cover 19 categories, including greater market access for farm goods, e-commerce, data storage and critical minerals, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-seeks-india-trade-deal-e-commerce-crops-data-storage-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GDG52Q5NFJO3FU3SHJYOX56TQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>