<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:34:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:34:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街为特朗普 2.0 做好准备：关税、减税和波动性]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）重返白宫，华尔街正期待着可能出现的低税、放松管制以及一位对股市和美元等一切问题都能迅速发声的美国总统。【原文：With Donald Trump heading back to the White House, Wall Street is anticipating the potential for lower taxes, deregulation and a U.S. president who is quick to sound off on everything from the stock market to the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-girds-trump-20-tariffs-tax-cuts-volatility-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULTBMMFY3FKZJH4RMYSNCZ5RKE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普大选获胜：为什么这次中国经济更容易受到任何新关税的影响？]]></title><description><![CDATA[已当选为下一任美国总统的唐纳德-特朗普威胁要对美国进口中国商品征收 60% 的关税，这给世界第二大经济体带来了重大的增长风险。【原文：A threat by Donald Trump, who has been elected as the next U.S. president, to impose 60% tariffs on U.S. imports of Chinese goods poses major growth risks for the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/why-chinas-economy-is-more-vulnerable-trump-tariffs-this-time-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSTEXB66Z5NITFJNP4S4D43E7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:28:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普回国将减缓而非阻止美国清洁能源的蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫后，美国的能源政策将重新聚焦于最大限度地提高石油和天然气产量，而不再关注应对气候变化，但共和党在周二的总统选举中获胜不太可能大幅减缓美国可再生能源的蓬勃发展。【原文：Donald Trump's return to the White House will refocus the nation's energy policy onto maximizing oil and gas production and away from fighting climate change, but the Republican win in Tuesday's presidential elections is unlikely to dramatically slow the U.S. renewable energy boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-return-will-slow-not-stop-us-clean-energy-boom-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7DYRUTF75LUZCNT6OKLKAOALY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对 "特朗普 2.0 "输赢的押注刺激市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）被迅速确认为下一任美国总统，这推动了美元汇率的上涨，并惩罚了欧元，因为投资者押注进口商品关税会影响贸易，而减税则会使美国企业受益。【原文：Donald Trump's rapid confirmation as the next U.S. president propelled the dollar and punished the euro as investors bet on tariffs on imports affecting trade while tax cuts could benefit U.S. business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bets-trump-20-winners-losers-whip-up-markets-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DS5WFAD5CJKSHN434BSA72ECOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场对美联储缩减资产负债表的空间更有信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周的美联储会议上，金融市场对美国央行持续缩减资产负债表的前景比以往任何时候都更加明朗。【原文：Financial markets are heading into this week's Federal Reserve meeting with more clarity over the outlook for the U.S. central bank's ongoing balance sheet drawdown than they've had in a while, and those keeping close tabs on the process see it continuing into next year even as the Fed keeps cutting interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/markets-more-confident-fed-balance-sheet-drawdown-has-room-run-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3I4NQ6AIFBOJ3LUWUADNX4P74E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[信贷紧缩为美联储降息增添理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储有充足的理由在周四宣布人们普遍预期的降息，其中包括通胀下降和劳动力市场降温导致美国人更难找到工作。【原文：The Federal Reserve has plenty of reasons to deliver a widely expected interest rate cut on Thursday, including a decline in inflation and a cooling in labor markets that makes it harder for Americans to find jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tight-credit-conditions-add-case-fed-interest-rate-cut-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FC3CHBIZURILNPCFCURKBYDCWU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将审理 Facebook 为逃避证券欺诈诉讼而提出的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院将于本周三审理 Meta 旗下 Facebook 公司的诉讼，以阻止该公司股东提起的联邦证券欺诈诉讼，这些股东指控该社交媒体平台在滥用用户数据方面误导了他们。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court is set on Wednesday to consider a bid by Meta's Facebook to scuttle a federal securities fraud lawsuit brought by shareholders who accused the social media platform of misleading them about the misuse of its user data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-hear-facebook-bid-escape-securities-fraud-suit-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMHJRT2EEVIDZJJHVQV5C5UPVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 11:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国廉价的伊朗石油供应面临特朗普加强制裁的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在今年 1 月就任美国总统后加大对德黑兰的制裁力度，中国将面临廉价伊朗原油供应的挤压，而伊朗原油约占全球最大石油买家进口量的 13%。【原文：China faces a squeeze on supplies of cheap Iranian crude, which make up about 13% of imports by the world's biggest buyer of oil, if Donald Trump ramps up enforcement of sanctions on Tehran after his return as U.S. president in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-cheap-iranian-oil-supply-risk-tighter-trump-sanctions-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNKCVF7T5NIMDDDJUV2GHUDDWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:57:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康宁公司因与手机制造商达成独家供货协议遭欧盟反垄断监管机构调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构周三开始调查美国玻璃制造商康宁公司与手机制造商和玻璃原料加工公司达成的独家供应协议，因为他们担心这些协议可能会将竞争对手的玻璃生产商排除在大部分市场之外。【原文：EU antitrust regulators opened on Wednesday an investigation into U.S. glass maker Corning's exclusive supply deals with mobile phone makers and raw glass processing companies on concerns that these may exclude rival glass producers from large segments of the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/corning-investigated-by-eu-antitrust-regulators-over-exclusive-supply-deals-with-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46WUU3BMQBJMJDNXEGM6HJ33WM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:56:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 特朗普获胜美元飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXOZ6FY4KROWJL6LY6FX22UWUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:51:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Rivian 或将公布上市以来的首次季度营收下降报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian 预计将于周四公布自三年前上市以来的首次季度收入下降，此前零部件短缺迫使这家电动 SUV 和皮卡制造商在上个月削减了 2024 年的生产目标。【原文：Rivian is expected to report on Thursday its first drop in quarterly revenue since going public three years ago, after a shortage of parts forced the maker of electric SUVs and pickups to slash its 2024 production target last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-rivian-may-report-first-quarterly-revenue-drop-since-ipo-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2GZW4BGXZIRTGKANTUGYJSRYU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达州拒绝娱乐性大麻合法化，大麻股大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二晚些时候，佛罗里达州娱乐性销售和使用大麻合法化的投票措施未能获得通过，导致大麻公司股价暴跌，并对在合法化运动中投资数百万美元的大麻公司造成了打击。【原文：A ballot measure to legalize the recreational sale and use of marijuana in Florida failed to pass late Tuesday, sending shares of pot companies into freefall and dealing a blow to cannabis firms that had invested millions in the legalization campaign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/pot-stocks-dive-florida-rejects-legalization-recreational-marijuana-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUSXMXC52ZNANM5W6TRJM5YCT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:48:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agoda 首席执行官：赌场可能改变泰国旅游业的游戏规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着这个依赖旅游业的国家越来越接近赌博合法化，专注于亚洲的在线旅行社 Agoda 的一位高管周三表示，赌场和相关景点将大大促进外国游客到泰国旅游。【原文：Casinos and related attractions would significantly boost foreign arrivals to Thailand, a top executive at the Asia-focused online travel agency Agoda said on Wednesday, as the tourism-reliant country moves closer to legalising gambling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/casinos-could-be-game-changer-thailands-tourism-industry-agoda-ceo-says-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDD4ZE6UQFK5JCOH5BQLZC4EVU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马淡化特朗普胜选对美国关税的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国高档汽车制造商宝马公司首席执行官周三表示，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）可能担任美国总统的情况下，潜在的进口关税甚至可能使宝马公司受益，他指出，宝马公司在当地拥有强大的足迹，包括其全球最大的工厂。【原文：Potential import tariffs under a possible U.S. presidency of Donald Trump may even benefit BMW , the German premium carmaker's CEO said on Wednesday, pointing to its strong local footprint that includes its largest plant worldwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-downplays-fears-over-us-tariffs-trump-election-win-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRXOHL2DSZLS5O4WYBSIXWG5MY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果特朗普征收关税，韩国贸易部长认为企业将加大对美投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国贸易部长周三表示，如果下届美国政府出台更高的关税，他认为韩国企业将在美国进行更多投资。【原文：South Korea's trade minister said on Wednesday he saw domestic companies investing more in the United States if the next U.S. administration introduces higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/south-korean-trade-minister-sees-firms-investing-more-us-if-trump-imposes-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GPMJZEMOJMHRDAXJHKNJQONCA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:35:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：特朗普当选总统对全球市场的利害关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普似乎准备重返白宫，美元和股市被视为赢家，但共和党总统职位可能会对债券、新兴市场、清洁能源和可持续投资造成压力。【原文：As Donald Trump appears poised to head back to the White House, the U.S. dollar and stock market are seen as winners, but a Republican presidency could weigh on bonds, emerging markets, clean energy and sustainable investing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/whats-stake-global-markets-trump-presidency-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OY3FBLKCMJOY7MJCZQJ2DKO2ZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普胜选将影响全球经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在下一任美国总统竞选中获胜，如果得到确认，将对世界其他地区产生深刻而直接的经济影响。【原文：Donald Trump's victory in the race to become the next U.S. president will, if confirmed, have economic consequences for the rest of the world that are likely to be deep and quite immediate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-victory-reverberate-through-global-economy-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLDKRZFYOFKGPC25CYZPQDAWAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前总统特朗普临近第二任期，其媒体业务和特斯拉业务激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国大选的一些关键州尚未公布结果，但特斯拉、唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的媒体业务以及专注于国内市场的小型公司的股价周三大涨，预计这位前总统将获胜。【原文：Shares of Tesla , Donald Trump's media business and domestic-focused small-cap companies surged on Wednesday in anticipation of a win for the former president even though some key states in the U.S. election are yet to post results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-media-business-tesla-surge-former-president-nears-second-term-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2IUWQPIOFO35IEMVI3CWS4P4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彪马首席执行官：公司已 "做好准备 "应对可能的关税增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国体育用品制造商彪马公司首席执行官阿尔内-弗罗因特（Arne Freundt）周三在被问及唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对美国部分进口商品征收关税的计划可能产生的影响时表示，彪马公司已做好充分准备，可对关税上调做出迅速反应。【原文：German sportswear maker Puma is well positioned to react swiftly to tariff increases, CEO Arne Freundt said on Wednesday, when asked about the potential impact of Donald Trump's plans to impose tariffs on some imports to the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/puma-ceo-company-well-positioned-cope-with-potential-tariff-increases-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQC3IVFGYBI4JAPMGIVZNA7M2U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:37:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国再次呼吁意大利取消网络税]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，美国最近再次呼吁意大利废除国内网络税，并称如果罗马无视美国的要求，美国的坚持将增加报复的风险。【原文：The United States has recently renewed calls for Italy to repeal its domestic web tax, people familiar with the matter told Reuters, saying the U.S.' insistence increases the risk of retaliation if Rome ignores the request.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/united-states-renews-calls-italy-scrap-its-web-tax-sources-say-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NV32G77RDZKHPOJNQ7EO7JJSHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:36:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普 2.0 对贸易、移民、气候变化和电动汽车意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普赢得总统大选将对美国的贸易政策、气候变化、乌克兰战争、电动汽车、美国人的税收和非法移民产生巨大影响。【原文：A Donald Trump presidential election victory would have huge implications for U.S. trade policy, climate change, the war in Ukraine, electric vehicles, Americans' taxes and illegal immigration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/factbox-what-trump-20-would-mean-trade-migrants-climate-change-electric-cars-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFOOSGCAANLONKCXXXEOB6RXEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:32:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[裕信银行首席执行官力推合并优势，表现优于德国商业银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合信贷银行首席执行官 Andrea Orcel 周三表示，银行需要提高效率和盈利能力，并表示相信，在权衡与德国商业银行的潜在交易时，"人们会看清事实"。【原文：UniCredit CEO Andrea Orcel said on Wednesday banks need to be more efficient and profitable and expressed confidence that "people will look at the facts" when weighing up a potential deal with Commerzbank .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-ceo-pushes-merger-credentials-it-outperforms-commerzbank-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMVPI2UBUVMHDI55AIVJECQD6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:32:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威兹航空公司在对欧盟批准的罗马尼亚援助 TAROM 的质疑中败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[威兹航空公司（Wizz Air）周三对罗马尼亚竞争对手 TAROM 的增资提出了质疑，该增资由罗马尼亚出资，并获得了欧盟竞争监管机构的批准。【原文：Budget airline Wizz Air on Wednesday lost its challenge against a capital increase for Romanian rival TAROM funded by Romania and approved by EU competition regulators, as Europe's second-top court dismissed its arguments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/wizz-air-loses-challenge-against-eu-approved-romanian-aid-tarom-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HRRVNUZIZL5BOZBTCP37RD23Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧元区 10 月份采购经理人指数（PMI）显示企业经营保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元区上个月的商业活动保持稳定，与 9 月份的小幅下滑相比略有改善，这主要得益于该集团占主导地位的服务业的扩张抵消了制造业持续下滑（但已趋于稳定）的影响。【原文：Euro zone business activity held steady last month, a small improvement from September's modest decline, supported by an expansion in the bloc's dominant services industry that offset an ongoing - but stabilising - decline in manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-business-holds-steady-october-pmi-shows-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7CZ3TKHWRP5RMBHHRE3M7YDKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:12:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布获胜后，标普 500 指数期货飙升至历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布在美国总统大选中获胜后，美国 500 指数期货周三大幅广泛反弹，触及历史新高。【原文：S&amp;P 500 futures touched a record high in sharp and broad-based rally on Wednesday after Republican Donald Trump claimed victory in the U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sp-500-futures-soar-record-high-after-trump-claims-victory-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQ23PBAFGFNELMTHCYNFD5K2QI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 09:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘿，蠢货，这不仅仅是经济问题。是通货膨胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[比尔-克林顿的战略家詹姆斯-卡维尔（James Carville）曾在 1992 年说过，美国总统选举的核心是 "经济，笨蛋"。【原文：U.S. presidential elections are all about "the economy, stupid", said Bill Clinton's strategist James Carville in 1992.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hey-stupid-it-wasnt-just-economy-it-was-inflation-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZEBNKVR4RI4PFNMI62Y72V7OI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 08:58:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上任在即，中国股市下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）再次担任总统和共和党控制美国国会的前景有可能加剧贸易和技术方面的紧张局势，中国人民币和股市周三大幅下跌。【原文：China's yuan and stock markets fell sharply on Wednesday as the prospect of another Donald Trump presidency and Republican control of U.S. Congress risked heightened tensions over trade and technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-markets-drop-trump-presidency-looms-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CS2AXXHLRL63MJUS7SCIXVLVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 08:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥斯纳布吕克工厂的大众汽车工人举行新一轮警告性罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车奥斯纳布吕克工厂被认为是德国汽车制造商重组计划中可能关闭的目标，该工厂的工人将于周三举行新一轮警告性罢工，IG Metall 工会表示，这是地区性抗议薪资活动的一部分。【原文：Workers at Volkswagen's Osnabrueck plant, considered a possible target for closure under the German automaker's restructuring plans, are holding fresh warning strikes on Wednesday as part of regional protests over pay, the IG Metall union said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-workers-osnabrueck-plant-hold-fresh-warning-strike-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QX5I35K6ANKB3ET2Y4KIOVKXSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 08:33:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国新鹏押注增程混合动力技术以提高销量]]></title><description><![CDATA[新鹏汽车周三发布了其增程型混合动力技术，这家中国电动汽车制造商押注于转向比纯电动汽车更具成本竞争力的此类产品，以促进销售并提高盈利能力。【原文：Xpeng unveiled its extended-range hybrid technology on Wednesday, as the Chinese electric vehicle maker bets on a pivot to such products that are more cost-competitive than pure EVs to boost sales and improve profitability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-xpeng-bets-extended-range-hybrid-tech-boost-sales-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIBVFMVRMVPN7CBRJGRSQILSWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 08:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场倾向于特朗普获胜，墨西哥比索跌至两年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥比索周三跌至两年多来的最弱水平，因为市场为唐纳德-特朗普在美国大选中获胜做好了准备，从而延续了这个新兴市场风向标的连续波动和疲软。【原文：Mexico's peso sank to its weakest level in over two years on Wednesday, as markets braced for a win for Donald Trump the U.S. election, extending a streak of volatility and weakness for the emerging markets bellwether.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/mexicos-peso-slumps-two-year-low-markets-tilt-towards-trump-win-2024-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTPCWFYKOZKBZI6SSTQTGYE7YI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 07:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>