<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 09:37:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 09:37:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[市场溃败加剧，期货暴跌，标普 500 指数逼近熊市区域]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周一大幅下挫，S&amp;P 500指数似乎将确认进入熊市，投资者因担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税计划会对经济造成影响而纷纷抛售政府债券。【原文：U.S. stock index futures plummeted on Monday, and the S&amp;P 500 looked set to confirm a bear market, as investors barreled into government bonds on economic worries over the fallout of U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariff plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-plunge-sp-500-eyes-bear-territory-market-rout-worsens-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKWP6B2ILBMIZKOX3G3YPCMHF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 09:19:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，CATL 正在洽谈收购 Nio 电力部门的控股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位知情人士告诉路透社，中国电池巨头 CATL 正在洽谈收购电动汽车制造商 Nio 动力部门的控股权。【原文：Chinese battery giant CATL is in talks to buy a controlling stake in electric vehicle maker Nio's power unit, which runs more than 3,000 battery swapping stations in China, four people with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/catl-talks-buy-controlling-stake-nios-power-unit-sources-say-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CHA745XJJICVFNN4QII3PW7HM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 09:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报道称微软合资公司微创软件将停止中国业务并裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国媒体《财经》周一援引消息人士的话报道，微软的合资企业微创软件将从周二起停止在中国的运营，此举将导致裁员约2000人。【原文：Microsoft's joint venture Wicresoft will cease its China operations from Tuesday, a move that will lead to the layoff of about 2,000 staff, Chinese media outlet Caijing reported on Monday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-venture-wicresoft-halt-china-operations-lay-off-staff-report-says-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7G5ZBAUHNJZJKCVD3VFXYKC2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:57:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据媒体报道，德国在线经纪商 Trade Republic 因股价下跌而遭遇故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[据德国媒体报道，由于全球股市大跌，德国在线经纪商 Trade Republic 周一遭遇故障。【原文：The German online broker Trade Republic suffered an outage on Monday as stocks fell in a global rout, German media reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/german-online-broker-trade-republic-suffers-outage-stocks-tank-media-report-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4WNFOZZHJKLTB55YXWFQE7ZG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔 500 指数期货有望确认熊市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，标普 500 指数期货进一步下跌，与历史高点相比跌幅超过 20%，由于全球市场担心经济衰退，标普 500 指数有望确认进入熊市。【原文：Futures tied to the S&amp;P 500 fell further on Monday and were down more than 20% from their all-time highs, putting the benchmark on course to confirm a bear market as recession fears hammered global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sp-500-futures-pace-confirm-bear-market-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEEFB75ODBJOZIE4AQXBGNB75Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:45:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市下跌，非美国投资者对美元的需求激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[在全球股市遭受猛烈抛售之后，货币市场周一开始出现紧张迹象，各种衡量美元需求的指标均创下几个月来的最高水平。【原文：Money markets on Monday began showing signs of strain following an aggressive selloff engulfing global equities, sending various measures of demand for dollars to their strongest in months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/demand-dollars-non-us-investors-surges-stocks-crumble-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O674YSAYERMFJDBY3HLLFQ2XNA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道德国默茨担心市场进一步崩溃，呼吁迅速采取关税行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布全面征收关税后，德国候任总理弗里德里希-默茨（Friedrich Merz）周一呼吁迅速采取行动，确保德国的竞争力，以应对股市和债券市场的下滑。【原文：Chancellor-in-waiting Friedrich Merz called on Monday for swift action to secure Germany's competitiveness in response to sliding stock and bond markets, following U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/fearing-further-market-meltdown-germanys-merz-calls-swift-action-tariffs-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EL4UKK5VFNM6ZGEWSQ47PKCO5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:27:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[桑坦德银行和巴西开发银行利用巴西气候基金支持蒙巴重新造林]]></title><description><![CDATA[植树造林初创公司Mombak周一表示，该公司与巴西桑坦德银行（Santander Brasil）和巴西开发银行（BNDES）达成了一项协议，获得了1亿雷亚尔（约合1780万美元）的资金，期待着碳清除市场的快速增长。【原文：Reforestation startup Mombak has secured 100 million reais ($17.8 million) in a deal with Santander Brasil and Brazilian development bank BNDES, it said on Monday, eyeing rapid growth in the carbon removal market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/santander-bndes-back-mombak-reforestation-drawing-brazil-climate-fund-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BD5TDE5PJOX3ARFCPG6NYIYGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国主权基金汇金在市场低迷之际买入国内股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国主权基金中央汇金投资周一表示，它正在增持中国股票，并将捍卫市场稳定。【原文：China's sovereign fund Central Huijin Investment said on Monday it is increasing holdings in China stocks and will defend market stability - comments that follow a slide in local shares amid fears a widening trade war will unleash a deep recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-sovereign-fund-huijin-buying-domestic-stocks-market-slumps-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TX66ZRQI5MIRMMLSFJYUJMZT4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 07:59:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着市场崩溃的加深，亚洲决策者正在采取哪些措施？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布全面征收关税，激起了广泛的经济衰退忧虑，亚洲各国的政策制定者正准备采取措施支持金融市场。【原文：Policymakers cross Asia are preparing measures to support financial markets as a rout deepened following sweeping tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump that stoked widespread recession worries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/what-measures-are-asian-policymakers-taking-market-rout-deepens-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBXH2PWMGBNX5CANLVYDV2AAG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 07:51:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰认为欧盟一致同意对特朗普关税采取 "冷静、有节制 "的应对措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰贸易部长周一表示，他相信欧盟各国在 "冷静、有节制地 "应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税问题上已达成强烈共识，美国的数字服务目前不会成为征税对象。【原文：Ireland's trade minister on Monday said he believes there is a strong consensus among European Union countries for a "calm, measured" response to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs and that U.S. digital services will not be targeted at this point.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ireland-sees-eu-consensus-calm-measured-response-trump-tariffs-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEPU72ROCZO6BOX2LH4XPXZ5MU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 07:35:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金投降，投资者准备在市场崩溃中追加保证金]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些对冲基金表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战抹去了数万亿美元的市值，迫使它们减少使用借来的现金进行交易，因此它们正在抛售全部或大部分持有的股票。【原文：Some hedge funds say they are offloading all or most of their holdings of stocks as U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war wipes out trillions of dollars of market value and forces them to curtail trading using borrowed cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/global-markets-tariffs-margincalls-pix-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4HNUHNXOVNHBNZWGN2YU5OVQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 07:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲银行股因担心关税引发经济衰退而扩大跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全面关税政策引发了对全面贸易战和全球经济衰退的担忧，德国贷款机构的股票连续第三天下跌。【原文：Shares in German lenders continued their losses for a third day as U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs ignited fears of an all-out trade war and a global economic recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/european-bank-shares-extend-losses-fear-tariff-induced-recession-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHMV6CZNFNM33D7PT6NG6I7JDI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，空中客车公司三月份交付了 71 架飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士称，空中客车公司 3 月份交付了 71 架喷气式飞机，使第一季度的交付量达到 136 架。【原文：Airbus delivered 71 jets in March, bringing first-quarter deliveries to 136 units, industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-delivered-71-airplanes-march-sources-say-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZAREZJPPZNM7IYMRPHKJAYIJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司最容易受到中国报复性进口关税的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国对所有美国商品征收 34% 的关税，这是对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的针锋相对的打击，必将扰乱从航空到农业的各个行业。【原文：China's move to impose 34% tariffs on all U.S. goods in a tit-for-tat blow against U.S. President Donald Trump is set to roil industries from aviation to agriculture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-companies-most-vulnerable-chinas-retaliatory-import-tariffs-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWGQ77Z66BM6DKBJB74TXP2PEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国向美国公司表示将始终为外资企业提供保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部副部长凌激对包括特斯拉和通用电气医疗在内的美国公司表示，中国将始终为在华外资企业提供保护，包括来自美国的企业。【原文：China's Vice Commerce Minister Ling Ji told U.S. companies including Tesla and GE Healthcare that the country would always provide protection for foreign funded firms in China, including those from the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/china-tells-us-companies-it-will-always-provide-protection-foreign-funded-firms-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKIFNF7JCFM4NOGMU35FEMX4AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，维基百科运营商对印度法院删除内容的命令提出上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，两位直接了解此事的消息人士称，在线百科全书维基百科的运营商对新德里法院要求删除其在国内新闻网站页面上被认为具有诽谤性的言论的命令提出了质疑。【原文：The operator of online encyclopedia Wikipedia has challenged a New Delhi court's order to remove statements deemed defamatory from its page on a domestic news website, two sources with direct knowledge of the matter said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/wikipedia-operator-appeals-indian-courts-order-remove-content-sources-say-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSCER24S6FPEFFEN2HT4S5SZ34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行称部分日本企业担心美国贸易政策的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行在周一举行的地区分行经理季度会议后发表声明说，一些日本公司担心美国贸易政策的不确定性加剧会打击它们的利润和产量。【原文：Some Japanese companies are worried about heightened uncertainty over U.S. trade policy that could hit their profits and output, the central bank said in a statement on Monday after a quarterly meeting of its regional branch managers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/some-japan-firms-worry-over-us-trade-policy-uncertainty-boj-says-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGRSBCDZV5IOFO4JQPO47RUHPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:17:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在经济走势不明朗的情况下，美联储不会 "认沽]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在他认为有必要的时候发出了强烈的信息，在 COVID-19 大流行病袭来时，他在电视上承诺最大限度地支持经济；在 2022 年的一次简短演讲中，他就通货膨胀问题发出了严厉的信息；在 2023 年硅谷银行倒闭后，他跳出来支持金融市场。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell has sent strong messages when he felt they were needed, going on television to pledge maximum support for the economy when the COVID-19 pandemic struck, using a terse 2022 speech for a stern message about inflation, and jumping in to backstop financial markets after the 2023 failure of Silicon Valley Bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/no-fed-put-when-its-unclear-which-way-economy-may-pivot-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CE6YFHIAUZPJFIZ4GSDP46KC3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场痛苦蔓延，亚洲信贷开始动荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲信贷市场变得动荡不安，由于经济衰退的担忧波及整个金融市场，企业和主权违约的保险成本上升。【原文：Credit markets turned shaky in Asia on Monday, with the cost of insuring against corporate and sovereign default higher as recession fears rippled across financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asia-credit-starts-wobble-market-pain-spreads-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSVWGY67N5K47JI4EQUCBUN3XY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标关税药物的致命副作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN25PGO64FKI7LLCLSHHGRRLNE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:35:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：特朗普关税可能使欧元增长放缓 0.5 至 1 个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊央行行长亚尼斯-斯托纳拉斯（Yannis Stournaras）在周一发表的一篇采访中告诉《金融时报》，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税措施可能会使欧元区经济增长放缓0.5至1个百分点。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff measures could slow euro area economic growth by between 0.5 and 1 percentage points, Greek central bank governor Yannis Stournaras told the Financial Times in an interview published on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/trump-tariffs-could-slow-euro-growth-by-05-1-percentage-points-ft-reports-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7U4WYFBXZLK7MDJ2NUBUERUNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:22:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子称电视机业务受美国关税影响较小，因为墨西哥有产出]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子的一位高管周一表示，由于三星电子的电视机主要在墨西哥生产，预计其电视机业务受美国关税的影响将小于竞争对手。【原文：Samsung Electronics' television business is expected to be less affected by U.S. tariffs than rivals because its TVs are mainly produced in Mexico, an executive said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-elec-says-tv-business-be-less-affected-by-us-tariffs-than-rivals-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YN73C6HHYNISJAPFUXM7D5MLXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:16:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度塔塔汽车公司下滑 8%，因为豪华车部门 JLR 暂停对美出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）25%的关税生效后，生产豪华汽车的捷豹路虎（JLR）暂停向美国出口其英国制造的汽车，印度汽车制造商塔塔汽车公司（Tata Motors）的股价周一下挫8%。【原文：Shares of Indian automaker Tata Motors sank 8% on Monday after Jaguar Land Rover (JLR), which makes luxury cars, paused exports of its British-made cars to the U.S. following President Donald Trump's 25% tariff came into effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/indias-tata-motors-slides-8-after-luxury-arm-jlr-pauses-exports-us-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IC5KJU5SEBMMNN3XBOTTC4F6UY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 04:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛将美国经济衰退几率上调至 45]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）将美国未来12个月经济衰退的几率上调至45%，与其他投资银行一道修订了他们的预测，因为在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收关税之后，市场担心会爆发贸易战。【原文：Goldman Sachs has raised the odds of a U.S. recession to 45% in the next 12 months, joining other investment banks in revising their forecast as fears of a trade war grip markets after sweeping tariffs from U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-raises-odds-us-recession-45-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TISX7SIFQVIPZGZG4CZSZJT3UQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:56:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 Horizon Robotics 公司宣布与大众汽车合作开发先进的智能驾驶技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的地平线机器人公司（Horizon Robotics）周一宣布将与大众汽车公司合作开发先进的驾驶辅助解决方案，从而扩大了与德国汽车制造商的合作。【原文：China's Horizon Robotics announced on Monday that it would cooperate with Volkswagen on advanced driver assistance solution, extending its co-operation with the German automaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-horizon-robotics-announces-partnership-with-volkswagen-advanced-smart-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IULCQT7F6ZPNTI47TX4QOUGANM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:45:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税 "药方 "为全球市场注入动荡因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）警告外国政府，要取消全面关税，他们将不得不支付 "一大笔钱"，并将这些关税称为 "药品"，这引发了周一全球金融市场的进一步动荡。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump warned foreign governments they would have to pay "a lot of money" to lift sweeping tariffs, characterising the duties as "medicine" and triggering further carnage across global financial markets on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trumps-tariff-medicine-injects-turmoil-into-global-markets-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2QFVOZCXRLJ7E4PGSTX646Y2I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度官员称，尽管美国加征关税，印度仍将维持 2025/26 年的经济增长预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度财政部一位官员表示，尽管美国新关税导致全球经济混乱，但如果油价保持在每桶70美元以下，印度很可能实现2025/26财年（4月至3月）6.3%-6.8%的预期增长目标。【原文：India is likely to meet its projected growth target of 6.3%-6.8% for the 2025/26 fiscal year (April-March) if oil prices remain below $70 per barrel, despite global disruptions due to new U.S. tariffs, a finance ministry official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-maintains-202526-growth-projection-despite-us-tariffs-official-says-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYZKTSYJIVLWTOMA343LKR2WRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行将降息25个基点，经济学家称美国加征关税后可能进一步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计新西兰央行将于周三将其官方现金利率下调25个基点至3.50%，经济学家称，随着该行对美国关税及其潜在的全球经济影响做出反应，2025年可能会有更多的降息举措。【原文：New Zealand’s central bank is expected to cut its official cash rate by 25 basis points to 3.50% on Wednesday and economists say the bank could make more cuts in 2025 as it reacts to U.S. tariffs and their potential global economic fallout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/rbnz-cut-rates-by-25bps-economists-say-more-cuts-possible-after-us-tariffs-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SM45I7UO7BNULJJELSJK6LOSMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国茶壶炼油厂开工率提高，但需求困境和制裁带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士和分析师表示，中国陷入困境的独立炼油企业的运行率最近有所回升，但近期仍面临国内燃料需求不振的压力，以及美国制裁和关税带来的供应风险。【原文：Run rates for China's struggling independent oil refiners have nudged up recently, but still face near-term pressure over tepid domestic fuel demand and supply risks from U.S. sanctions and tariffs, industry participants and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/china-teapot-oil-refiners-improve-run-rates-demand-woes-sanctions-weigh-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PDAMZUKK5OMBKOAOQ2V6U3BFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 02:58:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>