<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:04:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:04:45 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能推动需求回升，美国股票基金每周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至9月24日的一周，美国股票基金吸引了新的现金，结束了连续两周的资金外流，原因是英伟达（Nvidia）宣布可能向OpenAI投资1000亿美元后，风险情绪有所改善。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted fresh cash in the week to September 24, snapping two-weeks of outflows, as risk sentiment improved following Nvidia’s announcement of a potential $100 billion investment in OpenAI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-draw-weekly-inflows-ai-boost-sparks-renewed-demand-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2UF7654LZOB5GJYMQHB5Z7X7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能乐观情绪和美联储减息押注提振情绪，全球股票基金录得周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至9月24日的一周内，全球股票基金三周来首次录得资金净流入，原因是人工智能投资的乐观情绪和对美国可能降息的重新押注提升了投资者情绪。【原文：Global equity funds recorded net inflows for the first time in three weeks in the week to September 24, as optimism around artificial intelligence investments and renewed bets on potential U.S. rate cuts lifted investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORBZNOTCOBNK5OPCAI7QQB3PQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司获得 FAA 批准在波音 737-800 型飞机上安装 Starlink 互联网]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周五表示，美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）已批准其首架干线飞机配备 Starlink 互联网，为 10 月 15 日的首次商业飞行扫清了障碍。【原文：United Airlines said on Friday the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration has approved its first mainline aircraft equipped with Starlink internet, clearing the way for a first commercial flight on October 15.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-gets-faa-approval-starlink-internet-boeing-737-800-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32XXMGPFWRMT3JIXQ3HLONFSJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度称与美国的贸易谈判具有 "建设性"，希望早日达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度周五表示，印度官员在本周访问华盛顿期间与美国官员举行了 "建设性 "会谈，双方同意继续讨论尽快达成互利贸易协议的问题。【原文：India said on Friday its officials held “constructive” talks with U.S. counterparts during a visit to Washington this week, and both sides agreed to continue discussions aimed at concluding a mutually beneficial trade deal soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-says-trade-talks-with-us-constructive-eyes-early-deal-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETOUUTDGGROMXCIGYCW2PS26WI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:21:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴金通胀和就业面临的风险可能有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周五表示，他认为失业率或通胀率大幅上升的风险有限，这使得美联储在讨论进一步降息时能够平衡其两大目标。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said Friday he sees limited risks of a big rise in either unemployment or inflation, letting the Fed balance its two goals as it debates further interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-barkin-risks-both-inflation-jobs-may-be-limited-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27LSIQZXIFIIDM5HYABUSTHWZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 8 月份 PCE 符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五称，8月份个人消费支出价格指数（PCE）上升0.3%，7月份为上升0.2%，与路透社调查的经济学家的预期一致。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Friday its Personal Consumption Expenditures Price Index (PCE) rose 0.3% in August, versus the prior 0.2% rise in July and matched the estimate of economists polled by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-us-pce-matches-expectations-august-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPM7TOELSRIJTOZT5YCS3S54KY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普新关税打击 Wayfair、Williams-Sonoma 股价；La-Z-Boy 股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普总统宣布对进口家具征收关税后，零售商 Williams-Sonoma 和 Wayfair 的股价周五下跌，而主要在美国生产的 La-Z-Boy 和 Ethan Allen 的股价则上涨。【原文：Shares of retailers Williams-Sonoma and Wayfair , fell on Friday after President Donald Trump unveiled tariffs on furniture imports, while those of La-Z-Boy and Ethan Allen , which manufacture largely in the U.S., gained.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/wayfair-williams-sonoma-shares-slide-trump-targets-furniture-imports-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3YYYTI4DZNGDGSL5QCC3MN2SI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普提出要求后，阿斯利康将下调部分直接面向美国患者的药品价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康（AstraZeneca）周五表示，它将向美国现金支付患者直接销售其糖尿病和哮喘药物，折扣最高可达上市价格的七折，这是在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普施压后最新一家这样做的制药公司。【原文：AstraZeneca said on Friday it will sell its diabetes and asthma drugs direct to cash-paying U.S. patients at a discount of up to 70% off list prices, the latest pharma company to do so after pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-cut-some-direct-to-patient-us-drug-prices-after-trump-demand-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQNRANWNRNKIJGUINQUREE4VPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:53:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国默茨称欧洲仍过于依赖美国软件]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希-梅尔茨（Friedrich Merz）周五表示，德国仍然过于依赖美国的软件，呼吁欧洲更加重视数字主权和自己的数据中心。【原文：Germany still depends far too much on software from the United States, Chancellor Friedrich Merz said on Friday, calling for Europe to focus more on digital sovereignty and its own data centres.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/germanys-merz-says-europe-still-far-too-dependent-software-us-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5B7PX6Y3O5J7FNJ5RUZSHJIB5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司的 Thaad 导弹防御系统瞄准欧洲市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国防务承包商洛克希德-马丁公司告诉德国《商报》，该公司正在寻求向欧洲买家推销其 Thaad 导弹防御系统，因为欧洲各国政府都在加快军费开支以应对俄罗斯的威胁。【原文：U.S. defence contractor Lockheed Martin is seeking to market its Thaad missile defence system to European buyers, the company told German newspaper Handelsblatt, as governments across the continent accelerate military spending in response to Russian threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-martin-targets-european-market-thaad-missile-defence-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDMAJMDUJFNZJOZ7A5CN6WNOMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月份消费者支出稳健增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份，美国消费者支出的增长略高于预期，使经济在第三季度继续保持稳健增长，同时通胀继续以一定的速度上升。【原文：U.S. consumer spending increased slightly more than expected in August, keeping the economy on solid ground as the third quarter progressed, while inflation continued to rise at a measured pace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-spending-increases-solidly-august-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46546EM4TBKHNGXXQSOL2XUEVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:39:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 7 月国内生产总值在连续三个月萎缩后出现反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的数据显示，由于采矿业、制造业和批发贸易促进了经济增长，加拿大7月份的月度国内生产总值从连续三个月的萎缩中反弹，增长了0.2%。【原文：Canada's monthly gross domestic product rebounded from three months of contraction to grow by 0.2% in July as mining, manufacturing and wholesale trade boosted growth, data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-gdp-rebounds-july-after-three-months-contraction-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHGWDNLJOVOB3DDAZU72NVV2VM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利邮政考虑收取数字身份识别费，分析师认为可能增加 1 亿欧元利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利邮政公司（Poste Italiane）的分析师在周五的每日报告中写道，在与公司管理层进行了一次情况通报后，意大利邮政公司正在考虑对其数字身份服务的用户收取年度管理费。【原文：Poste Italiane is considering introducing an annual management fee for users of its digital identity service, analysts wrote in their daily reports on Friday following a briefing with the company's management.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/poste-italiane-considers-digital-identity-fee-analysts-see-potential-100-mln-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGUGQ3JSWNLNJAN4AVXQLWVLHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道汉莎航空周一宣布裁员数千人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，汉莎航空将在周一举行的六年来首次全公司范围的资本市场日上宣布裁员数千人，以向市场表明其提高效率的决心。【原文：Lufthansa is expected to announce several thousand job cuts on Monday at its first company-wide capital markets day in six years, according to two sources close to the matter, as it seeks to show the market its commitment to increasing efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/lufthansa-announce-thousands-job-cuts-monday-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKR24KXGO5JIVJV7QOA7LWFSS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，FAA 将放宽波音 737 MAX 的生产限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美国联邦航空管理局将放宽对波音737 MAX生产的限制。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration is set to ease restrictions on Boeing's 737 MAX production, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-ease-boeing-737-max-production-restrictions-wsj-reports-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3RESJAP55MC3EVOGA6RW45U3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的能源转向加速了美国太阳能和风能企业的兼并和资产出售]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士和分析师表示，特朗普政府在可再生能源领域的迅速退却，已经在美国较小的太阳能和风能公司中掀起了整合和资产出售的浪潮，因为这些公司正竭力维持生存。【原文：The Trump administration's rapid retreat from renewable energy has kicked off consolidation and asset sales among smaller U.S. solar and wind power companies as they scramble to stay afloat, industry insiders and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trumps-energy-pivot-accelerates-us-solar-wind-power-mergers-asset-sales-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEONRJRHZRIZDFNLX4PNMNKNLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:34:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将在英国推出无广告的 Facebook 和 Instagram 订阅服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周五表示，它将在未来几周内向英国的 Facebook 和 Instagram 用户提供无广告订阅选项。【原文：Meta Platforms said on Friday it would offer an ad-free subscription option to Facebook and Instagram users in the United Kingdom in the coming weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-launch-ad-free-facebook-instagram-subscriptions-uk-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JC5VATZKABJLFPFP464APYIWLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国还要加征关税？中国的 "家具王国 "表示已经采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国的 "家具王国 "乐从，有一条巨大的购物中心带，商贩们对来自华盛顿的最新一轮关税避而不谈，称他们早已放弃了美国市场。【原文：In China's "Furniture Kingdom" of Lecong, home to a strip of cavernous malls, vendors shrugged off the latest round of tariffs from Washington, saying they've long given up on the U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/more-us-tariffs-chinas-furniture-kingdom-says-its-already-moved-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74AWVCCXMRJCDCZIQOWSLI2UHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:38:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标美联储的艰难工作变得更难]]></title><description><![CDATA[看看投资回报率团队周末要阅读、观看和收听什么节目。【原文：Check out what the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NL36YEMAJFILLN67HIAWV23GTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布对卡车征收关税，戴姆勒卡车和特拉通股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对重型卡车征收关税后，戴姆勒卡车公司和特拉通公司的股价周五下跌，加剧了对汽车行业造成重创的贸易紧张局势。【原文：Shares in Daimler Truck and Traton fell on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump announced tariffs on heavy-duty trucks, adding to trade tensions that have hit the automotive sector hard.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/daimler-truck-traton-shares-fall-trump-announces-truck-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23AIJPYIFRITBMA4MUDIBHDBHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:11:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国表示推动美国制药关税取得更好结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，除非企业在美国建立生产基地，否则将对其征收 100% 的新关税，英国周五表示，正在就药品关税问题向美国施压，希望能取得有利的结果。【原文：Britain on Friday said it was pressing the United States on pharmaceutical tariffs in hope of a beneficial outcome, after President Donald Trump said a new 100% tariff would apply to firms unless they build a manufacturing presence in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/britain-says-pushing-better-outcome-us-pharma-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PB4Y6SLS65OOXMDQ2QNDY2INPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 投资者期待就业数据支持降息路径，股市价格高企]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的美国就业数据对华尔街来说可能需要慎之又慎，既要显示劳动力市场降温，支持进一步降息，又不能加剧对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：Next week's U.S. jobs data may need to tread a fine line for Wall Street, revealing a cooling labor market that supports further interest rate cuts without fueling fears about a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-look-jobs-data-support-rate-cut-path-pricey-stock-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5ABLSBCLNPJFCO5YTKHYH5CVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大天然气生产商在价格创历史新低之际削减产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些公司和分析师表示，加拿大西部的一些天然气生产商正在积极减产，以缓解持续过剩的天然气供应，本周天然气价格跌至创纪录的负值。【原文：Some natural gas producers in Western Canada are aggressively cutting output in an effort to ease an ongoing glut that this week tipped prices for the fuel into record negative territory, companies and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/canadian-natgas-producers-cut-output-amid-record-low-prices-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6OVDRSTXZNS3EQO6J5V3VY3ZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国防部门罢工持续第九周，波音公司感受不到经济痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周五，位于圣路易斯的波音防务公司的机械师罢工达到了53天，与去年西北地区的国际机械师和航空航天工人协会工会成员的罢工相同，他们为该公司制造了大部分商用喷气机。【原文：A strike by machinists at Boeing Defense in St. Louis reached 53 days on Friday, matching last year’s walkout by fellow International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers union members in the Northwest who make most of the company's commercial jets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeing-feels-little-economic-pain-strike-defense-unit-head-ninth-week-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4IXI37YQFPVVD7WTK33JXGB6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:02:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟和日本对美国药品关税上限表示信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，他将于下周对美国药品征收 100%的关税。【原文：The European Union and Japan expressed confidence on Friday that they had secured limits on U.S. tariffs on pharmaceuticals, which President Donald Trump said he would impose next week at a rate of 100%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eu-japan-express-confidence-in-capped-us-tariffs-drugs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVV57Q7DPVP7XNBLS7RQ7YLPHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为通胀数据做好准备，华尔街期货涨跌不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货涨跌不一，投资者在等待可能左右降息押注的关键通胀数据，同时也在权衡对多种进口商品征收新关税的影响。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were mixed on Friday, as investors awaited key inflation data that could sway bets on interest rate cuts, while also weighing the impact of fresh tariffs on a broad range of imported goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-mixed-investors-brace-inflation-data-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WQ6XQJCMJOOTKG2HSCEDVNAL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卫星合并在即，欧洲航天局警告反对垄断]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲航天局的一位高级官员说，要达到与美国和中国竞争对手竞争的规模，可能需要合并，但过于集中可能会限制选择。【原文：A senior official from the European Space Agency said mergers could be needed to reach the scale to compete with U.S. and Chinese rivals, but that too much concentration could limit choice.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/european-space-agency-warns-against-monopolies-satellite-merger-looms-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKZBQOJL3VOEXOQIT7GP2ZF3L4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚要求美国对家具、汽车和航空航天零部件实行零关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚贸易部一位官员周五表示，马来西亚已要求美国考虑对其出口的家具、汽车和航空航天产品征收零关税。【原文：Malaysia has asked the United States to consider imposing zero tariff rates on its exports of furniture, automotive and aerospace products, a Malaysian trade ministry official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/malaysia-asks-us-zero-tariff-rate-furniture-automotive-aerospace-parts-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQKFZPSHBNO7DMLKTTSXEL3DCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行发出稳定币警告后，英国银行继续推行代币化存款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国最大的贷款机构正在推进明年推出客户存款代币化版本的计划，此举是在英格兰银行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）呼吁优先考虑该技术而非稳定币之后采取的。【原文：Britain's biggest lenders are pushing ahead with plans to launch tokenised versions of customer deposits next year, a move that follows Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey's plea to prioritise the technology over stablecoins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/uk-banks-press-with-tokenised-deposits-after-boe-stablecoin-warning-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4TSTRQGL5MG3MS5F7JP7S6LJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行明年将进行新的数字欧元实验]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）周五表示，它将在明年就数字欧元可能实现的目标进行新的实验，这是它在一个被视为保持欧元区金融独立于美国的关键项目上迈出的又一步。【原文：The European Central Bank said on Friday it would conduct new experiments next year about what could be achieved through a digital euro, in a further step for a project it sees as key for preserving the euro zone's financial autonomy from the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ecb-conduct-new-digital-euro-experiments-next-year-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BNYJHSCJFPZXHFLGBUNE64YJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:35:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>