<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:35:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:35:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普我们将与中国达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，他希望与中国达成一项贸易协议，但他没有提供具体细节，也没有表明在两个超级大国明显陷入僵局的情况下将如何展开谈判。【原文：President Donald Trump on Thursday said he expects to make a trade deal with China, though he offered no specifics or indications of how talks would get underway with the two superpowers at an apparent impasse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-we-will-have-trade-deal-with-china-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ45R262ORKUNDMKU3NPM2XOCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MP 材料公司因关税问题停止运往中国的稀土货物]]></title><description><![CDATA[MP Materials 公司周四表示，已停止向中国运输稀土精矿，以应对报复性关税和出口管制，该公司股价在午后交易中下跌了 6.3%。【原文：MP Materials said on Thursday it had stopped shipping rare earth concentrate to China, in response to retaliatory tariffs and export controls, sending its shares down 6.3% in afternoon trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/mp-materials-stops-china-bound-rare-earth-shipments-over-tariffs-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WL4BJNUZCBKDJLAPMPDTRG5BCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:29:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商四周来首次增加油气钻机]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周四在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周增加了石油和天然气钻机，这是四周以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week added oil and natural gas rigs for the first time in four weeks, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-add-oil-gas-rigs-first-time-four-weeks-baker-hughes-says-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWBZ4DBIRFOYXCQUSLFGGXAW24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:12:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社：美国财政部正与联邦机构商谈放松银行监管事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）正在与联邦和其他银行机构举行非公开会议，这是他为简化监督和协调放松监管计划而扩大努力的一部分。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent is hosting private meetings with federal and other bank agencies as a part of his expanded effort to streamline oversight and coordinate plans to ease regulation, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-treasury-talks-with-federal-agencies-ease-bank-oversight-bloomberg-news-says-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HP3OHRYFVZMBVKSNJLQHFVLMBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司向经销商下调柴油价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国营石油公司（Petrobras）在周四的一份声明中说，从周五开始，该公司将把出售给经销商的柴油价格平均每升降低 0.12 雷亚尔（0.0205 美元）。【原文：Brazilian state-run oil company Petrobras will reduce the price of diesel sold to distributors by an average 0.12 real ($0.0205) per liter starting on Friday, it said in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazils-petrobras-cuts-diesel-prices-distributors-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34JIN5W6FBNT7BD4J22Q2B2T3E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德再次获准持有大型公用事业股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦能源监管机构周四再次批准贝莱德持有公用事业公司的主要股份，这是该全球顶级资产管理公司在人们对其影响力过大的担忧中取得的胜利。【原文：U.S. federal energy regulators on Thursday gave BlackRock renewed permission to own major stakes of public utility companies, a win for the world's top asset manager over concerns that it wields too much influence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-wins-renewed-permission-own-big-utility-stakes-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4LLZJHZTJPM3AATPAXS72ELO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税给前景蒙上阴影，美国油田服务公司为盈利做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的财报很可能会让人们一窥全球三大油田服务公司如何应对美国关税反复无常以及近期油价下滑所带来的不确定性。【原文：Results next week will likely provide a peek into how the world's top three oilfield services companies are navigating the uncertainty fueled by the on-again, off-again U.S. tariffs, as well as a recent slide in oil prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oilfield-services-firms-brace-earnings-tariffs-cloud-outlook-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNT3FDSVZZLTRPO5S2JEEL6GAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:41:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在不断恶化的经济迷雾中艰难预测业务量]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易战给美国航空公司带来了自 COVID 大流行以来最大的不确定性。【原文：President Donald Trump's trade war has created the biggest uncertainty for U.S. airlines since the COVID pandemic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-struggle-forecast-their-business-worsening-economic-fog-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7OMMU2RLZI3BE4GFG3GX4QHUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大人 2 月份购买的美股数量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管加拿大和美国之间的关系十分紧张，但官方数据周四显示，随着美国股市创下历史新高，加拿大人在二月份购买了创纪录数量的美国股票。【原文：Although tensions between Canada and the United States are high, Canadians bought a record amount of American shares in February, as U.S. stock markets hit an all-time high, official data indicated on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadians-bought-record-amount-us-shares-february-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIPWFYQMC5PALJ2KXSPGKBPLIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场认为欧洲央行将在关税打击下进一步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）宣布降息，交易员们相信，如果贸易紧张局势对脆弱的经济造成影响，该央行将进一步放宽政策。【原文：Traders saw the all-clear on Thursday from the European Central Bank to bet on even steeper interest rate cuts ahead, confident the central bank will ease policy further if trade tensions dent a fragile economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/markets-see-door-wide-open-more-ecb-rate-cuts-tariff-hit-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIXUWXHPY5NCFLSLDVRKUYFU5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:26:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行将未来 3 个月金价目标上调至每盎司 3,500 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗研究公司周四将未来三个月的黄金价格目标从每盎司3,200美元上调至3,500美元，原因是在关税风险和市场疲软的背景下，中国的保险公司和避险资金开始买入黄金。【原文：Citi Research on Thursday raised its gold price target for the next three months to $3,500 per ounce from $3,200, driven by fresh gold buying from Chinese insurers and safe-haven flows amid tariff risks and market weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/citi-raises-gold-price-target-next-3-months-3500-per-ounce-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F2IN4ZARROZTBKKLKVBHVWGWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:17:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官将在听证会后决定 Citgo 母公司拍卖的起拍价]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周四举行的听证会上，债权人陈述了他们的观点，预计美国法院将在未来几天内确认或否决 Contrarian Funds 关联公司提出的 37 亿美元收购要约，该要约旨在为委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份的新一轮竞购设定底线。【原文：A U.S. court is expected to confirm or reject in coming days a $3.7 billion offer by an affiliate of Contrarian Funds aimed at setting a floor for a new bidding round for shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum, following a hearing where creditors made their arguments on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-decide-starting-bid-citgo-parent-auction-following-hearing-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJ7ZBK7I25LTVIUUATIYGERXR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:14:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美国市场充满挑战，欧莱雅仍实现销售额增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅周四公布，由于欧洲市场对面霜和香水的强劲需求帮助抵消了美国市场的挑战，该公司第一季度的同类销售额增长了 3.5%，超过了预期的放缓增长。【原文：L'Oreal reported a 3.5% rise in like-for-like first-quarter sales on Thursday, beating expectations for slower growth, as strong demand for its face creams and perfume in Europe helped counter challenging conditions in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loreal-sales-rise-35-first-quarter-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMICYVPNMFNRLOB7JDLNDHZMPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国茶叶连锁企业茶奇网在纳斯达克首秀表现强劲，估值达 62 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国茶叶连锁企业茶奇网周四在纳斯达克上市，股价上涨 21%，估值达到 62 亿美元。【原文：Chinese tea chain Chagee secured a valuation of $6.2 billion after its shares gained 21% in the Nasdaq debut on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinese-tea-chain-chagee-valued-62-billion-strong-nasdaq-debut-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAAZ43CSOVPUPDWOV7DI2CNHEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音在中国的交付工厂成为关税战的最新热点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，波音公司面临着对华出口关税影响的新问题，因为上海附近一家飞机完工厂里等待完工的喷气式飞机的命运成为焦点。【原文：Boeing faced new questions over the impact of tariffs on exports to China on Thursday as the spotlight fell on the fate of jets waiting at an aircraft completion plant near Shanghai.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-delivery-plant-china-latest-hot-spot-tariff-war-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUIOKO7YTZP2RKTFFZWDDSGVUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 15:47:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁格奥尔基耶娃称中美两国都有贸易不满]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周四表示，美国和中国都有贸易方面的不满，但重要的是，世界上最大的两个经济体应减少不确定性，并就更公平、基于规则的贸易体系达成一致。【原文：International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said on Thursday that the U.S. and China both have trade grievances, but it was important for the world's two largest economies to reduce uncertainty and agree on a fairer, rules-based trading system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/imfs-georgieva-says-both-us-china-have-trade-grievances-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TO4NPH4ICZLDFOFMTXYHDKOD4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 15:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美光调整业务部门，突出人工智能数据中心需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美光科技公司（Micron Technology）周四表示，该公司正在重新调整其业务部门，以专注于大型云计算提供商对其内存芯片与人工智能相关的需求。【原文：Micron Technology said on Thursday it is reshuffling its business segments to focus on the artificial intelligence-linked demand for its memory chips from large-scale cloud providers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/micron-rejigs-business-units-highlight-ai-data-center-demand-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RKIYM5AI5IWTCVCZEF2YOWCMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 15:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABB 将增加美国本地生产以降低关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士工程集团ABB首席执行官莫滕-维罗德（Morten Wierod）周四表示，ABB正在扩大其在美国和其他国家的本地生产，以减轻美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税的影响。【原文：Swiss engineering group ABB is expanding its local production in the United States and other countries to mitigate the impact of tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump, Chief Executive Morten Wierod said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/abb-increase-local-us-production-reduce-tariff-impact-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VASM23FY2ZLM3CVOTELI3VGEFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:47:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道摩根大通加强激进主义防御小组，聘请两位董事总经理]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部备忘录，摩根大通正在为其全球股东参与和 M&amp;A 资本市场部门招聘两名资深银行家，以加强该部门的业务，因为企业面临着来自世界各地企业煽动者越来越大的压力。【原文：JPMorgan Chase is hiring two veteran bankers in its global shareholder engagement and M&amp;A capital markets group, beefing up the business as corporations face increasing pressure from corporate agitators around the world, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-beefs-up-activism-defense-group-hires-two-managing-directors-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POF7LIK6CRJ5JMOZQNZXILYDG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官认定谷歌非法垄断在线广告技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周四表示，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司非法主导了两个在线广告技术市场，在美国提起的反垄断案中再次打击了这家科技巨头。【原文：Alphabet's Google illegally dominated two markets for online advertising technology, a federal judge said on Thursday, dealing another blow to the tech titan in an antitrust case brought by the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-judge-finds-google-holds-illegal-online-ad-tech-monopolies-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EF6DIWIUUNN7PEKQYQUK6TTB24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:43:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）预计增长预测将 "明显下调"，但不会出现全球衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周四表示，贸易紧张局势的加剧和全球贸易体系的全面转变将引发国际货币基金组织（IMF）经济预测的下调，但预计不会出现全球性衰退。【原文：Rising trade tensions and sweeping shifts in the global trading system will trigger downward revisions of the IMF's economic forecasts but no global recession is expected, IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-expects-notable-markdowns-growth-forecasts-no-global-recession-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGVVN732QRLM7NFBT7Z6UYIMPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国避险地位动摇，PIMCO看跌美元和国债]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国债券巨头 PIMCO 表示，美国贸易政策中的保护主义强化了降低美元和国债风险敞口的理由，而对外国债券市场的更大依赖变得更具吸引力。【原文：U.S. bond giant PIMCO said protectionism in U.S. trade policy strengthened the case for dialing down exposure to the U.S. dollar and Treasury bonds, while greater reliance on foreign bond markets had become more attractive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/pimco-bearish-dollar-treasuries-us-safe-haven-status-wavers-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO4WKF3E7NJM7M2QVEBD35FMCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁试图解雇美联储主席鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的解职 "来得不够快"，同时呼吁美国央行降息。【原文：U.S President Donald Trump said on Thursday that Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's termination "cannot come fast enough", while calling for the U.S. central bank to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-threatens-try-fire-fed-chief-powell-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFHYQ5ZRRVJNNIRUXLAQ3BMG3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[令主要央行头疼的关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税令全球经济前景黯淡，迫使各大央行重新评估下一步行动。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs have darkened the global economic backdrop, forcing big central banks to reassess their next steps.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-central-banks-graphic-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVEEXPY5JFJWTLQY24ZSTEKJZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:33:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司任命内部人士埃文-斯科特为新任首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司周四宣布财务总监赫苏斯-马拉维（Jesus Malave）离职，并任命内部人士埃文-斯科特（Evan Scott）为其继任者，即刻生效。【原文：Lockheed Martin on Thursday announced the departure of its finance chief, Jesus Malave, and named insider Evan Scott as his successor, effective immediately.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-martin-appoints-insider-evan-scott-new-cfo-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLBYLUTJMFP4NAYTEMLPOFVRJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯认为无需改变货币政策 - Fox Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周四表示，由于特朗普政府的关税可能会推高通胀、削弱经济增长并推高失业率，他认为近期没有必要改变央行的利率政策。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams said Thursday he sees no imminent need for a change in central bank interest rate policy as Trump administration tariffs are likely to drive up inflation, weaken growth and push up unemployment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-williams-sees-no-looming-need-change-monetary-policy-fox-business-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHAWKWKQ5BII3ACTADWJ2QG6HE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[收费收入强劲，支出减少，道富银行季度利润跃升 39]]></title><description><![CDATA[托管银行道富银行（State Street）周四公布的第一季度利润大增 39%，得益于管理客户资产的支出减少和费用增加。【原文：Custodian bank State Street on Thursday reported a 39% jump in first-quarter profit, benefitting from lower expenses and higher fees earned from managing client assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/state-streets-quarterly-profit-jumps-39-strong-fee-income-lower-expenses-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPCTSNQ4V5OELGNZOCBNCHYFL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:21:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空任命太阳之乡高管戴夫-戴维斯为新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国折扣航空公司精神航空（Spirit Airlines）周四表示，该公司已任命竞争对手太阳国航空公司（Sun Country）高管戴夫-戴维斯（Dave Davis）为新任首席执行官。【原文：U.S. discount carrier Spirit Airlines said on Thursday it has appointed rival Sun Country executive, Dave Davis, as its new CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-appoints-sun-country-executive-davis-new-ceo-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRE3SXKZ4NINBFDOPSOVMIDITU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡星展银行首席执行官告诉企业 "系好安全带 "应对关税不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡最大的银行星展集团（DBS Group）首席执行官陈苏山（Tan Su Shan）周四表示，企业必须做好准备，应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税所引发的剧烈波动和不确定性，并转变经营方式。【原文：The CEO of Singapore's biggest bank, DBS Group , Tan Su Shan, said on Thursday that businesses have to brace for heightened volatility and uncertainty triggered by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, and transform how they operate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ceo-singapores-dbs-tells-businesses-buckle-up-tariff-uncertainty-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TLIVFXRBZNSRKCHQLCYAVXTKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:15:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉加德在欧洲央行新闻发布会上发表评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行周四一年来第七次降息，希望支撑已经陷入困境的欧元区经济，因为美国关税将给欧元区经济带来巨大冲击。【原文：The European Central Bank cut interest rates for the seventh time in a year on Thursday, looking to prop up an already struggling euro zone economy that will take a large hit from U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/lagarde-comments-ecb-press-conference-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZVUCM4QDJLWBB3YJ35XPJ4QUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:13:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>