<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:37:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:37:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[埃利奥特增持股份后，英国石油公司股价创八月以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社援引消息人士的话报道埃利奥特管理公司（Elliott Management）已增持英国石油公司股票后，英国石油公司股价在周一早盘交易中最多上涨了 7%，达到 8 月份以来的最高点。【原文：Shares in oil major BP rose as much as 7% to their highest since August in early trade on Monday after Reuters reported Elliott Management had built a stake in the company, citing a source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bp-shares-hit-highest-since-august-after-elliott-builds-stake-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R453VW77MVONVL4U5N5ANXH44I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:20:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收关税，德国钢铁制造商股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将对所有进口钢铁和铝征收 25% 的新关税后，德国钢铁制造商蒂森克虏伯（Thyssenkrupp）和萨尔茨吉特（Salzgitter）的股票下跌。【原文：Shares in German steelmakers Thyssenkrupp and Salzgitter are down after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would slap new tariffs of 25% on all steel and aluminium imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-steelmakers-tumble-trump-threatens-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCGKVRO2Z5PFLPCTHJPRZ6HF7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子投资者德卡将投票反对吉姆-哈格曼-斯纳布担任董事长]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子股东德卡投资公司（Deka Investment）周一表示，将投票反对吉姆-哈格曼-斯纳布（Jim Hagemann Snabe）连任这家德国工程集团的董事长。【原文：Siemens shareholder Deka Investment will vote against the reelection of Jim Hagemann Snabe as chairman at the German engineering group, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siemens-investor-deka-vote-against-jim-hagemann-snabe-chairman-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTUX4Q7GDJJJFLY7VRMEAJAPPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 07:53:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康 1 月份营收同比增长 3.16%，第一季度增长强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约电子制造商、苹果公司最大的 iPhone 组装商台湾富士康周一发布报告称，其 1 月份收入同比增长 3.16%。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker and Apple's biggest iPhone assembler, reported on Monday that its January revenue rose 3.16% on year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-january-revenue-up-316-yy-sees-strong-growth-q1-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSEIFUW4CNL4RFBSNF6K4NBW3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 07:51:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受 1 月地震影响，台积电第一季度营收接近预期下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约芯片制造商台积电周一表示，其第一季度营收将接近预期目标的下限，因为该公司预计 1 月份震撼该岛的地震将带来 1.61 亿美元的影响。【原文：TSMC , the world's biggest contract chipmaker, said on Monday its first-quarter revenue would be closer to the lower end of its guidance, as it expects a $161 million impact from an earthquake that rocked the island in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-sees-q1-revenue-near-lower-end-guidance-january-earthquake-impact-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RL3ZGZ46ZLFVLM4N7FVEAVCKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 07:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对钢铁和铝征收关税令金属生产商感到不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）计划对所有进口到美国的钢材和铝材征收 25% 的新关税，这可能会扰乱金属贸易流动，从而在周一对亚洲生产商的股价造成影响。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's plan to impose new 25% tariffs on all imports of steel and aluminium into the United States weighed on shares of producers in Asia on Monday as it threatened to disrupt trade flows in the metals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-steel-aluminium-tariffs-rattle-makers-metals-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ND7KAGLEIJLYTK24MRBCSB755I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本资生堂称中国市场销售低迷导致年度利润骤降 73]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本化妆品巨头资生堂周一表示，由于中国市场销售低迷，其全年利润下降了 73%。【原文：Japanese cosmetics giant Shiseido said on Monday its full-year profit fell 73% amid sluggish sales in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/japans-shiseido-says-profit-plunges-73-amid-sluggish-sales-china-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7HK25R7MFMXLCMQKHFK4BF3VI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁拥有美国的债务？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府发行了近 36 万亿美元的债务，其债券是全球金融体系的基石。【原文：The U.S. government has nearly $36 trillion of debt on issue and its bonds are the bedrock of the global financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/who-owns-us-debt-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LP3K5BMCTBJJBMFEBO5D23LGGY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国的钢铁和铝从哪里来？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，他将在现有金属关税的基础上对所有进口到美国的钢铁和铝征收 25% 的关税，这是他贸易政策改革的又一次重大升级。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday he will introduce 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminum imports into the United States, on top of existing metals duties, in another major escalation of his trade policy overhaul.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/where-does-us-get-its-steel-aluminum-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJUHTFLTTNOPXL3A5PT7NAA43Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:14:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺基亚任命贾斯汀-霍塔德（Justin Hotard）为新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[芬兰诺基亚公司周一表示，该公司首席执行官佩卡-伦德马克（Pekka Lundmark）将卸任，并已任命贾斯汀-霍塔德（Justin Hotard）接替其职务。【原文：Finland's Nokia on Monday said its CEO Pekka Lundmark would step down and that it had appointed Justin Hotard to take over his role.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nokia-ceo-steps-down-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBHD4RRGERJT7H7MKR54IOHAIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标所有关税，所有时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXHHQLTH5VMLPKXIPKMJ6IY6YE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 05:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴黎人工智能峰会吸引世界各国领导人和首席执行官翘首技术浪潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界各国领导人和技术高管周一将在巴黎召开会议，讨论如何安全地拥抱人工智能。【原文：World leaders and technology executives are convening in Paris on Monday to discuss how to safely embrace artificial intelligence at a time of mounting resistance to heavy-handed red tape that businesses say stifles innovation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/paris-ai-summit-draws-world-leaders-ceos-eager-technology-wave-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52JOGTHATVIC7OQ6QSX2WN33YQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 05:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发出关税威胁后，铝因供应风险而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将对所有进口钢铁和铝征收 25% 的新关税之后，铝价在周一因供应风险而上涨。【原文：Aluminium prices rose on Monday due to supply risks after U.S. President Donald Trump said he was set to impose new 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminium imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/aluminium-rises-supply-risks-after-trump-tariff-threat-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLF6NFW3ERJ4DEXYWKKSGPJGOQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 04:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得益于外国投资回报，日本 2024 年经常账户盈余创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财政部周一公布的数据显示，日本去年的经常账户盈余跃升至创纪录水平，原因是日元走软提高了外国投资回报，从而帮助抵消了贸易逆差。【原文：Japan's current account surplus jumped to a record last year, data from the finance ministry showed on Monday, as a weaker yen boosted returns on foreign investments that helped to comfortably offset a trade deficit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-runs-record-current-account-surplus-2024-foreign-investment-returns-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KC5VZUXTRJNGPDC3WCE3WIUF7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:43:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾希望购买阿拉斯加天然气，以抵御美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾经济部周一表示，台湾对阿拉斯加的天然气 "相当感兴趣"，并将继续评估购买的可行性，因为台湾政府希望缩小与美国的贸易顺差并避免关税。【原文：Taiwan is "quite interested" in natural gas from Alaska and will continue to assess the feasibility of purchases, the economy ministry said on Monday, as the government looks to narrow the trade surplus with the United States and head off tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/taiwan-looks-buy-alaskan-natural-gas-seeks-head-off-us-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URZHI65EABKXBETTILVEZI3MR4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁特朗普称美国低等分币的时机已到]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周日在其社交媒体 "真相"（Truth）账户上发帖称，美国财政部已下令停止生产被称为 "便士 "的一美分硬币。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent has been ordered to cease production of the one-cent coin known as the penny, President Donald Trump said in a posting on his Truth Social media account on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/billionaire-trump-says-times-up-lowly-us-penny-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6EQK5WANJKB5JKCFWPYOB7C4A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚全球锂业公司寻求政府帮助，指控中国企图控制该公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚全球锂资源公司（Global Lithium Resources）正在向政府施压，要求在本周召开股东大会之前，制止中国投资者对其基础资产的收购企图。【原文：Australia's Global Lithium Resources is pressing the government to halt what it calls a takeover attempt by Chinese investors of its cornerstone asset ahead of a shareholder meeting this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australias-global-lithium-seeks-government-help-alleging-chinese-control-attempt-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRCMYK4OQNOTJM4OGTGA7UBPNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 02:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场对特朗普征收钢铝进口关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，他将在现有金属关税的基础上，对所有进口到美国的钢铁和铝征收25%的新关税。他还表示将在周二或周三宣布对等关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday he will introduce new 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminum imports into the U.S., on top of existing metals duties. He also said he will announce reciprocal tariffs on Tuesday or Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/markets-react-trumps-tariffs-steel-aluminium-imports-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIAIKEHXFNN6HHGYOWRJEPKAXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 02:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[控股股东结构可能发生变化，东风汽车股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商东风汽车表示，在重组过程中，公司控股股东结构可能会发生变化，随后东风汽车股价最高飙升 85.8%。【原文：Shares of Dongfeng Motor soared as much as 85.8% after the Chinese automaker flagged a possible change in the company's controlling shareholder structure amid a restructuring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shares-dongfeng-motor-jump-possible-change-controlling-shareholder-structure-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWGQK7C37ROMLP2R3MFJGX5VSU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:53:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因特朗普关税威胁而上涨，欧元接近两年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将对所有进口钢铁和铝征收25%的新关税后，美元周一走强，给欧元以及以大宗商品为主的澳元和新西兰元带来压力。【原文：The dollar firmed on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he was set to impose new 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminium imports, putting pressure on the euro and the commodity-focused Australian and New Zealand dollars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-gains-trump-tariff-threats-euro-near-2-year-low-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSYYRJRWFNP3TBMAOSNMWU6YVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:50:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚称其钢铁和铝出口为美国创造就业机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚贸易部长表示，澳大利亚对美国的钢铁和铝出口创造了 "高薪的美国工作"，并且是共同国防利益的关键。【原文：Australia's trade minister said its steel and aluminium exports to the U.S. create "good paying American jobs" and are key to shared defence interests, as Canberra presses Washington for an exemption to President Donald Trump's planned tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australia-says-its-steel-aluminium-exports-create-american-jobs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6377QCMSYRIHRFXOVJNNIW3HCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:49:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者权衡美国新关税措施，石油走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周一走高，尽管投资者正在权衡美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的最新关税威胁，这次是对所有进口钢铁和铝征收关税，这可能会抑制全球经济增长和能源需求。【原文：Oil prices ticked higher on Monday even as investors weighed U.S. President Donald Trump's latest tariff threat, this time on all steel and aluminium imports, which could dampen global economic growth and energy demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-ticks-higher-investors-weigh-new-us-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PN3J2N66VMQZDJCGK7TZ3AHDA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:41:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税有望促进澳大利亚博思格钢铁公司美国业务增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将宣布对所有进口钢铁和铝征收 25% 的关税后，博思格钢铁公司的股价在周一创下了两个月来的新高，这可能有利于这家澳大利亚钢铁制造商在美国的业务。【原文：Shares of BlueScope Steel hit a two-month high on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he will announce 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminum imports, which could benefit the Australian steelmaker's U.S operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australias-bluescope-steel-rises-hopes-trump-tariffs-boosting-its-us-ops-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MKBBQ23DBKM3ANXYCJE3NQIXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国出口中心义乌，贸易商对特朗普的关税避之唯恐不及]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日，中国出口制造业中心义乌的贸易商们对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国征收关税和采取的举措不以为然，一些贸易商表示，他们已做好准备来缓解这一打击。【原文：Traders in China's export manufacturing hub of Yiwu shrugged off U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs and moves against China on Sunday, with some saying they made preparations to soften the blow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-export-hub-yiwu-traders-shrug-off-trumps-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTGKBJJSTZKZ5IRDJTRW2OUNBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 01:09:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普谈关税，韩国钢铁企业股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将征收新关税后，韩国钢铁制造商的股票周一下跌。【原文：Shares of South Korean steelmakers dropped on Monday, after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would introduce new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/shares-south-korean-steelmakers-drop-trump-talks-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWR47WKRJFPHZORZ7SDRYR6J2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[T-Mobile 与 Starlink 开始大规模卫星连接测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[T-Mobile周日表示，该公司已开始大规模测试由SpaceX的Starlink提供的卫星对手机服务，这家美国无线运营商的目标是消除移动死角，并将连接扩展到偏远地区。【原文：T-Mobile said on Sunday it has started wide-scale testing of its satellite-to-cell service, powered by SpaceX's Starlink, as the U.S. wireless carrier aims to eliminate mobile dead zones and extend connectivity to remote areas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/t-mobile-starlink-start-wide-scale-testing-satellite-based-connectivity-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MMZJGJRTFMPBAGMKJBLW7GUBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国大陆蚕食份额，台湾传统芯片业思考未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[2015 年，台湾力晶科技公司与中国东部城市合肥达成协议，建立新的芯片代工厂，希望此举有助于更好地进入前景广阔的中国市场。【原文：When Taiwan's Powerchip Technology entered a deal with the eastern Chinese city of Hefei in 2015 to set up a new chip foundry, it hoped the move would help provide better access the promising Chinese market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-legacy-chip-industry-contemplates-future-china-eats-into-share-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKA3IG3YUZO7JGVGN2OPFXOO3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁拒绝就特朗普反对持有美国钢铁多数股权的声明发表评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新日铁公司周一拒绝就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于任何人不得拥有美国钢铁公司多数股权的声明发表评论。【原文：Japan's Nippon Steel on Monday declined to comment on U.S. President Donald Trump's statement that no one can have a majority stake in U.S. Steel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steel-declines-comment-trump-statement-opposing-majority-stake-us-steel-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5QQ7MTETVMSTOWXCTWCD3IXWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下滑，美元因关税威胁而攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）再次警告即将对包括钢铁和铝在内的产品征收关税，这一通胀举措可能会限制降息的空间，随后华尔街股票期货下跌，美元广泛上涨。【原文：Wall Street share futures fell and the dollar rose broadly on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump repeated warnings of imminent tariffs including on steel and aluminium, an inflationary move that could limit the scope for rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7KIW2BOEVKMDH3QBWAHSKGEKE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡星展银行第四季度净利润同比增长 10%，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡最大的银行星展集团周一向证券交易所提交的文件显示，由于商业账目和市场交易双双增长，该集团第四季度的净利润比去年同期增长了10%。【原文：DBS Group , Singapore's biggest bank, posted a 10% rise in net profit in the fourth quarter from a year earlier on the back of growth in both commercial book and markets trading, according to stock exchange filing on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/singapore-bank-dbs-fourth-quarter-net-profit-rises-10-year-2025-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZMHTH7EABOOZF3AFK5UX7A2PE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 22:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>