<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:40:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:40:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[网络中断后，Binance 服务开始恢复]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Binance 在 X 上发文称，亚马逊网络服务数据中心的一个临时问题暂时中断了该平台的订单和取款服务，此后，Binance 的服务已开始恢复和复原。【原文：Crypto exchange Binance's services have started to resume and recover after a temporary issue involving a Amazon Web Services data center temporarily disrupted the platform servicing orders and withdrawals, it said in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/binance-services-start-recover-after-network-interruption-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V46GYLYYIJORJGT4FFKOC77UX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:27:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，中国下令停止波音飞机的交付]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周二援引知情人士的话称，中国已下令其航空公司不再接收任何波音喷气式飞机，以回应美国对中国商品征收 145% 关税的决定。【原文：China has ordered its airlines not to take any further deliveries of Boeing jets in response to the U.S. decision to impose 145% tariffs on Chinese goods, Bloomberg News said on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/china-orders-halts-boeing-jet-deliveries-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYCRTHR4HRJW5CSQQIWNK6U3OQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国最大的贸易博览会上，出口商称美国市场被 "冻结 "了]]></title><description><![CDATA[Candice Li 说，华盛顿对中国商品加征 145% 的关税后，她的公司生产的医疗器械在美国的订单消失了。【原文：Candice Li says that after Washington raised tariffs on Chinese goods by 145%, U.S. orders for the medical devices her firm is making have vanished.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-largest-trade-fair-exporters-say-us-markets-are-frozen-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAIOKK6DORKAPJRRO45B2APUNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:14:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本竞争监督机构向谷歌发出停止令]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本竞争监督机构周二向 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司发出了停止和终止反竞争行为的命令，这是首次对美国科技巨头采取此类行动。【原文：Japan's competition watchdog issued a cease and desist order to Alphabet's Google on Tuesday for anticompetitive practices in the first such action against a U.S. tech giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/japan-competition-watchdog-issues-cease-desist-order-google-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPEPBURS25IUHAHEMWLB674NR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:24:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奢侈品巨头路威酩轩集团第一季度销售额不及预期，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的奢侈品集团路威酩轩集团（LVMH）公布的第一季度收入低于预期，该集团股价周二下滑。【原文：LVMH shares slid lower on Tuesday after the world's largest luxury group posted first quarter revenues that undershot expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lvmh-shares-slump-after-luxury-giants-q1-sales-miss-forecast-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMTFT3XRBZOVZKP6Z5HIPKSB64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行调查显示，全球投资者抛售美股的速度创下纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美银全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）周二表示，全球投资者在过去两个月中减持美股的数量创下历史新高，并认为引发全球经济衰退的贸易战是市场面临的最大风险、【原文：Global investors have slashed their holdings of U.S. stocks by a record amount in the past two months, and think a trade war that triggers global recession is the biggest risk for markets, BofA Global Research said on Tuesday,】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-investors-dump-holdings-us-stocks-record-pace-bofa-survey-says-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFR54KS2ZJMGDFHVYWAYHTDI4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚电信公司 U Mobile 将与中国华为和中兴通讯合作建设 5G 网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚移动数据服务公司 U Mobile 周二表示，将利用中国华为技术公司和中兴通讯的基础设施技术，推出马来西亚第二个 5G 网络。【原文：Malaysian mobile data service company U Mobile said on Tuesday it will use infrastructure technology from China's Huawei Technologies and ZTE to roll out Malaysia's second 5G network.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/malaysia-telco-u-mobile-partner-with-chinas-huawei-zte-5g-network-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDTY32GCFFKGLFVSOHMWZFSCCQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:22:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉扎德在阿布扎比设立金融咨询办事处，扩大在阿联酋的业务范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉扎德投资银行（Lazard）周二表示，将在阿联酋首都阿布扎比开设一家办事处，作为该投资银行在阿联酋的主要金融咨询中心，从而加强其在阿联酋的业务布局。【原文：Lazard is strengthening its footprint in the United Arab Emirates by opening an office in the capital city of Abu Dhabi which will serve as the investment bank's main financial advisory hub in the country, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/lazard-boosts-uae-footprint-with-financial-advisory-office-abu-dhabi-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C32WRWI4JFIGXMHDOJOS36UJGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Atlas Holdings 将以 3.47 亿美元收购纸币印刷商 De La Rue]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权公司 Atlas Holdings 周二表示，将以 2.63 亿英镑（3.471 亿美元）的价格收购英国纸币印刷商 De La Rue。【原文：U.S. private equity firm Atlas Holdings will buy British banknote printer De La Rue for 263 million pounds ($347.1 million), the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/banknote-printer-de-la-rue-be-bought-347-million-by-atlas-holdings-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UB6X7UHJKBO5XARKDLDAKMOI6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:10:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜尔斯道夫第一季度销售额略超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国消费品制造商拜尔斯道夫（Beiersdorf）周二公布的第一季度集团销售额略高于市场预期，这主要得益于其皮肤护理部门。【原文：German consumer goods maker Beiersdorf on Tuesday reported first-quarter group sales marginally ahead of market expectations, helped by its derma division.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/beiersdorf-reports-first-quarter-sales-marginally-ahead-expectations-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E47RRSRYCZO73KVUDCISEHHLUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:09:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价下跌令新兴市场原油出口国雪上加霜]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，主要由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税导致的原油价格暴跌将挤压新兴市场石油出口国的预算，而潜在的经济放缓也可能抑制进口国的任何收益。【原文：A steep drop in crude oil prices largely due to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs will squeeze budgets of emerging market oil exporters, analysts said, while the potential economic slowdown could also curb any benefits for importers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-price-drop-turns-up-heat-emerging-market-crude-exporters-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27PBVQ45ONPWFB4M7ULY3EPXA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:08:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[应用材料公司收购先进封装公司 BESI 9% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国计算机芯片设备供应商应用材料公司周一表示，已收购必益半导体工业公司（BESI）9%的股份。【原文：Applied Materials has bought a 9% stake in BE Semiconductor industries (BESI) , the U.S.-based computer chip equipment supplier said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/applied-materials-buys-9-stake-advanced-packaging-firm-besi-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MP4VVPVEDBOZZHORNFYPCDHJCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[导航专家 TomTom 因汽车技术销售而超出季度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰数字地图专家 TomTom 周二公布，由于汽车定位技术业务表现强于预期，其第一季度收入略有增长，超出预期。【原文：Dutch digital mapping specialist TomTom reported on Tuesday a marginal rise in its first-quarter revenue, beating expectations, supported by a stronger-than-anticipated performance in its automotive location technology business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/navigation-specialist-tomtom-beats-quarterly-revenue-forecast-auto-tech-sales-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JAG6NOB6NKLRISTFSQTPP4GRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:14:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税阴影笼罩，爱立信第一季度核心盈利增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱立信周二公布的第一季度核心盈利远好于预期，这得益于总收入的增加，这家电信设备制造商正在为来自其最大市场美国的关税影响做准备。【原文：Ericsson reported much better than expected first-quarter core earnings on Tuesday, helped by a higher gross income, as the telecoms equipment maker braces for the impact of tariffs from the United States, its biggest market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ericssons-core-earnings-rise-1st-quarter-trumps-tariffs-loom-large-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQ57NCCDLNNKNOHZNVZPAHECII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税不确定性为 ASML 盈利前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，计算机芯片设备制造商ASML公布第一季度财报，投资者将寻求美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）计划对半导体行业征收关税所带来的风险。【原文：Investors will seek clarity on the risks posed by tariffs U.S. President Donald Trump plans to impose on the semiconductor industry when computer chip equipment maker ASML reports first-quarter earnings on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tariffs-uncertainty-clouds-outlook-asmls-earnings-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGGZH3G7SFK4JKSHXINAJN4XTI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，受关税影响，日产将削减美国畅销车型的日本产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士表示，日产汽车将在5月至7月期间削减其在美国最畅销车型Rogue SUV在日本的产量，成为因美国新进口关税而改变生产计划的最新一家全球汽车制造商。【原文：Nissan will cut Japanese production of its top-selling U.S. model, the Rogue SUV, over May-July, said a person familiar with the matter, becoming the latest global automaker to alter manufacturing plans in response to new U.S. import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-cut-japanese-production-top-selling-us-model-due-tariffs-source-says-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TJZQ2MP4VPQDFA4JIVX7SUGFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 04:39:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价税收和关税成为关注焦点，救市反弹步履维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4GNVII36VK4VDLQ3DPCDL77OI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 04:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国智璞人工智能公司迈出上市第一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创公司智普人工智能（Zhipu AI）已启动首次公开募股的初步步骤，旨在成为中国首家上市的新兴人工智能公司。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence startup Zhipu AI has initiated preliminary steps toward an initial public offering, aiming to become the first of China's emerging AI companies to go public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinas-zhipu-ai-takes-initial-steps-an-ipo-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZZUC32K55L2HPYASW4HX2HJCI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 04:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国阴云密布的破产案暴露了外国投资者的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国破产法在执行方面的漏洞会使债权人容易受到不透明交易和恶意破产申请的影响，这些企业试图逃避付款义务。【原文：Gaps in enforcement of China's insolvency laws can leave creditors vulnerable to opaque dealings and malicious bankruptcy filings by firms seeking to evade payment obligations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-murky-bankruptcies-expose-hazards-foreign-investors-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F6NSXMF5RVOOREVYJRCOAWJ74Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 04:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚赌场运营商星际公司上半年亏损扩大，修复工作困难重重]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚陷入困境的赌场运营商星际娱乐公司（Star Entertainment）周二公布的上半年亏损超过了预期，尽管该公司已经启动了一揽子救援计划，但补救成本仍在继续增加。【原文：Australia's embattled casino operator Star Entertainment reported a bigger-than-expected first-half loss on Tuesday, as remediation costs continue to bite even though it has a rescue package already underway.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/casino-firm-star-entertainment-posts-bigger-than-expected-first-half-loss-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXQI3W4Q4NJEVIT6GODTJLS4OU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税有所缓和，亚洲股市上涨，债券持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市小幅走高，受助于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）暗示可能对已实施的汽车相关征税给予豁免后汽车公司股票的上涨。【原文：Asia shares edged slightly higher on Tuesday, helped by gains in auto companies after U.S. President Donald Trump suggested he might grant exemptions on auto-related levies already in place.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LS2UQDOZEBLHDAAQIZOXTW2ITU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元持稳，交易员努力应对关税不确定性和波动性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑欧元周二持稳，但仍接近上周创下的三年低点和兑日元的六个月低点，因为投资者难以理解美国关税的前后变化。【原文：The dollar was steady on Tuesday but stayed close to the three-year low against the euro and a six-month trough against the yen it hit last week as investors struggled to make sense of the back-and-forth changes on U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-steady-traders-grapple-with-tariff-uncertainty-volatility-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36M6R3WBUBJRDJRPCUZABY7L3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾模拟美国关税对半导体行业的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾经济部长周二表示，台湾将模拟美国对半导体行业征收关税的影响，并寻求与华盛顿就这一问题进行会谈。【原文：Taiwan will simulate the impact of any U.S. tariffs on the semiconductor industry and seek talks with Washington on the issue, the island's economy minister said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwan-simulate-impact-us-tariffs-semiconductor-sector-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B32WYV2HIFPNFA6YX2HGYDWWD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国指责美国发动 "先进 "网络攻击，点名指控美国国家安全局特工]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国东北城市哈尔滨警方指控美国国家安全局（NSA）在今年 2 月亚冬会期间发动了针对重要行业的 "先进 "网络攻击。【原文：Chinese police in the northeastern city of Harbin have accused the United States National Security Agency (NSA) of launching "advanced" cyberattacks during the Asian Winter Games in February, targeting essential industries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/chinas-harbin-says-us-launched-advanced-cyber-attacks-winter-games-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5ECFBV6AFMLPEYHIWNQEYWABY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 01:32:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行官员认为全球短期流动性不会大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行一位高级官员周二表示，全球金融市场正在经历波动，但短期流动性并未大幅下降。【原文：Global financial markets are experiencing volatility but not seeing a huge decline in short-term liquidity, a senior Bank of Japan official said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/boj-official-sees-no-huge-drop-global-short-term-liquidity-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUBTTHUIDJMYBBOQZG7SBSL3AI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 01:29:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD 首席执行官称准备在亚利桑那州开始芯片生产，在美国生产更多人工智能服务器]]></title><description><![CDATA[先进微设备公司（Advanced Micro Devices）首席执行官苏丽莎周二表示，该公司已准备好在亚利桑那州的工厂开始芯片生产，并肯定会在美国生产更多的人工智能服务器。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices' Chief Executive Lisa Su said on Tuesday that it is ready to start chip production at its Arizona plant and will certainly make more AI servers in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/amd-ceo-says-ready-start-chip-production-arizona-make-more-ai-servers-us-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVZBCLHCSFPBBPWXB4M5VWB6IA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 01:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国可能豁免汽车关税，中国原油进口回升，油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提出新的关税豁免以及中国原油进口因预期伊朗供应收紧而反弹的提振，油价攀升。【原文：Oil prices climbed in early trading on Tuesday, boosted by new tariff exemptions floated by President Donald Trump and a rebound in China crude oil imports in anticipation of tighter Iranian supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-potential-us-tariff-exemptions-cars-pick-up-china-crude-imports-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIEIVZT7LNOMNB6BALZINCIQMA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 01:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西金融科技公司 Meliuz 提出扩大比特币储备战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西金融科技公司Meliuz周一表示，它将提议扩大比特币储备战略，旨在使加密货币成为该公司金库中的主要战略资产。【原文：Brazilian fintech Meliuz said on Monday it will propose expanding its bitcoin reserves strategy, aiming to make the cryptocurrency the main strategic asset in the firm's treasury.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/brazil-fintech-meliuz-proposes-expanding-bitcoin-reserves-strategy-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YA56TCFLVRNFXBYAUB7K3ZR7UA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:30:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部贝森特支持阿根廷经济改革，并将目光投向中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）说，他周一会见了阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱，强调特朗普政府全力支持经济改革，这些改革正在将这个拉美国家 "从悬崖边上拉回来"。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said he met with Argentine President Javier Milei on Monday to underscore the Trump administration's full support for economic reforms that were bringing the Latin American country "back from the precipice."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-treasurys-bessent-backs-argentinas-economic-reforms-with-eye-china-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERISRIFUENKOBJFP2SRYGFGNUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:09:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储博斯蒂克：在不确定性迷雾中采取大胆举措并不明智]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周一表示，特朗普政府的关税和其他政策所带来的不确定性迷雾已使经济陷入 "大停顿"，家庭和企业没有进行大的投资，他建议美国央行在情况更加明朗之前应按兵不动。【原文：Atlanta Federal Reserve Bank President Raphael Bostic said on Monday the fog of uncertainty over the Trump administration's tariff and other policies has put the economy into a "big pause" where households and businesses aren't making big investments, and suggested the U.S. central bank should stay on hold until there is more clarity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-bostic-bold-moves-wouldnt-be-prudent-amid-fog-uncertainty-2025-04-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJQJL62F5ZPZLPIJCPFFX5V2OY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>