<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:04:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:04:31 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[数字医疗公司 Omada 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[虚拟慢性病护理提供商 Omada Health 已申请在美国上市，这是今年预计将有的一连串医疗保健公司上市中的最新一家。【原文：Virtual chronic care provider Omada Health has filed to go public in the United States, the latest in a string of healthcare listings expected this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/digital-health-company-omada-files-us-ipo-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5APZPWSXJJTBNYW6PUYPEWQY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:51:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美联储鲍曼从高盛、戴维斯-波尔克和 BPI 挑选员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美国联邦储备局局长米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）已从银行界挑选了三名工作人员。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman has picked three staffers from the banking world, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bowman-picks-staff-goldman-davis-polk-bpi-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZU33R4UMQRPD7AL4WWI4DBJVZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道贸易商称中国购买加拿大和澳大利亚小麦，因高温影响作物生长]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商说，最近几周，中国买家从澳大利亚和加拿大购买了 40 万至 50 万吨小麦，因为高温有可能损害中国农业中心地带的作物。【原文：Chinese buyers bought between 400,000 and 500,000 metric tons of wheat from Australia and Canada in recent weeks, traders said, as heat threatens to damage crops in China’s agricultural heartlands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-buys-canadian-australian-wheat-heat-hits-crop-traders-say-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVTVTKXYI5KQJCOMNIKA4TADXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长敦促国会在七月中旬前提高债务限额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五敦促国会在七月中旬之前提高联邦政府的债务限额，以避免出现将颠覆全球市场的违约事件。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Friday urged Congress to raise the federal government's debt limit by mid-July to avoid a default that would upend global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-treasury-secretary-urges-congress-raise-debt-limit-by-mid-july-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ME2FIZQMBIVDLEWMVB2T3C7UU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:32:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示，即使达成贸易协议，美国仍将维持 10%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五表示，即使在达成贸易协议后，美国仍将维持对进口商品征收 10%关税的基准，并补充说，如果有国家提供重要的贸易条件，则可能会有豁免。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Friday that the U.S. will maintain a baseline 10% tariff on imports even after trade deals are struck, adding there could be exemptions when countries offer significant trade terms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-us-will-maintain-10-tariffs-even-after-trade-deals-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWXWH74OERIIXJR7GRBIJ4DARE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对进口商用喷气机和发动机展开国家安全调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五表示，已对商用飞机、喷气发动机和零部件的进口展开国家安全调查。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Friday it has opened a national security investigation into the import of commercial aircraft, jet engines and parts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-opens-national-security-probe-into-imported-commercial-jets-engines-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QYYZFFZPNORJGCOLAMYNQBERY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:06:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，贝恩资本将以 100 亿美元的估值收购 PCI 制药公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，贝恩资本正在洽谈以 100 亿美元的估值收购合同药品制造商 PCI Pharma Services。【原文：Bain Capital is in talks to buy contract drug manufacturer PCI Pharma Services at a valuation of $10 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bain-capital-buy-pci-pharma-10-billion-valuation-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YMS3GH3ZNPO5K4QVJGIBWSWUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储主席哈马克希望在确定利率前获得明确数据，6 月前数据不会太多]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联储主席贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周五表示，美联储需要更多的时间来观察经济对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税和其他政策的反应，然后才能找出正确的应对措施。【原文：The Federal Reserve needs more time to see how the economy responds to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff and other policies before figuring out the right response, Cleveland Federal Reserve President Beth Hammack said on Friday, noting that much of the administration's sweeping agenda remains unclear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-hammack-wants-clear-data-before-moving-rates-not-much-data-by-june-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y3HLG7B7ZKRZISDE7IKG4PYTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税令贸易崩溃，集装箱航运公司缩减亚美航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[海运顾问说，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对世界头号出口国征收惩罚性关税，导致贸易崩溃，主要集装箱航运公司正在暂停至少六条中美之间的每周定期航线。【原文：Major container shipping companies are suspending at least six scheduled weekly routes between China and the United States as President Donald Trump's punishing tariffs on the world's top exporting country collapse trade, maritime consultants said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/container-shipping-firms-cull-asia-us-service-trump-tariffs-collapse-trade-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRHPQ5XKQZJGXB53YUVKMT7T7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：日内瓦公约]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EMACIGS7ZPYRMVWLLRTHI2SRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，新日铁高管下周将前往华盛顿推动美国钢铁交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士透露，新日铁副董事长森隆弘（Takahiro Mori）将于下周前往华盛顿，为该公司以 150 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司的交易争取批准。【原文：Nippon Steel Vice Chairman Takahiro Mori is headed to Washington next week as the company seeks to win approval of its $15 billion bid for U.S. Steel , a person familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nippon-steel-exec-headed-washington-next-week-push-us-steel-deal-source-says-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZATJEC2UZBNMXGWVCQ4ZZ4TROY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:29:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将签署不鼓励对监管违法行为进行刑事执法的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员周五告诉路透社，唐纳德-特朗普总统计划签署一项行政命令，阻止对监管违法行为的刑事执法，以打击联邦法规的过度刑事化。【原文：President Donald Trump plans to sign an executive order discouraging criminal enforcement of regulatory offenses, in a bid to combat the overcriminalization of federal regulations, a White House official told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-sign-order-discouraging-criminal-enforcement-regulatory-offenses-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JINRSHU6TBIUBE2PNFT3SL4BFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:59:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将允许在新英格兰海洋保护区进行商业捕鱼]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位白宫官员透露，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五将发布一项公告，恢复新英格兰附近一个海洋国家纪念碑的商业捕鱼权限。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday will issue a proclamation restoring commercial fishing access to a marine national monument off New England, according to a White House official.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/trump-allow-commercial-fishing-new-england-marine-monument-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7F26HEFQNJSTD4SOBUXCMWQ7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:57:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TechCrunch 报道：美国劳工部放弃对 Scale AI 的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[TechCrunch 周五援引一位直接熟悉此事的消息人士的话报道称，美国劳工部停止了对 Scale AI 是否遵守《公平劳动标准法案》的调查。【原文：The U.S. Department of Labor stopped its investigation into Scale AI's compliance with the Fair Labor Standards Act, TechCrunch reported on Friday, citing a source directly familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-department-labor-drops-investigation-into-scale-ai-techcrunch-reports-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4FDMW3ZDBNNDNNIUVQSA4GLF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:47:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席沃什强调降低利率的途径，并对美联储提出新的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-沃什（Kevin Warsh）显然是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）挑选的下一任美联储主席的热门人选，他周五提出了特朗普一再催促现任美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）降低政策利率的可能途径，并对美联储的货币政策行为提出了新的嘲讽。【原文：Kevin Warsh, an apparent frontrunner to be U.S. President Donald Trump's pick to be the next chair of the Federal Reserve, on Friday suggested a possible pathway to the lower policy rates that Trump has repeatedly pressed the current Fed Chair Jerome Powell to deliver, and delivered a fresh dig at the Fed's conduct of monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ex-feds-warsh-highlights-path-lower-rates-takes-fresh-dig-fed-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3S3UVTLWXVMHNA5MRKNTT7KRZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政策不确定性助推美国政府债务套期保值上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[过去一个月来，美国政府债务的投保成本明显攀升，而且仍然居高不下，原因是投资者对迫在眉睫的美国借贷限额政治辩论以及整体政策的不确定性忧心忡忡。【原文：The cost of insuring exposure to U.S. government debt has climbed noticeably over the past month and remains stubbornly high, as jittery investors brace for a looming U.S. borrowing-limit political debate as well as overall policy uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/policy-uncertainty-fuels-rise-us-government-debt-hedging-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWEEFNXD4BMADBI5XGEMRUXMIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 18:42:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，特朗普不会单方面降低对华关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五表示，美国不会在中国不做出让步的情况下单方面降低对中国商品的关税。几小时后，特朗普提出了将目前145%的关税税率降至80%的想法，双方正准备在瑞士举行会谈。【原文：President Donald Trump remains firm that the United States is not going to unilaterally reduce tariffs on Chinese goods without concessions from China, the White House said on Friday, hours after Trump floated the idea of reducing the current rate of 145% down to 80% as the two sides prepare for talks between in Switzerland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-wont-unilaterally-lower-china-tariffs-white-house-says-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSWWQ6DAYNIU3AJNCPLUPU7SA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者监督机构将废除 2011 年以来发布的数十项金融监督政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局周五发布了一份清单，列出了该机构计划废除的近 70 份政策和监管指导文件，这些文件可追溯到十多年前。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau issued a list on Friday of nearly 70 policy and regulatory guidance documents stretching back more than a decade that the agency plans to rescind.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-consumer-watchdog-scrap-scores-financial-oversight-policies-issued-since-2011-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKI27JMPHNIWLCPMVZX23DYBGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:36:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国油气钻机数降至 1 月以来最低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周削减了石油和天然气钻井平台的数量，创下 1 月份以来的最低水平。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating to their lowest since January, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-gas-rig-count-falls-lowest-since-january-baker-hughes-says-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6UBDON22BNYZNK6LL4HD5E4YM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼影业与罗斯曼续签电影集团首席执行官合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼电影公司周五表示，已与其电影集团董事长兼首席执行官汤姆-罗斯曼（Tom Rothman）签订了一份多年期续约合同。【原文：Sony Pictures said on Friday it had entered into a multi-year contract extension with its motion picture group's chairman and CEO, Tom Rothman.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/sony-pictures-extends-rothmans-contract-ceo-its-motion-picture-group-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCGCOMWOM5M3FPDFKEISIGGGRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:14:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人力资源技术公司 Rippling 以 168 亿美元的估值获得新一轮融资，暂无上市计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[人力资源软件初创公司 Rippling 周五表示，该公司在 G 轮融资中筹集了 4.5 亿美元，估值达 168 亿美元。【原文：HR software startup Rippling said on Friday it raised $450 million in a Series G funding round, valuing the company at $16.8 billion, as it expands its workforce management products and focuses on growing revenue globally over profitability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/hr-tech-firm-rippling-raises-new-funding-168-billion-valuation-no-ipo-plans-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAMZSH6WFJNEVHVE6JBFSDGW7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递董事会成员被任命为美国邮政局领导]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国邮政局董事会周五表示，在白宫施压要求前任局长于 3 月辞职后，任命联邦快递董事会成员、废物管理公司前首席执行官大卫-斯坦纳（David Steiner）为新任邮政局长。【原文：The U.S. Postal Service Board on Friday said it named David Steiner, a FedEx board member and former CEO of Waste Management, as the new postmaster general after the White House pressured the prior leader to resign in March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fedex-board-member-tapped-lead-us-postal-service-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35PC4DUHSFN43LJ2XSQIHRSHAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:53:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[壳牌在美国海湾佩尔迪多近海开发项目的两口油井面临延误]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国最大的近海生产商壳牌石油公司（Shell）表示，其在佩尔迪多近海开发项目中用于提高产量的两口油井被推迟到今年年底，而其中一口油井已于 3 月份投产。【原文：Shell , the top U.S. offshore producer, said this week that two of its wells to boost production at the Perdido offshore development were delayed to the end of the year, while one was brought online in March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-faces-delays-two-wells-offshore-perdido-development-us-gulf-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OFKIM5HERJN3KL6LRYBEWTJCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员以不确定性为由重申耐心政策立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周政策会议结束后，美联储第一波官员周五重申，由于特朗普政府的贸易政策加剧了经济前景的风险，当前的经济不确定性要求货币政策保持耐心。【原文：The first wave of Federal Reserve officials to weigh in after this week's policy meeting reiterated on Friday that the current economic uncertainty calls for monetary policy patience as Trump administration trade policy boosts risks to the outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-officials-citing-uncertainty-reiterate-patient-policy-stance-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQDAA5E6TJMHTBLUTHMEVYXE5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic 称，司法部在谷歌搜索中提出的建议可能会阻碍人工智能投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创企业、谷歌合作伙伴Anthropic周五在一份法庭文件中表示，美国司法部在针对Alphabet旗下谷歌公司的反垄断案中提出的建议可能会阻碍人工智能投资。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice's proposals in an antitrust case against Alphabet's Google risk chilling artificial intelligence investments, AI startup and Google partner Anthropic said in a court filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/anthropic-says-dojs-proposal-google-search-could-chill-ai-investment-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5QT3PRUMVNQLEGXYDABVALCQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家人制作人工智能视频，描述亚利桑那州男子在法庭上对凶手的陈述]]></title><description><![CDATA[本月，在亚利桑那州的一个法庭上，一个由人工智能创建的模拟死者向凶手发表了讲话，这似乎是美国法庭上的首例此类事件之一。【原文：A simulation of a dead man created by artificial intelligence addressed his killer in an Arizona court this month, in what appears to be one of the first such instances in a U.S. courtroom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/family-creates-ai-video-depict-arizona-man-addressing-his-killer-court-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URMBV66GNNKSDGAGK4GQZ7QVKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:27:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国油田巨头为艰难时期做好准备，因为价格下滑令生产商感到不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国顶级油田服务公司已经发出信号，随着近期油价下滑促使生产商减少钻探活动并重新考虑预算，未来一段时期将充满挑战。【原文：Top U.S. oilfield service firms have signaled a challenging period ahead as a recent slide in oil prices pushes producers to temper their drilling activity and rethink their budgets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oilfield-giants-brace-tough-times-price-slide-rattles-producers-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JK5HFQKSKJKMFBQWRGMINIHZX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:57:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃勒表示，美联储的独立结构已证明其价值]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）周五表示，美联储理事会的结构 "经受住了时间的考验"，应该予以保留。【原文：The structure of the Federal Reserve's Board of Governors, with members who cannot be fired over policy disputes and serve for periods staggered across presidential terms, has "stood the test of time" and should be preserved, Fed Governor Christopher Waller said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-independent-structure-has-proved-its-worth-waller-says-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQFEQFETUZOX3GZBIL4GZQXAPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌以 5000 万美元和解黑人员工种族偏见诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌同意支付 5000 万美元，以解决一起指控该搜索引擎公司对黑人员工存在系统性种族偏见的诉讼。【原文：Google agreed to pay $50 million to settle a lawsuit accusing the search engine company of systemic racial bias against Black employees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/google-settles-black-employees-racial-bias-lawsuit-50-million-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUTPCD2ZURL2RHKHKH5Z2WLIPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:31:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国邮政公布季度净亏损 33 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国邮政服务公司周五报告称，在截至 3 月 31 日的三个月中，该公司净亏损 33 亿美元，亏损原因是该公司继续提高邮票价格并寻求削减成本的方法。【原文：The U.S. Postal Service on Friday reported a net loss of $3.3 billion for the three months ending March 31 as the money-losing agency continues to hike stamp prices and look at ways to cut costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-postal-service-reports-33-billion-quarterly-net-loss-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QYLSWZVIVLZHMGUX2535C2SPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:45:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>