<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:10:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:10:25 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥将首都机场的部分航班时刻从墨西哥航空公司移交给美国航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）周一表示，墨西哥航空公司已同意将该国繁忙的首都机场的部分航班时段移交给美国航空公司，而两国之间正在就航班分配问题争执不休。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Monday that Mexican airlines had agreed to hand over some flight slots at the nation's busy capital airport to U.S. carriers, amid an ongoing spat between the countries over flight distribution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-hands-over-some-flight-slots-capital-airport-mexican-airlines-us-carriers-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">564EY2GSBFIA3GSSMOUIRB7ZI4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉赢得撤销黑人工厂工人种族偏见集体诉讼的竞标]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州的一名法官裁定，特斯拉旗舰装配厂的 6000 名黑人工人不能就所谓的种族骚扰提起集体诉讼，这推翻了之前的裁决，是首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的电动汽车制造商取得的一项重大胜利。【原文：A California state judge has ruled that 6,000 Black workers at Tesla's flagship assembly plant cannot sue over alleged racial harassment as a class, reversing an earlier ruling in a major victory for CEO Elon Musk's electric vehicle maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tesla-wins-bid-undo-race-bias-class-action-by-black-factory-workers-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AX2A6FYITFIQ5ESQJMSSDEAITM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月建筑支出反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于较高的抵押贷款利率继续拖累独户住宅的建设，美国建筑支出在 8 月份意外反弹，这很可能是受房屋翻新的推动。【原文：U.S. construction spending unexpectedly rebounded in August, likely lifted by home renovations as higher mortgage rates continued to weigh on single-family homebuilding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-construction-spending-rebounds-august-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BFU2EEHHNMXBKMY62HLBZAUZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Celero 从 Alphabet 的 CapitalG 基金和其他机构融资 1.4 亿美元，用于开发人工智能网络芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[由网络行业资深人士创办的美国初创公司 Celero Communications 周一表示，该公司已筹集到 1.4 亿美元资金，用于制造一种芯片，这种芯片将有助于跨越遥远的距离连接人工智能数据中心。【原文：Celero Communications, a U.S. startup founded by networking industry veterans, on Monday said it has raised $140 million to build a chip that will help link artificial intelligence data centers across vast distances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/celero-raises-140-million-alphabets-capitalg-fund-others-ai-networking-chip-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPBVJEPBRNKEHEW2OYPWNHSPPY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广播公司辛克莱增持竞争对手斯克里普斯股份，力促合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国广播公司辛克莱（Sinclair）周一披露了持有较小的竞争对手斯克里普斯公司（E.W. Scripps）8.2%股份的消息，并表示已就合并两家公司的交易进行了数月谈判。【原文：U.S. broadcaster Sinclair on Monday disclosed an 8.2% stake in smaller rival E.W. Scripps and said it has been in talks for months about a deal that would combine the companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/broadcaster-sinclair-builds-stake-rival-scripps-presses-merger-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SASAJ5555NNFHHEGCJPHUJL5JU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国指责 Vinted 未能防止未成年人访问成人内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国儿童保护机构负责人萨拉-埃尔-海瑞（Sarah El Hairy）要求监管机构调查二手服装市场 Vinted，因为它未能阻止未成年人访问成人内容，这是法国针对电子商务巨头采取的又一举措。【原文：France's child protection agency chief Sarah El Hairy has asked the regulator to investigate second-hand clothes marketplace Vinted for failing to prevent minors accessing adult content, in another move against e-commerce giants in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/france-targets-vinted-failure-prevent-underage-access-adult-content-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVP75W2LQ5LFNPTGO4WJBMEJ5E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:52:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰斐逊：美联储需缓慢推进进一步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储副主席菲利普-杰斐逊（Philip Jefferson）周一表示，美国央行需要 "缓慢推进 "任何进一步的降息措施，因为其放松政策的水平很可能会停止对通胀的下行压力。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson said on Monday the U.S. central bank needs to "proceed slowly" with any further interest rate cuts as it eases policy towards a level that would likely stop putting downward pressure on inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-needs-move-slowly-with-further-rate-cuts-jefferson-says-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFBEM26JYVNF7IVTKV6ZM2ABUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:33:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，亚马逊寻求通过出售美国债券融资 120 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周一援引知情人士的话报道称，亚马逊正寻求从公司债券市场融资约 120 亿美元，这是亚马逊约三年来首次以美元进行此类交易。【原文：Amazon is looking to raise about $12 billion from the corporate bond market in its first such deal in U.S. dollars in about three years, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-seeks-raise-12-billion-us-bond-sale-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4ITTKS2ZBKUBC3Z456JZEWRYQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特将在亚马逊上销售二手车，加入现代汽车的行列]]></title><description><![CDATA[从本周一开始，亚马逊的购物者可以在电子商务平台上浏览和购买福特汽车的汽车，这是继现代汽车之后，又一家为希望避开经销商地段的客户提供在线选择的公司。【原文：Amazon shoppers can browse and buy Ford Motor vehicles on the e-commerce platform starting on Monday, joining Hyundai in adding online options for customers who want to avoid dealership lots.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-sell-used-vehicles-amazon-joining-hyundai-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAPJUCYY6ZOQPKOY2IVZP4DVOQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，彼得-蒂尔的基金在第三季度减持了英伟达股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份监管文件显示，科技亿万富翁彼得-蒂尔（Peter Thiel）的对冲基金在第三季度出售了其在英伟达（Nvidia）公司的全部股份，这加剧了人们对人工智能泡沫的担忧。【原文：Tech billionaire Peter Thiel's hedge fund has sold off its entire stake in Nvidia during the third quarter, a regulatory filing showed, intensifying worries of an artificial intelligence bubble.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/peter-thiels-fund-offloaded-nvidia-stake-third-quarter-filing-shows-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SZ5ERDTGVKEVGGFFY6H625KHE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 将在新协议中购买 PayPal 在欧洲的 BNPL 贷款，金额高达 754 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[PayPal 和 KKR 周一表示，双方续签了合作协议，投资巨头将购买这家支付服务提供商在欧洲的 650 亿欧元（约合 754 亿美元）"先买后付 "贷款。【原文：PayPal and KKR have renewed their partnership that will see the investment giant purchase up to 65 billion euros ($75.4 billion) of the payments provider's European buy now, pay later loans, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kkr-buy-up-754-billion-paypals-european-bnpl-loans-renewed-deal-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLAOAO4HQRKG7GD3QLFRJJTWLU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:46:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫顾问哈塞特称就业市场信号不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周一表示，就业市场的信号喜忧参半，劳动力市场可能正在放缓。【原文：White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett on Monday said there have been mixed signals in the job market, and that the labor market could be slowing down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/white-house-adviser-hassett-says-there-have-been-mixed-signals-job-market-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G246IOMF6BIGPLWNPGBCKF7KYQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:39:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克公司在 Cidara 实验性流感药物中看到了超过 50 亿美元的商机]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司周一表示，预计 Cidara Therapeutics 公司的试验性流感药物将带来超过 50 亿美元的商业机会，而且预计该药物在上市前无需经过美国疾控中心疫苗顾问小组的审查。【原文：Merck said on Monday it expects a commercial opportunity exceeding $5 billion from Cidara Therapeutics' experimental flu drug, and does not anticipate it to require a review by the U.S. CDC's vaccine advisory panel before launch.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-expects-over-5-billion-commercial-opportunity-cidaras-flu-drug-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDKIOXXORBJCZAIXUA7INQMQFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银集团在有关美国可能采取行动的谈判报道后重申瑞士基地的地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，瑞银集团主席科尔姆-凯莱赫（Colm Kelleher）和美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）曾私下讨论过将瑞银总部迁往美国的事宜，对此瑞银集团周一表示，希望继续在瑞士开展业务。【原文：UBS said on Monday it wants to continue operating from Switzerland in response to a report that UBS chair Colm Kelleher and U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent had privately discussed moving the bank's headquarters to the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-reaffirms-swiss-base-after-report-talks-possible-us-move-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5XBM2LYUBPLVIEYKM6FZSOZYU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:26:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[J&J 将以 30.5 亿美元收购癌症疗法开发商 Halda Therapeutics]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司周一表示，将以 30.5 亿美元现金收购私人控股的 Halda Therapeutics 公司，从而扩大该医疗技术集团在实体瘤和前列腺癌治疗领域的业务。【原文：Johnson & Johnson said on Monday it would buy privately held Halda Therapeutics for $3.05 billion in cash, expanding the medtech conglomerate's presence in solid tumors and prostate cancer treatments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/jj-buy-cancer-therapy-developer-halda-therapeutics-305-billion-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZ7V2RRFBJMK7M7MLEPXP5PUOA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:07:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Novo Nordisk rolls out $349 Wegovy cash price ahead of plan]]></title><description><![CDATA[Novo Nordisk said on Monday it has begun selling its popular weight-loss drug Wegovy for $349 a month to cash payers, months ahead of the timeline set out with the Trump administration.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-rolls-out-349-wegovy-cash-price-ahead-plan-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJNFXWYEFZL4JOEJFSPSJ4CDTA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:55:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China's C919, rival to Boeing and Airbus, makes debut display outside Asia]]></title><description><![CDATA[China staged a Middle East debut for its C919 jetliner with a flying display at the Dubai Airshow on Monday, its first outside East Asia, as it showcases plans to compete with Airbus and Boeing.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-c919-rival-boeing-airbus-makes-debut-display-outside-asia-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56TAIFOSQVKDDNIFNAHI3RQ3VQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[气泡袋制造商希悦尔将以 103 亿美元的 CD&R 交易实现私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国包装公司希悦尔公司（Sealed Air Corp）周一表示，同意被私募股权公司 CD&amp;R 以 103 亿美元（包括债务）的价格收购，这笔交易将使该公司退出股市。【原文：U.S. packaging company Sealed Air Corp said on Monday it agreed to be bought by private equity firm CD&amp;R for $10.3 billion, including debt, in a deal that will take the company off the stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/sealed-air-be-bought-by-cdr-103-billion-deal-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6Y67HMPYUJPZPPLCM3Q7R6XVEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:06:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，杰夫-贝索斯将共同领导人工智能初创公司，这是他自亚马逊之后首次担任运营职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周一报道，杰夫-贝索斯（Jeff Bezos）将担任一家新成立的人工智能初创公司的联合首席执行官，该公司专注于人工智能在计算机、汽车和航天器的工程和制造领域的应用。【原文：Jeff Bezos will serve as co-chief executive officer of a new artificial intelligence startup that focuses on AI for engineering and manufacturing of computers, automobiles and spacecraft, the New York Times reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/jeff-bezos-co-lead-ai-startup-first-operational-role-since-amazon-nyt-reports-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJSQSFA35BPUFFYZROANC63MB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:49:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商新鹏汽车预计第四季度收入疲软 竞争激烈]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商新鹏汽车周一预计第四季度营收将低于预期，因为在全球最大的汽车市场上，旷日持久的价格战和愈演愈烈的竞争有可能导致其增长放缓。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle maker XPeng forecast fourth-quarter revenue below estimates on Monday, as a prolonged price war and intensifying competition in the world's largest auto market threaten to slow its growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-ev-maker-xpeng-forecasts-weak-fourth-quarter-revenue-amid-fierce-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Y6TCZYUMRLZLLFW4VTBTSTHGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：英伟达和数据下滑前恢复平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOTZOU6Z2NIZZG3HMAOG43XYBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:45:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利投票结果显示极右翼势力强劲，为市场谨慎反弹奠定基础]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师周一表示，智利总统选举的第一轮投票结果应该会对比索、股票和债券产生积极影响，预计这有可能为更多有利于市场的举措铺平道路。【原文：The outcome of the first-round vote in Chile's presidential election should be positive for the peso, stocks and bonds, analysts said on Monday, expecting this could potentially pave the way for more market-friendly initiatives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chile-vote-sets-stage-cautious-market-rally-strong-far-right-showing-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPXWLXXMC5LTHBLNQ2CNUNNO2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:44:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院将考虑恢复泰诺与自闭症案件的审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院预计将于周一听取寻求重启泰诺诉讼的家庭的辩论，此前特朗普政府公开宣传他们的主张，即这种流行的止痛药与儿童自闭症有关。【原文：A U.S. appeals court is expected to hear arguments on Monday from families seeking to revive their lawsuits over Tylenol, after the Trump administration publicly promoted their claims that the popular painkiller is linked to autism in children.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-appeals-court-weigh-reviving-cases-over-tylenol-autism-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMTXQHMDCJPD5MVGZN4CCUCSSM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[散户投资者购买美国股市下跌股票的信念减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[散户投资者对美国股市反弹能力的信心有减弱的迹象，市场数据和分析师的观察都表明，他们逢低买入的热情正在减退。【原文：Retail investors are showing signs of waning confidence in the U.S. stock market's ability to rebound, with market data and analysts' observations both indicating an ebb in their enthusiasm about buying dips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retail-investors-show-less-conviction-buying-us-stock-market-dips-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OULHORXKRN63EMH4WWP5EMU3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GMI Cloud 将在台湾建造价值 5 亿美元的人工智能数据中心，采用 Nvidia 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国云服务提供商 GMI Cloud 周一表示，在美国芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）的支持下，该公司将在台湾建立一个价值 5 亿美元的人工智能数据中心。【原文：U.S.-based cloud services provider GMI Cloud said on Monday it will build a $500 million artificial intelligence data centre in Taiwan with the support of U.S. chipmaker Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/gmi-cloud-build-500-million-ai-data-centre-in-taiwan-with-nvidia-chips-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K3ODPJIC7VJPZEEGZ7YGGXP6P4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场等待英伟达财报和政府数据，美股期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街主要股指期货周一走高，为包括人工智能巨头英伟达（Nvidia）财报和政府数据发布在内的密集一周拉开了序幕，而在伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）披露持有该公司股份后，Alphabet跳涨。【原文：Futures for Wall Street's main indexes were higher on Monday, kicking off a packed week that includes AI giant Nvidia's earnings and resumption of government data releases, while Alphabet jumped after Berkshire Hathaway disclosed a stake in the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-rise-markets-await-nvidia-earnings-government-data-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PDSKZNLFVPNXEO2LT5V3CHOWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国电力集团与 OpCore 公司将在法国开发价值 40 亿欧元的数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国公用事业公司 EDF 和电信集团 Iliad 与 InfraVia Capital Partners 的合资企业 OpCore 周一表示，双方已就开发一个超大规模数据中心进行了独家谈判。【原文：French utility EDF and OpCore, a joint venture between telecoms group Iliad and InfraVia Capital Partners, have entered into exclusive negotiations to develop a hyperscale data centre, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/edf-opcore-develop-4-billion-euros-data-centre-france-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QOCCUC2CVOGHN6KGNIES3LYXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度监管机构将在法庭上拒绝简街的数据请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解此事的消息人士称，印度市场监管机构本周将向法院表示，在美国公司就一项证券交易禁令提起上诉后，该机构认为没有理由向简街公司公布更多数据和文件。【原文：India's markets regulator will tell a court this week that it sees no reason to release additional data and documents to Jane Street, two sources with direct knowledge of the matter said, after the U.S. firm appealed a securities trading ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-regulator-decline-jane-street-data-request-court-sources-say-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ6Z525SCVLW5BWWFRYOXZ66ZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔披露 49 亿美元持股后，谷歌母公司 Alphabet 股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）披露持有这家科技巨头的股份后，Alphabet 的股价在周一盘前交易中上涨了 5.5%，这可能是巴菲特领导下的这家企业集团最后的重大举措之一。【原文：Alphabet's shares rose 5.5% in premarket trading on Monday after Berkshire Hathaway disclosed a stake in the tech giant, marking what could be one of the final major moves by the conglomerate under the leadership of Warren Buffett.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-parent-alphabets-shares-rally-after-berkshire-reveals-49-billion-stake-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOTND6LALVI3DDKRHN6THW4KJQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 09:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[入侵奥巴马账户的英国推特黑客被勒令偿还 540 万美元比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国检察官周一表示，一名因 2020 年推特（Twitter）黑客攻击事件而被定罪的男子已被勒令偿还价值 410 万英镑（约合 540 万美元）的比特币。【原文：A man convicted over a 2020 Twitter hack that compromised accounts of high-profile figures including former U.S. President Barack Obama has been ordered to repay 4.1 million pounds ($5.40 million) worth of Bitcoin, British prosecutors said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-twitter-hacker-who-breached-obama-accounts-ordered-repay-41-million-pounds-2025-11-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWRKLHFJSNNEBF5L7OC7XLMDEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 09:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>