<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:05:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:05:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美联储鹰派再现，国债收紧]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CR26MWJI5RONZJYMJHMLPLU64Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，银行游说监管机构制定国家标准，以遏制州政府的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士称，美国银行正在向货币监理署（Office of the Comptroller of the Currency）请愿，要求制定提供银行服务的国家标准，以凌驾于各州的规定之上。
 这些消息人士在私下会谈时拒绝透露身份，他们说，特别是大型银行，正在游说制定统一的美国法规，概述它们如何发放贷款、发行债券或提供投资银行服务，或评估反洗钱风险，同时限制州政府对其业务的权力。
 路透社首次报道的这一重新推动国家标准的举措，是银行业为在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府下锁定更有利规则而做出的全面努力的一部分。
 消息人士称，这些变化将使贷款机构更容易运营。这些修改还将削弱各州通过所谓的 "去银行化"（debanking）规则干扰银行运营的权力，"去银行化 "是指银行基于政治或宗教信仰拒绝为客户提供服务。
 此前，个别州曾因贷款人在枪支、气候变化、多样性和其他社会问题上的政策而惩罚银行并禁止其开展业务。【原文：U.S. banks are petitioning the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency to seek national standards for providing banking services that would override state-imposed rules, three sources familiar with the matter said.
 Large banks, in particular, are lobbying for uniform U.S. regulations outlining how they can make loans, issue bonds or provide investment banking services, or assess anti-money laundering risks while curbing state powers over their operations, said the sources, who declined to be identified while discussing private talks.
 The renewed push for national standards, which is being reported by Reuters for the first time, is part of a sweeping effort by the banking industry to lock in more favorable rules under U.S. President Donald Trump's administration.
 The changes would make it easier for lenders to operate, the sources said. They would also curtail states' power to disrupt banks' operations with rules on so-called "debanking," a practice in which banks allegedly deny services to customers based on political or religious beliefs.
 Individual states have previously punished banks and barred them from doing business based on lenders' policies on guns, climate change, diversity and other social issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/banks-lobby-regulators-national-standards-curb-state-influence-sources-say-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYQ5U2MRYBO5ZLY3JN4DWPLDT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:34:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美国科技股动荡不安，投资者聚焦英伟达业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技股的震荡提高了英伟达公司（Nvidia Corp）周三公布季度业绩的风险，这家半导体巨头的财报将对炙手可热的人工智能交易构成关键考验。【原文：A wobble in U.S. technology shares has raised the stakes for Nvidia Corp's quarterly results on Wednesday, with earnings from the semiconductor giant posing a crucial test for the scorching AI trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-zero-nvidia-results-us-tech-stocks-waver-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHALUE4GFJKD5GELYXBN6DLNP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cenovus Energy 将以 69.3 亿加元收购 MEG Energy]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大石油生产商 MEG Energy 周五表示，该公司已同意被更大的同行 Cenovus Energy 以现金加股票的方式收购，交易价值 69.3 亿加元，从而创建加拿大最大的油砂公司之一。【原文：Canadian oil producer MEG Energy said on Friday it has agreed to be acquired by larger peer Cenovus Energy in a cash-and-stock deal worth C$6.93 billion, to create one of the largest oil sands companies in Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/cenovus-energy-acquire-meg-energy-c693-billion-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZOOGTZDMJLHXOMG5W7OO77KVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰克逊霍尔会议前聚焦美国各行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）将在杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）研讨会上发表讲话，届时华尔街将寻求9月降息的确认，这对市场尤其是对利率敏感的行业来说可能是一个关键时刻。【原文：Wall Street will search for confirmation of a September interest rate cut when Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell speaks at the Jackson Hole symposium on Friday, a potentially pivotal moment for the market and rate-sensitive sectors in particular.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-sectors-spotlight-ahead-feds-jackson-hole-gathering-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAQIL65NUJMY3BB2XYLOGNF5SM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通同意向马来西亚支付 3.3 亿美元以解决 1MDB 问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通与马来西亚政府双方周五表示，摩根大通将向马来西亚政府支付 3.3 亿美元，作为解决其在国家基金 1MDB 数十亿美元丑闻中所扮演角色的所有相关事宜的和解协议的一部分。【原文：JPMorgan Chase will pay the Malaysian government $330 million as part of a settlement to resolve all matters related to its role in the multi-billion dollar scandal at state fund 1MDB, both parties said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/jpmorgan-agrees-pay-malaysia-330-million-settle-1mdb-issues-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBRSMMU2JFMSBD746PIKS4PTXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克着眼中国发展，以户外运动改革为中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克将于本周一推出一款新的越野跑鞋，以此拉开进军蓬勃发展的户外休闲市场的序幕，这将考验耐克能否将一个鲜为人知的子品牌打造成一个有意义的增长引擎。【原文：Nike's push into the booming outdoor recreation market — which will kick off on Monday with the launch of a new trail running shoe — will test whether it can turn a little-known sub-brand into a meaningful growth engine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nike-eyes-china-growth-with-outdoor-sports-revamp-center-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQRLZVVZEZNUXINPAXYZWQDIVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加航工会违抗加拿大政府命令可能会使工人更加大胆]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府去年曾四次出面援助七家公司，利用《劳动法》的一项模糊条款制止了罢工。然而，由于加拿大航空公司的空乘人员拒绝服从，罢工持续了三天，周日的类似法令宣告失败。【原文：Canada's government stepped in four times to aid seven companies last year, stopping strikes using an obscure Labour Code provision. A similar decree on Sunday failed, however, as Air Canada's flight attendants refused to obey and stayed on strike for three days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-canada-unions-defiance-canadian-government-order-could-embolden-workers-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBTJLILXENOINMG4XIQX3J3YO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在白宫的注视下，美联储鲍威尔将暗示是否降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周五将在杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）年度经济会议上发表演讲，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对央行施加了前所未有的压力，但喜忧参半的经济数据可能会使鲍威尔走向中间立场，从而使一些重大问题悬而未决。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's speech to the annual Jackson Hole economic conference on Friday comes amid unprecedented pressure on the central bank from President Donald Trump, but mixed economic data may pull Powell toward a middle ground that leaves major questions unresolved.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/with-white-house-watching-feds-powell-hint-yes-or-no-rate-cuts-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHVMGAU36BNHLA4QMM5TF4K2HM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Dream11、顶级游戏应用程序在禁令之后停止了基于金钱的游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度议会周四通过禁令后，印度的一些顶级手机游戏应用程序暂停了真钱游戏，这威胁到了这个曾预计到 2029 年将达到 36 亿美元的行业的未来。【原文：Some of India's top mobile gaming apps have suspended real-money games after parliament passed a ban on Thursday, threatening the future of a sector once projected to hit $3.6 billion by 2029.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-dream11-top-gaming-apps-halt-money-based-games-after-ban-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3ZDR5VVLFK5RP6LVOICIRVQQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔杰克逊霍尔演讲前美国股指期货走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在杰克逊霍尔经济研讨会（Jackson Hole Economic Symposium）上发表讲话之前，周五与华尔街主要股指挂钩的期货价格走高。【原文：Future tied to Wall Street's main stock indexes inched higher on Friday in the run-up to Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's speech at the Jackson Hole Economic Symposium, which would shed more light on the interest-rate path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-edge-higher-ahead-powells-jackson-hole-speech-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56XSNKVUYZPJTFRMSK457TZONM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 09:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴伐利亚北欧公司收入超出预期，收购竞标即将启动]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴伐利亚北欧公司（Bavarian Nordic）周五公布的第二季度收入高于预期，原因是其旅行健康和公共防备业务表现强劲。【原文：Bavarian Nordic , subject of a takeover offer valuing the vaccine maker at about 19 billion Danish crowns ($3 billion), reported a higher than expected revenue for the second quarter on Friday, citing a strong performance in both its travel health and public preparedness businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bavarian-nordic-beats-revenue-expectations-launch-takeover-bid-nears-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP4CB7C5VJL4LOATXYGNO6UNI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 09:44:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 DHL 与同行一道限制美国包裹服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国邮政服务集团 DHL 周五表示，将暂停向美国运送企业标准包裹，这与欧洲同行因美国即将对低价值包裹征收关税而采取的类似举措一致。【原文：German postal services group DHL said on Friday it would suspend the shipment of standard parcels for businesses to the United States, in line with similar moves by European peers deterred by looming U.S. customs duties for low-value packages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/germanys-dhl-joins-peers-restricting-us-bound-parcel-services-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAOCUUNIZJKJRFYJPF5NA2MUYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 09:38:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发布稀土行业管理暂行办法]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五发布了稀土开采、冶炼和分离活动控制和管理暂行办法。【原文：China released on Friday interim measures for the control and management of its rare earths mining, smelting and separation activities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-releases-interim-measures-regulating-rare-earths-industry-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIEHMMXJH5MUTAISROEXLC4BIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:14:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DHL：德国邮政暂停向美国运输商业包裹]]></title><description><![CDATA[经营德国邮政服务的 DHL 表示，将从 8 月 22 日起暂停接收和运输商业客户寄往美国的含有货物的包裹和邮件。【原文：DHL , which runs Germany's postal service Deutsche Post, said it will suspend acceptance and transport of parcels and postal items containing goods from business customers destined for the United States from August 22.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dhl-german-postal-service-suspend-transport-business-parcels-us-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4WLGDIANVMLDKU36T5WKCJLAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:12:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道叙利亚将重估货币价值，去掉两个零，以求稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[自 2011 年战争爆发以来，叙利亚镑已贬值 99% 以上，目前 1 美元兑 1 万叙利亚镑，而战前的汇率为 1 美元兑 50 叙利亚镑。【原文：The Syrian pound has lost more than 99% of its value since war erupted in 2011, with the exchange rate now at around 10,000 pounds to the U.S. dollar, compared to 50 before the war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/syria-revalue-currency-dropping-two-zeros-bid-stability-sources-say-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73WUQFSTHFPGTHUCLAVU33N6FQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从 500 亿美元到破产，投资者计算恒大市场尝试的成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国恒大集团曾是中国首屈一指的开发商，2009 年在香港上市是中国民营开发商中规模最大的一次，也是全球房地产行业负债最多的企业。【原文：China Evergrande Group, for the most part, lived true to its name -- it was once the country's premier developer, its listing in Hong Kong in 2009 was the biggest by a Chinese private developer, and it had the largest pile of debt in the property sector globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/50-billion-bust-investors-count-cost-evergrandes-market-tryst-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RQX2DUFBJRIG3MGD3GIEDZGPGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Nazara Tech 称 PokerBaazi 运营商停止了基于货币的在线游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度纳扎拉科技公司（Nazara Tech）周五表示，其联营公司月光科技公司（Moonshine Technologies）已停止提供用钱玩的在线游戏，月光科技公司运营着 PokerBaazi 和其他基于纸牌的平台。【原文：India's Nazara Tech said on Friday its associate firm, Moonshine Technologies, which operates PokerBaazi and other card-based platforms, has ceased offering online games played with money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-nazara-tech-says-pokerbaazi-operator-halts-money-based-online-games-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKEIF3OK3FOXFMEOIJKDNTLC3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:55:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 7 月进口美国稀土矿激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 7 月份从美国进口的稀土矿大幅跃升，可能是美国供应商 MP Materials 公司的货物在海关的最终结算。【原文：The sharp jump in China's imports of rare earth ore from the United States in July was probably the final customs accounting of shipments from U.S. supplier MP Materials .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-imports-us-rare-earth-ore-surge-july-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KJITAGDYJOWZADPV2O3NDENUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[StanChart 在美国诉讼案中获得有利裁决后股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行称，美国司法部在一桩旷日持久的民事案件中做出了有利裁决，该行股价周五上涨 3%。【原文：Standard Chartered shares rose 3% on Friday after what the bank said was a favourable ruling by the U.S. Department of Justice in a long running civil case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stanchart-shares-rise-after-favourable-ruling-us-litigation-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVBRV5EGKZMFZBN2VB3TVFLGYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典瓦伦贝里公司将联合成立人工智能公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦贝格周五表示，阿斯利康、爱立信、萨博、SEB 和沃伦贝格投资公司将联合成立一家人工智能公司，为瑞典公司开发先进的人工智能基础设施。【原文：AstraZeneca , Ericsson , Saab , SEB and Wallenberg Investments will jointly launch an artificial intelligence company to develop advanced AI infrastructure for Swedish companies, Wallenberg said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swedens-wallenberg-companies-launch-joint-ai-company-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHUFWOAFYRI4NFTRGWALVL25C4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:28:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，马斯克寻求扎克伯格帮助竞购 OpenAI]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 在周四提交的一份法庭文件中说，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）曾试图让竞争对手马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）参与其财团今年早些时候以 974 亿美元竞购 OpenAI 的交易，但这位 Meta Platforms 公司的首席执行官并没有加入。【原文：Elon Musk tried to enlist rival Mark Zuckerberg for the $97.4 billion bid that his consortium made for OpenAI earlier this year, but the CEO of Meta Platforms did not come on board, OpenAI said in a court filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/musk-sought-zuckerberg-help-openai-bid-court-filing-shows-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSDIZFM7R5IMBGJAFYQQBE644M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:22:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，星巴克将在两周内对中国业务进行非约束性竞标]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，星巴克已要求一批入围的潜在竞购者在未来两周内就其中国业务的股份提交不具约束力的竞购书。【原文：Starbucks has asked a short-listed group of potential bidders to submit non-binding bids for a stake in its China business within the next two weeks, two people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/starbucks-expects-non-binding-bids-china-business-within-two-weeks-sources-say-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B27DPGK6TJJORHABT74ZPSNEUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构因洗钱问题责令 Binance 部门进行审计]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚金融犯罪监察局周五下令Binance当地部门任命一名外部审计师，因为该部门在反洗钱和反恐融资控制方面存在问题。【原文：Australia's financial crime watchdog on Friday ordered the local unit of Binance to appoint an external auditor after identifying concerns related to its anti-money laundering and counter terrorism financing controls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-watchdog-orders-binance-unit-conduct-audit-over-money-laundering-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XOZ5WDFIBKG5F6LJJEYS3DZLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:31:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美韩峰会可能讨论哪些问题？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）与韩国总统李在明（Lee Jae Myung）周一在华盛顿举行首次首脑会谈，此前两国于上月达成贸易协议，将美国对亚洲盟友的关税从威胁的25%降至15%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump hosts South Korean President Lee Jae Myung in Washington for their first summit meeting on Monday, after the countries struck a trade deal last month lowering U.S. tariffs on the Asian ally to 15% from a threatened 25%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/what-issues-are-likely-be-discussed-us-south-korea-summit-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FK2GQKBQOZKDVLRQYARV2JMTTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国将人工智能投资作为支持增长的首要政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国关税造成的贸易阻力，韩国政府下调了今年的经济增长预期，韩国周五誓言将人工智能投资作为政策的重中之重。【原文：South Korea vowed on Friday to make investment in artificial intelligence a top policy priority, as the government slashed its economic growth projection for this year due to trade headwinds caused by U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-makes-ai-investment-top-policy-priority-support-flagging-growth-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCL23GH7ZFNLDHBC44FRZRT75E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：最后一次夏日狂欢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔-斯图尔特-亨特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FZ3E5JIFFILDNARCE77HON6FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 04:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将速度最快的 Cybertruck 在美国的售价提高 1.5 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据特斯拉网站上的定价信息，特斯拉已将其 Cybertruck 最快车型的价格提高了 1.5 万美元。【原文：Tesla has raised the price of its fastest variant of Cybertruck by $15,000, according to pricing information on the automaker's website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-raises-price-fastest-cybertruck-by-15000-us-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6CTQUFBHZN6BNW5XJ3MEMF63A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 04:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alvarez & Marsal 高层表示将把印度的全球能力中心人数增加两倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[咨询公司 Alvarez & Marsal 的一位高管告诉路透社，该公司计划到 2028 年底将其在印度的全球能力中心员工增加近两倍，达到 2,000 人。【原文：Consulting firm Alvarez & Marsal plans to nearly triple its global capability centre staff in India to 2,000 by the end of 2028, a top executive told Reuters, joining a growing league of firms seeking to tap talent in the world's most populous nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/alvarez-marsal-triple-global-capability-centre-headcount-india-top-exec-says-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3F2HQ7GVJNCRP37M6KEKUKDEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 04:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百度支持的芯片设计公司昆仑万维赢得中国移动价值数百万元的订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国百度支持的半导体设计公司昆仑万维（Kunlunxin）赢得了电信公司中国移动人工智能项目价值数百万元人民币的芯片订单，因为中国政府正在推动国产芯片替代英伟达（Nvidia）。【原文：China's Baidu-backed semiconductor design firm Kunlunxin has won chip orders worth millions of yuan from telecoms firm China Mobile AI projects as authorities push for domestic alternatives to Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/baidu-backed-chip-designer-kunlunxin-wins-millions-yuan-worth-china-mobile-2025-08-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WHPAZ462RLOTMCCSSLFU53HDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 04:39:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>