<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:36:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:36:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[总统表示，大多数汽车制造商将留在墨西哥]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆周二表示，大多数在墨西哥设厂的汽车企业高管都表示，到目前为止，他们还没有搬迁工厂的计划。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Tuesday that the majority of automobile executives with plants in Mexico have said that, as of now, they have no plans to move their factories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/most-automakers-stay-put-mexico-president-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYXQXGVVVFMDLOXAUM7ZD4G4RU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Boaz Weinstein 的 Saba Capital 出售英国信托公司 Keystone Positive Change 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一份监管文件显示，美国激进投资者 Boaz Weinstein 的 Saba Capital 已出售其在英国投资信托公司 Keystone Positive Change (KPC) 近 30% 的股份。【原文：U.S. activist investor Boaz Weinstein's Saba Capital has sold its nearly 30% stake in British investment trust Keystone Positive Change (KPC) , a regulatory filing showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/boaz-weinsteins-saba-capital-sells-stake-uk-trust-keystone-positive-change-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BH5NYBSBINJYNEBXPHVUTH5PMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰美洲证券融资主管在银行重组中离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士告诉路透社，汇丰银行美洲证券融资主管格雷戈里-布恩（Gregory Bunn）将在任职两年后离职，因为该银行将该部门并入另外两个部门。【原文：HSBC's head of securities financing for the Americas, Gregory Bunn, is leaving after two years in the post as the lender merges the unit into two others, a person with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-americas-head-securities-finance-leaves-amid-bank-restructuring-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VM2RBSSQRBLHRAYEJM2DDJMLUY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:26:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大油气公司首席执行官避免在价格下跌期间做出 "草率 "决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大两家石油和天然气生产商的首席执行官周二表示，在全球油价徘徊在四年低点、经济衰退担忧加剧之际，他们正努力避免做出草率的决定。【原文：The CEOs of two Canadian oil and gas producers said on Tuesday they are seeking to avoid making rash decisions, as global oil prices hover around four-year lows and recession fears grow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/canadian-oil-gas-ceos-avoiding-rash-decisions-during-price-rout-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNUNO5YYFFJ4LEDIPTTOAK4MKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:17:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司三月份交付量同比增长 41]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二宣布，3月份交付了41架喷气式飞机，高于去年同期的29架，但这一数字略低于1月份的45架和2月份的44架。【原文：Boeing delivered 41 jets in March, up from 29 during the same month a year ago, the company announced Tuesday, though the figure was slightly lower than the 45 handed over in January and 44 in February.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-deliveries-march-jump-by-41-compared-year-earlier-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57W62QCIEBNIDD6PH6FX5H6RMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 CFPB 要求撤销拜登时代针对速汇金的案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，美国消费者金融最高监管机构已要求联邦法院退出该机构自己对速汇金公司提起的 2022 年诉讼案，让纽约总检察长成为唯一的原告。【原文：The top U.S. watchdog for consumer finance has asked a federal court to withdraw from the agency's own 2022 case against MoneyGram, leaving the New York attorney general as the sole plaintiff, according to court papers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-cfpb-asks-exit-biden-era-case-against-moneygram-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBL6HLXR4VLOHAG46NTFKOXUII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲希望减轻初创企业的人工智能合规负担]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份欧盟委员会文件显示，欧盟委员会计划征求反馈意见，以帮助努力遵守欧盟人工智能使用规则的初创企业减轻监管负担。【原文：The European Commission plans to seek feedback to help lighten the regulatory burden for startups struggling to comply with European Union rules on the use of artificial intelligence, according to a Commission document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/europe-wants-lighten-ai-compliance-burden-startups-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4OLXVYUBVIZXNO3UWNRWDQOKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 15:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界黄金协会称第一季度黄金 ETF 流入量为三年来最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界黄金协会（WGC）周二公布的数据显示，2025年1月至3月，实物黄金交易所交易基金（ETF）创下三年来最大季度流入量。【原文：Physically backed gold exchange-traded funds (ETFs) registered the largest quarterly inflow in three years in January-March, 2025, data from the World Gold Council (WGC) showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-etfs-drew-largest-inflow-three-years-q1-says-wgc-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRES4R57WFIFHGAAQQXDXTQHFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）寻求募集 200 亿美元巨型基金，因为全球都在关注美国的人工智能初创企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，风险投资公司安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）正寻求筹集约200亿美元，这将是该公司历史上规模最大的基金，以利用全球投资者对支持美国人工智能公司的兴趣。【原文：Venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz is seeking to raise about $20 billion in what will be the largest fund in its history, to capitalize on global investors' interest in backing U.S. artificial intelligence companies, sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/andreessen-horowitz-seeks-raise-20-billion-megafund-amid-global-interest-us-ai-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GCXGDBPARLL3P265AZGWBYYAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:33:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国主要贸易伙伴对特朗普关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对美国进口产品全面征收新关税，将矛头指向世界各国，这是对全球贸易体系几十年来最严重的打击。【原文：Donald Trump's sweeping new tariffs on U.S. imports have targeted countries across the world in the most serious blow to the global trading system in decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/how-top-us-trading-partners-have-reacted-trump-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLK6L66IZJNXDASAUCCFYKAYOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比尔-阿克曼呼吁暂停实施特朗普的关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[支持唐纳德-特朗普竞选总统的亿万富翁投资者比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）周二在社交媒体上发文称，美国应在贸易谈判期间推迟实施新的关税措施长达90天。【原文：The U.S. should delay implementing its new tariffs for up to 90 days while trade negotiations take place, billionaire investor Bill Ackman, who endorsed Donald Trump's run for president, said in a social media post on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/bill-ackman-calls-pause-implementing-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPQ4354C75MM3MBA6D25ZKJXMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，德国经济研究所将 2025 年的经济增长预测下调至 0.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士周二告诉路透社，德国经济机构已将今年的经济增长预期从9月份的0.8%下调至0.1%，并补充说这一调整尚未包括美国最新宣布的关税。【原文：German economic institutes have cut their forecast for this year to 0.1% growth from the 0.8% growth expected in September, two sources told Reuters on Tuesday, adding that the revision does not include yet the latest tariffs announced by the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-economic-institutes-cut-forecast-2025-01-growth-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IA33KY3DB5MAFN6XFISYGVNCNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 X 公司达成协议，将 Twitch 从广告支出诉讼中撤诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 公司已达成一项协议，以解决关于直播流媒体服务公司 Twitch 与其他公司和一个广告行业组织合谋抵制该社交媒体平台，导致其广告收入减少的指控。【原文：Elon Musk’s X has reached an agreement to resolve claims that live streaming service Twitch conspired with other companies and an advertising industry group to boycott the social media platform, causing it to lose ad revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/musks-x-reaches-deal-drop-twitch-lawsuit-over-ad-spending-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TDVR5JIORJG3A752V3HHAWQTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:53:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行在特朗普表态后取消美国多元化目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）周二表示，该行将取消其在全美范围内的多元化和包容性目标，成为继美国总统反对其包容性目标之后，又一家放弃该目标的英国公司。【原文：Barclays is scrapping its diversity and inclusivity targets across the United States, the bank said on Tuesday, becoming the latest British company to abandon its inclusivity goals following the U.S. President's opposition to them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/barclays-scraps-diversity-targets-us-following-trumps-stance-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5DTFE3FZBKBXDMPTDDDN3L3UE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行业盈利可能因经济衰退担忧而蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国贷款机构本周开始公布财报，投资者的关注点可能会从利润转向银行老板们在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布征收巨额关税并引发市场大跌后对经济的言论。【原文：As U.S. lenders begin to report earnings this week, investors' focus will likely shift from profits to bank bosses' remarks on the economy after President Donald Trump unveiled steep tariffs and triggered a market selloff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-earnings-likely-be-overshadowed-by-recession-concerns-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYWGXHTSAZOPFHTOPAA2BYN5JY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:31:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球市场衰退令欧洲奢侈品牌前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[越来越多的人担心唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税闪电战将使全球陷入经济衰退，这使年收入 4000 亿美元的奢侈品行业希望美国富豪能帮助其走出多年来最大的低谷。【原文：Growing fears that Donald Trump's tariff blitz will plunge the world into recession are dashing hopes in the $400-billion-a-year luxury industry that wealthy Americans might help to pull it out of the biggest slump in years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-market-rout-darkens-outlook-european-luxury-labels-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RMO452HFQRLBDASJD3EA76P7LU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:26:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利安托法加斯塔公司预计铜需求将抵御关税动荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利安托法加斯塔公司（Antofagasta）负责人表示，美国关税引发的贸易战给金属需求带来了风险，不过他预测人工智能和其他技术可以抵消经济疲软造成的传统消费损失。【原文：The trade war stirred by U.S. tariffs raises a risk for metal demand, the head of Chile's Antofagasta said, although he predicted AI and other technology could offset any loss of traditional consumption caused by economic weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chiles-antofagasta-expects-copper-demand-defy-tariff-turmoil-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TE3J22DGVLJBCIBDEJK4K3SUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国暂停提供资金后，世贸组织旨在减少人事费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织周二表示，在美国暂停向该机构提供资金后，该组织正在审查员工成本。【原文：The World Trade Organization said on Tuesday it is reviewing staff costs after the United States paused funding to the institution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/wto-aims-reduce-staffing-costs-after-us-funding-pause-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNDAY2RWBBMOHFNA2SUQUYLWR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部解散加密货币执法部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，美国司法部正在解散其国家加密货币执法小组，并命令检察官将重点放在涉及利用数字货币为非法业务融资的卡特尔和恐怖组织的刑事调查上。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department is disbanding its National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team and ordering prosecutors to focus instead on criminal investigations involving cartels and terrorist groups that use digital currency to finance illicit business, according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-justice-dept-disbands-cryptocurrency-enforcement-unit-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROV5KPAAEJODNGAUHILSZH6S3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:12:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息称美光将从 4 月 9 日起对部分产品征收关税相关附加费]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟知内情的消息人士称，美国内存芯片制造商美光科技（Micron Technology）已告知美国客户，该公司计划从周三起对部分产品征收附加费，以应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的新关税。【原文：U.S. memory chipmaker Micron Technology has told U.S. customers it plans to impose a surcharge on some products from Wednesday to account for U.S. President Donald Trump's new tariffs, four sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/micron-impose-tariff-related-surcharge-some-products-april-9-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAW25MNISBMITFMYLNIND6FPJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财长称中国关税升级是个大错误]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，美国的关税谈判是其他国家呼吁的结果，而不是金融市场下滑的结果，中国的升级是一个大错误。【原文：U.S. tariff negotiations are the result of calls from other countries not sliding financial markets and China's escalation is a big mistake, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/china-tariff-escalation-big-mistake-us-treasury-secretary-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CGR2SYE7IRM3VB643VRYYTWDFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立陶宛对 Revolut 罚款 350 万欧元，因其未能防止洗钱]]></title><description><![CDATA[立陶宛中央银行周一表示，已对英国最有价值的初创公司 Revolut 罚款 350 万欧元（383 万美元），原因是该公司在防止洗钱方面存在失误。【原文：Lithuania's central bank has fined Britain's most valuable start-up Revolut 3.5 million euros ($3.83 million) for failures in money-laundering prevention, the bank said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/lithuania-fines-revolut-35-million-euros-money-laundering-prevention-failures-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXEDHLBSAZMCBOZY2SHZEXEOL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司瑞波将以 12.5 亿美元收购主要经纪商 Hidden Road]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞波公司（Ripple）周二表示，将以 12.5 亿美元的价格收购多资产主经纪商 Hidden Road，这也是该加密货币公司最大的收购交易之一。【原文：Ripple said on Tuesday it will buy multi-asset prime broker Hidden Road in a $1.25 billion deal, making it one of the largest acquisitions by the crypto company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/crypto-firm-ripple-buy-prime-broker-hidden-road-125-billion-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKFXIDBWQZMGZOKX3CLE5SRHXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈雷首席执行官蔡茨计划于 2025 年退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国摩托车制造商哈雷戴维森（Harley-Davidson）的约亨-蔡茨（Jochen Zeitz）周二表示，在担任首席执行官五年后，他计划于 2025 年退休。【原文：Harley-Davidson's Jochen Zeitz plans to retire as CEO in 2025 after five years in the role, the American motorcycle maker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/harley-davidson-says-ceo-plans-retire-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFOB3NW4CJJWPEU5ZLYTBIGOMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:55:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 停止在波兰生产 Leapmotor 电动车，转而寻求其他选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利汽车制造商 Stellantis 周二表示，已停止在波兰生产其中国合作伙伴 Leapmotor 的 T03 小型电动汽车，并正在评估替代生产方案。【原文：Stellantis has stopped making its Chinese partner Leapmotor's T03 small electric car in Poland and is assessing alternative production options, the Franco-Italian automaker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-says-it-stopped-making-small-ev-leapmotor-car-poland-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5VLHRB73NPLJBLYICEMSF2LNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:24:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税冲击下服装零售商推迟订单、冻结招聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周三对从越南和中国进口的产品加征关税生效之前，美国各地的服装和配饰零售商正在推迟订单并冻结招聘。【原文：Clothing and accessories retailers across the United States are delaying orders and freezing hiring ahead of tariff hikes that take effect Wednesday on products imported from Vietnam and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/clothing-retailers-delay-orders-freeze-hiring-tariffs-hit-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3TACSOV75MYJKJJ3UZEE3YVRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称第一季度意大利 Stellantis 产量进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[FIM Cisl 工会周二表示，Stellantis 意大利汽车产量在 2024 年降至近 70 年低点后，第一季度进一步下降，原因是新车型在明年之前不会支持汽车生产活动。【原文：Stellantis' Italian auto production dropped further in the first quarter after output in the country fell to an almost 70-year low in 2024, the FIM Cisl union said on Tuesday, as new models will not support activity before next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-output-italy-fell-further-first-quarter-union-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2D5L73F6ZIKJIDY3B3X4EKWOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普将签署行政命令促进煤炭行业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周二签署旨在促进美国煤炭工业发展的行政命令。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will sign executive orders on Tuesday aimed at boosting the nation's coal industry, sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-sign-executive-orders-boost-coal-industry-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THMIALX5BJPPJL2574ZI7K47QI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[断崖式下跌后，台湾启动 150 亿美元股票稳定基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾周二授权启动 150 亿美元的股票稳定基金，以支撑因美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收新进口关税而连续两天暴跌的市场。【原文：Taiwan authorised the activation of its $15 billion stock stabilisation fund on Tuesday to prop up the market after two days of sharp falls in reaction to U.S. President Donald Trump's new import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/taiwan-activates-15-billion-stock-stabilisation-fund-after-precipitous-falls-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7A5R4XDTNL3JB3XOTSCLEDTNI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RTX 的普惠公司开发增材制造技术，缩短发动机维修时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[RTX 公司周二表示，其发动机制造子公司普惠公司已为齿轮传动涡扇（GTF）发动机部件开发出一种增材制造维修工艺，可将加工时间缩短 60% 以上。【原文：RTX said on Tuesday its engine making subsidiary Pratt & Whitney has developed an additive manufacturing repair process for its geared turbofan (GTF) engine components, which would reduce process time by more than 60%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtxs-pratt-whitney-develops-additive-manufacturing-reduce-engine-repair-time-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKLVWGRMPZL4VA3FQG5KMK7EOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:13:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>