<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 12:43:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 12:43:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，美国证券交易委员会共和党领导的委员会加强了对调查的监督]]></title><description><![CDATA[这一变化发生在唐纳德-特朗普上台后美国证券交易委员会新领导层的领导下，尚未对外公布。【原文：The change happened under new leadership at the SEC since Donald Trump took office and has not been made public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/secs-republican-led-commission-tightens-oversight-probes-sources-say-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4TROP4DZRIEPAGHTMZZNRRO2E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 12:06:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税后，大众汽车指望通过谈判避免贸易冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令对来自墨西哥、加拿大和中国的商品征收关税后，欧洲最大的汽车制造商大众汽车公司周日表示，希望通过谈判避免贸易冲突。【原文：Volkswagen is counting on talks to avoid trade conflict, Europe's biggest carmaker said on Sunday, after U.S. President Donald Trump ordered tariffs on goods from Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-counts-talks-avoid-trade-conflict-after-trump-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BORIBBQVV5L57B3UTR6U7H2CN4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 11:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷开始就终止首席财务官和销售主管合同进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国豪华汽车制造商保时捷在周六晚些时候发表声明称，该公司的监事会已开始商讨提前结束财务总监鲁茨-梅施克（Lutz Meschke）和销售主管德特勒夫-冯-普拉滕（Detlev von Platen）的合同，因为该公司正努力提高盈利，但在中国的销售疲软。【原文：Porsche's supervisory board has started talks to end finance chief Lutz Meschke's and sales executive Detlev von Platen's contracts early, the German luxury carmaker said in a statement late on Saturday, as it struggles to boost flagging earnings and weak sales in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-starts-talks-end-cfo-sales-chief-contracts-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLHCBW3QOVJUJBQG7MX4VE6QEI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 10:45:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeWork 印度特许经营商申请在孟买上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国共享办公空间管理公司 WeWork 的印度特许经营商已在孟买申请首次公开募股，该公司提交的文件草案显示了这一点。【原文：The Indian franchisee of U.S. shared office space manager WeWork has filed for an initial public offering in Mumbai, draft papers filed by the company showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/weworks-india-franchisee-files-mumbai-ipo-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BWRCWXZQJJPZGR5EJSGAYLLGE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 09:46:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[续集帮助克服经济低迷，中国票房创下收入纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[春节假期期间，中国电影票房收入创下历史新高，因为在经济增长相对疲软的时期，其他类型的消费受到影响，而中国热门影片的续集却吸引了众多影院观众。【原文：China's movie box office took in record revenue during the Lunar New Year holiday, as sequels to popular Chinese hits drew theatregoers at a time when other types of spending have suffered during a period of relatively sluggish economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-box-office-sets-revenue-record-sequels-help-overcome-economic-malaise-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGLGVJUFMJNSHEP22DEK3X56RA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 09:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度预算选择经济糖衣炮弹而非改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度今年公布的年度财政预算比往年更为重要：作为印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪第三个任期内的第一份全面预算，它将为这个世界第五大经济体如何应对增长放缓和市场下滑定下基调。【原文：India's annual budget announcement was a bigger deal than usual this year: As the first full budget of Prime Minister Narendra Modi's third term, it will set the tone for how the world's fifth-largest economy confronts slowing growth and sagging markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-budget-opts-economic-sugar-rush-over-reform-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYAMPGOG2ZJNJPLMXIRD5SQBKQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 08:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北美企业为特朗普关税的影响做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[对北美企业来说，关税问题上的 "观望 "时刻已经结束。【原文：For North American companies, the "wait and see" moment on tariffs is over.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/north-american-companies-brace-fallout-trump-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RMI2GYI7FBMZ7ADTLJKFLKI4RY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 08:24:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道法律文件显示，大众汽车起诉印度，要求撤销 14 亿美元的 "巨额 "税收要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，大众汽车已起诉印度当局，要求撤销一项 "不可能实现的巨额 "14 亿美元的征税要求，认为该要求与新德里的汽车零部件进口税收规则相矛盾，并将阻碍公司的业务计划。【原文：Volkswagen has sued Indian authorities to quash an "impossibly enormous" tax demand of $1.4 billion, arguing the ask is contradictory to New Delhi's import taxation rules for car parts and will hamper the company's business plans, court papers show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-sues-india-quash-enormous-14-bln-tax-demand-legal-filing-shows-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNN56H2Y7JN3NOESDIWYCFTEHU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 07:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税令华尔街担忧盈利受挫和通胀压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周六签署了一项行政命令，对其最大的贸易伙伴征收关税。【原文：Investors are bracing for a looming hit to U.S. corporate profits and pressure on inflation after President Donald Trump on Saturday signed an executive order imposing tariffs on its largest trading partners, with markets seen as not having fully factored in risks from higher levies on foreign imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/tariffs-worry-wall-street-over-earnings-hit-inflation-pressure-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHYC7EBFBRLK7MV2DQRPS2BHAI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 06:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁安巴尼的信实公司在 2020 年应用程序禁令之后将 Shein 带回印度]]></title><description><![CDATA[信实零售（Reliance Retail）在印度推出了一款应用程序，根据授权协议销售中国 Shein 的时尚服饰，这距离 Shein 的应用程序因陷入外交纠纷而在印度被禁已近五年。【原文：Reliance Retail has launched an app in India to sell fashionwear from China's Shein under a licensing deal, almost five years since Shein's app was banned in the country after getting caught up in a diplomatic tussle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/billionaire-ambanis-reliance-brings-shein-back-india-after-2020-app-ban-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SVRQT3QLR5L25GMEPC7VB53YGQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 05:51:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收关税，拓展了贸易法的边界]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）以紧急制裁法为由，对加拿大和墨西哥进口商品征收 25% 的惩罚性关税，并对中国商品额外征收 10% 的关税，以遏制芬太尼和非法移民进入美国。【原文：President Donald Trump has pushed into new trade law territory with an emergency sanctions law to justify punishing 25% tariffs on Canadian and Mexican imports and an extra 10% duty on Chinese goods to curb fentanyl and illegal immigration into the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-stretches-trade-law-boundaries-with-canada-mexico-china-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMGCJSCDGVKVLCA6VGEKWTBA7M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 04:44:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国谴责特朗普征收关税："芬太尼是美国的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国政府周日谴责特朗普政府对中国进口商品征收威胁已久的 10%关税，同时为与美国谈判敞开大门，以避免冲突加深。【原文：China's government on Sunday denounced the Trump administration's imposition of a long-threatened 10% tariff on Chinese imports while leaving the door open for talks with the U.S. that could avoid a deepening conflict.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-denounces-trump-tariff-fentanyl-is-americas-problem-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72WBIZT7WNMPHMMDRBVKLDONK4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 04:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大特鲁多宣布反制关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理贾斯汀-特鲁多（Justin Trudeau）周六表示，加拿大将对1,550亿加元（约合1,065亿美元）的美国商品征收25%的关税，作为对美国关税的回应。【原文：Canada's Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said on Saturday Canada would impose 25% tariffs on C$155 billion ($106.5 billion) of U.S. goods in response to U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-trudeau-announces-counter-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRHBOEGTVZPQVC7CLMG4CKNVH4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 02:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥总统下令对美国征收报复性关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）周六表示，在美国对来自墨西哥的商品征收全面关税后，她命令经济部长实施关税和非关税措施，以捍卫墨西哥的利益。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Saturday she ordered her economy minister to implement tariff and non-tariff measures to defend her country's interests, after the U.S. slapped across-the-board duties on goods coming from Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexican-president-orders-retaliatory-tariffs-against-us-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYTBUBDJ4JI53KOSK4S4NOSYAI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 01:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普征收石油关税促进欧洲和亚洲炼油商发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和市场参与者告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对加拿大和墨西哥进口石油征收贸易关税，将为欧洲和亚洲炼油厂提供与美国竞争对手竞争的优势。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's trade tariffs on Canadian and Mexican oil imports will offer European and Asian refineries a competitive advantage against their U.S. rivals, analysts and market participants told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trumps-oil-tariffs-boost-european-asian-refiners-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6A3KLUAHZNDVHQZUD2ZL4DG2Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:49:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对特朗普对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周六下令从周二开始对加拿大和墨西哥进口商品征收25%的关税，对来自中国的商品征收10%的关税，并宣布在因毒品芬太尼和非法移民进入美国而引发的国家紧急状态结束之前，这些关税将一直有效。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Saturday ordered 25% tariffs on Canadian and Mexican imports and 10% on goods from China starting on Tuesday and declared that they would remain in place until a national emergency over the drug fentanyl and illegal immigration to the U.S. ends.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/reaction-trumps-imposition-tariffs-mexico-canada-china-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRI657HIJBK57BEFNUR5GRQQJ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 23:49:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RPT 由于特朗普对加拿大和墨西哥石油征收关税，油泵价格将上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[燃料批发公司表示，他们别无选择，只能将成本转嫁给消费者。【原文：Companies in wholesale fuel say they have little choice but to pass cost to consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pump-prices-set-rise-trump-tariffs-hit-canadian-mexican-oil-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4DBBFBR45OQ3PQQ3TDLRP2FCI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 23:44:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令对墨西哥、加拿大和中国商品征收高额关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫官员说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六下令从周二开始对加拿大和墨西哥的进口商品征收25%的关税，对来自中国的商品征收10%的关税，以应对芬太尼和非法外国人进入美国的国家紧急状态。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Saturday ordered 25% tariffs on Canadian and Mexican imports and 10% on goods from China starting on Tuesday to address a national emergency over fentanyl and illegal aliens entering the U.S., White House officials said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-orders-steep-tariffs-goods-mexico-canada-china-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6ICSTV2EFPN3FS4JA5TT2UEDA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 22:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥部长表示美国将允许恢复进口墨西哥牛肉]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥农业部长周六在社交网站 X 上发文称，美国在签署谅解备忘录后将允许墨西哥恢复牛肉进口。【原文：The United States will permit the resumption of Mexican beef imports after it signed a memorandum of understanding to do so, Mexico's agriculture minister said in a post on social media site X on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/united-states-allow-resumption-mexican-beef-imports-says-mexican-minister-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WUOKD3ZWRMD7DK567WA2ORTKE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 19:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁阿克曼将在内华达州重新组建管理公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司潘兴广场（Pershing Square）的所有者比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）周六表示，他将在内华达州重新注册他的管理公司。【原文：Bill Ackman, the owner of investment firm Pershing Square, said on Saturday that he is reincorporating his management company in Nevada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/billionaire-ackman-reincorporate-management-company-nevada-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZQWOYO6DZON5NWUDXJWUF4QEA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 16:16:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：欧盟将要求特姆、Shein 和亚马逊为 "不安全 "商品承担责任]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周六报道，欧盟正计划让 Temu、Shein 和亚马逊市场等电子商务平台为网上销售的危险或非法产品承担责任。【原文：The European Union is planning to make e-commerce platforms such as Temu, Shein and Amazon Marketplace liable for dangerous or illegal products sold online, the Financial Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/eu-make-temu-shein-amazon-liable-unsafe-goods-ft-reports-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJMMFMDTPFNYXDHDWQ3U5YSXCA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 16:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察：两名前员工如何推动马里与巴里克的强硬谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉谈判情况的人士称，两名了解巴里克黄金公司在西非运营情况的前公司高管正在帮助推动马里要求这家加拿大矿商支付约 2 亿美元。【原文：Two former company executives with inside knowledge of Barrick Gold's operations in West Africa are helping to drive Mali's demands for a payment of around $200 million from the Canadian miner, according to people familiar with the talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/how-two-former-employees-are-driving-malis-hardball-talks-with-barrick-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOJSLAPIXFLS7KY7F45XNC462Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 15:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳与挑战拉丁裔奖学金计划的诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦当劳表示，它将修改一项向拉丁裔和西班牙裔学生颁发奖学金的计划，取消任何基于申请人种族或族裔的资格标准，以解决一个反对平权法案的团体提起的诉讼。【原文：McDonald's said it will revise a program that awards scholarships to Latino and Hispanic students to eliminate any eligibility criteria based on applicants' race or ethnicity, to settle a lawsuit by a group opposed to affirmative action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mcdonalds-settles-lawsuit-challenging-latino-scholarship-program-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVTQME6K6BLP3IFAEXYPVHW724</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 12:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[好市多与卡车司机谈判委员会达成临时协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡车司机工会周六表示，其谈判委员会已与美国零售商好市多批发公司（Costco Wholesale）就新合同达成临时协议。【原文：The Teamsters labor union said on Saturday that its negotiating committee has reached a tentative agreement for a new contract with U.S. retailer Costco Wholesale .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/costco-teamsters-negotiating-committee-reach-tentative-agreement-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2CA3U7JEZMOLB7ODNZKK2TCSU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度财政预算案 印度削减部分智能手机零部件进口税，为苹果、小米等公司打气]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度财政部长尼尔马拉-西塔拉曼（Nirmala Sitharaman）周六在年度预算中宣布，印度已取消对生产手机的一些关键部件征收进口关税，这将促进本地生产，并使苹果和小米等公司受益。【原文：India has removed import duties on some components key to producing mobile phones, Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced in the annual budget on Saturday, in a boost for local production efforts and benefiting firms such as Apple and Xiaomi .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-budget-india-axes-import-tax-some-smartphone-parts-boost-apple-xiaomi-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4TFJ623AJJALJHRVRCR3TJWKE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 07:56:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普准备下令对墨西哥、加拿大和中国商品征收高额关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普预计将于周六签署一项命令，对来自墨西哥和加拿大的商品征收 25% 的高额新关税，对来自中国的进口商品征收 10% 的关税，这可能会扰乱价值超过 2.1 万亿美元的年度贸易。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is expected to sign an order on Saturday imposing hefty new tariffs of 25% on goods from Mexico and Canada and 10% on imports from China, potentially disrupting more than $2.1 trillion worth of annual trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-readies-order-steep-tariffs-goods-mexico-canada-china-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THWHTJ7P3BLKLMGNO5TOW7LPTQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 05:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，1 月份中国房价和销量进一步下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家领先的房地产研究机构周六表示，1 月份中国新建住房销售量和现有住宅价格均继续下降。【原文：China's sales of new housing and prices for existing residential units both continued to decline in January, a leading real estate research institute said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-home-prices-sales-slip-further-january-report-shows-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6UK22A7BBKYFB2VRHZWH2PZGM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 04:14:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门称 "稳定信心 "是关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最高金融市场监管机构周六表示，"稳定市场、稳定信心、稳定预期 "是政府为领先技术提供更好资本准入的优先事项。【原文：China's top financial market regulator said on Saturday that "stabilising the market, stabilising confidence and stabilising expectations" were priorities as the government works to provide better access to capital for leading technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-market-regulator-says-stabilising-confidence-key-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPSMUJ5QZZKDRNGEYURVKCCZSU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克表示，公司和工会撤回了针对对方的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克及其代表 10,000 多名咖啡师的工会同意撤回对对方提起的诉讼，该公司称，此前一天双方同意引入一名调解员，以帮助恢复陷入僵局的谈判。【原文：Starbucks and its union representing over 10,000 baristas have agreed to withdraw lawsuits filed against each other, the company said, a day after the two sides agreed to bring in a mediator to help resume stalled negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-union-withdraw-lawsuits-filed-against-each-other-company-says-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FLR57SJOZISZMMURVFSJ7XNHQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:44:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司与专业投资者合作，共同拥有音乐版权组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司（Warner Bros Discovery）与媒体音乐版权投资和管理公司 Cutting Edge Group 周五表示，双方已成立一家合资企业，共同拥有这家娱乐工作室的电影和电视音乐目录。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery and Cutting Edge Group, an investor and manager of media music rights, have created a joint venture to co-own the entertainment studio's catalog of film and TV music, the companies said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-discovery-partners-with-specialist-investor-co-own-music-rights-2025-02-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KE4YAM265BMB5FLQ3PAY2MIUQQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:07:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>