<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:42:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:42:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》：特朗普暂停出口管制以支持中国贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周一称，美国已暂停限制对华技术出口，以避免干扰与中国政府的贸易谈判，并支持唐纳德-特朗普总统为确保今年与习近平主席会晤所做的努力。【原文：The U.S. has paused curbs on tech exports to China to avoid disrupting trade talks with Beijing and support President Donald Trump's efforts to secure a meeting with President Xi Jinping this year, the Financial Times said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-pauses-export-controls-bolster-china-trade-deal-ft-says-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFV5JF2K4NOINF5NZOJFLJJGFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[啤酒制造商喜力上半年利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰啤酒制造商喜力周一公布，尽管其在欧洲的销售受到拖累，关税风险增加，但其半年有机营业利润仍增长了 7.4%，超过了分析师的预期。【原文：Dutch brewer Heineken on Monday reported a 7.4% rise in half-year organic operating profit, ahead of analyst expectations, even as its sales in Europe dragged and tariff risks increased.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/brewer-heinekens-first-half-profits-beat-forecasts-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFF6PY6KVJNJ5EZYCI2SQLA27Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国人工智能企业结成联盟，在美国遏制下打造国内生态系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的人工智能公司宣布成立两个新的产业联盟，旨在发展国内生态系统，减少对外国技术的依赖，同时寻求应对美国对先进的英伟达芯片组的出口限制。【原文：China's artificial intelligence companies have announced two new industry alliances, aiming to develop a domestic ecosystem to reduce dependence on foreign tech as they seek to cope with U.S. export restrictions on advanced Nvidia chipsets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-ai-firms-form-alliances-build-domestic-ecosystem-amid-us-curbs-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7HQRJVP5ZPQTEYGZYWO4CHX4Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 04:55:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：美国和欧盟避免关税冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔-斯图尔特-亨特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">336NYHJVWJOGLC4GMBHND7HEUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 04:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美就延长关税休战展开新谈判，为特朗普与习近平会晤铺平道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美两国高级经济官员将于周一在斯德哥尔摩重开会谈，试图解决作为世界前两大经济体之间贸易战核心的长期经济争端，旨在将休战期延长三个月，并阻止大幅提高关税。【原文：Top U.S. and Chinese economic officials will resume talks in Stockholm on Monday to try to tackle longstanding economic disputes at the centre of a trade war between the world's top two economies, aiming to extend a truce by three months and keeping sharply higher tariffs at bay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-launch-new-talks-tariff-truce-extension-easing-path-trump-xi-meeting-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27A2B2ANG5IMXBBGV4AZVTDC2A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟达成协议后，股市为特朗普的贸易协定艺术欢呼雀跃]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，在美国和欧盟达成贸易协议后，全球股市上涨，欧元走强，这提振了市场情绪，并为美联储和日本央行政策会议为首的关键一周提供了明朗的前景。【原文：Global stocks rose and the euro firmed on Monday after a tradeagreement between the United States and the EU lifted sentiment and provided clarity in a pivotal week headlined by the Federal Reserve and the Bank of Japan policy meetings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATRLRHCT55IXDL7V2HLD2JOXZM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:16:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美欧达成协议，贸易乐观情绪升温，石油上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国与欧盟达成贸易协议并可能延长与中国的关税暂停期之后，油价周一上涨，从而减少了人们对潜在的更高关税将限制经济活动并影响燃料需求的担忧。【原文：Oil prices rose on Monday after the U.S. reached a trade deal with the European Union and may extend a tariff pause with China, reducing concerns that potentially higher levies would limit economic activity and impact fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-us-eu-deal-lifts-trade-optimism-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANOWMNXHYFJZHFR4V4YHUMQMGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:09:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和欧盟达成关税协议后欧元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和欧盟宣布达成框架贸易协定后，欧元周一上涨，这是避免全球贸易战的一系列协议中的最新一项。【原文：The euro gained on Monday following the announcement of a framework trade agreement between the United States and the European Union, the latest in a flurry of deals to avert a global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/euro-rises-after-us-eu-agree-tariff-deal-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNN3RA46RBK6BPZN53WD4OTGTI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:57:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子签订 165 亿美元半导体供应合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子公司（Samsung Electronics）周一表示，它已签署了一份价值 165 亿美元的合同，向一家全球大型企业供应半导体。【原文：Samsung Electronics said on Monday it has signed a contract valued at $16.5 billion to supply semiconductors to a major global corporation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/samsung-elec-signs-165-billion-contract-supply-semiconductors-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPTKMTH3A5NCBKBL556RRMWPEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[长江和记为 228 亿美元的港口销售寻找中国竞标伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[长江和记周一表示，希望中国的一家大型战略投资者加入竞购其价值 228 亿美元港口业务的财团，此前有媒体报道称国有企业中国远洋海运集团可能加入该财团。【原文：CK Hutchison said on Monday it wants a major Chinese strategic investor to join the consortium bidding for its $22.8 billion ports business, after media reports that state-owned China COSCO Shipping Corp may join the group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ck-hutchison-eyes-chinese-bidding-partner-228-billion-port-sale-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFVMKJOUNJMKXNYDJIEOEJOMAI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WiseTech Global 任命内部人士 Zubin Appoo 为永久首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚物流软件制造商 WiseTech Global 周一表示，已任命其参谋长 Zubin Appoo 为公司永久首席执行官，接替临时首席执行官 Andrew Cartledge。【原文：Australian logistics software maker WiseTech Global on Monday said it named its chief of staff, Zubin Appoo, as its permanent chief executive, to replace interim CEO Andrew Cartledge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/wisetech-global-appoints-insider-zubin-appoo-permanent-ceo-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYJ43FQARBNBVEPNE6KGWFCUOU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 22:49:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[不敌美国的欧洲接受了最差的美国贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[最终，欧洲发现自己缺乏影响力，无法按照自己的条件将唐纳德-特朗普的美国拉入贸易协定，因此签署了一份自己还能接受的协议--尽管这份协议明显对美国有利。【原文：In the end, Europe found it lacked the leverage to pull Donald Trump's America into a trade pact on its terms and so has signed up to a deal it can just about stomach - albeit one that is clearly skewed in the U.S.'s favour.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/out-gunned-europe-accepts-least-worst-us-trade-deal-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SALSKKHNCZOHVL7WKE2GMGI5GA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟与美国周日就贸易协议的主要内容达成一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和欧盟周日就一项框架贸易协议达成一致，结束了大西洋两岸工业和消费者数月来的不确定性。【原文：The U.S. and the European Union agreed on a framework trade deal on Sunday, ending months of uncertainty for industry and consumers on both sides of the Atlantic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/key-elements-eu-us-trade-deal-agreed-sunday-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FYAT3TZG5L4XOX25JHZJBZDRE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:35:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟冯德莱恩：贸易协议在不确定时期带来确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）周日表示，美国对欧盟进口商品征收 15%的基准税率将适用于汽车、半导体和医药产品。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen on Sunday said a U.S. baseline tariff rate of 15% on imported EU goods would apply to cars, semiconductors and pharmaceutical goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eus-von-der-leyen-trade-deal-delivers-certainty-uncertain-times-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUPJ6FF2BBNZNBBTX6NAJUAV64</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国预计两周内对芯片进口调查有结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周日表示，特朗普政府将在两周内宣布对半导体进口进行国家安全调查的结果，但未提供详情。【原文：The Trump administration will announce the result of a national security probe into imports of semiconductors in two weeks, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said on Sunday, without providing details.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-expects-result-probe-into-chip-imports-two-weeks-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAB273Q66JJ2PKNV76SLNI6TMI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:26:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 对美国和欧盟贸易协定的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，美国和欧盟已就一项贸易协议达成协议，其中包括对欧盟进入美国的商品征收15%的关税，以及欧盟大量采购美国能源和军事装备。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Sunday said the United States and the European Union had reached agreement on a trade deal that includes a 15% tariff on EU goods entering the U.S. and significant EU purchases of U.S. energy and military equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-reaction-us-eu-trade-deal-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPJDLSIZQJI4ZJNCS7RQHORONU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司的合同提议遭工会成员拒绝]]></title><description><![CDATA[在圣路易斯地区组装波音战斗机的工会成员周日以 "压倒性多数票 "否决了波音公司的合同提议。【原文：Union members who assemble Boeing's fighter jets in the St. Louis area have "overwhelmingly voted" to reject the company's contract offer on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeings-contract-offer-rejected-by-union-members-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JH636HV6FBKRFEBCQ5CWA4RHEM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与欧盟达成贸易协议，欧盟将全面征收 15%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普说，该协议包括欧盟对美国能源和军事装备的大量采购，以及欧盟对美国 6000 亿美元的投资。【原文：The deal includes significant EU purchases of U.S. energy and military equipment and $600 billion in investments in the U.S. by the European Union, Trump said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-eu-agree-trade-deal-eu-will-see-15-tariff-across-board-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26LZIEQ7D5LDFISYNRCAMXPQXI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:49:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国即将与中国达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周日表示，他的政府即将与中国达成一项贸易协议，但没有透露其他细节。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday his administration was close to reaching a trade deal with China, but gave no other details.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-us-is-close-reaching-trade-deal-with-china-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMZGD6PCKVKZVCGVH2VFNBZSXQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:23:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南华早报》报道：中美将在瑞典谈判中将关税暂停再延长90天]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《南华早报》（SCMP）周日援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道，北京和华盛顿有望在周一开始的斯德哥尔摩贸易谈判中将关税休战再延长三个月。【原文：Beijing and Washington are expected to extend their tariff truce by another three months at trade talks in Stockholm beginning on Monday, the South China Morning Post (SCMP) reported on Sunday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-extend-tariff-pause-sweden-talks-by-another-90-days-scmp-reports-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IAXGPBOURNALNXXK2352YYATU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 16:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[孟加拉国订购 25 架波音飞机，作为推动缓解美国关税的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高级官员周日表示，孟加拉国已向波音公司订购了 25 架飞机，并加大了对主要美国商品的进口，以努力化解贸易紧张局势，降低特朗普政府征收的高额关税。【原文：Bangladesh has ordered 25 aircraft from Boeing and ramped up imports of key American goods in an effort to defuse trade tensions and bring down the steep tariffs imposed by the Trump administration, a senior official said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/bangladesh-orders-25-boeing-planes-part-push-ease-us-tariffs-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VIOLSUJI7JIGTB3GIWHXYLYMMU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 16:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美重启关税谈判，努力延长停战期]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美两国高级谈判代表周一在斯德哥尔摩举行会晤，以解决两国贸易战核心的长期经济纠纷，旨在延长休战期，避免大幅提高关税。【原文：Senior U.S. and Chinese negotiators meet in Stockholm on Monday to tackle longstanding economic disputes at the centre of the countries' trade war, aiming to extend a truce keeping sharply higher tariffs at bay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-resume-tariff-talks-effort-extend-truce-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EF4PFXPQWFOIJMRZL2JKCT3HJU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长称特朗普非常喜欢 TikTok，但应用程序必须转为美国所有]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周日表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普喜欢TikTok，但这款由中国人拥有的短视频应用程序必须转为美国人所有。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump likes TikTok but the Chinese-owned short video app, used by some 170 million Americans, has to move to U.S. ownership, Secretary of Commerce Howard Lutnick said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-commerce-secretary-says-trump-really-likes-tiktok-app-has-move-us-ownership-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXW26ACJKVMY3CGHYQ2YPVPBAU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长称欧洲必须开放市场才能达成降低关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周日表示，欧盟必须对美国出口产品开放市场，以说服美国总统唐纳德-特朗普降低威胁将于8月1日生效的30%的关税税率。【原文：The European Union must open up its markets for U.S. exports in order to convince U.S. President Donald Trump to reduce a threatened 30% tariff rate due to kick in on August 1, U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said on Sunday, adding Brussels clearly wanted to make a deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-commerce-secretary-says-europe-must-open-markets-get-lower-tariff-deal-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BCGUTGDQJNOH7BPWG24VOYSCXI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国亚马逊浆果阿萨伊爱好者将感受到关税压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[几乎所有在美国、欧洲和亚洲销售的阿萨伊果肉都来自巴西。【原文：Nearly all of the açaí pulp sold in the U.S., as well as in Europe and Asia, where people have also developed a taste for the tangy fruit, comes from Brazil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-lovers-amazon-berry-aa-feel-tariff-pinch-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5GHFHYT35MIRNW2YWEJSDPNBI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度科技公司 TCS 将裁员 2%，影响 1.2 万多个工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度最大的 IT 服务提供商塔塔咨询服务公司周日表示，将在 2026 财年裁员 2%，主要影响中高层管理人员。【原文：India's largest IT services provider Tata Consultancy Services will reduce its workforce by 2% in its 2026 financial year, primarily affecting middle and senior management, the company said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-tech-company-tcs-cut-workforce-by-2-affecting-more-than-12000-jobs-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4XYZYT3CNIWPKS4LUWTIJOSII</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 10:36:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南华早报》称美国商业代表团将访华]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《南华早报》周日援引两位熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道，美中贸易全国委员会的一个高级代表团将于本周访问中国，并有望会见中国高级官员。【原文：A high-level delegation from the U.S.-China Business Council will visit China this week and is expected to meet senior Chinese officials, the South China Morning Post reported on Sunday, citing two sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-business-delegation-visit-china-scmp-says-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5J6H6PN2INMGLCXNPNSRACA2H4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 06:26:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普和欧盟冯德莱恩将于周日会晤，以达成贸易协议，避免贸易战]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）将于周日与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）会面，以达成一项针对欧洲的贸易协议，该协议可能会对大多数欧盟商品征收 15%的基准关税，但会结束欧盟公司数月来的不确定性。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen is set to meet U.S. President Donald Trump on Sunday to clinch a trade deal for Europe that would likely see a 15% baseline tariff on most EU goods, but end months of uncertainty for EU companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-eus-von-der-leyen-meet-sunday-clinch-trade-deal-avert-trade-war-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45DY7JEYBBKSZJFMITNULXGPQE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 04:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 月份中国工业利润进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日的数据显示，6月份中国工业利润继续下降，原因是在国内需求低迷和全球贸易不确定性挥之不去的情况下，根深蒂固的生产通缩给企业带来了更大的利润压力。【原文：China's industrial profits continued to fall in June, data showed on Sunday, as entrenched producer deflation put more margin pressure on businesses in the face of subdued domestic demand and lingering global trade uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-industrial-profits-fall-further-june-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7SC6PBVZNOLXHFB2VGS5CSF6U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 01:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》报道，特斯拉向机器人出租车用户介绍加州司机式服务的最新情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》（Business Insider）援引特斯拉周六发送给用户的通知截图报道，特斯拉向机器人出租车用户发送了一份新的服务条款协议，详细说明了其计划在加州湾区推出的服务。
该通知称："如果您的乘车服务在加利福尼亚州进行，则将根据加利福尼亚州公用事业委员会的授权，由一名安全驾驶员使用全自动驾驶（监督）系统进行。"通知还补充说，在加利福尼亚州以外的乘车服务将 "自动进行"，这证实了路透社一天前的报道。【原文：Tesla sent robotaxi users a new terms-of-service agreement detailing its planned launch in California's Bay Area, Business Insider reported citing a screenshot of the notification sent to users on Saturday.
The notification said, "If your ride is taking place in California, it is being conducted with a safety driver using Full Self-Driving (Supervised) pursuant to authority from the California Public Utilities Commission," adding that rides taken outside California are "conducted autonomously," confirming Reuters reporting from a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-updates-robotaxi-users-about-chauffeur-style-service-california-business-2025-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DELZOX6RNJPSRJ7P64SAE4UEOQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 00:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>