<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:06:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:06:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[说明：Wegovy 加入医疗保险价格谈判对患者和公司意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周五公布了 2027 年医疗保险价格谈判的 15 种处方药清单，其中包括诺和诺德公司的减肥药 Wegovy。以下是华尔街分析师对该名单的看法：【原文：The U.S. government on Friday announced a list of 15 prescription medicines targeted for Medicare price negotiations for 2027, which includes Novo Nordisk's blockbuster weight-loss drug Wegovy. Here's what Wall Street analysts say about the inclusion:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/what-wegovys-inclusion-medicare-price-negotiation-means-patients-company-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VD6SDUUKOVKOPFDCDRMP3TXZKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 的奶油和糖果销售商受到美国禁令的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 预计将于周日关闭，这对依赖该短视频网站谋生的中小型公司和所谓的 "有影响力的人 "构成了最大的威胁，而大品牌预计将转向其他网站。【原文：TikTok's expected Sunday shutdown poses the biggest threat to the universe of small- and medium-sized firms and so-called influencers who depend on the short-form video site for their livelihood, while big brands are expected to move to other sites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktoks-purveyors-creams-candies-under-threat-us-ban-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPIX64QVEJP2LBKLJQZCF3P2SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登将为 ioneer 内华达锂矿提供的贷款增至近 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的文件显示，美国能源部已敲定向 ioneer 的 Rhyolite Ridge 锂项目提供 9.96 亿美元的贷款，比初步融资报价增加了 2.96 亿美元，此举旨在促进乔-拜登总统的绿色能源事业。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy has finalized a $996 million loan for ioneer's Rhyolite Ridge lithium project, according to documents reviewed by Reuters, an increase of $296 million from a preliminary funding offer and a move aimed at boosting President Joe Biden's green energy legacy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/biden-boosts-loan-ioneers-nevada-lithium-mine-nearly-1-billion-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVU6EI66VJMMBGPBWIWDUXJ37E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CBO 称，美国清洁能源税收补贴将在 10 年内耗资 8250 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会预算办公室主任菲利普-斯瓦格（Philip Swagel）周五表示，根据乔-拜登总统签署的《通货膨胀削减法案》，美国清洁能源税收补贴将在未来10年内使美国预算赤字增加8250亿美元，远远高于最初估计的10年2700亿美元。【原文：U.S. clean energy tax subsidies under President Joe Biden's signature Inflation Reduction Act will boost U.S. budget deficits by $825 billion over the next 10 years, Congressional Budget Office director Philip Swagel said on Friday, far above the initial $270 billion 10-year estimate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-clean-energy-tax-subsidies-cost-825-billion-over-10-years-cbo-says-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEOTMZQZJVKARJWF72CHAXV6WI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道高管称玻利维亚正与阿根廷谈判，以在需求激增之际重启天然气供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[玻利维亚国营能源公司 YPFB 正在商谈重启对阿根廷的天然气出口，因为夏季热浪导致需求激增，这凸显了布宜诺斯艾利斯政府在实现能源自给自足方面面临的挑战。【原文：Bolivia's state-run energy firm YPFB is in talks to restart gas exports to Argentina amid a surge in demand spurred by a summer heat wave, underscoring the challenge for the government in Buenos Aires as it looks to become energy self-sufficient.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bolivia-talks-with-argentina-restart-gas-supply-amid-demand-spike-executive-says-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OO6GZXUNZVLZTH3TZWL4GOCP6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:56:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数字货币集团、前 Genesis 首席执行官因 SEC 指控支付 3850 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周五表示，数字货币集团公司（Digital Currency Group Inc.【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday said Digital Currency Group Inc. and the CEO of its now-defunct subsidiary Genesis Global Capital LLC have agreed to pay a combined $38.5 million in civil penalties to settle charges they misled investors about Genesis's financial condition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/digital-currency-group-former-genesis-ceo-pay-385-mln-over-sec-charges-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6JYMXOOBVOAFBSVDHLACDTPJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:44:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储退出全球气候变化监管组织]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会周五宣布退出一个由各国央行和监管机构组成的全球机构，该机构致力于探索如何应对金融体系中的气候风险。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve announced on Friday it had withdrawn from a global body of central banks and regulators devoted to exploring ways to police climate risk in the financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/federal-reserve-announces-exit-regulatory-climate-change-group-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JS2R6R3UCBN2HBM5YDIQ2MSSMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局对 SpaceX 的 "星际飞船 "爆炸展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周五表示，将监督埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索公司（SpaceX）对前一天爆炸性的 "星际飞船"（Starship）试飞的调查，这次试飞迫使数十架航班改道以避开碎片。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said on Friday it will oversee an investigation by Elon Musk's SpaceX into an explosive Starship test flight the previous day that forced airlines to divert dozens of flights to avoid debris.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/us-faa-opens-probe-into-spacexs-starship-explosion-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2L5GYD2KBI6VMGHUTEQOMDZPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登政府在最后一刻颁布规则遏制低价值货物运输]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周五在最后一刻发布了拟议规则，以遏制低于800美元 "最低 "门槛的免税进口，拒绝对受美国其他惩罚性关税影响的低价值货物给予豁免。【原文：The Biden administration on Friday issued last-minute proposed rules to curb duty-free imports under the $800 "de minimis" threshold, denying the low-value shipments exemption for goods that are subject to other punitive U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/biden-administration-posts-last-minute-rule-curb-low-value-shipments-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4WFOYBUXVMGJBME7K4ALI7JOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:23:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商削减油气钻井平台至 2021 年 12 月以来最低水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第二周削减石油和天然气钻井平台数量，创下自2021年12月以来的最低水平。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating for a second week in a row to the lowest since December 2021, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-cut-oil-gas-rigs-lowest-since-december-2021-baker-hughes-says-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMYHRYADWVMILDKY5XYGV43HCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:14:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管机构称 Vanguard 将支付 1.064 亿美元了结美国证券交易委员会的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）周五表示，先锋集团（Vanguard Group）已同意支付 1.064 亿美元，以了结该委员会对其在资本收益分配和散户投资者税收后果方面的误导性声明的指控。【原文：The Vanguard Group has agreed to pay $106.4 million to settle U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) charges over misleading statements related to capital gains distributions and tax consequences for retail investors, the regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/vanguard-pay-1064-mln-settle-us-sec-charges-regulator-says-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALSATQVP75IXLA2IRSBJBHGEXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:10:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[禁令临近，TikTok 首席执行官感谢特朗普推动应用程序在美国继续使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 首席执行官周受资（Shou Zi Chew）周五表示，他要感谢美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）承诺与该公司合作，并找到一个能让该应用在美国继续使用的解决方案。【原文：TikTok CEO Shou Zi Chew said on Friday he wants to thank U.S. President-elect Donald Trump for his commitment to work with the company and find a solution that keeps the app available in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-ceo-thanks-trump-push-keep-app-available-us-ban-looms-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2NA7XETM5JMTOKWKF7KJ4Q34U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国立法者为最高法院支持 TikTok 禁令欢呼雀跃]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国两党的立法者对最高法院周五做出的一项裁决表示欢迎，该裁决维持了一项法律，即允许中国流行的社交媒体应用 TikTok 在周日之前被一家美国公司收购，否则将被禁用。【原文：U.S. lawmakers on both sides of the aisle hailed a ruling by the Supreme Court on Friday that upheld a law that gives popular Chinese-owned social media app TikTok until Sunday to be bought by an American company or be banned.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-lawmakers-cheer-supreme-court-upholding-tiktok-ban-law-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XGU2DONUJKW7AK2SJWN5KADCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[田纳西州总检察长与贝莱德就 ESG 争议达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[田纳西州总检察长乔纳森-斯克梅蒂（Jonathan Skrmetti）周五宣布与贝莱德达成和解，解决了资产管理公司在其投资实践中就环境、社会和公司治理因素的作用误导客户的指控。【原文：Tennessee Attorney General Jonathan Skrmetti announced a settlement with BlackRock on Friday, resolving allegations that the asset manager misled customers regarding the role of ESG factors in its investment practices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tennessee-attorney-general-settles-esg-dispute-with-blackrock-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6HAIX4V7ERKCXKVCU6GAEI7WDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:49:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[殖民地管道公司在因泄漏而关闭后重启汽油主干道]]></title><description><![CDATA[Colonial 管道公司周五表示，本周早些时候因佐治亚州保定县发生泄漏而关闭的汽油主干道已重新启动，该管道将燃料从美国墨西哥湾沿岸输送到东海岸市场。【原文：The Colonial Pipeline said on Friday it restarted its main gasoline artery, which delivers fuel from the U.S. Gulf Coast to East Coast markets, after it was shut earlier this week due to a leak in Paulding County, Georgia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/colonial-pipeline-restarts-main-gasoline-artery-after-spill-related-shutdown-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GYG5IB6GZJDFNLLBVVAUFDRSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛任命供应链高管戴夫-古吉纳为美国电子商务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份公司备忘录，沃尔玛供应链执行副总裁戴夫-古吉纳（Dave Guggina）将接替汤姆-沃德（Tom Ward），成为该零售商的美国首席电子商务官。【原文：Walmart's Executive Vice President of Supply Chain Dave Guggina will become the retailer's U.S. chief e-commerce officer, replacing Tom Ward, according to a company memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-names-supply-chain-executive-dave-guggina-us-e-commerce-chief-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWIODQE2BVIDRMNK6I3EJPJNFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:30:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，法国白兰地制造商在特朗普就职典礼前提升美国出口量]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易数据显示，法国干邑制造商在 12 月份增加了对美国的发货量，原因是分销商在美国需求出现改善迹象的同时，为应对可能的新关税而增加了库存。【原文：French cognac makers increased shipments to the United States in December, trade data showed, as distributors fill up their stocks to prepare for possible new tariffs while demand in the country shows signs of improvement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/frances-cognac-makers-lift-us-exports-ahead-trump-inauguration-data-shows-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XG2CQKFM3RLIJH63ZAW6OPBLWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:07:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构责令本田公司为损害司机信用报告支付 1280 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[本田公司的美国融资部门周五被美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）勒令支付 1280 万美元，原因是其报告的不准确信息影响了 30 万本田和讴歌汽车驾驶员的信用报告。【原文：Honda's U.S. financing arm was ordered on Friday by the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau to pay $12.8 million for reporting inaccurate information that affected the credit reports of 300,000 drivers of Honda and Acura vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-regulator-orders-honda-unit-pay-128-million-harming-drivers-credit-reports-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQNASGLKNVMNLG3YT63F33HWMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:46:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诉讼称宝洁公司被控在Charmin卫生纸中进行 "绿色包装]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项新的诉讼指控宝洁公司（Procter &amp; Gamble）在其卫生纸的来源方面以误导性的环保声明（即所谓的 "洗绿"）欺骗了Charmin的购买者。【原文：A new lawsuit accuses Procter &amp; Gamble of deceiving Charmin purchasers with misleading environmental claims, known as greenwashing, about how it sources its toilet paper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/procter-gamble-accused-greenwashing-charmin-toilet-paper-lawsuit-says-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIT6MVNLQBOBVLVGTPLGIWSPFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[米莱的阿根廷 14 年来首次实现预算盈余]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的数据显示，阿根廷在 2024 年实现了十多年来的首次预算盈余，这标志着自由主义者哈维尔-米莱（Javier Milei）总统及其全面紧缩政策在上任后的第一个完整年度取得了胜利。【原文：Argentina brought in its first budget surplus in more than a decade in 2024, data published on Friday showed, marking a win for libertarian President Javier Milei and his sweeping austerity push in his first full year in office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-logs-first-financial-surplus-14-years-2024-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWQHEQEZCFJBTF42UKFN3T4S24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:39:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 上瘾者从美国禁令中看到一线希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 在美国进入了最后几个小时，周日可能会被禁用，这引起了深受喜爱的视频流应用程序忠实用户的抗议。【原文：TikTok is entering its final hours in the U.S. ahead of a potential ban effective on Sunday, prompting howls of protest from devoted users of the beloved video-streaming app.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-addicts-see-silver-lining-us-ban-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLRAMBCSB5OMJF7DJMRXVTBU6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:39:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[运营商表示，纽约电网已准备好满足寒流需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约独立系统运营商（NYISO）周五表示，该州电网已做好准备，以满足周一至周三寒流来袭期间的预期电力需求。【原文：The New York Independent System Operator (NYISO) said on Friday that the state's electric grid is prepared to meet anticipated power demand during a forecasted cold snap from Monday to Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-yorks-electric-grid-ready-meet-cold-snap-demand-operator-says-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72N4XMKWRJI3JMF6KUEKY5CY5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉百事可乐向沃尔玛提供独家折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五起诉百事可乐向一家大型零售商提供优惠价格，一位熟悉此事的消息人士证实，这家零售商就是沃尔玛。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission sued Pepsi on Friday for offering preferential pricing to a larger retailer, whom a source familiar with the matter confirmed was Walmart.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-pepsi-over-exclusive-discounts-walmart-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXFXM3ZHIRNULFAVYOSXRU67VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉新任评级主管寻找特朗普治下美国政策的答案]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉新任主权评级主管表示，在夏季进行下一次评级审查时，该公司可能会对唐纳德-特朗普的第二个总统任期可能对美国信用评级产生的影响有一个更清晰的认识。【原文：Fitch new head of sovereign ratings says the firm is likely to have a clearer picture of how Donald Trump’s second term as president could impact the U.S. credit rating by the time of its next rating review in the summer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fitchs-new-rating-chief-looking-answers-us-policy-under-trump-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBDXI75OBJJFPILEIPMYZ53R4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:09:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空航天集团对支持国家安全和工业的特定关税持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普建议对包括墨西哥和加拿大在内的国家征收关税后，美国最大的航空航天贸易集团周五为讨论具体关税问题敞开了大门。【原文：The largest U.S. aerospace trade group opened the door on Friday to discussions on specific tariffs, after President-elect Donald Trump suggested slapping duties on countries including Mexico and Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-aero-group-open-select-tariffs-supporting-natl-security-industry-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXQII2DAYBIFZOX766IUHIYQ5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 TikTok 由他决定，但未提供细节]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，TikTok 应用程序的未来将由他来决定，但他没有详细说明他将采取哪些措施。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump said on Friday the decision on the future of the TikTok app will be up to him, but he did not provide any detail about what steps he would take.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-tiktok-decision-is-up-him-offers-no-details-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75R4PG6GTRI7FBO264Y5ZAAKPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:59:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商集团提起诉讼，要求阻止美国的自动紧急制动规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表主要汽车制造商的一个团体周五表示，它已提起诉讼，要求阻止乔-拜登总统政府制定的一项具有里程碑意义的规定，即到2029年，几乎所有的新车和卡车都必须配备先进的自动紧急制动系统。【原文：A group representing major automakers on Friday said it filed lawsuit to block a landmark rule from the administration of President Joe Biden requiring nearly all new cars and trucks by 2029 to have advanced automatic emergency braking systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/automaker-group-files-lawsuit-block-us-automatic-emergency-braking-rule-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBNVVRPO2BMBTOPS6PRFZ6EVXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:52:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SLB 称其俄罗斯业务与美国新制裁保持一致，但收入下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[油田服务供应商 SLB 周五表示，其目前在俄罗斯的业务仍与美国对俄罗斯的新制裁保持一致，但在该国的收入正在下降。【原文：Oilfield service provider SLB on Friday said its current business in Russia still aligns with new U.S. sanctions on Russia, but that revenue in the country was declining.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/slb-says-its-russia-business-aligns-with-new-us-sanctions-revenue-drops-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWLEEFYT5ZKHZIFK26E6B45JSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:52:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[战略家称，特朗普的关税计划可能是赢得筹码的赌局]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）下周重返白宫，全球投资者都在为一场全球贸易战做准备，一些经济学家和战略家认为，他提出的大幅提高关税的建议很可能成为一种谈判工具。【原文：As investors the world over brace for a global trade war with U.S. President-elect Donald Trump returning to the White House next week, several economists and strategists believe his proposed hefty tariff hikes could well be a negotiation tool.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-tariff-plan-could-be-gambit-win-leverage-strategists-say-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TTFKZUORVIUVBMF3Z3WGH2EQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫美国人应继续使用 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周五表示，Tiktok 应继续向美国人开放，但最高法院就禁止该应用程序的法律作出裁决的时机意味着它必须由特朗普政府来处理。【原文：The White House said on Friday that Tiktok should remain available to Americans but the timing of the Supreme Court ruling on a law banning the app means it must fall to the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-tiktok-should-remain-available-americans-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDKSAJNU3VLD5J7UR7ZT4AVS2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>