<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 23:05:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 23:05:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[边疆航空公司因特朗普贸易战打击旅游业而取消预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的贸易战打击了旅游需求，边疆航空公司（Frontier Airlines）的母公司边疆集团（Frontier Group）周四撤回了全年业绩预期，并警告称第一季度将出现亏损。【原文：Frontier Group , the parent of Frontier Airlines, withdrew its full-year forecast on Thursday and warned of a loss in the first quarter, as U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war has hit travel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/frontier-airlines-scraps-forecast-trumps-trade-war-hits-travel-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GXWGMRJXROE5PUMC7YHWBL4W4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 22:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国碧桂园与部分债权人达成债务重组协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国房地产开发商碧桂园周五表示，已与持有其现有债券债务近 30% 的债权人达成协议，并即将与另一组银行债权人敲定条款。【原文：Chinese property developer Country Garden said on Friday it had reached an agreement with creditors holding nearly 30% of its existing bond debt and was close to finalising terms with another group of bank creditors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-country-garden-reaches-debt-restructuring-deal-with-some-creditors-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YK25ARO3KBLUVASZFO5D2AG2YY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 22:34:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金错失了大部分股市缓解性反弹行情]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布在90天内暂停征收部分关税，引发美股大幅反弹，全球股票多空对冲基金错过了其中的大部分机会。【原文：Global equities long/short hedge funds missed out on most of a massive rally in U.S. stocks on Wednesday triggered by U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of a pause on some tariffs for 90 days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/hedge-funds-miss-most-relief-rally-equities-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYSZZKW3RJJKFF757B6PF4LR7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴拿马运河管理机构称 3 月份运量降至每天 33.7 艘船]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马运河是世界上第二繁忙的水道，根据其管理机构周四发布的公告，3 月份通过该运河的船只数量下降到平均每天 33.7 艘，当月共有 1,045 艘船只通过。【原文：The number of vessels that transited the Panama Canal, the world's second-busiest waterway, fell to an average of 33.7 per day in March for a total of 1,045 ships that month, according to a bulletin on Thursday by its administrative authority.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/panama-canal-traffic-fell-337-ships-per-day-march-authority-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHNLENGDUNJOPIAFRL3ALN55AY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 21:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普暂停加征关税前的适时期权交易引质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据显示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三在社交媒体上发布暂停征收关税的消息令美国股市反弹之前的几分钟里，一些身份不明的期权交易商下了价值数百万美元的赌注，赌市场会反弹。【原文：In the minutes before President Donald Trump's social media post on Wednesday pausing tariffs sent the U.S. stock market rallying, some unidentified options traders placed bets worth millions of dollars that the market would rebound, data shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/well-timed-options-trades-ahead-trumps-tariff-pause-draw-questions-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGJHAXOQR5L7JD46OWXWNEOW7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 21:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 关税现实来袭，市场宿醉未醒]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-graphics-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWUMCBN4NJIBRCEOIDXRVMRGZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 21:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究发现，特朗普 25% 的汽车关税可能使美国汽车制造商损失 1080 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车研究中心（Center for Automotive Research）的一项最新分析发现，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）于 4 月初征收的 25% 的汽车关税将使美国汽车制造商在 2025 年的成本增加约 1,080 亿美元。【原文：A new analysis by the Center for Automotive Research has found that President Donald Trump's 25% auto tariffs imposed in early April will increase costs by about $108 billion for automakers in the U.S. in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/study-finds-trumps-25-auto-tariffs-could-cost-us-automakers-108-billion-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CY7QWY4IYRNMPPRPILHBDXQCVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 21:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称瑞银聘请埃文-雷恩（Evan Raine）担任媒体和电信并购主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的一份内部备忘录显示，瑞银集团已聘请埃文-雷恩（Evan Raine）担任美洲地区媒体和电信投资银行部主管，以从该行业的交易中获取更多市场份额。【原文：UBS Group has hired Evan Raine as its head of media and telecom investment banking in the Americas to capture more market share from deals in the sector, according to an internal memo reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-hires-evan-raine-head-media-telecom-ma-memo-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6VT3IT64FKHHJRTP2IZ5CD75A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普怒斥 SentinelOne，网络安全行业陷入沉默]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普总统对网络安全行业的一位重要成员采取行动后，该行业大部分时间都保持沉默。【原文：The cybersecurity industry has gone mostly quiet after President Donald Trump took action against one of its prominent members.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/cybersecurity-industry-falls-silent-trump-turns-ire-sentinelone-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTEYW7U3BBLPBIF5O6U7TNBEFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:38:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙漠中的电子汽车特斯拉在沙特阿拉伯上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周四在沙特阿拉伯启动运营，这表明首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）已与沙特阿拉伯王国修好关系，而且这个石油之都正在推进一项雄心勃勃的电动汽车政策。【原文：Tesla launched operations in Saudi Arabia on Thursday, a sign that Chief Executive Elon Musk has patched up relations with the kingdom and that the oil capital was moving forward with an ambitious electric-vehicle policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/cybertrucks-desert-tesla-launches-saudi-arabia-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXPPDBMAMNP7LMNRHPD4MAX7TI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税推升通胀风险，美联储主席柯林斯认为美联储将保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周四表示，特朗普政府目前正在推行的大规模贸易关税几乎肯定会推高通胀并抑制经济增长，至少在短期内如此。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said Thursday that large trade tariffs now being pursued by the Trump administration will almost certainly drive inflation higher and depress growth, at least in the near term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-collins-sees-steady-fed-tariffs-push-up-inflation-risks-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJNBPF426RITVHVCUOU2WWZA3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[冯德莱恩向《金融时报》表示，如果特朗普贸易谈判失败，欧盟可能会对大型科技公司征税]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）周四告诉《金融时报》，如果与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的谈判未能结束其针对欧洲的关税战，欧盟准备部署其最强有力的贸易措施，并可能对美国数字公司征税。【原文：The EU is prepared to deploy its most powerful trade measures and may impose levies on U.S. digital companies if negotiations with U.S. President Donald Trump fail to end his tariff war against Europe, EU President Ursula von der Leyen told the Financial Times on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-could-tax-big-tech-if-trump-trade-talks-fail-von-der-leyen-says-ft-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EERSKCY4HVO37HKFMFLEXSXQXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税环境影响，罗技撤回 2026 财年业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗技国际公司（Logitech International）周四表示，由于关税环境带来的持续不确定性，公司将撤回对 2026 财年的预测。【原文：Logitech International on Thursday said it is withdrawing its forecast for fiscal 2026 due to continuing uncertainty caused by the tariff environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/logitech-withdraws-fiscal-2026-outlook-due-tariff-environment-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKU5BGO3IBPERPBGBGDX2KPTCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称，美国银行业监管机构开始与两性平等办公室工作人员合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周四发给监管人员的一封电子邮件显示，美国联邦存款保险公司已从埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的政府效率部（Department of Government Efficiency）招聘了几名员工。【原文：The U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation has brought on several staffers with Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency, according to an email sent to regulatory staff Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-regulator-begins-work-with-doge-staff-email-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FITQIJTZ7ZNJLPO72LKWCGQLK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利 Codelco 公司 2 月份铜产量下降 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利铜业委员会（Cochilco）周四公布的数据显示，智利国营矿业公司 Codelco 2 月份的铜产量同比下降了 6%，降至 9.81 万吨。【原文：Copper production from Chilean state-run miner Codelco dipped 6% year-over-year in February, data from copper commission Cochilco showed on Thursday, slipping to 98,100 metric tons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/copper-output-chiles-codelco-slips-6-february-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTH3DUJR5RLRZBTNPKMWOBNNTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:50:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[象牙海岸威胁提高可可价格以应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[西非国家象牙海岸农业部长周四表示，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提议的关税生效，世界最大的可可生产国象牙海岸可能会采取措施提高可可产品的价格。【原文：Ivory Coast, the world's biggest cocoa producer, could take measures to make the product more expensive if tariffs proposed by U.S. President Donald Trump go into effect, the West African country's agriculture minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/ivory-coast-threatens-more-expensive-cocoa-response-us-tariffs-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHAGSXWFBBIBLNUE7KPWNKI7RU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:28:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智能手机和大豆：卷入中美贸易战的主要产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美贸易战不断升级，导致可能影响多种产品的高额关税。【原文：An escalating trade war between the United States and China is leading to steep tariffs that could affect a wide range of products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/smartphones-soybeans-top-products-caught-up-us-china-trade-war-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANWMT37R4BMDZPVVSYOUTWXU4Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国卫生部长对 COVID 疫苗疗效表示担忧后，Novavax 股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[疫苗生产商 Novavax 的股价周四暴跌 22%，原因是美国卫生与公众服务部部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪在接受哥伦比亚广播公司新闻频道采访时对该公司生产的 COVID-19 疫苗表示担忧。【原文：Vaccine maker Novavax's shares plunged over 22% on Thursday after Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. raised concerns about the company's COVID-19 vaccine in an interview with CBS News.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novavax-shares-tumble-after-us-health-secretary-raises-concerns-over-covid-shots-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPHXCZL3PVONTJVWAE32Z4L4LI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税加剧风险，加拿大出口商寻求贸易保险]]></title><description><![CDATA[保险公司表示，一种鲜为人知的保险产品正在加拿大受到追捧，因为出口商们正在寻求防范美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税所造成的供应商和客户的损失和破产。【原文：A little-known insurance product is gaining traction in Canada as exporters seek to guard against losses and bankruptcies of their suppliers and customers due to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, insurers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadian-exporters-inquire-trade-insurance-trumps-tariffs-heighten-risk-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QGWHEQB5ZPODEX6RC6OR5X4CY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国工业部长表示支持意法半导体首席执行官奇瑞]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国工业部长马克-费拉齐（Marc Ferracci）周四表示，他支持意法半导体公司（STMicroelectronics）首席执行官让-马克-谢里（Jean-Marc Chery），因为该公司董事会两名成员被指控进行内幕交易。【原文：French Industry Minister Marc Ferracci said on Thursday he supported STMicroelectronics CEO Jean-Marc Chery amid allegations of insider trading by two members of its managing board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/french-industry-minister-says-he-supports-stmicroelectronics-ceo-chery-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INJ6QT7ODZN67D2HI5ZBCXM3TE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场动荡刺激资金寻觅，私人信贷二级市场销售额将上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[基金经理和高管们表示，随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战引发的市场波动加剧，迫使他们寻找新的方式来筹集现金，投资者正准备加紧出售其持有的私人信贷资产。【原文：Investors are preparing to step up sales of their private credit holdings, as heightened market volatility unleashed by U.S. President Donald Trump's trade wars forces them to find new ways to raise cash, fund managers and executives say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/private-credit-secondary-sales-set-rise-market-turmoil-spurs-hunt-cash-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STX64ZUCNVKQREDJWADTXIGHQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:25:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Janus Henderson 称，经济衰退迫在眉睫，投资者应减少股票投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[管理着 3,790 亿美元资产的 Janus Henderson 基金经理表示，由于关税可能导致全球经济增长放缓，该公司正建议投资者减持股票，购买更多投资级主权债券。【原文：Janus Henderson, which manages $379 billion in assets, is advising investors to cut stock holdings and buy more investment-grade sovereign bonds as tariffs threaten to slow global growth, a fund manager said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/janus-henderson-says-investors-should-cut-down-exposure-stocks-recession-looms-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFNQL44C4FIR7ABKAGBTWSY5HQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:25:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士称，美国将继续对道明银行和 Balfour Beatty 实施监控]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国司法部决定继续对军事住房公司贝尔福比蒂社区（Balfour Beatty Communities）和加拿大道明银行（TD Bank）进行企业监控，因为特朗普政府正在对这一做法进行审查。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department has decided to keep corporate monitors in place for military housing company Balfour Beatty Communities and Canadian lender TD Bank , amid the Trump administration's ongoing review of the practice, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-keep-monitors-place-td-bank-balfour-beatty-people-familiar-say-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7W5S4SHX25NHROBWUEPHD6A3FE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:17:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比如果经济重回正轨，降息仍有可能]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯汀-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周四表示，降息仍有可能在某个时候出现，但与美国贸易政策的巨大变化有关的不确定性使得目前很难知道经济将如何发展以及美国央行的利率政策应如何调整。【原文：Interest rate cuts remain possible at some point, but uncertainty related to huge changes in U.S. trade policy make it hard to know how the economy will fare for now and how the U.S. central bank's rate policy should be adjusted, Austan Goolsbee, president of the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago, said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-goolsbee-rate-cuts-still-possible-if-economy-gets-back-track-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LO3OGOTZ2JPF5HVSKEM7Y6TB7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场动荡不安，中国茶叶品牌茶奇在美国上市，目标估值 51 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国茶叶连锁企业茶奇网周四表示，冒着波涛汹涌的市场环境，其美国首次公开募股的目标估值将高达 51 亿美元。【原文：Chinese tea chain Chagee said on Thursday it was targeting a valuation of up to $5.1 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, braving choppy market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinese-tea-chain-chagee-aims-raise-411-million-us-ipo-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CW5YB4LNM5O37LSVM4UF7GH5XY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:44:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示，中欧将研究制定电动汽车最低价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人周四表示，欧盟和中国已同意研究对中国制造的电动汽车设定最低价格，而不是欧盟去年征收的关税。【原文：The European Union and China have agreed to look into setting minimum prices on Chinese-made electric vehicles instead of tariffs imposed by the EU last year, a European Commission spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-china-start-talks-lifting-eu-tariffs-chinese-electric-vehicles-handelsblatt-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5TRBCIDO5JX7KC7BIODSB6LGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次威胁对药品征收关税，诺华计划投资 230 亿美元在美国建厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士制药商诺华公司（Novartis）周四表示，该公司计划斥资 230 亿美元在美国新建和扩建 10 家工厂，以应对特朗普政府再次威胁征收药品进口关税。【原文：Swiss drugmaker Novartis said on Thursday it plans to spend $23 billion to build and expand 10 facilities in the U.S., as it grapples with renewed threats of drug import duties from the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-plans-invest-23-billion-us-plants-trump-renews-drug-tariff-threats-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLEKCUM2ZRK47NLZOYJBI2MWQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡普里旨在通过降低价格和亚马逊电商销售重振 Michael Kors]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡普里控股公司在斥资 14 亿美元将范思哲出售给普拉达之后，可能不得不放弃其奢侈时尚品牌的形象，转而依靠中端定价以及与亚马逊网站的合作来打造其 Michael Kors 品牌。【原文：Capri Holdings may have to let go of its image as a luxury fashion house and bank on mid-tier pricing as well as a partnership with Amazon.com for its Michael Kors brand following its $1.4 billion sale of Versace to Prada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/capri-aims-revive-michael-kors-with-lower-prices-amazon-e-commerce-sales-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZ2ZXH2AZNN4LJWIKL7EDMAGZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Modelo 的所有者 Constellation 称，特朗普的移民政策打击了西语裔顾客]]></title><description><![CDATA[公司高管周四表示，由于特朗普打击移民，墨西哥和其他主要市场西班牙裔人口的需求放缓，Modelo Especial 所有者 Constellation Brands 的啤酒销售受到打击。【原文：Modelo Especial owner Constellation Brands' beer sales are taking a hit as demand from Hispanic populations in Mexico and other key markets slows down amid Trump's crackdown on immigration, company executives said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/modelo-owner-constellation-says-trump-immigration-crackdown-hitting-hispanic-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GV7JNVXLRFJZPEVHDPW2KEE6VU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:25:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新液化天然气工厂将提高 Venture Global 的利润，因为 Calcasieu 为长期客户提供服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Global 公司即将开始将路易斯安那州出口终端的液化天然气货物出售给长期客户，而不是全球出价最高的竞标者，但该公司计划在其正在新建的一个更大的终端采用这种有争议但利润丰厚的做法。【原文：Venture Global Inc is about to start selling liquefied natural gas cargoes from a Louisiana export terminal to long-term customers rather than to the highest global bidder, but it plans to employ the controversial but lucrative practice at a new and bigger terminal that it is starting up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-lng-plant-boost-venture-global-profits-calcasieu-serves-long-term-customers-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMDOO2M3XRMEBGQVUVJTU2SHAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>