<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:13:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:13:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税威胁后，美国科技股在欧洲市场下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技巨头股价周一在欧洲市场下跌，此前美国总统特朗普誓言将对欧洲国家实施一系列不断加码的关税，直至美国获准购买格陵兰岛。【原文：Shares of U.S. tech giants ​fell in Europe ‌on Monday after President Donald Trump's vow to implement an increasing ‌range of tariffs on ​European countries until the U.S. is allowed ‍to buy Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-big-tech-stocks-fall-europe-after-trump-tariff-threats-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBMIQURXENPENAMKGLQHDCCK3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:33:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASM国际订单超出市场预期，中国订单反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造设备供应商爱思迈（ASM International）周一公布的2025年第四季度初步订单量超出市场预期，这得益于中国订单的回升。【原文：Computer chip equipment maker ASM International on Monday reported preliminary bookings above market expectations for the fourth quarter of 2025, backed by a rebound in orders from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asm-international-reports-bookings-above-market-view-china-orders-rebound-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZY4MFXLLBJOAHGMEPFYILKQZZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉有望成为加拿大开放中国电动汽车市场后的早期赢家]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家指出，得益于特斯拉早先将上海工厂生产的汽车运往加拿大的举措以及其已建立的加拿大销售网络，该公司有望成为首批受益于加拿大取消对中国产电动汽车100%关税的汽车制造商之一。【原文：Tesla is poised to be one of the first automakers to benefit from Canada's move to remove 100% tariffs on Chinese-made EVs, thanks to its early efforts to ship cars from its Shanghai plant there and its established Canadian sales network, experts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-poised-be-early-winner-canada-opens-door-chinese-made-evs-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INBUWLF6FNLSTDB2D3YNQ3J5SA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:38:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间要闻：美国挑衅最大债权国]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩·科尔为您解析欧洲及全球市场今日展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZUCN6637JO4ZDAJHZ5VECCDKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国总统李明博与意大利总理梅洛尼同意加强人工智能和芯片领域的合作。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据韩国青瓦台消息，韩国总统李在明与意大利总理乔尔吉娅·梅洛尼周一达成共识，将扩大在人工智能、航空航天、芯片及关键矿产等领域的合作。【原文：South Korean President Lee Jae Myung and Italian Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni agreed on Monday to expand cooperation in sectors such as artificial intelligence, aerospace, chips and critical minerals, according to the Blue House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/south-koreas-lee-italys-meloni-agree-strengthen-cooperation-ai-chips-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FO7NIPBLHNLCROTAMYOH3YI27U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者抛售美元寻求避险，因特朗普威胁对格陵兰岛征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者纷纷涌向避险资产，而欧洲各国则准备在周一作出反击。此前美国总统特朗普威胁要对阻碍其收购丹麦北极领地格陵兰岛计划的盟友加征关税。【原文：Investors headed for safe havens while Europe prepared to push back on Monday after U.S President Donald Trump threatened escalating tariffs on allies in the way of his ambition to buy the Danish arctic territory of Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/investors-sell-dollar-seek-safety-trump-threatens-greenland-tariffs-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HLU4VK7XZL6ZFQRKMWHFIGFZQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 02:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价持稳，伊朗抗议活动消退降低美国发动袭击的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一油价基本持平，此前一个交易日曾上涨。伊朗对抗议活动实施致命镇压后，国内动荡平息，降低了美国袭击这个中东主要产油国从而扰乱供应的可能性。【原文：Oil prices were little changed on Monday, after rising in the previous session, as Iran's deadly crackdown on protests quelled the civil unrest in the country, reducing the chance of a U.S. attack on the major Middle Eastern producer that could disrupt supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-steady-ebbing-iranian-protests-lower-chance-us-attack-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6WPLSQTBNJRFLKRUND5RGNLKM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 02:17:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国第四季度GDP增速降至三年低点，全年增速达官方目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国第四季度经济增速放缓至三年低点，主要受国内需求疲软影响。尽管全年增速达到政府预期目标，但贸易摩擦和结构性失衡仍对经济前景构成重大风险。【原文：China's economic growth slowed to a three-year low in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, and while the full-year pace hit Beijing's target, trade tensions and structural imbalances pose significant risks to the outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-q4-gdp-grows-45-yy-just-ahead-market-forecast-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHHXA45R7FMWLOLGJ3J5WGEDJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 02:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美光18亿美元收购案提振力晶科技股价]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾力晶半导体制造股份有限公司股价周一上涨近10%，此前美国内存芯片制造商美光科技宣布将收购该公司的一座晶圆厂。【原文：Shares of Taiwan’s Powerchip Semiconductor Manufacturing Corp rose nearly 10% on Monday after U.S. memory chipmaker Micron Technology said it would buy a fabrication plant from the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/microns-18-billion-acquisition-boosts-powerchip-shares-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VSLHR3PIRORXJLWQACGOKSGLU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本大选临近，消费税下调可能性增大]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本即将举行的提前大选很可能导致消费税率下调，因为执政党和在野党高层周日均强调，有必要通过降税来缓解家庭因生活成本上升而承受的压力。【原文：Japan's expected snap general election is increasingly likely to lead to a cut in the consumption tax rate, as ruling and opposition party executives on Sunday stressed the need to do so to cushion the hit to households from rising living costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-looming-election-heightens-chance-sales-tax-cut-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAFYF3EZRJOEXOENG7Z3HPZ2QE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乐施会称：亿万富翁财富创历史新高，影响力持续扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[反贫困组织乐施会周一表示，去年全球亿万富翁财富增速达到近年平均水平的三倍，创下历史新高，加剧了威胁民主稳定的经济与政治分化。【原文：Billionaire wealth surged at three times its recent pace last year to reach its highest level on record, deepening economic and political divides that threaten democratic stability, anti-poverty group ​Oxfam said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/billionaires-wealth-hits-new-peak-their-clout-grows-oxfam-says-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ID27CUBO3RKUTEAZ3PTQORFJCI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:15:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元承压，避险资产走高，因特朗普就格陵兰问题加码关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周一走低，因特朗普总统就格陵兰问题对欧洲发出最新关税威胁令投资者感到不安，资金涌入避险资产日元和瑞士法郎，市场整体呈现避险情绪。【原文：The dollar fell on Monday, as investors unnerved by U.S. President Donald Trump's latest tariff threats against Europe over Greenland piled ​into the safe-haven yen and Swiss franc, in a broad risk-averse ‌move across markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-under-pressure-safe-havens-rise-trump-ups-tariff-ante-over-greenland-2026-01-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQLLFL3IHBOI5KVMVMBXPKVOKE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚西拉资源公司为特斯拉石墨供应协议争取更多时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚西拉资源公司周一表示，已与特斯拉达成协议，将解决涉嫌违反石墨供应协议的最后期限第三次延期。【原文：Australia's Syrah Resources said on Monday it agreed with Tesla to extend for the third time a deadline to resolve an alleged breach of their graphite supply agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/australias-syrah-resources-buys-more-time-tesla-graphite-supply-deal-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53MQEZBX7JNBJGFBQDQMEV2KIE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:57:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下跌，美元因美国关税威胁走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周一走低，此前总统特朗普威胁对八个欧洲国家加征关税，直至美国获准购买格陵兰岛，此举导致美元兑避险货币日元和瑞士法郎走弱。【原文：U.S. stock futures slid on Monday after President Donald Trump threatened to slap extra tariffs on eight European nations until the U.S. is allowed ​to buy Greenland, pushing the dollar down on the safe-haven yen and Swiss franc.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2KEVZAFGZJCLFJLGQGZV5SGRA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国经济有望实现2025年增长目标，尽管第四季度表现疲软，前景仍趋暗淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国第四季度经济增速可能放缓至三年低点，因内需疲软；尽管全年增速有望接近政府目标，但贸易紧张局势和结构性失衡对经济前景构成重大风险。【原文：China's economic growth likely slowed to a three‑year low in the fourth quarter as domestic demand softened, and while the full‑year pace is ​set to hit close to Beijing's target, trade tensions and structural imbalances pose significant risks to the outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-economy-poised-hit-2025-growth-target-despite-weaker-q4-outlook-darkens-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YICMCWZUHNPHZD4N4OV3JXQCR4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道，欧盟正考虑对美国实施1080亿美元的报复性关税，以回应特朗普对格陵兰岛的威胁。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周日报道，欧洲各国首都可能对美国征收价值930亿欧元（1077.1亿美元）的关税，或限制美国企业进入欧盟市场，以回应美国总统特朗普对反对其收购格陵兰岛计划的北约盟国的威胁。【原文：European capitals may hit the U.S. with 93 billion euros ($107.71 billion) worth of tariffs or restrict American companies from the bloc's market in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's threats to NATO allies opposed to his campaign to take over Greenland, the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-considers-108-billion-retaliatory-tariffs-us-over-trumps-greenland-threat-ft-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIZYL2KUY5JMHII3U6L2CN4MAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:54:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁对欧洲加征更多关税以示对格陵兰岛的立场，市场神经紧绷]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普承诺，在允许美国收购格陵兰岛之前，将对部分欧洲国家的进口商品加征关税。此举可能在周一金融市场重启时引发剧烈震荡。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has promised to implement further tariffs on imports of goods from some European countries until the U.S. is allowed to acquire Greenland, a move that could send a jolt through financial markets when they reopen on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/view-markets-edge-trump-threatens-more-tariffs-europe-over-greenland-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6M23IETIBOK3G5V2RWUTVUCP4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[允许优步、来福车在以色列运营的法案获委员会批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列部长委员会周日批准了一项法律，允许优步和Lyft等拼车服务在以色列运营，旨在降低出租车费用。【原文：An Israeli ministerial committee on Sunday approved a law that would allow shared ride hailing services such as Uber and Lyft to operate in Israel in a bid to lower taxi costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bill-allow-uber-lyft-israel-gains-committee-approval-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5MF2CDGDZLCHCCDON5OCXG5BA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:13:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰表示，欧盟必将对美国任何新关税采取报复措施，这一点毋庸置疑。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟将对美国因格陵兰问题对欧洲盟友实施关税威胁采取报复措施，但爱尔兰总理周日表示，考虑动用欧盟"反胁迫工具"为时尚早。【原文：The European Union will retaliate if U.S. tariff threats against European allies over Greenland materialise, but it is premature to consider using the bloc's "Anti-Coercion Instrument", Ireland's prime minister said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/be-no-doubt-eu-will-retaliate-any-new-us-tariffs-ireland-says-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6V5KJTWTGFNW3G4KB3WAZ34IOA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁对欧洲加征关税，全球市场面临新一轮冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球市场本周面临新一轮波动，此前美国总统特朗普誓言对八个欧洲国家征收关税，直至美国获准购买格陵兰岛。【原文：Global markets face a fresh bout of volatility this week after President Donald Trump vowed to slap tariffs on eight European nations until the U.S. is allowed to buy Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/world-markets-face-fresh-jolt-trump-vows-tariffs-europe-over-greenland-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIFGP7SY2RLT3LWPSUECIQKT2I</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:58:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《金融时报》报道，红杉资本将与新加坡政府投资公司、Coatue共同投资Anthropic公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周日援引知情人士消息报道，风险投资公司红杉资本正与新加坡政府投资公司（GIC）及美国投资机构Coatue共同参与Anthropic的融资轮，该轮融资目标为250亿美元，公司估值达3500亿美元。【原文：Venture capital firm Sequoia is joining ​Singapore's GIC and U.S. investor Coatue in ‌a funding round for Anthropic which aims to raise $25 billion at a $350 billion valuation, the Financial Times reported on Sunday, citing sources ‌familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/sequoia-join-gic-coatue-anthropic-investment-ft-reports-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXHLIYIIABL5FFVYHV7KDYVLYE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:12:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国官员称将与美国谈判争取芯片关税优惠条款]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统府发言人周日在电视简报会上表示，韩国将就美国对内存芯片进口征收关税寻求有利条件。【原文：South Korea will seek favourable terms for U.S. tariffs on imports of memory chips, a presidential office spokesperson said at a televised briefing on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-negotiate-with-us-favourable-chip-tariff-terms-official-says-2026-01-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQNLVTGCGFN53DA2XOPIY4YTSY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:53:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府大力推动降低汽车价格，淡化电动汽车发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府汽车政策最高官员周六宣称，通过取消车辆排放法规，联邦政府正致力于降低汽车价格，因为购车负担能力仍是美国民众的核心关切。【原文：The Trump administration's top auto policy officials on Saturday touted federal efforts to lower car prices by eliminating vehicle emissions regulations, as affordability remains a key concern among Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-administration-touts-push-lower-car-prices-de-emphasize-evs-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XODH3PMLP5JRHHTRR4SFX6QWKY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员称欧盟应考虑将格陵兰关税问题与美欧贸易协议分开处理]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔周六表示，欧洲是否愿意因格陵兰问题而面临特朗普总统对部分欧洲国家提出新的关税威胁，取决于欧洲自身的决定。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Saturday it is up to Europe to decide whether it wants to raise new tariff threats from President Donald Trump against some European countries over Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/us-official-says-eu-should-consider-separating-greenland-tariff-issue-us-trade-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7ADNTJZCBI3ZMRW5D7RKB35WE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:25:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称从未向摩根大通的戴蒙提供美联储主席职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周六表示，他从未提议提名摩根大通首席执行官杰米·戴蒙担任美联储主席一职，这与本周的一份报道相矛盾。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Saturday said he never offered to nominate JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon for the job of Federal Reserve chair, contradicting a report this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-he-never-offered-fed-chair-job-jpmorgans-dimon-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LKKN2XPEVKJLBHH5MEOS37J44</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普誓言对八个欧洲国家征收关税以示对格陵兰岛的立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周六誓言，将在欧洲盟国对美国实施关税升级浪潮直至美国获准购买格陵兰岛，此举加剧了围绕这座丹麦广袤北极岛屿未来归属的争端。【原文：President Donald Trump on Saturday vowed to implement a wave of increasing tariffs on European allies until the United States is allowed to buy Greenland, escalating a row over the future of Denmark's vast Arctic island.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-vows-tariffs-eight-european-nations-over-greenland-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RFQ6EYQ7SFNY3GPVXSRL43CLAU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院就美联储委员丽莎·库克任命案展开角逐，测试特朗普经济权力的边界]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，在唐纳德·特朗普总统第二任期开始四个月后，美国最高法院就表明了其意图保护美联储免受政治干预的立场。本周三，当大法官们审议特朗普解雇美联储理事丽莎·库克的合法性时，他们维护美国央行独立性的决心将面临考验。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court signaled four months into Donald Trump's second presidential term last year its interest in shielding the Federal Reserve from political interference. When the justices on Wednesday consider the legality of his bid to fire Fed Governor Lisa Cook, their willingness to preserve the U.S. central bank's independence will be ​put to the test.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/supreme-court-tests-limits-trumps-power-over-economy-fight-over-feds-lisa-cook-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K36EAWN3AFNNLI5AI6WRR42KQ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国首席执行官们对特朗普的政策提出温和反对]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国商会首席执行官苏珊娜·克拉克于昏暗的宴会厅发表演讲时，她呼吁企业高管在捍卫自由市场对抗政府管控时"无所畏惧"，并强调美国必须保持"对世界的开放，对全球人才、商品、思想和创新的开放"。【原文：Speaking before a darkened ballroom on Thursday, U.S. Chamber of Commerce CEO Suzanne Clark called on executives to be "fearless" in defense of free markets over government control and said the U.S. must remain "open to the world, open to the global exchange of talent and goods and ideas and innovation."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/american-ceos-push-back-trump-mildly-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLNDXE7SGNKC7MSJ7AQY3V6ISY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克要求OpenAI和微软归还高达1340亿美元的"不当得利"]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的法庭文件显示，埃隆·马斯克正向OpenAI和微软索赔高达1340亿美元，他主张自己有权获得这两家公司因其早期支持人工智能初创企业而获得的"不当得利"。【原文：Elon Musk is seeking up to $134 billion from OpenAI and Microsoft , arguing he deserves the "wrongful gains" that they received from his early support of the artificial-intelligence startup, according to a court filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musk-seeks-up-134-billion-openai-microsoft-wrongful-gains-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JO4CNN6IHNJATCSU6D4HXCFEMA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道称欧盟将禁止中国供应商进入关键基础设施领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周六报道，欧盟正着手逐步淘汰该地区关键基础设施中的中国制造设备，禁止华为、中兴等公司进入电信网络、太阳能系统和安检扫描仪领域。【原文：The European Union is moving to phase out Chinese‑made equipment from the zone's critical infrastructure, barring companies such as Huawei and ZTE from telecom networks, solar systems and security scanners, the Financial Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-bar-chinese-suppliers-critical-infrastructure-ft-reports-2026-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OEF7ZZ64ZKQJO733PV2PSBMCY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 05:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>