<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 11:33:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 11:33:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[民主党参议员称，特朗普政府逮捕哈利勒时滥用了移民法]]></title><description><![CDATA[由八名民主党参议员组成的小组周五指责特朗普政府滥用美国移民法，逮捕哥伦比亚大学学生马哈茂德-哈利勒（Mahmoud Khalil），因为他参加了支持巴勒斯坦的抗议活动。【原文：A group of eight Democratic Senators on Friday accused the Trump administration of abusing the country's immigration laws in arresting Columbia University student Mahmoud Khalil over his participation in pro-Palestinian protests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-abused-immigration-laws-with-khalils-arrest-democratic-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3N44KHDKJ5LORPSM5H5K3WYVL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道联邦调查局缩减国内恐怖主义调查的人员编制和追踪范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的消息人士透露，联邦调查局已经削减了一个专注于国内恐怖主义的办公室的人员编制，并取消了一个用于追踪此类调查的工具，这一转变可能会削弱执法部门打击白人至上主义者和反政府极端分子的能力。【原文：The FBI has cut staffing in an office focused on domestic terrorism and has scrapped a tool used to track such investigations, in a shift that could undermine law enforcement’s ability to counter white supremacists and anti-government extremists, according to sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fbi-scales-back-staffing-tracking-domestic-terrorism-probes-sources-say-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VEU7H7Y6ZIPNB53PYSB6LLDRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:11:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普横行国会，选民对民主党的反应感到沮丧]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党选民希瑟-奥格登（Heather Ogden）对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统攻击联邦官僚机构的行为感到愤怒，她希望自己的政党能表现出更多的战斗力。【原文：Democratic voter Heather Ogden is furious at President Donald Trump's assault on the federal bureaucracy - and she wishes her party would show more fight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/voters-frustrated-with-democrats-response-trump-runs-roughshod-over-congress-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRWZJ7MY6VMCBIFZ5NHRQZCSRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普以大刀阔斧的行动考验美国宪法秩序]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）重返白宫后大刀阔斧地行使权力，这是对 18 世纪建立的美国宪法制衡体系的考验，因为总统几乎没有遇到国会的抵制，与联邦司法机构的紧张关系也在升级。【原文：Donald Trump's sweeping assertion of power since returning to the White House is testing the U.S. constitutional system of checks and balances established in the 18th century as the president faces scant resistance from Congress and tensions with the federal judiciary escalate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/with-sweeping-actions-trump-tests-us-constitutional-order-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTSD6I6YXJLXPFVXD6PZRZ3GME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫审查联邦机构第二轮大规模裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，白宫官员正在审查联邦机构的裁员计划，预计此举将导致在未来几周内大规模解雇数千名政府工作人员。【原文：White House officials are reviewing federal agencies' downsizing plans, a move expected to result in the mass firing of thousands of government workers within the coming weeks, two sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-begins-review-federal-agency-plans-second-round-mass-layoffs-sources-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXCE2XQOCFOJNPNHWUTYL6YZA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普国家税务总局高管声称国税局技术预算可节省 15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[受特朗普政府委托负责审查美国国内税收署技术现代化项目的科技初创企业高管周四表示，他已经取消了税务机构预算中价值约 15 亿美元的合同。【原文：The tech startup executive charged by the Trump administration with reviewing the Internal Revenue Service's technology modernization program said on Thursday that he has canceled contracts worth about $1.5 billion from the tax agency's budget.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-doge-executive-claims-15-billion-savings-irs-technology-budget-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46GZZZ7S3FO6FF2AK4CSGAIBJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州大学洛杉矶分校因 2024 年暴徒袭击亲巴勒斯坦抗议者而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份法庭文件显示，加州大学洛杉矶分校周四因 2024 年暴徒袭击支持巴勒斯坦的抗议者而被起诉，当时正值美国校园抗议以色列加沙战争运动的高峰期。【原文：The University of California, Los Angeles, was sued on Thursday over a 2024 mob attack on pro-Palestinian protesters at the height of the U.S. campus protest movement against Israel's war in Gaza, a court filing showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ucla-sued-over-2024-mob-attack-pro-palestinian-protesters-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PA5W5UZQIZKG5CX3UPTBW2HAYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 02:56:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，五角大楼将向马斯克介绍可能与中国开战的绝密计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周四援引美国官员的话报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的亲密盟友、亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周五将听取五角大楼关于美国军方应对可能与中国爆发的任何战争的计划的简报。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk, U.S. President Donald Trump's close ally, is due to be briefed on Friday by the Pentagon on the U.S. military's plan for any war that might break out with China, the New York Times reported on Thursday, citing U.S. officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-brief-musk-top-secret-plan-potential-war-with-china-nyt-reports-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2QAKQXIDWNPQJDGUAW46KAZXQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 02:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称五角大楼将授予美国空军下一代战斗机合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[据了解该计划的消息人士称，五角大楼最快将于本周五宣布其关于下一代战斗机合同的决定，该合同最初价值超过 200 亿美元，尽管早些时候人们对预算限制和优先事项转移表示担忧。【原文：The Pentagon is set to announce its decision on a next-generation fighter jet contract initially worth more than $20 billion as soon as Friday, despite earlier concerns about budget constraints and shifting priorities, sources briefed on the plan said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/pentagon-set-award-us-air-forces-next-generation-fighter-jet-contract-sources-2025-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L27K3SOFGZPFXA67FYSQHQQNYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普撤回针对保罗-魏斯律师事务所的行政命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，他将撤回针对纽约律师事务所保罗-魏斯-里夫金-沃顿-加里森（Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison）的行政命令。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday he is withdrawing an executive order targeting New York law firm Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-withdraws-executive-order-targeting-paul-weiss-law-firm-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66OAJVZ3RVONZO7UR6ZKGLTRTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 23:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特斯拉以旧换新在马斯克的反弹中再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃德蒙兹（Edmunds）的数据显示，在抗议首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）担任美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）顾问的浪潮中，本月特斯拉电动汽车的交易量创下历史新高。【原文：Motorists have traded in a record number of Tesla electric vehicles this month, Edmunds data showed, amid a wave of protests against CEO Elon Musk's work as an adviser to U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-trade-ins-pace-record-high-amid-musk-backlash-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22DOJTRRRBOMLBZ32RZSGKGU3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 22:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国疫苗咨询会议改在四月举行]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部发言人周四在一封电子邮件中说，一个为美国疾病控制中心提供建议的免疫专家小组将于四月召开会议，此前的一次会议曾被推迟。【原文：A panel of immunization experts that advises the U.S. Centers for Disease Control will convene in April after a previous meeting had been postponed, a spokesman for the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services said in an email on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-vaccine-advisory-meeting-rescheduled-april-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GHCZSZTFJOM5BYZYRVRLZMJLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 22:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准 Alnylam 治疗罕见心脏病的药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四批准了 Alnylam 公司治疗一种罕见致命心脏病的药物，从而允许一种新型药物进入由辉瑞公司的大片药物 Vyndaqel 占据的市场。【原文：U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved Alnylam's drug to treat a rare and deadly heart disease on Thursday, allowing the entry of a new type of medicine in a market dominated by Pfizer's blockbuster Vyndaqel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-alnylams-drug-rare-heart-condition-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6F4B6RSL7ZLWLHQ4RXIW2FHQR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官禁止特朗普政府驱逐亲巴勒斯坦学生]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴达尔-汗-苏里（Badar Khan Suri）是一名在华盛顿乔治敦大学学习的印度男子，他的律师称美国在指控他损害美国外交政策后试图将其驱逐出境。【原文：A judge has ordered President Donald Trump's administration not to deport Badar Khan Suri, an Indian man studying at Washington's Georgetown University whose lawyer has said the United States was seeking to remove him after it accused him of harming U.S. foreign policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/judge-bars-trump-administration-deporting-pro-palestinian-student-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMX6XFZWVRJ23OLSEYPZXWTT7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:38:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普任命的法官录制枪支教程抨击法院裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国上诉法院的一位保守派法官采取了不同寻常的措施，录下了自己操作几把手枪并解释其装置的过程，以此来解释他的同事们为何错误地支持了加利福尼亚州禁止装弹量超过 10 发的弹夹的法律。【原文：A conservative U.S. appeals court judge took the unusual step on Thursday of recording himself handling several handguns and explaining their mechanisms to explain why his colleagues had wrongly upheld a California law banning magazines that hold more than 10 rounds of ammunition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-appointed-judge-records-gun-tutorial-slam-court-ruling-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHIGOBW6JFLNXATR7QKU4A33ZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新墨西哥州落选候选人在枪击民主党官员的阴谋中被判有罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[检察官周四表示，新墨西哥州陪审团认定一名失败的共和党州众议员候选人在阿尔伯克基民主党官员家中发生的一系列驾车枪击案中的所有罪名成立。【原文：A New Mexico jury found a failed Republican candidate for the state House of Representatives guilty on all counts related to a series of drive-by shootings at the homes of Democratic officials in Albuquerque, prosecutors said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/failed-new-mexico-candidate-found-guilty-plot-shoot-democratic-officials-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFOAQYHGSZKNZOAFPQVVVDMUE4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构呼吁对标志性桥梁进行紧急安全评估]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会周四呼吁对 68 座桥梁进行紧急安全评估，其中包括金门大桥、切萨皮克湾大桥、布鲁克林大桥、乔治-华盛顿大桥和芝加哥天桥等标志性桥梁。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board on Thursday called for urgent safety assessments of 68 bridges including iconic crossings like the Golden Gate, Chesapeake Bay, Brooklyn, George Washington and Chicago Skyway bridges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-agency-calls-urgent-safety-assessments-iconic-bridges-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IH7DA5W4H5KLVFM6LOXTOZMAGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 20:54:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：纽蒙特公司前高管被任命为美国能源委员会矿业监督员]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉这一任命的消息人士告诉路透社，前纽蒙特公司高管大卫-科普利（David Copley）已被任命为美国国家能源主导委员会矿业投资组合的负责人。【原文：Former Newmont executive David Copley has been named to oversee the mining portfolio for the U.S. National Energy Dominance Council, two sources familiar with the appointment told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/former-newmont-executive-tapped-oversee-mining-us-energy-council-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIUCOQ62OBLGLBUBGWRGLVVVQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 20:38:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称白宫考虑由伯吉斯领导疾病预防控制中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟知内情的消息人士透露，白宫在上周撤回了对疫苗问题评论家戴夫-韦尔登（Dave Weldon）的提名后，正在考虑由前共和党众议员迈克尔-伯吉斯（Michael Burgess）来管理美国疾病控制和预防中心。【原文：The White House is considering former Republican Representative Michael Burgess to run the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention after withdrawing the nomination of vaccine critic Dave Weldon last week, according to three sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/white-house-considering-burgess-lead-cdc-sources-say-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HH2ZCXNWJZIPBPULQ4SWTZUCWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 20:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府将开放阿拉斯加更多土地用于石油和天然气钻探]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国内政部长道格-伯格姆（Doug Burgum）周四宣布，将采取措施开放更多的石油和天然气租赁面积，并取消对在阿拉斯加修建液化天然气管道和采矿道路的限制，以执行唐纳德-特朗普总统的行政命令，消除该州能源开发的障碍。【原文：U.S. Interior Secretary Doug Burgum on Thursday announced steps to open up more acreage for oil and gas leasing and lift restrictions on building an LNG pipeline and mining road in Alaska, carrying out President Donald Trump's executive order to remove barriers to energy development in the state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-open-more-alaska-acres-oil-gas-drilling-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZPCAUZ7AZI73D5KBWESH6SRGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 20:31:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止埃隆-马斯克的 DOGE 获取社保记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周四阻止了埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的政府效率部（Department of Government Efficiency）查阅社会保障记录，作为其在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统领导下追捕欺诈和浪费行为的一部分，并称这种行为是 "钓鱼探险"。【原文：A federal judge on Thursday blocked Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency from accessing Social Security records as part of its hunt under President Donald Trump for fraud and waste, calling the effort a "fishing expedition."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-elon-musks-doge-accessing-social-security-records-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5HU6MGWSNLSNIL6TD3EXFPYWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 20:25:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官阻止埃隆-马斯克的 DOGE 获取社保记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周四阻止了埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的政府效率部（Department of Government Efficiency）查阅社会保障记录，作为其在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统领导下追捕欺诈和浪费行为的一部分，并称这种行为是 "钓鱼探险"。【原文：A federal judge on Thursday blocked Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency from accessing Social Security records as part of its hunt under President Donald Trump for fraud and waste, calling the effort a "fishing expedition."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-blocks-elon-musks-doge-accessing-social-security-records-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5HU6MGWSNLSNIL6TD3EXFPYWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 20:25:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空航班因机组人员将奥兰多滑行道误认为跑道而取消起飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局称，美国西南航空公司一架航班周四在奥兰多机场起飞时，误在滑行道而非跑道上起飞，导致飞机中止起飞。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said a Southwest Airlines flight at Orlando airport on Thursday aborted takeoff after it mistakenly began to depart on a taxiway rather than the runway.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/southwest-flight-cancels-takeoff-after-crew-mistook-orlando-taxiway-runway-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4KY5DFJ4FPRTDVA3VYDAORDBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 20:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局宣布建立在线数据库追踪食品污染物]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四推出了一个可在线搜索的数据库，列出了人类食品中的污染物含量，这反映了卫生部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪自上任以来为减少食品中的化学物质所做的不懈努力。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration on Thursday launched an online searchable database listing contaminant levels in human foods, reflecting Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.'s ongoing efforts to reduce chemicals in food since taking office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-announces-online-database-track-food-contaminants-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAMAE4KCFROVPBI3UGC3I3TY54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 19:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国延长纽约结束曼哈顿拥堵计划的最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府周四将纽约州3月21日结束曼哈顿交通拥堵收费项目的最后期限延长了30天。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration on Thursday extended by 30 days a March 21 deadline for New York state to end Manhattan's congestion pricing program.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-extends-deadline-new-york-end-manhattan-congestion-program-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7I4TSIQCUBLHPBJIBRNUOISAJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 19:46:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在白宫签署命令，为解散教育部再下一城]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将于周四签署一项行政命令，试图解散教育部，将学校政策交由各州制定，兑现让保守派人士振奋、让教育倡导者担忧的竞选承诺。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will sign an executive order on Thursday that seeks to dismantle the Department of Education and leave school policy in the hands of states, making good on a campaign promise that has energized conservatives and worried education advocates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-takes-fresh-stab-dismantling-department-education-with-order-signing-white-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YF6XYQGREBN4FIPFNOKR53GERM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 19:27:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国拒绝墨西哥关于科罗拉多河水特别输送通道的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院周四表示，美国将首次拒绝墨西哥提出的一项非条约请求，即为科罗拉多河水向提华纳提供一条特别输送渠道。【原文：The U.S. Department of State said on Thursday that the United States will for the first time deny a non-treaty request by Mexico for a special delivery channel for Colorado River water to be delivered to Tijuana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-denies-mexicos-request-special-delivery-channel-colorado-river-water-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2URHGWJUBIFDPJRX5EZT4CPDU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 19:24:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[玛丽亚-凯莉赢得《我想要的圣诞礼物就是你》版权官司]]></title><description><![CDATA[流行歌手玛丽亚-凯莉（Mariah Carey）打赢了一场官司，这场官司声称玛丽亚-凯莉非法抄袭了她的节日巨作《All I Want for Christmas Is You》中的同名乡村歌曲元素。【原文：Pop singer Mariah Carey defeated a lawsuit claiming she illegally copied elements of her holiday megahit "All I Want for Christmas Is You" from a country song of the same name.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/mariah-carey-wins-copyright-lawsuit-over-all-i-want-christmas-is-you-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKSVOLQQT5N73PKI4ZMQDTV3KE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 18:40:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学在特朗普最后期限前满足对校园抗议活动的要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学周四将在最后期限前对九项关于收紧校园抗议限制的要求做出回应，特朗普政府称，这些要求是就恢复被暂停的4亿美元联邦拨款展开谈判的先决条件。【原文：Columbia University faced a Thursday deadline to respond to nine demands on tightening restrictions on campus protests that the Trump administration says are preconditions for opening talks on restoring $400 million in suspended federal funding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/columbia-up-against-trump-deadline-meeting-demands-over-campus-protests-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RA6OKG2CYBOR5NGPUHO6GTOJ5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 17:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部长称，针对特斯拉的纵火犯将面临指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部长帕梅拉-邦迪（Pamela Bondi）周四表示，已有三人因特斯拉汽车经销商和充电站纵火事件受到指控。
司法部没有具体说明指控罪名，但表示这些人每人将面临 5 到 20 年的监禁。【原文：U.S. Attorney General Pamela Bondi on Thursday said three people have been charged related to arson incidents at Tesla car dealerships and charging stations.
Without specifying the charges, the Justice Department said the individuals each face between five and 20 years in prison.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-attorney-general-says-alleged-arsonists-targeting-tesla-face-charges-2025-03-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVGWYLDO7NLRTEBDME372Y6JDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 17:41:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>