<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:23:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:23:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴拿马总统表示港口合同不会授予单一运营商]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马总统何塞·劳尔·穆利诺周四表示，将不再向单一企业授予运营权，此前香港和记黄埔有限公司运营的两座港口已由其持有并运营近三十年。【原文：Panamanian President Jose Raul Mulino said on Thursday that the concession of contracts to operate two ports held and operated for nearly three decades by Hong Kong's CK Hutchison Holdings will "never again" be issued to a single company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/panamas-president-says-port-contracts-will-not-be-issued-single-operator-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUYPEMNPVZJVZD5QQBXP2SXGOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威瑞森消费者业务部门负责人离职，公司正全力推进转型计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国无线运营商威瑞森公司消费者业务部门负责人索米亚纳拉扬·桑帕斯即将离职，该公司正在新任首席执行官丹·舒尔曼的领导下实施转型计划。【原文：Verizon consumer division chief Sowmyanarayan Sampath is stepping down as the U.S. wireless carrier mounts a turnaround effort under its new CEO Dan Schulman.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/verizon-consumer-division-head-departing-company-mounts-turnaround-effort-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CX5E5ZPR5PFFLXHAOE2XDVVGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月职位空缺降至逾五年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国12月职位空缺降至逾五年最低水平，此前因2025年末劳动力市场状况趋缓，上月数据亦被下调。【原文：U.S. job openings dropped to the lowest level in more than five years in December and data for the prior month was revised lower amid a softening in labor market conditions at the end of 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-job-openings-drop-more-than-five-year-low-december-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KW2ANSKW6NORDEEG7TYKL6WORY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德将就Wegovy配制问题对Hims & Hers采取法律行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德周四表示，将对Hims & Hers公司采取法律行动。此前这家在线远程医疗公司宣布，将开始提供该丹麦集团Wegovy药片的复方仿制药，每月售价49美元。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Thursday it would take legal action against Hims & Hers after the online telehealth company said it will begin offering compounded copies of the Danish group's Wegovy pill at an introductory price of $49 per month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/novo-nordisk-take-legal-action-against-hims-hers-wegovy-compounding-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4FK3HJVLVMKNO45WJF2VISAII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton因需求疲软第三季度营收表现疲软，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Peloton Interactive周四预测第三季度营收低于华尔街预期，指出其健身设备需求疲软，股价应声暴跌约25%，跌至近一年半以来的最低点。【原文：Peloton Interactive forecast third-quarter revenue below Wall Street estimates on Thursday, pointing to weak demand for its fitness equipment, with shares plunging about 25% to their lowest level in about a year and a half.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/peloton-flags-soft-third-quarter-revenue-subdued-demand-shares-slump-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMYM6RH47RKLJHSKIYSFVXN53Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员要求美国政府披露联邦航空管理局局长是否出售了其持有的航空公司股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名美国民主党参议员周四向交通部询问，联邦航空管理局局长是否已出售其持有的共和航空股份，以及他是否将因未在规定的剥离期限前出售股份而被迫放弃相关收益。【原文：Three Democratic U.S. senators on Thursday asked the Transportation Department if the head of the Federal Aviation Administration has sold his shares in Republic Airways and whether he will be forced to give up any gains for not selling the stake before a required divestment date.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/senators-ask-us-disclose-if-faa-administrator-sold-stake-airline-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMHNSJVXXZIDVB26RAHQGDXSBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，是否因货币政策选择起诉沃什取决于特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周四拒绝承诺，若特朗普政府提名的美联储主席人选凯文·沃什推行与总统立场相左的货币政策，政府将不会起诉他。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent declined on Thursday to commit the Trump administration to not suing Kevin Warsh, its nominee to be Federal Reserve Chair, if he follows a monetary path opposed by the president.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-up-trump-whether-warsh-might-be-sued-monetary-policy-choices-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOAKAYAL6NLOFJDNKYOWOCKEIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉能可与力拓第三次终止合并谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓集团周四表示，已终止与嘉能可的收购谈判。此次收购本可缔造全球最大的矿业公司，但双方未能就为股东创造价值的协议达成共识。【原文：Rio Tinto said on Thursday that it was no longer in talks with Glencore about a takeover that would have created the world's largest mining company as it could not reach an agreement that would deliver value to its shareholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/glencore-rio-abandon-merger-talks-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XCFB7XG2JMDFLZFFMXKZDTOWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:23:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主要央行分道扬镳之年]]></title><description><![CDATA[主要经济体的央行正分道扬镳：澳大利亚本周时隔两年首次加息，而其他央行即便已结束宽松政策，仍采取更为谨慎的立场。【原文：Central banks in big economies are parting ways, with Australia this week raising interest rates for the first time in two years, while others are taking a more cautious approach even if they are likely done with easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/global-markets-central-banks-graphic-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEGO4QXNXJK5BFTCFPTDL47SSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，尽管已达成与凯雷集团的交易，竞争对手仍在竞购卢克石油资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位知情人士透露，尽管俄罗斯能源巨头卢克石油公司上周已初步同意将其全球资产组合出售给美国私募股权公司凯雷集团，但包括雪佛龙在内的至少两家公司仍在竞购这些资产。【原文：At least two companies including Chevron are vying for Lukoil’s global assets despite the Russian energy company's initial agreement last week to sell the portfolio to U.S. private equity firm Carlyle, four sources familiar with the conversations say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/rival-bidders-pursue-lukoil-assets-despite-carlyle-deal-sources-say-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RVDXJJVHBM3TJSWPFLRCLBZTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[查看Hims and Hers Health的复合制剂Wegovy药丸产品引发市场担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hims & Hers宣布将开始提供诺和诺德公司Wegovy药片的复合版本，首月优惠价为每月49美元。【原文：Hims & Hers said it would begin offering compounded versions of Novo Nordisk's Wegovy pill at an introductory price of $49 per month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/view-hims-hers-healths-compounded-wegovy-pill-offering-fuels-market-jitters-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFKXNJQGLNIW5OHC7UO7YZ5LYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:06:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR联合首席执行官表示，该公司约7%的资产配置于软件领域。]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司KKR的联合首席执行官周四表示，该公司投资组合中约7%为软件资产。此番表态是对市场波动的回应——此前市场担忧人工智能领域可能引发的行业颠覆及潜在亏损。【原文：Investment firm KKR holds around 7% of its portfolio in software assets, its co-CEO said on Thursday, responding to market volatility prompted by fears of disruption and potential losses in the sector linked to artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kkr-expects-arctos-sports-group-build-more-than-100-bln-assets-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D45E7S3ATRMLXPYN3Z7WUFHJ6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:41:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币交易所Gemini计划裁员最多200人，退出欧洲和澳大利亚市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[双子星空间站（Gemini Space Station）——由卡梅伦·温克莱沃斯和泰勒·温克莱沃斯兄弟创立的加密货币交易所——周四宣布，在更广泛的成本削减计划下，已批准一项全球裁员最多200人的方案，并将业务范围仅限于美国和新加坡。【原文：Gemini Space Station , the cryptocurrency exchange founded by Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, said on Thursday it approved a plan to cut up to 200 jobs globally and operate only in the U.S. and Singapore, under a broader cost-cutting effort.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/gemini-space-station-plans-cut-200-jobs-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VH4OTZ7EBVLV5IPRK3OJFBBAKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:38:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯洛文尼亚拟立法禁止15岁以下青少年使用社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯洛文尼亚副总理马泰·阿尔康周四在新闻发布会上表示，该国正准备立法草案，拟禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体。【原文：Slovenia is preparing draft legislation to ban social media access for children under 15, Deputy Prime Minister Matej Arcon told a news conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/slovenia-preparing-law-ban-access-social-media-minors-under-15-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5O225PXJJNX7CLMP6HMXOCE74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：美国航空与美联航在芝加哥的对决成为扭亏为盈承诺的关键考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空正试图向投资者证明，其能够缩小与竞争对手的利润差距并实现持续扭亏为盈。在芝加哥奥黑尔国际机场与美联航日益激烈的对峙，已成为检验这一承诺的最直观试金石——这场较量将直接影响2026年的业绩表现。【原文：American Airlines is trying to convince investors it can narrow the profit gap with rivals and deliver a sustained turnaround. The escalating showdown with United Airlines at Chicago's O'Hare International Airport has become one of the clearest tests of that promise — with real stakes for results in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/americans-chicago-showdown-with-united-airlines-becomes-key-test-turnaround-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">746LG7KJ6ZLWNEU3YYAJ6CULUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:26:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hershey sees strong 2026 even as cocoa costs weigh]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hershey forecast annual sales and profit above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, supported by resilient demand for its confectionery and salty snacks and continued benefits of earlier price hikes implemented to absorb rising costs.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hershey-sees-strong-2026-even-cocoa-costs-weigh-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXIXT4HBAFKRDCR5UFD5OOOGLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:11:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IQVIA forecasts weak annual profit on higher interest expenses]]></title><description><![CDATA[Healthcare data and clinical research provider IQVIA Holdings on Thursday forecast annual profit below Wall Street expectations, weighed down by higher interest costs, even as strong fourth-quarter results underscored improving demand from pharmaceutical clients.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/iqvia-forecasts-weak-annual-profit-higher-interest-expenses-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNJGFMGETBOFZKU3APPPAZEH2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI unveils AI agent service as part of push to attract businesses]]></title><description><![CDATA[Your next coworker might be generated by AI.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/openai-unveils-ai-agent-service-part-push-attract-businesses-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXXP6N76KFJSXLXSJ7A6XIXYAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[India monitoring evolving crypto trading to ensure tax compliance, top tax official says]]></title><description><![CDATA[India is talking to cryptocurrency exchanges to assess evolving trading activity as it seeks oversight over newer crypto products, according to a top tax official.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-monitoring-evolving-crypto-trading-ensure-tax-compliance-top-tax-official-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIYBV7SCPZMEDO6KISJGPQI6IU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US weekly jobless claims increase more than expected]]></title><description><![CDATA[The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased more than expected last week, likely boosted by snowstorms across much of the country, but labor market conditions remain stable.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-more-than-expected-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AF6IYLJDCRMONDTAHN6LZOIYPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Hims and Hers Health launches compounded copy of Wegovy pill at $49]]></title><description><![CDATA[Online telehealth company Hims and Hers Health will begin offering compounded copies of Novo Nordisk's new Wegovy pill at an introductory price of $49 per month, the company said Thursday, about $100 less than the brand name.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hims-hers-health-launches-copy-wegovy-pill-49-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOOFLPU2XNIF3BGG7M33WXOYBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球非美国股票基金吸引资金流入，投资者避开估值过高的美国科技股]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球非美国股票基金正吸引强劲资金流入，投资者正从估值过高的美国科技股转向更具多样性、估值较低的海外市场，这一趋势由美国宏观经济风险和美元走弱所驱动。【原文：Global ex-U.S. equity funds are attracting strong inflows as investors shift away from high-valuation U.S. tech stocks toward more diversified, lower-valued markets abroad, driven by U.S. macro risks and a weaker dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-funds-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXNJL5QKYNJ6LDT5D4GBAFVMV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙任命新任战略、交易及业务发展负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司周四公布了将于2026年生效的高层领导层变动计划，多名资深高管即将退休，内部候选人将接任战略、贸易及业务发展等关键岗位。【原文：Chevron Corp on Thursday outlined senior leadership changes that will take effect in 2026, with several long-serving executives retiring and internal candidates stepping into key roles across strategy, trading and business development.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-names-new-heads-strategy-trading-business-development-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LT3BQCJMAJLB5NOM6WJEHI7MSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:22:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉夫·劳伦对利润率的警示盖过了强于预期的季度销售额]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉夫·劳伦周四公布的第三季度销售额超出华尔街预期，但这家奢侈品零售商警告称美国关税将导致利润率承压，其股价在盘前交易中下跌6.6%。【原文：Ralph Lauren posted third-quarter sales that topped Wall Street estimates on Thursday, but the luxury retailer's warning of margin pressure tied to U.S. tariffs sent its shares down 6.6% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ralph-lauren-posts-third-quarter-sales-beat-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAPMOCXUBRKS3JOGFLOWARBRBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蓝猫基金盈利超预期，资产管理规模突破3000亿美元里程碑]]></title><description><![CDATA[蓝猫公司周四公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，其管理资产规模激增22%，突破3000亿美元大关，推动其股价在盘前交易中上涨2%。【原文：Blue Owl beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Thursday and posted a 22% surge in assets under management that crossed the $300 billion milestone, sending its shares up 2% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blue-owl-beats-profit-estimates-aum-crosses-300-billion-milestone-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THKKDINVIFIMFKWLFA5C6732HA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:57:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡迪纳尔健康公司上调年度利润预期，押注专科药品需求激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡迪纳尔健康公司周四上调了全年利润预期，此前其季度业绩超出华尔街预期。该公司押注于专业药品的强劲需求及其各业务板块的优异表现。【原文：Cardinal Health on Thursday raised its expectations for annual profit after surpassing Wall Street estimates for quarterly results, as it bets on robust demand for specialty medicines and strong performance across its segments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cardinal-health-boosts-annual-profit-forecast-banking-surging-demand-specialty-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLE3PROG3NLLHEAQXSZOE52X5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:55:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金遭人工智能抛售冲击，高盛称]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛在周三收盘后向客户发布的报告中指出，随着科技股抛售潮导致热门交易价值缩水，股票交易类大型对冲基金遭遇近一年来最惨淡的一天。【原文：Big hedge funds that trade in stocks had their worst day in almost a year on Wednesday as crowded trades lost value in the tech-driven selloff, Goldman Sachs said in a note to clients released after the market closed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-hit-by-ai-sell-off-goldman-sachs-says-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RB6MR6XAHVLSTLPAO6D4PXD2VU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:50:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约证券交易所母公司洲际交易所集团因交易量增长而利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[洲际交易所周四公布第四季度利润增长，这家纽约证券交易所母公司受益于波动市场中交易量的提升。【原文：Intercontinental Exchange posted a rise in fourth-quarter profit on Thursday, as the New York Stock Exchange parent benefited from stronger trading volumes in a volatile market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nyse-parent-ices-profit-rises-stronger-trading-volumes-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5XXOTLNQRNAFNCAD4IEU6QGQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国软件股在因人工智能颠覆担忧遭遇重挫后趋于稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[软件与数据服务类股周四在经历重挫后企稳，投资者正密切关注快速发展的人工智能工具是否开始冲击传统软件及订阅业务的需求。【原文：Software and data services stocks stabilized on Thursday after a bruising selloff, as investors looked for clues on whether fast-advancing artificial intelligence tools are starting to dent demand for traditional software and subscription businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-software-stocks-stabilize-after-bruising-selloff-ai-disruption-fears-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4M55GWM65JBTBWZDW74EFRVOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普拉达旗下品牌范思哲任命艾莱亚设计师彼得·穆利尔为创意总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利时尚品牌范思哲（Versace）去年被竞争对手普拉达（Prada）收购，该公司宣布任命历峰集团旗下品牌Alaïa的离任设计师彼得·穆利尔（Pieter Mulier）为新任创意总监。【原文：Versace, the Italian fashion brand which last year was acquired by rival Prada , said it had appointed as its new creative director Pieter Mulier, the outgoing designer of Richemont-owned Alaia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/prada-owned-versace-appoints-alaias-pieter-mulier-creative-director-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7BE423BJNLCLO4TUXXPPJDOOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:06:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>