<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:28:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:28:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通商业与投资银行任命哈拉米什为首席运营官，负责领导人工智能战略，备忘录显示。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一份内部备忘录显示，摩根大通商业与投资银行已任命内部人士盖伊·哈拉米什担任首席运营官，负责统筹该部门的数据与人工智能战略。【原文：JPMorgan Chase's commercial and investment bank has appointed insider Guy Halamish as chief operating officer to oversee data and AI strategy across the division, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgans-commercial-investment-bank-names-halamish-coo-lead-ai-strategy-memo-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POCOMPVXXFNSZE7P77IFDHLUGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic在最新融资轮估值达3800亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Anthropic周四宣布，其最新融资轮已筹集300亿美元资金，本轮融资由D. E. Shaw Ventures、ICONIQ和MGX等投资者共同领投，使这家Claude聊天机器人的制造商估值达到3800亿美元。【原文：AI startup Anthropic said on Thursday it has raised $30 billion in its latest funding round, which was co-led by investors including D. E. Shaw Ventures, ICONIQ and MGX, valuing the Claude chatbot maker at $380 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/anthropic-valued-380-billion-latest-funding-round-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5IO3IKPUJKIJNMMLUC4FU5TNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：知情人士称，康卡斯特旗下天空电视台与英国独立电视台22亿美元并购谈判进展放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，康卡斯特旗下天空集团与独立电视台就收购其广播频道及流媒体平台的谈判近几周已放缓，因收购华纳兄弟探索公司的争夺战正扰乱整个行业格局。【原文：Comcast-owned Sky's talks with ITV about buying its broadcast channels and streaming platform have slowed in recent weeks, three people with knowledge of the matter said, as the battle to buy Warner Bros Discovery disrupts the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/comcast-owned-skys-22-billion-itv-deal-talks-have-slowed-sources-say-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEJY4UNDNJKCTNUVNO7NW3FXNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:43:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称欧盟拟简化泛欧交易审批流程]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士称，欧洲企业若想通过收购扩大规模以增强与非欧盟竞争对手的竞争力，若交易涉及泛欧洲层面，则更可能获得监管机构批准。【原文：European companies looking to build scale through acquisitions to better compete with non-EU rivals could increase their chances of winning regulatory approval if deals are on a pan-European level, people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-looking-ease-path-pan-european-deal-approvals-sources-say-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEIQTXMHTRMHTBDVZYVZDYETC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:41:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉吉公司将关闭威斯康星州牛肉加工厂，裁员221人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业企业嘉吉公司将永久关闭其位于威斯康星州密尔沃基市的牛肉加工厂，裁撤221个岗位。根据该公司向州政府提交的文件显示，这是美国肉类加工企业成本持续攀升背景下最新关闭的牛肉加工厂。【原文：U.S. agribusiness Cargill will permanently close its beef processing facility in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, and eliminate 221 jobs, according to a filing with the state, the latest U.S. beef plant to be shuttered amid rising costs for meatpackers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cargill-close-wisconsin-beef-plant-cut-221-jobs-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VFE4WGT2BO3VNISR6DAHZZV4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟因谷歌搜索广告拍卖行为对其展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构正就谷歌在欧洲销售搜索广告的行为展开调查，路透社获得的一封致广告商的信函显示。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are investigating Alphabet unit Google over the sale of search advertisements in Europe, a letter to advertisers seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/google-targeted-by-eu-over-its-search-advertising-auction-practices-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">673YQ2Y2W5MHHF7YMCUNHCU25M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:21:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，帕洛阿尔托公司因担心北京报复而未将中国与中国黑客行动挂钩]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，Palo Alto Networks公司上周曝光了一起全球网络间谍活动，但该公司选择不将中国与该活动挂钩，因担心这家网络安全公司或其客户可能面临北京方面的报复。【原文：Palo Alto Networks opted not to tie China to a global cyberespionage campaign the firm exposed last week over concerns that the cybersecurity company or its clients could face retaliation from Beijing, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/palo-alto-chose-not-tie-china-hacking-campaign-fear-retaliation-beijing-sources-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS36BDPILFMX7MACBG2KRLCIKA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，谷歌因搜索广告定价问题再遭欧盟反垄断调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四报道，欧盟正对谷歌展开调查，因其涉嫌非法操纵搜索引擎广告价格。【原文：Google is being investigated by the European Union over concerns it is illegally rigging the cost of advertising on its search engine, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-hit-by-fresh-eu-antitrust-probe-over-search-ads-pricing-bloomberg-news-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXKDTJB5FJNZTL2TI6G2KIVYRI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:51:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲企业前景好转，但盈利预期下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[最新LSEG I/B/E/S预测数据显示，欧洲企业健康状况前景已有所改善。随着迄今为止财报季表现优于预期，欧洲蓝筹股指数已攀升至新高。【原文：The outlook for European corporate health has improved, the latest LSEG I/B/E/S forecasts showed on Thursday, as European blue-chip indices hit highs on the back of a better-than-anticipated earnings season so far.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-corporate-outlook-improves-earnings-forecast-fall-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UF2LNV6VNNJN7CLVTMRA7Q6VEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街监管机构将恢复部分裁减岗位，主席表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国金融监管机构负责人周四向国会表示，在去年应白宫要求大幅裁员后，华尔街顶级监管机构正着手恢复部分员工编制。【原文：Wall Street's top regulator is working to restore some of its workforce following last year's deep cuts at the behest of the White House, the agency's chief told Congress on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/wall-street-regulator-restore-some-jobs-after-cuts-chair-says-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOTLZJGKIROJHL5MXXJBHKF4GA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄牙批准对儿童使用社交媒体实施限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[葡萄牙议会周四在初审中通过一项法案，要求13至16岁青少年使用社交媒体须获得父母明确同意。这是欧洲首个实施此类限制的具体立法举措。【原文：Portugal's parliament on Thursday approved a bill, on its first reading, requiring explicit parental consent for children aged 13 to 16 to access social media, in one of the first concrete legislative moves in Europe to impose such restrictions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/portugal-approves-restrictions-social-media-access-children-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OYY4BQM75KELJC5UOMAUVGDAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:35:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[押注盈利驱动的股市波动的期权交易大获丰收]]></title><description><![CDATA[期权分析服务ORATS的数据显示，一种押注企业财报公布后股价将出现超预期波动的期权策略在本财报季表现异常出色。【原文：An options strategy that bets on stocks logging larger-than-expected moves on corporate results has performed unusually well this earnings season, data from options analytics service ORATS showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/options-bets-earnings-fueled-stock-swings-reap-big-gains-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXSKT5LVNFN2PKGPU6WYCS4WXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰电信公司Odido遭黑客攻击，600万账户受影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰T-Mobile前业务部门Odido周四表示，超过六百万账户的个人信息在一次黑客攻击中遭泄露，这是该国迄今为止规模最大的数据泄露事件之一。【原文：Odido, the former business of T-Mobile in the Netherlands, said on Thursday that personal information from more than six million accounts had been exposed in a hack, one of the largest such incidents in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/dutch-telecom-odido-hacked-6-million-accounts-affected-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPOI6W3NEFPUXA5KK5EOXFB4FA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品药品监督管理局批准更年期激素疗法标签变更]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四表示，已批准对六种更年期激素疗法的标签进行修改，删除其中关于心血管疾病、乳腺癌和可能痴呆症风险的说明。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Thursday it has approved labeling changes to six menopause hormone therapies to remove references to risks of cardiovascular disease, breast cancer, and probable dementia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-labeling-changes-menopausal-hormone-therapy-products-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44VQSLIBHVKZHBOMJZQBBFGC6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅第四季度销售额跃升6%]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅周四表示，其第四季度销售额增长6%，这得益于欧洲和北美地区对该集团护发产品和香水的强劲需求，抵消了北亚地区几乎停滞的增长。【原文：L'Oreal's fourth-quarter sales grew 6%, it said on Thursday, as strong demand for the group's haircare and perfumes in Europe and North America compensated for barely any growth in North Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/loreal-reports-6-jump-fourth-quarter-sales-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR2ULKGB35PKFL6TWN33FON2TA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，芝商所将在亚洲铝市场扩张中将台湾、香港仓库纳入交易范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，芝商所集团即将批准台湾和香港成为铝仓库地点。随着这家美国商品交易所加大对伦敦金属交易所（LME）在亚洲的挑战力度，此举具有重要意义。【原文：CME Group is set to approve Taiwan and Hong Kong as warehouse locations for aluminium, three sources with direct knowledge of the matter told Reuters, as the U.S. commodity exchange steps up its challenge to the London Metal Exchange (LME) in Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/cme-list-taiwan-hong-kong-warehouses-asia-aluminium-push-sources-say-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36H3BDUGFFPQ5FHAAFKVCHIX6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:53:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[育碧确认目标后，《刺客信条：克里夫》预订量强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电子游戏发行商育碧周四确认了全年财务目标，此前受其旗舰游戏《刺客信条》系列推动，第三季度预订量超出公司预期。【原文：French video game publisher Ubisoft confirmed its full-year financial targets on Thursday after third-quarter bookings exceeded company forecasts, driven by its flagship "Assassin's Creed" franchise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/ubisoft-confirms-targets-after-strong-assassins-creek-bookings-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNGJDF5QJZI4XB3BZZ3RJXDDSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:48:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新任卡夫亨氏首席执行官面临艰难抉择：分拆还是加倍下注]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡夫亨氏新任首席执行官史蒂夫·卡希兰面临艰难抉择：要么继续耗时耗力的分拆进程，要么在消费者信心低迷时期重振公司陷入困境的品牌。他无法两者兼顾。【原文：Kraft Heinz's new CEO Steve Cahillane was faced with a difficult choice. Either continue the time-consuming process of separating into two companies or revive the company's struggling brands during a time of weak consumer sentiment. He couldn't do both.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/new-kraft-heinz-ceos-difficult-choice-split-or-double-down-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAXEOI4PWROCRBV4DBYCADVXAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:39:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储报告称美国人承担了特朗普几乎所有关税的代价]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周四发布的一份报告称，美国民众几乎承担了特朗普总统加征的全部进口关税。【原文：Americans are shouldering almost all of President Donald Trump’s import tax surge, a report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ny-fed-report-says-americans-pay-almost-all-trumps-tariffs-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIOOUEGWANONVHXBLLI6TOZ55U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对于股市而言，人工智能正从"一船之举皆得利"转向"一船之沉皆受损"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者正逐渐发现，人工智能领域不仅是股票的沃土，更是布满地雷的险境。【原文：Investors are discovering that the artificial intelligence landscape is not just fertile ground for stocks -- it is also a minefield.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stock-market-ai-turns-lifting-all-boats-sinking-ships-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYS3JC3H6NLUBGKLLVUJVB5CEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:10:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西最高法院院长托福利否认收受款项，与Banco Master银行的沃卡罗存在关联]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西最高法院法官迪亚斯·托福利周四表示，他从未收受任何款项，也从未与Banco Master银行控股股东丹尼尔·沃卡罗存在任何关系。【原文：Brazil's Supreme Court Justice Dias Toffoli said on Thursday he has never received any payments and has never had any relationship with Banco Master's controlling shareholder Daniel Vorcaro.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/brazil-supreme-courts-toffoli-denies-receiving-payments-links-banco-masters-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVPYBZXMNNIAFBHYFECNWRLLB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:45:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银旗下PayPay提交美国IPO申请，距离公开市场更近一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[PayPay周四正式提交了在美国首次公开募股的申请文件。这家由软银支持的日本支付应用在经历了美国政府停摆导致的延迟后，正推进其备受期待的上市计划。【原文：PayPay publicly filed its paperwork for a U.S. initial public offering on Thursday, as the SoftBank-backed Japanese payments app moves ahead with its highly anticipated stock market flotation after a U.S. government shutdown-driven delay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/softbanks-paypay-moves-closer-public-markets-with-us-ipo-filing-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYCVJQAONBIJJHKBJ2UO5V2EIE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:39:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院委员会推进法案以加快新卫星审批进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商业委员会周四批准了一项旨在加快新卫星审批的法案。【原文：The U.S. Senate Commerce Committee on Thursday approved legislation aimed at speeding approval of new satellites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-senate-committee-advances-bill-speed-approvals-new-satellites-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLV4BJOEFVMATBMTPLJEA2DJS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:27:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国1月成屋销售量跌至逾两年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国1月份成屋销售量跌至逾两年最低水平，因库存下降推高房价。【原文：U.S. existing home sales tumbled to the lowest level in more than two years in January as falling inventory raised house prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-existing-home-sales-drop-more-than-two-year-low-january-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KELCC3D3ARMVZCTQQ5QHJZALUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者放弃高端车型转投入门级汽车，因经济承受能力受到冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[对美国消费者而言，平价汽车的热度已久未如此之高——自海湾战争推高油价、日本车企以"加满油箱，无需操心"的简单承诺抢占市场份额以来，这种景象便未曾重现。【原文：For American buyers, affordable cars have not been this hot since the Gulf War sent gas prices climbing and Japanese automakers took market share by offering a simple proposition: "fill it, forget about it".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/americans-ditch-premium-trims-entry-level-cars-affordability-takes-hit-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AOKCQLMDFIPZJKST7Q5HPJ7TQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帕洛阿尔托在完成250亿美元收购赛门铁克交易后，计划在特拉维夫实现双重上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克上市的帕洛阿尔托网络公司周四宣布，其股票也将登陆特拉维夫证券交易所。此前该公司已完成以250亿美元收购以色列同行赛博安软件的交易。【原文：Shares of Nasdaq-listed Palo Alto Networks will also trade on the Tel Aviv Stock Exchange, the cybersecurity firm said on Thursday, after it closed its $25 billion purchase of Israeli peer CyberArk Software .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/palo-alto-plans-dual-listing-tel-aviv-after-closing-25-billion-cyberark-deal-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BZ7QDO6HZNW7O45DOTGWWFIO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡夫亨氏预计2026年资本支出约为9.5亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡夫亨氏周四表示，预计2026年年度资本支出将达到约9.5亿美元，高于去年水平。此前一天，这家包装食品制造商暂停了分拆计划，并宣布了旨在提振业务的新投资举措。【原文：Kraft Heinz said on Thursday it expects annual capital spending of about $950 million in 2026, higher than last year, a day after the packaged-foods maker hit pause on its plans to split and announced new investments to boost its business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kraft-heinz-forecasts-about-950-million-2026-capital-spending-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5QXJLEOTZNOBDEGC6434CMPJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Counterpoint数据显示，中国1月智能手机销量同比下降23%]]></title><description><![CDATA[Counterpoint Research周四表示，受2025年基数较高及春节促销时间调整影响，中国智能手机1月销量同比下滑23%。【原文：China's smartphone sales fell 23% in January compared with a year ago due to a high base in 2025 and a shift in the timing of Chinese New Year promotions, Counterpoint Research said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinas-january-smartphone-sales-down-23-yy-says-counterpoint-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENXBU7262FIPRKG6HLG3ZPUUX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:17:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英美烟草公司称美国禁售电子烟或使非法销售减少三分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[英美烟草公司首席执行官周四向路透社表示，美国可能采取行动禁止进口部分一次性电子烟，此举或将使蓬勃发展的非监管电子烟市场萎缩三分之一，不过相关影响预计不会在2027年前显现。【原文：A potential U.S. move to block imports of some disposable vapes could cut the booming market for unregulated e-cigarettes by as much as a third, British American Tobacco's CEO told Reuters on Thursday, though any impact is unlikely before 2027.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-import-block-vapes-could-cut-illegal-sales-by-third-bat-says-2026-02-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQ6FJJDR75NSNDR7WRV4GR3OPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街券商预测美联储将在2026年中期降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括高盛和摩根士丹利在内的主要券商预计，美国联邦储备委员会将在6月实施下一次降息，而摩根大通则认为下次行动将是2027年的加息。【原文：Major brokerages, including Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley, expect the U.S. Federal Reserve to deliver its next interest-rate cut in June, while J.P. Morgan sees the next move as a hike in 2027.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-brokerages-pencil-fed-rate-cuts-mid2026-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HASFO633WZNLJG375TETBDP6W4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>