<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:39:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:39:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普抨击美联储主席库克，投资者震撼，期指下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货下滑，受较长期国债收益率上升的打压，原因是唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇美联储理事的决定再次引发了市场对央行独立性的担忧。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Tuesday, pressured by a rise in longer-dated Treasury bond yields as President Donald Trump's decision to fire a Federal Reserve governor renewed concerns about the central bank's independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/futures-slip-trump-attack-feds-cook-shakes-investors-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">356R2XJMMRPSHIE2VKF54R2R24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩凸显中美贸易战影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与特朗普政府达成不寻常的协议以及中国政府随后努力阻止进口之后，英伟达这家人工智能芯片制造商周三公布财报时，其在中国的业务将成为投资者关注的焦点。【原文：Nvidia's business in China will be the focus of investors when the AI chipmaker reports earnings on Wednesday, following an unusual deal with the Trump administration and Beijing's subsequent efforts to stall imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-results-spotlight-fallout-china-us-trade-war-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YO3RHPHUXBMODNJ653DWQN4SFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期权显示，财报发布后英伟达股价将波动 2,600 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国期权市场数据显示，在芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）周三公布第二季度财报后，期权交易商对该公司市值约 2,600 亿美元的波动进行了定价。【原文：Options traders are pricing in about a $260 billion swing in Nvidia's market value following the chipmaker's second-quarter earnings expected on Wednesday, U.S. options market data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-set-260-billion-price-swing-after-earnings-options-indicate-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KP4WA5KTTZKL7D2FIDAYTIU2LE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国法院认定 Apple Watch 不是 "二氧化碳中性产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，德国一家法院作出支持环保人士的裁决，认定这家美国科技公司误导了消费者，苹果公司不能再在德国宣传其 Apple Watch 是 "二氧化碳中性产品"。【原文：Apple can no longer advertise its Apple Watch as a "CO2-neutral product" in Germany, following a court ruling on Tuesday that sided with environmentalists in finding that the U.S. tech company had misled consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/apple-watch-not-co2-neutral-product-german-court-finds-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLXMMAP3FRJ6HA5EMRTHPJYVFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰银行因信息披露失误被香港监管机构罚款 420 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港监管机构周二表示，汇丰银行因信息披露失误被罚款 420 万港元（537,682.59 美元）。【原文：HSBC has been fined HK$4.2 million ($537,682.59) by Hong Kong regulators over disclosure failures, the regulators said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-fined-42-million-by-hong-kong-regulators-over-disclosure-failure-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SZ72D3LRFO3XIPFNS7BXCGFRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼称美国同意对其棕榈油、可可和橡胶免征关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼首席关税谈判代表周二表示，美国已原则上同意印尼出口的可可、棕榈油和橡胶免受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普自8月7日起征收的19%的关税。【原文：The United States has agreed in principle to exempt Indonesian exports of cocoa, palm oil and rubber from President Donald Trump's tariff of 19% imposed since August 7, the Southeast Asian nation's chief tariff negotiator said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-says-us-agrees-tariff-exemption-its-palm-oil-cocoa-rubber-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCTTVBLAIVJ2DBOPLT3SJ2SMW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:18:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对美联储的最新嘲讽引发的不安多于戏剧性]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普再次打击美联储的独立性之后，全球投资者大受打击，既担心政策政治化，又担心市场的回报。【原文：Global investors were shell-shocked on Tuesday after U.S. President Donald Trump struck another blow at the Federal Reserve's independence, caught between the concerns over politicisation of policy and the payoffs for markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-latest-fed-jab-breeds-more-dismay-than-drama-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2QI4EWTRZN3RM4XPVHJLXBYMA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国-挪威团队入围加拿大新潜艇交易决赛]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周二宣布，加拿大已为其新潜艇项目确定了两家候选公司，其中一家是德国与挪威的合作公司。【原文：Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney announced Tuesday that Canada has shortlisted two contenders for its new submarine program, with a German-Norwegian partnership among the finalists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/german-norwegian-team-finalist-canadas-new-submarine-deal-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYEMJ4DS6FIOZGHFAPHL77EETI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 08:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与美联储之争引发日本收益率不断走高的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普试图罢免美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）之后，日本政府债券收益率在周二测试了历史新高，这引发了人们对在一个可能更加鸽派的央行领导下通胀压力的担忧。【原文：Japanese government bond yields tested record highs on Tuesday after U.S. President Donald Trump's attempt to oust Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook, raising concerns about inflationary pressures under a potentially more dovish central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trumps-fed-battle-raises-risks-ever-higher-yields-japan-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SL3RWHR3TBKLZAWHSVX6GRCWSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 08:14:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查发现，三分之一的瑞士工程公司计划向欧盟转移]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士机械和电气工程行业协会（Swissmem）周二表示，面对坚挺的瑞士法郎和关税导致的美国业务下滑，31% 的瑞士机械和电气工程公司计划将部分业务转移到欧盟。【原文：Faced with a strong Swiss franc and a drop in U.S. business due to tariffs, 31% of Swiss mechanical and electrical engineering companies plan to transfer some operations to the European Union, industry association Swissmem said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/one-third-swiss-engineering-firms-plan-shift-eu-survey-finds-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMSV3UVQGFJKJLSPVQWEUMPUY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 08:11:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Klarna 将在下月的首次公开募股中寻求最高 140 亿美元的估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，瑞典金融科技公司 Klarna 将重启下月在美国上市的计划，估值在 130 亿至 140 亿美元之间。【原文：Swedish fintech Klarna will restart its plan to go public in the United States next month with a valuation of between $13 billion and $14 billion, according to two sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/klarna-seek-valuation-up-14-billion-ipo-next-month-sources-say-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNL7ROUEANNDNBG7C5DB7KN42Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:42:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，通用汽车公司将因燃油泄漏问题召回超过 2.35 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周二表示，通用汽车公司（General Motors）因燃料泄漏问题在美国召回了超过2.35万辆雪佛兰科尔维特（Chevrolet Corvette）汽车。【原文：General Motors is recalling more than 23,500 Chevrolet Corvette vehicles in the U.S over a fuel leak issue, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/general-motors-recall-over-23500-us-vehicles-over-fuel-leak-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QA2QWNVCSRPM5MBE5BIA2YHWNI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:23:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国政治风险和美联储担忧导致欧股下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，欧洲股市下跌，其中法国股市因国内政治不确定性加深而领跌，而市场对美国联邦储备局独立性的担忧加剧，抑制了全球对高风险资产的偏好。【原文：European shares dropped on Tuesday, led by losses in France as political uncertainty deepened in the country, while mounting concerns over the U.S. Federal Reserve's independence curbed appetite for riskier assets globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-shares-fall-french-political-risks-fed-concerns-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3H4RK6ORGBM4DOEK22MKFJT4SA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国企业在峰会上承诺向美国投资1500亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与韩国总统李在镕周一举行的峰会上，韩国公司吹捧了美国的一系列投资计划，涉及造船、核能、航空航天、能源和关键矿产等领域。【原文：South Korea touted a broad range of U.S. investment plans by its companies at Monday's summit between U.S. President Donald Trump and South Korean President Lee Jae Myung, spanning shipbuilding, nuclear energy, aerospace, energy and critical minerals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/south-korean-firms-pledge-150-billion-us-investments-summit-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSJ5NLTRKROWFKHOSFKLHNRX6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[幸运啤酒制造商 BAT 称财务总监本奇克下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[幸运牌（Lucky Strike）和登喜路（Dunhill）香烟的制造商英美烟草公司周二表示，公司财务总监索拉娅-本奇克（Soraya Benchikh）在任职约 15 个月后将立即卸任。【原文：British American Tobacco , the maker of Lucky Strike and Dunhill cigarettes, said on Tuesday that its finance chief Soraya Benchikh is stepping down with immediate effect, after about 15 months in the role.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lucky-strike-maker-bat-says-finance-chief-benchikh-steps-down-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">65RQMFFPFBNNBEQF77XQHEL5NE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔改变基调，摩根士丹利预计美联储将于 9 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）发表讲话，表示将重点转向劳动力市场风险，摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）预计美联储将于9月开始降息，而此前的观点是美联储将按兵不动直至2026年3月。【原文：Morgan Stanley expects the U.S. Federal Reserve to begin cutting interest rates in September, from its earlier view of the Fed staying on hold until March 2026, after Chair Jerome Powell signaled a shift in focus toward labor market risks in remarks at Jackson Hole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/morgan-stanley-expects-us-fed-deliver-september-rate-cut-powell-shifts-tone-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPPE5FMYJRN57PS5KZW6V6CIZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Telenor 的 KNL 公司看到了军用无线电需求的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威电信公司（Telenor）的芬兰子公司KNL周二表示，未来几年北约国家对其加密便携式无线电设备的需求将不断增加，这些国家希望加强战场通信。【原文：Telenor's Finnish subsidiary KNL said on Tuesday it is seeing rising demand in the coming years for its encrypted portable radio units from NATO countries looking to boost battlefield communications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/telenors-knl-sees-growth-military-radio-demand-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVITY53LXBLYFLNDFJWAH7SQYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国希望达成非约束性协议，引导 3500 亿美元的美国投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位韩国高级官员周一表示，美国和韩国已决定制定一项不具约束力的协议，以确定作为 7 月贸易协议一部分而达成的 3,500 亿美元投资基金的运作和结构。【原文：A top South Korean official said on Monday that the U.S. and South Korea had decided to establish a non-binding agreement to define the operation and structure of $350 billion in investment funds agreed as part of a July trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-eyes-non-binding-deal-steer-350-bln-us-investments-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7U2G6I54QVIRXH2NNRH42HWMBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:07:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[约翰爸爸将再次进军印度，计划在 2035 年前开设 650 家披萨店]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国比萨连锁店帕帕约翰国际公司（Papa John's International）的一位主特许经营高管表示，该公司计划在 10 月份之前重返印度市场，目标是在未来十年内在印度这个快餐连锁店一直难以维持销售增长的市场开设 650 家分店。【原文：U.S. pizza chain Papa John's International plans to return to India by October, said a master franchisee executive, aiming to open 650 stores over the next decade in a market where fast-food chains have been struggling to sustain sales growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/papa-johns-re-enter-india-with-plan-650-pizza-stores-by-2035-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54D6WEY3V5IZZKJAXAOGMDQBJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:57:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，梅赛德斯-奔驰养老金信托基金以 3.24 亿美元出售日产汽车股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，一位消息人士透露，德国汽车制造商梅赛德斯-奔驰的养老金信托基金以 478.3 亿日元（约合 3.2465 亿美元）的价格出售了其在日本日产汽车公司的全部股份。【原文：The pension trust of German automaker Mercedes-Benz has sold its entire shareholding in Japan's Nissan Motor for 47.83 billion yen ($324.65 million), a source said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-benz-pension-trust-sells-nissan-holding-324-million-source-says-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBVXOXGDCZLDJM4AZ7MOUWNERU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价市场再问特朗普："他能做到吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FA4A5QAIUJOTVG3I4DUQ5QJE3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:37:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行发出更多降息信号，但步伐未定]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行董事会在本月降息时判断，未来一年可能需要进一步放宽政策，而步伐可能是渐进式的，也可能是更快的，这取决于经济数据的流动情况。【原文：Australia's central bank board judged further policy easing would likely be needed over the coming year when it cut rates this month, and the pace could be gradual or quicker depending on the flow of economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-rba-signals-more-rate-cuts-ahead-pace-undecided-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSR2C3QVCBMQPKI4RSOSQ6Q57M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国从周三起征收新的高额关税，印度准备应对出口冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国土安全部的一份通知证实，华盛顿将从周三起对所有原产于印度的商品征收 25% 的额外关税，从而加大了对这个亚洲国家的贸易压力。【原文：Indian exporters are bracing for disruptions after a U.S. Homeland Security notification confirmed Washington will impose an additional 25% tariff on all Indian-origin goods from Wednesday, ramping up trade pressure on the Asian nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-braces-export-hit-us-imposes-steep-new-tariffs-wednesday-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GADCSHNUVNT7BLDF5AQQAUZVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:16:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普解雇美联储库克的法律前提是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一史无前例地下令解除丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）理事的联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve Board of Governors）职务，称有关她所拥有的房产抵押的问题是其政府刑事调查的对象，这足以成为解除其职务的理由。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday took the unprecedented step of ordering Governor Lisa Cook removed from the Federal Reserve Board of Governors, saying questions about the mortgages on properties she owns that are the subject of a criminal probe by his administration are sufficient cause for dismissal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/whats-known-about-legal-premise-trumps-effort-fire-feds-cook-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A327UMPTONJWLIQIH6LMKYIJ2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:58:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国豪赌重振陷入困境的美国造船业，向特朗普示好]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统李在明（Lee Jae Myung）在其首次正式美国之行中倚重 "让美国造船业再次伟大 "的承诺，而这两个盟国却在贸易和安全协议的其他细节上争论不休。【原文：South Korean President Lee Jae Myung is leaning on promises to "Make America Shipbuilding Great Again" during his first official U.S. trip, as the two allies wrangle over other details of their trade and security agreements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-korea-bets-big-reviving-troubled-us-shipbuilding-woo-trump-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4TD34TMCBN73IRBPCHJVDAMZM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:56:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称 Tekscend Photomask 东京 IPO 目标估值 20 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，日本芯片制造用光罩制造商 Tekscend Photomask 首次公开募股的目标估值为 3000 亿日元（约合 20 亿美元）。【原文：Tekscend Photomask, a Japanese manufacturer of photomasks for chipmaking, is aiming for a valuation of 300 billion yen ($2 billion) in its initial public offering, two sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tekscend-photomask-targets-2-billion-valuation-tokyo-ipo-sources-say-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWL6OM2KR5OJNEYMSFCBN6GHOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，Elliott 关联公司成为 Citgo 拍卖的领跑者]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法院官员周一称，对冲基金埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）的一家附属公司对委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 的母公司提出了最佳竞标，而矿商 Gold Reserve 领导的集团此前曾被推荐为胜出者。【原文：A U.S. court officer said on Monday an affiliate of hedge fund Elliott Investment Management made the best bid for the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum, against a group led by miner Gold Reserve previously recommended as the winner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/elliott-affiliate-emerges-frontrunner-citgo-auction-filing-says-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q65TSWRCKBOELN7JS7IQXXOVO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本财务大臣表示，日本仍对外汇走势感到担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣加藤胜信（Katsunobu Kato）周二表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布解除美联储理事职务后，日元走强，日本仍对外汇走势感到担忧。【原文：Japan remains alarmed over foreign exchange movement, Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato said on Tuesday, after the yen strengthened following U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of the removal of a Federal Reserve governor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-remains-alarmed-over-forex-movement-finance-minister-says-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNDORR2IYZIQHGPIUM5FM26XEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢特尼克称本周将更新日本对美投资 5500 亿美元的情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）表示，美国将于本周宣布日本对美投资 5500 亿美元的消息，据报道，日本的一位高级贸易特使正计划访问华盛顿，以正式确定这项交易。【原文：The United States will make an announcement this week on Japan's $550 billion investment in the U.S., Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said, as a top Japanese trade envoy is reportedly planning to visit Washington to formalise the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lutnick-says-update-coming-this-week-japans-550-billion-us-investment-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSRQDGEHXVMDPLRHRJNJZR4VVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 01:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行认为未来将有更多降息举措，但步伐未定]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社悉尼8月26日电）澳大利亚央行董事会在本月降息时判断，未来一年可能需要进一步放宽政策，根据经济数据的流动情况，步伐可能会渐进或加快。【原文：SYDNEY, Aug 26 (Reuters) - Australia's central bank board judged further policy easing would likely be needed over the coming year when it cut rates this month, and the pace could be gradual or quicker depending on the flow of economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-sees-more-rate-cuts-ahead-pace-undecided-2025-08-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNG6JXEH45LDXI67Z4QUWUGPE4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 01:42:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>