<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:06:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:06:43 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[韩国表示将为其在美国运营的公司提供明确的签证指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国最高安全顾问Wi Sung-lac周五表示，韩国政府将与美国官员进行会谈，以便为在美国运营的韩国公司提供明确的签证指南，并减轻留在美国的工人的担忧。【原文：South Korea's top security adviser Wi Sung-lac said on Friday that the government would talk to U.S. officials in order to provide clear visa guidelines for Korean companies operating there and to ease concerns for workers remaining in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/south-korea-says-provide-clear-visa-guidelines-its-companies-operating-us-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YPNHZHGFRI57JEFJCNMBQK3AA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟铝生产商推动征收 30% 废铝出口税]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟铝行业正敦促欧盟委员会对废金属出口征收约 30% 的关税，以阻止废金属涌出欧盟，造成国内生产商短缺。【原文：The European Union's aluminium sector is urging the European Commission to impose duties of around 30% on exports of scrap metal to stop it flooding out of the bloc and leaving domestic producers short.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/land-use-biodiversity/eu-aluminium-producers-push-30-scrap-export-levy-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4P3WWI3EBILLEWRV5KNKGSLWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:39:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度认为中国员工撤离不会对富士康造成重大影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府一位高级官员本周表示，富士康在过去几个月命令部分中国员工回国后，印度预计富士康在该国的业务不会受到重大干扰。【原文：India does not expect significant disruption to Foxconn’s operations in the country after the iPhone assembler ordered some employees from China to return home over the past few months, a top Indian government official said this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/india-sees-no-major-impact-foxconn-pullback-chinese-employees-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUS2ZVGJQFLL3L5PESZQF5O6MY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示接受微软解决 Teams 平台竞争问题的承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五表示，它已接受微软为解决与 Teams 平台有关的竞争问题而做出的承诺。【原文：The European Commission said on Friday it had accepted commitments offered by Microsoft to address competition concerns related to its Teams platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-says-it-accepts-microsofts-commitments-address-competition-concerns-over-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6FU26RDLFJX3COGZQUADQWCA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚关键矿产公司前往华盛顿]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，包括 Trafigura 旗下 Nyrstar 公司在内的 20 多家澳大利亚重要矿产公司将于下周前往美国，探索合作领域。【原文：More than 20 Australian critical minerals companies including Trafigura unit Nyrstar will head to the U.S. next week to explore areas for collaboration, four sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-critical-minerals-companies-head-washington-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZRQHLCXXNMTBBE3JKCF2ROYSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，Rivian公司将因高速公路辅助软件问题召回超过2.4万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，由于软件缺陷，Rivian公司将召回2.4万多辆2025年款的R1S和R1T电动汽车，该缺陷可能导致其免提公路辅助系统错误识别引导车辆。【原文：Rivian is recalling over 24,000 of its 2025 model year R1S and R1T electric vehicles due to a software defect that may cause its Hands-Free Highway Assist system to misidentify lead vehicles, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-recall-over-24000-us-vehicles-over-highway-assist-software-issue-nhtsa-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IRKKD6KFBL4BHSHFOS4Y7IDHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:23:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡 Carro 公司着眼于并购和进军澳大利亚，准备在澳大利亚两地上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[东南亚最大的二手车在线交易市场 Carro 公司首席执行官表示，该公司正在考虑两地上市，并计划最早在下个季度将业务扩展到澳大利亚，同时进行两到三项收购，为两地上市做准备。【原文：Carro, Southeast Asia's largest used-car online marketplace, is weighing a dual listing and plans to bulk up for it by expanding into Australia and pursuing two to three acquisitions as early as the next quarter, its CEO said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/singapores-carro-eyes-ma-australia-foray-ahead-potential-dual-listing-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYHA7PPFAJKSRBEYUQTA3XUM3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉里-埃里森联合创办甲骨文公司 48 年后重回巅峰]]></title><description><![CDATA[财富》杂志在封面上质疑甲骨文联合创始人拉里-埃里森是否会成为世界首富，而《商业周刊》则宣称埃里森 "又酷了"，并指出 "硅谷的坏小子正在复仇"。【原文：Fortune magazine wondered on its cover whether Oracle co-founder Larry Ellison might become the world's richest person, while BusinessWeek declared Ellison is "cool again," noting that "Silicon Valley's bad boy is having his revenge."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/larry-ellison-is-back-top-48-years-after-he-co-founded-oracle-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBSFBAUSXNNVZPOSMAQ4G2PWMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国投资者看淡康波指数再平衡，继续看好人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计投资者将继续追捧中国康佰康的股票，关键科技指数的洗牌迫在眉睫，可能导致价值超过 10 亿美元的被动抛售，但这不太可能动摇他们对人工智能风向标的信心。【原文：Investors are expected to remain hungry for China's Cambricon shares , with a looming reshuffle in a key tech index that could lead to over $1 billion worth of passive selling unlikely to shake their confidence in the AI bellwether.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-investors-seen-looking-past-cambricon-index-rebalance-staying-bullish-ai-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C23XOEZDCRNCLKOBVEMCZPITMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电信运营商将为 iPhone Air 提供 eSIM 支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[据苹果中国公司称，中国三大电信运营商将为苹果 iPhone Air 提供 eSIM 支持。【原文：China's three major telecom operators will provide eSIM support for Apple's iPhone Air, according to Apple China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinese-telecom-operators-provide-esim-support-iphone-air-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AWQN73M7ZLUXIDL6XGG2SOF34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乔治-阿玛尼遗嘱指示继承人逐步出售时装品牌或寻求 IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的一份遗嘱副本显示，已故时装设计师乔治-阿玛尼（Giorgio Armani）的遗嘱指示继承人在 18 个月内出售意大利时装公司 15%的股份，并在他去世后三到五年内将另外 30%至 54.9%的股份转让给同一买家。【原文：The will of late fashion designer Giorgio Armani instructs heirs to sell a 15% stake in the Italian fashion house within 18 months and later transfer an additional 30% to 54.9% to the same buyer between three and five years after his death, according to a copy of the will reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/giorgio-armanis-will-instructs-gradually-sell-fashion-brand-or-seek-ipo-document-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L52BQU6NBVKUHDO4BV22EOTZZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:29:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾推动芯片外交，新老盟友齐聚大型展会]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，全球领先的半导体公司齐聚台北，参加 Semicon 展会，讨论人工智能热潮：台湾利用其在芯片行业的主导地位促进外交目的。【原文：As leading global semiconductor companies gathered in Taipei this week for the Semicon trade show to discuss the AI boom, one area got a much more prominent role than before: Taiwan's use of its dominance of the chip industry to promote diplomatic aims.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/taiwan-promotes-chip-diplomacy-allies-old-new-mingle-major-trade-show-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6H5UIXEN55JOTMAZVIWYYN673Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利火箭制造商阿维奥公司批准增资 4 亿欧元以提高产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利火箭制造商阿维奥公司（Avio）周四批准了一项4亿欧元（约合4.6896亿美元）的增资计划，以便在全球航天和国防工业商机无限之际，为扩大生产能力提供资金。【原文：Italian rocket maker Avio approved a 400-million-euro ($468.96 million) capital increase plan on Thursday to finance expanded manufacturing capacity at a time of robust opportunities in the global space and defence industries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/italian-rocket-maker-avio-approves-400-million-euro-capital-raise-boost-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RW3HS7TU2NIKRDGCTU5DSJ325M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 06:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会将驳回尼古拉前首席执行官的起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周四提出动议，要求驳回对尼古拉公司（Nikola）创始人兼前首席执行官特雷弗-米尔顿（Trevor Milton）的起诉。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission moved on Thursday to dismiss its case againt Trevor Milton, the founder and former CEO of Nikola, a company that sought to make electric and hydrogen-powered trucks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-dismiss-case-against-former-nikola-ceo-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HULWTRJKBIHTCANSVWCAHYIEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息在即，中国陷入政策困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）为下周的降息预期做准备之际，中国央行很可能会抵制近期的宽松政策，因为它正处于两难境地：如何支撑疲软的经济，同时又不进一步助长火热的股市。【原文：As the U.S. Federal Reserve gears up for an expected rate cut next week, China's central bank is likely to resist a near-term easing in policy as it grapples with a dilemma: how to shore up a weak economy without further fuelling a hot stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-caught-policy-dilemma-fed-rate-cut-looms-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHS7LKOPQNN7FFIOKOGHPKZ3NA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:36:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，Apple Watch 高血压功能获 FDA 批准，将于下周推出]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果公司周四获得美国食品和药物管理局（FDA）批准后，将于下周在其智能手表上推出高血压检测功能。【原文：Apple will roll out a hypertension detection feature on its smartwatch next week after receiving U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) clearance on Thursday, Bloomberg News reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apple-watch-hypertension-feature-wins-fda-nod-rollout-next-week-bloomberg-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHT6AR7Z4BLN7CBPFMCWVDFJIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:30:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价市场呼叫美联储：请给我们五张票]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/take-five/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XXYER57QVLGXJXBXG4RJMUKDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府债务压力如何席卷全球市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[从英国到日本，人们对各地政府财政状况的担忧不断升级，迄今为止，这种担忧主要被控制在债券市场内部，但大型投资者正在为压力蔓延到从大型科技到住房和货币等各种资产做好准备。【原文：Escalating fears about government finances everywhere from Britain to Japan have so far been contained mostly within bond markets, but big investors are preparing for stress to spread across assets from big tech to housing and currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-debt-graphic-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JZGWKL7ROBN4ZMTCS6J7S4QGRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Via Transportation 及其股东在美国首次公开募股中融资 4.93 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[交通技术公司 Via Transportation 周四与一些现有投资者一起在美国首次公开募股中募集了 4.929 亿美元，成为 9 月份新股发行活动反弹的最新一家公司。【原文：Transit tech firm Via Transportation , along with some existing investors, raised $492.9 million in its U.S. initial public offering on Thursday, becoming the latest company to join the rebound in activity for fresh flotations in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/via-transportation-shareholders-raise-493-million-us-ipo-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y5MAWSZDRPRRAL6X564HCSAAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南调查对信贷员数据的网络攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南网络安全机构和路透社看到的一份文件显示，越南一个包含债权人数据的大型数据库遭到黑客攻击，目前仍在评估漏洞造成的影响。【原文：A large database in Vietnam containing data on creditors has been attacked by hackers, and the impact of the breach is still being assessed, according to the country's cybersecurity agency as well as a document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/vietnam-investigates-cyberattack-creditors-data-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQPSUBD4NBIHVJF2PABUK2MUBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚抑制数据中心增长，使中国获得人工智能芯片变得更加复杂]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为数据中心的热点地区，马来西亚正在控制扩张步伐，业内人士和分析师预计，此举将阻碍中国获得对提高人工智能能力至关重要的强大芯片的努力。【原文：Malaysia, a hotspot for data centres, is reining in the pace of expansion in a move industry insiders and analysts expect will hinder China's efforts to gain access to powerful chips that are crucial to improving its artificial intelligence capabilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/malaysia-reins-data-centre-growth-complicating-chinas-ai-chip-access-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJJXKHU5ENIHRGIIXA37RAF764</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SK 海力士称完成内部认证后准备生产 HBM4]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国 SK 海力士周五表示，该公司已完成下一代高带宽内存 4（HBM4）芯片的内部认证程序，并建立了面向客户的生产系统。【原文：South Korea's SK Hynix said on Friday it has completed its internal certification process for next generation high-bandwidth memory 4(HBM4) chips and established a production system for customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/sk-hynix-says-readying-hbm4-production-after-completing-internal-certification-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPIGNZ2CG5NJJDGQF32TMHZTU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:13:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲市场乘美联储宽松周期东风再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市跟随华尔街走高，原因是美国再次降息的前景日益明朗，有望降低全球借贷成本，从而缓解债券市场的压力并拖累美元。【原文：Asian share markets followed Wall Street higher on Friday as the growing prospect of several more U.S. rate cuts promised to lower borrowing costs globally, a relief to stressed bond markets and a drag on the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1pix-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRF4CYEYFFPTDLXS4LSGTM4ALQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[申请失业救济人数支撑美联储降息观点，美元受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元继续承压，原因是美国申请失业救济人数激增和通胀率小幅上扬，使投资者对美联储下周及以后可能的降息保持高度关注。【原文：The dollar remained under pressure on Friday as a surge in U.S. jobless claims and a modest tick up in inflation kept investors zeroed in on likely Federal Reserve interest rate cuts next week and beyond.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-back-foot-jobless-claims-firm-up-fed-rate-cut-views-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YDNYTDBIRJUFO3YCJZCZZYZD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应过剩和美国需求担忧导致油价跌幅扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在上一交易日大跌后周五走低，原因是市场担心美国需求可能走软，以及广泛的供应过剩抵消了对中东冲突和乌克兰战争导致供应中断的担忧。【原文：Oil prices edged lower on Friday after big falls in the last session over concerns about possible softening of U.S. demand and broad oversupply that offset worry about supply disruption from conflict in the Middle East and war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-extend-losses-oversupply-us-demand-concerns-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZZLRU7BFBINLAUFEBVOPO52VQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美日重申外汇承诺，为干预留有余地]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周五发表的一份联合声明，美国和日本重申了对 "市场决定 "汇率的承诺，同时同意外汇干预应仅限于应对过度波动。【原文：The United States and Japan reaffirmed their commitment to "market determined" exchange rates, while agreeing that foreign exchange interventions should be reserved for combating excess volatility, according to a joint statement released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-japan-reaffirm-fx-commitments-leave-room-interventions-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UR23RZR3MZOSZFRI5MD3S3XLBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 01:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[连锁咖啡馆黑岩咖啡吧在美国首次公开募股中融资 2.94 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[黑石咖啡吧周四表示，该咖啡连锁店已在美国首次公开募股中募集到 2.941 亿美元，为关税动荡后备受关注的消费者上市奠定了基础。【原文：Black Rock Coffee Bar has raised $294.1 million in its U.S. initial public offering, the cafe chain said on Thursday, setting the stage for a closely-watched consumer listing in the aftermath of the tariff turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/cafe-chain-black-rock-coffee-bar-raises-294-million-us-ipo-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXHUTEOFXNKWHLLNEHXOOCR2DM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:56:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，OpenAI、Nvidia 将宣布对英国数据中心的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，OpenAI 和英伟达计划在下周与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普同时前往英国时，承诺支持数十亿美元的英国数据中心投资。【原文：OpenAI and Nvidia plan to pledge support for billions of dollars in UK data center investments when they head to the country next week at the same time as U.S. President Donald Trump, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/openai-nvidia-set-announce-uk-data-center-investments-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGGUXKAFCBKJXDNL2KXX5LREPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道贝森特与中国副总理将于下周在马德里就贸易和 TikTok 举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四表示，美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）计划下周在马德里与中国国务院副总理何立峰及其他高级官员继续就贸易、经济和国家安全问题进行讨论。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent plans to with Chinese Vice Premier He Lifeng and other senior officials next week in Madrid to continue their discussions on trade, economic and national security issues, the Treasury said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-chinese-vice-premier-meet-madrid-next-week-trade-tiktok-2025-09-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFLLWXFQIRIQLMESYJ5DZ3U34M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 支持的 Legence 在美国首次公开募股中融资 7.28 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[工程与维护服务供应商 Legence 周四在美国首次公开募股中募集到 7.28 亿美元，在投资者热情高涨的背景下，该公司成为众多寻求上市的公司中的一员。【原文：Engineering and maintenance services provider Legence raised $728 million in its U.S. initial public offering on Thursday, adding its name to the string of companies looking to go public amid heightened investor enthusiasm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/blackstone-backed-legence-raises-728-million-us-ipo-2025-09-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKJPLHXPNNN3TETEKO4PF6P46M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>