<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:33:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:33:43 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[市场在美国数据公布前等待时机，股市漂移，美元震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，股市难以找到方向，而美元则跌跌不休，因为本周早些时候市场翘尾因素带来的欣喜情绪逐渐消退，交易员们期待着当天晚些时候的美国数据能带来进一步的催化剂。【原文：Stocks struggled for direction on Thursday while the dollar stumbled as the euphoria from market tailwinds earlier in the week fizzled out, with traders looking to U.S. data later in the day for further catalysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4MIJ2BIXVI75FH5N2H2R6VC7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:27:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因贸易协议的不确定性而摇摆不定；韩元成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在动荡不安的一周里，投资者对中美关税休战的欣慰让位于对各种贸易协议形式不确定性的谨慎情绪，而韩元在大幅波动后趋于稳定。【原文：The dollar wobbled on Thursday in a turbulent week that saw investor relief at the U.S.-China tariff truce give way to a cautious mood amid uncertainty over the shape of various trade deals, while the South Korean won steadied after sharp moves.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-wavers-uncertainty-over-trade-deals-skorean-won-focus-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RA4FP4HFTZMOHK2FKGXBHEN5RA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国第一季度经济增长可能因投资和消费疲软而放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对经济学家进行的一项调查显示，受私人投资低迷、家庭消费疲软和旅游业下滑的影响，泰国第一季度的经济增长可能放缓。【原文：Economic growth in Thailand likely slowed in the first quarter, weighed down by subdued private investment, weaker household consumption and a drop in tourism, according to a Reuters poll of economists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thai-growth-likely-slowed-first-quarter-weak-investment-consumption-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIZHR2WZSRMALDKD6KRSSPMOBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾台北国际电脑展将展示人工智能进展，Nvidia 的黄晓明将成为中心人物]]></title><description><![CDATA[在下周举行的台湾年度电脑展上，人们将再次聚焦英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋和最新的人工智能技术，同时也会关注美国提高关税可能带来的破坏性影响。【原文：At Taiwan's annual Computex trade show next week, the spotlight is expected to fall, once again, on Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang and the latest in artificial intelligence, but also on the potential destablising impact of higher U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-computex-showcase-ai-advances-nvidias-huang-take-centre-stage-2025-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXW2EFKOFVLLJLR5CP65NJVCSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[库存增加引发供应过剩担忧，美国油价下跌逾 1 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国原油期货周四早盘下跌超过 1 美元，因为上周美国原油库存意外增加，引发了投资者对供应过剩的担忧。【原文：U.S. crude futures declined more than $1 in early trade on Thursday after an unexpected build in U.S. crude oil inventories last week raised investor concerns about oversupply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-oil-prices-drop-more-than-1-inventory-build-raises-oversupply-fear-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LF44CUYFBKW7PJMEIHADAPNHM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:22:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，UnitedHealth 因可能存在医疗保险欺诈而受到刑事调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，美国司法部（DOJ）正在对联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）可能存在的医疗保险欺诈行为进行刑事调查。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) is carrying out a criminal investigation into UnitedHealth Group for possible Medicare fraud, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-under-criminal-probe-possible-medicare-fraud-wsj-reports-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBFYFEO3MVJN3OBKJQXIHQ6TIQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国要求反垄断监管机构关注经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国周四要求其反垄断监管机构在兼并控制、数字市场和消费者保护方面采取更加及时、透明和反应迅速的干预措施，从而推动经济增长，并最大限度地减少企业面临的不确定性。【原文：Britain on Thursday told its antitrust regulator to get behind its push for economic growth and minimise uncertainty for businesses by making more timely, transparent and responsive interventions in merger control, digital markets and consumer protection.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/britain-tells-antitrust-regulator-focus-economic-growth-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQEQVJV6NJLANMILE6MDJ32LJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈雷戴维森在旨在罢免首席执行官的董事会斗争中取得胜利]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈雷戴维森公司在一份声明中说，该公司周三击退了投资者 H Partners 提出的罢免包括首席执行官在内的三名董事的提议。【原文：Harley-Davidson on Wednesday beat back investor H Partners' proposal to remove three directors, including the CEO, the company said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/harley-davidson-scores-victory-board-battle-aimed-removing-ceo-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3AUTIEZAJKHLH5ZSWZDARU36U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vizion称，关税暂停后中国至美国海运货物预订量激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[集装箱跟踪软件供应商Vizion周三表示，在中美两国暂停针锋相对的惩罚性关税之后，美国从中国到美国的集装箱运输预订量激增了近300%。【原文：U.S. bookings for container transport from China to the United States spiked almost 300% in the wake of the United States and China pausing punishing tit-for-tat tariffs, container-tracking software provider Vizion said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-ocean-cargo-bookings-surge-after-tariff-pause-vizion-says-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6QPNDKHP5KFPI3TEYGVLPRPOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovery 的 Citrone 称美国移动是他最看好的股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[Discovery Capital 的创始人罗布-西特龙（Rob Citrone）周三表示，他目前最喜欢的股票是墨西哥的 America Movil，因为该公司的业务涉及拉丁美洲的许多不同国家。【原文：Discovery Capital's founder Rob Citrone said on Wednesday his favorite stock at this moment is Mexico's America Movil due to its exposure to many different countries in Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/discoverys-citrone-says-america-movil-is-his-top-stock-name-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAKWGAD2W5NHBPDGBUW23XGLOQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Point72 的科恩认为关税混乱导致经济放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[Point72 资产管理公司创始人史蒂文-科恩（Steven Cohen）周三表示，他认为美国经济很可能会因为关税威胁而放缓，但即便如此，美联储也不会立即采取降息行动。【原文：Point72 Asset Management’s founder, Steven Cohen, said on Wednesday he believes the U.S. economy will very likely slow down because of tariff threats, but even so the Federal Reserve will not act immediately to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/point72s-cohen-sees-economic-slowdown-amid-tariff-confusion-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGPONP5HOBLTNOZONRDNPMPQHE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:12:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府废除拜登时代限制出售美国人个人数据的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周三发布的一份联邦登记公告，美国消费者金融保护局将取消前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）提出的一项提案，该提案将严格限制数据经纪商出售美国人的私人信息。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau is scrapping a proposal issued under former President Joe Biden that would have sharply limited the sale of Americans' private information by data brokers, according to a Federal Register notice issued Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-administration-scraps-biden-era-plan-limit-sale-americans-personal-data-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J75TOJJPUJIHLLCALRZF3RK5IM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道亚马逊裁减设备与服务部门职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周三在其设备与服务部门裁员约 100 人，该部门负责监督 Kindle、Echo 扬声器、Alexa 语音助手和 Zoox 自动驾驶汽车等多种产品的开发。【原文：Amazon on Wednesday cut about 100 jobs in its devices and services unit, the group overseeing development of such diverse products as the Kindle, Echo speakers, Alexa voice assistant and Zoox self-driving cars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/amazon-trims-jobs-devices-services-unit-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGJSUDZW3RL3XODNWLZTIELOSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，迪克体育用品公司完成收购竞争对手 Foot Locker 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三援引知情人士的话报道，迪克体育用品公司（Dick's Sporting Goods）即将达成一项交易，以约 23 亿美元的价格收购竞争对手鞋类零售商 Foot Locker。【原文：Dick's Sporting Goods was nearing a deal to buy rival footwear retailer Foot Locker for about $2.3 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dicks-sporting-goods-closes-deal-buy-rival-foot-locker-wsj-reports-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUSV3Z3KUVNXPE2ZL4QC7SARVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:30:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 Loblaw 公司称特朗普关税导致更多产品涨价]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大零售商洛布劳（Loblaw）周三警告说，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税给企业的供应链成本带来压力，价格上涨将影响到更多产品。【原文：Canadian retailer Loblaw warned on Wednesday that prices increases will affect more products as U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs put pressure on supply-chain costs for companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-loblaw-says-more-products-see-price-hikes-due-trump-tariffs-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GF3G6TMZMNPV3HLIEIQNJPU7VQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:07:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：标准普尔 500 指数完成 2025 次往返之旅]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNXJTJJP2NJYFBCOASMXNULVII</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国即将允许阿联酋进口数百万英伟达人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉情况的消息人士称，美国已与阿拉伯联合酋长国达成初步协议，允许阿联酋从2025年起每年进口50万片英伟达最先进的人工智能芯片，这将推动阿联酋建设对开发人工智能模型至关重要的数据中心。【原文：The U.S. has a preliminary agreement with the United Arab Emirates to allow it to import 500,000 of Nvidia's most advanced AI chips per year, starting in 2025, two sources familiar with the situation said, boosting the Emirates' construction of data centers vital to developing artificial intelligence models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-close-letting-uae-import-millions-nvidias-ai-chips-sources-say-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WF5I33225JWTBXZOXR3CHUZEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:48:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对巴西牛肉供应链的审计显示，在减少与亚马逊森林砍伐的联系方面取得了进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据联邦检察官和巴西肉类包装商达成的和解协议，巴西的大部分牛肉供应链已摆脱了与亚马逊雨林破坏的联系。【原文：A settlement involving federal prosecutors and Brazilian meat packers has helped wean much of the country's beef supply chain from links to Amazon rainforest destruction, according to company audits of their cattle purchases in six states that prosecutors unveiled on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/audits-brazil-beef-supply-chain-show-progress-reducing-links-amazon-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CO6VJZRBBLIPN26NGO23IOO3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:25:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新堡垒能源公司因各业务部门表现疲软而出现季度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国液化天然气公司新堡垒能源（New Fortress Energy）周三公布第一季度业绩亏损，受船舶、码头和基础设施两部分业绩疲软的影响，该公司股价在盘后交易中下跌近19%。【原文：U.S. LNG firm New Fortress Energy posted a loss in the first quarter on Wednesday, hurt by weak performance across both its segments of ships, and terminals and infrastructure, sending the shares down nearly 19% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-fortress-energy-posts-quarterly-loss-all-segments-show-weak-performance-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SVYK64L3DVKY5MZY5ZPGCGAMVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:24:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能驱动需求，思科上调全年业绩预期；股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[思科系统公司（Cisco Systems）周三上调了年度业绩预期，押注在人工智能热潮的推动下，云计算客户对其网络设备的需求将保持稳定。【原文：Cisco Systems raised its annual results forecast on Wednesday, betting on steady demand from cloud customers for its networking equipment, driven by the artificial intelligence boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cisco-raises-full-year-results-forecast-shares-rise-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73PT4CCLYJIRBLLUL3YHLLFEHE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:15:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达支持的 CoreWeave 第一季度营收超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[CoreWeave 周三发布了其作为上市公司的首份财报，季度营收超出华尔街预期，这表明市场对这家由英伟达（Nvidia）支持的人工智能云计算初创公司的服务需求强劲。【原文：CoreWeave on Wednesday beat Wall Street estimate for quarterly revenue in its first set of results as a public company, signaling strength in demand for the Nvidia-backed AI cloud computing startup's services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-backed-coreweave-beats-first-quarter-revenue-estimate-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JOCISWVN6ZKDVE52ZJESFVELUU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:13:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber 和 iFood 宣布在巴西建立战略合作伙伴关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步科技公司（Uber Technologies Inc）和巴西送餐应用 iFood 周三宣布在巴西建立战略合作伙伴关系。【原文：Uber Technologies Inc and iFood, a Brazilian food delivery app, on Wednesday announced a strategic partnership in Brazil, where delivery and ride-hailing services have grown rapidly in recent years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/uber-ifood-announce-strategic-partnership-brazil-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7IVWX6RHBRKXJDQI4NQEWZKOIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司预计 F-35 获奖时间早于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防承包商洛克希德-马丁公司的财务主管周三表示，该公司预计将比之前预计的更快获得F-35喷气式战斗机的最终合同。【原文：Lockheed Martin expects to be awarded a finalized contract on its F-35 jets, which have been beset by delays in a technology upgrade, sooner than it previously anticipated, the U.S. defense contractor's finance chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-martin-anticipates-sooner-than-expected-f-35-award-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLJTZYR5E5OBHPMAAQZVNA44QI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aeva 出售 6% 股份并达成生产协议，股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Aeva Technologies 是一家由苹果公司前工程师创办的公司，主要生产用于工厂和自动驾驶汽车的传感器。该公司周三表示，已将 6% 的股份以 5000 万美元的价格出售给了一家未具名的战略合作伙伴，该合作伙伴未来还将负责公司的部分生产业务。【原文：Aeva Technologies , a firm founded by former Apple engineers that makes sensors used in factories and self-driving vehicles, on Wednesday said it had sold a 6% stake for $50 million to an unnamed strategic partner that will also handle some of its manufacturing in the future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/aeva-sells-6-stake-inks-manufacturing-deal-shares-rise-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCPLINSYVNNCHAURRSFVVEBFEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 称广告支持服务拥有 9,400 万用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 宣布，目前其广告支持层的订户已从 11 月的 7000 万增至 9400 万。【原文：Netflix announced it now has 94 million subscribers to its advertising-supported tier, up from 70 million in November.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-says-ad-supported-service-has-94-million-subscribers-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NR73OMM6BZM63EREYSQ7X7Y4OQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:44:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伍德麦肯兹认为未来 15 年满足天然气发电需求面临挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源研究公司伍德麦肯兹（Wood Mackenzie）周三在一份报告中说，由于制造限制、成本上升和可再生能源的竞争，燃气轮机市场在未来 15 年可能难以满足强劲的需求。【原文：The gas turbine market might have trouble satisfying strong demand in the next 15 years due to manufacturing constraints, rising costs and competition from renewables, energy research firm Wood Mackenzie said in a report on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/wood-mackenzie-sees-challenges-meeting-gas-power-demand-over-next-15-years-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWPMZCGCR5IGTELJXFONVKOLFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:30:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，微软Office-Teams报价很可能避免欧盟反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉此事的人士周三表示，由于欧盟监管机构可能会接受微软对其 Office 和 Teams 产品提出的收购要约，微软将避免被处以巨额反垄断罚款。【原文：Microsoft is set to stave off a possible hefty antitrust fine as EU regulators are likely to accept an offer on its Office and Teams products, three people familiar with the matter said on Wednesday, amid tensions with the United States over the EU's scrutiny of Big Tech.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-antitrust-regulators-accept-microsofts-office-teams-offer-sources-say-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJM6KKVAXZOONIEVYG22OTFWUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:47:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商敦促欧盟委员会打击威士卡和万事达卡]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的零售商和在线零售巨头敦促欧盟委员会控制威士卡和万事达卡涉嫌收取的高额费用，称其损害了集团的竞争力并妨碍了竞争对手。【原文：Europe's largest retailers and online retail giants have urged the European Commission to rein in allegedly high fees charged by Visa and Mastercard , saying they hurt the bloc's competitiveness and hamper rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/retailers-urge-european-commission-crack-down-visa-mastercard-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5OA5P3FD5OALDOATUVD7JRHBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:32:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准艾伯维治疗一种肺癌的药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局已批准艾伯维公司的药物用于治疗一种曾接受过治疗的成人肺癌患者。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has approved AbbVie's drug to treat adults with a type of lung cancer who have received previous treatment, the drugmaker said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-abbvies-drug-type-lung-cancer-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UH2OVPIGIVIJHCDQPWTKW7COXY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:23:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛如何应对特朗普的关税，为零售业健康发展提供线索]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为美国零售业的风向标，沃尔玛的业绩将在本周四证明，为什么阿肯色州的这个庞然大物最有能力应对特朗普政府关税带来的不确定性。【原文：Results from Walmart , a bellwether for the U.S. retail industry, will offer proof on Thursday why the Arkansas behemoth is best placed to navigate the uncertainty from the Trump administration's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/how-walmart-handles-trumps-tariffs-could-offer-clues-retail-health-2025-05-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKIW6JPNGNIBRKHUN5GGM3PABA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>