<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:07:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:06:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普关税影响，沃尔沃汽车新任首席执行官求助于中国所有者吉利汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税压力下，沃尔沃汽车公司新任首席执行官哈坎-塞缪尔森（Hakan Samuelsson）既要与中国大股东吉利汽车公司[RIC:RIC:GEELY.UL]合作削减成本，又要设法继续向美国消费者销售汽车。【原文：Under pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, Volvo Cars' new CEO Hakan Samuelsson is juggling the task of working with Chinese majority owner Geely [RIC:RIC:GEELY.UL] to cut costs with attempting to keep selling cars to U.S consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/troubled-by-trumps-tariffs-volvo-cars-new-ceo-turns-chinese-owner-geely-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QX52OXULXRPIXPYXZ6LSGNFFDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税不确定性影响，Stellantis 暂停全年业绩预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 公司周三表示，在 2024 年利润下降之后，由于美国关税政策演变的不确定影响，该公司将暂停今年温和复苏的指导。【原文：Stellantis said on Wednesday it was suspending its guidance for a moderate recovery this year, after a profit drop in 2024, due to the uncertain impact of evolving U.S. tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-suspends-full-year-forecasts-due-us-tariff-uncertainties-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQVJBAJXBNMUDNV37OTU27KH4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国物流集团 DHL 第一季度盈利增长，但对贸易持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国物流公司 DHL 周三公布了第一季度的销售额和盈利增长情况。【原文：German logistics company DHL on Wednesday posted higher sales and earnings in the first quarter, a period dominated by tensions over U.S. import tariffs that could both help and hinder the group's bottom line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/german-logistics-group-dhl-posts-higher-earnings-q1-cautious-trade-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTJBO3UYARPAFOIEQBSDBS373Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[永不下跪中国利用朝鲜战争和人工智能备忘录回击特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国正在利用其宣传机器对美国的关税进行反击，利用冷战时期的形象推出视频，抨击 "帝国主义者"，并传达一个简单的信息--向恶霸屈服是危险的，我们不会退缩。【原文：China is leveraging its propaganda machine to hit back at U.S. tariffs, rolling out videos using Cold War imagery to lambaste "imperialists" and send a simple message - capitulation to bullies is dangerous, and we won't back down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/never-kneel-china-taps-korean-war-ai-memes-hit-back-trump-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRTCQQIYNVM6XE7EYMBHL5DUZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世创电子材料下调全年核心利润率目标，但确认销售前景，尽管美国仍将加征关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国半导体材料供应商世创电子材料（Siltronic）周三下调了其年度核心利润率预期，理由是预计长期协议之外的价格会带来负面影响，但确认了全年销售指导，称目前还无法估计美国关税的影响。【原文：German semiconductor materials supplier Siltronic on Wednesday cut its annual core profit margin forecast, citing expected negative price effects outside of long-term agreements, but confirmed full-year sales guidance, saying it's not yet possible to estimate the impact of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siltronic-cuts-full-year-core-profit-margin-target-confirms-sales-outlook-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEMIFSQCSVM7XGM6Q65DP3RI7Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车称贸易紧张局势和电动汽车成本将拖累利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司周三表示，预计全年营业利润将低于预期，这是汽车行业在面临关税不确定性的情况下，又一家下调业绩展望的汽车制造商。【原文：Volkswagen said on Wednesday it expects annual operative profit at the bottom end of its forecast, the latest carmaker to dampen its outlook as an industry already pressured by costs and competition grapples with tariff uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-says-trade-tensions-ev-costs-weigh-profits-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6W4VLKDN5NNBHNFSNJ7EZAFGSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于关税影响，奔驰第一季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰（Mercedes-Benz）周三报告称，第一季度汽车业务利润率下降，并警告称关税可能会影响其全年收益，贸易紧张局势迫使这家豪华汽车制造商取消了对前景的展望。【原文：Mercedes-Benz on Wednesday reported lower profitability in its cars business in the first quarter and warned that tariffs could impact its full-year earnings, as trade tensions forced the luxury carmaker to scrap its outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-reports-less-profitable-cars-segment-q1-tariffs-bite-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3FMVMYUKVIM7EPLOJGWRPHEJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:12:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲国防初创企业如何吸引人工智能人才]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些曾经可能前往美国的欧洲科技工作者正在考虑就近创办防务初创企业。还有一些人则从海外工作岗位赶回欧洲。【原文：Some European tech workers who might once have headed to the United States are looking at defence startups closer to home. Others are rushing back to Europe from jobs abroad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mission-before-money-how-europes-defence-startups-are-luring-ai-talent-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXB6VVMEZRLHNPHV4LU6VKV3W4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街混乱冲击欧洲，投资者寻求新的关税保护市场利基]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国政策冲击引发欧洲经济增长风险的一个月里，投资者纷纷撤离华尔街，将目光转向拉美货币和金矿股等利基市场，以求摆脱贸易焦虑。【原文：Investors who rushed out of Wall Street during a month of U.S. policy shocks that raised European growth risks are turning their attention to niche markets such as Latin American currencies and gold mining stocks in a new bid to out-run trade angst.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-investors-analysis-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBBRO2U6PZICRADMYVWFOPKGX4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发市场波动，瑞银第一季度利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士银行瑞银集团（UBS）周三公布的第一季度净利润好于预期，主要得益于美国关税动荡后市场动荡导致的交易收益增加，该行称这可能会推迟企业交易。【原文：Swiss bank UBS on Wednesday posted better than expected first-quarter net profit, helped by stronger earnings in trading driven by market turbulence in the wake of U.S. tariff turmoil, which it said could delay corporate deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-1q-profit-tops-expectations-tariff-driven-volatility-markets-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMSKX6XCP5N3PHRBIKPE5KYSEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:55:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙 Caixabank 第一季度净利润增长 46%，银行业税收影响降低]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙储蓄银行（Caixabank）周三表示，与 2024 年同期相比，该银行第一季度净利润增长了 46%，原因是银行税重新征收带来的影响降低，抵消了利率下降导致的贷款收入减少。【原文：Spain's Caixabank on Wednesday said its net profit rose 46% in the first quarter compared to the same period in 2024 as a lower impact from the renewed banking tax offset a drop in lending income caused by lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/caixabanks-first-quarter-net-profit-rises-46-same-period-2024-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBAAQAODQJPANEXZW3EXIPXGPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 数据潮为动荡的四月画上句号]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYTP6PWL4ZOBLHISJZQ64SCSBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国加大转基因玉米种植力度，但国家控制和零星试验让业界充满猜测]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和高管表示，中国今年的转基因玉米种植量将是去年的四到五倍，这为因国家严格控制、公众怀疑和试验结果不一而放缓的转基因玉米推广工作注入了动力。【原文：China will plant four to five times more genetically modified (GM) corn this year than last, analysts and executives say, building momentum in a rollout that has been slowed by tight state controls, public scepticism, and mixed trial outcomes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-ramps-up-gm-corn-planting-state-controls-patchy-trials-keep-industry-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BI3VQPZJ6FMPBIHIVCJTPB5GDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，中国 CATL 最快将于下周在香港上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解此事的消息人士称，中国电池巨头 CATL 计划最早于下周在香港上市，这将是四年来香港最大规模的股票销售。【原文：Chinese battery giant CATL plans to launch its Hong Kong listing as early as next week, two sources with direct knowledge of the matter said, in what is set to be the city's largest share sale in four years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-catl-launch-hong-kong-listing-early-next-week-sources-say-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZUNW4WPENOK5EHYV2HDW2OFPU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称中国制定美国制造商品免征 125% 关税清单]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士说，中国已经制定了一份美国制造的产品清单，这些产品将被豁免125%的关税，并且正在悄悄地通知各公司有关这一政策，因为中国政府正在寻求缓解其与华盛顿贸易战的影响。【原文：China has created a list of U.S.-made products that would be exempted from its 125% tariffs and is quietly notifying companies about the policy, two people familiar with the matter said, as Beijing seeks to ease the impact of its trade war with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-creates-list-us-made-goods-exempt-125-tariffs-sources-say-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2WAS72PIVLG5L33THOSGUYVE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税前的囤积可能损害美国第一季度经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经济在第一季度很可能出现停滞甚至萎缩，急于避免成本上升的企业大量进口商品，凸显了唐纳德-特朗普总统经常混乱的关税政策的破坏性。【原文：The U.S. economy likely stalled or even contracted in the first quarter, swamped by a deluge of imported goods by businesses eager to avoid higher costs, underscoring the disruptive nature of President Donald Trump's often chaotic tariff policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stockpiling-ahead-tariffs-likely-hurt-us-economy-first-quarter-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26RPDQN7NVLTVJKXRRG4YOHTF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚财政部长在大选中强调核心通胀率下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚财政部长吉姆-查莫斯（Jim Chalmers）表示，在年度核心通胀率放缓至三年低点后，市场有理由期待更多的降息举措，并在竞争激烈的全国大选前三天强调了降息的重要性。【原文：Australia Treasurer Jim Chalmers said the market was justified to expect more interest rate cuts after annual core inflation slowed to a three-year low, highlighting the decline three days ahead of a closely-contested national election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australia-treasurer-election-mode-highlights-drop-core-inflation-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFVHUOSTXZJQ7K6J2QZJSCJB5M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:48:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国官员前往华盛顿就美国关税问题举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[首尔工业部表示，韩国工业部官员将于周三前往华盛顿与美国贸易代表同行进行 "技术讨论"，希望就美国关税问题达成潜在协议取得进展。【原文：South Korean Industry Ministry officials will travel to Washington on Wednesday for "technical discussions" with U.S. Trade Representative counterparts hoping to make progress on a potential deal over U.S. tariffs, Seoul's ministry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/south-korea-officials-heading-washington-talks-with-ustr-over-tariffs-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP7WXVKFYZI5JEP6CWHCUMUICI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金流动 摩根士丹利称，关税冲击后亚洲对冲基金增加日本和印度的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）表示，亚洲对冲基金在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）于本月初发布全面关税政策后迅速削减了对日本和印度股市的持仓，上周又蹑手蹑脚地重返市场。【原文：Asian hedge funds tiptoed back into the market last week, adding to their positions in Japan and India shares, after quickly cutting exposure when U.S. President Donald Trump unleashed sweeping tariffs at the start of the month, Morgan Stanley said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/hedge-flow-asia-hedge-funds-add-japan-india-after-tariff-shock-says-morgan-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGKZAMUYY5PHJAKYSPTWSCZAMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 02:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税加剧全球增长担忧，股市震荡，油价疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，全球贸易紧张局势可能缓和，但经济前景恶化，受唐纳德-特朗普关税影响的企业发出低迷信号，抵消了人们对全球贸易紧张局势可能缓和的宽慰，股市难以找到方向，油价下滑。【原文：Shares struggled for direction on Wednesday and oil prices slid as relief over a potential easing of global trade tensions was offset by a worsening economic outlook and dour signals from corporates swept up by Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XX447UGC4VIYTOW7QI3J2FECVY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 02:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税打击出口订单，中国工厂活动放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项私营部门调查显示，第二季度伊始，中国工厂活动放缓，新出口订单大幅减少，就业人数恢复下降。【原文：China's factory activity slowed at the start of the second quarter, with a sharp fall in new export orders and the resumption of employment declines, a private-sector survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-factory-activity-slows-us-tariffs-hit-export-orders-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJYD3NHGAJNX7CQM24CMJVTF34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 02:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚第一季度通胀率高于预期，但核心通胀率降至三年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚第一季度消费者物价涨幅略高于预期，但年度核心通胀率仍放缓至三年低点，这为下月再次降息提供了更多理由。【原文：Australian consumer prices rose slightly more than expected in the first quarter, but annual core inflation still slowed to a three-year low and added to the case for another cut in interest rates next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-q1-inflation-comes-above-forecasts-core-slows-3-year-low-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIYDMIER4VJKLNSEOJET3NBIQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 02:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称，DOGE 的工作导致向司法部移交欺诈案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，根据特朗普的盟友、亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）牵头成立的削减成本机构--政府效率部（Department of Government Efficiency）的调查结果，有人向司法部提交了欺诈案件。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday there were referrals for fraud made to the Justice Department based on the findings of the Department of Government Efficiency, the cost-cutting agency that Trump ally and billionaire Elon Musk spearheaded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-doge-work-led-fraud-referrals-justice-department-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6RDGNOUWJPZXKIGSWF7RICO3Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 02:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 4 月份工厂活动降速超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，一项官方工厂调查显示，中国 4 月份制造业活动萎缩，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的 "解放日 "一揽子关税措施断送了两个月的复苏之际，进一步刺激经济的呼声依然不绝于耳。【原文：China's manufacturing activity contracted in April, an official factory survey showed on Wednesday, keeping alive calls for further stimulus as Donald Trump's "Liberation Day" package of tariffs snapped two months of recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-factory-activity-falls-faster-than-expected-april-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Z2NKV5Z7BLCFFWOGHIZOAU26I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国制造业采购经理人指数显示 4 月制造业活动下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项官方调查显示，中国制造业活动在四月份出现萎缩，扭转了两个月来的复苏态势，并且由于唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收145%的关税，要求生产商停止前置出货，进一步刺激经济的呼声持续高涨。【原文：China's manufacturing activity contracted in April, an official survey showed on Wednesday, reversing two months of recovery and keeping alive calls for further stimulus as Donald Trump's 145% tariffs called time on producers front-loading shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-manufacturing-activity-falls-april-pmi-shows-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24DZ77QCPNJITPPNZ7EBXDMAHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税忧虑占据上风，美元持稳但脆弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周三持稳，但有望创下自2022年11月以来的最弱月度表现，原因是唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统领导下的美国贸易政策反复无常，导致美元走软，同时提振了欧元、日元和瑞士法郎。【原文：The U.S. dollar was steady on Wednesday but poised for its weakest monthly performance since November 2022 as erratic U.S. trade policies under President Donald Trump left the greenback vulnerable while boosting the euro, yen and Swiss franc.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-steady-vulnerable-tariff-worries-take-hold-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3HGNMNES5J3LOLGOB7ORNZ3NY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:45:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本工厂产出下滑，特朗普关税令制造商大受打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策对全球制造商和众多行业造成了冲击，日本 3 月份的工厂产出降幅超出预期，受其关键的汽车行业拖累。【原文：Japan's factory output fell more than expected in March, dragged down by its key motor vehicles industry, as U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff policies rattle manufacturers and a whole host of industries globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-factory-output-slides-trump-tariffs-jolt-manufacturers-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQERIXGR65IFXOZA3DAHS7WYTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[风暴和需求疲软打击赌场，星际娱乐公司第三季度出现亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[星空娱乐公司（Star Entertainment）周三表示，由于季节性疲软、赌场游客减少以及昆士兰州因三月暴风雨而关闭的地产，这家陷入困境的澳大利亚博彩运营商在第三季度出现了经营亏损。【原文：Star Entertainment said on Wednesday it swung to an operating loss in the third quarter, as seasonal weakness, dwindling casino visitors and Queensland property closures from March storms battered the troubled Australian gambling operator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/star-entertainment-swings-third-quarter-loss-storms-weak-demand-hit-casinos-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTTOHE3ARFOFVGOU24YENFOMRY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战担忧抑制需求前景，油价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普反复无常的关税政策引发了人们对全球经济增长和燃料需求疲软的担忧，油价在周三的亚洲早盘交易中走低。【原文：Oil prices edged lower in early Asian trading on Wednesday as President Donald Trump's erratic tariff policies raised concerns about weakening global economic growth and fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-fall-trade-war-concerns-dampen-demand-outlook-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIZ7LFZ5ZZOMHMXA3K45GHM5MM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:37:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩元疲软，韩国 LG 能源解决方案公司第一季度利润增长 138]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国电池公司 LG Energy Solution（LGES）周三公布第一季度利润增长 138%，主要得益于有利的汇率缓解了主要海外市场电动汽车（EV）销售增长放缓的影响。【原文：South Korean battery firm LG Energy Solution (LGES) on Wednesday posted a 138% rise in first-quarter profit, helped by favourable foreign exchange rates that cushioned slowing growth of electric vehicle (EV) sales in major overseas markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-koreas-lg-energy-solution-q1-profit-rises-138-weak-won-2025-04-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWEGC5ZWRZJG3DGS527AT325YY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>