<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:05:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:05:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，中国比亚迪在欧洲的销量首次超过特斯拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 JATO Dynamics 的一份报告，中国汽车制造商比亚迪在欧洲售出的电动汽车数量首次超过了特斯拉。【原文：Chinese automaker BYD sold more electric vehicles in Europe than Tesla for the first time, according to a report by JATO Dynamics, as an aging model lineup and CEO Elon Musk's politics hurt demand for the U.S. EV maker's cars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-byd-outsells-tesla-europe-first-time-report-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2HBKONAHBNUDMC5TEO7X4E5KQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：重锤落下]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TPDVGOAEBJCFFR3Z2TFXY7NM4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：诺和诺德前首席执行官卷土重来，指导新任首席执行官的人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[在诺和诺德的肥胖症药物Wegovy成为美国大片的几年前，当时的首席执行官拉斯-雷比恩-索伦森在哥本哈根的一次新闻发布会上说："你们什么都还没看到呢"【原文：Years before Novo Nordisk's obesity drug Wegovy became a U.S. blockbuster, then-CEO Lars Rebien Sorensen told a press conference in Copenhagen: "You ain't seen nothing yet."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novo-nordisks-former-chief-makes-comeback-steer-choice-new-ceo-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBGG6N7UTNJNXBKOZ6ETMA6A6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大道明银行因不良贷款拨备增加而利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[道明银行（TD Bank）周四公布第二季度利润下降，原因是这家加拿大贷款机构在不确定的经济环境中囤积资金，以应对潜在的不良贷款。【原文：TD Bank reported a fall in second-quarter profit on Thursday, as the Canadian lender stockpiled money to cover for potential bad loans in an uncertain economic environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadas-td-bank-profit-falls-hit-higher-bad-loan-provisions-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KKAEOWZKENJN3GPRWWQ77KKLOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国新药价格四年翻番，罕见病日益受到关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项分析发现，与2021年相比，去年美国新上市药品的价格增长了一倍多，因为公司利用科学进步开发了更多治疗罕见病的药物，而罕见病的价格通常很高。【原文：U.S. prices for newly-launched pharmaceuticals more than doubled last year compared to 2021, as companies leveraged scientific advances to develop more therapies for rare diseases, which typically command high prices, a Reuters analysis found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/prices-new-us-drugs-doubled-4-years-focus-rare-disease-grows-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SR43S2GULBMU3J5YO4IXNLHHG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:09:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谢因称欧盟收费和法国处罚将提高法国物价]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shein公司周四表示，如果欧盟关于收取手续费的提案得以推进，以及法国对快速时尚产品实施处罚的法案获得批准，法国消费者将为在低成本在线平台Shein上的购物支付更多费用。【原文：French consumers will pay more for their purchases from low-cost online platform Shein if a European Union proposal for a handling fee moves ahead and a French bill placing penalties on fast-fashion products is approved, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shein-says-eu-fees-french-penalties-would-increase-prices-france-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQJGIQSB2NIBHKWSTLXSOYWLBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达州新史诗宇宙主题公园的看点]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥兰多四分之一个多世纪以来的第一个新主题公园--史诗宇宙（Epic Universe）将于本周四开放。【原文：Orlando’s first new theme park in more than a quarter-century, Epic Universe, is set to open on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/what-expect-floridas-new-epic-universe-theme-park-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBFIONDFUVPQBAXRUMAMKUOX3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:07:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果 CP2 项目获得批准，Venture Global 将成为美国最大的液化天然气公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 LSEG 的数据和公司声明，如果 Venture Global 继续推进其在路易斯安那州的 CP2 项目，并继续在现有工厂超产，那么到明年它将成为美国最大的液化天然气公司。【原文：Venture Global is poised to become the largest U.S. liquefied natural gas company by next year if it proceeds with its CP2 project in Louisiana and continues overproduction at its existing plants, according to LSEG data and company statements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venture-global-track-become-top-us-lng-company-if-cp2-project-approved-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXBP63JOFRJMDFRC7OCM3NJTIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加强美联储预测的计划在地区主席中遭遇障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）建议在部分会议后发布详细的经济预测，以加强对货币政策的讨论，但这一建议遭到了地区银行负责人的抨击，他们担心很难就共同的前景达成一致，并有可能进一步混淆视听。【原文：A proposal for the U.S. Federal Reserve to release detailed economic forecasts after some of its meetings to anchor the discussion of monetary policy is drawing fire from the heads of its regional banks who worry it will be hard to agree on a common outlook and risks further confusing the public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/plan-beef-up-fed-forecasts-hits-hurdle-among-its-regional-presidents-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMSRRE65VNLXFCTN7P5NDEUQJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[猪不会飞美国高端牲畜饲养者在中国关税风波中损失数百万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦克-莱蒙博士的这些猪每头价值在2500美元到5000美元之间，本来应该在四月份从圣路易斯搭乘飞机飞往中国杭州，它们在飞机上打呼噜、打闹、吃燕麦和剥了壳的玉米，然后在中国的养猪场安家落户。【原文：Dr. Mike Lemmon's pigs, each valued between $2,500 and $5,000, were supposed to be on a plane bound for Hangzhou, China, from St. Louis in April, where’d they spend the flight snoring, play fighting and snacking on oats and husked corn before taking up residence at Chinese hog farms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/pigs-cant-fly-us-high-end-livestock-breeders-lose-millions-china-tariff-fallout-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQVYSNPNBRNYHDTRBEU3476KZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普税收法案引发债务担忧，美股期货走势低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者担心唐纳德-特朗普总统的税收和支出法案可能会大幅加重美国的债务负担，美国股指期货在前一交易日下跌后于周四企稳，当时国债收益率飙升。【原文：U.S. stock index futures steadied on Thursday after a fall in the previous session, when Treasury yields surged, as investors worried President Donald Trump's tax and spending bill could sharply inflate the country's debt burden.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-muted-trumps-tax-bill-stokes-debt-concerns-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6RJCO7QJBN5NNYFY2M5R4XW4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:52:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称中国计划制定法规帮助科技企业海外上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国证券监督管理委员会（CSRC）首席风险官严伯进在周四的新闻发布会上表示，中国将提供一个更加高效、透明和可预测的监管环境，以支持科技公司在海外上市。【原文：China will provide a more efficient, transparent and predictable regulatory environment to support technology firms listing overseas, Chief Risk Officer at the China Securities Regulatory Commission (CSRC) Yan Bojin said at a news briefing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/china-plans-regulation-aid-tech-firms-listing-overseas-official-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QI4KXPIPSJOGFL5UV2GWDEJ6MQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[长江和记证实阿庞特的 MSC 是港口交易的主要投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[长江和记周四证实，意大利亿万富翁詹路易吉-阿庞特（Gianluigi Aponte）家族经营的地中海航运公司（MSC Mediterranean Shipping Company）是寻求从香港企业集团手中购买 43 个港口的集团的主要投资者。【原文：CK Hutchison confirmed on Thursday that Italian billionaire Gianluigi Aponte's family-run MSC Mediterranean Shipping Company is the main investor in a group seeking to buy 43 ports from the Hong Kong conglomerate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ck-hutchison-confirms-apontes-msc-is-main-investor-ports-deal-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEU2OJJQ4RP3LMASFNXK55L7YI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，日本下调全球经济展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[面对美国贸易政策的不确定性，日本政府周四下调了对全球经济的评估，这表明日本政府对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税的影响不断扩大感到担忧。【原文：Japan's government on Thursday downgraded its assessment on the global economy in the face of uncertainty over U.S. trade policy, signalling its alarm over the broadening fallout from President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-downgrades-view-global-economy-us-tariffs-bite-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6I6Q4M3MAZO65KIR34ARREM46A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行首席执行官称 2025 年为 "清算之年]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行首席执行官克里斯蒂安-苏宁（Christian Sewing）在周四计划向股东发表的讲话中称 2025 年是 "清算之年"，股东们要求他提供有关德国最大贷款机构未来发展道路的详细信息。【原文：Deutsche Bank CEO Christian Sewing called 2025 a "year of reckoning" in remarks he planned to deliver on Thursday to shareholders demanding details on the path forward for Germany's largest lender.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-ceo-calls-2025-year-reckoning-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4K2OD2MUCZN4VHBMLER6SFNW4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行：尽管贸易战仍在继续，但澳大利亚出口商对中国商业前景持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行的一位高级官员周四表示，澳大利亚出口商对在中国的业务前景持乐观态度，因为美国的关税可能会增强他们在中国市场的竞争优势。【原文：Australian exporters are upbeat on their business outlook in China as U.S. tariffs could enhance their competitive edge in Chinese markets, a top central bank official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/australian-exporters-upbeat-business-outlook-china-despite-trade-war-central-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XJWMYWWPZPDVFTJBL3D6B75TU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游戏延期动摇行业利润，《Embracer》倚重旧作]]></title><description><![CDATA[古墓丽影》的所有者 Embracer 公司首席执行官拉尔斯-温格福斯（Lars Wingefors）周四表示，在 AAA 级游戏发行量减少的情况下，Embracer 公司正依靠其游戏目录来维持现金流，但这并不是一个长期的转变。【原文：Tomb Raider owner Embracer is leaning on its back catalogue to maintain cash flow while fewer AAA games are being released, but this is not a long-term shift, CEO Lars Wingefors said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/embracer-leans-back-catalogue-game-delays-shake-industry-profits-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPJ5HU6LFVIMJLICWIEN74ZUJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国准备支持食品出口商抵御美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部周四表示，韩国将为农业和食品出口商准备支持措施，同时密切关注美国关税对该行业的影响。【原文：South Korea will prepare support measures for agricultural and food exporters, while closely monitoring the impact of U.S. tariffs on the sector, the finance ministry said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-prepare-support-food-exporters-weather-us-tariffs-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCKUYH4T35MVXOFNRFEHNTUPCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BPM 银行敦促联合信贷银行在无法满足政府要求时放弃竞标]]></title><description><![CDATA[鉴于由首席执行官 Andrea Orcel 领导的 Banco BPM 银行已告知当局，该银行无法满足罗马为批准 BPM 收购所规定的条件，BPM 银行周四敦促收购方意大利联合信贷银行放弃收购要约。【原文：Banco BPM on Thursday urged suitor UniCredit to abandon its buyout offer, given the bank led by CEO Andrea Orcel has told authorities it cannot comply with the conditions Rome has imposed to authorise the BPM takeover.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/banco-bpm-urges-unicredit-drop-bid-if-it-cant-meet-govts-demands-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GT3UXCXOQ5JR5LIQACENPZWFZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 07:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，欧佩克+讨论在 7 月再次大幅增产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，欧佩克+成员国正在讨论是否同意在6月1日的会议上再次大幅增产。【原文：OPEC+ members are discussing whether to agree on another large production increase at their meeting on June 1, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-discusses-making-another-large-output-hike-july-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPWV6GDX5BLFXG5TW7AZFCOFHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 07:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓首席执行官斯陶霍尔姆将于 2025 年晚些时候卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓（Rio Tinto）周四表示，首席执行官雅各布-斯陶霍尔姆（Jakob Stausholm）将于 2025 年晚些时候卸任。【原文：Rio Tinto on Thursday said Chief Executive Officer Jakob Stausholm will step down later in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/rio-tinto-ceo-stausholm-step-down-later-2025-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOCOOHOWDVIKBFH2X46Y6T3APM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出租方 SMBC 称波音和空客的产量取得了一些进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[飞机租赁巨头 SMBC Aviation Capital 的负责人周四表示，波音公司和空中客车公司在促进飞机制造方面取得了进展，但要实现稳定、可预测的生产周期 "还有一段路要走"。【原文：Boeing and Airbus have made progress in boosting aircraft manufacturing, but there is "a way to go" to get a stable, predictable production cycle, the head of aircraft leasing giant SMBC Aviation Capital said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/smbc-proceeds-russian-jet-insurance-settlements-hit-14-billion-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALOTNKEZCROVFLV7CPAJZBG6WY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢首席执行官表示将重新聚焦核心业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引瑞士食品巨头雀巢公司首席执行官劳伦特-弗莱克西的话说，在涉足保健品等 "削弱了组织结构 "的细分市场后，雀巢正在重新专注于集团的核心业务。【原文：Swiss food giant Nestle is refocusing on the group's core business after straying into segments like health supplements that "weakened the fabric of the organisation," CEO Laurent Freixe was quoted as saying in the Financial Times on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nestle-refocus-core-business-ceo-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ7GYUUMLRIUXJFLV5IURXXBAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道首席执行官：中美贸易休战或将减轻小松公司1.4亿美元的关税损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[这家日本公司的首席执行官表示，利润下降的前景可能没有人们担心的那么糟糕。【原文：The Japanese company's CEO suggested its outlook for lower profits may not be as bad as feared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-trade-truce-may-ease-komatsus-tariff-pain-by-140-million-ceo-says-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNZV3Q343FOXZPVYVJDW4OX5SU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:39:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者称任何中台冲突都无处藏身]]></title><description><![CDATA[外国投资者曾经几乎无法想象中国会入侵邻国台湾，但随着唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）成为美国总统，许多人将其视为必须做好准备的尾部风险情景，尽管他们找不到这样做的方法。【原文：Foreign investors could once barely imagine that China would invade neighbouring Taiwan, but with Donald Trump as president of the United States, many view it as a tail-risk scenario they must prepare for, although they cannot find ways to do so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/no-place-hide-any-china-taiwan-conflict-investors-say-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URIGXX6SXRKJ5FERDBGFKY45OU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，摩根大通戴蒙警告美国存在滞胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，摩根大通首席执行官杰米-戴蒙（Jamie Dimon）表示，他不能排除美国经济将陷入滞胀的可能性，因为美国面临着地缘政治、赤字和物价压力等巨大风险。【原文：JPMorgan Chase & Co CEO Jamie Dimon said that he can’t rule out that the U.S. economy will fall into stagflation as the country faces huge risks from geopolitics, deficits and price pressures, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgans-dimon-warns-us-stagflation-risk-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHOWVBGOSJJY7CSPNQDARX6STI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:18:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本对超长债券收益率上升的可能反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本超长期国债收益率飙升至历史新高，因为减税和大笔支出的政治呼声日益高涨，吸引了投资者对该国财政困境的关注。【原文：Japan's super-long government bond yields have spiked to record highs, as mounting political calls for tax cuts and big spending draw investors' attention to the country's fiscal woes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japans-possible-response-rise-super-long-bond-yields-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XF5FMVRSBNNYHHRHYHJSGX2GNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:09:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：欧盟对在特朗普关税一揽子方案中延长龙虾协议持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引两位官员的话报道称，作为旨在取消美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收的关税的更广泛方案的一部分，欧盟对延长给予美国龙虾免税准入的协议持开放态度。【原文：The European Union is open to extending a deal giving U.S. lobsters duty-free access as part of a broader package aimed at removing tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing two officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-open-extending-lobster-deal-package-trump-tariffs-ft-reports-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNLEA55VF5JYVJRJFESDBH4GJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行夏季暂停宽松周期的理由越来越充分]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行预计将在 6 月再次降息，但由于经济状况好于预期，且通胀挑战开始逐渐显现，因此在 6 月之后暂停降息的可能性越来越大。【原文：The European Central Bank is expected to cut interest rates once again in June but the case is growing for a pause beyond that as the economy is holding up better than feared and an inflation challenge is starting to creep up on the horizon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/case-growing-summer-pause-ecb-easing-cycle-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTG27L7RVJMIDCJIQMS6J6JWOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行为香港员工推出人工智能工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团（Citigroup）周四表示，该公司为香港员工推出了一套人工智能（AI）工具--花旗人工智能（Citi AI）。【原文：Citigroup has launched Citi AI, a suite of artificial intelligence (AI) tools for its employees in Hong Kong, the bank said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/citi-launches-ai-tools-hong-kong-employees-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMCEV5UGYBKH7A4FOIV7ZYKLV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 04:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>