<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:37:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:37:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司寻求新的西雅图航班，各航空公司争夺华盛顿特区航班时刻]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）计划于本周四宣布，它将申请在西雅图和华盛顿里根国家机场之间新开一班航班，因为各航空公司正在争夺每天五个新航班。【原文：Delta Air Lines plans to announce on Thursday it will apply for a new flight between Seattle and Washington Reagan National Airport as airlines battle over five new daily flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-seeks-new-seattle-flight-airlines-jockey-over-dc-slots-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTHEVYDV2RL6HNO47CZ6N7GICE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:05:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood 以 2 亿美元收购 Bitstamp，豪赌加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易平台 Robinhood Markets 周四表示，它已同意以约 2 亿美元的现金收购加密货币交易所 Bitstamp，从而以其有史以来最大的一笔交易加速向数字资产领域的更广泛推进。【原文：Trading platform Robinhood Markets said on Thursday it has agreed to buy cryptocurrency exchange Bitstamp for around $200 million in cash, speeding up a broader push into digital assets with its biggest ever deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/robinhood-bets-big-crypto-with-200-million-deal-bitstamp-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RL6GZ3ZRTZP33MNCAINXYADS2A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:02:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国尼奥公司预计第二季度电动汽车销量将增长一倍多]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商新奥周四表示，预计第二季度电动汽车交付量将比去年同期增长一倍多，达到54,000至56,000辆。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle maker Nio said on Thursday that it expected its EV deliveries in the second quarter to more than double from a year ago to between 54,000 and 56,000.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-nio-expects-q2-ev-sales-more-than-double-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUIHH7RK4JIFNJRNE3MQVBLIQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技股反弹后期指受抑；英伟达继续攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在等待衡量美国劳动力市场强劲程度的新数据，周四标普500指数和道指期货变化不大，而纳斯达克指数期货走高，原因是人工智能热门股英伟达（Nvidia）的上涨提振了科技板块的乐观情绪。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 and the Dow futures were little changed on Thursday as investors awaited fresh data to gauge the U.S. labor market strength, while the Nasdaq futures inched higher as gains in AI-favorite Nvidia boosted optimism around the tech sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-subdued-after-tech-rally-nvidia-continues-climb-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IE4ESKLSIVOCBAAQIIX5JSGPHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价新高：英伟达领先苹果，欧洲央行和英国央行放宽政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5ABUFTUYROE7NY74MD7DDFY24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[限期用完免税电池板，美国太阳能项目将蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对来自东南亚的太阳能电池板为期两年的免关税期将于本周四到期，美国项目开发商在今年年底前使用在此期间免税囤积的大量设备的时间开始倒计时。【原文：A two-year U.S. tariff holiday on solar panels from Southeast Asia expires on Thursday, starting the clock ticking for American project developers to use the huge amount of equipment they stockpiled duty-free over that period by the end of this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-solar-projects-could-boom-amid-deadline-use-up-tax-exempt-panel-glut-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63MZJJ2VWBLR5FCWT3QWOMCNFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:09:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小型企业可能显示出美国招聘放缓的趋势]]></title><description><![CDATA[Worxbee 是一家提供虚拟行政助理服务的小型企业，与大流行病期间的许多公司一样，当首席执行官肯齐-比金斯（Kenzie Biggins）认为她找到了一个合适的人选时，她就请来了工作人员。【原文：Like many firms during the pandemic Worxbee, a small business that provides virtual executive assistant services, brought on bodies when Chief Executive Kenzie Biggins thought she found a good match.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/small-business-may-show-coming-us-hiring-slowdown-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULWD63AGNBMRTFY6LDJ5U2CTUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:09:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：德文郡能源公司如何错过美国油气巨额交易浪潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉谈判情况的人士透露，在过去 12 个月中，美国石油和天然气生产商德文能源公司（Devon Energy）至少在三家同行的收购竞标中败北，原因是其股票被拒绝作为收购货币。【原文：U.S. oil and gas producer Devon Energy has lost bids to acquire at least three of its peers in the last 12 months because its shares were spurned as acquisition currency, according to people familiar with the negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/how-devon-energy-missed-out-us-oil-gas-mega-deal-wave-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULDZDPAWL5NYFOXKXBLDWBZ5UU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：插电式污染器？拜登的排放规则如何对混合动力卡车和 SUV 手软？]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府在今年 3 月宣布新的美国汽车尾气排放法规时，对汽车行业做出了让步，允许电动汽车的过渡比一年前提出的要慢得多。【原文：When the Biden administration announced new U.S. auto-emissions regulations in March, it made concessions to industry allowing for a much slower electric-vehicle transition than it had proposed a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/plug-in-polluters-how-bidens-emissions-rules-go-soft-hybrid-trucks-suvs-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72LCNZ72VVJH7MCFHBUDTIK63M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅赛德斯总裁期待欧盟尽快就中国电动汽车关税问题做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰（Mercedes Benz）首席执行官奥拉-凯勒纽斯（Ola Kaellenius）周四在一次行业会议上表示，他预计欧盟将很快就中国电动汽车进口关税问题做出决定。【原文：Mercedes Benz CEO Ola Kaellenius expects a decision on EU's import tariffs on Chinese electric vehicles soon, he said at an industry conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-chief-expects-eu-decision-chinese-evs-tariffs-soon-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25NJAN4LNVMQLEQDXZGOOONGAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称从未使用 WTO 禁止的电动汽车补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国外交部发言人周四表示，中国从未向电动汽车提供世界贸易组织禁止的补贴。【原文：China never makes use of subsidies for electric vehicles that have been prohibited by the World Trade Organization, a spokesperson for its foreign ministry said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-says-it-never-uses-ev-subsidies-barred-by-wto-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVFKCJHAERNDND66EQC72L2ANE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 08:14:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 4 月工业订单意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国联邦统计局周四公布的数据显示，由于大规模订单数量较上月大幅减少，4月份德国工业订单出人意料地出现下降，连续第四个月下降。【原文：German industrial orders unexpectedly fell in April, marking the fourth month in a row of decreases, due to a significantly smaller number of large-scale orders compared with the previous month, according to federal statistics office data on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-industrial-orders-unexpectedly-fall-april-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5D4P6HURFOD5A6PCGQUJJW3YU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受谢因、特穆欢迎的免关税货运遭遇美国海关障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家说，美国对处理来自与中国有关联的申银万国和特木网等巨头的数十亿美元廉价网上购物订单的报关行实施了新的打击，这很可能会造成交货延误和瓶颈。【原文：A new U.S. crackdown on customs brokers handling billions of dollars in inexpensive online shopping orders from giants like China-linked Shein and Temu is likely to cause delivery delays and bottlenecks, industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/no-tariff-shipments-popular-with-shein-temu-hit-us-customs-speedbump-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHXNDQZYFFKX7I3UYUI6OJAKRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注复苏，人头马君度酒股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在经历了利润大幅下降的艰难一年后，人头马君度酒公司表示对未来增长充满信心，该公司股价周四上涨超过 6%。【原文：Remy Cointreau's shares rose more than 6% on Thursday after the drinks company expressed confidence about future growth following a tough year where profits fell sharply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/remy-cointreaus-profit-slumps-nearly-28-beats-estimates-sees-sales-recovery-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7PVE2XQ7NNQFLADZZR6URX6YM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 05:36:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达的惊人涨幅日益推动华尔街创纪录的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[推动美国股市创下历史新高的涨势越来越依赖于炙手可热的芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）和其他几只巨型股票，这重新引发了人们对市场表现已与几家公司捆绑在一起的担忧。【原文：A rally that has propelled U.S. equities to record highs increasingly rests on red-hot chipmaker Nvidia and a handful of other giant stocks, reviving concerns that the market’s performance has become tied to a cluster of companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidias-stunning-gains-increasingly-power-wall-streets-record-run-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXBQQ5RGGVO6BCTMGGMRCQKAJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 05:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 因使用个人数据训练人工智能模型而收到 11 起欧盟投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周四遭到 11 起投诉，原因是该公司提出的修改方案将在未征得同意的情况下使用个人数据训练其人工智能模型，这可能违反了欧盟的隐私规则。【原文：Meta Platforms was hit with 11 complaints on Thursday over proposed changes that would see it use personal data to train its artificial intelligence models without asking for consent, which may breach European Union privacy rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-gets-11-eu-complaints-over-use-personal-data-train-ai-models-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJF2W75Q5FNEPB7Q2OAM5ACER4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 05:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，亿万富翁李泽楷的 FWD 集团重启香港上市计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁李泽楷重启了泛亚保险公司富登集团在香港上市的计划，三位直接了解此事的人士表示，此前富登集团上市的尝试因监管延迟和市场波动而受挫。【原文：Billionaire Richard Li has revived plans to list pan-Asian insurer FWD Group in Hong Kong, said three people with direct knowledge of the matter, after regulatory delay and market volatility scuppered previous attempts to take it public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/billionaire-richard-lis-fwd-group-revives-hong-kong-ipo-plan-sources-say-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKOBVACRRNOM5APYGRBKAZY3KE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[碧桂园香港清盘聆讯进一步延期至七月]]></title><description><![CDATA[陷入困境的碧桂园在周四提交的一份文件中称，香港高等法院已将寻求对这家中国房地产开发商进行清算的呈请聆讯进一步延期至 7 月 29 日。【原文：Embattled Country Garden said in a filing on Thursday the Hong Kong High Court had further adjourned a hearing of a petition seeking liquidation of the Chinese property developer to July 29.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/country-gardens-hong-kong-liquidation-hearing-further-adjourned-july-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHOQY5DLBFP2TLXJD6FARUAXTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:51:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，美国监管机构将对微软、OpenAI 和 Nvidia 展开反垄断调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周三援引知情人士的话报道，美国司法部和联邦贸易委员会已达成协议，允许他们对微软、OpenAI 和 Nvidia 在人工智能产业中的主导地位展开反垄断调查。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department and the Federal Trade Commission have reached a deal that allows them to proceed with antitrust investigations into the dominant roles that Microsoft , OpenAI and Nvidia play in the artificial intelligence industry, the New York Times reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-regulators-open-antitrust-inquiries-microsoft-openai-nvidia-nyt-reports-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNMNAGBWCJKC5MHIDG45JHE7GY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标E-C-B 的时间到了]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KH2NURMZQFPV7AGWYM2NNS55XU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会主席称，美国以太坊 ETF 的推出时间取决于发行商的行动速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）主席加里-根斯勒（Gary Gensler）周三表示，与加密货币以太坊挂钩的交易所交易基金（ETF）何时能开始交易，主要取决于发行商对美国证券交易委员会的询问做出回应的速度。【原文：The timing for when exchange-traded funds (ETFs) tied to the cryptocurrency ether can begin trading depends largely on how quickly issuers respond to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's queries, Chair Gary Gensler said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/timing-us-ether-etf-launches-depends-how-fast-issuers-can-move-sec-chair-says-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKPJK7CSVRJ2JD57QJUXYYY23E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，美国太阳能发电装机量创季度纪录，占新增发电量的 75]]></title><description><![CDATA[伍德麦肯兹公司（Wood Mackenzie）和太阳能产业协会（Solar Energy Industries Association）周四发布的一份报告显示，随着太阳能电池板的安装量创下季度记录，今年年初美国电网新增发电能力中的75%来自太阳能。【原文：Solar accounted for 75% of electricity generation capacity added to the U.S. power grid early this year as installations of panels rose to a quarterly record, according to a report published by Wood Mackenzie and the Solar Energy Industries Association on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-solar-installations-hit-quarterly-record-making-up-75-new-power-added-report-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABH2ZGNAA5MU7DJDOBVGHPRZOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息押注蓄势待发，亚洲股市反弹；欧洲央行成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周四上涨，原因是市场对美国联邦储备委员会可能在 9 月份降息的预期不断升温，而欧元在欧洲央行政策会议召开前走高，市场普遍预期欧洲央行将降息。【原文：Asian shares gained on Thursday on rising expectations the U.S. Federal Reserve will likely cut interest rates in September, while the euro advanced ahead of the European Central Bank policy meeting where a rate cut is widely expected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QD3XA3F4KBO6HPQQ4S4IT4G344</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:32:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称 KKR、GIP 和印度太平洋集团成立 250 亿美元地区基础设施合作公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长吉娜-雷蒙多（Gina Raimondo）周四表示，私募股权公司KKR和全球基础设施合作伙伴（GIP）与新成立的印度-太平洋繁荣伙伴组织正在组建一个联盟，将向该地区的基础设施投资250亿美元。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo said on Thursday that private equity firms KKR and Global Infrastructure Partners (GIP) and the newly formed Indo-Pacific Partnership for Prosperity were forming a coalition to invest $25 billion in infrastructure in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/kkr-gip-indo-pacific-group-form-25-billion-regional-infrastructure-tie-up-us-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DY5UNR7O7JNDPFCB3BS2HMKZHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:20:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行中村警告称日本可能无法实现 2025 年后的物价目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本鸽派决策者中村丰明（Toyoaki Nakamura）周四表示，如果消费停滞不前，明年日本的通胀率可能达不到央行设定的2%的目标，这凸显了进一步加息时机的不确定性。【原文：Japan may see inflation fall short of the central bank's 2% target next year if consumption stagnates, its dovish policymaker Toyoaki Nakamura said on Thursday, highlighting uncertainty over the timing of further interest rate hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-may-miss-bojs-price-target-2025-says-policymaker-nakamura-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACGB5K42TRJOXM5CEAN5ZQX634</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:11:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行决议前欧元持稳，美元下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在欧洲中央银行（ECB）做出政策决定之前，欧元略微走强，交易员认为欧洲中央银行几乎肯定会降息，而美元则因再次押注美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）今年有望进入宽松周期而有所回落。【原文：The euro firmed a touch on Thursday ahead of a policy decision from the European Central Bank (ECB) where traders consider a rate cut all but certain, while the dollar eased on renewed bets of a U.S. Federal Reserve easing cycle expected this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/euro-steadies-ahead-ecb-decision-dollar-dips-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWTFLHAJZJNYZHZ4B6LVUNR3JY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 01:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 4 月贸易顺差反弹，进口大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的数据显示，澳大利亚 4 月份的货物贸易顺差出现反弹，原因是进口在连续数月增长后出现下滑，尽管铁和煤的出口也出现疲软。【原文：Australia's surplus on trade goods rebounded in April as imports took a dive after several months of gains, though exports of iron and coal also softened, data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-trade-surplus-rebounds-april-imports-dive-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZ6CKQVMJVLB7IGX46VVFCEQEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 01:48:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息预期增强，石油上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[石油在周四亚洲早盘交易中上涨，原因是市场对美联储将在9月份降息的预期不断升温，而且市场从与美国库存增加和欧佩克+计划增加供应有关的大跌中反弹。【原文：Oil rose in early Asian trading on Thursday on rising expectations the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates in September, and as the market rebounded from a selloff related to growing U.S. inventories and an OPEC+ plan to increase supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-strengthening-fed-rate-cut-expectations-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEQUA6DBH5KWRDPWPV4EGJ7MPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 01:28:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[好市多的日本工资为改善日本低工资和经济状况提供了途径]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，好市多批发公司（Costco Wholesale）在离东京不远的一个日本农村小镇开设了仓库，提供了数百个薪水令人瞠目的工作岗位，附近的一家面条连锁店采取了一个激进的措施：将小时工资提高了三分之一。【原文：When Costco Wholesale opened its warehouse in a rural Japanese town not far from Tokyo last year offering hundreds of jobs at eye-popping pay, a nearby noodle shop chain took a drastic step: it hiked hourly wages by a third.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/costcos-japan-wages-provide-pathway-firing-up-nations-low-pay-economy-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTK6ASGXZFOVPDY5SVVH2MHOVY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 01:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《时尚商业》报道，香奈儿创意总监维吉妮-维阿尔（Virginie Viard）将退出香奈儿品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[据时尚新闻网站 Business of Fashion 周三报道，奢侈时尚品牌香奈儿的创意总监 Virginie Viard 即将离职。【原文：Luxury fashion brand Chanel's creative director Virginie Viard is set to leave the company, fashion news website Business of Fashion reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chanels-creative-director-virginie-viard-exit-brand-business-fashion-reports-2024-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOITZXN2VBO7PGU7BPXUHKCJEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>