<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:09:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:09:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 节假日季度预测显示人工智能广告战略初见成效]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit 周四预计第四季度营收将高于华尔街预期，这要归功于其人工智能驱动的广告工具，这些工具正在促进社交媒体平台的营销支出。【原文：Reddit forecast fourth-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, thanks to its artificial intelligence-powered advertising tools that are boosting marketing spending on the social media platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/reddits-holiday-quarter-forecast-shows-ai-ad-strategy-paying-off-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GHHADL3MFM4DDO3WOK7TM4CIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:07:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊预测季度营收大幅低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周四预测的季度营收基本低于华尔街预期，原因是零售业务疲软，而企业继续在人工智能方面不遗余力地投入，对其云服务的需求强劲。【原文：Amazon.com forecast quarterly revenue largely below Wall Street estimates on Thursday, hurt by a weaker retail business as strong demand for its cloud services as businesses continue to spend relentlessly on artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-forecasts-quarterly-revenue-largely-below-estimates-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLBYJXBAC5M2DLMZXEUIGMKZSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预防药物助力艾滋病销售额增长，吉利德公司利润增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司（Gilead Sciences）周四表示，其第三季度艾滋病药物销售额增长了 4%，达到 53 亿美元，其中新的预防药物 Yeztugo 的销售额达到 3900 万美元，帮助其利润超过了华尔街的预期。【原文：Gilead Sciences said on Thursday its HIV drug sales rose 4% to $5.3 billion in the third quarter including $39 million for its new prevention drug Yeztugo, helping to boost its profit above Wall Street estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/gilead-posts-higher-profit-hiv-sales-rise-helped-by-prevention-drugs-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RK22TCN7RLNNE2B6SAVARS2UA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美联储鲍曼拟削减银行监管部门约 30]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）的最高银行警察米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）宣布，计划重组该机构的监督和监管部门，并将该部门的人员缩减约 30%。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve's top bank cop, Michelle Bowman, announced plans to reorganize the agency's supervision and regulation division and shrink the unit's staff by roughly 30%, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-bowman-moves-reduce-bank-supervision-unit-by-about-30-bloomberg-news-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEFLSOP2PFLVZGYD4YYZG3RE4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Globalstar 在出售过程中吸引了 SpaceX 的兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周四援引知情人士的话报道称，Globalstar 正在探索潜在的出售方案，并已与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX 公司以及其他潜在买家进行了早期讨论。【原文：Globalstar is exploring a potential sale and has held early discussions with Elon Musk's SpaceX among other prospective buyers, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/globalstar-draws-spacex-interest-sale-process-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UPHERQ3D5OMVAY57NHZ7WZ5KE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:50:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，福特将在印度投资 3.7 亿美元生产新型发动机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引一位熟知内情的人士的话报道，福特正计划在印度投资约 3.7 亿美元生产新型发动机。【原文：Ford is planning to invest about $370 million in India to make new engines, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/ford-invest-370-million-india-new-engines-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNAXTEZLHVPAJIC5DCCMYTZOHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:46:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普和习近平同意暂停征收中断贸易的港口费]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国周四同意暂停对对方船只征收针锋相对的费用，这些费用已成为世界两大经济体之间更广泛贸易战的主要刺激因素，并推高了海运成本。【原文：The U.S. and China agreed on Thursday to pause tit-for-tat fees on each other's ships that became a major irritant in the broader trade war between the world's two largest economies and pushed up ocean freight costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-xi-agree-pause-dueling-port-fees-that-disrupted-trade-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UVKWK5O2NPBNOUSAORREPQGTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:43:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，英伟达将向人工智能初创公司 Poolside 投资最多 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，英伟达（Nvidia）将向人工智能公司 Poolside 投资最多 10 亿美元，这笔交易将使这家初创公司的估值翻两番。【原文：Nvidia will invest up to $1 billion in AI company Poolside, in a deal that would quadruple the startup's valuation, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-invest-up-1-billion-ai-startup-poolside-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRVNR7REAVIHVG7ELCJXYJKT7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易休战后，中国的投资能力有所增强]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国与美国达成的最新贸易休战协议消除了外国投资者的一大顾虑，他们全年都对投资中国股市持谨慎态度，而中国股市则以 2019 年以来最强劲的年度表现超越了大多数其他主要股市。【原文：China's latest trade truce with the United States removes one big deterrent for foreign investors who've been circumspect all year about investing in a stock market that's outrun most other major ones with its strongest annual run since 2019.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/after-trade-truce-china-becomes-bit-more-investible-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSFF4NJNI5L4ZKKHHZDUBARVGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[去中心化加密货币交易所 dYdX 计划年底前进入美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[顶级去中心化加密货币交易平台之一 dYdX 的总裁在接受路透社采访时表示，dYdX 正准备在今年年底前进入美国市场，这是这家以衍生品为重点的交易所的一次转变，此前美国用户无法使用该平台。【原文：One of the top decentralized cryptocurrency trading platforms, dYdX, is preparing to enter the U.S. market by the end of the year, in a shift for the derivatives-focused exchange that was previously not available to American users, the president of dYdX told Reuters in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/decentralized-crypto-exchange-dydx-plans-us-market-entry-by-year-end-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXOW4AV4WNIDHHMZ2DVBAL2LOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称中国本季将购买 1200 万吨大豆]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，在长达数月的关税战停止了对美国本季大豆的所有采购后，中国已同意在本季至1月期间购买1200万吨美国大豆，低于上一季的2250万吨。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday that China has agreed to buy 12 million metric tons of American soybeans during the current season through January, down from 22.5 million tons in the prior season after a months-long tariff battle halted all purchases of the current U.S. harvest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-buy-12-million-metric-tons-soybeans-this-season-bessent-says-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGQ5ZUCLONI3JC2F5GWPX6ZCKY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:25:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[看涨期权交易将推动标普 500 指数在 7,000 点附近波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[据期权专家称，一波看涨期权交易放大了美国股市向另一个重要里程碑迈进的步伐，并使交易商们做好了在未来几天或几周内市场波动可能会被夸大的准备。【原文：A wave of bullish options trading has amplified the U.S. stock market's advance toward another major milestone and left dealers positioned so that market swings are likely to be exaggerated in coming days or weeks, according to options specialists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bullish-options-plays-set-boost-sp-500-gyrations-around-7000-level-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GA5V3GTMFNL2LCWZ2KM234ADIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:22:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德改变策略，大胆突袭辉瑞肥胖症交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）迟迟未能阻止辉瑞（Pfizer）对美国肥胖症生物技术公司 Metsera 的收购，这标志着这家丹麦制药商正在积极转变，在新任首席执行官和董事会的领导下，力图在减肥药市场重振雄风。【原文：Novo Nordisk's late bid to hijack Pfizer's takeover of U.S. obesity biotech Metsera marks an aggressive shift from the Danish drugmaker as it seeks to regain ground in the weight-loss drug market under a new CEO and board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/novo-nordisk-changes-tack-with-bold-raid-pfizer-obesity-deal-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLXHOFA52VPAZNEYHIZ3Z6AIGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟文件显示，欧盟希望借助网络平台打击混合威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，根据欧盟委员会将于下月公布的一项提案，受具有里程碑意义的欧盟技术规则约束的在线平台必须检测和应对欧洲的混合威胁。【原文：Online platforms subject to landmark EU tech rules could be required to detect and tackle hybrid threats in Europe under a proposal set to be announced by the European Commission next month and seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/eu-wants-enlist-online-platforms-fight-hybrid-threats-eu-document-shows-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVBFPFUWX5MCFNV2ZGMZUOZLQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储最新降息对您的资金意味着什么--即使下一次降息还不确定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会周三将其关键利率目标下调了四分之一个百分点。但美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）告诫说，2025年再次降息并不能保证。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve cut its key interest-rate target by a quarter of a percentage point on Wednesday. But Fed Chair Jerome Powell cautioned that another move in 2025 is not guaranteed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/what-latest-fed-rate-cut-means-your-money-even-if-next-one-is-not-certain-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMWALHETTVN3VGIMZIG6QWLAXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿肯色州力争成为美国锂电中心，克服中国竞争和技术挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿肯色州在争夺成为美国锂生产中心的过程中面临着中国的激烈竞争、市场价格下挫和技术挑战，但该州官员和行业高管本周表示，这些障碍都是可以克服的。【原文：Arkansas faces stiff Chinese competition, sagging market prices and technological challenges as it vies to become the hub for U.S. lithium production, obstacles that state officials and industry executives said this week are surmountable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/arkansas-aims-become-us-lithium-hub-overcoming-chinese-competition-tech-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFDBY36XCFIKPLUWFFW4X2MLF4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:11:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球音乐集团因泰勒-斯威夫特（Taylor Swift）的销售增长而收入超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）周四公布的第三季度营收高于市场预期，泰勒-斯威夫特（Taylor Swift）的新作推动了实体专辑的销售。【原文：Universal Music Group on Thursday reported third-quarter revenue above market expectations with Taylor Swift's new release boosting physical album sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/universal-music-group-q3-revenue-beats-market-forecasts-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOF2TQB5ZJMLBI3FVH7YFWSREQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟技术负责人维尔库宁将于周五会见芯片制造商 Nexperia]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟技术负责人亨娜-维尔库宁（Henna Virkkunen）将于周五会见芯片制造商耐克斯派瑞（Nexperia），她是在周四早些时候与英飞凌（Infineon）、意法半导体（STMicroelectronics）、恩智浦（NXP）和 Acea 的首席执行官举行虚拟会议后在 X 上表示的。【原文：EU tech chief Henna Virkkunen will meet chipmaker Nexperia on Friday, she said on X after hosting virtual meetings with the chief executives of Infineon , STMicroelectronics, NXP and Acea earlier on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-tech-chief-virkkunen-meet-chipmaker-nexperia-friday-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJXLEDRXG5KITH6U6EUMPEUMSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国肥胖症生物技术公司 Metsera 成为诺和、辉瑞竞购战的焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[Metsera 已成为肥胖症药物市场的热门产品。【原文：Metsera has become the obesity drug market's hottest ticket.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/metsera-us-obesity-biotech-centre-novo-pfizer-bidding-war-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDOWBNSDTRIARA5GSCNG3T6EFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir起诉离职组建 "山寨 "Percepta人工智能公司的工程师]]></title><description><![CDATA[帕兰提尔科技公司（Palantir Technologies）周四起诉了两名前高级工程师，指控他们利用该软件公司的秘密信息创办了一家 "山寨 "公司--Percepta AI。【原文：Palantir Technologies on Thursday sued two of its former senior engineers, accusing them of using the software company's secret information to launch a "copycat" firm, Percepta AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/palantir-sues-engineers-who-left-form-copycat-percepta-ai-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGJ5IHTDJNON3BEO46GICFIBL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:58:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球央行对降息趋于谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会周三将利率下调四分之一个百分点后，与其他主要利率制定者重新保持一致，但由于华盛顿停摆使其预测镜头变得模糊不清，美联储回绝了市场对其将继续下调利率的押注。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve has moved back into line with other major rate setters after it cut rates by a quarter point on Wednesday but pushed back against market bets that it would keep going as the Washington shutdown fogs up its forecasting lens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-cenbank-graphic-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74GJ6AL2LJI7ZHXZHKNLF57JRE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息称长江和记与伊利亚特考虑合并意大利业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，香港企业集团长江和记一直在研究将其意大利电信部门 Wind Tre 与法国电信集团 Iliad 的意大利业务合并的可能性。【原文：Hong Kong conglomerate CK Hutchison has been studying a potential tie-up of its Italian telecom unit Wind Tre and the Italian operations of French telecoms group Iliad, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ck-hutchison-iliad-consider-tie-up-up-their-italian-operations-sources-say-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5GSWREAOZOXJAAK6RIWHFXY44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[C.H.罗宾逊股价创历史新高，以人工智能驱动的涨势抵御货运低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗宾逊公司（C.H. Robinson）的股价周四大涨超过 20%，创下历史新高，投资者对这家全球货运代理公司因人工智能驱动的效率而实现季度利润增长感到高兴，而此时物流业的其他公司却在苦苦挣扎。【原文：Shares of C.H. Robinson surged more than 20% to a record high on Thursday as investors cheered the global freight forwarder's quarterly profit beat due to AI-driven efficiencies at a time when the rest of the logistics sector has struggled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ch-robinsons-shares-hit-record-high-defying-freight-slump-with-ai-driven-gains-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGWFN5YPGJMCXHR57D2S6OFLME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯科股东拒绝 90 亿美元的 CoreWeave 收购要约，交易终止]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密矿机制造商 Core Scientific 周四结束了出售给 CoreWeave 的交易，因为股东投票反对该提议，这标志着长达数月的投资者和代理机构反对该协议的运动达到了高潮。【原文：Crypto miner Core Scientific on Thursday ended a deal for its sale to CoreWeave after shareholders voted against the proposal, marking the culmination of months-long investor and proxy campaigns against the agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/core-scientific-terminates-9-billion-merger-deal-with-coreweave-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJKKIXNXB5PIVAGOJCTTPM77I4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[时装设计师 Bob Mackie 就服装系列起诉 JCPenney]]></title><description><![CDATA[曾为雪儿、卡罗尔-伯内特、埃尔顿-约翰和泰勒-斯威夫特等名人设计服装的时装设计师兼服装师鲍勃-麦基（Bob Mackie）起诉 JCPenney，称其未经许可使用自己的姓名、签名和肖像销售服装。【原文：Bob Mackie, the fashion designer and costumer who has outfitted celebrities like Cher, Carol Burnett, Elton John and Taylor Swift, has sued JCPenney for allegedly using his name, signature and likeness without permission to sell apparel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/fashion-designer-bob-mackie-sues-jcpenney-over-apparel-line-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3EMUH5VAZPAJDCWTDLVMN5Z5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:18:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能热潮推动万亿美元科技估值，芯片制造商押注创纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，顶级科技公司创下了新的估值里程碑，这些公司的股价因预期人工智能热潮将推动对人工智能芯片和计算基础设施的强劲需求而攀升。【原文：Top technology companies hit fresh valuation milestones in October, as their shares climbed on expectations of robust demand for AI chips and computing infrastructure driven by the artificial intelligence boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-markets-marketcap-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UD56EX4KBLCBNAFFYKPGLOCUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 首席执行官表示，Stellantis 已成立 "作战室 "处理 Nexperia 芯片危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis公司首席执行官周四表示，Stellantis已经成立了一个 "作战室"，以应对荷兰Nexperia集团因中美贸易战而出现的问题可能导致的芯片短缺。【原文：Stellantis has set up a "war room" to address possible chip shortages stemming from issues at Dutch group Nexperia linked to the U.S.-China trade war, the automaker's CEO said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-has-set-up-war-room-manage-nexperia-chip-crisis-ceo-says-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEPNBBZQJZN47HAXIWQBRHU7PY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由 KKR 支持的 ContourGlobal 为美国太阳能项目完成 3.5 亿美元的一揽子融资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国投资基金 KKR 旗下的 ContourGlobal 集团周四表示，该集团已获得价值超过 3.5 亿美元的一揽子融资，以支持其在科罗拉多州的太阳能设施建设。【原文：ContourGlobal has secured a funding package worth more than $350 million to support its solar installations in Colorado, the group owned by U.S. investment fund KKR said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/kkr-backed-contourglobal-seals-350-mln-funding-package-us-solar-project-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RFRJ7M42IZNFFHNIKVKNFZMEAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:59:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯兰诺瓦因早餐产品需求回升，季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯兰诺瓦公司周四公布的第三季度销售额和利润超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于市场对其即食早餐和零食（包括 Pringles 和 Pop-Tarts）的强劲需求，尽管宏观经济的不确定性依然存在。【原文：Kellanova beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter sales and profit on Thursday, driven by resilient demand for its ready-to-eat breakfast items and snacks, including Pringles and Pop-Tarts, even as macroeconomic uncertainty looms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kellanova-beats-quarterly-estimates-resilient-demand-breakfast-items-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5HDFI564SNOC5BALPTHKLOFP2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:57:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国航空公司在暑运中恢复盈利，但挑战依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[在暑运旺季的带动下，中国三大航空公司在第三季度实现了一年来首次集体盈利，但由于供过于求继续拖累国内航空市场，这种复苏可能稍纵即逝。【原文：China's three biggest airlines posted their first collective quarterly profit in a year in the third quarter on the back of the peak summer season, but the recovery could be fleeting as oversupply continues to drag down the domestic aviation market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/chinese-airlines-return-profit-summer-surge-challenges-persist-2025-10-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUGX6T2NDZNF5IR7A22OXO4OCM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>