<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:05:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:05:29 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟对在贸易谈判中降低美国化肥关税持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟农业委员克里斯托夫-汉森（Christophe Hansen）告诉路透社，欧盟愿意在与特朗普政府的贸易谈判中降低美国进口化肥的关税，但不会为达成协议而削弱其食品安全标准。【原文：The European Union is open to lowering tariffs on U.S. fertiliser imports as an offer in trade talks with the Trump administration, but will not weaken its food safety standards in pursuit of a deal, EU agriculture commissioner Christophe Hansen told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-open-lowering-tariffs-us-fertilisers-trade-talks-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITLL3H7XGRMRHFGXSXQ2S22JLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 新任首席执行官 Filosa 年收入将高达 2300 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份文件显示，Stellantis 公司新任首席执行官安东尼奥-菲洛萨（Antonio Filosa）在执掌公司的头两年将获得至少 400 万美元的年薪，从 2028 年起，包括奖金在内的年薪将增至 2300 万美元，但他的薪酬将低于前任卡洛斯-塔瓦雷斯（Carlos Tavares）。【原文：Stellantis' new CEO Antonio Filosa will earn at least $4 million annually in his first two years at the helm, rising to up to $23 million a year from 2028, including bonuses, a document showed, although his remuneration will be lower than predecessor Carlos Tavares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/stellantis-new-ceo-filosa-set-earn-up-23-million-year-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIQH4DSSZZI7BHTFTF3SZKOB4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:44:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑜伽服公司警告关税将削弱利润，Lululemon 股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lululemon Athletica 的股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌了 21%，这家高端紧身裤制造商警告称，与关税相关的成本以及北美和中国等主要市场的不均衡需求将影响其今年的利润。【原文：Lululemon Athletica's shares fell 21% in premarket trading on Friday, as the maker of high-end leggings warned that tariff-related costs and uneven demand in key markets of North America and China will dent its profits this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lululemon-shares-tumble-yogawear-firm-warns-tariffs-will-crimp-profit-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKV5ZX2TOBJPFPBUOPTFH7W32Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业数据公布前，华尔街期货走高；特斯拉反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在投资者等待月度就业数据之际，美国股指期货上扬，而特斯拉股价则因首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）之间的紧张关系出现降温迹象而反弹。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged up on Friday as investors awaited monthly payrolls data, while Tesla shares rebounded on signs of cooling tensions between CEO Elon Musk and U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/wall-street-futures-edge-up-ahead-jobs-data-tesla-rebounds-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOREDSM32ZP7JFIHENZL2LAHAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉亏损 3800 亿美元，创 2025 年顶级公司最大亏损纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于电动汽车需求下降、首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）与极右翼组织的关系引发政治争议，以及现在他与唐纳德-特朗普总统的公开不和，特斯拉成为今年表现最差的大盘股。【原文：Tesla is the worst-performing large-cap stock this year, thanks to declining electric vehicle demand, Chief Executive Elon Musk's political controversies over his ties to far-right groups, and now, his public feud with President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-markets-marketcap-pix-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIXMR2YB2FKY7AMHZKCABVTRII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Miniso 集团考虑分拆流行玩具业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miniso 集团周五表示，正在对其流行玩具业务 "TOP TOY "分拆上市的可能性进行初步评估。【原文：Miniso Group said on Friday it was making a preliminary assessment of a potential spin-off listing of its pop toy business operating under the brand, "TOP TOY".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/miniso-group-mulls-spin-off-its-pop-toy-business-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXB7ZC2RRNMV3FXHVV5HMZNIH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:11:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 通胀数据、政策进展成焦点，美股屡创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市的反弹已将主要股指推向创纪录水平的边缘，新的经济数据以及贸易和财政政策的发展将考验股市在短期内是否会再创新高。【原文：The U.S. stock rebound has driven key indexes to the cusp of record levels, with fresh economic data and trade and fiscal policy developments set to test whether equities will get an extra push higher in the near term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-us-stocks-edge-toward-records-with-inflation-data-policy-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCCDB32FZFMAHCGSTUU6BZXWNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[稳定币迈向主流可能撼动部分美国国债市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着稳定币一步步成为主流，美国国债市场的某些部分，尤其是短期到期的证券，可能会因为与加密货币世界的联系更加紧密而容易受到波动的影响。【原文：As stablecoins take a step toward becoming mainstream, some segments of the U.S. Treasury market, notably securities with short-term maturities, could be vulnerable to volatility as they become more closely tied to the world of cryptocurrency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stablecoins-step-toward-mainstream-could-shake-up-parts-us-treasury-market-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2B4BBQDW7NKUVDEISV5YSIDFHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+增加产量，美国轻质甜原油需求下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+"供应量的增加和全球新石油流的上线，增加了欧洲和亚洲炼油厂的选择，并抑制了对美国轻质甜原油的出口需求，从而导致美国主要产油区的油价下跌。【原文：Rising OPEC+ supplies and new streams of oil coming online globally are increasing options for European and Asian refiners and weighing on export demand for light sweet U.S. crude, contributing to lower prices in the country's main oil-producing regions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/demand-us-light-sweet-crude-drops-opec-ramps-up-output-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4D672FKMCBMJRD5GMR52YLQZWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克与特朗普争吵后，特斯拉卖空者获利约 40 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）之间的公开争吵导致特斯拉股价创下有史以来最大单日跌幅后，交易商周四从特斯拉股票空头头寸中获利 40 亿美元。【原文：Traders raked in $4 billion in profit from their short positions in Tesla shares on Thursday after a public feud between President Donald Trump and CEO Elon Musk led to the stock's biggest single-day drop ever.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-short-sellers-pocket-about-4-billion-profits-after-musk-trump-spat-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5PRWVUJBBL7JBGK4U2LJ3ENTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国默茨公司希望在特朗普会谈后建立汽车关税抵消机制]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希-默茨（Friedrich Merz）周五表示，他将寻求达成一项协议，即美国汽车可以免税进口到欧洲，以换取同样数量的出口到美国的汽车的关税减免。【原文：German Chancellor Friedrich Merz said on Friday that he would pursue a deal under which U.S. cars could be imported into Europe duty free in exchange for tariff waivers on the same number of vehicles exported to the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/germanys-merz-eyes-car-tariff-offsetting-mechanism-after-trump-talks-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOZOID5IXRNYTPMJX3KGBZVQMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博通股价下跌，原因是营收预期不尽如人意]]></title><description><![CDATA[博通（Broadcom）股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌近 4%，此前该公司的第三季度营收预期未能打动在人工智能热潮中极度看好芯片股的投资者。【原文：Broadcom shares fell nearly 4% in premarket trading on Friday, after the company's third-quarter revenue forecast failed to impress investors who have been extremely bullish on chip stocks amid an artificial intelligence boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/broadcom-shares-drop-revenue-forecast-fails-impress-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5WMP2F7NJPPRPNUJPPG4I6RBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，马斯克的 "星链 "公司从印度电信部获得关键许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周五告诉路透社，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的Starlink公司已获得印度电信部颁发的关键许可证，为这家卫星供应商扫清了一大障碍，使其离在印度开展商业运营更近了一步。【原文：Elon Musk's Starlink has received a key licence from India's telecoms ministry, sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters on Friday, clearing a major hurdle for the satellite provider and taking it closer to launching commercial operations in India.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/musks-starlink-gets-key-india-licence-telecoms-ministry-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CDCX2SMGRKMPCLYIRLBQKSTZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士法郎走强为何可能导致其重回负利率水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士可能成为首个恢复负利率以应对货币飙升和物价下跌的大型经济体，这凸显出在全球贸易战持续发酵的背景下，央行可能很快就会耗尽常规政策工具。【原文：Switzerland could be the first big economy to return to negative interest rates to fight a surging currency and falling prices, highlighting how quickly central bankers may be running out of conventional policy tools as a global trade war rages on.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/why-switzerlands-strong-franc-could-lead-it-back-negative-interest-rates-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2E56BFSLBKZ7M2HYMUDOXVCYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:28:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙对委内瑞拉石油的进口在美国制裁截止日期前枯竭]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府设定的关键制裁期限之前，西班牙在四月份没有从委内瑞拉进口原油。【原文：Spain didn't import crude oil from Venezuela in April, ahead of a key sanctions deadline set by U.S. President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/spains-imports-venezuelan-oil-dry-up-ahead-us-sanctions-deadline-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUACRVF43VNELN2RZA5KB7SN6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:20:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五月份世界粮食价格下降，谷物、糖和蔬菜价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国粮食及农业组织周五表示，受谷物、糖和植物油价格明显下跌的影响，5月份全球粮食商品价格有所下降。【原文：Global food commodity prices declined in May, driven by marked drops in cereal, sugar, and vegetable oil prices, the United Nations' Food and Agriculture Organization said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-food-prices-dip-may-cereal-sugar-vegoils-drop-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKEXRDVN5FMILIUZ4ECNFLZFGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国稀土武器改变贸易战战场轮廓]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周争夺稀土出口许可证的行为表明，中国已设计出一种更好、目标更明确的贸易战武器。【原文：The scramble in recent weeks to secure export licences for rare earths shows China has devised a better, more precisely targeted weapon for trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-rare-earth-weapon-changes-contours-trade-war-battlefield-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDPXHLODGNJQTOC3IC5HOSZIBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本前最高外汇外交官预计年底前日元将升至140附近]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本前最高货币外交官周五表示，美日利率差距的缩小，而不是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普削弱美元的任何努力，将有可能使日元兑美元汇率在年底前升至135-140左右。【原文：A narrowing U.S.-Japan interest rate gap, rather than any effort by President Donald Trump to weaken the dollar, will likely lift the yen to around 135-140 against the U.S. unit by year-end, Japan's former top currency diplomat said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-ex-top-fx-diplomat-expects-yen-rise-near-140-by-year-end-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3E72A3WT5J55DGGCTYK7J6C4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市迎来 15 个月来最大单月外资流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份，亚洲股市吸引了强劲的外资流入，因为市场对美国提高关税会对经济造成直接冲击的担忧有所缓解，这促使此前退出该地区大额集中头寸的投资者回流。【原文：Asian equities attracted strong foreign inflows in May as concerns over an immediate economic hit from higher U.S. tariffs eased, prompting a return by investors who had previously exited large and concentrated positions in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/asian-equities-see-largest-monthly-foreign-inflow-15-months-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57BEN2J3M5IWFNPMX4UX3YSNOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卫星公司 SES 聘用航空业资深人士担任新任财务总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲卫星公司 SES 周五表示，已任命 Elisabeth Pataki 为新任财务总监。【原文：SES has appointed Elisabeth Pataki as its new finance chief, the European satellite company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/satellite-firm-ses-taps-aerospace-veteran-new-finance-chief-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5L2UVTNNDBJMHIPRRSTDJ67VKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪将日产企业家族评级下调至 Ba2]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构穆迪（Moody's）周五将日产汽车公司的企业家族评级从Ba1下调至Ba2，这家陷入困境的日本汽车制造商正努力推动扭亏为盈。【原文：Global ratings agency Moody's on Friday cut Nissan Motor Co Ltd's corporate family rating to Ba2 from Ba1, as the embattled Japanese automaker seeks to push through a turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/moodys-cuts-nissan-corporate-family-rating-ba2-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLQMORM4J5OV7CAOYF5CN3QNUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:21:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政治报》报道马斯克与白宫将举行电话会议，特斯拉股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周五，在法兰克福上市的特斯拉股票上涨了 5.6%，此前 Politico 报道称，白宫助手已安排与首席执行官埃隆-马斯克通话，以便在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普公开交恶后促成和平。【原文：Tesla shares listed in Frankfurt rose 5.6% on Friday after Politico reported White House aides have scheduled a call with CEO Elon Musk to broker peace after a public feud with U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-shares-rise-politico-reports-musk-white-house-hold-call-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN46NHYPEZNLLFBTYPKQSFKW4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易不确定性导致中国 5 月出口可能放缓 - 路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国降低了对中国商品的关税，但由于贸易战余波未了以及中美关系的不确定性影响了出货量，中国 5 月份的出口增长可能有所放缓。【原文：Growth in China's exports likely slowed in May despite a lowering of U.S. tariffs on Chinese goods, as the fallout from the still-unresolved trade war and uncertainties in Sino-U.S. ties weighed on shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-exports-likely-slowed-may-amid-trade-uncertainties-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2H6USKLJFJOPXMF5AQWS2SLCUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国达索系统公司将盈利目标推迟至 2029 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国软件公司达索系统（Dassault Systemes）周五将中期每股收益（EPS）预测的目标期限延长了一年，而此时汽车需求疲软和关税带来的不确定性正对其业务造成压力。【原文：French software company Dassault Systemes extended the target period of its medium-term earnings per share (EPS) forecast by one year on Friday, at a time when weak auto demand and tariff-driven uncertainty weigh on its business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frances-dassault-systemes-delays-earnings-target-timeline-until-2029-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URXH6KAFK5LGXC64PC7QFVM3AY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:41:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行被列入美国观察名单后否认操纵货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国将瑞士列入因不公平货币和贸易行为而受到监控的国家名单之后，瑞士央行周五表示，瑞士国家银行没有参与货币操纵。【原文：The Swiss National Bank does not engage in currency manipulation, the central bank said on Friday, after the United States added Switzerland to a list of countries being monitored for unfair currency and trade practices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swiss-national-bank-denies-currency-manipulation-after-being-put-us-watch-list-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNLRBOOT3JJ6DKCRZCB4VE7CEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价特朗普与马斯克的争吵震撼了薪资前市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-markets-view-europe-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWTFHLJINZMF5PT6KIG24I35MQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对市场而言，欧洲央行降息的终点越来越近了]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于欧洲央行认为自己有能力应对美国关税政策引发的全球经济不确定性，交易员们对欧洲央行暂停降息的信心与日俱增。【原文：Traders are increasingly confident the European Central Bank will pause its run of interest rate cuts now that the central bank sees itself as well-positioned to deal with global economic uncertainty fuelled by U.S. tariff policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/markets-end-ecb-rate-cuts-just-got-closer-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMPRWTUR5VMZZBCQNXN2JLNE5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计美国 5 月就业增长缓慢；失业率保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于企业在关税不确定性的逆风中挣扎，5 月份美国的就业增长可能大幅放缓，但可能还不足以让谨慎的美联储很快恢复降息。【原文：U.S. job growth likely slowed considerably in May as businesses struggled with headwinds from tariff uncertainty, but probably not enough for a cautious Federal Reserve to resume cutting interest rates anytime soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/slow-us-job-growth-anticipated-may-unemployment-rate-seen-steady-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQZD5DPXZNOBLLHDXPTEKQLZMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:12:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与马斯克的 "兄弟情 "演变为合同和弹劾问题上的争吵]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果两人长期不和，导致马斯克失去竞选开支，或削弱硅谷对特朗普的支持，共和党在明年的中期选举中就更难保住国会控制权。【原文：A prolonged feud between the pair could make it harder for Republicans to keep control of Congress in next year's midterm elections if it leads to a loss of Musk's campaign spending or erodes support for Trump in Silicon Valley.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-musk-bromance-descends-into-brawl-over-contracts-impeachment-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WG5S2RETRNLQXDB34YTIEOUH7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾和硕表示已进入评估美国工厂计划的最后阶段]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果和戴尔的主要供应商和硕联合公司（Pegatron）总裁兼首席执行官郑匡志周五告诉股东们，该公司对其美国工厂计划的评估已进入最后阶段，并将于本月或下月公布决定。【原文：Key Apple and Dell supplier Pegatron is in the final stage of evaluating its U.S. factory plan and is set to unveil a decision this month or next, its president and CEO Kuang-Chih Cheng told shareholders on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/pegatron-is-final-stage-evaluating-us-factory-plan-ceo-says-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBIVKSM6CZPMBIWBXM76XXBQCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:43:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>