<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:09:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:09:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，摩根大通考虑提供由客户持有的加密货币支持的贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周二援引知情人士的话报道称，摩根大通正在探索最早于明年提供由客户持有的加密货币（包括比特币和以太币）支持的贷款的计划。【原文：JPMorgan Chase is exploring plans to offer loans backed by clients' cryptocurrency holdings, including bitcoin and ethereum, as early as next year, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-considers-offering-loans-backed-by-clients-cryptocurrency-holdings-ft-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOE2BDI2SJJWHCGJYEMJHG5MXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:48:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价欧洲公司为坚挺欧元带来的痛苦做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLBGUZENTBKFLIRSSK6TP7JM2Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，印尼计划与美国公司签订价值 80 亿美元的炼油厂合同，同时达成关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的消息人士和路透社看到的经济部官方介绍，印尼主权财富基金 Danantara 计划与美国工程公司 KBR Inc 签订一份价值 80 亿美元的工程、采购和施工合同，以建造 17 座模块化炼油厂。【原文：Indonesian sovereign wealth fund Danantara plans to sign an $8 billion engineering, procurement and construction contract with U.S. engineering firm KBR Inc to build 17 modular refineries, according to two sources familiar with the matter and an official economic ministry presentation seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/indonesia-plans-8-bln-refineries-contract-with-us-firm-amid-tariffs-deal-sources-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MICIYHKA7NKDBFJ6QCEAESWDRQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本大选结果如何搅乱日本央行的政策路径]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本大选的结果可能会使央行陷入双重困境，因为大额支出的前景可能会使通胀率持续走高，而潜在的长期政治瘫痪和全球贸易战则为缓慢加息提供了令人信服的理由。【原文：Japan's election outcome may put the central bank in a double bind as prospects of big spending could keep inflation elevated while potentially prolonged political paralysis and a global trade war provide compelling reasons to go slow on rate hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/how-japans-election-outcome-muddles-bojs-policy-path-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLVVEGGGLRNQVH3JKB3WI5BEDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《洛杉矶时报》报道，《南方公园》主创人员与派拉蒙达成 15 亿美元的流媒体协议]]></title><description><![CDATA["据《洛杉矶时报》周一报道，以满嘴脏话的儿童为主角的动画喜剧《南方公园》已与派拉蒙公司达成了价值 15 亿美元的流媒体协议。【原文："South Park," the animated comedy featuring foul-mouthed children, has reached a $1.5 billion streaming deal with Paramount , the LA Times reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/south-park-creators-reach-15-billion-streaming-deal-with-paramount-la-times-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BICKJ4TNFJL23NFL6LWISP7H5E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Counterpoint 称中国第二季度智能手机出货量下降 2.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[Counterpoint Research 周二称，中国第二季度智能手机出货量同比下降 2.4%。【原文：Smartphone shipments in China were down 2.4% for the second quarter compared with a year ago, Counterpoint Research said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinas-q2-smartphone-shipments-down-24-says-counterpoint-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MFHUSTP65L6TMFZQUSST2B5NM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在韩国的 "苹果郡"，果农乞求不要成为美国贸易协议的牺牲品]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国青城郡种植的苹果以其美味而闻名。但果农们担心，他们的生活方式可能会受到大量廉价美国进口苹果的威胁。【原文：The apples grown in the South Korean county of Cheongsong are renowned for their flavour. But farmers worry that their way of life could be under threat from an influx of cheap U.S. imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-koreas-apple-county-farmers-beg-not-be-sacrificed-us-trade-deal-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYMMQZP4YJLNVF35PWQGKE6KNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:14:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市坚挺，投资者关注关税谈判和盈利情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[受华尔街在一系列企业财报公布前创下收盘纪录新高的提振，亚洲股市周二在四年最高点附近保持了阵地，同时投资者也在评估美国与其贸易伙伴之间的关税谈判。【原文：Asian share markets held their ground near a four-year peak on Tuesday, buoyed by Wall Street's closing record high ahead of a slate of corporate earnings while investors took stock of tariff negotiations between the U.S. and its trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDUBKH7LSNIRFM2SGP7JELBRXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行警惕过快降息，谨慎等待更多数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社悉尼7月22日电）澳大利亚央行判断，在四次会议内第三次降息不符合其谨慎渐进的宽松战略，这也是澳大利亚央行本月持稳令市场震惊的原因。【原文：SYDNEY, July 22 (Reuters) - Australia's central bank judged lowering interest rates for a third time within four meetings was not consistent with its strategy of easing in a cautious and gradual manner, a reason that it shocked markets by holding steady this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-wary-cutting-rates-too-quickly-prudent-await-more-data-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOIBZ3YFRRJ2HI73EHURGIXRXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战加剧燃料需求担忧，石油走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国和欧盟这两个主要原油消费国之间正在酝酿的贸易战会降低经济活动，从而抑制燃料需求的增长，投资者情绪低落，周二油价下跌。【原文：Oil prices edged down on Tuesday as concerns the brewing trade war between major crude consumers the U.S. and the European Union will curb fuel demand growth by lowering economic activity weighed on investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-edges-lower-trade-war-concerns-increase-worries-about-fuel-demand-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTVVQUMQNFKBZGXV45KPL6FOKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待关税进一步明朗，美元举棋不定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元在本周初短暂下跌后，周二在狭窄区间内交投，因为在8月1日各国与美国达成协议或面临高额关税的最后期限到来之前，投资者在关注贸易谈判是否取得进展。【原文：The dollar traded in a tight range on Tuesday after a brief fall at the start of the week, as investors watched out for any progress on trade talks ahead of an August 1 deadline for countries to strike deals with the U.S. or face steep tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-indecisive-investors-await-more-tariff-clarity-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLB5X3NHJVJQLIDZS3NXP34E3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特呼吁深化美国银行监管改革，废除双重资本要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一呼吁对他所称的过时的金融监管体系进行更深层次的改革，并表示监管机构应考虑废除拜登时代关于银行双重资本要求结构的 "有缺陷 "的建议。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Monday called for deeper reforms of what he called an antiquated financial regulatory system and said regulators should consider scrapping a "flawed," Biden-era proposal for a dual capital requirement structure for banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bessent-calls-deeper-us-bank-regulatory-reforms-scrapping-dual-capital-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNEC5WPMBBPPPPMNI5EIXUZIPQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:54:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，软银和 OpenAI 的星际之门计划在年底前建立小型数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周一报道，"星际之门"（Stargate）是由 ChatGPT 的创建者 OpenAI、软银（SoftBank）和甲骨文（Oracle）共同发起的一项耗资数十亿美元的计划，旨在推动美国的人工智能发展。【原文：Stargate, a multi-billion-dollar effort by ChatGPT's creator OpenAI, SoftBank and Oracle to supercharge the U.S.' AI ambitions is now setting the more modest goal of building a small data center by the end of the year, likely in Ohio, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/softbank-openais-stargate-aims-building-small-data-center-by-year-end-wsj-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSLWNRXFYZIL3JB4ITZVRRNPZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:15:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称美联储需要详尽审查非货币政策操作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一呼吁美联储对其非货币政策操作进行详尽审查，以确保 "任务蠕变 "不会危及其核心货币政策任务的独立性。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Monday called on the Federal Reserve to conduct an exhaustive review of its non-monetary policy operations to ensure that "mission creep" does not jeopardize the independence of its core monetary policy mission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bessent-says-fed-needs-exhaustive-review-non-monetary-policy-operations-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VN6M6C5Q5RNMBD56JOOBSPJPSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[激进分子 Elliott 增持 Equinix 股份，并与公司举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉此事的人士周一表示，激进投资者埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）对数据中心运营商 Equinix 进行了大量投资，并在过去几周增持了股份，此前该公司股价在上个月暴跌。【原文：Activist investor Elliott Investment Management has a large investment in data center operator Equinix and has increased its stake in the last weeks, a person familiar with the matter said on Monday, after the company's stock price tumbled last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/activist-elliott-grows-stake-equinix-holds-talks-with-company-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZ5L756UOVK33LGC6M7A4TQ2LM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌和 OpenAI 的人工智能模型在全球数学竞赛中赢得里程碑式的金牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司（Google）和 OpenAI 公司表示，它们的人工智能模型在全球数学竞赛中获得了金奖，这标志着在建立可与人类智能相媲美的强大系统的竞赛中，数学能力取得了突破性进展。【原文：Alphabet's Google and OpenAI said their artificial-intelligence models won gold medals at a global mathematics competition, signaling a breakthrough in math capabilities in the race to build powerful systems that can rival human intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/google-openais-ai-models-win-milestone-gold-at-global-math-competition-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GPZKEYQANLFDOZXL4TXFRWRKI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，BNSF 铁路公司选择高盛收购铁路公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉此事的消息人士周一告诉路透社，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的 BNSF Railway 正在与高盛（Goldman Sachs）合作，探讨收购竞争对手的铁路公司。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway-owned BNSF Railway is working with Goldman Sachs to explore the takeover of a rival railroad, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/bnsf-railway-taps-goldman-sachs-railroad-acquisition-sources-say-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOXS4B4WAFMU3GIUTP2OBYZLGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:56:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球音乐秘密申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）周一披露，该公司已秘密申请在美国首次公开募股，投资者对首次公开募股的乐观情绪与日俱增。【原文：Universal Music Group disclosed on Monday it had confidentially filed for a U.S. initial public offering, amid growing investor optimism for IPOs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/universal-music-confidentially-files-us-ipo-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6OOJGFFMVJKXKRMJHRNF7NFGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西将就美国关税问题调查外汇内幕交易嫌疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一的一份法庭文件，巴西最高法院法官亚历山大-德-莫赖斯（Alexandre de Moraes）授权对美国7月宣布对所有巴西进口商品征收50%关税之前涉嫌使用外汇交易特权信息一事进行调查。【原文：Brazil's Supreme Court Justice Alexandre de Moraes authorized an investigation into the alleged use of privileged information on foreign exchange transactions before the announcement of the 50% U.S. tariff on all Brazilian imports in July, according to a Monday court filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/brazil-investigate-suspected-fx-insider-trading-us-tariffs-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CFJWQRU4FL4FD5VI2HJNU4J2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:42:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）第二季度结束时积压订单达 297 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周一公布的一份证券文件显示，该公司第二季度的确定订单积压额为297亿美元，比去年同期增长了40%。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer said on Monday its firm order backlog ended the second quarter at $29.7 billion, up 40% from a year earlier, according to a securities filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazil-planemaker-embraer-ends-q2-with-backlog-297-billion-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNT3KMUOZVNPLCZBD2LKF7OCXA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医药关税威胁迫在眉睫，阿斯利康公布 500 亿美元美国投资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康公司周一表示，计划到2030年斥资500亿美元扩大在美国的生产和研究能力，这是一家制药公司为应对唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税政策而进行的最新一笔巨额投资。【原文：AstraZeneca plans to spend $50 billion to expand manufacturing and research capabilities in the U.S. by 2030, it said on Monday, the latest big investment by a pharmaceutical company reacting to President Donald Trump's tariff policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/astrazeneca-unveils-50-billion-us-investment-pharma-tariff-threat-looms-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYQL7M64WVIDDO6EFYDLO2GHIY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[W.W. R. Berkley 第二季度利润因承保强劲而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[商业保险公司 W. R. Berkley 周一公布，受强劲的投资收益和稳定的承保业绩提振，第二季度利润有所增长。【原文：Commercial insurer W. R. Berkley reported a rise in second-quarter profit on Monday, boosted by robust investment gains and steady underwriting performance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/w-r-berkley-second-quarter-profit-rises-strong-underwriting-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRQFYP5GVFKRTKN66OCLND2JVU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[恩智浦第二季度收入下降 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商恩智浦半导体（NXP Semiconductors）周一公布，第二季度营收下降 6%，主要原因是通信和基础设施市场疲软。【原文：Chipmaker NXP Semiconductors posted a 6% drop in second-quarter revenue on Monday, led by weakness in communications and infrastructure segment amid broader market softness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nxp-second-quarter-revenue-falls-6-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KK4XOF2M2NJX3C4MC5NNZMIPLU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:10:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：股市乐观情绪难消]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTUTMWY27VMVZFJEIGUOQ22BYU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉与挑战路易斯安那州直销禁令的诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周一就针对路易斯安那州及多家汽车经销商和贸易团体的诉讼达成和解，特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的电动汽车公司在诉讼中对该州自 2017 年以来禁止直接向消费者销售汽车的禁令提出质疑。【原文：Tesla on Monday settled a lawsuit against Louisiana and various auto dealerships and trade groups, in which CEO Elon Musk's electric car company challenged the state's ban since 2017 on direct vehicle sales to consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tesla-settles-lawsuit-challenging-louisiana-direct-sales-ban-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBTHAKHYSRMGXATNI5G56ONDXI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[税务软件公司 Avalara 秘密申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[税务软件公司 Avalara 周一披露，该公司已秘密申请在美国首次公开发行股票，投资者对新股上市的乐观情绪与日俱增。【原文：Tax software company Avalara disclosed on Monday it had confidentially filed for a U.S. initial public offering, as investor optimism for new listings grows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tax-software-company-avalara-confidentially-files-us-ipo-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGLTLBGR3BMLZAXSBDPE6CBX34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织称二号官员戈皮纳特将于 8 月底离职，返回哈佛大学工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）周一发表声明称，该组织二号官员吉塔-戈皮纳特（Gita Gopinath）将于 8 月底离职，返回哈佛大学工作。【原文：Gita Gopinath, the No. 2 official at the International Monetary Fund, will leave her post at the end of August to return to Harvard University, the IMF said in a statement on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imf-says-no-2-official-gopinath-leaving-end-august-return-harvard-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MII4LYU3JBPQ7GZBGSVQCIAB34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府要求美国上诉法院阻止恢复联邦贸易委员会委员斯劳特职务的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周一要求美国上诉法院阻止一项法院命令，该命令允许民主党的美国联邦贸易委员会委员丽贝卡-斯劳特（Rebecca Slaughter）恢复在该机构的职务，尽管白宫试图解除她的职务。【原文：President Donald Trump’s administration on Monday asked a U.S. appeals court to block a court order that allowed Democratic U.S. Federal Trade Commissioner Rebecca Slaughter to resume her role at the agency, despite the White House’s effort to remove her from office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-administration-asks-us-appeals-court-block-order-reinstating-ftc-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UF3JDQTK75NY7MOGKLVCFECYXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:19:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士称，美国零售巨头好市多将在印度建立全球能力中心，雇佣 1000 名员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉该计划的人士告诉路透社，美国零售商好市多批发公司（Costco Wholesale Corp）将在印度海德拉巴开设其首个全球能力中心（GCC）。【原文：U.S. retailer Costco Wholesale Corp will open its first global capability centre (GCC) in India in Hyderabad, two people familiar with the plans told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-retail-giant-costco-set-up-global-capability-centre-india-employ-1000-people-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNHGIKMRH5N75CONNJ6SCVVIH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立法者希望美国科技公司首席执行官解决对海底电缆的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名共和党众议员周一询问 Alphabet、Facebook 母公司 Meta、亚马逊公司和微软公司的首席执行官，这些科技公司是否采取了足够的保障措施，以应对中国和俄罗斯对海底通信电缆日益增长的担忧。【原文：Three Republican House lawmakers on Monday asked the CEOs of Alphabet , Facebook-parent Meta , Amazon.com and Microsoft if the tech firms have adopted adequate safeguards to address growing concerns about China and Russia on submarine communications cables.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/lawmakers-want-us-tech-ceos-address-concerns-about-submarine-cables-2025-07-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVOQ2YSPJRLMTPXITK2PVXEMEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:56:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>