<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:43:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:43:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[丰田将全年营业利润预期下调 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周四将全年营业利润预期下调了 16%，原因是日元升值和美国提高进口关税对其财务业绩造成了影响。【原文：Toyota Motor cut its full-year operating profit forecast by 16% on Thursday as an appreciating yen and higher U.S. import tariffs weighed on its financial results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-cuts-full-year-operating-profit-estimate-by-16-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMY3BVF7WVKSJBUMMUUQ3AUOGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安联第二季度利润好于预期并确认目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国安联集团（Allianz）周四公布第二季度净利润增长 13%，好于预期，并确认了全年目标。【原文：Germany's Allianz on Thursday posted a better-than-expected 13% rise in second-quarter net profit and confirmed its target for the full year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/allianz-posts-better-than-expected-q2-profit-confirms-target-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAYR374WLRPKZNM3T473KBJNNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:17:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国电信第二季度利润达到预期，并上调了指导目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国电信公司周四公布的第二季度核心利润符合分析师预期，称德国和美国的业绩持续增长，并上调了全年利润指导。【原文：Deutsche Telekom reported second quarter core profit in line with analyst expectations on Thursday, citing continued growth in both Germany and the U.S., and edged up its full-year profit guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/deutsche-telekom-meets-q2-profit-expectations-lifts-guidance-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPNALWXUA5KADMC7D7BDZKTCR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:13:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元疲软拖累西门子第三季度业绩符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子周四公布的最新季度工业利润符合预期，尽管美元走软对这家德国工程集团的业绩造成了影响。【原文：Siemens reported industrial profit in line with forecasts for its latest quarter on Thursday, although the weakening dollar weighed on the German engineering group's figures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/siemens-reports-q3-results-line-with-forecasts-weak-dollar-weighs-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REJO3FCDQVKUHLUSXCLWZPACXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道卢比奥命令美国外交官针对欧洲科技法开展游说活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份内部外交电报显示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府已指示美国驻欧洲外交官开展游说活动，以反对欧盟的《数字服务法案》（Digital Services Act）。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration has instructed U.S. diplomats in Europe to launch a lobbying campaign to build an opposition to the European Union's Digital Services Act, which Washington says stifles free speech and imposes costs on U.S. tech companies, an internal diplomatic cable seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/rubio-orders-us-diplomats-launch-lobbying-blitz-against-europes-tech-law-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SMSAKEULZKOVI5YHKIDNRURKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价英国央行将降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEOUMMEM2JL5DKURJMEBOY2TOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在澳大利亚的住房争夺战中，政治转变选择了新手而非新移民]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚的经济适用房计划已在悉尼富人区莫斯曼（Mosman）展开，新的规划法对该地区长期以来的发展阻力提出了挑战。【原文：Australia's affordable housing push has arrived in the wealthy Sydney suburb of Mosman, where new planning laws now challenge longstanding resistance to development in the leafy area known for mansions and sweeping harbour views.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-housing-war-political-shift-picks-newbies-over-nimbys-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGKYKKE3WVJK3NERBMDYAZVSLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国经济担忧和关税紧张局势影响，日本投资者抛售外国股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 8 月 2 日的一周内，由于对美国经济前景和一系列新的贸易关税持谨慎态度，主要市场出现回落，日本投资者大幅抛售外国股票。【原文：Japanese investors significantly sold foreign stocks in the week to August 2 as major markets retreated on caution over U.S. economic outlook and a new set of trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japanese-investors-ditch-foreign-stocks-us-economic-concerns-tariff-tensions-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSG62G53BVJP3EVNGWW6ZU4MYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提高关税税率打击美国主要贸易伙伴的商品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四开始对数十个贸易伙伴征收10%至50%的较高关税，这是对他在不大规模破坏全球供应链、不提高通胀率和不遭到贸易伙伴强烈报复的情况下缩小美国贸易赤字的战略的考验。【原文：President Donald Trump's higher tariff rates of 10% to 50% on dozens of trading partners kicked in on Thursday, testing his strategy for shrinking U.S. trade deficits without massive disruptions to global supply chains, higher inflation and stiff retaliation from trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trumps-higher-tariff-rates-hit-goods-major-us-trading-partners-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JOXEMOCTFO6VODYKP5BNDBMWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商担心 "贴纸冲击"，在涨价问题上与品牌商发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[在关税带来的成本上升和消费者勒紧裤腰带的双重压力下，大型零售商正与妮维雅制造商拜尔斯道夫和啤酒制造商喜力等消费品牌的生产商发生冲突，因为他们希望避免可能损害销售的价格冲击。【原文：Caught between rising costs from tariffs and belt-tightening consumers, big retailers are clashing with the producers of consumer brands such as Nivea-maker Beiersdorf and brewer Heineken , as they look to avoid sticker shock that could hurt sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/wary-sticker-shock-retailers-clash-with-brands-price-hikes-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4MOW46G7NJ4FIAQKCNH2ZJJPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国稀土出口在上月达到峰值后于 7 月下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的海关数据显示，中国的稀土出口在一个月前创下纪录后，7月份下滑了23%，尽管初步数据还不完整，无法就中国政府加快发货的承诺得出肯定的结论。【原文：Rare earth exports from China slumped 23% in July after hitting a record a month earlier, customs data showed on Thursday, although the preliminary data is too incomplete to draw firm conclusions about Beijing's commitment to speed up shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-rare-earth-exports-slid-july-after-hitting-peak-prior-month-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPMVVJNI7NNC3EWMGEUWVCJEBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国7月出口高于预期，急于在特朗普关税最后期限前完成任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 7 月份的出口超过了预期，因为制造商充分利用了北京和华盛顿之间脆弱的关税休战协议，在本月晚些时候迫在眉睫的最后期限到来之前发货。【原文：China's exports beat forecasts in July, as manufacturers made the most of a fragile tariff truce between Beijing and Washington to ship goods ahead of a looming deadline later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-july-exports-top-forecasts-amid-rush-meet-trump-tariff-deadline-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWW5P6WWAZLCZJAL7HDLXAJ474</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:33:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼将年度利润预期上调 4%，理由是贸易战影响较小]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼公司周四将全年营业利润预期上调 4%，至 1.33 万亿日元（约合 90.1 亿美元），理由是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战影响减弱。【原文：Sony raised its full-year operating profit forecast on Thursday by 4% to 1.33 trillion yen ($9.01 billion), citing a diminished impact from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sony-hikes-annual-profit-forecast-by-4-citing-smaller-trade-war-impact-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBK5Q3ZO7RMJ5FSGBGDUPL4PUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市攀升，美元受美联储宽松政策押注影响下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲股市上涨，日本股市创下历史新高，原因是华尔街科技股领涨、盈利向好以及对美国降息的预期不断增强，这些因素提振了市场情绪。【原文：Asian equities rose on Thursday, with Japanese shares hitting a record high, as tech-led gains on Wall Street, upbeat earnings and growing expectations for U.S. rate cuts boosted sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDCCOJVWHZMY3AVGPVML6U23MQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 AMP 半年盈利改善，但股价受利润下滑拖累]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚货币基金管理公司 AMP 公布了较高的半年收益，理由是其财富平台的净现金流强劲以及银行部门的利润率有所改善，但低于市场预期，导致其股价下跌。【原文：Australian money manager AMP posted higher half-year earnings, citing strong net cashflows in its wealth platform and margin improvement in its banking unit, but fell short of market expectations, which sent its shares lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-amp-half-year-earnings-improve-shares-drag-profit-miss-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5ZUWY6EOJPZDHDGBDPFNCTSGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因美国需求强劲而上涨，但制裁的不确定性依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四上涨，暂停了连续五天的跌势，原因是有迹象表明全球最大的石油用户美国的需求稳定，尽管美俄就乌克兰战争举行会谈的前景缓解了对进一步制裁导致供应中断的担忧。【原文：Oil prices rose on Thursday, pausing a five-day losing streak, on signs of steady demand in the U.S., the world's biggest oil user, though the prospect of U.S.-Russian talks on the Ukraine war eased concerns of supply disruptions from further sanctions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-us-demand-strength-though-sanctions-uncertainty-remains-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZE3XKIURAVKAFALIFU6HX6YY6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 01:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因美国经济忧虑和美联储任命而持跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美元兑主要货币继续走低，原因是美联储降息的预期不断升温，而且人们担心党派纷争会逐渐渗入美国的主要机构。【原文：The dollar remained lower against major peers on Thursday, as expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts grew and concerns swirled about partisanship creeping into key U.S. institutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-holds-losses-us-economy-concerns-fed-appointments-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAKDG2TOAVLP5JZ76RV7ZCHZUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 01:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普希望在东京和伦敦有更多美国人接机。这可能很难实现]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普说得没错，日本和欧洲很少购买美国制造的汽车，但这与贸易壁垒关系不大。从东京到伦敦，许多消费者都认为底特律生产的汽车太大、太耗油。【原文：Donald Trump is right that Japan and Europe buy few American-made cars - but it has little to do with trade barriers. From Tokyo to London, many consumers see Detroit's offerings as simply too big and too gas-guzzling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-wants-more-american-pick-ups-tokyo-london-that-may-be-hard-sell-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">536FGUWPRBO3XAA2HZU43LQPHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 01:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税影响，韩国芯片制造商 SK 海力士股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示美国将对芯片征收约100%的关税后，韩国芯片制造商SK海力士的股价在周四早盘交易中下跌了3.1%。【原文：Shares in South Korean chipmaker SK Hynix fell 3.1% in early Thursday trade, after President Donald Trump said the U.S. will impose a tariff of about 100% on chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/shares-south-korean-chipmaker-sk-hynix-tumble-us-tariffs-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEV6S5ARVRO5PAPVYTDMXNAQEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:46:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国贸易特使称三星和 SK 海力士不会被美国征收 100% 的芯片关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国最高贸易特使杨汉九（Yeo Han-koo）周四表示，芯片制造商三星电子（Samsung Electronics）和SK海力士（SK Hynix）不会被美国征收100%的芯片关税。【原文：South Korea's top trade envoy Yeo Han-koo said on Thursday that chipmakers Samsung Electronics and SK Hynix will not be subject to 100% U.S. tariffs on chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-trade-envoy-says-samsung-sk-hynix-will-not-be-subject-100-us-tariffs-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HK6RNH2TH5I47I6OC3XH2PPPKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局下令美联航航班在多个机场停飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周三表示，美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）的航班在美国多个机场停飞，而该公司自己也表示，其团队正在努力尽快解决技术故障问题。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday it issued a ground stop for United Airlines flights at several U.S. airports while the company itself said its teams were working to resolve a tech outage as soon as possible.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-faa-issues-ground-stop-united-airlines-flights-several-airports-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MU26NI3A2ZMYVALBGYJVDCDHIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:28:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银的人工智能投资热潮将成为第一季度财报的焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，日本软银集团（SoftBank Group）将公布财报，其对人工智能公司的巨额投资将成为焦点。【原文：When Japan's SoftBank Group reports earnings on Thursday, its mammoth investments in artificial intelligence companies are set to take the spotlight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbanks-ai-investment-spree-be-focus-q1-earnings-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFXJRUS4AFNKHMBHDC4O6KVVOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本敦促美国尽快实施汽车关税削减措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周四表示，日本最高贸易谈判代表赤泽亮世要求美国迅速执行双边贸易协议中达成的措施，包括降低汽车和汽车零部件关税。【原文：Japan's top trade negotiator Ryosei Akazawa requested that the U.S. swiftly implement measures agreed upon in a bilateral trade deal, including lowering automobile and auto parts tariffs, Japan's government said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-urges-us-swiftly-implement-auto-tariff-cut-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7AHXK4Y2KNOZ5L3EA2HNFCNRTE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示派拉蒙联席首席执行官罗宾斯将卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周三看到的一份备忘录，帮助派拉蒙+流媒体服务发展壮大的布莱恩-罗宾斯（Brian Robbins）在派拉蒙全球与 Skydance Media 合并完成后，将辞去派拉蒙全球联席首席执行官一职。【原文：Brian Robbins, who helped grow the Paramount+ streaming service, is stepping down as Paramount Global's co-CEO, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Wednesday, following the completion of its merger with Skydance Media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/paramounts-co-ceo-robbins-step-down-memo-shows-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXTHZ7LR5JOA7HR4YG6NKJXG5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大都会人寿的利润因承保利润率下降而下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[大都会人寿周三公布的第二季度调整后利润下降了 16%，原因是保费下降抵消了投资收益增加带来的收益。【原文：MetLife posted a 16% fall in second-quarter adjusted profit on Wednesday, as weaker premiums offset gains from higher investment income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/metlifes-profit-falls-less-favorable-underwriting-margins-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AZ5OTNASJOQRNR3NICTY4TBAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:50:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡星展银行第二季度净利润增长 1%，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡最大的银行星展集团周四公布，由于总收入增加，第二季度净利润同比增长 1%。【原文：DBS Group , Singapore's biggest bank, on Thursday posted a 1% rise in net profit in the second quarter from a year earlier on the back of higher total income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/singapores-bank-dbs-second-quarter-net-profit-rises-1-beats-forecast-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEWXL6KI5VOZRBBHJBG6VUYWTY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[能源转让公司称，美国限制乙烷供应将增加与中国签订合同的难度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国乙烷出口商Energy Transfer公司周三表示，尽管美国最近取消了对中国出口乙烷的限制，但这可能会增加与中国公司签订合同的难度。【原文：Recent U.S. restrictions on ethane exports to China will likely make it more difficult to contract with Chinese companies, even though they have already been lifted, U.S. exporter Energy Transfer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-ethane-curbs-will-make-contracting-china-harder-energy-transfer-says-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBUW5S5F6VIV3P3RI5NHMCFVYU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称可能就俄罗斯石油对中国征收更多关税，类似于对印度征税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三表示，他可能会宣布对中国进一步征收关税，类似于早些时候因印度购买俄罗斯石油而宣布对印度征收25%关税的做法，这取决于事态的发展。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday said he could announce further tariffs on China similar to the 25% duties announced earlier on India over its purchases of Russian oil, depending on what happens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-says-he-could-impose-more-tariffs-china-similar-india-duties-over-russian-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQDJA7K7IRJYFLVBUY5WSQR55I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司称将与三星合作，从德州工厂获得新芯片技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周三表示，它正与三星电子在后者位于得克萨斯州的芯片生产厂合作，"推出一种创新的芯片制造新技术"。【原文：Apple said on Wednesday it is working with Samsung Electronics at the latter's chip production plant in Texas to "to launch an innovative new technology for making chips."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-says-it-is-partnering-with-samsung-new-chip-technology-texas-plant-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOLFUOKRGRKY3PHKVGRSYVHPUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:23:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[竞争加剧，通用汽车与现代汽车签署首份联合开发五款汽车的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司和现代汽车公司周三宣布，双方首次达成了联合开发五款汽车的协议。【原文：General Motors and Hyundai Motor announced on Wednesday their first agreement to jointly develop five vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/general-motors-hyundai-ink-first-joint-deal-develop-five-vehicles-amid-rising-2025-08-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7XC75QRQZPCDIBQBGEUZ32474</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 22:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>