<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:04:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:04:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普媒体敦促美国监管机构调查其股票空头头寸]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）拥有多数股权的媒体公司特朗普媒体与科技集团（Trump Media & Technology Group）周四表示，已要求美国证券交易委员会（SEC）调查其股票最近的空头头寸。【原文：The media company majority owned by President Donald Trump, Trump Media & Technology Group , said on Thursday it had asked the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to investigate a recent short position in its stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-media-presses-us-regulator-investigate-short-positions-its-stocks-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UQ42FPYF5KQ5IKQVNVXVQKJT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 季度业绩超出华尔街目标，收入前景乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，Netflix 的季度业绩超出华尔街预期，并提出了乐观的收入展望，在唐纳德-特朗普总统反复无常的关税计划所带来的经济不确定性中显示出信心。【原文：Netflix exceeded Wall Street expectations for quarterly results and offered a bullish revenue outlook on Thursday, signaling confidence amid the economic uncertainty surrounding President Donald Trump's erratic tariff plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-quarterly-results-beat-wall-st-targets-revenue-outlook-upbeat-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNMUDQNSTVM5LISXBEVME3JONQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 另类投资部门 BXMA 第一季度报告增长 2.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为全球最大的对冲基金投资者，黑石集团的多元资产投资部门 BXMA 在第一季度获得了 2.3% 的扣除费用后回报率，远远超过 HFRX 全球对冲基金指数 0.53% 的回报率。【原文：Blackstone Group's multi-asset investing BXMA unit, the world's largest investor in hedge funds, posted a 2.3% return after fees in the first quarter, handily outpacing the HFRX Global Hedge Fund Index 0.53% return.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstones-alternatives-unit-bxma-reports-23-gain-q1-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6WGLA4SC5L45FIKCT2RGMM7A4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：对谷歌非法广告技术垄断的裁决意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法官裁定谷歌在广告技术领域存在非法垄断，这为美国检察官寻求与谷歌分手埋下了伏笔。以下是此案涉及的内容以及谷歌所有者 Alphabet 今后将面临的问题。【原文：A U.S. judge's ruling that Google has illegal monopolies in ad technology sets up the possibility of U.S. prosecutors seeking a breakup. Here's what the case involves and what Google owner Alphabet faces from here.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/what-does-ruling-googles-illegal-ad-tech-monopoly-mean-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RENT7HIMCVNNVDX6TC4YI7GEZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:29:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Coindesk 报道，Kraken 在首次公开募股前裁员数百人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Coindesk 周四报道，加密货币交易所 Kraken 在过去几个月中已在其所有业务领域裁员数百人，以便在计划上市前精简业务。【原文：Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken has laid off hundreds of employees in the past several months across all areas of its business to streamline its operations ahead of its planned IPO, Coindesk reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kraken-lays-off-hundreds-ahead-ipo-coindesk-reports-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQH6TOHBGRJM7N222AN6TFZZOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国务院称，美国希望刚果矿产交易有私营部门合作伙伴的参与]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院发言人塔米-布鲁斯（Tammy Bruce）周四表示，美国预计正在与刚果民主共和国（DRC）谈判的矿产交易将涉及一系列私营部门合作伙伴。【原文：The United States expects a minerals deal being negotiated with the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC) will involve a range of private sector partners, State Department spokesperson Tammy Bruce said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-expects-congo-minerals-deal-involve-private-sector-partners-state-dept-says-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVZKSKN76ZNRRKKREWRTDIYABQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》称，特朗普曾与被视为可能继任者的沃什讨论过解雇美联储主席鲍威尔的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，唐纳德-特朗普总统已私下讨论解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔数月之久，并与前美联储理事凯文-沃什（Kevin Warsh）谈论过此事，包括随后选择沃什接替鲍威尔的可能性。【原文：President Donald Trump has privately discussed firing Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell for months and talked about it with former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, including the possibility of then selecting Warsh as Powell's replacement, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-has-discussed-firing-feds-powell-with-warsh-eyed-possibe-successor-wsj-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQAFKWZTIJLPJPZIPXEJM3BDQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌从宿舍到互联网霸主的历程]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官裁定，谷歌非法垄断了数字广告市场，为这个近 27 年前从斯坦福大学宿舍起家的互联网帝国的解体铺平了道路。【原文：A U.S. judge has ruled that Google illegally monopolized digital advertising markets, paving the way for a break up of the internet empire that was started out of a Stanford University dormitory nearly 27 years ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/googles-journey-dorm-internet-dominance-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJ276PUN3JKLVEBWAW2AY2QSHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GTCR 将从 Worldpay 242.5 亿美元的出售中获得丰厚的意外之财]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周四表示，私募股权公司 GTCR 向 Global Payments 出售其在支付处理商 Worldpay 55% 的股份后，有望获得约两倍于其投资的回报。【原文：Private equity firm GTCR is poised to garner a return of about two times its investment in Worldpay, after the sale of its 55% stake in the payments processor to Global Payments, people familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/gtcr-set-reap-handsome-windfall-worldpays-2425-billion-sale-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7A36X66M3VNRXH3PKMTQX4XPRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令叫停纽约风电项目，令近海产业目瞪口呆，并威胁到其他项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三晚些时候，特朗普政府决定叫停 Equinor 在纽约海岸的 Empire Wind 1 号风电场的建设，这在海上风电行业引起了震动，使人们担心代表着数十亿投资的已获完全许可的开发项目并不安全。【原文：The Trump administration's decision to halt construction of Equinor's Empire Wind 1 farm off the coast of New York late on Wednesday sent shockwaves through the offshore wind industry, raising concerns that fully-permitted developments representing billions in investment aren't safe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-order-halt-ny-wind-project-stuns-offshore-industry-threatens-other-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXHESVE2YZKXJFR7R77XYHRH6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对美国法官裁定谷歌非法垄断广告技术的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名法官周四裁定，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌非法主导了两个在线广告技术市场，这对这家科技巨头造成了又一次打击，并为美国反垄断检察官寻求拆分其广告产品铺平了道路。【原文：Alphabet's Google illegally dominates two markets for online advertising technology, a judge ruled on Thursday, dealing another blow to the tech giant and paving the way for U.S. antitrust prosecutors to seek a breakup of its advertising products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/reaction-us-judge-ruling-that-google-holds-illegal-monopolies-ad-tech-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5ALGLDOJBK6NMUSTAXN5UCYYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称乌克兰谈判后将于下周四签署矿产协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美国将于下周四签署一项新的矿产协议，这显然是指与乌克兰的谈判。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday that the U.S. would sign a new minerals deal next Thursday, in an apparent reference to talks with Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-minerals-deal-be-signed-next-thursday-after-ukraine-talks-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYRVKYAZ4VN6JAXKT7VS2HMYC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗将三个月黄金目标价格上调至每盎司 3,500 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗研究公司（Citi Research）周四在一份报告中称，在关税风险和市场疲软的背景下，中国保险商的新一轮买盘和避险资金的流入将未来三个月的黄金价格目标从每盎司3200美元上调至3500美元。【原文：Citi Research raised its gold price target for the next three months to $3,500 per ounce from $3,200, led by fresh buying from Chinese insurers and safe-haven flows amid tariff risks and market weakness, it said in a note on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/citi-raises-three-month-gold-price-target-3500-per-ounce-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISNHBC6OVBIF7AEFP4EDF2CWDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称，如果他要求美联储主席鲍威尔离职，鲍威尔就会离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，他相信如果特朗普要求美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔离职，他就会离职。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday he believes Federal Reserve chairman Jerome Powell will leave his job if Trump asks him to do so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-fed-chair-powell-will-leave-if-he-asks-him-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAID6JJVWFPZNAQX3UAKIJF2DQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》报道，苹果公司首席执行官与卢特尼克就关税对 iPhone 价格的影响进行了交谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周四援引两位熟悉电话内容的人士的话报道，苹果公司首席执行官蒂姆-库克（Tim Cook）上周与美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策对 iPhone 价格的潜在影响进行了交谈。【原文：Apple CEO Tim Cook spoke with U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick last week about the potential impact of President Donald Trump's tariffs on iPhone prices, the Washington Post reported on Thursday, citing two people familiar with the phone call.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-ceo-spoke-with-lutnick-about-tariffs-impact-iphone-prices-washington-post-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKWNCQPPTNJ5FJ3BLTO5UBNSAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:43:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被特朗普排除在关税之外后，黄金开始从美国返回瑞士]]></title><description><![CDATA[官方数据显示，为防范美国可能对进口金条征收广泛关税，自12月以来，交易商们一直将黄金运往纽约。【原文：Gold, which traders have been flying to New York since December as a precaution against the possibility of broad U.S. tariffs hitting bullion imports, is being shipped back to Switzerland, where it came from, official data shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-starts-coming-back-switzerland-us-after-exclusion-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJZ7TWCUOBOBNJ25GKA3VONYAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普我们将与中国达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，他希望与中国达成一项贸易协议，但他没有提供具体细节，也没有表明在两个超级大国明显陷入僵局的情况下将如何展开谈判。【原文：President Donald Trump on Thursday said he expects to make a trade deal with China, though he offered no specifics or indications of how talks would get underway with the two superpowers at an apparent impasse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-we-will-have-trade-deal-with-china-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ45R262ORKUNDMKU3NPM2XOCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MP 材料公司因关税问题停止运往中国的稀土货物]]></title><description><![CDATA[MP Materials 公司周四表示，已停止向中国运输稀土精矿，以应对报复性关税和出口管制，该公司股价在午后交易中下跌了 6.3%。【原文：MP Materials said on Thursday it had stopped shipping rare earth concentrate to China, in response to retaliatory tariffs and export controls, sending its shares down 6.3% in afternoon trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/mp-materials-stops-china-bound-rare-earth-shipments-over-tariffs-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WL4BJNUZCBKDJLAPMPDTRG5BCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:29:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商四周来首次增加油气钻机]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周四在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周增加了石油和天然气钻机，这是四周以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week added oil and natural gas rigs for the first time in four weeks, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-add-oil-gas-rigs-first-time-four-weeks-baker-hughes-says-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWBZ4DBIRFOYXCQUSLFGGXAW24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:12:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社：美国财政部正与联邦机构商谈放松银行监管事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）正在与联邦和其他银行机构举行非公开会议，这是他为简化监督和协调放松监管计划而扩大努力的一部分。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent is hosting private meetings with federal and other bank agencies as a part of his expanded effort to streamline oversight and coordinate plans to ease regulation, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-treasury-talks-with-federal-agencies-ease-bank-oversight-bloomberg-news-says-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HP3OHRYFVZMBVKSNJLQHFVLMBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司向经销商下调柴油价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国营石油公司（Petrobras）在周四的一份声明中说，从周五开始，该公司将把出售给经销商的柴油价格平均每升降低 0.12 雷亚尔（0.0205 美元）。【原文：Brazilian state-run oil company Petrobras will reduce the price of diesel sold to distributors by an average 0.12 real ($0.0205) per liter starting on Friday, it said in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazils-petrobras-cuts-diesel-prices-distributors-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34JIN5W6FBNT7BD4J22Q2B2T3E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德再次获准持有大型公用事业股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦能源监管机构周四再次批准贝莱德持有公用事业公司的主要股份，这是该全球顶级资产管理公司在人们对其影响力过大的担忧中取得的胜利。【原文：U.S. federal energy regulators on Thursday gave BlackRock renewed permission to own major stakes of public utility companies, a win for the world's top asset manager over concerns that it wields too much influence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-wins-renewed-permission-own-big-utility-stakes-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4LLZJHZTJPM3AATPAXS72ELO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税给前景蒙上阴影，美国油田服务公司为盈利做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的财报很可能会让人们一窥全球三大油田服务公司如何应对美国关税反复无常以及近期油价下滑所带来的不确定性。【原文：Results next week will likely provide a peek into how the world's top three oilfield services companies are navigating the uncertainty fueled by the on-again, off-again U.S. tariffs, as well as a recent slide in oil prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oilfield-services-firms-brace-earnings-tariffs-cloud-outlook-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNT3FDSVZZLTRPO5S2JEEL6GAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:41:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在不断恶化的经济迷雾中艰难预测业务量]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易战给美国航空公司带来了自 COVID 大流行以来最大的不确定性。【原文：President Donald Trump's trade war has created the biggest uncertainty for U.S. airlines since the COVID pandemic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-struggle-forecast-their-business-worsening-economic-fog-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7OMMU2RLZI3BE4GFG3GX4QHUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大人 2 月份购买的美股数量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管加拿大和美国之间的关系十分紧张，但官方数据周四显示，随着美国股市创下历史新高，加拿大人在二月份购买了创纪录数量的美国股票。【原文：Although tensions between Canada and the United States are high, Canadians bought a record amount of American shares in February, as U.S. stock markets hit an all-time high, official data indicated on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadians-bought-record-amount-us-shares-february-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIPWFYQMC5PALJ2KXSPGKBPLIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场认为欧洲央行将在关税打击下进一步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）宣布降息，交易员们相信，如果贸易紧张局势对脆弱的经济造成影响，该央行将进一步放宽政策。【原文：Traders saw the all-clear on Thursday from the European Central Bank to bet on even steeper interest rate cuts ahead, confident the central bank will ease policy further if trade tensions dent a fragile economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/markets-see-door-wide-open-more-ecb-rate-cuts-tariff-hit-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIXUWXHPY5NCFLSLDVRKUYFU5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:26:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行将未来 3 个月金价目标上调至每盎司 3,500 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗研究公司周四将未来三个月的黄金价格目标从每盎司3,200美元上调至3,500美元，原因是在关税风险和市场疲软的背景下，中国的保险公司和避险资金开始买入黄金。【原文：Citi Research on Thursday raised its gold price target for the next three months to $3,500 per ounce from $3,200, driven by fresh gold buying from Chinese insurers and safe-haven flows amid tariff risks and market weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/citi-raises-gold-price-target-next-3-months-3500-per-ounce-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F2IN4ZARROZTBKKLKVBHVWGWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:17:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官将在听证会后决定 Citgo 母公司拍卖的起拍价]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周四举行的听证会上，债权人陈述了他们的观点，预计美国法院将在未来几天内确认或否决 Contrarian Funds 关联公司提出的 37 亿美元收购要约，该要约旨在为委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份的新一轮竞购设定底线。【原文：A U.S. court is expected to confirm or reject in coming days a $3.7 billion offer by an affiliate of Contrarian Funds aimed at setting a floor for a new bidding round for shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum, following a hearing where creditors made their arguments on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-decide-starting-bid-citgo-parent-auction-following-hearing-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJ7ZBK7I25LTVIUUATIYGERXR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:14:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美国市场充满挑战，欧莱雅仍实现销售额增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅周四公布，由于欧洲市场对面霜和香水的强劲需求帮助抵消了美国市场的挑战，该公司第一季度的同类销售额增长了 3.5%，超过了预期的放缓增长。【原文：L'Oreal reported a 3.5% rise in like-for-like first-quarter sales on Thursday, beating expectations for slower growth, as strong demand for its face creams and perfume in Europe helped counter challenging conditions in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loreal-sales-rise-35-first-quarter-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMICYVPNMFNRLOB7JDLNDHZMPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国茶叶连锁企业茶奇网在纳斯达克首秀表现强劲，估值达 62 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国茶叶连锁企业茶奇网周四在纳斯达克上市，股价上涨 21%，估值达到 62 亿美元。【原文：Chinese tea chain Chagee secured a valuation of $6.2 billion after its shares gained 21% in the Nasdaq debut on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinese-tea-chain-chagee-valued-62-billion-strong-nasdaq-debut-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAAZ43CSOVPUPDWOV7DI2CNHEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>