<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 04:07:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 04:07:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司与工会谈判代表将于周三恢复合同谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际机械师和航空航天工人协会（IAM）表示，在周二未能就工资和养老金等关键问题达成一致后，波音公司与其最大的工会将于周三在联邦调解员在场的情况下恢复合同谈判。【原文：Boeing and its largest union will resume contract talks on Wednesday, in the presence of federal mediators, after failing to agree on key issues of wages and pensions on Tuesday, the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM) said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-union-negotiators-set-resume-talks-wednesday-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ERENS6XFVMXJP2PMKSYRBPK3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 03:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元回落，亚洲股市涨跌不一，美联储阴影笼罩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元回吐了隔夜的部分涨幅，而亚洲股市则表现不一，因为交易员们在权衡美联储当天晚些时候超大规模降息的可能性。【原文：The dollar ceded some of its overnight gains on Wednesday while Asian stocks put in a mixed display as traders weighed the odds of a super-sized Federal Reserve interest rate cut later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWVJD6FL7VNUXIVEVZE4AAWZQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 02:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：日本执政党竞选如何影响日本央行加息时机？]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本执政党领导人竞选将决定谁将成为下一任首相，这可能会使央行将超宽松货币政策正常化的计划复杂化。【原文：Japan's ruling party leadership race, which will determine who becomes next prime minister, could complicate the central bank's plan to normalise ultra-loose monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/how-would-japans-ruling-party-race-affect-boj-rate-hike-timing-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAUVLTXRLVLQDPJVMYWHP3SWLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 02:13:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价持稳，投资者关注美联储决议]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在等待美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）的降息预期，加上中东可能发生更多暴力事件，油价在前两个交易日上涨后，周三趋于稳定。【原文：Oil prices steadied on Wednesday, after rising in the previous two sessions, as investors await the U.S. Federal Reserve's anticipated interest rate cut, with the potential for more violence in the Middle East supporting the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-steady-with-investors-focusing-fed-decision-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJ6Y5GKUCJJFNI3JNVN56Q6MCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 01:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本出口大幅放缓，机械订单萎缩，经济复苏受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本 8 月份的出口增长大幅放缓，原因是对美国的发货量三年来首次出现下降，而 7 月份的机械订单出人意料地出现萎缩，这对正在努力实现稳健复苏的日本经济来说是一个令人担忧的迹象。【原文：Japan's export growth slowed sharply in August as shipments to the U.S. dropped for the first time in three years, while machinery orders unexpectedly shrank in July in a worrying sign for an economy struggling to mount a solid recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-exports-rise-slower-pace-pressuring-fragile-economic-recovery-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQXLTTU4GZIAXN3DFDYWNTSO3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:19:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元在美联储会议前站稳脚跟]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国零售销售强于预期，交易商略微降低了对美国宽松周期将以大幅降息开始的押注，美元周三企稳。【原文：The dollar steadied on Wednesday as stronger-than-expected U.S. retail sales had traders slightly trimming bets that the U.S. easing cycle will begin with an outsized interest rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-catches-footing-ahead-fed-2024-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NQHIKA2FFNDJFGF647GVW7PBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司的决定推迟至大选之后]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士周二表示，负责审查新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司的国家安全委员会批准了两家公司重新提交交易申请的请求，这使得拜登政府可以在美国总统大选之后再决定是否阻止该交易。【原文：A national security committee reviewing Nippon Steel's bid for U.S. Steel granted a request by the companies to refile their bid for approval of the deal, a person familiar with the matter said on Tuesday, giving the Biden administration until after the U.S. presidential election to make a decision about whether to block the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-decision-nippons-bid-us-steel-pushed-back-until-after-election-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GB4ZIZ7OSJOKXJS5EMUJI5V6GI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会主席表示，UAW 将在 Stellantis 工厂举行罢工投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合汽车工人工会主席肖恩-费恩（Shawn Fain）周二表示，该工会计划在未来几天内在一个或多个斯泰兰特地区举行罢工授权投票，这可能会导致针对吉普车制造商的破坏性罢工。【原文：The United Auto Workers union plans to hold strike authorization votes at one or more of its Stellantis locals in the coming days, union president Shawn Fain said on Tuesday, which could lead to a disruptive walkout against the Jeep maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uaw-union-prepares-hold-strike-authorization-votes-stellantis-locals-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXADA7VKLRI43LY4QJXD67235Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:31:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，诺和诺德称 Ozempic "极有可能 "进入 2027 年医疗保险谈判名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二援引一位公司高管的话报道，丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司预计，其糖尿病药物Ozempic "极有可能 "进入美国政府2027年的价格谈判名单。【原文：Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk expects its diabetes drug Ozempic will "very likely" be on the U.S. government's 2027 list of price negotiations, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday citing a company executive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-says-ozempic-very-likely-be-2027-medicare-negotiation-list-bloomberg-news-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YXKYVZ7LVOEJBPLMLC7T3MHLA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:17:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：美国推动越南海底电缆计划远离中国的内幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[会谈知情人士透露，美国正敦促越南在其到2030年建设10条新海底电缆的计划中避免中国电缆铺设公司HMN Technologies和其他中国公司参与。【原文：The United States is urging Vietnam to avoid Chinese cable-laying firm HMN Technologies and other Chinese companies in its plans to build 10 new undersea cables by 2030, sources with knowledge of the talks said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/inside-us-push-steer-vietnams-subsea-cable-plans-away-china-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYAL5F56CBKCVOWAEEZKLFVRQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标美联储千钧一发--等待即将结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X37ODNU3KFIR7NQNE2BMLTPF74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:51:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[23andMe独立董事因首席执行官的收购计划不尽如人意而退出董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[基因检测公司 23andMe 的独立董事周二表示，由于没有收到首席执行官安妮-沃西基（Anne Wojcicki）令人满意的私有化要约，他们已辞去公司董事会职务。【原文：The independent directors of genetic testing firm 23andMe said on Tuesday they have resigned from the company's board after not receiving a satisfactory take-private offer from CEO Anne Wojcicki.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/23andme-independent-directors-quit-board-over-unsatisfactory-buyout-plan-ceo-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITRKURGW6VLXFJ3LGWONWWDQDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长表示，哥伦比亚政府不会改变 2025 年拟议预算值]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚财政部长里卡多-博尼利亚（Ricardo Bonilla）周二在接受采访时表示，哥伦比亚政府将不会修改其 2025 年拟议预算中的 523 万亿比索（约合 1239 亿美元）。【原文：Colombia's government will not modify the value of 523 trillion pesos ($123.9 billion) for its proposed 2025 budget, Finance Minister Ricardo Bonilla said in an interview on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-government-will-not-change-proposed-2025-budget-value-finance-minister-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VLHVVJN2JL5ZEIIQEYQ2V4KWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:27:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）授予直觉机器公司价值 48 亿美元的导航服务合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）周二表示，已授予直觉机器公司一份价值高达 48.2 亿美元的合同，为近太空任务提供通信和导航服务。【原文：NASA has awarded Intuitive Machines a contract of up to $4.82 billion for communication and navigation services for missions in the near space region, the space exploration company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/nasa-awards-48-bln-navigation-services-contract-intuitive-machines-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKFS4M5QWFJQ5HKBHKWVWNT56A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敦促宽大处理 FTX 公司的卡罗琳-埃里森，并列举了对班克曼-弗里德的帮助]]></title><description><![CDATA[前 FTX 加密货币高管卡罗琳-埃里森（Caroline Ellison）因在交易所倒闭中扮演的角色而被判刑，美国检察官以她帮助 FTX 创始人山姆-班克曼-弗里德（Sam Bankman-Fried）入狱 25 年为由，为她求情。【原文：U.S. prosecutors made a case for leniency for former FTX cryptocurrency executive Caroline Ellison when she is sentenced over her role in the exchange's collapse, citing her help in sending FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried to prison for 25 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-urges-leniency-ftxs-caroline-ellison-cites-help-against-bankman-fried-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXSWS7DG3FPTRJZUHM76GDQC2M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[能源公司高管表示，他们相信副总统卡马拉-哈里斯确实对压裂持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些天然气行业的高层管理人员周二表示，他们相信副总统卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）的承诺是可信的，如果她在11月5日的美国总统选举中获胜，她将继续允许天然气压裂，因为这位民主党候选人明白，如果不这样做，能源价格将会上涨。【原文：Some top natural gas executives on Tuesday said they believe Vice President Kamala Harris was credible when she pledged to continue to allow natural-gas fracking if she wins the Nov. 5 election to become U.S. president, since the Democratic candidate understands energy prices would rise otherwise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/energy-execs-say-they-believe-vp-kamala-harris-is-indeed-open-fracking-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYPBNFIKABOJXDT6AJIYREXQ7Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:46:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[作为成本削减计划的一部分，Blink Charging 将裁减 14% 的全球员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车充电设备制造商 Blink Charging 周二表示，作为成本削减计划的一部分，公司将在全球范围内裁员约 14%。【原文：Electric vehicle charging equipment maker Blink Charging said on Tuesday it would lay off about 14% of its global workforce, as part of a cost reduction plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/blink-charging-cut-14-global-workforce-part-cost-reduction-plan-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKYNTPBN2ZPADCL2JR6XIH4URU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，史蒂夫-科恩停止为对冲基金 Point72 进行交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，对冲基金 Point72 资产管理公司的创始人、亿万富翁史蒂夫-科恩（Steve Cohen）已退出交易大厅，将专注于推动公司的发展。【原文：Steve Cohen, billionaire and founder of hedge fund Point72 Asset Management, has stepped away from the trading floor and will focus on driving the firm's growth, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/steve-cohen-stops-trading-hedge-fund-point72-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FCU45MZRZO55HF5SVE7FXYAIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:24:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：微软和贝莱德计划成立 300 亿美元基金，投资人工智能基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周二援引知情人士的话报道称，贝莱德正准备与微软共同发起一个规模超过 300 亿美元的人工智能投资基金，用于建设数据中心和能源项目，以满足人工智能带来的日益增长的需求。【原文：BlackRock is preparing to launch a more than $30 billion artificial intelligence investment fund with Microsoft to build data centers and energy projects to meet growing demands stemming from AI, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday, citing people briefed about the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/microsoft-blackrock-plan-30-bln-fund-invest-ai-infrastructure-ft-reports-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUYJ527KFNIARB2YAFE6NJ7GUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:21:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：备忘录称，激进分子埃利奥特告诉西南航空的机械师，它仍希望首席执行官下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份工会备忘录，激进投资者埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）告诉西南航空公司的一个高层工会，即使在该航空公司承诺调整董事会之后，它仍然希望更换首席执行官罗伯特-乔丹（Robert Jordan）。【原文：Activist investor Elliott Investment Management told one of Southwest Airlines' top unions it still wants to replace CEO Robert Jordan, according to a union memo seen by Reuters, even after the carrier pledged to shake up its board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/activist-elliott-tells-southwest-air-mechanics-it-still-wants-ceos-ouster-memo-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTMDPPHETBOMBAFHGICJX6KCRQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EA 对年度预订充满信心，宣布推出《战地》新作]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子游戏发行商电子艺界（Electronic Arts）在周二举行的投资者日会议上表示，预计将实现其年度预订额预测的高端目标，并推出了多人射击游戏《战地》的下一版。【原文：Videogame publisher Electronic Arts said it expects to achieve the high end of its annual bookings forecast and unveiled the next installment of its multi-player shooter game "Battlefield" at its investor day conference on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ea-confident-about-annual-bookings-announces-new-battlefield-title-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMESF4A2YFODPMWTAZIWDUZWFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 Neuralink 公司因植入大脑而获得美国食品及药物管理局的突破性设备标签]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的脑芯片初创公司 Neuralink 周二表示，其植入物已获得美国食品和药物管理局的 "突破性设备 "称号。【原文：Elon Musk's brain-chip startup Neuralink said on Tuesday its implant had received the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's "breakthrough device" designation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/musks-neuralink-receives-fdas-breakthrough-device-tag-brain-implant-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4VUU5KJAZJPNMPVKDDMRH47NA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:18:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道油价低迷，美国将寻求600万桶石油储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟知此事的消息人士周二表示，拜登政府将为战略石油储备寻求多达 600 万桶石油，如果这一采购计划得以完成，将是继 2022 年历史性出售石油之后最大的一次石油储备补充。【原文：The Biden administration will seek up to 6 million barrels of oil for the Strategic Petroleum Reserve, a source familiar with issue said on Tuesday, a purchase that if completed will match its largest yet in the replenishment of the stash after a historic sale in 2022.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-seek-6-million-barrels-oil-reserve-amid-low-oil-price-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZB2DCYPZVOBTJM7W4OW3DUHOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[运输部称阿拉斯加航空和夏威夷航空可完成合并交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部周二表示，在双方同意保留夏威夷的主要航线并采取消费者保护措施后，美国交通部已同意允许阿拉斯加航空公司以 19 亿美元的价格完成对夏威夷航空公司的收购。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department said on Tuesday it had agreed to allow Alaska Airlines to close on its $1.9 billion acquisition of Hawaiian Airlines , after the carriers agreed to maintain key Hawaiian routes and adopt consumer protections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/alaska-airlines-hawaiian-can-close-merger-deal-dot-says-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2EEKGY7TFINVENGFIFWZR2AXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FTX 审计师就美国证券交易委员会失职案达成和解并支付罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[FTX 的一名前审计师将支付 195 万美元，以了结美国证券交易委员会的两起案件，包括因涉嫌在审计山姆-班克曼-弗里德（Sam Bankman-Fried）领导的加密货币交易所时玩忽职守而被判定犯有欺诈罪。【原文：A former auditor for FTX will pay $1.95 million to settle two U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission cases, including for alleged negligence in auditing the cryptocurrency exchange Sam Bankman-Fried led before being convicted of fraud.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ftx-auditor-settles-us-sec-negligence-case-pays-fine-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J3HDT7QHG5JFXDH5EBUURX6GY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员桑德斯称，仿制药制造商可以低于每月 100 美元的价格销售 Ozempic]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员伯尼-桑德斯（Bernie Sanders）周二表示，他得到了主要仿制药公司的确认，他们可以以每月不到 100 美元的价格出售诺和诺德糖尿病药物 Ozempic 的仿制药。【原文：U.S. Senator Bernie Sanders said on Tuesday he received confirmation from major generic pharmaceutical companies that they could sell copycat versions of Novo Nordisk's diabetes drug Ozempic for less than $100 a month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-senator-sanders-says-generic-drugmakers-could-sell-ozempic-less-than-100month-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DAQJ4NJ2BNHXHKXHAD3HMNZ2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府官员称拜登不会阻止东海岸港口可能发生的罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）的一位政府官员周二表示，如果码头工人未能在10月1日的最后期限前签订新的劳动合同，他不打算援引联邦法律来阻止东海岸和墨西哥湾的港口罢工。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden does not intend to invoke a federal law to prevent a port strike on the East Coast and Gulf of Mexico if dockworkers fail to secure a new labor contract by an Oct. 1 deadline, an administration official said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/biden-wont-block-potential-strike-east-coast-ports-administration-official-says-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WFWR7HWG5LRHH7JT3WI7XVGJA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:15:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snap 推出新版 Spectacles 眼镜，进一步押注增强现实技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[Snap 周二宣布推出 Spectacles 增强现实眼镜的升级版，并加倍押注可增强现实世界视角的可穿戴设备将成为下一个科技前沿。【原文：Snap announced an upgraded version of its Spectacles augmented-reality glasses on Tuesday, doubling down on its bet that wearable devices to enhance the view of the real world will be one of the next frontiers in tech.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/snap-advances-bet-augmented-reality-with-new-version-spectacles-glasses-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZF35SESWDNKGNPDJZXXVPXQHIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨姆规则制定者认为美联储因劳动力市场担忧降息 50 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[前美联储经济学家克劳迪娅-萨姆（Claudia Sahm）表示，美国经济并未陷入衰退，但劳动力市场的疲软可能会让美联储感到担忧，从而在周三将利率下调50个基点。【原文：The U.S. economy is not in a recession but labor-market weakness might worry the Federal Reserve enough to cut interest rates by 50 basis points on Wednesday, former Fed economist Claudia Sahm said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/sahm-rule-creator-sees-50-bps-fed-rate-cut-labor-market-worries-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4WMM6P7FNPZXBKCEF57M6WLSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:55:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的媒体股票在内幕交易限制解除前下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的媒体公司股价周二连续第二个交易日下跌，原因是美国前总统和其他内部人士出售股票的限制即将结束。【原文：Shares of Donald Trump's media company fell for a second session on Tuesday ahead of the end of restrictions on share sales by the former U.S. president and other insiders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-media-stock-falls-before-insider-trading-restrictions-lift-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCHANIYYKROWHKS2ESJTTEVXFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:50:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>