<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 07:04:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 07:04:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，越南监管机构建议批准中国商飞公司的喷气式飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的文件显示，越南航空监管机构已提议承认中国的飞机设计认证等同于美国标准，从而为中国国有飞机制造商中国商飞公司的喷气式飞机进入越南市场提供便利。【原文：Vietnam's aviation regulator has proposed to recognise China's aircraft design certifications as equivalent to U.S. standards, facilitating the entry of jets from Chinese state-owned planemaker COMAC, according to documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietnam-regulator-proposes-approval-chinese-comac-jets-documents-show-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWY2CNZ2PFMJBOWZYFURN2FQQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雨果博斯预计 2025 年销售额将与上年持平]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hugo Boss 周四表示，在 2024 年销售额略超市场预期后，预计全年销售额将与去年基本持平。【原文：Hugo Boss said on Thursday it expected annual sales to remain broadly in line with last year, after its 2024 sales slightly surpassed market expectations.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hugo-boss-expects-2025-sales-prior-years-level-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DU7XEJV3RFJB3B5W6JS6C5FRPU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:47:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，百威啤酒亚太区将裁员数千人，以降低成本 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，百威啤酒亚太有限公司计划今年裁员数千人，以缩减成本。【原文：Budweiser Brewing Co APAC Ltd is planning to cut thousands of jobs this year as it looks to shrink costs, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter, as the beer maker struggles with weak consumer demand in China.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/budweiser-apac-cut-thousands-jobs-reduce-costs-by-15-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMO65IMKSNOG5KCNVW7CLAE63E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南非标准银行年度利润增长 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[非洲资产规模最大的银行--标准银行（Standard Bank）周四公布年度利润增长 4%，并宣布派发每股 763 美分的末期股息。【原文：Africa's biggest lender by assets, Standard Bank , on Thursday reported annual profit rose by 4% and declared a final dividend of 763 cents a share.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/africa/south-africas-standard-bank-reports-4-rise-annual-profit-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H66BEMY77BPU7MNKKHWYBFAEQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用集团创下年度利润新高，顶级投资者准备参加股东大会角逐]]></title><description><![CDATA[Generali 周四公布了 2024 年的创纪录利润，符合预期，首席执行官菲利普-多内特（Philippe Donnet）准备在下个月就其连任问题面临关键的股东投票。【原文：Generali on Thursday posted a record profit for 2024, in line with expectations, as Chief Executive Philippe Donnet prepares to face a key shareholder vote next month over his reappointment.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/europe/generali-posts-record-fy-profit-ahead-key-shareholder-vote-new-board-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUONVVZ2PBKKPC54NFCEOAC6TI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:14:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[透视：波音 787 喷气式客机的故障部件如何在意大利的雷达监视下飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[2020 年 5 月的一个星期六上午，意大利警察在南部港口城市布林迪西一家小型飞机零部件工厂附近抓获了两名向下水道倾倒化学废料的男子。【原文：On a Saturday morning in May, 2020, Italian police officers caught two men pouring chemical waste into the sewers in the southern port city of Brindisi, near a small plane components factory.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/how-faulty-parts-boeings-787-jets-flew-below-radar-italy-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBFPNKF3X5KAVNLAPGBHBR3HS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:08:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行本月将维持利率不变，第三季度（最有可能在 7 月）将利率上调至 0.75%：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，超过三分之二的经济学家预计日本央行将在 3 月 19 日的会议上维持关键利率稳定，并在第三季度将利率上调 25 个基点至 0.75%，最有可能在 7 月份上调。【原文：The Bank of Japan is expected to keep its key interest rate steady at its March 19 meeting, with over two-thirds of economists expecting a 25-basis-point hike to 0.75% in the third quarter, most likely in July, a Reuters poll showed.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/boj-set-hold-rates-this-month-hike-075-q3-most-likely-july-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBBSXDRICVLJRALVOHNBR3Z3DE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:09:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡检方称美国服务器欺诈案涉及 3.9 亿美元交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡检方称，根据周四的庭审记录，一起涉及新加坡公司提供的服务器被转移到海外的欺诈案涉及价值 3.9 亿美元的交易。【原文：Singapore prosecutors said a fraud case involving servers supplied by Singapore-based firms that were moved offshore involves transactions worth $390 million, according to court proceedings on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-prosecutors-says-us-servers-fraud-case-involves-390-million-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QFFSGD7Z7ZK65HJXGMV2XS7INE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡检方称美国服务器欺诈案涉及 3.9 亿美元交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡检方称，根据周四的庭审记录，一起涉及新加坡公司提供的服务器被转移到海外的欺诈案涉及价值 3.9 亿美元的交易。【原文：Singapore prosecutors said a fraud case involving servers supplied by Singapore-based firms that were moved offshore involves transactions worth $390 million, according to court proceedings on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-prosecutors-says-us-servers-fraud-case-involves-390-million-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QFFSGD7Z7ZK65HJXGMV2XS7INE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀温和，股市上涨；贸易紧张局势提振收益率]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，科技股引领亚洲股市上扬，在不温不火的通胀数据缓解了市场对美国经济状况的担忧之后，科技股追随华尔街的涨势。【原文：Tech stocks led advances in Asia on Thursday, taking their cue from Wall Street's gains after tepid inflation data allayed concerns over the state of the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VN5TQXS32FLTXJ5X5IQNHRSN6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔新任首席执行官陈立武曾是成功的弱者]]></title><description><![CDATA[陈立武可能是你从未听说过的最有权势的技术高管之一。当他走上这个星球上最受瞩目的职位之一--陷入困境、声名显赫的芯片制造商英特尔公司的首席执行官岗位时，他的表现将得到充分展示。【原文：Lip-Bu Tan may be one of the most powerful technology executives you've never heard of. As he steps into one of the highest-profile jobs on the planet, CEO of troubled, storied chipmaker Intel, his performance will be on full display.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/intels-new-ceo-lip-bu-tan-has-history-successful-underdog-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPSBPR47IRISHIW7NJKLOJWQPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:30:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[担忧关税战升级对全球经济的影响，石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对关税战加剧对全球经济增长和能源需求影响的担忧超过了美国汽油库存超预期减少所带来的积极情绪，油价在前一天飙升后于周四有所回落。【原文：Oil prices eased on Thursday after surging the day before as worries about the impact of intensifying tariff wars on global economic growth and energy demand outweighed the positive sentiment from a larger-than-expected draw in U.S. gasoline stocks.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-eases-concerns-about-escalating-tariff-wars-impact-global-economy-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GKDS5H6WFIL5F2YNYBETTPD74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战搅动市场，收益率上升带动美元反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国国债收益率上升，美元周四小幅反弹，但由于投资者难以确定不断升级的全球贸易战对美国通胀和经济增长的影响，各国货币在狭窄区间内交投。【原文：The dollar rebounded slightly on Thursday thanks to a rise in U.S. Treasury yields, though currencies traded in tight ranges as investors struggled to determine the impact of an escalating global trade war on U.S. inflation and growth.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-bounces-rise-yields-trade-war-roils-markets-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEN73RYETVJNLKLMIT54YI234E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[应美国要求，印度逮捕被控洗钱的加密货币管理员]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度打击犯罪最高机构周三表示，印度当局应华盛顿的要求逮捕了一名加密货币交易所管理员，他被指控共谋洗钱和违反制裁。【原文：Indian authorities arrested at Washington's request a cryptocurrency exchange administrator accused of money laundering conspiracy and violating sanctions, India's top crime fighting bureau said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us-request-india-arrests-crypto-administrator-accused-money-laundering-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJYPZQWCRBMZFITTISQQBA4X4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:35:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[库什-塔德访问东京，对 Seven & I 展开魅力攻势]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alimentation Couche-Tard 公司将寻求解决日本 Seven & i 公司的反垄断问题，因为这家加拿大公司的管理层即将开始东京之行，以推进其 470 亿美元收购 7-Eleven 便利店运营商的谈判。【原文：Alimentation Couche-Tard will seek to address antitrust concerns of Japan's Seven & i as the Canadian company's management kicks off a Tokyo visit to push forward talks for its $47 billion bid for the operator of 7-Eleven convenience stores.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/deals/couche-tard-goes-charm-offensive-seven-i-with-tokyo-visit-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDOY4LWQBNPEPFVNL5TY3EQLZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 赢得停止推广前员工撰写的《粗心的人》讲述书的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据社交媒体公司公布的裁决书副本，Meta Platforms 周三赢得了一项紧急仲裁裁决，暂时停止宣传一名前员工的自述书籍《粗心的人》。【原文：Meta Platforms on Wednesday won an emergency arbitration ruling to temporarily stop promotion of the tell-all book "Careless People" by a former employee, according to a copy of the ruling published by the social media company.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/meta-wins-halt-promotion-careless-people-tell-all-book-by-former-employee-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OACG7TQCMVIAJPHCEWFN6LJPUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔新任首席执行官陈立武是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司周三任命前董事会成员陈立武为首席执行官，这家陷入困境的美国芯片制造公司正试图走出最黯淡的时期之一。【原文：Intel tapped former board member Lip-Bu Tan as its CEO on Wednesday, as the struggling American chipmaking icon attempts to emerge from one of its bleakest periods.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/who-is-new-intel-ceo-lip-bu-tan-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMIYNHNNEZKVLMSBQYTP36KC64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构起诉 FIIG Securities 网络安全失误]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚证券监管机构周四表示，它正在将固定收益经纪商 FIIG 告上法庭，指控该公司在四年时间里未能采取足够的网络安全措施，致使一名黑客得以潜入其 IT 网络。【原文：The Australian securities watchdog said on Thursday it is taking fixed-income broker FIIG to court, alleging it failed to implement adequate cybersecurity measures over a four-year period, enabling a hacker to infiltrate its IT network.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/australia-regulator-sues-fiig-securities-cybersecurity-failures-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJQ3QG2DM5I4FIM4UGNB3QCHHU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:17:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通收购矿业巨头力拓超过 5%的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周四向当地交易所提交的文件显示，摩根大通已持有澳大利亚矿业集团力拓 5.36% 的股份。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has taken a 5.36% stake in Australia's mining conglomerate Rio Tinto , an exchange filing to the local bourse showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/deals/jpmorgan-scoops-over-5-stake-mining-major-rio-tinto-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5OYYADSYVLEZLNK2UFUOBMQGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Meta 的扎克伯格周三在白宫举行了会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，Meta Platforms 首席执行官马克-扎克伯格周三在白宫与特朗普政府官员举行了会谈。【原文：Meta Platforms Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg held meetings at the White House with Trump administration officials on Wednesday, according to a source familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/metas-zuckerberg-held-meetings-white-house-wednesday-source-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QUMAS344BL3ZMXMPBR23KDMDU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，投资者在经济低迷时买入华丽 7 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的数据显示，在最近美国股市大跌期间，个人投资者抢购了与 "华丽七雄 "科技大盘股挂钩的交易所交易基金的股票。【原文：Individual investors snapped up shares of an exchange-traded fund tied to the "Magnificent Seven" group of technology megacap stocks during the recent nosedive in the U.S. stock market, according to data on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-bought-magnificent-7-etf-amid-downturn-data-shows-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4XM4VSQWJKPPHIUF5X7NYG6GY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:21:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道贸易组织称美国食品巨头百事可乐和康瑞格拉寻求豁免部分进口商品关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封信，包括桂格燕麦和福尔杰咖啡在内的主要包装食品制造商要求美国总统唐纳德-特朗普有针对性地豁免可可和水果等进口商品的关税。【原文：Major packaged food makers including Quaker Oats and Folgers coffee asked U.S. President Donald J. Trump for targeted exemptions from tariffs on imports like cocoa and fruit, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-food-giants-pepsico-conagra-seek-exempt-some-imports-tariffs-trade-group-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVSXQOHPKJJRVO5A2ZHPLYDMBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：华尔街终于反弹了。但能持续多久？]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IL3BIN32D5KL7BA6RWUWVNEPWU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[激进投资者以气候风险和收益不佳为由，反对伍德赛德公司董事选举]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚企业责任中心（ACCR）周四对伍德赛德能源公司（Woodside Energy）即将举行的年度股东大会上的所有董事选举表示反对，理由之一是该公司在管理气候风险方面存在失误。【原文：The Australasian Centre for Corporate Responsibility (ACCR) expressed dissent on Thursday against all directors due for election at the upcoming annual general meeting of Woodside Energy , citing failures in managing climate risks, among other reasons.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/activist-investor-defies-woodside-directors-election-citing-climate-risk-poor-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76MEYG5FVJIY5CSKECPJLWTJNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会撤回推迟亚马逊因裁员而受审的申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）周三推翻了其一名律师在法庭上的说法，即需要推迟对亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）消费者保护案的审理，此前该委员会曾以削减成本措施导致 "资源严重不足 "为由推迟审理。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Wednesday reversed one of its lawyer's statements in court that it needed to delay the trial in its consumer protection case against Amazon.com , after earlier citing "severe resource shortfalls" caused by cost cutting measures.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/ftc-withdraws-bid-delay-amazon-trial-over-doge-cuts-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QPL43SWMFI65C7PA4BUCVOTO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:37:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 美国风能和太阳能开发仍有很大发展空间，微软高管称可用于数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软能源副总裁鲍比-霍利斯（Bobby Hollis）周三在休斯敦举行的CERAWeek能源会议上告诉路透社记者，美国的风能和太阳能开发仍有很大的扩展空间，可以为数据中心提供电力，特别是在中西部风能走廊和阳光充足的西南部地区。【原文：U.S. wind and solar development still has significant room for expansion to power data centers, particularly in the Midwest wind corridor and sunny southwest, Microsoft VP of Energy Bobby Hollis told Reuters at the CERAWeek energy conference in Houston on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-us-wind-solar-development-still-has-much-room-grow-data-centers-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A64TMKBJFPQLE4WJADDVYQGR4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DHL 集团首席执行官：尽管美国采取关税政策，全球贸易仍将增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国 DHL 集团首席执行官托比亚斯-迈耶（Tobias Meyer）周三告诉路透社记者，随着全球对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策作出反应，全球贸易预计将增长，尽管增长不那么强劲。【原文：Global trade is forecast to grow, albeit less robustly, as the world reacts to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff policies, Germany's DHL Group CEO Tobias Meyer told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-trade-grow-despite-us-tariff-policies-says-dhl-group-ceo-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Z7PDXGM5ZMW3NBSD5HHMXSHCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 人工智能、液化天然气需求将使美国天然气使用量持续创历史新高，但瓶颈问题仍是威胁所在]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周举行的一次会议上，高管们表示，由于液化天然气（LNG）需求和数据中心耗电量的飙升，美国天然气使用量将继续创下历史新高，同时他们也警告说，基础设施的缺乏可能会对该行业造成损害。【原文：U.S. natural gas use is set to continue hitting record highs due to soaring liquefied natural gas (LNG) demand and power consumption from data centers, executives said at a conference this week, while also warning a lack of infrastructure could hurt the industry.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-ai-lng-demand-keep-us-natgas-use-record-highs-bottlenecks-threaten-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARVW5EANSBL3FOCY7CXNRN35CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CEERAWEEK 美国石油高管下周将与特朗普会晤]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油协会（American Petroleum Institute）周三表示，美国石油生产商将于下周与唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统会面。【原文：U.S. oil producers will meet with President Donald Trump next week, leading industry group the American Petroleum Institute said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceeraweek-us-oil-executives-meet-with-trump-next-week-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A2TFXVAXLVJE5AIKGKLX6YZUK4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空公司完成财务重组，退出破产保护程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空母公司精神航空控股公司（Spirit Aviation Holdings）周三表示，这家低成本航空公司已成功完成财务重组。【原文：Spirit Airlines parent Spirit Aviation Holdings said on Wednesday that the low-cost carrier has successfully completed its financial restructuring.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-emerges-chapter-11-bankruptcy-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4BIUCGX3FKBVD6TDH3LYZTPWQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>