<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:04:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:04:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[耶鲁大学研究人员称，特朗普暂停加征关税对降低总体关税率作用不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[耶鲁大学的研究人员周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普收回了他征收的部分高额关税，但这对降低平均进口税率并没有起到什么作用，而他的征税浪潮曾使平均进口税率升至较高水平。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's rollback of some of the steep tariffs he has imposed has done little to lower the average import duty rate from the elevated levels to which his wave of levies had driven them, researchers from Yale University said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-tariff-pause-does-little-lower-overall-tariff-rates-yale-researchers-say-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR6NUKWAKNPHXOMQMU4BKKQGXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[声明称，美国钢铁公司和新日铁公司与特朗普政府密切合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司和新日本制铁公司正在与特朗普政府密切合作，"以确保获得重大投资"，美国钢铁公司周四表示，在此之前，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的讲话使这两家公司长期寻求的合作获得绿灯的希望变得渺茫。【原文：U.S. Steel and Nippon Steel are working closely with the Trump administration "to secure a significant investment," U.S. Steel said on Thursday, after remarks from President Donald Trump dimmed hopes for a greenlight of the companies' long-sought tie-up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-nippon-steel-working-closely-with-trump-administration-statement-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7CTMI4NNFM6LNYU6L7YU7BCFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:54:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西贷款公司 BRB 首席执行官称，随着交易调整，Banco Master 的价格有望降低]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西商业银行总裁周四表示，巴西政府控制的银行巴西商业银行（BRB）收购 Banco Master 部分贷款机构资产的交易，可能会排除 "远超过 "230 亿雷亚尔（38.9 亿美元）的资产。【原文：The acquisition of some of lender Banco Master's assets by Brazil's government-controlled bank BRB is likely to exclude "much more" than 23 billion reais ($3.89 billion) in assets, BRB's president said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/brazilian-lender-brb-expects-lower-banco-master-price-with-deal-adjustment-ceo-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RVHPLY3DFODLP7UGIFZTXH6Y4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场关税混乱持续，华尔街转而大幅走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心高关税对全球经济的影响，华尔街主要股指周四再次重挫，与上一交易日美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）临时降低对一些国家征收关税时的历史性股价涨幅相比出现了逆转。【原文：Wall Street's main indexes fell hard again on Thursday on concerns over the impact of high tariffs on the global economy, marking a U-turn from the previous session's historic share gains when U.S. President Donald Trump moved to temporarily lower the levies on some countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-views-quotes-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZ6DIRVJGRPMXDM4OQPIJZ5IEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普暂停关税不会改变美联储看到未来风险的基本面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普暂停征收部分新的进口税，这可能减轻了金融市场目前所承受的压力，但同样的一系列情况仍在继续，这些情况重置了美国的经济前景，使衰退风险上升，通胀率可能上升。【原文：President Donald Trump's pause on some of his new import taxes may have lessened the stress that had been building in financial markets for now, but leaves in place the same set of circumstances that had reset the U.S. economic outlook with rising recession risks and potentially rising inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-tariff-pause-wont-change-fundamentals-fed-that-sees-risks-ahead-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHTUYLWP7VIVJIZCCZFMAUMYAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称债券抛售引发不稳定威胁，影响特朗普关税转向]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周四表示，最近几天美国国债价格下跌引发的金融不稳定威胁很可能影响了唐纳德-特朗普总统扭转方向、部分暂停关税行动的决定。【原文：Former U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Thursday that the threat of financial instability prompted by falling prices for U.S. Treasury debt in recent days likely influenced President Donald Trump's decision to reverse course and partially pause his tariff campaign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/yellen-says-bond-sell-off-raised-instability-threat-influencing-trump-tariff-u-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SI5EQBVSKFPXVL4HMUVG7E7W7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈克表示，美联储应在金融科技领域发挥领导作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联储主席帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）周四在一个金融技术创新会议上发表演讲时，在准备好的发言稿中没有对经济前景或货币政策发表评论。【原文：Philadelphia Federal Reserve President Patrick Harker did not comment on the outlook for the economy or monetary policy in prepared remarks for a speech to a financial technology innovation conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fed-should-lead-financial-technology-space-harker-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZI6L2JC27RPHNO6UHO7DDEH4F4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约总检察长敦促国会加强加密货币监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长莱蒂西亚-詹姆斯（Letitia James）周四敦促立法者通过立法，为加密货币建立联邦监管框架，认为数字资产投资者迫切需要更有力的保护。【原文：New York Attorney General Letitia James urged lawmakers on Thursday to pass legislation to create a federal regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies, arguing that digital asset investors urgently need stronger protections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/new-york-attorney-general-urges-congress-bolster-crypto-regulations-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PSB5YIALJII5CKXLSPLH6CN2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌降低面向美国联邦机构的商业软件价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌将为美国联邦机构提供商业应用软件套餐的大幅折扣，该公司希望利用特朗普政府削减成本的推动力，削弱微软长期以来对政府软件市场的控制。【原文：Google will offer steep discounts to U.S. federal agencies for its business apps package as the company looks to capitalize on the Trump administration's cost-cutting push and chip away at Microsoft's longstanding grip on the government software market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-slashes-business-software-prices-us-federal-agencies-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7ZCDJ7B7ZOSBEYSZQRQEO425Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥银行美国关税可能对通胀两端造成压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥银行五位董事会成员中的大多数都认为，与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税相关的风险将对墨西哥通胀产生向上和向下的压力。【原文：Most of the Bank of Mexico's five governing board members agreed that the risks associated with U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs will exert both upward and downward pressures on Mexican inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-mexico-us-tariffs-may-exert-pressure-both-ends-inflation-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBNITINWAFNK3JC3JXSDDXZKLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:50:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司在印度寻找勘探机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）勘探与生产主管西尔维娅-多斯安若斯（Sylvia dos Anjos）周四表示，该公司正在权衡今年将在印度举行的石油区块拍卖所带来的机遇。【原文：Brazil's Petrobras is weighing opportunities from an oil block auction set to take place this year in India, said the state-run oil firm's head of exploration and production, Sylvia dos Anjos, on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazils-petrobras-eyes-exploration-opportunities-india-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BL6OYPL34NJ5JKYM356UGCR4EM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西官员表示，巴西将继续与美国谈判，同时寻求扩大贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西外贸秘书塔蒂亚娜-普拉泽雷斯（Tatiana Prazeres）周四表示，巴西将继续与美国进行贸易谈判，同时重申其对多边主义的支持，并寻求扩大其贸易协定网络。【原文：Brazil will pursue trade negotiations with the U.S. while reaffirming its support for multilateralism and seeking to expand its network of trade agreements, Foreign Trade Secretary Tatiana Prazeres said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-pursue-us-talks-while-seeking-expand-trade-deals-says-official-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2SD2I4URZK37PXGNNWDER7IRI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:40:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈雷戴维森董事会成员辞职，称对公司 "严重关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈雷戴维森公司的一位董事在致该摩托车制造商董事会的一封信中表达了对公司现状的 "严重关切"，并因此辞职。【原文：A Harley-Davidson director has resigned after expressing "grave concerns" about the current state of the company in a letter to the motorcycle maker's board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/harley-davidson-board-member-resigns-cites-grave-concerns-about-company-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYRKOELRXNMUPCUI5ZGRD7GIM4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油倡导者撤回领导美国土地局的提名]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院参议员迈克-李（Mike Lee）周四在参议院听证会上表示，石油业说客凯瑟琳-斯加玛（Kathleen Sgamma）已撤回对她领导美国土地管理局的提名。【原文：Oil industry lobbyist Kathleen Sgamma has withdrawn her nomination to lead the U.S. Bureau of Land Management, Senator Mike Lee said at a Senate hearing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/oil-advocate-withdraws-nomination-lead-us-land-bureau-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INGSYCUTFZKUTOAKO7VYYR3EKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税暂停令首席执行官们心存疑虑：90 天后会发生什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）突然改变了全面进口关税的立场，但这并不能缓解企业对其贸易战及其混乱实施所带来的后果的担忧：成本飙升、订单减少和供应链受阻。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's sudden about-face on sweeping import tariffs did little to soothe companies' worries about the fallout from his trade war and its chaotic implementation: soaring costs, falling orders and snarled supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariff-pause-leaves-ceos-asking-what-happens-90-days-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CM5YHBIPJBO6PFEWXRBJBBJTC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼誓言作为最高银行监管者制定 "务实 "规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周四向立法者表示，她将全面改革美国中央银行对大型银行的监管方式，鼓励创新，并为金融系统制定 "务实 "的规则。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman told lawmakers on Thursday that she would overhaul how the U.S. central bank monitors large banks, encourage innovation, and pursue "pragmatic" rules for the financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-bowman-vows-pragmatic-rulemaking-top-bank-regulator-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJYJQZBDNVJQ3B5I6RGHVQPIMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车供应商诺瓦雷斯和法雷奥要求预付关税费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国汽车供应商诺瓦瑞斯（Novares）和法雷奥（Valeo）的高管们表示，他们正要求客户预付美国新关税的全部费用，这凸显了唐纳德-特朗普总统对汽车进口征收关税对全球汽车制造商的打击。【原文：French automotive suppliers Novares and Valeo are asking customers to cover the full cost of new U.S. duties upfront, company executives said, underlining the hit to global carmakers from President Donald Trump's tariffs on car imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/auto-suppliers-novares-valeo-demand-upfront-payment-cover-tariff-cost-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KALM57N7EFKUZJET5CWUJWXIGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，高盛将美国汽车销量预期下调近 100 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税导致购车成本增加，高盛（Goldman Sachs）周四将今年美国汽车销量预期下调了近100万辆。【原文：Goldman Sachs on Thursday cut its estimate for automobile sales in the U.S. for this year by nearly 1 million units, as President Donald Trump's tariffs make it more expensive to buy a vehicle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/goldman-cuts-us-auto-sales-estimate-by-nearly-1-million-units-due-tariffs-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNYKW5YDBJJARALGXZII4WEG24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:26:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师报告称宝马考虑在美国斯帕坦堡工厂增加班次]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝马公司高管在周四的分析师电话会议上表示，宝马公司正在考虑为其位于南卡罗来纳州的斯帕坦堡工厂增加班次，以提高多达8万辆的产量。【原文：BMW is considering adding shifts to its Spartanburg plant in South Carolina to boost output by up to 80,000 units, executives said on an analyst call on Thursday, as carmakers brainstorm ways to appease the Trump administration and ward off a mounting trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-considering-added-shifts-us-spartanburg-plant-analyst-note-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVFAWUHM5RJELP2A3GEOXMZ5II</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:25:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西桑托斯港寻求吸引大型船只]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责管理南半球最大港口的巴西桑托斯港务局表示，未来几年将加深港口的吃水深度，以吸引更大型的船只。【原文：Brazil's Santos Port Authority, which administers the largest port in the Southern Hemisphere, said the draft of the port will be deepened to attract larger vessels in coming years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-santos-port-seeks-attract-larger-vessels-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUNM7SIFSJOGHCAJAZU3Q3IJ3M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南非考虑采取汽车业激励措施作为关税缓冲]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非贸易、工业和竞争部长帕克斯-陶（Parks Tau）周四表示，南非正在考虑向汽车制造商提供额外的激励措施，以帮助缓解美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对汽车征收关税的影响。【原文：South Africa is considering offering additional incentives to automakers to help cushion the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on cars, Trade, Industry and Competition Minister Parks Tau said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-africa-considering-auto-industry-incentives-tariff-buffer-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTVYTMQCLNJGBMGCJYWAQKL7ZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鉴于关税风险，堪萨斯城联储施密德将继续关注通胀问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储主席杰夫-施密德（Jeff Schmid）周四表示，他将继续 "坚定地关注 "通胀以及美国新的进口税可能使价格上涨并导致公众通胀预期上升的风险。【原文：Kansas City Federal Reserve President Jeff Schmid said on Thursday he will remain "squarely focused" on inflation and the risk new U.S. import taxes could shift prices higher and feed into rising public inflation expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/kansas-city-feds-schmid-stay-focused-inflation-light-tariff-risks-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDLHSUJVKNL3HJGZRJQMZPKQSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，贸易战威胁预算，巴西准备新一轮石油拍卖]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟知内情的人士说，巴西政府正准备在今年额外拍卖近海油区的股权，以增加收入。【原文：Brazil's government is preparing an extra auction this year of stakes in offshore oil areas to boost revenue, a plan gaining steam amid falling oil prices and rising global trade uncertainty, said four people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazil-prepares-new-oil-auction-trade-war-threatens-budget-sources-say-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N64YV4KRGNNLRPCYNUDSLL2NNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:52:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利矿业公司 Codelco 董事长称第二季度中国需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利铜业巨头 Codelco 公司董事长周四告诉路透社，第二季度中国对红色金属的需求强劲。【原文：Chilean copper giant Codelco is seeing strong demand for the red metal from China in the second quarter, the firm's chairman told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chilean-miner-codelco-logging-strong-q2-demand-china-chairman-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWFO3KNU4VOMJB6ZLQXRBUFV3E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普眨眼 "重新定义波动性，S 市场出现反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在关税问题上的转向给市场带来了更大的波动，让投资者从股票市场滑向避险天堂，又从避险天堂滑回股票市场。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's U-turn on tariffs has rained yet more volatility on markets, leaving investors skidding from stocks to safe-havens and back, and while previous crises have seen bigger moves, few have been this fast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-volatility-graphic-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCKXLQPYXVORRKNNNQC26RUGCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:47:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[支付公司布洛克因合规失误在纽约被罚款 4000 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约金融服务监管机构周四表示，Block 公司将支付 4000 万美元的罚款，以了结对该支付公司反洗钱合规计划严重失误以及现金应用程序平台虚拟货币合规失误的指控。【原文：Block will pay a $40 million fine to settle accusations the payments company had significant failures in its anti-money laundering compliance program and virtual currency compliance failures on its Cash App platform, New York's financial services regulator said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/payments-company-block-pay-40-million-fine-new-york-over-compliance-failures-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHUF4NF5AFLQTLN4IWCGGKT5XI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:45:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨约纳与皮德蒙特合并成立 Elevra Lithium 公司，董事会成员人数相等]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚赛约纳矿业公司（Sayona Mining）和皮德蒙特矿业公司（Piedmont）周四表示，赛约纳矿业公司收购皮德蒙特矿业公司后，合并后的公司将被命名为 Elevra Lithium，其董事会将由两家公司各提名四名成员组成。【原文：The combined company following Australia-based Sayona Mining's deal to buy Piedmont will be known as Elevra Lithium and its board will have four nominees from each of the two firms, the miners said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/sayona-piedmont-merger-forms-elevra-lithium-with-equal-board-representation-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3DUFW6MRJIOTKFFAGFHPATD7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:44:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 试图以折扣吸引心怀不满的特斯拉车主]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电动汽车制造商 Polestar 正在为美国的特斯拉车主提供高达 20,000 美元的 Polestar 3 汽车租赁折扣，该公司的目标客户是避开首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）汽车品牌的车主。【原文：Polestar is offering discounts of up to $20,000 towards a lease of its Polestar 3 vehicle for current Tesla owners in the United States, as the Swedish EV maker targets drivers shunning CEO Elon Musk's car brand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestar-bids-lure-disgruntled-tesla-owners-with-discounts-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NUD7D6XWBNYNBGH5HOZ5DMVGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储必须防止关税助长持续通胀：罗根]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-洛根周四在讲话中表示，高于预期的关税 "很可能 "会同时提高失业率和通胀率，她在讲话中明确表示，她最关心的是控制通胀和通胀预期。【原文：Higher-than-expected tariffs would "very likely" raise both unemployment and inflation, Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan said on Thursday in remarks that made clear her most immediate concern is keeping inflation, and inflation expectations, in check.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-must-keep-tariffs-fostering-persistent-inflation-logan-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHXEVBDRNZNGVJNTO4ESNXFXTE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车调整生产，将在全电动汽车工厂裁员 200 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）周四表示，该公司将在底特律的纯电动零工厂（Factory Zero）裁员，并调整生产 "以适应市场动态"。【原文：General Motors is laying off workers at its all-electric Factory Zero plant in Detroit where it is adjusting production "to align with market dynamics," the company said Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-lay-off-200-workers-all-ev-plant-it-adjusts-production-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOCDSLSINVKZRFZZ2YKI77DMBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>