<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:14:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:14:31 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国为 2026 年消费品以旧换新计划拨款 89 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据国家通讯社新华社周二报道，中国已拨出 625 亿元人民币（89.4 亿美元）超长专项国债资金，用于支持明年的消费品以旧换新计划。【原文：China has allocated 62.5 billion yuan ($8.94 billion) in ultra-long special treasury bond funds to support its consumer goods trade-in scheme next year, state news agency Xinhua reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-allocates-89-billion-fund-2026-consumer-goods-trade-in-scheme-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CQVDHPXXBNURCXA72NE5W5URM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债券在 2025 年大放异彩，但明年的回报可能会失去高度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国债券投资者可能会在 2026 年面临更严峻的考验，一些市场观察人士预测，随着美联储调低降息幅度，以及潜在的财政刺激政策使辉煌一年后的前景变得更加复杂，美国债券投资者的回报率将放缓。【原文：U.S. bond investors may face a tougher 2026, with some market-watchers forecasting slower returns as the Federal Reserve dials back rate cuts and potential fiscal stimulus complicates the outlook after a banner year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-bonds-shined-2025-returns-could-lose-altitude-next-year-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVUKQI5YQNILBMU6B7RO5RQBH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉季度交付量下降，原因是缺乏税收抵免和竞争抑制了需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉第四季度的交付量预计将下降，原因是美国税收抵免的丧失和全球竞争的加剧削弱了需求，即使该公司推出了其最畅销电动汽车的廉价版。【原文：Tesla deliveries were expected to fall in the fourth quarter, as the loss of U.S. tax credits and rising global competition sapped demand even as the company rolled out cheaper versions of its best-selling electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-quarterly-deliveries-seen-falling-lack-tax-credits-competition-sap-demand-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYLML2NFHVKYVNYRCNQGPZBPVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储 2025 年最终会议纪要将揭示政策分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储 12 月 9 日至 10 日政策会议的会议纪要预计将于周二公布，会议纪要将重新揭示决策者在连续第三次下调短期利率的决定上存在的分歧，并发出在 2026 年维持近期利率不变的信号。【原文：Minutes of the Federal Reserve's December 9-10 policy meeting are expected on Tuesday to shed fresh light on disagreements among policymakers over a decision to reduce short-term rates a third straight time and signal a near-term hold on rates in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/final-fed-minutes-2025-shed-light-policy-divisions-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5XXG4QNMNLAXA2O25ECQ3UJ6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普削减资金使美国消费者监督机构濒临倒闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[田纳西州孟菲斯市 33 岁的特殊教育教师比安卡-琼斯（Bianca Jones）几年前决定要买房，于是她开始查阅自己的益百利信用报告。她被自己的发现震惊了。【原文：When Bianca Jones, a 33-year-old special education teacher in Memphis, Tennessee, decided a couple of years ago that she wanted to buy a house, she started digging into her Experian credit report. She was shocked by what she found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trumps-funding-cuts-put-americas-consumer-watchdog-brink-collapse-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPBZY3SQZZMKPOC26SMN5HDKJQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技股领跌止住年末涨势，美股期货企稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于科技股再次面临抛售压力，在三大股指创下近两周来最大单日跌幅一天后，美国股指期货周二企稳。【原文：U.S. stock index futures steadied on Tuesday, a day after the three main indexes logged their steepest one-day decline in nearly two weeks as technology stocks came under renewed selling pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-stabilize-after-tech-led-dip-halts-year-end-rally-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ND2E66TCMFNWNL7RJVXL4TRR4M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:01:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国规定芯片制造商必须采用 50%的国产设备]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的人士表示，中国要求芯片制造商在增加新产能时至少使用 50%的国产设备，因为中国政府正在推动建立自给自足的半导体供应链。【原文：China is requiring chipmakers to use at least 50% domestically made equipment for adding new capacity, three people familiar with the matter said, as Beijing pushes to build a self-sufficient semiconductor supply chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-mandates-50-domestic-equipment-rule-chipmakers-sources-say-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWZU7DS6IBM3HP7ACT4QHX75LE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cleary Gottlieb 律师事务所聘请 Alsheimer 负责激进主义业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际律师事务所 Cleary Gottlieb Steen & Hamilton 聘请了一位业内资深人士来领导其股东激进主义辩护业务，因为越来越多的律师事务所正在增强能力，以保护面临公司煽动者的客户。【原文：International law firm Cleary Gottlieb Steen & Hamilton has hired an industry veteran to lead its shareholder activism defense practice as more law firms build out capabilities to protect clients facing corporate agitators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/law-firm-cleary-gottlieb-hires-alsheimer-activism-practice-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WU4HJELPUBOTZL6NVCG5Y3VEQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:45:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称三星获美国年度批准向中国出口芯片制造工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士透露，三星电子已获得美国政府颁发的年度许可证，可在 2026 年将芯片制造设备引入其在中国的工厂。【原文：Samsung Electronics has received an annual licence from the U.S. government to bring in chip manufacturing equipment to its facilities in China for 2026, a person familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/samsung-wins-us-annual-approval-chipmaking-tool-shipments-china-source-says-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFYCAQGCARI2LKLD55RZMJ2TNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市受科技股拖累走低，黄金白银降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市追随华尔街科技股的跌势而下滑，而白银和黄金则在从历史高位大幅回落后企稳，贵金属令人难以置信的涨势也随之消退。【原文：Asian shares slipped on Tuesday, tracking Wall Street's tech slump, while silver and gold steadied after a sharp pullback from record highs took some froth off the precious metals' incredible rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UOKEXKA5HNINFBFTE5N2VHTBMM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:34:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价小幅回落；投资者对俄乌紧张局势保持警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在上一交易日上涨超过2%后，周二早盘略有回落，部分原因是贵金属回落的溢出效应，即使俄乌紧张局势升级也使市场对供应中断的担忧难以消除。【原文：Oil prices retreated a touch early on Tuesday after rising more than 2% in the previous session, partly driven by spillover from a pullback in precious metals even as escalating Russia–Ukraine tensions left markets grappling with supply disruption fears.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-retreat-slightly-investors-wary-russiaukraine-tensions-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOKCCZAJ7RKVXE7J6GREF2G2Y4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:58:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元在美联储会议纪要前持稳，2025年惨淡收场]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储公布 12 月会议纪要报告之前，美元周二持稳，预计该报告将揭示央行内部对明年政策路径的分歧。【原文：The U.S. dollar was steady on Tuesday ahead of the Federal Reserve's release of its December minutes report, which is expected to reveal divisions inside the central bank about next year's policy pathway.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-steady-ahead-fed-minutes-sluggish-end-dismal-2025-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6PGHN42JBNH7FFSAYEWCNNVIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[六家中国 IPO 在香港首次公开募股，融资 9 亿美元，为今年的辉煌业绩画上圆满句号]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，六家中国公司在香港首次上市交易，共募集资金约 69.9 亿港元（9 亿美元），其中大多数公司的开盘价高于其首次公开募股价格，为今年在亚洲股票资本市场占据主导地位的上市热潮画上了圆满的句号。【原文：Six Chinese companies made their Hong Kong trading debuts on Tuesday after raising about HK$6.99 billion ($900 million), with most opening above their IPO prices, rounding off a resurgent year for listings as the city dominated Asian equity capital markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/six-china-ipos-debut-hong-kong-after-raising-900-mln-cap-banner-year-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHZ7MJRBV5LGFAHZHNBM6HEWUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[价格飙升引发新一代淘金者的澳大利亚淘金热]]></title><description><![CDATA[在澳大利亚历史悠久的金矿腹地，当维姬-普拉姆里奇（Vicki Plumridge）从土里挖出一块小金块时，她高兴得跳了起来。【原文：In the hinterlands of Australia's historic goldfields, Vicki Plumridge jumps for joy when she digs a small golden nugget out of the earth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/soaring-prices-spark-australia-gold-rush-new-generation-fortune-hunters-2025-12-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CKH2UCTX4RK6HEYM5ZP3637KDI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将收购中国初创公司 Manus 以增强先进的人工智能功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 公司周一表示，它将收购中国人工智能初创公司 Manus，因为这家科技巨头正加速在其平台上整合先进的人工智能。【原文：Meta said on Monday it would acquire Chinese artificial intelligence startup Manus, as the technology giant accelerates efforts to integrate advanced AI across its platforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/meta-acquire-chinese-startup-manus-boost-advanced-ai-features-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2IC6GAXWURMAVPWJLMEJ3SEITU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 23:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼宣布波音公司为以色列签订 86 亿美元的 F-15 喷气式战斗机合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在佛罗里达州会见以色列总理本雅明-内塔尼亚胡后，五角大楼周一表示，波音公司获得了一份价值86亿美元的F-15以色列项目合同。【原文：Boeing was given an $8.6 billion contract for the F-15 Israel Program, the Pentagon said on Monday, after U.S. President Donald Trump met Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in Florida.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/pentagon-announces-86-billion-boeing-contract-f-15-jets-israel-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UH55SENODJNE7OCYQLYL4QSPNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 23:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团董事会批准出售俄罗斯 AO 花旗银行，标榜亏损 12 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周一表示，其董事会已批准将其在俄罗斯的剩余业务 AO Citibank 出售给投资银行复兴资本的计划，此举将导致本季度税前亏损约 12 亿美元。【原文：Citigroup said on Monday its board has approved a plan to sell AO Citibank, its remaining business in Russia, to investment bank Renaissance Capital, a move that will result in a pre-tax loss of about $1.2 billion in the current quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/citigroup-board-approves-sale-russia-unit-ao-citibank-flags-12-billion-loss-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WA53X5S3J5NXZGNRUIQZFT2DPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 22:37:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[气象学家警告 "炸弹气旋 "来袭，冬季风暴 "艾萨拉 "阻断美国旅行]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，冬季风暴 "艾斯拉 "连续第三天扰乱了美国东北部、中西部和五大湖区的假日出行，造成数千次航班延误和数百次航班取消，航空公司争先恐后地恢复航班，气象学家警告说，酝酿中的 "炸弹气旋 "可能会在新年假期前进一步阻碍出行。【原文：Winter Storm Ezra disrupted holiday travel across the U.S. Northeast, Midwest and Great Lakes for a third straight day on Monday, causing thousands of flight delays and hundreds of cancellations as airlines scrambled to recover and meteorologists warned of a brewing "bomb cyclone" that could further snarl trips ahead of the New Year's holiday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/winter-storm-ezra-snarls-us-travel-meteorologists-warn-bomb-cyclone-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4AGY3OIEAVNL7DPBHHILIIPRQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行在年底压力下利用美联储流动性工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储的数据显示，周一美联储的一个重要隔夜流动性工具的使用量有所增加。【原文：A key Federal Reserve overnight liquidity facility saw increased use on Monday, data from the New York Fed showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/banks-tap-fed-liquidity-tool-amid-year-end-pressures-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVP26BDDIBJJNDUPCI6QGCADAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，英国章鱼能源公司接近出售克拉肯公司股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻（Sky News）援引消息人士的话报道，章鱼能源集团（Octopus Energy Group）即将出售其软件部门克拉肯科技公司（Kraken Technologies）的大量股份，这笔交易对该公司的估值将达到 90 亿至 100 亿美元。【原文：Octopus Energy Group is close to selling a significant stake in its software unit, Kraken Technologies, in a deal that would value the business at $9 billion to $10 billion, Sky News reported, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/uks-octopus-energy-nears-kraken-stake-sale-sky-news-reports-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWXAHHTILFLU5BYXR7ECK4VV6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:53:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道巴西大豆贸易公司将放弃亚马逊保护协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解此事的人士告诉路透社，世界上一些最大的大豆贸易商正准备打破他们达成的协议，停止砍伐亚马逊雨林，以维护巴西第一大农业州的税收优惠。【原文：Some of the world's largest soybean traders are preparing to break their agreement to curb deforestation of the Amazon rainforest to preserve tax benefits in Brazil's top farm state, two people with direct knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/soy-trading-firms-abandon-amazon-protection-pact-brazil-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDHOLU4E7JNPXL6OCR4NFHNLCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NAR 称美国 11 月成屋待售激增至近三年来最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国全国房地产经纪人协会（National Association of Realtors）周一表示，由于经济承受能力的改善吸引了大量买家，11 月份美国旧房购买合同出人意料地创下了近三年来的最高纪录。【原文：Contracts to purchase previously owned U.S. homes unexpectedly shot to the highest in nearly three years in November, as improving affordability conditions drew in buyers, the National Association of Realtors said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-pending-home-sales-surge-highest-nearly-3-years-november-nar-says-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWUZLQTITBJWTC76SLEGJZ6VNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[两家中国航空公司计划购买价值高达 82 亿美元的空客飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据证券交易所文件显示，中国春秋航空和吉祥航空周一分别宣布了购买30架和25架空客A320系列喷气机的计划。【原文：China's Spring Airlines and Juneyao Airlines on Monday announced plans to buy 30 and 25 Airbus A320-family jets respectively, according to stock exchange filings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/two-chinese-airlines-plan-airbus-jet-purchases-worth-up-82-billion-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMQSN2AHPVICTLCPQOKHIX3BEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Verisk pulls plug on $2.4 billion AccuLynx deal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Data analytics firm Verisk said on Monday it had pulled the plug on its planned $2.35 billion acquisition of roofing software maker AccuLynx.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/verisk-pulls-plug-24-billion-acculynx-deal-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Z3MG6LIDFMTBF6T5T4MFAZVZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:50:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德与礼来下调减肥药在中国的价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[据丹麦制药商和中国药品供应商称，诺和诺德公司和礼来公司正在降低其最畅销的肥胖症药物韦格威和蒙加罗在中国的价格。【原文：Novo Nordisk and Eli Lilly are lowering prices of their top-selling obesity drugs Wegovy and Mounjaro in China, according to the Danish drugmaker and Chinese drug suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-cuts-wegovy-prices-some-chinese-provinces-local-media-reports-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7GZB3EDFNMUPE5ERPVSJ2MECQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:51:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lululemon founder launches proxy fight for board changes, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lululemon Athletica's founder Chip Wilson has launched a proxy fight for a board shakeup, days after the apparel maker announced the exit of CEO Calvin McDonald, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/lululemon-founder-launches-proxy-fight-board-changes-wsj-reports-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOYQ7QWONVJJHL7CNBV4F4N62M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia takes $5 billion stake in Intel under September agreement]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia has purchased Intel shares worth $5 billion, the American semiconductor firm said in a filing on Monday, carrying out a transaction announced in September.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/nvidia-takes-5-billion-stake-intel-under-september-agreement-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5I4AZ7WQNOMJPUVWQBRGSRDHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026 年美国经济将面临重大税制变革]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家认为，特朗普的 "一个美丽的大法案 "中的减税措施是 2026 年美国经济的主要推动力，无论是对个人还是企业都是如此。以下是有关减税的一些细节。【原文：Economists see the tax cuts in Trump's One Big Beautiful Bill as a principal driver of the U.S. economy in 2026, both for individuals and businesses. Here's some detail about what's in store.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tax-changes-loom-large-us-economy-2026-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSI54JVFPZMDDFXZ3BH7HUQOIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货在上周反弹后走低，本周假期缩短]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周一下滑，在上周 S&amp;P 500 指数和道指创下收盘纪录新高后，本年度最后一个假期缩短的交易周以下跌拉开序幕。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Monday, kicking off the final holiday-shortened trading week of the year on a lower note, after the S&amp;P 500 and the Dow had closed at record highs last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-inch-lower-after-last-weeks-rally-holiday-shortened-week-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GV227PMVCZOM7HUM4VNXA5CI4I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[药片、TikTok 和减肥应用程序：GLP-1s 消费者驱动的未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果向医疗保健行业的高管们询问未来减肥药市场的情况，他们会打这样的比方：像流媒体视频会员一样按月订购 GLP-1 药物；通过智能手机应用程序管理剂量决定；像购买一双耐克鞋一样方便地获取药物。【原文：Ask executives in the healthcare industry about the future market for weight-loss drugs and the analogies are telling: monthly GLP-1 medicine subscriptions like a streaming video membership; dose decisions managed on a smartphone app; access made as easy as buying a pair of Nikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pills-tiktok-weight-loss-apps-consumer-driven-future-glp-1s-2025-12-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U63ESGM3ZFKR7HYZDA3Q3MVT5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>