<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:39:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:39:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[First Solar 上调年度销售展望，预计关税将导致价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[First Solar 周四上调了年度销售预期，因为这家美国太阳能电池板制造商预计，在对外国制造的电池板征收额外关税后，其产品价格将上涨。【原文：First Solar raised its annual sales forecast on Thursday, as the U.S. solar panel maker expects higher prices for its products following additional tariffs on foreign-made panels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/first-solar-raises-annual-sales-outlook-expects-higher-prices-due-tariffs-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DV232KTF7FKR5NIYFDZBC6DOCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:32:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[iPhone 销量飙升，苹果超出华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四公布的销售额和利润远超预期，这表明苹果公司为摆脱美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战而重新规划其庞大的全球供应链所做的努力迄今已取得成功。【原文：Apple on Thursday reported sales and profit that far surpassed expectations, showing that its efforts to re-route its sprawling global supply chain away from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war have so far succeeded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/apple-crushes-wall-street-expectations-iphone-sales-soar-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3CHOZO2HZMAZOZKRMB6NKSEB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得益于人工智能需求，Monolithic Power 预计第三季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，Monolithic Power Systems 预测第三季度营收将高于预期，该公司押注于人工智能生成推动数据中心扩张对其电源控制产品和半导体的强劲需求。【原文：Monolithic Power Systems forecast third-quarter revenue above estimates on Thursday, betting on strong demand for its power control products and semiconductors as generative artificial intelligence drives data center expansion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/monolithic-power-forecasts-third-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-ai-demand-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R27B655TWRNMXHFC7OUBNEZQVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:26:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[订阅收入增加，Coinbase 季度利润飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase Global 周四公布第二季度利润大幅增长，原因是其订阅和服务业务的收益抵消了交易收入的下滑。【原文：Coinbase Global reported a sharp rise in second-quarter profit on Thursday, as gains in its subscription and services business offset a dip in trading revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coinbase-quarterly-profit-jumps-subscription-revenue-boost-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJ4H5U4OY5OHNBQPVWDYAVY2PQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roku 第二季度营收超出预期，股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[受用户群扩大和广告销售的帮助，Roku 周四的第二季度营收超过了华尔街的预期，使其股价在盘后交易中上涨了 8%。【原文：Roku topped Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue on Thursday, helped by its expanding user base and advertising sales, sending its shares up 8% in trading after the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/roku-beats-second-quarter-revenue-estimates-shares-rise-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YK6KWMMKSRJQ7OG5GNJFALHBWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 预测人工智能驱动的广告力量将带来强劲收入，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit 周四预计第三季度营收将高于华尔街预期，押注于人工智能营销工具推动的数字广告业务增长，股价在盘后交易中上涨 9%。【原文：Reddit forecast third-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, betting on growing digital advertising driven by its artificial intelligence-powered marketing tools and sending its shares up 9% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/reddit-forecasts-strong-revenue-ai-driven-ad-strength-shares-surge-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KUNCF2ZYNMWDD77PODAQG2VQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路明缩小亏损，因节税而上调自由现金流预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[流明技术公司（Lumen Technologies）周四公布的第二季度亏损小于预期，并将全年自由现金流预期上调了 60% 以上，这得益于特朗普总统减税法案带来的成本节约。【原文：Lumen Technologies on Thursday reported a smaller-than-expected second-quarter loss and raised its full-year free cash flow forecast by more than 60%, helped by cost savings from President Trump's tax cut legislation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/lumen-narrows-loss-lifts-free-cash-flow-forecast-tax-savings-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HG7XWGOXQJMXXLYZBIJGIKHKZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司在出售给 Skydance 之前实现了盈利目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司（Paramount Global）周四公布的第二季度财报超过了华尔街的预期，该公司正在为出售给 Skydance Media 做准备。【原文：Paramount Global posted second-quarter earnings that exceeded Wall Street estimates on Thursday as the company prepares for a sale to Skydance Media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-global-beats-earnings-target-ahead-sale-skydance-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWJEUBWJKRKVZIQ2DVQNHWE7MA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:06:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊云计算业绩不佳，盘后股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周四预计第三季度销售额将高于市场预期，但在竞争对手大幅超出预期后，亚马逊网络服务（Amazon Web Services）云计算部门的业绩未能达到人们的高预期。【原文：Amazon.com forecast third-quarter sales above market estimates on Thursday but failed to live up to lofty expectations for its Amazon Web Services cloud computing unit after rivals handily beat expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-cloud-computing-results-fail-impress-shares-drop-after-hour-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXUYQK5NIBJCLIVIZ3EMOPW7H4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西企业对特朗普关税的反应既欣慰又怀疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三出人意料地公布了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普自8月6日起对巴西出口产品征收50%关税的近700个例外情况清单，巴西企业对此既感到欣慰又心存疑虑。【原文：Brazilian companies reacted with a mix of relief and doubt after the White House surprised them on Wednesday with a list of nearly 700 exceptions to the 50% tariff U.S. President Donald Trump imposed on the country's exports from August 6.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazilian-companies-react-trumps-tariffs-with-relief-doubt-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MDUUUNCPBONDMJBIS2MZU5BEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特朗普政府将扩大对美国稀土项目的价格支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位熟悉该计划的消息人士告诉路透社记者，白宫高层官员上周告诉一批稀土公司，他们正在推行一种大流行病时代的方法，通过保证稀土产品的最低价格来提高美国关键矿物的产量，并遏制中国的市场主导地位。【原文：Top White House officials told a group of rare earths firms last week that they are pursuing a pandemic-era approach to boost U.S. critical minerals production and curb China's market dominance by guaranteeing a minimum price for their products, five sources familiar with the plan told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/land-use-biodiversity/trump-administration-expand-price-support-us-rare-earths-projects-sources-say-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTTXLNHPCFIHNOHQNA2NO65G5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:48:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司向圣路易斯国防工人提供新合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国飞机制造商波音公司（Boeing）周四向代表波音国防部门约3200名工厂工人的工会发出了一份新的合同要约。【原文：U.S. planemaker Boeing sent a new contract offer on Thursday to the union representing roughly 3,200 factory workers at Boeing's defense division, mostly in the St. Louis area.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeing-makes-new-contract-offer-st-louis-defense-workers-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5ZE73K4FRKMFIKAUJS2TF47AE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:47:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，Blackstone 成为收购 Enverus 的领跑者]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，Blackstone Inc 已成为收购能源数据提供商 Enverus 的领跑者，该公司目前由一家竞争对手私募股权投资公司所有。【原文：Blackstone Inc has emerged as the frontrunner to buy energy-focused data provider Enverus, which is currently owned by a rival private equity firm, sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/blackstone-emerges-frontrunner-buy-enverus-sources-say-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ESVBMLUUAFKJXLQLRVOIBXZWUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普向 17 位制药公司首席执行官施压，要求降低美国药品价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普致信 17 家主要制药公司的首席执行官，敦促他们立即采取行动降低美国人的处方药成本。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump sent letters to the chief executives of 17 major pharmaceutical companies, urging immediate action to lower the cost of prescription drugs for Americans, the White House said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-pressures-17-pharma-ceos-cut-us-drug-prices-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TN5QKOJHGJNW3NUO4VREH66YTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:28:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普希望的美联储降息之路可能涉及更高的失业率]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统可能会将降低美联储利率视为解决两个政治难题的办法，即偿还 36 万亿美元政府债务的成本和高昂的购房成本，但这条道路可能会触及民选官员通常试图避免的第三条轨道--失业率上升。【原文：President Donald Trump may see lower Federal Reserve interest rates as a fix for two politically potent problems, the cost of servicing $36 trillion in government debt and the high cost of home ownership, but the path there may touch a third rail elected officials typically try to avoid - rising unemployment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/path-fed-rate-cuts-trump-wants-may-involve-higher-unemployment-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6LEGV2IBVPLRA4VDJQBG4FU2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:06:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，激进分子 Carronade 推动拆分 Viasat，称估值可能跃升 500]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引知情人士的话报道称，激进投资者 Carronade Capital Management 正敦促 Viasat 分拆其宽带和国防部门。【原文：Activist investor Carronade Capital Management is urging Viasat to split its broadband and defense units, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/activist-carronade-pushes-viasat-breakup-says-valuation-could-jump-500-ft-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMZWI6WIUROBTE65R2Y3WDFVUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在提高关税的最后期限即将到来之际，特朗普给予墨西哥 90 天关税暂缓期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）给予墨西哥 90 天的暂缓征收更高关税的时间，以便就更广泛的贸易协议进行谈判，但随着周五协议最后期限的临近，预计他将对大多数其他国家发布更高的最终税率。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump gave Mexico a 90-day reprieve from higher tariffs to negotiate a broader trade deal but was expected to issue higher final duty rates for most other countries as the clock wound down on his Friday deal deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-gives-mexico-90-day-tariff-reprieve-deadline-higher-duties-looms-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTZ2SZTHVBJONLFS2CM2DNHMMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:45:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber 称一些性侵指控者提交了假收据]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步表示，它发现了 100 多起声称其司机对其进行性侵犯或骚扰的乘客提供假收据或篡改收据以证明乘车情况，或不解释其无法提供收据的情况。【原文：Uber said it found more than 100 instances in which passengers who claimed its drivers sexually assaulted or harassed them offered bogus or doctored receipts to prove ridership, or did not explain their inability to provide receipts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uber-says-some-sexual-assault-accusers-submitted-fake-receipts-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYRCXNDPTVIJLMQ4UOBHLJDZNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:30:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党参议员提出新的保障措施，以保持 TikTok 的在线状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员埃德-马基（Ed Markey）周四提出了新的国家安全保障措施，以确保 TikTok 能够继续在线，因为这款有 1.7 亿美国人使用的短视频应用程序的命运仍不明朗。【原文：Democratic Senator Ed Markey on Thursday proposed new national security safeguards that would ensure TikTok could remain online as the fate of the short video app used by 170 million Americans remains uncertain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/democratic-senator-proposes-new-safeguards-keep-tiktok-online-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7LV7IV2BFOU7BPXFAMRIP5CQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:22:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西银行争相了解美国对最高法院法官的制裁范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对最高法院的一位法官实施了全面制裁，该法官负责监督对唐纳德-特朗普总统的一位盟友进行的刑事审判，巴西的银行正在争先恐后地评估这一制裁对国内造成的影响，法律团队正在权衡在经济上孤立这位法官的举动会如何波及巴西的金融体系。【原文：Brazilian banks are scrambling to assess the domestic fallout from sweeping U.S. sanctions against a Supreme Court justice who oversees a criminal trial against an ally of President Donald Trump, as legal teams weigh how the move to isolate the judge financially could ripple through Brazil's financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/brazilian-banks-scramble-understand-scope-us-sanctions-supreme-court-justice-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CGYSOJWD5BNN5GS6D4K7IDMFOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:13:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴姆勒卡车公司因北美市场疲软而下调主要利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于 "北美市场持续疲软"，全球最大的卡车制造商之一戴姆勒卡车公司（Daimler Truck）周四下调了2025年的关键利润预期，这是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对进口商品征收关税之际，戴姆勒卡车公司发出的最新警告。【原文：Daimler Truck , one of the world's biggest truckmakers, on Thursday slashed a key profit forecast for 2025 due to "continuous market weakness in North America", the latest warning from industry as U.S. President Donald Trump imposes tariffs on imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/daimler-truck-slashes-key-profit-forecast-north-america-weakness-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5AKX7AKTJPQ3BF26SZ6CLDATA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券监管机构提出适应加密货币的全面计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券监管机构负责人周四公布了全面改革资本市场监管的计划，以适应加密货币和基于区块链的交易，这对长期以来一直推动定制规则的数字资产行业来说是一个重大胜利。【原文：The head of the U.S. securities regulator unveiled sweeping plans to overhaul capital markets regulations on Thursday to accommodate cryptocurrencies and blockchain-based trading, in a major win for the digital asset industry, which has long pushed for tailored rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-securities-regulator-lays-out-sweeping-plans-accommodate-crypto-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YJW24IPRBPG3DNMS5QJBFBIT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[申博姆称墨西哥获得新的关税缓期，90 天内达成贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆周四表示，她在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的通话中争取到了暂停新关税生效和90天的贸易协议谈判期。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Thursday that she secured a pause on new tariffs coming into effect and a 90-day period to work on a trade deal in a call with U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/sheinbaum-says-mexico-secures-new-tariff-reprieve-90-days-strike-trade-deal-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GK6HZ2B5VFLL3PGBJ5A7FDIUZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:55:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 Epic Games 案中，谷歌就应用商店改革提出的上诉败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周四未能说服美国上诉委员会推翻陪审团的裁决和联邦法院要求该科技巨头改造其应用程序商店 Play 的命令。【原文：Alphabet’s Google on Thursday failed to persuade a U.S. appeals panel to overturn a jury verdict and federal court order requiring the technology giant to revamp its app store Play.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/google-loses-appeal-over-app-store-reforms-epic-games-case-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6W3PRUMX3FLJBK7SXAM4STWDHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:50:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软称俄罗斯安全局在网络间谍活动中以外国驻莫斯科使馆为目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司周四表示，俄罗斯政府的一个主要网络间谍单位正在利用当地的互联网服务提供商部署恶意软件，攻击驻莫斯科的使馆和外交机构。【原文：One of the Russian government’s premier cyber espionage units is deploying malware against embassies and diplomatic organizations in Moscow by leveraging local internet service providers, Microsoft said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/russias-fsb-targets-foreign-embassies-moscow-cyber-espionage-campaign-microsoft-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISBIGOI2NVJSJMFN2CUODOF2MI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:25:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院最高民主党人批评联合太平洋公司收购诺福克南方公司的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院民主党领袖查克-舒默（Chuck Schumer）批评联合太平洋公司（Union Pacific）计划以 850 亿美元的交易价格收购诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern），从而创建美国首家海岸至海岸货运铁路运营商。【原文：Senate Democratic Leader Chuck Schumer criticized Union Pacific's plan to acquire Norfolk Southern in a $85 billion deal to create the first U.S. coast-to-coast freight rail operator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/top-senate-democrat-criticizes-union-pacific-deal-buy-norfolk-southern-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHNH7ZZWYRL6FPSG62UTD57CSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:13:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，约 15.4 万名联邦工作人员接受了特朗普政府的买断提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士周四表示，今年约有15.4万名联邦雇员接受了特朗普政府提供的买断服务，这是为精简联邦员工队伍而采取的更广泛措施的一部分。【原文：Roughly 154,000 federal employees have taken buyouts offered by the Trump administration this year, part of a broader push to slim the federal workforce, a person familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/about-154000-federal-workers-took-trump-administrations-buyout-offers-source-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLJCLWZ7HBLOBGAKFV6BUIDBMU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CK Hutchison- 经营的巴拿马港口可能由国家合伙接管，总统说]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马总统何塞-劳尔-穆利诺（Jose Raul Mulino）周四表示，如果法院宣布与香港长江和记黄埔签订的运营巴拿马运河附近两个重要港口的合同无效，那么公私合营企业将接管这两个港口。【原文：Public-private partnerships could take over two key ports near the Panama Canal if courts invalidate a contract with Hong Kong-based CK Hutchison's to operate them, Panama's President Jose Raul Mulino said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ck-hutchison-operated-panama-ports-could-be-taken-over-by-state-partnerships-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLN2IZHIMZJDZDCKWSFPBU2H6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国停止减免包裹税威胁 eBay 和 Etsy 交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[下个月，在 eBay 和 Etsy 等平台上购买二手、古董或手工制品的美国人将面临高额的国际购物关税，这可能会损害这些点对点网站的贸易。【原文：Americans shopping for secondhand, vintage or handmade items on platforms like eBay and Etsy face steep customs duties on international purchases next month, potentially hurting trade on those peer-to-peer sites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-end-parcel-tax-relief-threatens-ebay-etsy-trade-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKKCGFAGXNK7FKQ2V2ILBTQO2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称埃克森、雪佛龙利润将降至大流行病以来最低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于石油和天然气价格下跌导致收入减少，美国顶级石油生产商埃克森美孚（Exxon Mobil）和雪佛龙（Chevron）周五发布的第二季度财报预计将创下四年来的最低收益。【原文：Top U.S. oil producers Exxon Mobil and Chevron are expected to report their lowest earnings in four years when they release second-quarter results on Friday, as weaker oil and gas prices slashed revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-chevron-profits-drop-lowest-point-since-pandemic-analysts-say-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRG3FYF27VKJ5H6IR3UQELV35I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>