<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:35:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:35:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Global defensive sector funds see surge in inflows on slowdown fears]]></title><description><![CDATA[Global defensive sector funds are in demand from investors as concerns about a slowdown in the U.S. economy forces them to seek assets such as consumer staples and utilities stocks that can withstand weakness in labour markets and commodities.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-sectors-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H73L7O7PEFKNVJQJMUTXLXPMBA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:57:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Express Scripts sues FTC over drug pricing report, court documents show]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pharmacy benefit manager Express Scripts has sued the U.S. Federal Trade Commission over the regulator's recent drug pricing report, asking a court to force the agency to withdraw its findings, according to court documents filed on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/express-scripts-sues-ftc-over-drug-pricing-report-court-documents-show-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD5ZSJPYSBKZJE6M3I6BBAZ5EI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:46:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Futures inch up ahead of economic data, Fed's rate-cut decision]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. stock index futures edged higher as investors awaited a batch of economic data and clung to hopes the Federal Reserve would deliver a supersized interest-rate cut at its monetary policy meeting, which starts on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-inch-up-ahead-economic-data-feds-rate-cut-decision-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WT2WPZHSM5IPTOP6K6VZ7YXHBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:25:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big Tech, calls for looser rules await new EU antitrust chief]]></title><description><![CDATA[Teresa Ribera will have to square up to Big Tech, banks and airlines if confirmed as Europe's new antitrust chief, while juggling calls for looser rules to help create EU champions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/big-tech-calls-looser-rules-await-new-eu-antitrust-chief-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUWKF6D2YZPHRNZG5YIKTQSJLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:23:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMERICAS New highs, rotation as Fed meets with retail healthcheck]]></title><description><![CDATA[A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIVTB2OORRLVRDNFHHT67GBJBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ignoring risk, investors still buying US junk debt with weak protections]]></title><description><![CDATA[When U.S.-based construction material supplier Wilsonart issued a junk bond to raise $500 million to fund an acquisition this summer, a research firm warned potential investors that the terms of the deal offered them weak protections.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ignoring-risk-investors-still-buying-us-junk-debt-with-weak-protections-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BPYBOZAWFKPVLY73GMYTKPLSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kroger-Albertson's US anti-trust trial to end but other legal blocks loom]]></title><description><![CDATA[The trial where U.S. anti-trust regulators made their case to block Kroger's $25 billion bid to buy rival grocer Albertsons will conclude on Tuesday, but the deal's legal challenges have just begun, with two more trials this month to hear complaints the merger could jack up grocery bills.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/kroger-albertsons-us-anti-trust-trial-end-other-legal-blocks-loom-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WR7KYYC3NJMZAODRI7XV2JS4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: US retailer holiday hiring set to be lower than last year]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. retailers will hire fewer seasonal workers this holiday season than last year due to a softer labor market and tighter consumer spending heading into the crucial shopping period, according to a report by Challenger, Gray &amp; Christmas provided exclusively to Reuters.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-retailer-holiday-hiring-set-be-lower-than-last-year-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BMQSVRZCBPR7P5KKNFXK6636E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed rate cut uncertainties rattle balance sheet outlook]]></title><description><![CDATA[Uncertainty over the size of an initial interest rate cut expected Wednesday from the Federal Reserve has sparked a related debate over the possibility of an accelerated halt to the central bank’s balance sheet drawdown.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-rate-cut-uncertainties-rattle-balance-sheet-outlook-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23YFLA5G55KDNIG4V4VBYTZ2JU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bond investors debate recession risks with Fed easing finally at hand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bond investors are more cautious and divided over prospects for recession in the world's largest economy with the Federal Reserve poised to cut interest rates on Wednesday for the first time in more than four years.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bond-investors-debate-recession-risks-with-fed-easing-finally-hand-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHVGM4RD5RNYXKIDVO5JBHOP6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Boeing, union negotiators to meet as striking workers dig in]]></title><description><![CDATA[Negotiators at Boeing and its largest union are due to resume talks over a labor contract on Tuesday, as the planemaker seeks to bring a swift end to a strike that is costing the indebted company an estimated $100 million a day.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-union-negotiators-meet-striking-workers-dig-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSWREA2JLFLTHIZGQEZTSDVKFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者担忧墨西哥司法改革，机遇也随之而来]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥的司法改革引发了投资者对法治和政府机构实力不确定性的担忧，但随着改革价格的确定，一些分析师认为可能会出现买入机会。【原文：Mexico's judicial reform has triggered investor concerns about uncertainty over the rule of law and the strength of the government's institutions, yet with the reform now priced in, some analysts argue there may be buying opportunities forming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-judicial-reform-stokes-investor-fears-though-some-analysts-bullish-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RPSD3TI2TZNYHMQ3NFNKXYGUMU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究称，2023 年美国太阳能就业岗位将增加 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[据非营利性机构州际可再生能源委员会周一公布的一项名为 "全国太阳能就业普查 "的年度研究显示，去年美国太阳能行业的就业岗位增加了6%，达到近28万个，为历史最高水平。【原文：U.S. solar industry jobs rose 6% last year to nearly 280,000, their highest level ever, according to an annual study known as the National Solar Jobs Census published on Monday by the nonprofit Interstate Renewable Energy Council.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-solar-jobs-rise-6-2023-study-says-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LV57P6TI75NMBKR5N3NQ423B6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国卡特尔办公室表示，撤销超级 RTL 和尼克频道的合并计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国卡特尔办公室周二表示，德国广播公司 RTL 和派拉蒙已撤回将儿童电视网 Super RTL 与 Nickelodeon 合并的申请。【原文：German broadcaster RTL and Paramount have withdrawn their bid to merge Super RTL, a children's television network, with Nickelodeon, said the German cartel office on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/planned-merger-super-rtl-nickelodeon-withdrawn-says-german-cartel-office-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUKC2H3N3FMUBH5POH5HPVX3IE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 08:48:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国肖尔茨：英特尔承诺在德国建厂，尽管时间有所延迟]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理奥拉夫-肖尔茨（Olaf Scholz）周二表示，尽管美国芯片制造商英特尔（Intel）宣布采取节约成本的措施，将其在德国东部建厂的计划推迟两年，但英特尔仍将坚持这一计划。【原文：German Chancellor Olaf Scholz said on Tuesday that Intel is committed to its plan to build plants in eastern Germany despite the U.S. chipmaker's announcement that it is delaying construction by two years amid cost-saving measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/germanys-scholz-intel-committed-german-site-despite-delay-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XC3NQQWE5RLQ7LUOUEAHULB5EQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 08:34:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行调查显示，9 月降息热提振投资者情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周二公布的一项对基金经理的调查显示，由于对美国经济软着陆和美联储降息的乐观预期，9月份全球投资者情绪出现了自6月份以来的首次好转。【原文：Global investor sentiment improved in September for the first time since June on optimism over a soft landing and interest rate cuts by the U.S. Federal Reserve, a BofA survey of fund mangers published on Tuesday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/rate-cut-fever-boosts-investor-sentiment-september-bofa-survey-shows-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADQTQBKMMZIWXEF7WKUJPZNIZU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 07:11:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[到 2028 年，UMG 调整后的复合核心利润增长率将超过 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰勒-斯威夫特（Taylor Swift）所在的音乐厂牌环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）预计，到 2028 年，其调整后未计利息、税项、折旧及摊销前利润（EBITDA）的复合年增长率（CAGR）将超过 10%。【原文：Music label Universal Music Group , home to Taylor Swift, expects a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) in its adjusted earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation and amortisation (EBITDA) of more than 10% through 2028.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/umg-sees-adjusted-compound-core-profit-growth-more-than-10-through-2028-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6WBPFOMAVIOLCG5F4I6YXBT3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 07:07:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flutter 以 26 亿美元收购 Snaitech，押注意大利博彩市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Flutter Entertainment 周二表示，它将以 23 亿欧元（26 亿美元）的价格收购 Snaitech，其中包括赌博技术集团 Playtech 的债务，从而巩固其作为意大利领先赌博公司的地位。【原文：Flutter Entertainment said on Tuesday it would buy Snaitech for 2.3 billion euros ($2.6 billion) including debt from gambling technology group Playtech , cementing its position as the leading gambling firm in Italy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/uks-playtech-sell-italian-unit-flutter-256-bln-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36UIFECRVNKMPFKXOMLKUTNLBA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:10:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EssilorLuxottica 与 Meta 拓展智能眼镜合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[依视路公司（EssilorLuxottica）周二表示，将扩大与 Meta Platforms 公司的长期合作关系，在下一个十年继续开发智能眼镜。【原文：EssilorLuxottica said on Tuesday it will extend its long-standing partnership with Meta Platforms to continue the development of smart eyewear into the next decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/essilorluxottica-expands-smart-glasses-partnership-with-meta-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSIA3GTUDZJSZC3J34WLCE2UPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:51:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价日元的重要一周开始了]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTGW3QXPJ5JZ7DFOJJYOBQKS4M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:34:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度尼西亚 8 月份贸易顺差超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼官方数据周二显示，由于进出口超出预期，印尼8月份贸易顺差超过预期。【原文：Indonesia booked a bigger-than-expected trade surplus in August as exports and imports beat forecasts, official data showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/indonesias-trade-surplus-beat-forecast-aug-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UCBF2CDERMMXBCKQ42QFONWCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，美国和日本即将达成遏制向中国出口芯片技术的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周二援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，尽管东京方面对中国政府威胁报复日本公司感到震惊，但美国和日本仍接近达成一项协议，以遏制对中国芯片业的技术出口。【原文：The United States and Japan are close to a deal to curb tech exports to China's chip industry despite alarm in Tokyo about Beijing's threat to retaliate against Japanese companies, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-japan-near-deal-curb-chip-technology-exports-china-ft-reports-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4F7ZBBOWRNLBARB7CU7V7UGKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:22:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五角大楼向火箭发动机制造商 Ursa Major 颁发 1250 万美元奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国火箭推进器初创公司Ursa Major周二表示，该公司获得了一份价值1250万美元的合同，用于新型固体燃料火箭发动机的生产和测试。【原文：U.S. rocket propulsion startup Ursa Major said on Tuesday it was awarded a $12.5 million contract to build out production and testing for new solid fuel rocket engines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/pentagon-awards-rocket-motor-maker-ursa-major-125-million-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOULIGYLHBO6RDTKW4AD7YO3NE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:14:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，驾驶员在使用部分自动化技术时更容易分心]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二的一项新研究表明，在使用部分自动化系统时，驾驶员更有可能从事非驾驶活动，如查看手机或吃三明治，有些驾驶员很容易绕过限制分心的规定。【原文：Drivers are more likely to engage in non-driving activities, such as checking their phones or eating a sandwich, when using partial automation systems, with some easily skirting rules set to limit distractions, new research showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/drivers-more-likely-be-distracted-while-using-partial-automation-tech-study-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJKZ3NNTSJNI7P73TFTCJHQ4LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，中央银行数字货币的发展势头日益强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前共有 134 个国家（占全球经济总量的 98%）正在探索本国货币的数字版本，其中近一半国家处于高级阶段，而中国、巴哈马和尼日利亚等先驱国家的使用率已开始回升。【原文：A total of 134 countries representing 98% of the global economy are now exploring digital versions of their currencies, with almost half at an advanced stage and pioneers like China, the Bahamas and Nigeria starting to see a pick up in usage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/central-bank-digital-currency-momentum-growing-study-shows-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPPMZPLNUNKATFYD44H4RMT4XA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美的集团以 40 亿美元在香港上市，股价上涨 9.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国家电制造商美的集团周二在香港首次上市交易中上涨达 9.5%，此前该公司在香港进行了近四年来最大规模的股票发行，募集资金近 40 亿美元，为中国大型股票发行的复苏带来了希望。【原文：Chinese home appliances maker Midea Group rose by up to 9.5% on its trading debut in Hong Kong on Tuesday after raising nearly $4 billion in the city's largest share offering in almost four years, bolstering hopes for a revival in large Chinese issuances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/midea-group-shares-rise-95-hong-kong-after-4-bln-listing-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQG72RARK5I7NJGNBQAXDCBQN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在加密货币业务揭幕仪式上提供的细节不多]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一对共和党前总统、其家人和同事在 X Spaces 直播活动中公布的新加密货币业务提供了很少的细节。【原文：Donald Trump on Monday offered few details about a new cryptocurrency business that the Republican former president, his family and associates unveiled in a live event on X Spaces.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-offers-little-detail-crypto-business-unveiling-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MP5ILZZOZZPONJJN5A56NX2O7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本财务大臣称，Seven & i 的新 "核心 "标签并未提高收购门槛]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣铃木俊一周二表示，日本零售巨头 Seven &amp; i 控股公司作为国家安全 "核心 "企业的新地位不会对潜在收购造成额外障碍。【原文：Finance Minister Shunichi Suzuki said on Tuesday that Japanese retail giant Seven &amp; i Holdings' new status as a company "core" to national security would not raise additional hurdles to a potential buyout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japan-finance-minister-says-seven-is-new-core-tag-doesnt-raise-bar-buyout-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AE2QUKX7C5PCDMIFU6K2ZZB6ZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 02:27:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国产量令人担忧，库存预期下降，石油涨势扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周二延续涨势，原因是市场对飓风弗朗辛过后美国产量的担忧，以及对美国原油库存减少的预期。【原文：Oil prices extended gains on Tuesday as the market eyed U.S. output concerns in the aftermath of Hurricane Francine and expectations of lower U.S. crude stockpiles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-extends-gains-us-output-concerns-expected-drop-stockpiles-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3Y4XEM6RBJRNLUZP2COQRHRXU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市试探性上涨；美元和收益率因美联储减息押注过大而受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市震荡，美元和美国国债收益率承压，此时距离美联储宽松周期的预期启动仅有一天时间，决策者可能会大幅降息。【原文：Asian stocks wobbled on Tuesday while the dollar and U.S. Treasury yields came under pressure, with just a day to go before the expected start of the Federal Reserve's easing cycle that could see policymakers deliver an outsized rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEIDAEY6QNIEHKL7TJKYFQPBTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:31:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>