<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:05:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:05:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国比亚迪为供应商设定可协商的降价目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[比亚迪一位高管在社交媒体平台微博上发布的帖子显示，中国汽车制造商比亚迪为大规模采购的供应商设定了可协商的降价目标。【原文：Chinese automaker BYD has set negotiable price reduction targets for suppliers of large-scale purchases, a BYD executive's post on social media platform Weibo shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-byd-sets-negotiable-price-reduction-targets-suppliers-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPN3QNFH45JUZEVQQN2ZBUVTJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 04:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鸟击后 FAA 将不要求立即对 737 MAX 发动机采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周二表示，在西南航空公司（Southwest Airlines）的飞机于 2023 年发生两起鸟击事件后，美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）在召集了一个审查委员会审议对波音 737 MAX 发动机的担忧后，不会要求立即采取任何行动。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said on Tuesday it will not require any immediate action after convening a review board to consider concerns about Boeing 737 MAX engines after two bird strike incidents on Southwest Airlines planes in 2023.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-will-not-require-immediate-737-max-engine-action-after-bird-strikes-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CD2MV5X3PNN7ZAY325XEFZJV6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 04:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税忧虑引发亚洲股市疲软；日元坚挺]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收新关税一天后，投资者对即将上任的美国总统特朗普可能会对哪些国家征收关税感到担忧，亚洲股市周三大幅下挫。【原文：Asian stocks were heavy on Wednesday as investors fretted over what countries could be targeted for tariffs under incoming U.S. President Donald Trump, a day after he pledged new levies on Canada, Mexico and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWIANWFZK5NONLRY2QEJT5BMNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 03:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾富士康称全球制造业布局使其免受特朗普关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾富士康周三表示，预计美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普征收新关税的影响将小于其竞争对手，理由是富士康的生产足迹遍布全球。【原文：Taiwan’s Foxconn said on Wednesday it expects any impact of new tariffs from U.S. President-elect Donald Trump to hit it less than its rivals, citing its global manufacturing footprint.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/taiwans-foxconn-says-global-manufacturing-footprint-shield-it-trumps-tariffs-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WMP3QUDNZPRPMLY4IE74SJVKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 03:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南总理希望美国承认越南的市场经济地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南总理范明正周三在一次商业峰会上表示，他希望美国承认越南为市场经济国家，并指出其他 70 多个国家已经承认越南为市场经济国家。【原文：Vietnam's Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh told a business summit on Wednesday that he hoped the United States would recognise Vietnam as a market economy, noting that more than 70 other countries already did.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/vietnam-pm-hopes-us-will-recognise-country-market-economy-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GT4MCXMLNOGRDZ5OKIYV2JWIQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 02:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车将回购价值 7.16 亿美元的股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车在周三提交的一份监管文件中称，该公司将从周四开始回购价值 1 万亿韩元（7.1579 亿美元）的股票，为期三个月。【原文：Hyundai Motor will buy back 1 trillion won ($715.79 million) worth of shares starting on Thursday over three months, the company said in a regulatory filing on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-buy-back-716-mln-worth-shares-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJADIFUNSFK2JDMYSWDXPXJ33Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 02:39:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 10 月工业利润降幅收窄，但需求依然疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的官方数据显示，受上年同期基数较低的影响，中国 10 月份工业利润降幅收窄，但由于经济仍在与需求疲软和通货紧缩压力作斗争，盈利方面的不利因素依然严峻。【原文：China's October industrial profits narrowed their earlier declines, helped by a low base the previous year, official data showed on Wednesday, but headwinds on earnings remain stiff with the economy still battling weak demand and deflation pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-oct-industrial-profits-extend-decline-weak-demand-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQXR236QUZNOPDSXZEB3V7UDEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 02:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关注以色列-真主党停火和欧佩克+政策，油价保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三早盘，油价趋于稳定，市场正在评估以色列与真主党之间达成停火协议的潜在影响，并将于周日召开欧佩克+会议。【原文：Oil prices steadied in early trade on Wednesday, with markets assessing the potential impact of a ceasefire deal between Israel and Hezbollah, and ahead of Sunday's OPEC+ meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-steady-amid-focus-israel-hezbollah-ceasefire-opec-policy-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJ2LPUPLBNIXFEWOP7Q5TBHBAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:58:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国营媒体驳斥特朗普关税誓言，关注芬太尼问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二晚些时候，中国国家媒体在社论中对美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺对中国商品征收额外关税撇清责任，指责这位前总统将中国未能解决芬太尼危机归咎于中国。【原文：China's state media shrugged off U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's pledge to slap additional tariffs on Chinese goods in editorials late on Tuesday, accusing the former president of blaming China for the country's failure to address the fentanyl crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/china-state-media-dismiss-trumps-tariff-vow-focus-fentanyl-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5TWDEDUUJJYDNP2F5GZYJTCEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰将现金利率下调 50 个基点，进一步放宽政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰央行周三将现金利率下调50个基点至4.25%，原因是年通胀率接近其目标区间2%的中点，且经济活动依然低迷。【原文：New Zealand's central bank cut the cash rate by 50 basis points to 4.25% on Wednesday, as annual inflation ran near the 2% midpoint of its target range and economic activity remained subdued.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/new-zealand-cuts-cash-rate-by-50-bps-flags-further-cuts-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5OSP4P4PNJURJTMMN442OEFZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：中国恒大投资者慎重抗议，要求采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，数百名在中国恒大倒闭事件中损失了积蓄的中国投资者本月发起了一场协调运动，要求当局提供这家倒闭房地产开发商的最新情况。【原文：Hundreds of Chinese investors who lost savings in the collapse of China Evergrande launched a coordinated campaign this month to press authorities for an update on the failed property developer, according to people with knowledge of the effort.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/careful-protest-china-evergrandes-investors-press-action-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVW52P4YNZNYVHEWT65J4VYA5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:26:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主要货币盘整，市场在美国通胀数据公布前重整旗鼓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元兑主要货币汇率持稳，投资者继续评估当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税承诺，同时关注当天晚些时候公布的美国关键通胀数据。【原文：The U.S. dollar steadied against major peers on Wednesday as investors continued to take stock of President-elect Donald Trump's tariff pledges, while keeping an eye on a key inflation figure out of the U.S. later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/major-currencies-consolidate-market-regroups-ahead-us-inflation-measure-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AKORQFMKFMKNK5SKBKHIGPXCQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提议的关税可能如何影响大宗商品和能源]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周一承诺对美国的三大贸易伙伴--加拿大、墨西哥和中国--征收关税。拟议的关税将影响包括石油、天然气、农业和制造业在内的众多行业，有可能改变长期以来形成的贸易模式和供应链。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump on Monday pledged tariffs on the United States' three largest trading partners - Canada, Mexico and China. The proposed tariffs would affect a wide range of industries, including oil, natural gas, agriculture and manufacturing, potentially altering long-established trade patterns and supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/how-trumps-proposed-tariffs-might-affect-commodities-energy-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GTILIN7GNJF7D4GZOZITIFGHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 01:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚参议院委员会支持禁止儿童使用社交媒体的法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚参议院的一个委员会支持一项禁止 16 岁以下儿童使用社交媒体的法案，但表示社交媒体平台不应强迫用户提交护照和其他数字身份证明等个人数据来证明自己的年龄。【原文：An Australian Senate committee has backed a bill that would ban social media for children under 16 but said social media platforms should not force users to submit personal data such as passport and other digital identification to prove their age.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/australia-senate-committee-backs-bill-ban-social-media-children-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWURRCT5Z5KH5AVW5HX5VQFD6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 23:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普任命贾米森-格里尔为美国贸易代表，加强关税计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周二选择了贸易律师杰米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）担任他的新任美国贸易代表，提升了他在第一任期对华贸易战中的一位重要老将，以执行有望颠覆全球贸易的全面关税议程。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump on Tuesday chose trade lawyer Jamieson Greer as his new U.S. trade representative, elevating a key veteran of his first-term trade war against China to execute a sweeping tariff agenda that promises to upend global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-name-jamieson-greer-us-trade-representative-bloomberg-reports-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQB7SOJM4ZIJ3LNOSDTOZ7OVQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 23:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联航称 FAA 人员短缺导致纽瓦克枢纽严重混乱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周二表示，空中交通管制员的严重短缺对纽约市外繁忙的新泽西州纽瓦克枢纽的旅客造成了 "重大干扰"。【原文：United Airlines said on Tuesday that an acute shortage of air traffic controllers was causing "significant disruption" for travelers at its busy Newark, New Jersey, hub outside of New York City.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-says-faa-staffing-shortages-causing-significant-disruption-newark-hub-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XICRYWNOXZMNDKVIMEMY7O4L6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 23:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价特朗普关税承诺激荡货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-pix-graphic-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EJUUCYTBROOHDBFDPAS6PNQQ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:49:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储部分决策者对降低隔夜回购利率持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储最近一次会议的纪要显示，一些美联储决策者认为可能很快就会降低银行和货币市场基金存放在美联储的资金利率，使其再次与政策利率区间的底部相匹配。【原文：Some Federal Reserve policymakers believe it may soon be time to lower the rate on funds that banks and money market funds park at the Fed, minutes from the Fed's most recent meeting indicated, so that it once again matches the bottom of the range of the policy rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/some-fed-policymakers-open-lowering-overnight-repo-rate-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WF3OSQZGVNY7D7GEMNFFWYVPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:38:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠普预测第一季度利润低于预期，原因是个人电脑市场需求低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠普公司周二预测其第一季度利润低于华尔街预期，表明个人电脑市场需求持续低迷，公司股价在盘后交易中下跌了 8.4%。【原文：HP forecast its first-quarter profit below Wall Street expectations on Tuesday, signaling persistent choppy demand in the personal computers market and sending the company's shares down 8.4% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/hp-forecasts-q1-profit-below-estimates-sluggish-demand-pc-market-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JF2IFV6RWJMZZD5TQRTSBWIAAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:23:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺德斯特龙（Nordstrom）季度业绩超出预期，打破百货公司需求疲软的趋势]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺德斯特龙百货公司（Nordstrom）周二公布的第三季度营收和利润均超出预期，这主要得益于其百货公司对 On Running、Hoka 和 Vuori 等流行品牌的需求上升。【原文：Nordstrom beat third-quarter revenue and profit estimates on Tuesday, helped by rising demand for popular brands including On Running, Hoka and Vuori at its department stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nordstrom-beats-quarterly-estimates-breaking-weak-demand-trend-department-stores-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2R7XCO45NKH3IGLAVDPRTFZ6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:12:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴尔第三季度营收因个人电脑疲软而不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，戴尔科技公司第三季度营收不及华尔街预期，受传统 PC 需求疲软和竞争对手服务器制造商激烈竞争的影响。【原文：Dell Technologies missed Wall Street expectations for third-quarter revenue on Tuesday, weighed down by weaker demand for its traditional PCs and stiff competition from rival server makers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/dells-third-quarter-revenue-misses-pc-weakness-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TTCN7A3NJLQZCYJDRFDKJHOOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:09:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 打败股东对增长预测的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，Netflix 赢得了一项股东诉讼的撤诉，该诉讼指控这家流媒体公司淡化账户共享对用户增长的影响，即付费会员与其他家庭的非付费会员共享用户名和密码。【原文：Netflix won the dismissal on Tuesday of a shareholder lawsuit accusing the streaming company of downplaying the impact on subscriber growth of account sharing, where paying members share user names and passwords with nonpaying members in other households.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-growth-forecasts-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CJR5GPZA5KYFJ7VCNAHD7PAGY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车和其他美国汽车制造商将因特朗普关税而遭受重创]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普计划对来自墨西哥和加拿大的所有进口商品征收 25% 的税，这可能会打击美国汽车制造商，尤其是通用汽车公司的底线，并提高美国消费者购买 SUV 和皮卡的价格。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's plan to slap a 25% tax on all imports from Mexico and Canada could strike the bottom lines of U.S. automakers, especially General Motors , and raise prices of SUVs and pickup trucks for U.S. consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-other-us-automakers-would-take-big-hit-trump-tariffs-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJH3V64TJJIBJFFC5IBEIHUHXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:43:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从牛肉和猪肉到鳄梨和龙舌兰酒，特朗普关税可能会提高食品和酒类价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[农业经济学家和行业高管表示，如果当选总统唐纳德-特朗普落实对来自墨西哥和加拿大的商品加征关税的计划，明年美国鳄梨、草莓和其他新鲜农产品的价格可能会上涨，消费者可能会面临短缺。【原文：U.S. prices may rise next year for avocados, strawberries and other fresh produce, and consumers could face shortages, if President-elect Donald Trump follows through on plans to slap tariffs on goods from Mexico and Canada, agricultural economists and industry executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-tariffs-could-raise-grocery-liquor-bills-beef-pork-avocados-tequila-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMXC64JIONPXXCLR4MM27ICYFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通：夹在经济巨头之间的新兴市场面临艰难的 2025 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）在其年度展望报告中称，由于美国政策的转变和中国增长的不确定性，新兴市场将迎来艰难而不确定的一年，并预测新兴市场债券基金将出现大规模资金外流。【原文：Emerging markets are in for a tough and uncertain year due to policy shifts in the United States and uncertain growth in China, JPMorgan said in its annual outlook, predicting emerging markets bond funds were in line for sizeable outflows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging-markets-caught-between-economic-giants-face-tough-2025-jpmorgan-says-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIN4IUVJSBPCLDNLGLDLDGUHSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:34:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Twinkie制造商Hostess监督小肯尼迪的反糖、反包装食品议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：Twinkie maker JM Smucker is planning to monitor and assess any changes in food and nutrition regulations that Robert F. Kennedy Jr. could implement as President-elect Donald Trump's potential top health agency head.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/twinkie-maker-hostess-monitoring-rfk-jrs-anti-sugar-anti-packaged-food-agenda-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PW62A2OYJM33GX5D7VVLALR2Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:23:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币期权交易显示，在未能突破 100,000 美元后，有更多人押注回撤]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一家加密货币交易平台援引最近的期权活动称，在比特币未能达到 10 万美元的历史峰值后，全球最大加密货币的投资者预计比特币将大幅下行。【原文：Investors in the world's largest cryptocurrency are anticipating a significant downward move after bitcoin failed to hit an all-time peak of $100,000, according to a crypto trading platform citing recent options activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-options-trade-shows-more-bets-retreat-after-failing-breach-100000-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJZZKDNEEFNONBJVSOBTEMLRAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:22:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[削减国税局资金将增加美国赤字，减缓服务速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部副部长瓦利-阿德耶莫（Wally Adeyemo）周二表示，国会共和党人长期以来一直希望削减国内税收署的经费，这将在十年内使联邦赤字增加 1400 亿美元，并会减缓服务速度，减少对大公司的复杂审计。【原文：Cuts in funding for the Internal Revenue Service, long eyed by Republicans in Congress, would increase the federal deficit by $140 billion over a decade, slow service and reduce complex audits of big companies, Deputy Treasury Secretary Wally Adeyemo said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/irs-funding-cut-would-increase-us-deficit-slow-service-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JAUJIE6LX5O6VFEHSCXFL4EFSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:18:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储以波动性和对中性利率的疑虑为由放缓宽松政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本月早些时候的会议上，美联储官员在他们可能需要将利率下调多少的问题上出现了分歧，但作为一个整体，他们一致认为这是一个避免就未来几周美国货币政策可能如何演变给出太多具体指导的时刻。【原文：Federal Reserve officials appeared divided at their meeting earlier this month over how much farther they may need to cut interest rates, but as a group agreed this was a moment to avoid giving much concrete guidance about how U.S. monetary policy is likely to evolve in the weeks ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-cites-volatility-doubts-about-neutral-rate-reasons-go-slow-easing-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGAQF3MIAJNVJKHQMBIFH5JDWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻消息人士称，特朗普将根据贸易计划对来自墨西哥和加拿大的石油征收 25% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉该计划的消息人士周二告诉路透社，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普计划在上任首日对加拿大和墨西哥进口商品征收 25% 的关税，但原油不在贸易惩罚之列。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's plan to impose 25% tariffs on Canadian and Mexican imports in his first day in office does not exempt crude oil from the trade penalties, two sources familiar with the plan told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-would-impose-25-tariffs-oil-mexico-canada-under-trade-plan-sources-say-2024-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPZRBY5JPJLHBHK4SZ4MZ3QNGM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>