<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:34:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:34:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，电动汽车制造商尼古拉正在探索包括潜在出售在内的各种方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，电动汽车制造商尼古拉公司正在探索各种方案，包括出售部分业务或整个公司，因为它正在与资金短缺作斗争。【原文：EV maker Nikola is exploring options including selling parts of its business or the entire company as it struggles with a cash crunch, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-nikola-exploring-options-including-potential-sale-bloomberg-news-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIFNDODF7RMEXNTVTXBQNWU6JQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币的魅力让达沃斯的一些投资者望而却步]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管眼看着比特币一路飙升，突破了 10 万美元，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）也宣誓就任美国 "加密货币总统"，但一些全球最大的投资者本周表示，他们仍计划保持观望。【原文：Despite watching Bitcoin's scorching run past $100,000 and the inauguration of Donald Trump, who has pledged to be a "crypto president" in the U.S., some of the world's largest investors said this week they still plan to stay on the sidelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cryptos-charms-leave-some-investors-davos-cold-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFVOBQ2GBRI2FAU3FZ4DM6K3GY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康任命内部人士接替遇害高管担任保险部门首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）周四任命医疗保险业务主管蒂姆-诺埃尔（Tim Noel）担任其健康保险业务的最高职位，这是在该部门前首席执行官布莱恩-汤普森（Brian Thompson）遇害一个月后。【原文：UnitedHealth Group on Thursday named Tim Noel, the head of its Medicare business, to the top job at its health insurance business, a month after the unit's former CEO Brian Thompson was killed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-taps-medicare-head-ceo-insurance-business-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OSHZXGATNOVRKA7SOK6NZRYG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:41:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令成立加密货币工作组]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四签署了一项命令，要求成立一个加密货币工作组。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday signed an order to create a cryptocurrency working group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-signs-order-create-cryptocurrency-working-group-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZP55NNRCNPFLHLX2BAMBPNJIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:23:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 推出自动化网络任务工具，人工智能代理占据中心位置]]></title><description><![CDATA[生成式人工智能领域的重量级公司 OpenAI 周四预览了一款可以在网络上为用户执行任务的人工智能代理，它正努力在日益激烈的竞争中增强其聊天机器人的功能。【原文：Generative artificial intelligence heavyweight OpenAI on Thursday previewed an AI agent that can carry out tasks on the web for users, as it seeks to enhance its chatbot amid intensifying competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-unveils-tool-automate-web-tasks-ai-agents-take-center-stage-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VK7EBZNZLNJ5TFGG72NZPCCMBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:11:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱立信首席技术官在达沃斯表示，爱立信已准备好利用特朗普的科技政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电信设备制造商爱立信公司首席技术官表示，预计在唐纳德-特朗普总统的领导下，美国将继续走在技术发展的前沿，该公司已准备好利用这一优势。【原文：Swedish telecom gear maker Ericsson expects the United States to continue to be at the forefront of technology development under President Donald Trump, which the company is ready to take advantage of, its chief technology officer said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ericsson-ready-take-advantage-trumps-tech-policies-cto-says-davos-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYZQUPMDDBN3VCXPD6WMFUO3M4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 19:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国将保证向欧洲供应液化天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美国将保证向欧洲供应液化天然气，尽管人们担心这一蓬勃发展的出口行业可能会提高美国消费者的天然气价格。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday the United States would guarantee supplies of liquefied natural gas to Europe, even amid worries that the booming export industry could boost prices of gas for U.S. consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-says-us-will-guarantee-lng-supplies-europe-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXBXIXUEI5PY7PKUEWJKRDMUKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 19:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院允许反洗钱法生效]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周四为一项反洗钱联邦法律的实施扫清了障碍，该法律要求公司实体向美国财政部披露其真实受益所有人的身份。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court cleared the way on Thursday for the enforcement of an anti-money laundering federal law that requires corporate entities to disclose the identities of their real beneficial owners to the U.S. Treasury Department.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-allows-anti-money-laundering-law-take-effect-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFA2E6B7WVKD3EN2BQSM34AC6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 19:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管特朗普呼吁钻探，但石油业不太可能贸然前往阿拉斯加]]></title><description><![CDATA[公司官员和行业代表告诉路透社记者，在唐纳德-特朗普总统发布行政命令允许美国石油和天然气公司扩大在阿拉斯加和北极地区的开发后，这些公司不太可能这样做。【原文：U.S. oil and gas companies are unlikely to expand development in Alaska and the Arctic following President Donald Trump's executive order enabling them to do so, company officials and industry representatives told Reuters, noting a future president could easily reverse Trump's move.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-industry-unlikely-rush-alaska-despite-trumps-call-drill-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2J5D4WYRVJWVBKTHWJ5AZV72Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：5000 亿美元人工智能数据中心计划背后，美国初创企业与科技巨头的角逐]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对私营部门进行大规模投资，以建设更多的人工智能数据中心，这让人们将目光投向了规模相对较小、业务相对灵活、有望在科技领域发挥更大作用的云计算公司。【原文：This week's announcement by President Donald Trump of a massive private-sector investment to build more AI data centers casts a spotlight on a relatively small and nimble class of cloud computing firms positioned to play a bigger role in the tech sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/behind-500-billion-ai-data-center-plan-us-startups-jockey-with-tech-giants-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ5XHPPTDVKW3NIITAG64RNGWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普发布行政令前后，美联储砍掉了网站上的多元化栏目]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储已经删除了其网站上的 "多样性与包容性 "栏目，之前链接到美国中央银行多样性标准声明及其经济学家和研究人员的种族、民族和性别构成数据的链接现在默认跳转到其主页。【原文：The Federal Reserve has scrubbed a "Diversity and Inclusion" section from its website, with previous links to a statement of the U.S. central bank's diversity standards and data on the racial, ethnic and gender makeup of its economists and researchers now defaulting to its home page.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-axed-diversity-section-website-around-time-trumps-executive-order-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBSG2VV3R5LV3DZYK57APS6PZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:40:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普敦促实现和平，乌克兰在达沃斯寻求复苏投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[在乌克兰总统讨论执行停火所需的维和部队以及美国总统唐纳德-特朗普敦促结束三年战争之际，乌克兰官员本周正在寻求私人投资者帮助重建国家。【原文：As Ukraine's president discussed peacekeeping forces needed to enforce any ceasefire and U.S. President Donald Trump urged an end to three years of war, Ukrainian officials were courting private investors this week to help rebuild the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ukraine-seeks-recovery-investment-davos-trump-urges-peace-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBHDIYF7NRNZVAOLBD3UPEVVQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Epic Games 启动在自有移动商店中添加第三方游戏的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA["堡垒之夜》（Fortnite）制作商Epic Games周四表示，它将在全球谷歌安卓平台上的自有市场应用中添加19款第三方游戏，并在欧盟苹果iOS平台上添加16款游戏。【原文："Fortnite" maker Epic Games said on Thursday it will add 19 third-party games to its own marketplace app on Google's Android globally and 16 games on Apple's iOS in the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/epic-games-kicks-off-plan-add-third-party-games-own-mobile-store-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6O5VE732LVMCDHQB37HEG4JDAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Perplexity 首次在安卓平台上推出人工智能助手，挑战 Alexa 和 ChatGPT]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Perplexity周四为安卓设备推出了一款基于代理的助手，希望与更大的竞争对手OpenAI的ChatGPT以及苹果的Siri和亚马逊的Alexa等现有助手一较高下。【原文：Artificial intelligence startup Perplexity launched an agent-based assistant for Android devices on Thursday as it looks to take on larger rival OpenAI's ChatGPT and incumbent assistants such as Apple's Siri and Amazon's Alexa.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/perplexity-debuts-ai-assistant-android-challenge-alexa-chatgpt-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZBM3YK6VNPW3LYFFHRBPFS3UY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通警告：新兴经济体面临资本流动 "骤停"]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资银行摩根大通（JPMorgan）周四警告说，由于唐纳德-特朗普总统的 "美国优先 "政策刺激了美国经济，吸走了穷国的资金，新兴市场可能会出现可怕的资本流动 "骤停"。【原文：Emerging markets could be seeing a dreaded "sudden stop" of capital flows as President Donald Trump's 'America First' policies pump up the U.S. economy and suck money away from poorer countries, investment bank JPMorgan warned on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging-economies-facing-sudden-stop-capital-flows-jpmorgan-warns-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFRUFEUXZRJJNL4PDNX5IY2XHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铝业公司首席执行官表示，特朗普的关税可能会改变金属流向]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铝业公司（Alcoa）首席执行官威廉-奥普林格（William Oplinger）周四表示，如果美国对加拿大进口商品征收关税，该公司可能会将澳大利亚的产品运往美国。【原文：Alcoa will likely send its Australian output to the U.S. if the United States imposes tariff on Canadian imports, the aluminum producer's CEO William Oplinger said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-tariffs-could-redirect-metal-flows-alcoa-ceo-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRZXTPGX4ZL5ZJ4VAVPIC3M6AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:57:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普呼吁沙特投资 1 万亿美元，降低油价]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，他将要求沙特阿拉伯和欧佩克降低石油成本，并将要求利雅得把计划中的美国投资计划从最初报道的6000亿美元增加到1万亿美元。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday said he will demand Saudi Arabia and OPEC bring down the cost of oil and will ask Riyadh to increase a planned U.S. investment package to $1 trillion from an initial reported $600 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-calls-1-trillion-saudi-investment-lower-oil-prices-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZF4RGOJUZOZLCHRXCEF7SPPBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:54:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普指责美国银行和 JPM 不与保守派做生意]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四通过视频链接在瑞士达沃斯世界经济论坛上发表讲话，指责美国银行和摩根大通的首席执行官没有为保守派提供银行服务，但没有提供任何不当行为的证据或具体细节。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump, addressing the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, via video link on Thursday, accused the CEOs of Bank of America and JPMorgan Chase of not providing banking services to conservatives, but offered no evidence or specifics of any wrongdoing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-accuses-bank-america-jpm-not-doing-business-with-conservatives-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNEG2SYO4FK65ONDAQX2OAUXKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，华纳兄弟发现公司游戏部门主管将在 12 年后卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份内部备忘录，华纳兄弟发现公司游戏部门主管大卫-哈达德（David Haddad）在任职 12 年后将离开公司。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery's gaming unit head David Haddad is leaving the company after 12 years in the role, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-discoverys-gaming-unit-chief-step-down-after-12-years-memo-shows-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBDQN2RRTZJZ7AYLR7OCHH62FM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普渡制药公司与萨克尔公司达成价值 74 亿美元的全国阿片类药物和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州总检察长肯-帕克斯顿（Ken Paxton）周四表示，普渡制药公司及其萨克勒（Sackler）家族所有者已达成一项新的 74 亿美元的和解协议，以解决数千起指控止痛药奥施康定（Oxycontin）导致美国阿片类药物成瘾危机蔓延的诉讼。【原文：Purdue Pharma and its Sackler family owners have reached a new $7.4 billion settlement to resolve thousands of lawsuits alleging that the pain medication Oxycontin caused a widespread opioid addiction crisis in the U.S., Texas attorney general Ken Paxton said Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/purdue-pharma-sacklers-reach-74-bln-national-opioid-settlement-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBYALPGD65IENG5F3UKTM4ID2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:06:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行可能将利率上调至 17 年来的最高点，并发出更多加息信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行预计将于周五将利率上调至自2008年全球金融危机以来从未有过的水平，因为全球股市的广泛反弹平息了决策者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税威胁可能会扰乱市场的担忧。【原文：The Bank of Japan is expected to raise interest rates on Friday to levels unseen since the 2008 global financial crisis, as a broad worldwide stocks rally calms policymakers' fears U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats could upend markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-likely-raise-rates-highest-17-years-signal-more-hikes-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BVNFV3MKJJQJJ6PT2HQ2VBYYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顶级基金经理称，特朗普政策可能加剧债券市场对通胀的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于唐纳德-特朗普总统的移民和贸易政策，监管着超过 20 万亿美元资金的美国巨型资产管理公司预计价格压力将持续存在，这种情况很可能在今年继续威胁债券市场。【原文：Giant U.S. asset managers overseeing well over $20 trillion are anticipating continued price pressures because of President Donald Trump's immigration and trade policies, a scenario that will likely keep threatening the bond market this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/trump-policies-likely-raise-bond-markets-inflation-fears-top-money-managers-say-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HH2YND7B2RJVHPOXDU6R7T5PG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康卡斯特推出体育与新闻电视套餐吸引流媒体用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[康卡斯特周四宣布推出面向其 Xfinity 互联网用户的新视频套餐 "Sports &amp; News TV"，这是其在流媒体时代保持竞争力战略的一部分。【原文：Comcast announced on Thursday the launch of Sports &amp; News TV, a new video package for its Xfinity internet customers, as part of its strategy to remain competitive in the streaming era.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/comcast-launches-sports-news-tv-package-attract-streaming-customers-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRUFOKYZLVLSDFE4PM4FA4MXLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:51:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将立即要求降低利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，他将要求立即降息，其他国家也应效仿。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday said he would demand that interest rates drop immediately, and that other countries should follow suit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-says-he-will-demand-lower-interest-rates-immediately-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UDPGE7AEBMTVNZTFTY5XVYHAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:32:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普致全球企业：在美国生产产品或面临关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四在世界经济论坛上表示，企业如果想避免面临关税，就应该在美国生产产品。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump told the World Economic Forum on Thursday that businesses should make their products in the United States if they want to avoid facing a tariff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-world-companies-make-products-us-or-face-tariff-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRQ6OWMNIBLL5LY7NY5B54COSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:25:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利航天局称，意大利与星链公司的交易不会带来安全风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利国家航天局（ASI）局长周四表示，意大利与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的Starlink公司之间可能达成的安全卫星通信协议不会带来安全风险。【原文：A possible deal between Italy and Elon Musk's Starlink for secure satellite communications would not pose a security risk, the head of national space agency ASI said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/italian-deal-with-starlink-would-not-be-security-risk-space-agency-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MB7HN2NJSBIIRMUOFSSBNL5OR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国电动汽车制造商向欧盟法院提出关税挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟法院网站周四公布的文件显示，中国电动汽车（EV）制造商比亚迪、吉利和上汽已向欧盟法院（CJEU）提出对欧盟进口关税的质疑。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle (EV) makers BYD , Geely and SAIC have challenged the EU's import tariffs at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), filings on the court's website showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-ev-makers-file-challenges-tariffs-eu-court-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPU3PQFFAFOIZN4MJULZJKADTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:12:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）在推进数字化进程中裁员 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份内部备忘录，华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）旗下的 CNN 将裁员约 6%，因为这家电视新闻媒体将继续把重点转向更加以数字为中心的战略。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery-owned CNN will lay off about 6% of its workforce as the TV news outlet continues to shift its focus toward a more digital-centric strategy, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cnn-cut-jobs-by-6-amid-digital-push-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5R3PVDMRQBOMHNMLQFYAIB3O2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:53:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚国家石油公司称康菲石油公司成为马来西亚天然气项目的唯一运营商]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚国家石油公司（Petronas）周四表示，该公司已正式将其在该国一组油气田的承包权转让给美国康菲石油公司（ConocoPhillips）的一个部门。【原文：Malaysia's Petronas on Thursday said it has officially transferred its contractual right for a cluster of oil and gas fields in the country to a unit of US-based firm ConocoPhillips .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/conocophillips-takes-over-sole-operator-gas-project-malaysia-petronas-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVPCA3B2ZJOCHD3HKDS3EARKWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PayPal 因网络安全失误被纽约罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州金融服务监督员阿德里安娜-哈里斯（Adrienne Harris）周四表示，PayPal 将因网络安全故障导致客户社保号码泄露而支付 200 万美元的民事罚款。【原文：PayPal will pay a $2 million civil fine over cybersecurity failures that led to the exposure of customers' Social Security numbers, New York state's financial services superintendent Adrienne Harris said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/paypal-fined-by-new-york-cybersecurity-failures-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCDBHTHZNJJ6PIYZIZF6Q2C7N4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>