<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:35:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:35:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文公司表示，数据中心故障导致美国TikTok用户遭遇问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[甲骨文公司周二表示，美国用户在使用社交媒体应用TikTok时遇到的问题，是由于甲骨文数据中心发生临时性天气相关停电所致。【原文：Oracle said on Tuesday that issues faced by U.S. users of social media app TikTok are the result of a temporary weather-related power outage at an Oracle data center.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oracle-says-outage-data-center-causes-issues-faced-by-us-tiktok-users-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZ2YR43L5BJRXGLBU7YA5YDFYI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:17:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空订购31架空客客机，推进远程机队升级计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空周二宣布将采购31架空客宽体客机，作为其现代化国际机队并支持未来增长的长期计划的一部分。该公司正着力满足企业客户及高收入旅客的需求。【原文：Delta Air Lines said on Tuesday it would purchase 31 Airbus widebody jets as part of a long-term plan to modernize its international fleet and support future growth as it focuses on demand from corporate and high-income travelers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-orders-31-airbus-jets-latest-longhaul-fleet-upgrade-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMNLIIKFXFKOXOCWSYRJAGP4CI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[矿业巨头墨西哥集团第四季度净利润翻倍，得益于金属价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥集团周二表示，受金属价格上涨和销量增长推动，这家全球最大铜生产商之一的第四季度净利润几乎翻倍，这完全抵消了因石油平台停运和汇率不利因素导致的基础设施业务疲软。【原文：Grupo Mexico , one of the world's largest copper producers, nearly doubled its fourth-quarter net profit on higher metals prices and stronger volumes, it said on Tuesday, more than offsetting weaker infrastructure results tied to suspended oil platforms and foreign-exchange headwinds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mining-giant-grupo-mexicos-net-profit-doubles-fourth-quarter-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35LLSOR3CBOLPFTOCY6K7LYS3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元跌至四年低点，特朗普对此不以为意]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美元兑一篮子货币延续跌势，跌至四年低点。【原文：The U.S. dollar extended losses to sink to a four-year low against a basket of currencies on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-sinks-four-year-low-trump-brushes-off-decline-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3VYPSZM5FIYXBJRW436TOH3I4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团驳斥针对高管的骚扰指控，寻求将案件移交仲裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周二强烈驳斥了前董事总经理的指控。该董事总经理以财富管理主管安迪·西格涉嫌性骚扰为由起诉该银行，花旗表示她曾对西格表达"坚定"支持，且此案应通过仲裁解决。【原文：Citigroup on Tuesday forcefully rejected accusations by a former managing director who sued the bank over alleged sexual harassment by wealth management chief Andy Sieg, saying she expressed "steadfast" support for him and that her case belongs in arbitration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/citigroup-rejects-harassment-claims-against-top-executive-seeks-move-case-into-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYOZSLLZANKHDMO37B7KMS4TCI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普预测在宣布美联储主席人选后利率将下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周二表示，他将很快宣布美联储主席人选，并预测新主席上任后利率将下降。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday said he will soon announce his pick to serve as head of the Federal Reserve, and predicted interest rates would decline after the new chair takes over.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-predicts-interest-rates-will-come-down-after-he-announces-fed-chair-pick-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJSRLIW6P5PU7HH3GSGSWMOTQ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普指出拖拉机制造商迪尔公司在北卡罗来纳州投资7000万美元建设工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统特朗普周二在演讲中宣布，农业设备制造商约翰迪尔公司将在北卡罗来纳州投资7000万美元建设工厂。【原文：Farm-equipment maker Deere & Co ​is making a $70 ‌million factory investment in North Carolina, U.S. President ‌Donald Trump said in ​a speech on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-notes-70-million-factory-investment-by-tractor-maker-deere-north-carolina-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SJJUFB2JFKBLBC5VMDJRMYWRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙任命资深高管托马斯·霍顿加入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司周二宣布，已任命美国航空前董事长兼首席执行官托马斯·W·霍顿加入这家能源巨头的董事会，担任独立董事。【原文：Chevron said on Tuesday it has appointed former American Airlines Chairman and CEO Thomas W. Horton to the energy major's board as an independent director.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/chevron-appoints-veteran-executive-thomas-horton-board-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CV4P5UZTOJKNRA2KSDIPIT23E4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PPG工业公司第四季度利润未达预期，预计2026年欧洲工业市场将持续疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球涂料供应商PPG工业公司周二表示，预计未来一年欧洲及全球工业终端市场需求将持续疲软。此前该公司第四季度利润未达华尔街预期。【原文：Global paint supplier PPG Industries said on Tuesday it expects demand in Europe and across global industrial end-use markets to remain soft ​in the coming year, after the company fell short of Wall ‌Street's fourth-quarter profit expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ppg-industries-sees-soft-european-industrial-markets-2026-after-q4-profit-miss-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRO4HANPIBOIVIANXSG3QTUVSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:16:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 极端分化]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球股市与标普500指数周二创下新高，得益于美国企业财报普遍强劲。与此同时，市场对美国总统特朗普政策方向的担忧推升避险资产黄金价格至新高，美元汇率则跌至四年低点。【原文：World stocks and the S&amp;P 500 hit new highs on Tuesday, boosted by a flood of strong U.S. earnings reports, while anxiety over U.S. President Donald Trump's policy direction sent safe-haven gold to fresh peaks and sank the dollar to a four-year low.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WHJG7XPBFK6HJNMVN7GIMF57U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希捷预测季度业绩将超预期，因数据存储需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[希捷科技周二公布的第三季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，得益于企业扩大人工智能应用规模所带来的数据存储设备强劲需求。【原文：Seagate Technology forecast third-quarter revenue and profit above Wall Street expectations on Tuesday, benefiting from strong demand for its data storage devices as enterprises scale up their use of artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/seagate-forecasts-quarterly-results-above-estimates-strong-data-storage-demand-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VVXFTZYPNKZ7PC2C5BPHZ7UDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国医保局公布礼来、辉瑞和艾伯维三家药企药品名单，将参与下一轮医保价格谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦医疗保险和医疗补助服务中心周二公布了第三轮联邦医疗保险药品价格谈判计划的新一批品牌药名单，涵盖礼来、辉瑞和艾伯维等大型制药企业，其中包括首批纳入联邦医疗保险B部分报销范围的药品。【原文：The U.S. Centers for Medicare & Medicaid Services on Tuesday named a new group of branded drugs from major pharmaceutical companies including Eli Lilly , Pfizer and AbbVie for the third cycle of the Medicare Drug Price Negotiation Program, including the first products reimbursed under Medicare Part B.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-medicare-names-eli-lilly-pfizer-abbvie-drugs-next-medicare-price-talks-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMBAC7BMEVKN5A3F62HE3SRMZ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美元价值"非常棒"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周二被问及是否认为美元贬值过多时表示，美元价值非常高。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump ​on Tuesday said the value of the ‌dollar is great when asked whether he thought it had declined too much.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-value-dollar-is-great-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NEDD4ZZBG5OINBZLDY3RM2AL3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:50:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，私募股权公司奥达克斯集团正为BlueCat Networks寻求超过15亿美元的融资。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，私募股权公司奥达克斯集团正考虑出售网络安全服务商BlueCat Networks，该交易可能价值超过15亿美元。【原文：Private equity firm Audax Group is exploring a sale of cybersecurity provider BlueCat Networks, which could fetch more than $1.5 billion, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/private-equity-firm-audax-group-seeks-over-15-billion-bluecat-networks-sources-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZT4LJL77JPV5JTRM5EQNTD2WM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:42:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司2025年订单积压量创纪录达316亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司周二发布的证券文件显示，截至第四季度末，其确认订单积压量达到创纪录的316亿美元，较上年同期增长20%。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer's firm order backlog stood at a record $31.6 billion at the end of the fourth quarter, up 20% from a year earlier, according to a securities filing published on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-ends-2025-with-record-backlog-316-billion-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CGB24TXKRNPCRIOPWXJRK4RRTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗技公布疫情以来最佳季度利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗技国际周二公布了疫情以来的最佳季度财报，这家电脑外设制造商受益于视频会议设备销量增长和教育支出增加。【原文：Logitech International reported its best quarterly earnings since the pandemic on Tuesday, as the computer peripherals maker was boosted by higher sales of video conferencing equipment and educational spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/computer-mouse-maker-logitech-posts-best-quarterly-profit-since-pandemic-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDUK3AZZBNNAFKUL4STAJQXHM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德州仪器预测季度销售额将超预期，得益于模拟芯片需求增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德州仪器周二公布的季度营收和利润预期均高于华尔街预测，表明其模拟芯片需求在经历长期市场低迷后正逐步复苏，该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨5%。【原文：Texas Instruments forecast first-quarter revenue and profit above Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, signaling recovering demand for its analog chips following ​a prolonged market slump and sending its shares up 5% in extended ‌trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/analog-chipmaker-texas-instruments-forecasts-first-quarter-revenue-above-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRAYCICVJJN4FDS44FRMVS2DRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:06:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自动驾驶卡车公司Gatik锁定6亿美元合同收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gatik周二宣布已获得6亿美元的合同收入，并部署了全自动无人驾驶卡车投入商业运营，彰显了这家自动驾驶卡车公司立志在行业内建立坚实立足点的雄心。【原文：Gatik said on Tuesday it has secured $600 million in contracted revenue and deployed fully driverless trucks for commercial operations, underscoring the autonomous trucking firm's ambitions to establish a strong foothold in the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/self-driving-truck-firm-gatik-secures-600-million-contracted-revenue-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W6DTLGBHT5NBNEPWKODT5GW2FY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称拉丁美洲电子商务规模将突破2150亿美元，消费者对快速配送的需求日益增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[咨询公司Endeavor与电商巨头MercadoLibre周二发布的报告显示，随着消费者对平台忠诚度下降，开始更重视可靠配送和透明定价而非华丽的个性化服务，拉丁美洲今年网购规模预计将达2153.1亿美元。【原文：Online shopping in Latin America is projected to reach $215.31 billion this year, as consumers become less loyal to platforms and begin to prioritize reliable delivery and transparent pricing over flashy personalization, according to a report on Tuesday by consulting firm Endeavor and e-commerce giant MercadoLibre .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/latin-american-e-commerce-top-215-billion-consumers-demand-rapid-delivery-report-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLB274WCHJKP3NQJD5CA4SIGX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:23:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院小组委员会将就Netflix与华纳兄弟拟议交易举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院司法委员会周二表示，其反垄断小组委员会将于下周就奈飞与华纳兄弟拟议的合并案举行听证会。【原文：The U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee said on Tuesday that its antitrust subcommittee will hold a hearing next week on a proposed tie-up between Netflix and Warner Brothers .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/senate-subcommittee-hold-hearing-proposed-netflix-warner-bros-deal-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JDW7VHJG5PB7LRT77OH7XAGJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:28:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关键预测市场押注黑石集团的里德尔成为下一任美联储主席的赔率颇高]]></title><description><![CDATA[预测市场Kalshi的数据显示，贝莱德首席债券投资经理里克·里德尔已成为接替现任美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的热门人选，后者任期即将届满。【原文：BlackRock's chief bond investment manager Rick Rieder is now the clear favorite to succeed current Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell when his term is up, according to prediction market Kalshi.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/key-prediction-market-putting-strong-odds-blackrocks-rieder-next-fed-chair-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWH4CL7CGZKILG67VRGFQLNLGQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:15:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭记录显示，壳牌公司与Venture Global的法律纠纷焦点在于与工程师的沟通记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[壳牌公司对液化天然气生产商Venture Global胜诉的仲裁结果提出质疑，其核心争议点在于美国企业与独立工程公司Lummus Consultants之间可能存在的沟通往来。路透社获得的法庭听证会记录草案显示了这一情况。【原文：Shell's challenge to its arbitration defeat to liquefied natural gas producer Venture Global centres on potential communications between the U.S. firm and independent engineer Lummus Consultants, a draft court hearing transcript seen by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/shells-legal-fight-against-venture-global-focuses-communication-with-engineer-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5AQMK5ZZVJ3HF33LMBTN6IMYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭文件指控Meta首席执行官扎克伯格阻挠了针对未成年人性话题聊天机器人的限制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据新墨西哥州法院案件中提交并于周一公开的Meta内部文件显示，该公司首席执行官马克·扎克伯格批准允许未成年人使用AI聊天机器人伴侣，尽管安全团队曾警告这些机器人具备进行性互动的能力。【原文：Meta Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg approved allowing minors to access AI chatbot companions that safety staffers warned were capable of sexual interactions, according to internal Meta documents filed in a New Mexico state court case and made public Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/meta-ceo-zuckerberg-blocked-curbs-sex-talking-chatbots-minors-court-filing-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTHRGFFDLZLBZJO4NB5SF2DWMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:59:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称雪佛龙要求伊拉克改善条款后再接管卢克石油油田]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名知情人士透露，美国石油巨头雪佛龙正敦促伊拉克提高西古尔纳2号油田的回报率，作为从俄罗斯卢克石油公司收购该项目的条件。【原文：U.S. oil major Chevron is pushing Iraq to improve returns on the giant West Qurna 2 oil field as a condition for buying the project from Russia's Lukoil , three sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-seeks-better-terms-iraq-before-taking-over-lukoil-oilfield-sources-say-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHFRN5MBABPFDK72RVSCKOCUCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场动态：华尔街押注下任美联储主席将挺身对抗特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普上周对任命下一任美联储主席一事表示遗憾：他说问题在于，这些人一旦上任就会改变立场。华尔街正指望这一点。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump bemoaned last week his issue with naming the next Federal Reserve chair: The problem, he said, is they change once they have the job. Wall Street is counting on it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/market-wall-streets-banking-next-fed-chair-stand-up-trump-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7LQT4O7HJLE5PPA4XSRCYF3LY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称美国将很快颁布通用许可证，解除对委内瑞拉石油行业部分制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名知情人士周二透露，美国官员正着手尽快颁布一项通用许可证，以解除对委内瑞拉能源领域的部分制裁。此举改变了此前为寻求在该国开展业务的企业提供个别制裁豁免的计划。【原文：U.S. officials are working to issue a general license soon that would lift some sanctions on Venezuela's energy sector, three sources familiar with the preparation said on Tuesday, a shift from a previous plan to grant individual exemptions to sanctions for companies seeking to do business in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-issue-general-license-soon-lifting-some-sanctions-venezuelan-oil-industry-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLS3OICDARMB7BOGC6FIH7HZN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟官员称Shein可能面临欧盟调查，但不会采取临时措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会一位高级官员周二表示，中国快时尚电商平台Shein可能因平台销售非法产品面临欧盟调查，但不太可能被勒令暂停运营。【原文：Chinese fast-fashion online retailer Shein could face an EU investigation on the sale of illegal products on its platform, but is unlikely to be hit with an order to suspend its website, a senior European Commission official said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/shein-could-face-eu-investigation-no-interim-measure-commission-official-says-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2C5CUZ6PZOKBFYXHWPHOOJXKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:41:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉原油回归或将削减美国燃料油进口]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着炼油商大量采购新到港的委内瑞拉重质原油，今年美国对进口燃料油的需求将出现下滑。这些原油可生产出更多国产燃料油，进而加工成汽油和柴油等高附加值产品。【原文：U.S. demand for imported fuel oil is set to fall this year as refiners snap up new flows of heavy Venezuelan crude, yielding more domestically produced fuel oil that can be processed into higher-value products such as gasoline and diesel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/return-venezuelan-crude-could-cut-us-fuel-oil-imports-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KD3BCR6FW5KGHKYKKQM7VIWG44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Revolut在墨西哥启动全面银行业务，实现首次欧洲以外扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融科技公司Revolut周二宣布，已在墨西哥正式开展全面银行业务，标志着该公司在欧洲以外地区设立的首家银行正式运营。随着Revolut加速向高增长市场扩张，其全球业务版图持续扩大。【原文：Britain's Revolut said on Tuesday that it has officially launched full banking operations in Mexico, marking its first bank established outside of Europe as the fintech accelerates its expansion into high-growth markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/revolut-launches-full-banking-operations-mexico-first-expansion-outside-europe-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKPMOZ7WERMFZC3CJWXJ2E5UBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[渣打银行警告称，到2028年，美国银行可能因稳定币损失5000亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周二预测，以美元为支撑的加密货币代币（即稳定币）可能在2028年底前从美国银行体系抽走约5000亿美元存款。这项新分析或将加剧银行与加密货币公司之间围绕数字资产行业监管立法的博弈。【原文：U.S. dollar-backed crypto tokens ​known as stablecoins could pull around $500 billion in deposits out of U.S. banks by ‌the end of 2028, Standard Chartered estimated on Tuesday - new analysis that could intensify a fight between banks and crypto companies over legislation to set rules for the digital asset sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-banks-may-lose-500-billion-stablecoins-by-2028-standard-chartered-warns-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36V3A6PBJJJPVLQ25PNBTS7MVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>