<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:04:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:04:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[投资者质疑股息，Stellantis 股价跌至逾两年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周早些时候发布利润预警后，Stellantis 的股价在周四进一步下跌，原因是人们对该汽车制造商股息的可持续性感到担忧。【原文：Stellantis shares fell further on Thursday amid concerns over the sustainability of the automaker's dividend following a profit warning earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-shares-drop-over-2-year-low-investors-question-dividend-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUHN5USPXVKP3JQNWWCMV4B5EA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:21:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待劳动力数据，评估中东风险，期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周四下滑，市场在等待有关经济前景和美联储进一步降息可能性的数据，同时关注中东敌对行动的潜在升级。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Thursday as markets awaited data for insights on the economic outlook and the likelihood of further interest-rate cuts from the Federal Reserve, while watching for a potential escalation in Middle East hostilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-fall-investors-await-labor-data-assess-middle-east-risk-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RBCRSMNEZJVTEOAUKCXG57ZXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:18:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海伦飓风暴露了联邦紧急事务管理局在阿巴拉契亚地区的援助缺口]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着北卡罗来纳州西部居民的生活逐渐恢复正常，能够依靠联邦洪水保险的居民将寥寥无几。【原文：As residents of western North Carolina piece together their lives, few will be able to rely on federal flood insurance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/hurricane-helene-exposes-federal-assistance-gap-appalachian-areas-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5GO675AIZLQJLF3CXCG3WJO4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国写字楼市场在大幅打折促销后出现触底迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师告诉路透社记者，陷入困境的美国办公物业市场可能正在触底反弹，他们指出，在过去一个季度里，一连串受压物业以大幅折扣出售，帮助确立了新的定价基准。【原文：The beleaguered U.S. office property market may be bottoming out, analysts told Reuters, pointing to a string of sales of stressed properties at big discounts over the last quarter that have helped set a new pricing benchmark.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-office-market-shows-signs-bottoming-after-big-discount-sales-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6VO63OLMZKTLA3Q47ISKWA2RI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：欧洲和日本鹰派联合造势，美元大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYM66TBKHVMYHKKJ4RPSWMFYXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber 和 Lyft 司机将特斯拉用作临时机器人出租车，引发安全担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年 4 月，一辆为优步（Uber）服务的自动驾驶特斯拉汽车在拉斯维加斯郊区的一个十字路口撞上了一辆 SUV，这起事故引发了新的担忧，即越来越多的自称 "机器人出租车 "正在利用美国城市的监管灰色地带，危及生命安全。【原文：A self-driving Tesla carrying a passenger for Uber rammed into an SUV at an intersection in suburban Las Vegas in April, an accident that sparked new concerns that a growing stable of self-styled "robotaxis" is exploiting a regulatory gray area in U.S. cities, putting lives at risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-lyft-drivers-use-teslas-makeshift-robotaxis-raising-safety-concerns-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDE7MDOJ4RIDLDCC5OJYDXGYZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:04:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airbnb 推动游客天堂里约的短租热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[2019 年，当卡洛斯-爱德华多-穆兹第一次在 Airbnb 上出租他在里约热内卢海边的公寓时，他只是想赚点外快。他得到的是一份管理约 100 处房产的职业，以及一个科技平台如何改变南美最著名旅游目的地之一的前沿席位。【原文：When Carlos Eduardo Muzy first rented his beachside Rio de Janeiro apartment on Airbnb in 2019, he just wanted some extra cash. What he got was a career managing some 100 properties – and a front-row seat to how the tech platform is transforming one of South America's most famous tourist destinations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/airbnb-drives-short-term-rental-boom-tourist-haven-rio-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYVWSYPP5FNDNCWTN4EYONWBBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，特斯拉将召回超过 2.7 万辆 Cybertruck 汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周四表示，特斯拉将在美国召回27185辆Cybertruck汽车，原因是延迟的后视影像降低了车辆后方的可视性。【原文：Tesla is recalling 27,185 Cybertruck vehicles in the U.S. as a delayed rear view image reduces visibility behind the vehicle, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-recall-over-27000-cybertruck-vehicles-nhtsa-says-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEWEQKLEIVKF3M6ICLQDZNZBCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:47:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：美国限制措施迫在眉睫，中国药明康德探索出售制药部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周四援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，中国生物技术公司药明康德（WuXi AppTec）和药明生物（WuXi Biologics）正致力于出售其部分业务，这两家公司正成为美国即将出台的国家安全立法的目标。【原文：Chinese biotech companies WuXi AppTec and WuXi Biologics , which are being targeted by a forthcoming U.S. national security legislation, are working on sales of some of their operations, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/chinas-wuxi-explores-sale-pharma-units-us-restrictions-loom-ft-reports-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FXF7H74CVID3EEZSP7SNNF6UA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储大幅降息为各国央行 9 月宽松周期增添动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国联邦储备委员会的带领下，发达市场央行在 9 月份推出了自 COVID-19 疫情爆发时的宽松浪潮以来最大规模的降息举措，而巴西则开启了新一轮的紧缩周期。【原文：Led by the U.S. Federal Reserve, developed market central banks in September delivered their biggest interest rate cut push since the easing wave at the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, while Brazil kicked off a fresh tightening cycle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bumper-fed-rate-cut-supercharges-central-banks-easing-cycle-september-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MZENUPEQ5MAJALOKBALIJS7ZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 08:39:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SWIFT 将于明年试行实时数字货币交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球银行报文传送网络 SWIFT 周四表示，明年将试行代币化资产和数字货币的实时交易，这是将此类资产融入更广泛的金融体系的最新进展。【原文：Global bank messaging network SWIFT will trial live transactions of tokenised assets and digital currencies next year, it said on Thursday, the latest step in the currently slow-moving integration of such assets into the wider financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/swift-trial-live-digital-currency-transactions-next-year-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMBHHCUX6ZJ5XN72JFRBM35O44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 08:08:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+可以缓解伊朗石油冲击，但不能缓解更广泛的破坏]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果以色列摧毁伊朗的设施，欧佩克有足够的备用石油产能来弥补伊朗供应的全部损失，但如果伊朗报复性地打击其海湾邻国的设施，该生产国集团就会陷入困境。【原文：OPEC has enough spare oil capacity to compensate for a full loss of Iranian supply if Israel knocks out that country's facilities but the producer group would struggle if Iran retaliates by hitting installations of its Gulf neighbours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-could-cushion-iran-oil-shock-not-broader-disruption-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAL33JZHXZIMDHUV6ORQQAGFKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 08:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年剩余时间新兴市场货币将保持稳定或收窄涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，在美国联邦储备委员会抑制了激进降息的预期之后，大多数新兴市场货币在未来三个月内将在狭窄的区间内交易，或缩减今年迄今为止的部分涨幅。【原文：Most emerging market currencies are set to trade in tight ranges or pare some of the year-to-date gains in the next three months after the U.S. Federal Reserve curbed expectations for aggressive rate cuts, according to a Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/em-currencies-set-hold-steady-or-pare-gains-rest-2024-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHGQOYSO55L65KAVO5E7QOCDTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 07:28:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称澳新银行、古纳万家族考虑出售印尼帕宁银行的控制权]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士透露，澳大利亚澳新银行（ANZ）和印尼古纳万（Gunawan）家族正在考虑出售在雅加达上市的印尼潘宁银行（Bank Pan Indonesia Tbk PT，简称 "潘宁银行"）的联合控股权，双方均持有该银行的大量股份。【原文：Australian lender ANZ and Indonesia's Gunawan family are considering selling a combined controlling interest in Jakarta-listed Bank Pan Indonesia Tbk PT (Panin Bank) , in which they each hold substantial stakes, three sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/anz-gunawan-family-consider-selling-control-indonesias-panin-bank-sources-say-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKOVTKUWJFPS3KJDV6BGQHW3MA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 07:12:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[码头工人罢工进入第三天，美国港口船舶排队现象加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，集装箱船在美国主要港口外排起了长队，因为近半个世纪以来最大规模的码头工人罢工已进入第三天，罢工阻碍了卸货，并威胁到从香蕉到汽车零部件等各种产品的短缺。【原文：Long lines of container ships queued up outside major U.S. ports on Thursday as the biggest dockworker strike in nearly half a century entered its third day preventing unloading and threatening shortages of everything from bananas to auto parts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ship-queue-grows-us-ports-dockworker-strike-enters-third-day-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SG2U4223JM3JKHCEN3ZEWHRXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 05:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元看跌者关注全球收益率和经济增长的变化，以应对美元走软]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着全球央行纷纷降息，货币市场也随之动荡不安，交易员们正密切关注着全球各经济体的相对实力，以衡量如何最有效地应对美元下滑。【原文：Traders gauging how to best play a sliding U.S. dollar are eyeing the relative strength of economies around the world, as rate cuts from global central banks shake up currency markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-bears-eye-shifts-global-yields-growth-play-weakening-us-currency-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YC7WLZRAVPVPCJ6LOHMPAFAKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 05:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：采购经理人指数为降息铺平道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZEFSXPGKVOJXIH6HGMSCSPZ6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 04:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲律宾对科技巨头的数字服务征收 12% 的增值税]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲律宾国内税收机构周四表示，菲律宾将对亚马逊、Netflix、迪士尼和 Alphabet 等科技巨头提供的数字服务征收 12% 的增值税（VAT），此举将与国内实体企业公平竞争。【原文：The Philippines will impose a 12% value-added tax (VAT) on digital services offered by tech giants such as Amazon , Netflix , Disney , and Alphabet , in a move that will level the playing field with domestic brick and mortar players, the internal revenue agency said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/philippines-levies-12-vat-tax-digital-services-by-tech-giants-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VR3JGS4P6NJRXP25BVMFBLQYDU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 03:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行加息押注减弱，日本股市反弹，日元走软]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于今年进一步收紧货币政策的风险减弱，日本股市周四跳涨，日元下跌，而香港股市的飙升势头也得到了喘息。【原文：Japanese stocks jumped and the yen fell on Thursday as the risk of further tightening in monetary policy this year faded, while the sizzling rally in Hong Kong's share market took a breather.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWTDPPMS7NPMVGMG5HSPSX7QBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 02:15:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在日本央行总裁的出生地，上田的政策之谜昭然若揭]]></title><description><![CDATA[要想了解日本央行行长上田一夫在使世界第四大经济体摆脱货币刺激政策方面所面临的挑战，请看他的出生地。【原文：For a sense of the challenges Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda faces in weaning the world's fourth-largest economy off monetary stimulus, look no further than his birthplace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/bank-japan-chiefs-birthplace-uedas-policy-puzzle-is-laid-bare-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53GZTS7U3ROBLGVYAEIRDBXLW4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 02:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行决策者呼吁缓慢谨慎地上调利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行的一位鸽派决策者周四表示，日本央行有进一步加息的空间，但必须谨慎而缓慢地行动，以避免对经济造成伤害，这强化了市场对日本央行不会急于提高借贷成本的看法。【原文：Japan's central bank has scope to raise interest rates further but must move cautiously and slowly to avoid hurting the economy, a dovish policymaker said on Thursday, reinforcing market views it will be in no rush to lift borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-must-patiently-maintain-loose-policy-says-board-member-noguchi-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPKNKFQCLBJ3FPAOE7JDCZRS3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 01:54:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元兑日元汇率触及一个月高点，因美联储被认为需要时间降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑日元汇率周四升至一个月高点，原因是美国就业市场的强劲表现支持了美联储不必急于降息的观点。【原文：The dollar rose to a one-month high versus the yen on Thursday as robustness in the U.S. jobs market backed the idea that the Federal Reserve does not need to rush to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-hits-one-month-peak-yen-fed-seen-taking-time-with-rate-cuts-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTQOGYP6K5KIVJGKKP6BDUOSWY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本服务业连续第三个月扩张，但信心下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一项民间调查显示，日本服务业活动在 9 月份连续第三个月扩张，但速度略有放缓，信心也有所下降，这表明在制造业疲软的情况下，更广泛的经济出现了紧张。【原文：Japan's service sector activity expanded for the third straight month in September, but the pace slowed slightly and confidence dipped in a sign of the broader economic strains amid weakness in manufacturing, a private survey showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-service-sector-expands-third-month-confidence-dips-pmi-shows-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDPQDF774ZPTXALSAMMTQO5QKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:33:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东冲突加深导致石油上涨，全球供应前景限制涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四早盘，油价走高，原因是投资者权衡了中东冲突升级和原油流动中断的可能性，以及全球市场供应充足的情况。【原文：Oil prices ticked higher in early trade on Thursday as investors weighed the escalating conflict in the Middle East and the potential for disruption to crude flows, against an amply-supplied global market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-rises-middle-east-conflict-deepens-gains-capped-by-global-supply-outlook-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWISCAGVERLNRMD3DFALKKFL3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空董事购买 360 万股股票，反对更多领导层变动]]></title><description><![CDATA[西南航空董事拉克什-甘瓦尔（Rakesh Gangwal）在一位激进投资者日益增长的压力下被公司选入董事会，他买入了超过 1 亿美元的股票，并在周三表示，更多高层领导的变动将 "适得其反"。【原文：Southwest Airlines Director Rakesh Gangwal, who was picked by the company to join its board amid growing pressure from an activist investor, bought more than $100 million in stock and said on Wednesday more top level leadership changes would be "counterproductive."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-director-buys-36-mln-shares-opposes-more-leadership-changes-2024-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJ5CIEQ7JNKK7L2RZZREBMQKCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:27:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚西太平洋银行将向 Resimac 集团出售汽车金融贷款记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[西太平洋银行（Westpac Banking Corp）周四表示，将向非银行贷款机构 Resimac Group 出售其汽车融资贷款账簿，预计出售完成时价值为 14 亿澳元（9.6362 亿美元）至 16 亿澳元。【原文：Westpac Banking Corp said on Thursday it would sell its auto finance loans book to non-bank lender Resimac Group for an expected value of A$1.4 billion ($963.62 million) to A$1.6 billion at completion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-westpac-sell-auto-finance-loan-book-resimac-group-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAJCNWB4CNPCDJ337FNBHCAGQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 23:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，由于销售放缓，丰田将把美国电动汽车生产推迟到 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周四报道，日本汽车制造商丰田汽车公司将以设计调整和销售放缓为由，把在美国肯塔基州工厂生产电动汽车的时间推迟到2026年上半年。【原文：Japanese automaker Toyota Motor would postpone the production of electric vehicles at its Kentucky plant in the US to the first half of 2026, citing design adjustments and slowing sales, the Nikkei business daily reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-delay-us-ev-production-2026-amid-slowing-sales-nikkei-reports-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQDXYH3LWVMTLF3KAXEFEMQQUU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 22:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网站显示特斯拉在美国停产最经济实惠的 Model 3 车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[据特斯拉电动汽车制造商网站周三称，该公司最经济实惠的 Model 3 紧凑型轿车在美国已不再接受订购。【原文：Tesla's most affordable Model 3 compact sedan was no longer available for order in the U.S., according to the EV maker's website on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-discontinues-most-affordable-model-3-variant-us-website-shows-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOPNHC2PCNIHXB5JFXKJ6LBK4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 22:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会对限制其加密货币监管的决定提出上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周三表示，它将对法院限制其监管加密货币市场能力的裁决提起上诉。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Wednesday it is appealing a court ruling that restricted its ability to regulate cryptocurrency markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sec-appeals-decision-that-restricted-its-crypto-oversight-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BGL37K3GVNQDCHW4EMG5F7Z5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 22:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元因日本首相 "不体面 "的利率言论而受到冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZNHJ5OLDZLMZFC33SHA6HLQIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>