<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:07:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:07:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[梅西百货季度净销售额不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[梅西百货公司（Macy's）周一公布的初步财报显示，该公司第三季度销售额不及华尔街预期，原因是大幅促销活动未能吸引那些对购物持选择性态度的顾客。【原文：Macy's on Monday missed Wall Street expectations for third -quarter sales in its preliminary results, as steep promotions failed to attract customers who have turned selective on purchases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/macys-misses-quarterly-net-sales-expectations-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPEJBQ5L45J3NN3GGQCJACTMG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行将 2025 年标准普尔 500 指数预期从 6,500 点上调至 6,600 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）周一将 2025 年 S&amp;P 500 指数的预测值从 6500 点上调至 6600 点，原因是美国经济具有活力，通胀率逐步下降，巨型科技股的潜在盈利增长强劲。【原文：Barclays raised its 2025 forecast for the S&amp;P 500 index on Monday to 6,600 from 6,500, on the back of a resilient U.S. economy, gradual decrease in inflation and robust potential earnings growth of mega-cap technology stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-raises-2025-sp-500-index-forecast-6600-6500-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6CBEWXZ3JOM3POR4XQVBKSY7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:56:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百合花的陨落凸显了空中出租车的资金紧张问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[本月，德国的 Lilium 公司因现金危机而倒闭，使西方第一家载客空中出租车公司的竞争失去了一个引人注目的竞争对手，这使新兴行业面临的一个主要障碍成为新的焦点。【原文：The race to become the first Western air-taxi company to carry passengers lost a high-profile competitor this month when Germany's Lilium succumbed to a cash crisis, throwing a fresh spotlight on a major hurdle for the fledgling industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/liliums-fall-throws-spotlight-air-taxi-cash-crunch-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNB5DBDFWFJN3J4E6PVQA3EVCE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:53:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼称苹果公司 1 亿美元的投资方案不够充分]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚工业部周一表示，苹果公司提出的投资 1 亿美元建设配件和组件工厂的建议不足以让印尼允许这家科技巨头销售其最新款 iPhone。【原文：Indonesia said a $100 million investment proposal from Apple to build an accessory and component plant was not enough for the country to allow the tech giant to sell its latest iPhone model, its industry ministry said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indonesia-says-apples-100-mln-investment-proposal-inadequate-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSX35KNNTRMDFJXH2DE4TD55NA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：国债因贝森特的选择而反弹，美元回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLRIL74ZMJJHHKBXBGWWIFURXI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:45:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中央银行称泰国银行系统流动性严重过剩]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国一位助理行长周一表示，泰国银行系统流动性严重过剩，而央行并未加强贷款监管，这反映出银行不愿放贷。【原文：Thailand's banking system has large excess liquidity and the central bank has not tightened its lending supervision, an assistant governor said on Monday, reflecting banks' reluctance to lend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thai-banking-system-has-large-excess-liquidity-cbank-says-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISYZDCZHRNKHVIYBZ6MCH36TWQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:41:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国首席执行官向员工保证，道明银行准备聘请合规监督员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉情况的消息人士透露，道明银行正准备安装美国政府下令安装的监控器，并已采取行动向员工保证，道明银行有足够的资源来遵守禁止洗钱的法律。【原文：TD Bank is preparing to install U.S. government-ordered monitors and has moved to reassure employees that it had enough resources to comply with laws prohibiting money laundering, according to two sources familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/td-bank-prepares-hire-compliance-monitors-us-ceo-reassures-staff-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7Q33A7QTNI5DEJMGBTRPUM7BY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:32:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的大型减税计划可能因债券市场的谨慎而放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）领导的共和党人承诺在明年完全控制美国国会后将加大油门，几乎没有什么能阻止他们执行当选总统削减税收和重整全球贸易格局的承诺。【原文：Donald Trump's Republicans are promising to hit the gas next year when they assume full control of the U.S. Congress, with little to stop them from executing the president-elect's promises to slash taxes and reorder the global trade landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/trumps-big-tax-cut-plans-could-be-slowed-by-wary-bond-market-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7IKNXJ4MFMJZA3LXNLD4KWM7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：投资者挖掘新数据，预测零售商业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一些人预计会令人失望的节假日来临之际，高盛等华尔街投资者正在使用新的方法来监控购物者的行动和意图，以帮助确定本季度的赢家和输家。【原文：Heading into holidays some expect to disappoint, Wall Street investors like Goldman Sachs are using new ways to monitor shoppers' actions and intentions to help determine the season's winners and losers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/investors-mining-new-data-predict-retailers-results-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N7LSTLNJDVIC5EVCZWNQNYX6C4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圭亚那选择美国新创公司开采巨大天然气储量面临障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[圭亚那选择了一家名不见经传的美国初创公司来设计和开发项目，使其尚未开发的大量天然气资源货币化，而这些项目的成本可能高达 300 亿美元。
 成立一年之久的 Fulcrum LNG 公司面临着融资障碍，这可能会影响它的选择。最终，这个南美国家可能会依赖埃克森美孚牵头的财团，该财团控制着南美所有的天然气生产。【原文：Doubts are growing over Guyana's pick of a little-known U.S. startup to craft and develop projects to monetize its vast untapped natural gas resources that could cost up to $30 billion.
 Year-old Fulcrum LNG faces financing hurdles that could derail its selection. Ultimately, the South American nation may end up relying on a consortium led by Exxon Mobil , which controls all the production in the】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/guyanas-pick-new-us-startup-faces-hurdles-tap-vast-gas-reserves-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWNTGGNBOVLWNPWNDRCELBLWKA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌网络广告帝国案美国反垄断审判接近尾声]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部将于周一就谷歌非法主宰在线广告技术进行最后论证，以寻求对该公司的第二次反垄断胜利。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice will make its final argument on Monday that Google illegally dominated online advertising technology, seeking a second antitrust win against the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/googles-us-antitrust-trial-over-online-ad-empire-draws-close-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4O7UKWF2FBMKRMCGON5EFZ44SQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:04:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特朗普准备制定广泛的能源计划，以促进天然气出口和石油钻探]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉该计划的消息人士透露，唐纳德-特朗普的过渡团队正在制定一个范围广泛的能源方案，将在他上任后几天内推出，该方案将批准新液化天然气（LNG）项目的出口许可，并增加美国沿海和联邦土地上的石油钻探。【原文：Donald Trump's transition team is putting together a wide-ranging energy package to roll out within days of his taking office that would approve export permits for new liquefied natural gas (LNG) projects and increase oil drilling off the U.S. coast and on federal lands, according to two sources familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-prepares-wide-ranging-energy-plan-boost-gas-exports-oil-drilling-sources-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMEMLFVENVLQ3CZT4LTUBLOMNA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:03:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新任财政部长值得关注的五张关键图表]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五表示，他将提名斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）担任第79任美国财政部长，并为当选总统的激进经济政策打头阵。【原文：Donald Trump on Friday said he would nominate Scott Bessent to be the 79th U.S. Treasury secretary and frontman for the president-elect's aggressive economic policies, a slate that financial markets already anticipate will add to economic growth in the near term but also rekindle inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/five-key-charts-new-treasury-secretary-watch-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6SFRUETJBL7JKPXWFMVTFS7NU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道指期货创历史新高，市场盛赞特朗普的财政部长人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[受投资者对斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）被提名为财政部长的乐观情绪推动，道指合约周一触及纪录高位，领涨美国股指期货。【原文：Dow contracts touched a record high on Monday, leading gains among U.S. stock index futures, fueled by investor optimism over Scott Bessent's nomination as Treasury Secretary.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/dow-futures-hit-all-time-high-markets-laud-trumps-treasury-pick-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DJ7JZSVWRKEJB24YXIZJQF2CY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:56:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果供应商康宁在欧盟反垄断调查中提出放弃排他性交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周一表示，美国抗碎玻璃制造商康宁公司已主动提出放弃与手机制造商的所有排他性协议，以消除人们对其可能存在的反竞争行为的担忧。【原文：The European Commission on Monday said U.S. maker of break resisting glass Corning had offered to waive all exclusive deals with mobile phone manufactures to address concerns over possible anticompetitive behaviour.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-supplier-corning-offers-waive-exclusive-deals-eu-antitrust-probe-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTMDS2PRYVOBTNCONUCMCMOSLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中出租车公司 Vertical 称 Mudrick 将把部分票据转换为股权，并延长还款期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国垂直宇航公司（Vertical Aerospace）周一表示，投资者穆德里克资本（Mudrick Capital）已同意将其50%的未偿还可转换债务票据转换为股权，并将其余票据的偿还日期延长至2028年12月，从而为这家资金短缺的空中出租车制造商提供了财务喘息空间。【原文：UK-based Vertical Aerospace said on Monday that investor Mudrick Capital has agreed to convert 50% of its outstanding convertible debt notes to equity and extend the repayment date on the rest to December 2028, giving the cash-strapped air-taxi maker financial breathing room.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-taxi-firm-vertical-says-mudrick-covert-some-notes-equity-extend-repayment-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDCWAGV6FRN25MDEVK3V5FTSZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:22:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敲定授予 BAE 系统公司和火箭实验室半导体芯片合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，将最终确定向 BAE 系统公司提供近 6000 万美元的政府补贴，用于制造喷气机和卫星使用的芯片，以及向火箭实验室提供补贴，用于制造卫星和航天器使用的化合物半导体。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Monday it is finalizing nearly $60 million in government subsidies for BAE Systems to build chips used in jets and satellites, and for Rocket Lab to build compound semiconductors used in satellites and spacecraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-finalizes-awards-bae-systems-rocket-lab-semiconductor-chips-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR7WF6W4QZOXBPUMEABMUBFVO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，奥地利与俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司长达半个世纪的合作因天然气被没收而终止]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位消息人士告诉路透社，本月早些时候结束俄罗斯国有能源巨头俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司（Gazprom）与 OMV 长达 50 多年天然气流通的导火索是这家奥地利集团扣押了俄罗斯天然气，作为支付仲裁裁决价值的款项。【原文：The trigger that ended more than 50 years of gas flows from Russian state energy giant Gazprom to OMV earlier this month was the Austrian group's seizure of Russian gas as payment to cover the value of an arbitration award, five sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/austrias-half-century-bond-with-gazprom-ended-by-gas-seizure-sources-say-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMYSK24IWBKELH4EDVLIE4LWXI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:57:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金押注电力，扎堆材料行业，高盛集团称]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）称，截至上周五的一周内，全球对冲基金以两个月来最快的速度抛售了美国电力和水务公司股票，同时买入了美国化工、金属和矿业等材料类股票以及造纸和森林类股票。【原文：Global hedge funds sold U.S. electric and water utilities stocks at the fastest pace in two months while buying U.S. materials stocks such as chemicals, metals and mining as well as paper and forest shares in the week to Friday, Goldman Sachs said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-bet-against-power-pile-into-materials-says-goldman-sachs-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P642YXGN3VNWLCJDPYH5TA4VTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司表示不会为阿达尼集团的投资提供新的资金支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies SE）周一表示，鉴于美国联邦政府对阿达尼公司负责人及其侄子的起诉，道达尔能源公司将不再为其对阿达尼集团公司的投资提供新的资金支持。【原文：TotalEnergies SE said on Monday that it will not make any new financial contribution as part of its investments into the Adani group of companies amid a U.S. federal indictment against the head of the company and his nephew.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/totalenergies-says-it-will-make-no-new-financial-contribution-adani-group-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRTF2GFFKRIQVIEQY2Y6ZJDFTM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Expansion 称，Blackstone 将于 2025 年初将西班牙 Cirsa 股份在马德里上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地报纸 Expansion 周一援引未具名市场消息人士的话报道，私募股权投资者 Blackstone 计划于 2025 年上半年将西班牙博彩公司 Cirsa 的股票首次公开发行上市。【原文：Private equity investor Blackstone plans to list shares of Spanish gambling company Cirsa in the first half of 2025 in an initial public offering, local newspaper Expansion reported on Monday, citing unidentified market sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstone-list-spains-cirsa-shares-madrid-early-2025-expansion-says-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5XFGUQ2VJNO5XM3DI6IY4FUTLA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪称明年将推出新一代叶片电池]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家媒体 CGTN 周六报道，中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪表示，将于 2025 年推出新一代叶片电池。【原文：China's electric vehicle giant BYD said it will launch a new generation of blade batteries in 2025, Chinese state media CGTN reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-says-it-will-launch-new-generation-blade-batteries-next-year-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZ2LDED6TNIRFDRITHN47I6C4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英美资源集团同意以高达 37.8 亿美元的价格向皮博迪能源公司出售澳大利亚煤矿]]></title><description><![CDATA[英美资源集团（Anglo American）周一同意将其澳大利亚炼钢煤矿出售给皮博迪能源公司（Peabody Energy），现金对价高达 37.8 亿美元。【原文：Anglo American on Monday agreed to sell its Australian steelmaking coal mines to Peabody Energy for a cash consideration of up to $3.78 billion, in its first major disposal as part of a wider restructuring plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/anglo-agrees-sell-australian-coal-mines-up-378-bln-peabody-energy-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDXZURJ7LVOQDAERC3BQ3B46WA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国商务部副部长会见英伟达高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部表示，中国商务部副部长王受文周一在北京会见了英伟达全球现场运营执行副总裁 Jay Puri。【原文：Wang Shouwen, China's vice commerce minister, met with Jay Puri, an executive vice president of Nvidia's worldwide field operations, in Beijing on Monday, China's Ministry of Commerce said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-vice-commerce-minister-meets-with-nvidia-senior-executive-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VM5NVBBL7JLX5AXMS5NHQ4C55E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:40:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：债券反弹，美元因国债选择而下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O62ZRZEHCJMVBGEXMP4MMB7LWM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利联合信贷银行提出以 105.7 亿美元收购 BPM 银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）周一表示，它已提出收购竞争对手 Banco BPM 银行，股票交易价值约为 100.9 亿欧元（105.7 亿美元）。【原文：Italian lender UniCredit said on Monday it had offered to buy rival Banco BPM in a stock deal valued at about 10.09 billion euros ($10.57 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/italys-unicredit-offers-buy-banco-bpm-1057-bln-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVFM6YATUFLU3B4RSOTHNEOXLI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:25:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DHL 货运飞机在维尔纽斯机场附近坠毁，造成一死两伤]]></title><description><![CDATA[机场、警察和消防人员告诉路透社，一架 DHL 货运飞机于格林尼治标准时间周一 3 时 30 分左右在立陶宛维尔纽斯机场附近坠毁，造成一人死亡，两人受伤。【原文：A DHL cargo plane crashed near Lithuania’s Vilnius airport on Monday at about 0330 GMT, killing one person and injuring two others, airport, police and firefighter officials told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/dhl-cargo-plane-crashes-near-vilnius-airport-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZZVL5PCZ5KSVDGCQKPXZ2JM5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面对喜忧参半的 COP29 气候信息，企业界寻求详细信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果明年各国能够提出气候计划，并为市场和投资制定明确的政策，那么 COP29 就金融和碳市场达成的协议将为商业世界带来数十亿美元的资金流。【原文：COP29 deals on finance and carbon markets could lead to billions more dollars flowing around the business world if countries next year can deliver climate plans with clear policies for markets and investment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/business-seeks-details-face-mixed-cop29-climate-messages-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWZSOONI3BI7RGNNQRNMZEGDME</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元随国债提名债券收益率下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，由于美国财长人选似乎安抚了债券市场，并拉低了收益率，削弱了美元的部分汇率优势，美元稍稍回吐了近期涨幅。【原文：The dollar relinquished a little of its recent gains on Monday as the pick for U.S. Treasury secretary seemed to reassure the bond market and pulled yields lower, shaving some of the currency's rate advantage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-slips-with-bond-yields-treasury-nomination-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6P572C3G5NKZTGAU4RJJ2WFORY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：特朗普财政部长人选斯科特-贝森特将优先考虑减税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特在周日发表的一篇采访中告诉《华尔街日报》，他将优先兑现大选时的减税承诺。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's nominee for U.S. Treasury secretary, Scott Bessent, will prioritize delivering on election tax cut pledges, he told the Wall Street Journal in an interview published on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-treasury-pick-scott-bessent-prioritize-tax-cuts-wsj-reports-2024-11-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3T2YR2OXVFJ7DCLV4FMX7ACFOA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>