<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:06:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:06:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国对华加征关税，人民币跌至 2007 年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于不断升级的中美贸易战令货币市场惶恐不安，中国离岸人民币隔夜跌至历史新低，周三收于逾17年来最弱水平。【原文：China's yuan ended at its weakest level in more than 17 years on Wednesday after its offshore counterpart fell to a record low overnight, as an escalating Sino-U.S. trade war rattled currency markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yuan-falls-2007-lows-us-tariffs-china-kick-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUZ5IOKZOBKKJHMZVQNU3MVMFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航运集团三井物产抓住关税推动贸易路线转变的机遇--首席执行官称]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本第二大航运公司三井物产航运（Mitsui O.S.K.Lines，MOL）首席执行官桥本武（Takeshi Hashimoto）表示，该公司的目标是抓住美国新关税导致贸易路线发生变化所带来的机遇。【原文：Mitsui O.S.K. Lines (MOL) , Japan's second-largest shipping company, aims to capitalise on opportunities that emerge from a shift in trade routes driven by new U.S. tariffs, CEO Takeshi Hashimoto said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shipping-group-mitsui-osk-seize-opportunities-tariffs-drive-trade-route-shift-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UG7D4HHI5VIBHEHH26W4GQNLDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对等关税撼动全球贸易，期货市场步履维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的对等关税生效，加深了人们对其对全球经济造成损害的担忧，美国股指期货在前一交易日遭到严重抛售后，周三陷入困境。【原文：U.S. stock index futures struggled on Wednesday after a heavy sell-off in the previous session, as President Donald Trump's reciprocal tariff took effect, deepening worries about their damage to the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-struggle-trumps-reciprocal-tariffs-shake-up-global-trade-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVNX3CBQNRNJFD67QSZP25ODFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:44:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道苹果供应商 Luxshare 考虑在美国生产以应对关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果供应商力士德公司董事长周三在电话中告诉分析师，该公司正在与客户商讨如何应对美国关税，将更多生产转移到中国以外的地区，包括美国。【原文：Apple supplier Luxshare is in talks with customers on ways to respond to U.S. tariffs by shifting more production outside China, including the United States, its chairwoman told analysts in a telephone call on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-supplier-luxshare-weighs-manufacturing-us-tackle-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REIXYO5ZL5IDFAX3QW6DTFNLKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国审查社交媒体上与关税相关的部分内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国对数十个国家的 "对等 "关税生效（包括对中国商品征收104%的巨额关税）之后，中国于周三开始审查社交媒体上一些与关税相关的内容，而批评美国的帖子则成为热门话题。【原文：China began censoring some tariff-related content on social media on Wednesday after U.S. "reciprocal" tariffs on dozens of countries took effect, including massive 104% duties on Chinese goods, while posts criticising the U.S. were top hits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-censors-some-tariff-related-content-social-media-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGEUJK75V5N3FMOGUQX34JN5TI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场环境严峻，大众汽车公司的特拉托第一季度销售额下降 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，大众汽车卡车部门特拉托（Traton）报告称，第一季度交付量下降了 10%，原因是市场环境充满挑战。【原文：Volkswagen's truck unit Traton reported a 10% drop in first-quarter deliveries on Wednesday, citing a challenging market environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vws-traton-posts-10-drop-q1-sales-challenging-market-environment-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2EAUPF4JZPUVG3XSN33TJOHKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:16:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 为 110 亿美元的欧洲房地产收购狂潮做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blackstone 表示，尽管市场动荡加剧，但该公司已完成 98 亿欧元（108 亿美元）的欧洲房地产基金，押注该行业的复苏迹象。【原文：Blackstone has said it has closed a 9.8 billion euro ($10.8 billion) European property fund, as it bets on signs of recovery for the sector despite deepening market turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstone-gears-up-11-billion-european-property-buying-spree-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63FQSDQY2BNOVK7A3AM6Q66VE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本最高货币外交官敦促全球合作应对关税困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最高货币外交官周三表示，日本将与七国集团发达经济体和国际货币基金组织合作，帮助稳定美国关税引发的市场崩溃。【原文：Japan will cooperate with the Group of Seven advanced economies and the International Monetary Fund to help stablise a market rout unleashed by U.S. tariffs, the country's top currency diplomat said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-top-currency-diplomat-urges-global-cooperation-fight-tariff-woes-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COB2SSK5TNIWFLJAERYUIED2L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国监管机构在达成补救措施后结束对谷歌车载服务的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国联邦卡特尔局周三表示，在美国科技巨头承诺采取补救措施解决其对竞争的担忧后，该局已结束了对谷歌汽车服务的诉讼程序。【原文：Germany's Federal Cartel Office has closed proceedings into Google's automotive services after the U.S. tech giant committed to remedies addressing its concerns over competition, the regulator said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/german-regulator-ends-probe-into-googles-in-car-services-after-agreed-remedies-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNNLW3WKXJPEFMCTSVAPL5C2XU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车第一季度交付量增长 1.4%，几乎所有市场均有助益]]></title><description><![CDATA[在几乎所有市场需求增长的帮助下，德国汽车制造商大众汽车今年前三个月的汽车交付量略有上升。【原文：German carmaker Volkswagen saw a slight rise in vehicle deliveries during the first three months of the year, helped by growing demand in almost all markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-q1-deliveries-rise-14-helped-by-almost-all-markets-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22YPHYVWCRLIFANJIIZCESV65U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长诺特：关税会造成长期滞胀冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行（ECB）政策制定者克拉斯-克诺（Klaas Knot）周三表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收进口关税的做法很可能在长期内造成滞胀影响，在经济增长停滞的同时推高通胀。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping import tariffs are likely to have a stagflationary impact in the long term, driving up inflation while economic growth stalls, ECB policy maker Klaas Knot said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/tariffs-create-stagflationary-shock-long-term-ecbs-knot-says-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5VWGRR37FI5LI52VBUUFNQLTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士：欧洲央行准备应对关税对经济增长造成的超预期打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位消息人士告诉路透社，欧元区经济增长受美国贸易关税影响的跌幅可能比欧洲央行最初估计的要大得多，而且这场动荡还可能在短期内拖累通胀。【原文：Euro zone economic growth could fall much more from the impact of U.S. trade tariffs than initially estimated by the European Central Bank and the turmoil could also drag inflation down in the near term, four sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecb-braces-bigger-than-anticipated-growth-hit-tariffs-sources-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPXBKKXQINK6VKBJQ5TXOM3SXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:52:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税不确定，佩特拉钻石公司推迟库里南矿招标]]></title><description><![CDATA[拥有世界第三大钻石资源的佩特拉钻石公司（Petra Diamonds）周三表示，已推迟销售其南非库里南矿的宝石，直到美国关税的影响更加明朗。【原文：Petra Diamonds , which has the world's third-largest resource of diamonds, said on Wednesday it had delayed the sale of gems from its Cullinan Mine in South Africa until there was greater clarity around the impact of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/petra-diamonds-delays-cullinan-mine-tender-amid-us-tariff-uncertainty-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHZ6WULX6JJYXD2GLFEKVSQHFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税之后，法国商业游说团称对特朗普的看法有误]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国主要商业联合会领导人帕特里克-马丁（Patrick Martin）周三表示，他对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的看法是错误的，他说那些在一月份为亲商政策喝彩的法国企业没有想到他会继续征收关税。【原文：The leader of the main French business federation, Patrick Martin, said on Wednesday he had got it wrong on U.S. President Donald Trump, saying French firms who applauded pro-business policies in January did not imagine he would go ahead with tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/after-tariffs-french-business-lobby-says-it-got-it-wrong-trump-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6JNRCXFUVMSJF772RJJOFCFWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟国家将批准对美国关税的首次报复行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟国家预计将于周三批准该集团针对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税采取的首批反制措施，加入中国和加拿大的报复行列，并使一场可能演变为全球贸易战的冲突升级。【原文：European Union countries are expected to approve on Wednesday the bloc's first countermeasures against U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, joining China and Canada in retaliating and escalating a conflict that could become a global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-countries-set-approve-first-retaliation-against-us-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYKEITBVYZPH7AYMMX7PLHKE4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乐高在越南开设新工厂，以提高当地产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[玩具制造商乐高（Lego）周三表示，该公司已在越南开设了一家新工厂，目标是在亚太地区实现长期增长，并在更靠近消费者的地方进行生产。【原文：Toymaker Lego said on Wednesday it had opened a new factory in Vietnam, as it aims for long-term growth in the Asia-Pacific region and to produce closer to its consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lego-opens-new-factory-vietnam-increase-local-production-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIQMEIDYUVKYBAYH5HCPOKSAZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称美国贸易顺差 "不可避免"，警告已做好贸易战准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周三称，中国对美国的贸易顺差不可避免，并警告说，如果特朗普继续对中国商品征收关税以试图降低贸易顺差，中国有 "决心和手段 "继续与之抗争。【原文：China on Wednesday called its trade surplus with the United States an inevitability and warned it had the "determination and means" to continue the fight if Trump kept hitting Chinese goods with tariffs to try and bring it down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-says-it-does-not-want-trade-war-will-fight-us-tariff-hikes-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBHRIQMRZFLEBNOMLTINYF5LIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:16:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小型新兴市场美元债券重现跌势，巴基斯坦跌逾 6 美分]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国征收令人瞠目的 104% 关税的政策生效后，风险较小的新兴经济体发行的国际债券周三再次遭遇大幅下挫，再次引发全球市场动荡。【原文：International bonds issued by smaller, riskier, emerging economies suffered another sharp selloff on Wednesday after President Donald Trump's eye-watering 104% tariffs on China took effect, re-igniting turmoil across global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/small-emerging-market-dollar-bonds-resume-selloff-pakistan-drops-more-than-6-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPDNKXSHHZK6BPI2QFBC3RQJXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 3 月汽车销量同比增长 14.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管全球最大汽车市场的通货紧缩压力不断加深，但由于政府补贴的以旧换新促进了对电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车的需求，中国 3 月份的汽车销量同比增长了 14.4%。【原文：China's car sales rose 14.4% in March from a year earlier, as government-subsidised trade-ins bolstered demand for electric vehicles and plug-in hybrids, despite deepening deflationary pressures in the world's largest auto market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-car-sales-rise-144-year-march-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46NHZHB75JNETH53K2NB32SCSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 08:11:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称中国央行要求国有贷款机构减少美元购买量]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接知情人士周三表示，中国央行不会允许人民币大幅下跌，并已要求主要国有银行减少美元购买量。【原文：China's central bank will not allow sharp yuan declines and has asked major state-owned banks to reduce U.S. dollar purchases, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-central-bank-asks-state-lenders-reduce-dollar-purchases-sources-say-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z52JGUAJIVMJJKJHNJTYK74KUQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 07:52:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普征收 104% 关税，中国誓言采取坚决措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对中国进口商品征收104%的关税后，中国周三誓言将采取坚决有效的措施维护自身权益。【原文：China on Wednesday vowed to take resolute and effective measures to safeguard its rights and interests, after U.S. President Donald Trump's 104% duties on Chinese imports kicked in.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-vows-resolute-measures-trumps-104-tariffs-kick-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55E4XTMLWVKAZLJP2XADYPFHP4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 07:21:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受船运紧张和贸易战影响，亚洲买家回避美国农产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于华盛顿计划对与中国有联系的船只征收费用，并对主要的地区贸易伙伴全面征收进口关税，这些都引发了不确定性，并抑制了对美国产品的需求，亚洲买家正在减少对美国农产品的采购。【原文：Asian buyers are reducing purchases of U.S. agricultural goods as Washington's planned fees on China-linked vessels and sweeping import duties on key regional trading partners stoke uncertainty and dampen appetite for American products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asian-buyers-shun-us-farm-goods-hit-by-ship-crunch-trade-war-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UITOLDJGTRNZPN6TAFDXU4ZLZU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 07:09:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，近半数瑞士企业预计美国关税将带来重大打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项调查显示，瑞士企业担心美国关税将打击美国的需求，引发经济衰退，并使其在与竞争对手的竞争中处于不利地位。【原文：Swiss firms are concerned U.S. tariffs will hit demand in the United States, spark an economic downturn and put them at a disadvantage against rivals, a survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/nearly-half-swiss-firms-expect-major-hit-us-tariffs-survey-shows-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEVOWFQ2TZLATHZA2TIOZIFOVU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 07:04:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国部长敦促法国公司暂停在美投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[鉴于法国和欧洲与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政府在关税问题上的冲突，法国工业部长马克-费拉齐（Marc Ferracci）周三敦促法国企业暂停在美国的投资。【原文：French industry minister Marc Ferracci on Wednesday urged French companies to suspend their investments in the United States, given clashes between France and Europe with U.S. President Donald Trump's administration over tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/french-minister-urges-french-companies-suspend-investments-us-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNYJPZXXK5IDDKZXAW5WQFPVKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 07:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 Seven & i 公司称第四季度利润下降 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本七喜控股公司（Seven & i Holdings）周三表示，第四季度利润下降了 15%，这一结果很可能阻碍其抵御加拿大 Alimentation Couche-Tard 公司收购企图的能力。【原文：Japan's Seven & i Holdings said on Wednesday fourth-quarter profit fell 15%, a result that is likely to hamper its ability to fend off a takeover attempt by Canada's Alimentation Couche-Tard .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/japans-seven-i-says-q4-profit-fell-15-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ORMECKH45OWDGNXN2YV25PRQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 06:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行上田坚持加息立场，但发出关注风险的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田一夫（Kazuo Ueda）周三表示，如果经济持续复苏，央行将继续提高利率，但将 "不带先入为主 "地审查其经济预测是否实现。【原文：Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda said on Wednesday the central bank will continue to raise interest rates if the economy keeps recovering, but will scrutinise "without pre-conception" whether its economic forecasts materialise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/bojs-ueda-sticks-rate-hike-stance-signals-focus-risks-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5D44FWDARZLONAN6UHIPD6DBN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 06:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称中国将召开高级别会议应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士称，在与美国的贸易战不断升级之际，中国最高领导人计划最早于周三召开会议，讨论提振经济和稳定资本市场的措施。【原文：China's top leaders plan to convene a meeting as early as Wednesday to discuss measures to boost the economy and stabilise the capital markets, people with knowledge of the matter said, amid an escalating trade war with the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-hold-high-level-meeting-response-us-tariffs-say-sources-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7PQB76PIBM3RJWST63QN4QVU4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 06:28:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着贸易紧张局势升级，中国 3 月份银行贷款出现反弹：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三的一项民意调查显示，中国新增人民币贷款在2月份大幅下降后，3月份可能出现反弹，因为决策者承诺采取新的刺激措施，以应对全球贸易战不断恶化带来的日益严重的经济逆风。【原文：China's new yuan loans likely rebounded in March after a sharp fall in February, a Reuters poll showed on Wednesday, as policymakers pledged fresh stimulus to counter mounting economic headwinds amid a worsening global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-march-bank-loans-seen-rebounding-trade-tensions-escalate-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBLEM6G3BBNWFARNGR5B7PFAUM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 06:22:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Assura 公司同意 KKR-Stonepeak 20.6 亿美元的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[KKR-Stonepeak 财团周三表示，将以 16.1 亿英镑（20.6 亿美元）的价格收购英国医疗保健房地产投资信托公司 Assura。【原文：A KKR-Stonepeak consortium would buy British healthcare REIT Assura for 1.61 billion pounds ($2.06 billion), the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/uks-assura-rejects-15-billion-bid-php-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NP3FUCJ2MJMDBDAZSFASOZQHGQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 06:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优衣库运营商 Fast Retailing 第二季度利润大增 14%，关税问题迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[优衣库的经营者、日本 Fast Retailing 公司预计将于周四公布另一季度的强劲财报，但人们关注的焦点将是这家全球服装连锁店如何应对因美国新关税而陷入混乱的贸易环境。【原文：The operator of Uniqlo, Japan's Fast Retailing , is expected to post another quarter of strong earnings on Thursday, but the focus will be on how the global clothing chain navigates a trade environment thrown into disarray by new U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uniqlo-operator-fast-retailing-seen-posting-14-jump-q2-profit-tariffs-loom-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCC7SM374ZIW3F7PGYHM6ET5BY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 06:11:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>