<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:46:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:46:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[因冷却系统需求旺盛，开利利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[开利全球（Carrier Global）周二公布的第四季度利润好于预期，主要得益于对其供暖、通风和空调产品以及售后维修服务的需求。【原文：Carrier Global on Tuesday reported a better-than-expected fourth-quarter profit, benefiting from demand for its heating, ventilating and air conditioning products and aftermarket repair services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/carrier-profit-beats-estimates-demand-cooling-systems-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5ZTP6Q3XRI25K6PF4XJ4HRXEI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将废除家电和灯泡标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二在社交媒体上发文称，环境保护局将恢复以前对淋浴、马桶、洗碗机和其他电器的用水标准，以及以前对灯泡的用水标准。【原文：The Environmental Protection Agency will revert to previous water standards for showers, toilets, dishwashers and other appliances, and previous standards for light bulbs, U.S. President Donald Trump said in a social media post on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-roll-back-appliance-light-bulb-standards-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RL6BQUSZDJMJHNJ6VYV5B7NJEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:21:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着特朗普加密货币政策的成形，Binance 和美国证券交易委员会要求暂停法律战]]></title><description><![CDATA[Binance 和美国证券交易委员会以新成立的特别工作组的潜在影响为由，联合请求法院对监管机构针对该加密货币交易所的诉讼延期 60 天。【原文：Binance and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission have jointly asked a court for a 60-day stay on the regulator's lawsuit against the crypto exchange, citing the potential impact of a newly launched task force.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/binance-sec-request-pause-legal-battle-trumps-crypto-policy-takes-shape-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IASPWXFA2RO4JNWNJUP6HG4UFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:15:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[万豪全年业绩预期因中国经济放缓而受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[受大中华区酒店业绩不佳的影响，酒店运营商万豪国际集团周二预计 2025 年的利润和费用收入将低于华尔街预期，股价在盘前交易中下跌 1.6%。【原文：Hotel operator Marriott International forecast 2025 profit and fee revenue below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, hurt by poor performance at its hotels in Greater China, sending shares down 1.6% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/marriotts-2025-profit-forecast-falls-short-expectations-china-performance-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6BHRXTXIRNPLCQBZOI5W3ES7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可口可乐公司预测 2025 年有机收入增长不乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[可口可乐公司周二预测今年的有机收入增长将低于预期，这家饮料生产商在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）关税引发的不确定性中降低了预期。【原文：Coca-Cola on Tuesday forecast downbeat organic revenue growth this year on Tuesday, as the beverage maker tempers expectations amid uncertainty fueled by President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coca-cola-forecasts-downbeat-2025-organic-revenue-growth-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDIBBRA4LVKNDLKHIACAXXEDMM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[武器装备需求激增，莱多斯公司季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，国防承包商莱多斯公司（Leidos）第四季度盈利超出预期，主要得益于地缘政治紧张局势加剧，军费开支增加和武器需求旺盛。【原文：Defense contractor Leidos beat expectations for fourth-quarter earnings on Tuesday, aided by increased military spending and robust weapons demand amid rising geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/leidos-beats-quarterly-expectations-surging-weaponry-demand-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPEO4QDZYRMJVHSEA5WLNPW7XA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险公司 Humana 预测年度利润低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，Humana 预测的年度利润低于华尔街的预期，这表明其由政府支持的美国老年人计划的成本在今年剩余时间内仍将居高不下。【原文：Humana forecast annual profit below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, signaling that costs from its government-backed plans for older Americans would remain elevated for the rest of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/humana-forecasts-annual-profit-lower-than-estimates-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ILY5KQJFWZJMRB3PJVDLASD6CI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:40:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：鲍威尔和钢铁，人工智能在发挥作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BCWRFNJZR5O3ZC725GL4RCNAFE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:16:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子产品需求强劲，杜邦上调 2025 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[杜邦公司周二上调了 2025 年利润预期，第四季度盈利超过预期，原因是这家工业材料生产商受益于电子产品的强劲需求以及水和保护部门的复苏。【原文：DuPont de Nemours raised its 2025 profit forecast and beat fourth-quarter earnings estimates on Tuesday, as the industrial materials maker benefited from strong demand for electronics and a recovery in its water and protection segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dupont-raises-2025-profit-forecast-strong-electronics-demand-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJBDODC7UJOYHJNEY6W7P3K5NU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:12:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Ashtead 集团寻求股东批准在纽约上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国设备租赁公司 Ashtead 集团周二表示，将寻求股东批准，以推进其将主要上市地迁往美国并组建新的美国母公司的计划。【原文：British equipment rental firm Ashtead Group said on Tuesday that it would seek shareholder approval to move ahead with its plan to relocate its primary listing to the United States and form a new U.S. parent company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/uks-ashtead-group-seek-shareholder-approval-list-new-york-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHE2FHICLJPUNNRRA3ZCLFWNZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯雷利润低于预期，原因是资产出售收益减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，凯雷集团第四季度可分配利润低于市场预期，这给该另类资产管理公司资本市场业务的强劲增长蒙上了阴影。【原文：Carlyle Group's distributable earnings for the fourth quarter missed market expectations on Tuesday, overshadowing a strong growth in the alternative asset manager's capital market business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyles-profit-misses-estimates-lower-proceeds-asset-sales-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">65AR6NQIQZLZZM22UWNBOT6WE4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在赫斯交易悬而未决之际，雪佛龙努力补充石油和天然气储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司的石油和天然气储量已降至至少十年来的最低点，这凸显了这家美国大型企业计划收购石油生产商赫斯公司的重要性。【原文：Chevron's oil and gas reserves have fallen to the lowest point in at least a decade, highlighting the importance of the U.S. major's planned acquisition of oil producer Hess that has stalled due to a court battle with Exxon Mobil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-struggles-replace-oil-gas-reserves-amid-hess-deal-limbo-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RN4AWFE5CVIOHH5YEIM5P55AQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[许可证持有者称格陵兰废止铀禁令可重振大规模稀土项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[拥有格陵兰 Kvanefjeld 矿床开采许可证的矿业公司希望，新政府将在下月选举后废除铀矿开采禁令，从而有可能使世界上最大的稀土项目之一重新焕发活力。【原文：The mining company that owns the licence to Greenland's Kvanefjeld deposit is hopeful that a new government will repeal a ban on uranium mining after next month's election, potentially rejuvenating one of the world's largest rare earth projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/uranium-ban-repeal-greenland-could-revive-massive-rare-earth-project-licence-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XT4X3OIF3NLH5O2PEKFGVAQI7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普削减对外援助，中国在非洲建立太空联盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[在开罗郊区，一个尖端的太空实验室本应是非洲第一个生产本土卫星的实验室。然而，走进工厂，非洲制造的形象开始褪色【原文：On the outskirts of Cairo, a cutting-edge space lab was supposed to be the first in Africa to produce homegrown satellites. Step inside the plant, though, and the made-in-Africa image begins to fade】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/china-builds-space-alliances-africa-trump-cuts-foreign-aid-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDW7VLSK55JHZK2L36IQV3MLPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:06:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔将出席国会，手握良好数据但不确定性上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔将在国会山开始为期两天的听证会，听证会上，美国经济接近充分就业，预计通胀将有所缓解，而所有这些在特朗普政府的贸易和其他政策下将如何维持，仍存在很大的不确定性。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell begins two days of hearings on Capitol Hill on Tuesday with the economy around full employment, inflation expected to ease, and intense uncertainty about how all that will hold up under Trump administration trade and other policies that are still unfolding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-heads-congress-with-good-data-hand-rising-uncertainty-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYV2DVOKGNLKZO2WWFYOMZWMHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利选民重回保守派安全区，推动市场发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据最近的民意调查和政治分析家的分析，在经历了五年多有可能使智利社会两极分化的政治动荡之后，这个拉美第五大经济体的选民正在重新转向传统的温和保守主义。【原文：After more than five years of political upheaval that threatened to polarize Chilean society, voters in Latin America's fifth-largest economy are shifting back to their traditional moderate conservatism, according to recent polls and political analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chilean-voters-fall-back-conservative-safe-zone-propelling-markets-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWUGW76RA5K2FD4F7VPOM5VMVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔发表讲话，关税和通胀评论成为关注焦点，期指下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周二下滑，因为投资者在等待美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的证词，以了解关税及其对全球最大经济体通胀的影响。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Tuesday as investors awaited a testimony from Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell for insight on tariffs and their impact on inflation in the world's biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-dip-powell-speech-focus-tariff-inflation-comments-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSMR6XMB7NLCZE3DL3QMMXM7YA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 10:53:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提高钢铝关税，欧盟做好应对准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普决定对所有进口钢铁和铝征收关税，加剧了人们对贸易战的担忧，欧盟表示将采取 "坚定和适度的反制措施"。【原文：The European Union said it would respond with "firm and proportionate countermeasures" after U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to impose tariffs on all steel and aluminium imports, escalating fears of a trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/eu-readies-response-trump-hikes-steel-aluminium-tariffs-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LO33LBETZRPTDGTHDNVF3GVSSA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 10:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国副总统 JD Vance 在巴黎发表的人工智能演讲语录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国副总统 JD Vance 周二概述了唐纳德-特朗普总统政府的人工智能政策，将创新、去监管、保护言论自由和美国工人放在首位，他将此比喻为新工业革命的曙光。【原文：U.S. Vice President JD Vance outlined on Tuesday the artificial intelligence policies of President Donald Trump's administration, prioritising innovation, de-regulation, protection of free speech and U.S. workers in what he likened to the dawn of a new industrial revolution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/quotes-us-vice-president-jd-vances-ai-speech-paris-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EN5H45POFJNFXIRF4S3F26QFEI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 10:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称丰田将因制动液泄漏召回逾 10 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周二表示，丰田汽车公司正在召回106061辆美国汽车，原因是制动液泄漏可能会降低制动能力并增加车祸风险。【原文：Toyota Motor Corp is recalling 106,061 U.S. vehicles over a brake fluid leak that can reduce braking ability and increase the risk of a crash, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-recall-over-100000-us-vehicles-over-brake-fluid-leak-nhtsa-says-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QFTMCCTEKZNTDNKI2RFZ5GP3QQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 10:40:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁：评估美国关税对世界经济的影响为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周二表示，美国关税是一个 "不断演变的故事"，现在评估其对世界经济的影响还为时过早。【原文：U.S. tariffs are an "evolving story" and it is too early to assess their impact on the world economy, International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/too-early-assess-us-tariffs-impact-world-economy-imf-managing-director-says-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTHFKCKOTFOMLDYWMSEBGIVNRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 09:51:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者权衡特朗普最新关税威胁，黄金创纪录，股市涨跌不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，黄金飙升至历史新高，股市低迷，投资者为美国贸易政策的进一步转变做好准备，并等待美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔就关税和通胀问题发表讲话。【原文：Gold shot to a record high and stocks were subdued on Tuesday as investors braced for further shifts in U.S. trade policy and waited to hear from Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on tariffs and inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-global-markets-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWPXQ4AX3FPEFCR76JXOYTBKRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 09:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国中芯国际第四季度利润下滑 38.4%，不及预期，尽管收入有所增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最大的合约芯片制造商中芯国际集成电路制造有限公司公布第四季度利润同比下降 38.4%。【原文：Semiconductor Manufacturing International Corp , China's largest contract chipmaker, reported a 38.4% year-on-year fall in fourth-quarter profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-smic-q4-profit-slumps-384-misses-estimates-despite-revenue-growth-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEOD4WH74BM3ZFVZ22VVQNQYPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 09:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国冻结援助有可能将北京后院的影响力拱手让给中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府在一月份冻结了对柬埔寨最大的排雷组织的捐款，该组织致力于清除华盛顿过去在东南亚战争中留下的致命残留物，在此之后，该组织宣布了新的资金来源--来自中国。【原文：After U.S. President Donald Trump's administration froze donations in January to Cambodia's largest demining organization, which works to clear the countryside of deadly remnants of Washington's past wars in Southeast Asia, the group announced new funding - from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-aid-freeze-risks-handing-influence-china-beijings-backyard-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3EO6QUV2GBNO7M233A5XRJZ5GI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 09:12:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，中国泡沫红茶公司密雪将于二月晚些时候在香港首次公开募股，融资约 5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位直接知情人士透露，中国最大的泡沫红茶公司密雪集团将于 2 月底开始在香港首次公开募股的簿记工作，以筹集约 5 亿美元资金。【原文：China's largest bubble tea firm, Mixue Group, will begin bookbuilding for its Hong Kong initial public offering by the end of February to raise about $500 million, according to three sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/chinas-bubble-tea-firm-mixue-raise-about-500-million-hong-kong-ipo-later-feb-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLFSS4PUOVIWLD5VZJ5NEGJVOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 09:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特鲁多表示，加拿大将在必要时对 "不可接受的 "美国关税做出坚决有力的回应]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理贾斯汀-特鲁多（Justin Trudeau）周二表示，加拿大将努力强调美国征收钢铝关税的负面影响，如有必要，加拿大的回应将是坚定而明确的。【原文：Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said on Tuesday that Canada would seek to highlight the negative impact of the United States' steel and aluminium tariffs and that - if needed - the response from Canada would be firm and clear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-will-respond-unacceptable-us-tariffs-strongly-firmly-if-needed-trudeau-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B354OQAQLBLGRPNQXVHKXCELHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 08:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普金属关税推动黄金上涨，施压中国钢铁股]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对钢铁和铝征收 25% 的关税，使黄金在贸易冲突扩大和通胀忧虑的影响下屡创新高，而一些国家则对谈判抱有希望，中国钢铁企业股价承压。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's 25% tariffs on steel and aluminium sent gold to record highs on worries of widening trade conflict and inflation, while some countries held out hope for negotiations and Chinese steel firm shares came under pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-metals-tariffs-propel-gold-pressure-china-steel-shares-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYRDE74UNJMQBEGNHS2VT2PHA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 08:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1 月份中国汽车销量创近一年最大降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 1 月份的汽车销量同比下降了 12%，这是自 9 月份以来的首次下降，也是近一年来的最大降幅，因为汽车制造商们都在为全球最大汽车市场的激烈竞争做准备。【原文：China's car sales fell 12% in January from a year earlier, the first decline since September and the biggest drop in almost a year, as automakers braced for intense competition in the world's largest auto market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-car-sales-january-fall-12-year-earlier-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTGLGSQ4DFNGPMLQIZ4S4CUXTA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 08:13:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DP World 首席执行官：特朗普希望美国开放其他市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪拜港口和物流公司DP World首席执行官苏丹-艾哈迈德-本-苏拉耶姆（Sultan Ahmed bin Sulayem）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）希望，如果美国开放，其他市场也能开放。【原文：Dubai-owned ports and logistics company DP World's CEO Sultan Ahmed bin Sulayem said on Tuesday U.S. President Donald Trump expects other markets to be open if the United States is.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/dp-world-ceo-trump-expects-other-markets-be-open-if-us-is-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CX3PD5LZW5JQBDZHD5BOL4YKKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 07:57:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受中国关税影响，美国对印度的煤炭出口预计将增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位行业官员表示，在中国对从美国进口的能源征收关税后，预计美国将增加对印度的煤炭出口，这可能会侵蚀澳大利亚和俄罗斯在印度市场的份额。【原文：The United States is expected to boost coal exports to India after China imposed tariffs on energy imports from the U.S., five industry officials said, potentially eroding Australia and Russia's market shares in the Indian market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-coal-exports-india-expected-rise-due-china-tariffs-2025-02-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NM7C2CC2JIMJKOU23YXB5GPMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 07:42:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>