<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:05:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:05:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[日本 2 月通胀可能因恢复能源补贴而降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于能源补贴的恢复，日本 2 月份的核心通胀率可能比上月有所下降，但总体价格趋势可能会使决策者继续按计划在今年再次加息。【原文：Japan's core inflation likely decelerated in February from the previous month due to the resumption of energy subsidies, a Reuters poll showed, though the overall price trends will likely keep policymakers on track to raise rates again this year.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-inflation-likely-cooled-feb-energy-subsidy-resumption-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DR6D6SRB5N43FGRCYHKM2LZJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[已更新锂电池政策的航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲的几家航空公司已经更新了关于机上携带锂电池的指南。手机和电子烟等设备中都装有锂电池，一旦发生故障，就会产生烟雾、火灾或极度高温。【原文：Several airlines in Asia have updated their guidance on carrying lithium batteries onboard. The batteries are in devices such as cellphones and e-cigarettes, and can malfunction to produce smoke, fire or extreme heat.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airlines-that-have-updated-their-lithium-battery-policies-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQYAFVO4UFO4NFJTJFSTXY4MJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将讨论特朗普贸易战带来的经济风险，利率将保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行下周将维持利率稳定，并讨论不断升级的美国贸易战对依赖出口的日本经济构成了多大风险，这将是日本央行下一次加息时机的关键。【原文：The Bank of Japan is set to keep interest rates steady next week and discuss just how much of a risk the escalating U.S. trade war poses to the export-reliant economy, which will be key to the timing of its next rate hike.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-debate-economic-risks-trump-trade-war-rates-seen-steady-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGQNOPYRFVMHTKKOV2636NZVLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将讨论特朗普贸易战带来的经济风险，利率将保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行下周将维持利率稳定，并讨论不断升级的美国贸易战对依赖出口的日本经济构成了多大风险，这将是日本央行下一次加息时机的关键。【原文：The Bank of Japan is set to keep interest rates steady next week and discuss just how much of a risk the escalating U.S. trade war poses to the export-reliant economy, which will be key to the timing of its next rate hike.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-debate-economic-risks-trump-trade-war-rates-seen-steady-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGQNOPYRFVMHTKKOV2636NZVLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市持稳；贸易战升级，黄金创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球贸易紧张局势升级令投资者感到紧张，并引发了对避险资产的追捧，黄金创下了历史新高。【原文：Asia shares rose on Friday and global markets attempted a rebound after a brutal selloff, while gold reached a record as an escalation of global trade tensions left investors nervous and sparked a flight to safe-haven assets.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYYJ2JX4EZOVHLAZFTUYNPAC7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:12:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepSeek 之后，中国的基金经理们打败了 High-Flyer 的人工智能之路]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国对冲基金 "高飞"（High-Flyer）在市场交易中使用人工智能，引发了内地资产管理公司之间的人工智能军备竞赛，可能会撼动中国 10 万亿美元的基金管理行业。【原文：Chinese hedge fund High-Flyer's use of artificial intelligence in trading markets has spurred an AI arms race among mainland asset managers that could shake up the country's $10 trillion fund management industry.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/after-deepseek-chinese-fund-managers-beat-high-flyers-path-ai-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66WFKUGW3FI5VHXVVZYHMCQCG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球贸易紧张局势升级，美元坚挺，欧元漂移]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于市场正努力应对不断升级的全球贸易紧张局势和经济急剧下滑的风险，美元普遍走强，欧元则进一步远离五个月高点。【原文：The U.S. dollar was broadly firmer on Friday with the euro pulling further away from a five-month peak as markets grappled with escalating global trade tensions and risks of a sharp economic downturn.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-holds-firm-euro-drifts-global-trade-tensions-escalate-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3FEQUIDSZN35LNUDFWC4TASSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:26:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普让中国股市（在某种程度上）再度伟大]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发动的大范围贸易战引发了对经济衰退的担忧，全球投资者找到了一个不太可能的新避难所：中国股票。【原文：As U.S. President Donald Trump's wide-ranging trade war rouses fears of recession, global investors have found an unlikely new sanctuary: Chinese equities.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/donald-trump-makes-chinese-stocks-somewhat-great-again-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M33X4V4WA5KJDIIMIVAESVJL54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金再创新高，有望达到 3,000 美元峰值]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于美国关税的不确定性和对贸易紧张局势的担忧，以及对美联储放松货币政策的预期增强，黄金价格创下历史新高。【原文：Gold hit a record high on Friday, as uncertainty over U.S. tariffs and fears of trade tensions propelled prices, along with increased expectations of monetary policy easing by the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-mounts-record-summit-eyes-3000-peak-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z35ASMCMENI2PIW6OJQAS5OTCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 01:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，与硅谷相比，DeepSeek 将专注于研究而非收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，中国人工智能聊天机器人深鉴科技（DeepSeek）选择专注于研究而非营收，因为其亿万富翁创始人决定不效仿硅谷竞争对手，利用销售额突然飙升的机会。【原文：Chinese AI chatbot DeepSeek is choosing to focus on research over revenue, as its billionaire founder has decided not to follow Silicon Valley rivals by taking advantage of a sudden jump in sales, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/deepseek-focus-research-over-revenue-contrast-silicon-valley-ft-reports-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOXL2RIURRIERNA7X3ZTEPPX6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 01:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vietnam reviewing duties to boost import of US LNG, high-tech goods, PM says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vietnam is reviewing its duties on U.S. goods, including on liquefied natural gas, agriculture and high-tech products, Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh told the U.S. ambassador to the country, a report on the government's website said.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vietnam-reviewing-duties-us-lng-high-tech-products-pm-says-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXKO5DGO5ZIO3HBNM3Q6I3S2EY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Australian government to give ANZ $1.3 bln loan guarantee for Pacific operations]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Australian government will be giving ANZ Group a loan guarantee worth A$2 billion ($1.26 billion) to keep selling its services in the Pacific region, the lender said on Friday.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/australian-government-give-anz-13-bln-loan-guarantee-pacific-operations-2025-03-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UO4LMK5S6JK5PGWH5EQ5YN6VEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Samsung SDI to issue new shares and invest in U.S. joint venture with GM]]></title><description><![CDATA[Samsung SDI said it would issue new shares worth 2 trillion won ($1.38 billion) in a regulatory filing on Friday and use the proceeds to invest in a U.S. joint venture with General Motors and expand its factory capacity in Hungary among others.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/asia/samsung-sdi-issue-new-shares-invest-us-joint-venture-with-gm-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KJ6DU5RB5OO5MMDEPCAUNOBYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAweek: AI leading to faster, cheaper oil production, executives say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is speeding up oil and gas drilling and prompting companies to take a second look at places they had viewed as too difficult or expensive to develop, executives detailed during the CERAWeek conference in Houston.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-ai-leading-faster-cheaper-oil-production-executives-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PENN5ZILEFPYLGUSOYO6PWFQUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil's Eletrobras posts 25% rise in fourth-quarter net profit]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian power firm Eletrobras reported on Thursday a near 25% increase in its fourth-quarter net profit from a year earlier to 1.11 billion reais ($191.4 million).]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazils-eletrobras-posts-55-fall-fourth-quarter-net-profit-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YWBRQATPZJD5GVDPF3X55QOQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK, US hold private talks to resolve Apple encryption order, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[British officials held private talks with their U.S. counterparts to resolve concerns that UK is trying to force Apple to build a backdoor into Americans' encrypted data, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/uk-us-hold-private-talks-resolve-apple-encryption-order-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3S6ACJ3CJPCVHHX6RLDVGJJPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Foxconn to post higher Q4 profit on AI server demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker, is expected to report on Friday that fourth-quarter profit rose 2.35% on strong demand for artificial intelligence servers.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-post-higher-q4-profit-ai-server-demand-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3JZXXLPQNMOZBHEKKVYD25UOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US frees up almost $4.7 billion loan to TotalEnergies for Mozambique gas project, FT reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has released almost $5 billion in funding for a liquefied natural gas project by France's TotalEnergies in Mozambique, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-frees-up-almost-47-billion-loan-totalenergies-mozambique-gas-project-ft-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NABSASVBTZISRCNHGOTGBXKS4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Stock Exchange hires top ETF executives from Cboe, Nasdaq]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Texas Stock Exchange (TSXE), still months away from winning regulatory approval to begin operations, said it hired senior exchange-traded funds executives from Cboe Global Markets and Nasdaq to win a share of trading in the $11 trillion U.S. ETF market.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/texas-stock-exchange-hires-top-etf-executives-cboe-nasdaq-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWMOJTDJ4JO2RASNFNXC6TZBQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国大型玩具制造商加快将生产基地迁出中国的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与中国的贸易战愈演愈烈之际，沃尔玛和塔吉特的一家主要玩具供应商正在加快撤出中国的步伐，重新调整生产。【原文：A major supplier of toys to Walmart and Target is accelerating its shift out of China as it reshapes production amid President Donald Trump's intensifying trade war with the country.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/major-us-toymaker-speeds-up-plan-move-manufacturing-out-china-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32YHARYX7NPL7ONRYB54EPFT44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：贸易战担忧扼杀复苏希望，熊市开始发力]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKPR4AP6SZJMZL7DVVCXVOWXHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果计划推出可实时翻译对话的 AirPods 功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，苹果公司正在计划推出一项新的 AirPods 功能，允许该设备将与人的对话实时翻译成另一种语言。【原文：Apple is planning a new AirPods feature that would allow the device to live-translate conversations with people into another language, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/apple-plans-airpods-feature-that-can-live-translate-conversations-bloomberg-news-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3LIZF46RVKHXAOFZKTPMQZA7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 化妆品和香水假日需求强劲，季度业绩居首]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 公司周四公布的第四季度销售额和利润均超出预期，这预示着该公司将迎来一个强劲的假日旺季，因为购物者纷纷涌入其门店购买从化妆品到香水等各种产品，这使得该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨了 7%。【原文：Ulta Beauty beat sales and profit expectations for the fourth quarter on Thursday, signaling a robust holiday season as shoppers flocked to its stores for products ranging from cosmetics to perfumes, sending shares up 7% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ulta-beauty-tops-quarterly-results-strong-holiday-demand-cosmetics-perfumes-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDKUQN6YNBLVXGU6BZXQSMEGEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:47:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，软银和 OpenAI 将在大阪前夏普 LCD 工厂联合运营人工智能代理公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周五报道，软银计划将日本一家前夏普液晶面板工厂改造成一个数据中心，用于运行与美国 ChatGPT 开发商 OpenAI 合作开发的人工智能代理。【原文：SoftBank plans to transform a former Sharp LCD panel plant in Japan into a data center for operating artificial intelligence agents developed in collaboration with U.S.-based ChatGPT creator, OpenAI, according to a Nikkei report on Friday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/softbank-openai-jointly-run-ai-agents-ex-sharp-lcd-plant-osaka-nikkei-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TT2AI2P45OEFL7DXFSNY2W62E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:27:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔 500 指数调整的六张图表]]></title><description><![CDATA[一年多来，美国股市首次出现调整。现在的问题是，下滑是否会变得更加严重。【原文：For the first time in over a year, the U.S. stock market is in a correction. The question now is whether the slide is set to get worse.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/sp-500-correction-six-charts-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIBCDBU5VBJQTHTLLFL47MFRBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:14:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Compass is in talks to buy Buffett's real-estate brokerage unit, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Home brokerage Compass is in advanced talks to acquire Warren Buffett's real-estate brokerage business, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/deals/compass-is-talks-buy-buffetts-real-estate-brokerage-unit-wsj-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWH5WNCDN5MOZDAWHUYIDWBZGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉称可能成为报复性关税的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的特斯拉公司在给美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）的一封信中表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易战可能使特斯拉成为美国报复性关税的目标。【原文：Elon Musk's Tesla said in a letter to the US trade representative Jamieson Greer that President Donald Trump's trade war could make it a target for retaliatory tariffs against the U.S.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-warns-trump-administration-it-is-exposed-retaliatory-tariffs-ft-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECFO4V4Y5JKOTGAY7ETEQYDVEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[燃料短缺影响收成，玻利维亚豆农人心惶惶]]></title><description><![CDATA[在玻利维亚的圣克鲁斯农场地区，日益严重的燃料短缺开始影响农民收割庄稼的能力，这也是这个农业已成为主要经济驱动力的南美国家所担忧的问题。【原文：In Bolivia's farm region of Santa Cruz, a worsening fuel shortage is starting to hit farmers' ability to harvest their crops, a concern for the embattled South American country where agriculture has become a key economic driver.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/bolivias-soy-farmers-edge-fuel-shortage-hits-harvest-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5X7RX6YQJMB3GUIZ7HYVUPHUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:52:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关税之争中，通用汽车首席执行官周三会见特朗普 -- 白宫]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员告诉路透社，唐纳德-特朗普总统周三会见了通用汽车公司首席执行官玛丽-巴拉（Mary Barra），在关税战持续不断的情况下讨论了这家汽车制造商的投资计划。【原文：President Donald Trump met with General Motors CEO Mary Barra on Wednesday to talk about the automaker's investment plans amid an ongoing tariff war, a White House official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-ceo-met-with-trump-wednesday-amid-tariff-fight-white-house-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUWE3ZVTHNLVFOVMUOCARL3UBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部确认俄罗斯能源融资许可证到期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四证实，根据乔-拜登（Joe Biden）总统任期最后几天实施的严厉制裁措施，允许与俄罗斯金融机构停止能源交易的许可本周如期到期。【原文：The U.S. Treasury on Thursday confirmed that a license allowing a wind-down of energy transactions with Russian financial institutions expired as scheduled this week under stiff sanctions imposed in the final days of Joe Biden's presidency.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-treasury-confirms-expiration-russian-energy-financing-license-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BG56JYV7SBN5XOABP53N72G3QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>