<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:35:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:35:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国征收新关税，奢侈品和瑞士制表商股价受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对包括来自欧盟和瑞士的商品在内的商品征收新关税后，周四欧洲奢侈品公司股价下跌。【原文：Shares in European luxury companies dropped on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump announced new tariffs, including on goods from the European Union and Switzerland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/luxury-swiss-watchmaker-shares-take-hit-new-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHNTCIH4MRKUDDFEHKWAYRLA74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普激进关税导致贸易战升级，欧洲股市下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲股市周四跌至两个月低点，对贸易敏感的德国受到的打击最大，原因是美国新一轮咄咄逼人的关税措施使全球贸易战升级，并加剧了人们对经济放缓的担忧。【原文：European shares slumped to a two-month low on Thursday, with trade-sensitive Germany hit the hardest, as a fresh round of aggressive U.S. tariffs escalated a global trade war and stoked fears of an economic slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-shares-sink-trumps-aggressive-tariffs-escalate-trade-war-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFZXNN7TUNO3JGSKYWZ3ZVTY4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁克里廷斯基收购英国皇家邮政获得监管部门批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷克亿万富翁丹尼尔-克雷廷斯基（Daniel Kretinsky）的公司 EP Group 周四表示，他对英国皇家邮政所有者国际配送服务公司（International Distribution Services）的收购已通过所有监管条件。【原文：Czech billionaire Daniel Kretinsky's takeover of Royal Mail-owner International Distribution Services has cleared all regulatory conditions, his company EP Group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/billionaire-kretinsky-secures-regulatory-approval-royal-mail-takeover-bid-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYUBIG2ERNI2NDU4XHGKFLUPFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:26:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南被征收关税，耐克、阿迪达斯和彪马等运动服饰品牌股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对耐克、阿迪达斯和彪马等运动服装公司的主要采购市场越南、印尼和中国等地征收一系列新关税后，这些公司的股价周四大幅下跌。【原文：Shares in Nike, Adidas and Puma dropped sharply on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump imposed a raft of new tariffs, including on Vietnam, Indonesia, and China, key sourcing markets for the sportswear companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/sporting-goods-makers-adidas-puma-slump-after-trump-announces-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JILFXMPDRVPNFPBVYDQEHFV3SY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的全球关税以 "全方位封锁 "伤害中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年 7 月，中国户外家具制造商金超峰在越南建立了一家工厂，以逃避美国的高额关税。现在，随着华盛顿对河内和世界其他地区征收高额关税，他正打算关闭这家工厂。【原文：Chinese outdoor furniture maker Jin Chaofeng set up a factory in Vietnam last July to escape higher U.S. tariffs. Now he is looking to close it, as Washington imposes steep levies on Hanoi and the rest of the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-global-tariffs-hurt-china-with-all-round-blockade-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FU6XNZTV3NLMHOK5B5P3GQG35Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对中国征收关税后，苹果股价在法兰克福下跌 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对包括中国在内的贸易伙伴全面征收关税后，苹果公司股价在法兰克福下跌了 7%。【原文：Apple shares fell 7% in Frankfurt after U.S. President Donald Trump announced sweeping tariffs on trading partners including China where the U.S. group has a big manufacturing base.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-shares-drop-7-frankfurt-after-trump-tariffs-china-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYV57S5ER5NZJL6MHSHCISCTK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，腾讯支持的中国如意旨在通过可转换债券融资最多 5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，流媒体公司中国如意控股公司（China Ruyi Holdings）由游戏和互联网公司腾讯（Tencent）支持，计划下周发行可转换债券，融资额在 3 亿至 5 亿美元之间。【原文：Streaming media firm China Ruyi Holdings , backed by gaming and internet company Tencent , is aiming to raise between $300 million and $500 million in convertible bonds next week, two sources with knowledge of the plan said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/tencent-backed-china-ruyi-aims-raise-up-500-million-convertible-bonds-sources-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XRHEZ5WG5OWTEHEOGCCBHHZKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:55:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拼多多将投资 137 亿转型升级商户]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电子商务平台拼多多周四表示，未来三年，拼多多将投资1000亿元人民币（约合137亿美元）用于平台商户的转型升级。【原文：Chinese e-commerce platform Pinduoduo, which is owned by PDD Holdings , will invest 100 billion yuan ($13.7 billion)over the next three years in transforming and upgrading platform merchants, Pinduoduo said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/pinduoduo-invest-137-billion-transform-upgrade-merchants-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANLKGTXHGFIYLI2KPGZGH4XLEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:53:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界各国领导人谴责特朗普征收关税，部分领导人承诺采取报复行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界各国，包括美国的一些最亲密盟友，谴责唐纳德-特朗普总统宣布的对等关税，一些国家承诺采取反制措施，同时希望白宫对谈判持开放态度。【原文：Countries across the world, including some of America's closest allies, condemned President Donald Trump's announcement of reciprocal tariffs and some pledged counter-measures while hoping the White House would be open to negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/world-leaders-condemn-trumps-tariffs-some-pledge-retaliation-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNUM7TGZXZITFM4LX2CD74IINI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:46:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德商业战略主管卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦诺和诺德制药公司（Novo Nordisk）商业战略和企业事务主管卡米拉-西尔维斯特（Camilla Sylvest）周四表示，她已决定离开公司。【原文：Novo Nordisk's head of commercial strategy and corporate affairs, Camilla Sylvest, has decided to leave the company, the Danish drugmaker said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisks-head-commercial-strategy-steps-down-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBFDCQKXVBJPXAYN6NHWFGWNQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:35:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2030 年后，DHL 的邮件和包裹部门息税前利润将实现增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国物流集团 DHL 周四表示，预计其邮政与包裹部门的息税前利润（EBIT）将在 2030 年后完成转型后才会恢复增长。【原文：German logistics group DHL expects earnings before interest and taxes (EBIT) in its Post & Parcel division only to return to growth after the completion of its transformation process after 2030, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dhl-sees-ebit-growth-mail-parcel-division-after-2030-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVGOUXVDRFIXFD6TGM462JKKNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税打击尤为严重的东南亚国家准备与特朗普会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南政府周四表示将成立一个特别工作组，其他东南亚国家也表示计划寻求与华盛顿进行谈判，因为它们受到了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最严厉关税措施的冲击。【原文：Vietnam's government said on Thursday it would set up a task force and other Southeast Asian nations said they plan to seek talks with Washington as they reel from being hit with some of U.S. President Donald Trump's heftiest tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/southeast-asia-nations-hit-particularly-hard-by-us-tariffs-prep-talks-with-trump-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KEMAFH3QVIKBANSIS2Z6OYWQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:10:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：巴拿马会给贝莱德的港口交易带来新的麻烦吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[一旦中美洲国家公布对授予香港长江和记的 25 年特许经营权的审计结果，贝莱德试图获得巴拿马运河附近两个旗舰港口控制权的努力可能会再遇障碍。【原文：BlackRock could hit another roadblock in its attempt to secure control of two flagship ports near the Panama Canal once the Central American country releases an audit on a 25-year concession granted to Hong Kong-based CK Hutchison .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/could-panama-throw-new-wrench-into-blackrocks-ports-deal-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRA6U3PFSNIR5JH4C2VMTPXKWY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布加征关税后，欧洲股票期货下跌超过 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对贸易伙伴征收更多关税后，欧洲股票期货周四大幅下挫，全球贸易战愈演愈烈，有可能刺激通胀并阻碍经济增长。【原文：European stock futures plunged on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled more tariffs on trading partners, intensifying a global trade war that threatens to stoke inflation and stall growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-stock-futures-fall-over-2-after-trumps-tariff-announcement-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUGORWQBKVPARGRRPDAWW5UIOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士商业团体抨击特朗普关税有害且不合理]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士主要的商业游说团体周四反对美国对瑞士进口商品征收关税，认为这既有害又不合理，瑞士政府同时强调了尊重国际法的重要性。【原文：Switzerland's main business lobby on Thursday rejected U.S. tariffs on Swiss imports as harmful and unjustified, as the country's government stressed the importance of respecting international law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/swiss-business-group-slams-trump-tariffs-harmful-unjustified-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLBLGNTFVBOWFL4CFBD4IREEA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 05:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰时装零售商 LPP 第四季度利润不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰最大的时装零售商 LPP 周四公布，其第四季度净利润下降了 7%，降至 4.5 亿兹罗提（1.1755 亿美元），比分析师的预期低了 7000 万兹罗提，原因是尽管在线销售强劲，但运营成本上升拖累了盈利。【原文：Poland's biggest fashion retailer LPP reported a 7% drop in its fourth-quarter net profit to 450 million zlotys ($117.55 million) on Thursday, missing analysts' forecast by 70 million zlotys, as rising operational costs weighed on earnings despite strong online sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/polish-fashion-retailer-lpp-misses-q4-profit-forecasts-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DETKOO3DNOLLM5IILSSGLKZB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 05:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，印度珠宝出口将大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业官员表示，印度 320 亿美元的宝石和珠宝行业正准备应对出口急剧下降的局面，因为美国的高额关税将阻碍印度向其最大市场的海外销售。【原文：India's $32 billion gems and jewellery industry is bracing for a sharp fall in exports as hefty U.S. tariffs will impede overseas sales to its biggest market, industry officials said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/with-us-tariffs-indias-jewellery-exports-set-sharp-decline-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUGUSDI6HROLRIUT2WVWBH4A3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 05:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国总统马克龙将召集受美国关税影响的部门开会 - 法国总统府]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国总统府周四表示，法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙将于当天晚些时候在爱丽舍宫召集受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三宣布的进口关税影响的所有企业界代表。【原文：French President Emmanuel Macron will convene all representatives of business sectors hit by the import tariffs announced Wednesday by U.S. President Donald Trump at the Elysee palace later in the day, the French presidency said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/frances-macron-convene-sectors-hit-by-us-tariffs-french-presidency-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCK75ZV4M5IL5LWWAPHF6AOA4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：看来投资者真的不喜欢关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7K6CCVCSBI6XDFXLYZE66YS2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三菱计划未来 3 年投资 270 亿美元推动增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本贸易公司三菱商事（Mitsubishi Corp）周四表示，该公司计划在未来三年投资至少4万亿日元（270亿美元）以推动增长，并力争在2027/28财年将净利润提高到1.2万亿日元。【原文：Japanese trading house Mitsubishi Corp said on Thursday it planned to invest at least 4 trillion yen ($27 billion) over the next three years to drive growth and aimed to lift its net profit to 1.2 trillion yen in the 2027/28 financial year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/mitsubishi-corp-aims-12-trillion-yen-net-profit-202728-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GOEVJS245KUXLCCSMASBCCYZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟负责人表示，欧盟将针对美国的对等关税准备反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）将美国唐纳德-特朗普的普遍关税描述为对世界经济的重大打击，并表示如果谈判失败，欧盟准备采取反制措施。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen described U.S. Donald Trump's universal tariffs as a major blow to the world economy and said that the European Union was prepared to respond with countermeasures if negotiations failed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/eu-prepare-countermeasures-us-reciprocal-tariffs-says-eu-chief-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QADMRSBRQJP3ZIC2NNSYZFWB44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:35:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织认为日本可持续实现央行的通胀目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）周三表示，日本正呈现出可持续实现央行 2% 通胀目标的迹象，强劲的消费和资本支出可能会支撑日本经济。【原文：Japan is showing signs of sustainably achieving the central bank's 2% inflation target with robust consumption and capital expenditure likely to underpin the economy, the International Monetary Fund said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/imf-sees-japan-sustainably-hitting-central-banks-inflation-target-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EA36IVJRXJMP7PN3Q54G3NEWRI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布全面征收关税，避险黄金创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对主要贸易伙伴征收比预期更为激进的关税，扩大了全球贸易战，紧张的投资者纷纷转向避险资产，黄金在周四创下历史新高。【原文：Gold hit a record high on Thursday, as nervous investors rushed towards safe-haven assets after U.S. President Donald Trump announced more aggressive-than-anticipated tariffs against major trading partners, widening the global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/safe-haven-gold-hits-record-peak-trump-announces-sweeping-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSULCURIFZJXTNCUYP2DN5AEWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:18:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称，因特朗普加征关税，Stellantis 将关闭加拿大温莎工厂两周]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大工会 Unifor 周三表示，汽车制造商 Stellantis 将关闭其位于安大略省温莎的装配厂两周。【原文：Carmaker Stellantis will close its assembly plant in Windsor, Ontario for two weeks, Canadian labour union Unifor said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-close-canadas-windsor-plant-two-weeks-over-trump-tariffs-union-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AG35VCLX5ZNJFMDCMGTPVD65WE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的对等关税将如何影响印度的出口？]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对所有进入美国的商品提高贸易壁垒，印度在周三遭到了美国的对等征税。【原文：India was slapped with a reciprocal tax by the United States on Wednesday, as President Donald Trump raised trade barriers on all goods entering America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/how-will-trumps-reciprocal-tariffs-impact-indian-exports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJBLZ6GZGRKANG2P4BN5764PNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发全球反制承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三宣布对来自所有国家的商品征收 10%的新基准关税，并对其政府称对美国进口设置高壁垒的国家征收对等关税后，世界各国政府承诺对美国采取反制措施。【原文：Governments around the world pledged counter measures on the U.S. after President Donald Trump unveiled on Wednesday a new baseline 10% tariff on goods from all countries plus reciprocal tariffs on those that his administration says have high barriers to U.S. imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-tariffs-draw-global-promises-counter-measures-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOWEL7SVZRIXVHUNO6O4RLE5HI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:47:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称将采取一切措施应对特朗普的关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本贸易大臣武藤洋治周四表示，日本将保留所有选择来应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普新宣布的关税。【原文：Japanese Trade Minister Yoji Muto said on Thursday that Japan is leaving all options open to respond to U.S. President Donald Trump's newly announced tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-says-it-is-leaving-all-options-open-against-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFBIKM47QZLZZBPE4G57EZJV4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商业团体在关税后表示台美是共同繁荣的推动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国宣布加征关税后，台湾美国商会周四表示，台美伙伴关系是共同经济繁荣的推动力，也是该地区供应链安全与稳定的核心。【原文：The Taiwan-U.S. partnership is a driver of shared economic prosperity and central to supply chain security and stability in the region, the American Chamber of Commerce in Taiwan said on Thursday after U.S. tariffs were announced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/taiwan-us-driver-shared-prosperity-us-business-group-says-after-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44BYARRTBVOBHLB2MI2BV24KGY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国敦促美国取消对等关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周四表示，中国已敦促美国立即取消单边关税措施，并通过平等对话妥善解决与贸易伙伴的分歧。【原文：China has urged the United States to immediately cancel unilateral tariff measures and properly resolve differences with trading partners through equal dialogue, the commerce ministry said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/china-urges-us-cancel-reciprocal-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXX5QYNTYJMGZLMJVSB4DKDKDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：大众汽车将对受关税影响的汽车征收 "进口费]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，大众汽车将对受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收 25% 关税影响的车辆征收 "进口费"。【原文：Volkswagen will introduce an "import fee" on vehicles affected by the 25% tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-introduce-import-fee-tariff-hit-cars-wsj-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YV45SEUXAJKLRGMBNFEDZUOLJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>