<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:35:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:35:41 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[WLF 的 Zach Witkoff：1 美元被选为 MGX 在 Binance 投资的官方稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[World Liberty 联合创始人 Zach Witkoff 周四表示，1 美元已被选为阿布扎比支持的投资机构 MGX 投资 Binance 的官方稳定币。【原文：USD1 has been selected as official stablecoin for Abu Dhabi backed investment vehicle MGX's investment in Binance, Zach Witkoff, World Liberty's co-founder said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/wlfs-zach-witkoff-usd1-selected-official-stablecoin-mgx-investment-binance-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEMB5EI7PZKLNMMJPEFFQD2KVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，日本贸易公司对利润预测持保守态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国关税威胁全球供应链并增加经济不确定性，日本贸易公司三井物产株式会社、住友商事株式会社和双日株式会社周四发布了谨慎的本财年利润预测。【原文：Japanese trading houses Mitsui & Co , Sumitomo Corp and Sojitz on Thursday issued cautious profit forecasts for the current fiscal year as U.S. tariffs threaten global supply chains and increase economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japanese-trading-houses-conservative-profit-forecasts-amid-us-tariffs-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTZN5KKT2FNK7GEQLNQJXSBMXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:28:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行加剧经济增长阴霾，股市停滞不前，日元下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经济萎缩后，周四全球股市昏昏沉沉，尽管华尔街指日可待，美元也因日本央行下调经济增长预期而走高，日本央行下调经济增长预期的原因被归咎于美国贸易关税，日元因此走低。【原文：World stocks were groggy on Thursday after a contraction in the U.S. economy, although Wall Street was pointing higher and the dollar sprang up as a Bank of Japan growth forecast cut blamed on U.S. trade tariffs yanked the yen lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHYIX2YZJJO75LIRWXEP3YAKYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞安航空公司威胁称，如果关税影响价格，将寻求波音订单的替代品]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空首席执行官迈克尔-奥利里（Michael O'Leary）周四在一封信中表示，如果美国关税对其向波音公司订购的飞机价格造成实质性影响，瑞安航空将寻找其他飞机供应商。【原文：Ryanair would look for an alternative aircraft supplier if U.S. tariffs materially affect the price of planes it has ordered from Boeing , chief executive Michael O'Leary said in a letter on Thursday, adding that he would consider Chinese planemaker COMAC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ryanair-threatens-seek-alternative-boeing-order-if-tariffs-impact-price-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VE37ZPFXXRN7DEBGL47ZQJE4DI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:55:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，美国关税担忧打击了英国 4 月份的工厂出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项调查显示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的贸易战和英国增税对雇主产生了影响，4月份英国工厂出口出现了近五年来最大幅度的萎缩，成本压力加剧。【原文：British factory exports shrank at their sharpest pace in almost five years and cost pressures intensified in April, according to a survey that showed the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war and a UK tax hike for employers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/us-tariff-fears-hit-uk-factory-exports-april-pmi-shows-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HX6235ZL7BPHHK4BKC2RIIPGHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铝业公司称第二季度订单强劲，尽管有关税，但仍在评估西班牙电力风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[铝生产商美国铝业公司（Alcoa）周四表示，其第二季度的订单量依然强劲，尚未出现与美国关税有关的订单下降，同时还指出，本周西班牙的停电事故给其在西班牙的业务带来了风险。【原文：Aluminium producer Alcoa said on Thursday its order book for the second quarter remains robust and it has yet to see a drop in orders related to U.S. tariffs, while also noting that this week's power outage in Spain posed risks to its business there.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/alcoa-says-q2-order-book-strong-despite-tariffs-assessing-spain-power-risks-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOSTV57IOVN7DHNZYE5G52GQ5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元持续承压，亚洲外汇多头势头强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，由于对唐纳德-特朗普总统领导下的美国贸易政策的担忧继续削弱美元，投资者加大了对大多数亚洲货币的看涨押注。【原文：Investors ramped up their bullish bets on most Asian currencies, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday, as worries about U.S. trade policies under President Donald Trump continued to weaken the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/asian-fx-bulls-gain-momentum-dollar-stays-under-pressure-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SX26JCZYPJK6HINT7WWG2JXNNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:21:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约银行沙特地区总部获批，全球银行业务量增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约梅隆银行（Bank of New York Mellon）周四表示，该行已获得在沙特阿拉伯设立地区总部的许可。【原文：Bank of New York Mellon has received a licence to set up a regional headquarters in Saudi Arabia, it said on Thursday, joining others lured by incentives as the kingdom seeks to boost its appeal as a financial hub.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-gets-licence-saudi-regional-hq-global-banks-grow-presence-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZDMF5SHSJJHTP2EJXF4L5SLSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓称 19.35% 的股东投票支持双重上市审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓（Rio Tinto）周四表示，19.35% 的股东投票支持对公司的双重上市结构进行审查。【原文：Rio Tinto , said on Thursday that 19.35% of its shareholders had voted for a review of the company's dual-listed structure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/rio-tinto-says-1935-shareholders-voted-dual-listing-review-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UVEW3J46ZN57P62Q3IEOGJDCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰的关键矿产有哪些，我们对与美国的交易了解多少？]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰和美国周三签署了一项由美国总统唐纳德-特朗普大力推动的协议，美国将以优惠条件获得乌克兰新的矿产交易，并为乌克兰的重建提供投资资金。【原文：Ukraine and the United States on Wednesday signed a deal heavily promoted by U.S. President Donald Trump that will give the United States preferential access to new Ukrainian minerals deals and fund investment in Ukraine's reconstruction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/what-are-ukraines-critical-minerals-what-do-we-know-about-deal-with-us-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJOXWCB6Q5MNXHMR7FRBTAPFSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:50:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田在新闻发布会上的讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国关税的不确定性给世界第四大经济体的前景蒙上了阴影，日本央行周四维持利率稳定并下调了经济增长预期。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady and cut its growth forecasts on Thursday, as uncertainty surrounding U.S. tariffs clouds the outlook for the world's fourth-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/boj-governor-uedas-comments-news-conference-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BFICA2I6VJG5FIV2AOL4VYMWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管关税存在不确定性，英国劳斯莱斯仍对目标充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国工程公司罗尔斯-罗伊斯（Rolls-Royce）表示，尽管全球关税上涨带来了不确定性，但该公司仍有信心实现 2025 年的利润指导目标。【原文：British engineering company Rolls-Royce said it was confident of meeting 2025 profit guidance despite the uncertainty caused by global tariff rises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/uks-rolls-royce-confident-targets-despite-tariff-uncertainty-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXY7O2SUORLIZKB65V24T7J4AY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中央人民广播电台称，美国关税将使荷兰经济增长减少一个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰经济政策顾问 CPB 周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布的全面贸易关税将使荷兰到 2026 年的经济增长减少一个百分点。【原文：The sweeping trade tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump would reduce economic growth in the Netherlands by a percentage point through 2026, Dutch economic policy adviser CPB said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-tariffs-would-take-percentage-point-off-dutch-economic-growth-cpb-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2GGZPDJMZKMXCLB5W7HZF3KHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国营媒体称美国已与中国就关税问题进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[隶属于中国国家广播公司中央电视台的社交媒体账号 "玉渊潭天 "周四称，特朗普政府已与中国接触，寻求就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普单挑中国政府征收145%关税一事进行谈判。【原文：The Trump administration has approached China seeking talks on U.S. President Donald Trump's singling Beijing out for 145% tariffs, said Yuyuan Tantian, a social media account affiliated with Chinese state broadcaster CCTV said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-has-reached-out-china-talk-tariffs-state-media-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ2WQK6AFRIC5GJQ3M7CKJHKPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:48:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉董事长称董事会不会寻找新首席执行官接替马斯克]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉董事长罗宾-登霍尔姆（Robyn Denholm）周四表示，媒体关于董事会成员与招聘公司联系寻找新首席执行官接替埃隆-马斯克的报道是 "绝对错误的"。【原文：Tesla Chair Robyn Denholm on Thursday said the media report on board members reaching out to recruitment firms to look for a new CEO to replace Elon Musk was "absolutely false".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-chair-says-board-not-looking-new-ceo-replace-musk-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYBDK5B4C5OYHB7V2S7YZYTTMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:39:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 日本央行下调经济增长预期后，日元随日本国债收益率下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周四下调了经济增长和通胀预期，同时在华盛顿咄咄逼人且反复无常的关税政策所带来的不确定性背景下避免加息。【原文：The Bank of Japan cut its growth and inflation forecasts on Thursday while refraining from raising interest rates against a backdrop of uncertainty created by Washington's aggressive and erratic tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-yen-slides-with-jgb-yields-after-boj-cuts-growth-forecasts-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APHKFELTOVMA5PWSLA236CMVWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚首富表示，大选临近，她希望进行特朗普式的改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[矿业巨头吉娜-莱因哈特（Gina Rinehart）呼吁澳大利亚效仿美国，采取唐纳德-特朗普式的领导方式，削减政府开支，同时加强国防开支和能源安全。【原文：Mining magnate Gina Rinehart is calling for Australia to follow the U.S. lead by embarking on Donald Trump-style leadership to cut government largesse while boosting defence spending and energy security, as the country heads to the polls this weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/australias-richest-person-says-she-wants-trump-like-reforms-election-nears-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZGWYF2S5RNHFOAT5ZJIL4QJ24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:12:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，明治、Lactalis、Saputo、Warburg 可能参与恒天然 24 亿美元的出售竞标]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士本周透露，包括日本明治、法国 Lactalis 集团和加拿大 Saputo 公司在内的公司正在考虑竞购乳业巨头恒天然正在寻求剥离的乳制品业务。【原文：Companies including Japan's Meiji, French group Lactalis and Canada's Saputo are considering bidding for the units dairy giant Fonterra is seeking to divest, two sources with knowledge of the matter said this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/meiji-lactalis-saputo-warburg-may-bid-fonterras-24-billion-sale-sources-say-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUVXYMINFBN7BIYG2MCPFZASIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[原住民组织称，力拓在朱伊坎事件五年后仍未履行核心承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓集团（Rio Tinto）周四表示，力拓没有更新与一个原住民团体的协议，该团体在力拓开采铁矿石的土地上破坏了一个重要的原住民遗址，力拓未能履行五年前做出的承诺。【原文：Rio Tinto has not modernised its agreement with an Aboriginal group on whose lands it mines iron ore, failing to fulfil a commitment made five years ago when it destroyed an important Aboriginal heritage site, the group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/rio-tinto-has-not-fulfilled-core-pledge-five-years-juukan-aboriginal-group-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUHSKCYUOVLZDHVDDGPDACPOTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着特朗普兴奋情绪的消退，加密货币行业降临迪拜]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币爱好者们周三来到迪拜，聚集在海湾地区的烈日下，尽管有迹象表明围绕唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的加密货币立场的兴奋情绪正在消退，但他们还是希望该行业的兴旺情绪能够持续下去。【原文：Crypto enthusiasts descended on Dubai on Wednesday, gathering under the Gulf's scorching sun and hoping the industry's buoyant mood can keep going despite signs the euphoria around Donald Trump's crypto stance is ebbing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/crypto-industry-descends-dubai-trump-euphoria-recedes-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPDYK6CPL5MQZB3ZOJXGJ3IZPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长称泰国将寻求与贸易竞争对手征收类似关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国财政部长周四表示，由于关税的影响，泰国经济预计会遇到暂时的 "气穴"，泰国计划通过谈判使其关税与贸易竞争对手的关税更加一致。【原文：Thailand's economy is expected to encounter temporary "air pockets" due to the impact of tariffs, the finance minister said on Thursday, and the country plans to negotiate to align its tariffs more closely with those of its trade competitors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thailand-seek-tariffs-similar-trade-competitors-minister-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EXRUBB2X5MBLGFIVNW6ZHS6Z4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在做出液化天然气投资决定后，标普将伍德塞德公司的信用展望下调至 "负面]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，S&amp;P 全球评级公司将澳大利亚伍德赛德公司（Woodside）的信用展望从 "稳定 "调整为 "负面"，此前该能源公司就其路易斯安那液化天然气项目作出了 175 亿美元的最终投资决定。【原文：S&amp;P Global Ratings revised the credit outlook for Australia's Woodside to "negative" from "stable" on Thursday after the energy company reached a final investment decision of $17.5 billion on its Louisiana liquefied natural gas project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/sp-cuts-woodsides-credit-outlook-negative-after-lng-investment-decision-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAH3A227HRITNASPGCRMOS6PWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称中国 4 月转售房屋价格下降，原因是待售房产增多]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国一家房地产研究机构的报告称，由于更多住宅物业进入市场，加剧了购房者的竞争，4月份中国100个城市的转售住宅平均价格环比下降了0.7%。【原文：The average price of resale homes across 100 Chinese cities fell by 0.7% month-on-month in April, a report by a Chinese real estate research institute said, as more residential properties came onto the market boosting competition for buyers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-april-resale-home-prices-fall-more-properties-put-up-sale-report-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNFM76OG6FLATMJV2WNMHRBOS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:25:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚因黄金狂潮而对美国实现罕见贸易顺差]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策引发了黄金抢购热潮，使美国罕见的贸易顺差转为逆差，澳大利亚因此创下了三个月来对美出口的最好成绩。【原文：Australia has boasted its best three-month run of exports to the United States as President Donald Trump's tariff policies sparked a rush to buy gold, turning a rare U.S. trade surplus into a deficit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-boasts-rare-trade-surplus-with-us-gold-frenzy-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWGT7OYBCZOPDDEG6GBR3OJTYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行维持利率稳定，下调经济增长预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周四维持利率稳定并下调了经济增长预期，因为美国提高关税对全球需求的打击给日本脆弱的经济复苏前景蒙上了阴影。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady and slashed its growth forecasts on Thursday, as the hit to global demand from higher U.S. tariffs cloud the outlook for the country's fragile economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-keeps-rates-steady-cuts-growth-forecasts-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQZTOTF455LAZFC52WTQHZXF2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:14:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，阿达尼暂停与以色列塔塔公司就 100 亿美元印度芯片业务的谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）的集团已暂停与以色列塔牌半导体公司（Tower Semiconductor）就价值 100 亿美元的芯片项目进行讨论，因为这对该集团没有战略和商业意义，两位熟悉此事的人士告诉路透社记者。【原文：Indian billionaire Gautam Adani's group has paused discussions with Israel's Tower Semiconductor for a $10 billion chip project as it did not make strategic and commercial sense for the group, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/adani-pauses-talks-with-israels-tower-10-billion-india-chip-foray-sources-say-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBVE53S4KZJVVGKP2NHKULUKL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：特斯拉董事会开始物色首席执行官接班人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三援引熟悉相关讨论的人士的话报道，特斯拉董事会成员上个月联系了几家猎头公司，为首席执行官埃隆-马斯克寻找继任者。【原文：Tesla board members last month reached out to several executive search firms to look for a successor for CEO Elon Musk, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-board-opened-search-ceo-succeed-elon-musk-wsj-reports-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUKZJHEF4RNFPFBHYYGOEIXIBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:19:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元喘息，日元静待日本央行]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者关注贸易战可能降温的迹象，美元摆脱了疲软的美国数据，周四持稳，而日元则在等待日本央行会议的召开。【原文：The dollar sloughed off weak U.S. data to steady on Thursday as investors focused on signs the trade war may be cooling down, while the yen was waiting on a central bank meeting in Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-takes-breather-yen-waits-boj-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUVMTFAS3ZLIFOC7QCZLKE4PGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:12:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应忧虑导致油价下挫，油价喘了口气]]></title><description><![CDATA[受沙特阿拉伯可能增产的迹象以及美国第一季度经济萎缩的影响，油价周四走高，在前一天大幅下跌后略有回稳。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Thursday, steadying slightly after sharp losses on the previous day driven by signs Saudi Arabia could produce more, and as the U.S. economy contracted in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-take-breather-after-selloff-supply-worries-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZYAFLUURJL2RLOD4OYLTKNAJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片需求强劲，韩国 4 月出口意外增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的贸易数据显示，在芯片销售强劲的带动下，韩国 4 月份的出口出人意料地增长，尽管汽车行业受到了美国关税的拖累。【原文：South Korea's exports surprisingly rose in April, led by strong chip sales, trade data showed on Thursday, although the auto sector was weighed by U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/south-korea-april-exports-surprisingly-rise-robust-chip-demand-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBQHX4DQCFMLPCPBFKNVJ2CII4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:41:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>