<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:48:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:48:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Japan's services activity hits fastest growth in nearly a year, PMI shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's services activity expanded at its quickest pace in nearly a year while the overall private sector posted the fastest growth in 32 months, buoyed by robust demand, a private sector survey showed on Wednesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-services-activity-hits-fastest-growth-nearly-year-pmi-shows-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJC4XPGAV5OPHOKYN5H7RORM54</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:36:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Australia warns $3.2 trillion pension fund industry to lift systems investment]]></title><description><![CDATA[Australia's corporate regulator has warned the nation's A$4.5 trillion ($3.16 trillion) pension fund industry it needs to invest more in systems and technology to better prepare for the future and avoid becoming troubled like stock market operator ASX .]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-warns-32-trillion-pension-fund-industry-lift-systems-investment-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ME2O5OFQNRPL5AS2RDRG4YYRB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Former US agriculture officials, top Republican senator warn of farm country trouble]]></title><description><![CDATA[The chair of the U.S. Senate's agriculture committee warned on Tuesday that farmers were suffering heavy losses, while more than two dozen former industry leaders sounded the alarm about the risk of a "widespread collapse of American agriculture" ahead of a $12 billion government bailout expected to reach growers this month.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/former-us-agriculture-officials-top-republican-senator-warn-farm-country-trouble-2026-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QO6GBUDSURIIRK2YAZQ2CKFRIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump signs extension of Africa duty-free trade program, USTR says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday signed a law extending a preferential trade program for Africa through December 31, effective retroactively from September 30, 2025, the chief U.S. trade negotiator said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/trump-signs-extension-africa-duty-free-trade-program-ustr-says-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2GFJVRHD5NW3DPPGP3K2TF754</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democratic senators seek delay in nomination proceedings of Warsh for Fed chair]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Democratic members of the Senate Banking committee on Tuesday asked Republican committee chair Senator Tim Scott to delay the nomination proceedings for former Federal Reserve governor Kevin Warsh, President Donald Trump's pick to be the next chair of the U.S. central bank.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-senators-seek-delay-nomination-proceedings-warsh-fed-chair-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMAAUGXNSZKFXGTCOGZJJF5SS4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia nears deal to invest $20 billion in OpenAI funding round, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia is nearing a deal to invest $20 billion in OpenAI as part of its latest funding round, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-nears-deal-invest-20-billion-openai-funding-round-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P25YNKYETNK5NDPZ7CMW7KFJAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:31:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Private markets for retail savers will not end well, private equity executive Josh Harris says]]></title><description><![CDATA[A recent rush to sell private markets investments to everyday savers is risky and could have negative consequences for other investors too, prominent private equity executive Josh Harris said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/private-markets-retail-savers-will-not-end-well-private-equity-executive-josh-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHJYWOOBC5JZXH3GQIL2GOZ2HQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:19:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed's Miran resigns from White House job]]></title><description><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran resigned on Tuesday from his position as chair of the White House's Council of Economic Advisers, a White House spokesman said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-miran-resigns-white-house-job-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VARZRKOQDZPMPCF7NOJZRCVKGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yuan expected to rise in 2026, but Beijing has its reasons for saying not so fast]]></title><description><![CDATA[Booming exports are pushing up China's currency and while analysts think authorities will resist further gains, risks are to the upside and could test the country's fragile economy.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/yuan-expected-rise-2026-beijing-has-its-reasons-saying-not-so-fast-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXBB4MIEDZM4XABOADMXMEBHM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon's AWS CEO calls orbital data centers 'pretty far' from reality]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amazon's top cloud computing executive said space-based data centers are "pretty far" from being a reality, even as a number of startups and the company's own founder, Jeff Bezos, have pursued the idea.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/amazons-aws-ceo-says-orbital-data-centers-pretty-far-reality-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DREMWG2UVK2VGP7SE3PTPRSQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prudential's fourth-quarter profit jumps on underwriting strength]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prudential Financial on Tuesday reported a rise in fourth-quarter profit, helped by strong underwriting and gains from its investment portfolio.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/prudentials-fourth-quarter-profit-jumps-underwriting-strength-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5DUYHO5YBNOFCK2XR3S6N44EM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:17:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amcor misses quarterly sales estimates as tariffs weigh on demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Packaging firm Amcor , missed Wall Street estimates for second-quarter sales on Tuesday, as rising tariffs and weak consumer spending weighed on demand.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/amcor-misses-quarterly-sales-estimates-tariffs-weigh-demand-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OF6WHPJDM5NJDON6YDP2ZMJNJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TRADING DAY AI, geopolitics take their toll]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wall Street slumped on Tuesday on concerns that tech companies could face steeper competition and lower margins as a result of AI, while precious metals rebounded sharply on renewed U.S.-Iran tensions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHP3IUOSKFLLLH4AF44NPAYVQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Super Micro Computer raises annual revenue forecast amid strong demand for its servers]]></title><description><![CDATA[Super Micro Computer raised its annual revenue forecast on Tuesday, anticipating robust demand for its AI-optimized servers would continue as companies expand their data center capacity.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/super-micro-computer-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZW3773QB5OM5ICGJZI3QMSK4E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EA beats quarterly bookings estimates powered by new 'Battlefield' game]]></title><description><![CDATA[Electronic Arts beat expectations for third-quarter bookings on Tuesday, buoyed by strong sales of its new "Battlefield" title and signs that the videogame publisher's big bets on its best-selling shooter franchise were paying off.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ea-beats-quarterly-bookings-estimates-powered-by-new-battlefield-game-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZLMXUVJYVMDBNPBNNLTVTDPUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jack Henry second-quarter profit rises on strong bank tech demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jack Henry & Associates reported a higher second-quarter profit on Tuesday, driven by strong demand for its banking technology offerings.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/jack-henry-second-quarter-profit-rises-strong-bank-tech-demand-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFPXQR44INMHPND3O7NNCXXZ4Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skyworks Solutions forecasts upbeat earnings as 5G adoption lifts chip demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Skyworks Solutions forecast second-quarter earnings above estimates on Tuesday, signaling strong demand for its chips used in 5G phones.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/skyworks-solutions-forecasts-upbeat-earnings-5g-adoption-lifts-chip-demand-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JW5OBGEBVRPJHITQO34JK3J7TA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:45:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Corteva misses quarterly sales estimates on lower crop protection, seed demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Agrichemicals company Corteva missed Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter net sales on Tuesday, weighed by lower sales volumes in its crop protection and seeds business.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/corteva-misses-quarterly-sales-estimates-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH7B4DW2UJJKLA7MQZMF32U5OQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emerson Electric lifts profit forecast floor on automation demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Emerson Electric on Tuesday posted higher first-quarter profit and raised the bottom end of its 2026 adjusted per-share profit forecast, helped by strong demand for industrial automation equipment.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/emerson-electric-lifts-profit-forecast-floor-automation-demand-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECP6HYFQYJKW3C45NTZ433RNIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mondelez forecasts muted annual revenue, profit as price hikes pull down volume]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cadbury-parent Mondelez International forecast annual revenue and profit below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, as shoppers traded down from its higher-priced chocolates and snacks to cheaper alternatives.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mondelez-beats-fourth-quarter-revenue-estimates-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZ4TRMZO6NJRFGLQQW5PAVJZRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:22:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD forecasts sequential revenue decline, shares fall]]></title><description><![CDATA[Advanced Micro Devices on Tuesday forecast a slight decline in first-quarter revenue despite an unexpected boost from sales of its AI chips to China, raising doubt about whether it has the supply-chain clout to challenge Nvidia in the booming AI market.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/amd-forecasts-first-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBFUBDDDONJARJXVMUAWBC6BEU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:20:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chipotle forecasts annual sales below estimates as consumers cut spending]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chipotle Mexican Grill forecast annual comparable sales below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday as budget-conscious consumers have increasingly pulled back spending on dining out amid ongoing economic uncertainty.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chipotle-beats-quarterly-sales-estimates-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKLJCSPJY5KX5E6NSJ7FCEVCFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Clorox misses quarterly profit estimates on muted demand for its cleaning products, higher costs]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bleach maker Clorox missed market expectations for second-quarter profit on Tuesday, hurt by shoppers choosing cheaper alternatives to its cleaning products while it battled higher costs.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/clorox-misses-quarterly-profit-estimates-muted-demand-its-cleaning-products-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEHJXYEG4VMVTPORDSO7IRD6RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Match Group forecasts upbeat revenue as turnaround gains traction]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tinder parent Match Group forecast first-quarter revenue above estimates, signaling early gains from its turnaround push.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/match-group-forecasts-upbeat-revenue-turnaround-gains-traction-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4H3QKRR6JL27MO6JJYKE5QM6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take-Two raises annual bookings forecast]]></title><description><![CDATA[Take-Two Interactive raised its annual bookings forecast on Tuesday, betting on strong sales of its premium sports, action and mobile titles as it gears up to launch the highly-awaited "Grand Theft Auto VI" this year.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/take-two-raises-annual-bookings-forecast-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FPZYSIFLVNM5C2Y3WSUBU7TYI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Instruments in advanced talks to buy chip designer Silicon Laboratories, FT reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Texas Instruments is in advanced talks to buy chip designer Silicon Laboratories for about $7 billion, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/texas-instruments-advanced-talks-buy-chip-designer-silicon-laboratories-ft-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CYNQWMHYRO2TPDDRQOYCSEECQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amgen quarterly results beat Street estimates on higher sales, lower tax rate]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amgen on Tuesday reported fourth-quarter financial results that came in ahead of Wall Street expectations, driven by a 7% increase in drug sales and a lower tax rate.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/amgen-quarterly-results-beat-street-estimates-higher-sales-lower-tax-rate-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKNUDR2GDJIRVE5ZWJPACY3UNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lumen forecasts upbeat free cash flow, sees rising adoption of its digital products]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lumen Technologies forecast annual free cash flow exceeding Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, after posting a surprise adjusted profit in the fourth quarter, driven by strong demand for its connectivity solutions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/lumen-forecasts-upbeat-free-cash-flow-sees-rising-adoption-its-digital-products-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQBZL5LGJFIYNLS737W6G57OLA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US files appeal in Google search case, court filing shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. government and a majority of U.S. states on Tuesday said they will appeal the outcome of a landmark antitrust case against Alphabet's Google, according to court papers.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-states-file-appeal-google-search-case-court-filing-shows-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GS6WC37XM5IMBD4VJF6QESMBJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:59:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: KKR prepares OPI owner Wella Company for US IPO, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Investment firm KKR is preparing OPI nail polish owner Wella Company for an initial public offering in the U.S. as soon as this year that could value the global beauty company at meaningfully more than the $4.3 billion KKR paid for it, according to sources familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/kkr-prepares-opi-owner-wella-company-us-ipo-sources-say-2026-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWXVG4PBKZLCPO6NUCYBZ6UKVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:54:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>