<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:08:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:08:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国要求食品外卖巨头公平竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管机构周二表示，中国政府与包括京东、美团和阿里巴巴旗下 Ele.me 在内的国内餐饮外卖服务提供商举行了会议，讨论该行业的竞争问题。【原文：Chinese authorities held meetings with the country's food delivery service providers including JD.com , Meituan and Alibaba's Ele.me to discuss competition in the sector, the country's market regulator said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/china-asks-food-delivery-giants-compete-fairly-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EV2EZ5BBXJPBLCEQAQ4CHS6K5I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国债面临经济衰退和通货膨胀双重风险，避风港担忧加剧：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对债券策略师进行的一项调查显示，对美国国债避风港地位的担忧正在升温，预计未来一年基准 10 年期国债收益率将在贸易战导致的经济衰退和通货膨胀之间摇摆不定。【原文：Concerns for the safe haven status of U.S. Treasuries are rising with benchmark 10-year yields expected to drift sideways over the coming year, pinned between trade war-driven recession and inflation, according to a Reuters poll of bond strategists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/safe-haven-concerns-mount-us-treasuries-face-twin-recession-inflation-risks-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S73OFLZBWJNBBMG2H2MSKPEZ3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:56:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国乐购没有采购美国牛肉的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管上周美英达成贸易协议，允许美国牛肉进入英国市场，但英国最大的超市集团乐购仍未计划采购美国牛肉。【原文：Tesco , Britain's biggest supermarket group, has no plans to source American beef despite last week's U.S.-UK trade deal giving the product access to the UK market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/britains-tesco-has-no-plans-source-american-beef-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NI3LM3OYGJM2TF3GURC3NXLMKM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:23:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车首席财务官告诉《金融时报》，大众汽车将在 2026 年第三季度之前 "重新介入 "中国电动汽车市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车首席财务官周二在接受英国《金融时报》采访时表示，预计到 2026 年第三季度，大众汽车在中国推出的新产品将开始改善其在电池电动汽车领域的表现。【原文：Volkswagen's CFO expects the carmaker's new product launches in China to start improving its performance in the battery-electric vehicle segment by the third quarter of 2026, he said in an interview with the Financial Times on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-re-engage-china-ev-market-by-third-quarter-2026-cfo-tells-ft-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FG7SBHGBT5MENKKK6NC63WG56A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在扭亏为盈的努力下，Under Armour 季度销售额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Under Armour 周二公布的第四季度营收降幅小于预期，这主要得益于这家运动服装生产商努力精简产品线，从而推动了销售额的增长。【原文：Under Armour on Tuesday posted a smaller-than-expected drop in fourth-quarter revenue, helped by the sportswear maker's efforts to streamline its product lines that drove improved sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/under-armour-forecasts-quarterly-sales-below-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SE5KCSA77NKVDDG7F7QW4FJ4IU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood 斥资近 1.8 亿美元收购 WonderFi，向加拿大加密货币用户示好]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 周二表示，它将以 2.5 亿加元（约合 1.7898 亿美元）的价格收购加拿大加密货币公司 WonderFi，这家免佣金的流行经纪公司正寻求扩大其国际业务范围。【原文：Robinhood said on Tuesday it will buy Canadian crypto firm WonderFi for C$250 million ($178.98 million), as the popular commission-free brokerage looks to expand its international footprint.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/robinhood-woos-canadian-crypto-users-with-nearly-180-million-wonderfi-purchase-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOGHLG5XAJOWXI2PZ3QQLTQRHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:06:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联航将在高端旅行需求旺盛的情况下加强豪华服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）将在其即将投入运营的波音 787-9 Dreamliner 机队上增加高级座位和服务，以满足日益增长的豪华旅行需求。【原文：United Airlines will increase the number of premium seats and services on its upcoming fleet of Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner aircraft, as it looks to cash in on rising demand for luxury travel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/united-ramp-up-luxury-services-amid-robust-demand-premium-travel-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHZ6TXBVJ5IMXIRAWBNSWP6SAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 加入标普 500 指数，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase Global 的股价在周二的盘前交易中大涨近 10%，此前该加密货币交易所成为首个被纳入基准 S&amp;P 500 指数的数字资产交易商。【原文：Coinbase Global's shares jumped nearly 10% in premarket trading on Tuesday after the cryptocurrency exchange became the first digital asset player to be included in the benchmark S&amp;P 500 index .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coinbase-shares-jump-addition-sp-500-index-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PONTGTBYB5NH5MZXEIAQS6RSIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:03:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 重置、浪涌和保持]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUKGQDFUSZLTTKTJBQLO6H7JOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员称，美国可在不停止技术出口的情况下遏制人工智能芯片风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员周二表示，美国不需要阻止其人工智能芯片和技术在全球的传播来管理国家安全风险，这表明美国在向沙特阿拉伯等可信赖的盟国出口方面采取了更加开放的立场。【原文：The United States does not need to block the global spread of its AI chips and technology to manage national security risks, a White House official said on Tuesday, signalling a more open stance on exports to trusted allies such as Saudi Arabia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/us-can-curb-ai-chip-risks-without-halting-tech-exports-us-official-says-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JB7TZKDL7ZJXTEICF6FHMLVMXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hinge Health 在纽交所 IPO 的目标估值为 26 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字健康初创公司Hinge Health周二表示，其在美国首次公开募股的目标估值最高可达26亿美元。【原文：Digital health startup Hinge Health said on Tuesday it is targeting a valuation of up to $2.6 billion in its initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hinge-health-targets-26-billion-valuation-nyse-ipo-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4IBAFVFAVLGRNGKIQ4IU3XEJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:46:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康暂停年度预测，首席执行官安德鲁-威蒂卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）周二以医疗成本高于预期为由暂停了其年度预测，并表示首席执行官安德鲁-威蒂（Andrew Witty）已决定因个人原因下台，即刻生效，导致其股价盘前下跌 8%。【原文：UnitedHealth Group on Tuesday suspended its annual forecast citing higher-than-expected medical costs and said CEO Andrew Witty has decided to step down for personal reasons, effective immediately, sending its shares down 8% premarket.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-ceo-andrew-witty-steps-down-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FHDYTEV25M7XBEDUGRHBSACUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shopee 所有者 Sea 季度收入略低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，东南亚科技公司 Sea Ltd 第一季度营收略低于预期，原因是面对不确定的经济形势，消费者减少了在其电子商务平台上的消费。【原文：Southeast Asian technology firm Sea Ltd narrowly missed estimates for first-quarter revenue on Tuesday, as consumers dialed back spending on its e-commerce platform in the face of an uncertain economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/shopee-owner-sea-narrowly-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRASHDECEBPWNA65J7S2I24CLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:34:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽瓦克机场混乱，美国联合航空公司首当其冲]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽瓦克机场是美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）最大的枢纽机场之一，也是美国最繁忙的机场之一，由于该机场不断发生故障，航班延误和取消的情况不断增加，美国联合航空公司正面临着经济损失和潜在的长期声誉损害。【原文：United Airlines is facing a financial hit and potential long-term reputational harm as flight delays and cancellations pile up due to ongoing disruptions at Newark airport - one of its largest hubs and among the busiest in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-bears-brunt-newark-airport-chaos-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D53ECQHA2ZNCZLTPRAQO5YPABM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:31:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消防车价格高达 200 万美元，美国消防员要求进行反垄断调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的消防员工会要求反垄断机构调查生产消防车的公司，称行业整合导致成本飙升，等待时间长达数年，危及消防员和公众。【原文：The largest firefighters' labor union in the U.S. is demanding antitrust authorities investigate the companies that make fire trucks, saying industry consolidation has led to skyrocketing costs and years-long wait times, endangering fire fighters and the public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/fire-truck-prices-hit-2-million-us-firefighters-demand-an-antitrust-probe-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5X32MTOHTJJA7I7C4UIHK5CCEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:12:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4 月份美国小型企业景气度进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[4 月份，美国小企业信心连续第四个月下降，报告职位空缺的企业主比例降至四年多来的最低水平，这可能暗示着劳动力市场的显著放缓。【原文：U.S. small-business confidence fell for a fourth straight month in April, with the share of owners reporting job openings declining to the lowest level in more than four years, potentially hinting at a significant labor market slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-small-business-sentiment-declines-further-april-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTNYDWA2WVK6BE7SNJ7TWB6D6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农民称，尽管贸易休战，巴西在中国大豆市场仍有优势]]></title><description><![CDATA[生产商们说，如果没有额外的让步，北京和华盛顿之间令人惊讶的关税暂停将无助于美国农民在中国获得大豆销售，因为头号供应国巴西仍然具有价格竞争优势。【原文：A surprising tariff pause between Beijing and Washington will not help U.S. farmers gain soy sales in China without additional concessions, producers said, because top-supplier Brazil still has a competitive price advantage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-farmers-say-brazil-still-has-edge-chinas-soybean-market-despite-trade-truce-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DP6OVHJ2JRIVLIZSRE2WAW6L6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行业称美国放宽杠杆率规定可支持国债市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行业乐观地认为，美国监管机构很快就会采取行动，改变他们为典型的安全投资预留的资本额，尤其是在上个月国债市场动荡之后。【原文：The banking industry is optimistic that U.S. regulators will soon move to change how much capital they set aside against typically safe investments, particularly after the turmoil in Treasury markets last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/banking-sector-says-easing-us-leverage-rules-could-support-treasury-market-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2I6WMNZONNLXJTAEXIXNJ7FPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉对最畅销的 Model Y SUV 进行更新换代的道路坎坷不平]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉的投资者曾寄希望于该公司旗舰紧凑型 SUV 的更新换代来重振销量。但是，Model Y 最低的融资价格和它的便捷供应表明，这种期望是不现实的。【原文：Tesla investors had pinned their hopes on a refresh of the company's flagship compact SUV to reinvigorate sales. But rock-bottom financing deals for the Model Y and its easy availability suggest that this expectation is unrealistic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-refresh-best-selling-model-y-suv-starts-rocky-road-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKLBZ7EDQ5ICRETEH4UUOIEZU4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易休战涨势消退，通胀数据成为焦点，美股期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周二下跌，在中美贸易休战推动的大幅反弹后回落，投资者将焦点转向可能影响货币政策前景的美国关键通胀数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were down on Tuesday, pulling back after a sharp rally fueled by a U.S.-China trade truce, as investors turned their focus to a key U.S. inflation reading that could shape the outlook for monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-down-trade-truce-rally-fades-inflation-data-focus-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Q654RI2SBJIDGJ45GEXKHOGWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗杰-费德勒支持的安踏上调年度销售预期，促销和新品发布刺激需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗杰-费德勒（Roger Federer）支持的On Holding公司周二上调了年度销售预期，并表示将不得不采取选择性定价，以减轻美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税影响。【原文：Roger Federer-backed On Holding raised its annual sales forecast on Tuesday and said it would have to undertake selective pricing to mitigate impacts from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/roger-federer-backed-raises-annual-sales-forecast-promotions-new-launches-fuel-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQKW74QMXFNGHAPFITWVN3SYUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税不确定性挥之不去，中国对美出口商步履谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[邓金玲是一家向美国出口保温瓶的中国公司的经理，当她听到华盛顿削减对中国的惩罚性关税至少90天的消息时，她和丈夫打开了一瓶香槟。【原文：When she heard the news that Washington had slashed punitive tariffs on China for at least 90 days, Deng Jinling, manager of a Chinese company that exports thermos flasks to the U.S., popped open a bottle of champagne with her husband.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-exporters-us-tread-warily-tariff-uncertainties-linger-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5F37MBQWZLEFE4CI7K2VOWIKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的 JD.com 季度收入超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，中国电子商务巨头京东商城（JD.com）的季度营收超过了市场预期，这表明，即使美国加征关税和经济长期疲软影响了消费者情绪，该公司仍有稳定的需求。【原文：China's JD.com topped market estimates for quarterly revenue on Tuesday, in a sign the e-commerce giant saw steady demand even as U.S. tariffs and prolonged economic weakness weighed on consumer sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-jdcom-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3QLYXKF55OEJHBZPIUHU54YVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[订阅用户增加，腾讯音乐季度收入大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[受在线音乐服务用户增长的推动，腾讯音乐娱乐周二公布的第一季度营收超出分析师预期。【原文：Tencent Music Entertainment exceeded analysts' expectations for first-quarter revenue on Tuesday, driven by growth in subscribers for its online music services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tencent-music-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BKVTLWZLVOL7ACCQPHIPJMON4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:06:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德的芬克认为数万亿美元闲置，波动性持续存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）表示，在贸易战忧虑和美国经济不确定性的背景下，数万亿美元的金融火力被闲置在现金中，美国的赤字开始令投资者感到恐慌。【原文：BlackRock CEO Larry Fink says tens of trillions of dollars of financial firepower is sitting idle in cash amid trade war worries and uncertainty over the United States economy, whose deficits are beginning to spook investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrocks-fink-sees-trillions-dollars-idle-volatility-persists-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PZF3D2PGFKL5OPC6YDYSBRYTI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外国投资者 5 月重返亚洲股市，扭转了长期资金外流的局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对贸易谈判取得进展的乐观情绪缓解了对美国加征关税加剧全球经济放缓的担忧，5 月份迄今为止亚洲股市正在吸引外资，与今年前四个月的外资流出情况相比出现了急剧逆转。【原文：Asian equities are attracting foreign investments so far in May, marking a sharp reversal from outflows in the first four months of the year, as optimism over progress in trade talks has eased fears of U.S. tariffs fuelling a global economic slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/foreign-investors-return-asian-equities-may-reversing-prolonged-outflows-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XCSS7KDEJKWXIX6YBSTIGIYWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:45:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，2025 年美国的国外旅游支出将下降 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[据世界旅行和旅游理事会（World Travel and Tourism Council）称，由于政治和强势美元促使外国游客选择其他目的地，预计 2025 年美国的国际旅游支出将下降约 7%，即 125 亿美元。【原文：International travel spending in the United States is expected to decline about 7%, or $12.5 billion, in 2025 as politics and a strong dollar prompt foreign visitors to opt for other destinations, according to the World Travel and Tourism Council.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/foreign-travel-spending-us-decline-7-2025-report-says-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZS7TRWAQVOYRA72V72Z5TPUTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产汽车宣布新的成本节约措施，暂不公布 2025 财年业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本汽车制造商日产汽车公司周二宣布了一系列新的成本节约措施，包括再裁员1.1万人，并暂缓发布本年度至2026年3月的财务盈利预期。【原文：Japanese automaker Nissan announced on Tuesday a slate of new cost-saving measures including 11,000 more job cuts and held off on releasing financial earnings estimates for the current year through March 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-announces-new-cost-savings-measures-withholds-fy2025-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIDGQIPYLRKZ5MPXMR2WVGZUQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:18:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税闪电战达成交易，但未能解决全球贸易问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易专家和分析人士说，唐纳德-特朗普的关税闪电战正在达成一些初步协议，包括美国和中国的天价关税暂停90天，以及与英国达成一项有限的贸易协定，但这位美国总统远未重新平衡全球贸易流动。【原文：Donald Trump's tariff blitz is yielding some initial deals, including a 90-day pause in sky-high U.S. and Chinese duties and a limited trade pact with Britain, but the U.S. president is far from rebalancing global commerce flows, trade experts and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-tariff-blitz-yields-deals-misses-global-trade-fix-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJUG2QCTFJORNL35A235HYFRVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 M&S 称客户信息在网络攻击中被窃取]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国零售商玛莎百货公司周二表示，一些客户的个人信息在网络攻击中被窃取，这次攻击使其在线业务瘫痪了三个多星期。【原文：British retailer Marks and Spencer said on Tuesday some personal customer information was taken in the cyber attack that has crippled its online operation for more than three weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uks-ms-says-customer-information-was-taken-cyber-attack-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHZGMK3XGRMIPGFIJ4SCCI5CYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>