<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:05:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:05:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称诺和诺德应在美国寻找下一任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师告诉路透社记者，丹麦诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）正在物色下一任首席执行官来接替拉尔斯-弗鲁尔加德-约根森（Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen），该公司应该在大西洋彼岸寻找一位在其最大市场美国根深蒂固的领导者。【原文：As Denmark's Novo Nordisk shops for its next CEO to replace Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen, it should look across the Atlantic for a leader deeply entrenched in the United States, by far its largest market, analysts told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novo-nordisk-should-look-us-its-next-ceo-analysts-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZK5SF65GNL3VB4JIYIXQMO7QA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:50:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易缓和令需求回升，集装箱船船东忙得不可开交]]></title><description><![CDATA[运营商表示，自上周末中美两国宣布就针锋相对的惩罚性关税休战90天以来，中国至美国的集装箱船预订量激增，导致中国港口和工厂的交通堵塞，可能需要数周时间才能疏通。【原文：Container ship bookings for China-to-U.S. cargo have surged since the countries declared a 90-day truce on punitive tit-for-tat tariffs last weekend, operators said, spawning traffic jams at Chinese ports and factories that could take weeks to clear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/container-ship-owners-swamped-us-china-trade-detente-revives-demand-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F26ENYZWKNIZ7ATY5AERDJCA24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[禽流感爆发后阿根廷停止进口巴西家禽]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷国家卫生机构 Senasa 周五下令暂停从巴西进口禽源产品和副产品，巴西是世界上最大的鸡肉出口国，数小时前证实其一个商业家禽农场首次爆发禽流感。【原文：Argentina's state sanitation agency Senasa on Friday ordered a suspension of imports of products and byproducts of avian origin from Brazil, the world's largest chicken exporter that hours earlier confirmed its first outbreak of bird flu on a commercial poultry farm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/argentina-halts-brazil-poultry-imports-after-bird-flu-outbreak-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVRGREOTNJKBXFTIOX5Z7CV3CI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:56:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，OpenAI 将帮助阿联酋开发全球最大的数据中心之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周五报道，OpenAI 计划帮助阿联酋开发一个新的大型数据中心，该中心最终可能成为世界上最大的数据中心之一。【原文：OpenAI plans to help develop a massive new data center in the United Arab Emirates that may eventually be one of the largest in the world, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/openai-help-uae-develop-one-worlds-biggest-data-centers-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6GXXPQ4WFILPBRNMS7CI6TIBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:47:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达能旗下品牌 Oikos 酸奶进入蛋白奶昔市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[达能本周在其 Oikos 酸奶品牌下推出了一种新的蛋白质奶昔，因为竞争对手可口可乐的 Fairlife 和 Chobani 的类似产品受到了消费者和服用减肥药（如维格维）者的欢迎。【原文：Danone introduced a new protein shake under its Oikos yogurt brand this week as rivals Coca-Cola's Fairlife and Chobani with similar products gain popularity with consumers and those taking weight-loss drugs such as Wegovy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/danones-oikos-yogurt-brand-enters-protein-shake-market-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSSNXLJMNNOXVCZA5L6T7CBZOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从胰岛素到 Ozempic，诺和诺德首席执行官的发展史]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ozempic生产商诺和诺德公司周五解除了首席执行官拉尔斯-弗鲁尔加德-约根森（Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen）的职务，原因是该公司担心在竞争激烈的肥胖症药物市场上，美国竞争对手礼来公司（Eli Lilly）正在失去先发优势。【原文：Ozempic-maker Novo Nordisk on Friday ousted its CEO Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen over concerns the company is losing its first-mover advantage in the competitive obesity drug market to American rival Eli Lilly .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/insulin-ozempic-history-novo-nordisks-ceos-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TW2VW3JV2JIGLETAEP5HW3TGYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，瑞银正与客户就特朗普波动造成的外汇衍生品损失进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士透露，瑞银集团正在商谈赔偿一些客户的损失，因为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税引发了货币的剧烈波动，这些客户被卖出了复杂的外汇衍生品，导致他们的大部分投资化为乌有。【原文：UBS is in talks to compensate some clients for losses after they were sold complex foreign-exchange derivatives that wiped out much of their investments when U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs sparked wild moves in currencies, sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-talks-with-clients-over-fx-derivative-losses-trump-volatility-sources-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZGT43VMTBJVZPANWQPO3GPI6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:43:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迈克-诺沃格拉茨的银河数字公司在纳斯达克上市，加密货币迎来丰收周]]></title><description><![CDATA[由迈克-诺沃格拉茨（Mike Novogratz）创立的银河数字公司（Galaxy Digital）周五在纳斯达克首次亮相，为加密货币在公开市场上的重要一周画上了句号，Coinbase 也加入了 S&amp;P 500 指数，零售经纪商 eToro 也上市了。【原文：Galaxy Digital, founded by Mike Novogratz, made its Nasdaq debut on Friday, capping off a momentous week for cryptocurrency in public markets, with Coinbase joining the S&amp;P 500 and retail brokerage eToro also going public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mike-novogratzs-galaxy-digital-debuts-nasdaq-bumper-week-crypto-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXV3YMVHJVL57ILQLFQ734FPBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大空头 "投资者迈克尔-伯里将化妆品制造商雅诗兰黛的股份增加一倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克尔-伯里（Michael Burry）的 Scion 资产管理公司已将其在雅诗兰黛的持股翻了一番，而这家美容巨头的新任首席执行官正在指导公司进行转型，以克服北美和中国等主要市场需求疲软的问题。【原文：Michael Burry's Scion Asset Management has doubled its stake in Estee Lauder , at a time when the beauty giant's new CEO is steering the company through a transformation to overcome weak demand in key markets such as North America and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/big-short-investor-michael-burry-doubles-stake-cosmetics-maker-estee-lauder-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2QRWQQN5NIHBOP5IFYEBOFX5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:11:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税休战后美国货运业有望提振返校需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[专家们说，华盛顿和北京之间为期 90 天的贸易解冻可能会成为美国货运业的一个受欢迎的缓和措施，因为进口商们急于在繁忙的返校期到来之前锁定货物。【原文：A 90-day trade thaw between Washington and Beijing could prove to be a welcome reprieve for the U.S. freight industry, as importers rush to lock in shipments ahead of the busy back-to-school period, experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-freight-industry-hopes-back-to-school-demand-boost-after-tariff-truce-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITHBGLEJ4FPAFBBKGDENODQLUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:30:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国达飞轮船公司（CMA CGM）将重新部署船队以避免美国对中国船只征收港口费]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国达飞海运集团（CMA CGM）财务总监表示，该公司将重组其全球船队，以避免美国对中国建造的船只征收港口费。【原文：French shipping group CMA CGM will reorganise its global fleet to avoid U.S. port fees on Chinese-built vessels that are due to take effect from October, the company's finance director said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/frances-cma-cgm-redeploy-fleet-avoid-us-port-fees-chinese-vessels-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFKKV4WO4ZKW3BTM4REVWGUEDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:15:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，波音公司即将达成避免在致命坠机案中认罪和被起诉的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，波音公司已就两起造成 346 人死亡的 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故引发的欺诈案与美国检方达成了初步的不起诉协议。【原文：Boeing has reached a tentative nonprosecution agreement with U.S. prosecutors in a fraud case stemming from two fatal 737 MAX plane crashes that killed 346 people, people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-near-deal-avoid-guilty-plea-prosecution-fatal-crashes-case-sources-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OG4HH46ZXBNBFEYBZA2WHBFCF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月消费者情绪进一步恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于家庭仍然担心唐纳德-特朗普总统咄咄逼人且经常反复无常的贸易政策对经济的影响，美国消费者情绪在5月份进一步下滑，而一年期通胀预期飙升。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment slumped further in May while one-year inflation expectations surged as households remained concerned about the economic impact of President Donald Trump's aggressive and often erratic trade policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-deteriorates-further-may-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZW6YCPFZ2BN5FN2PGIETCUEYJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inditex 任命新首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Inditex 周五宣布了新的首席财务官和首席可持续发展官，对高层管理人员进行了调整，但没有详细说明变动的原因。【原文：Inditex on Friday announced a new chief financial officer and chief sustainability officer in a top management reshuffle, without detailing any reason for the changes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/inditex-appoints-new-chief-financial-officer-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFQAC72HMFNORNVDJ7BTCQQPZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Adevinta 正在探索出售其西班牙业务，因为公司所有者正在寻求解体]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，在线分类信息集团 Adevinta 正在探索出售其西班牙业务，因为其私募股权所有者寻求将公司拆分，以专注于三大市场并提高回报。【原文：Online classifieds group Adevinta is exploring the sale of its Spanish business, two sources with knowledge of the talks said, as its private equity owners seek to break-up the company to focus on three main markets and boost returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/adevinta-explores-sale-its-spanish-business-owners-pursue-break-up-sources-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHUFUHWE5NIPNI4TBA62HUM5IM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西首例商业公司禽流感病例引发中国禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西周五证实，该国南部一个商业养鸡场出现首例高传染性禽流感病毒病例，引发了其主要贸易伙伴中国的临时贸易禁令。【原文：Brazil on Friday confirmed its first case of the highly contagious bird flu virus on a commercial chicken farm in the south of the nation, triggering a temporary trade ban from its main trade partner China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/brazils-first-bird-flu-case-commercial-firm-triggers-chinese-ban-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHRMQW7GGRI5LFBRHQ6FGOMJ4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[头条新闻之外：解读特朗普的海湾 "万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五结束了他的海湾之行，白宫称他为美国经济争取到了超过 2 万亿美元的综合交易。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump was wrapping up his Gulf tour on Friday having secured what the White House says is over $2 trillion for the U.S. economy in combined deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/beyond-headlines-explaining-trumps-gulf-trillions-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPE2XSFBWRMGRDXBIN6QWHJ42U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[董事会主席表示，更换诺和诺德首席执行官的谈判持续了数周时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德公司董事会主席海尔格-伦德（Helge Lund）周五告诉路透社，诺和诺德公司与控制公司的诺和诺德基金会关于更换首席执行官的讨论在过去几周一直在进行。【原文：Discussions between Novo Nordisk and the Novo Nordisk Foundation that controls the company regarding a CEO change have been ongoing for the past few weeks, the company's board Chair Helge Lund told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/talks-replace-novo-nordisk-ceo-lasted-several-weeks-board-chair-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBEEOUOUEVOVDBHADHWUB6JTIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:17:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Verizon 在寻求美国批准 Frontier 交易的同时终止 DEI 计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普政府展开调查之后，以及在美国电信运营商寻求批准收购 Frontier Communications 公司之际，Verizon Communications 周五表示将终止多元化、公平和包容计划。【原文：Verizon Communications said Friday it is ending diversity, equity and inclusion programs after the Trump administration opened a probe and as the U.S. telecom carrier seeks approval to purchase Frontier Communications .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/verizon-ending-dei-programs-it-seeks-us-approval-frontier-deal-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCAH2ZS6TNJENBKMYQPXBSAAGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月份进口价格意外上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于资本货物成本的飙升抵消了能源产品价格的下降，美国 4 月份的进口价格意外上涨。【原文：U.S. import prices unexpectedly rose in April as a surge in the cost of capital goods offset cheaper energy products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-import-prices-unexpectedly-rise-in-april-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHNTQYPITZOG3K3YKXPDM25ICM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:11:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将吸纳 Chipotle 公司高管杰克-哈同加入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉电动汽车制造商杰克-哈顿（Jack Hartung）周五表示，特斯拉将于今年 6 月将奇波特尔公司（Chipotle）高管杰克-哈顿（Jack Hartung）纳入董事会和审计委员会。【原文：Tesla will add Chipotle executive Jack Hartung to its board of directors and audit committee in June, the electric vehicle maker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tesla-add-chipotle-executive-jack-hartung-board-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLQSJ7IALNNC7LYOYWZHP2CQFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车股东要求汽车制造商改革 "问题严重 "的治理结构]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，大众汽车的股东们再次对这家汽车制造商的公司治理提出批评，要求提高董事会的独立性，并对这家德国公司的控股家族的主导地位表示日益担忧。【原文：Volkswagen's shareholders renewed their criticism of the automaker's corporate governance on Friday, demanding greater board independence and expressing growing concern over the dominance of the German company's controlling families.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-shareholders-demand-carmaker-reform-highly-problematic-governance-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7VMSZOV2VPLHLD6MYCBBM4UTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰执政党报告其网站在选举前遭到攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰执政党公民纲领党（Civic Platform）的一位高级官员说，该党的网站周五遭到了网络攻击。【原文：The website of Poland's ruling Civic Platform party was hit by a cyberattack on Friday, a senior party official said, hours before the start of a campaign blackout before the first round of Sunday's presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/polish-ruling-party-reports-attack-its-website-before-election-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWUGTAOZRNMAXGZBEKABP7UMGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:58:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月份独户住宅开工量和建筑许可量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于进口材料关税和抵押贷款利率居高不下仍是住房市场的主要障碍，4 月份美国单户住宅建设出现下滑。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding fell in April as tariffs on imported materials and high mortgage rates remained major obstacles for the housing market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-single-family-housing-starts-building-permits-fell-april-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKHEEPXW3ZJPDASIG2QQUEZGI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国加密货币社区在接连发生绑架案后感到恐惧和愤怒]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一系列暴力绑架事件发生后，法国加密货币公司的老板们感到恐惧和愤怒。一些人加强了安保措施，并考虑配备保镖，而另一些人则呼吁加大打击犯罪的力度，同时放松监管，使加密货币的文件记录更加匿名。【原文：French crypto bosses have reacted with fear and anger after a series of violent kidnappings. While some have stepped up security and are considering bodyguards, others are calling for a tougher crackdown on crime plus deregulation to keep the crypto paper trail more anonymous.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/fear-anger-frances-crypto-community-after-spate-kidnappings-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBB5EK5XJBKLVDHW2UMWP5AYUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:40:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美空运因 "微量 "关税而下滑；航空公司调整航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业数据显示，本月中国对出境低值物品的免税政策被取消后，中国与美国之间的航空货运能力下降了近三分之一，削弱了亚洲主要航空公司的重要收入来源。【原文：Air freight capacity between China and the U.S. dropped by almost a third after a tax-free exemption for low-value items out of China was removed this month, industry data showed, denting a significant revenue stream for Asia's major airlines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-air-freight-tumbles-de-minimis-tariff-airlines-adjust-routes-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRTX5RBDZZJT5NNOMQCKZY5SYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点：肥胖症药物市场竞争白热化，威戈威生产商诺和诺德辞退首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wegovy生产商诺和诺德公司周五表示，公司首席执行官拉尔斯-弗鲁尔加德-约根森（Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen）将因担心公司在竞争激烈的肥胖症药物市场上失去先发优势而下台。【原文：Wegovy-maker Novo Nordisk said on Friday its CEO Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen will step down over concerns the company is losing its first-mover advantage in the highly competitive obesity drug market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/view-wegovy-maker-novo-nordisk-ousts-ceo-competition-obesity-drug-market-heats-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FIGD3JBWBJ6VCU3TCIVOS2K2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利和阿联酋宣布达成人工智能中心协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利工业部长阿道夫-乌尔索（Adolfo Urso）周五表示，意大利和阿拉伯联合酋长国已同意在意大利发展人工智能中心。【原文：Italy and the United Arab Emirates have agreed to develop an artificial intelligence hub in Italy, Industry Minister Adolfo Urso said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/italy-uae-announce-deal-artificial-intelligence-hub-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTUFMC4FTBPWHH3H6OBAJS6UEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，英伟达在美国芯片禁令后寻求上海研发基地]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位接近此事的消息人士称，Nvidia 正在上海寻找研发中心的选址，这反映了中国市场的战略意义，美国对先进芯片出口的限制打击了中国市场的销售。【原文：Nvidia is seeking a site in Shanghai for a research and development centre, three sources close to the matter said, reflecting the strategic significance of the Chinese market where U.S. curbs on advanced chip exports have hit sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-seeks-shanghai-rd-site-after-us-chip-curbs-say-sources-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BF6BGXZCMJO6BPT5GC3NCZAHYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:52:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 公司获得 19 亿美元退出融资，期限 5 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司在周五提交的一份文件中说，在破产保护的背景下，该公司获得了具有约束力的退出融资承诺，为期 5 年，总额达 19 亿美元。【原文：Brazil's airline Gol secured binding commitments for exit financing with a 5-year term totaling $1.90 billion, in context of chapter 11, it said in a filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/brazils-gol-secures-19-billion-exit-financing-with-5-year-term-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JLNAKET2BLA5A4LWHSVKRQ7RI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>