<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:36:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:36:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[运营商表示，纽约电网已准备好满足寒流需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约独立系统运营商（NYISO）周五表示，该州电网已做好准备，以满足周一至周三寒流来袭期间的预期电力需求。【原文：The New York Independent System Operator (NYISO) said on Friday that the state's electric grid is prepared to meet anticipated power demand during a forecasted cold snap from Monday to Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-yorks-electric-grid-ready-meet-cold-snap-demand-operator-says-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72N4XMKWRJI3JMF6KUEKY5CY5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉百事可乐向沃尔玛提供独家折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五起诉百事可乐向一家大型零售商提供优惠价格，一位熟悉此事的消息人士证实，这家零售商就是沃尔玛。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission sued Pepsi on Friday for offering preferential pricing to a larger retailer, whom a source familiar with the matter confirmed was Walmart.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sues-pepsi-over-exclusive-discounts-walmart-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXFXM3ZHIRNULFAVYOSXRU67VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉新任评级主管寻找特朗普治下美国政策的答案]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉新任主权评级主管表示，在夏季进行下一次评级审查时，该公司可能会对唐纳德-特朗普的第二个总统任期可能对美国信用评级产生的影响有一个更清晰的认识。【原文：Fitch new head of sovereign ratings says the firm is likely to have a clearer picture of how Donald Trump’s second term as president could impact the U.S. credit rating by the time of its next rating review in the summer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fitchs-new-rating-chief-looking-answers-us-policy-under-trump-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBDXI75OBJJFPILEIPMYZ53R4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:09:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空航天集团对支持国家安全和工业的特定关税持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普建议对包括墨西哥和加拿大在内的国家征收关税后，美国最大的航空航天贸易集团周五为讨论具体关税问题敞开了大门。【原文：The largest U.S. aerospace trade group opened the door on Friday to discussions on specific tariffs, after President-elect Donald Trump suggested slapping duties on countries including Mexico and Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-aero-group-open-select-tariffs-supporting-natl-security-industry-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXQII2DAYBIFZOX766IUHIYQ5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 TikTok 由他决定，但未提供细节]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，TikTok 应用程序的未来将由他来决定，但他没有详细说明他将采取哪些措施。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump said on Friday the decision on the future of the TikTok app will be up to him, but he did not provide any detail about what steps he would take.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-tiktok-decision-is-up-him-offers-no-details-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75R4PG6GTRI7FBO264Y5ZAAKPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:59:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商集团提起诉讼，要求阻止美国的自动紧急制动规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表主要汽车制造商的一个团体周五表示，它已提起诉讼，要求阻止乔-拜登总统政府制定的一项具有里程碑意义的规定，即到2029年，几乎所有的新车和卡车都必须配备先进的自动紧急制动系统。【原文：A group representing major automakers on Friday said it filed lawsuit to block a landmark rule from the administration of President Joe Biden requiring nearly all new cars and trucks by 2029 to have advanced automatic emergency braking systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/automaker-group-files-lawsuit-block-us-automatic-emergency-braking-rule-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBNVVRPO2BMBTOPS6PRFZ6EVXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:52:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SLB 称其俄罗斯业务与美国新制裁保持一致，但收入下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[油田服务供应商 SLB 周五表示，其目前在俄罗斯的业务仍与美国对俄罗斯的新制裁保持一致，但在该国的收入正在下降。【原文：Oilfield service provider SLB on Friday said its current business in Russia still aligns with new U.S. sanctions on Russia, but that revenue in the country was declining.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/slb-says-its-russia-business-aligns-with-new-us-sanctions-revenue-drops-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWLEEFYT5ZKHZIFK26E6B45JSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:52:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[战略家称，特朗普的关税计划可能是赢得筹码的赌局]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）下周重返白宫，全球投资者都在为一场全球贸易战做准备，一些经济学家和战略家认为，他提出的大幅提高关税的建议很可能成为一种谈判工具。【原文：As investors the world over brace for a global trade war with U.S. President-elect Donald Trump returning to the White House next week, several economists and strategists believe his proposed hefty tariff hikes could well be a negotiation tool.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-tariff-plan-could-be-gambit-win-leverage-strategists-say-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TTFKZUORVIUVBMF3Z3WGH2EQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫美国人应继续使用 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周五表示，Tiktok 应继续向美国人开放，但最高法院就禁止该应用程序的法律作出裁决的时机意味着它必须由特朗普政府来处理。【原文：The White House said on Friday that Tiktok should remain available to Americans but the timing of the Supreme Court ruling on a law banning the app means it must fall to the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-tiktok-should-remain-available-americans-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDKSAJNU3VLD5J7UR7ZT4AVS2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Generali Investments 收购美国投资公司 MGG 大部分股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利顶级保险公司 Generali 旗下的全球投资部门 Generali Investments 周五表示，已签署协议以 3.2 亿美元收购美国投资公司 MGG Investment Group 77% 的股份。【原文：Generali Investments, the global investment arm of Italy's top insurer Generali , said on Friday it had signed an agreement to buy a 77% stake in the U.S. investment firm MGG Investment Group for $320 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/generali-investments-buys-majority-stake-us-investment-firm-mgg-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVQ5N5FNJJNGTIWR3WYY5HACBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部发布与 "盐台风 "黑客攻击有关的制裁措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份声明称，美国财政部周五发布了与 "盐台风 "黑客攻击新加坡殷可成和网络安全公司四川聚信合网络科技有限公司有关的网络制裁。【原文：The U.S. Treasury department on Friday issued cyber-related sanctions related to the Salt Typhoon hack on Singaporean Yin Kechen and cybersecurity company Sichuan Juxinhe Network Technology Co., according to a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-treasury-dept-issues-sanctions-related-salt-typhoon-hack-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZNSREPSZVKE7JGUXHXINFMMQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月制造业产出加速增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[12 月份美国制造业产量激增，可能是因为波音公司的生产在这家航空航天巨头的工厂工人结束瘫痪性罢工后有所回升。【原文：U.S. manufacturing output surged in December likely as production at Boeing picked up following the end of a crippling strike by factory workers at the aerospace giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-output-accelerates-december-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIXB7XRAGRNL7KNI2UI27L2QBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:16:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院支持禁止 TikTok 的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五拒绝从一项法律中解救 TikTok，该法律要求这款流行的短视频应用程序必须由其中国母公司字节跳动出售，否则将以国家安全为由于周日在美国禁用，这对一个有近一半美国人使用的平台来说是一个重大打击。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court refused to rescue TikTok on Friday from a law that required the popular short-video app to be sold by its Chinese parent company ByteDance or banned on Sunday in the United States on national security grounds - a major blow to a platform used by nearly half of all Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-upholds-law-banning-tiktok-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USBCUDGDOBJNZN233S6LW3II5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:12:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股市因收益率下降和中国经济增长而跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于债券收益率下降、中国经济增长数据强于预期以及乐观的盈利支撑了风险资产，周五全球股市上涨，扩大了周涨幅。【原文：Global equities rose on Friday, adding to weekly gains, as declining bond yields, stronger than expected Chinese growth figures and upbeat earnings supported riskier assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6XWIFFNVFLJVKFT7FANZHIMHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:57:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者保护局就 Equifax 处理消费者纠纷问题罚款 1500 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局周五宣布对信用报告局 Equifax 罚款 1500 万美元，原因是该局未能充分调查消费者对其信用报告的争议。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau announced on Friday it had fined credit reporting bureau Equifax $15 million for failing to sufficiently investigate consumer disputes of its credit reports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumer-bureau-fines-equifax-15-million-issues-fixing-consumer-disputes-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HFVLFCT4FOU7JFJL6WTHZIFGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行和美林证券将支付 6000 万美元和解美国证券交易委员会的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）周五表示，富国银行的两家咨询公司和美林证券已同意支付合计 6000 万美元的民事罚款，以了结对合规失误的指控。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday said a pair of Wells Fargo Advisory firms and Merrill Lynch have agreed to pay a combined $60 million in civil penalties to settle charges over compliance failures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-firms-merrill-lynch-pay-60-mln-settle-sec-charges-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOKXCUDOGNNQPDA5OSGVXQFMTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[健身饮料公司 Celsius 将支付 300 万美元罚款，以了结美国证券交易委员会的会计案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周五表示，健身饮料公司 Celsius Holdings 将支付 300 万美元的民事罚款，以解决对其不当核算股票奖励的指控。【原文：Celsius Holdings , the fitness beverage company, will pay a $3 million civil fine to resolve charges it accounted improperly for stock-based awards, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/fitness-beverage-company-celsius-pay-3-million-fine-settle-us-sec-accounting-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQ4GQUUEJFMIBIOZSZCJSYEIYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:26:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国中型银行凭借强劲的手续费收入乘势而上]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国多家银行公布第四季度利润增长，延续了该行业的连胜势头，原因是资本市场的上扬缓解了贷款需求疲软带来的冲击。【原文：A raft of U.S. banks reported higher fourth-quarter profits on Friday, extending a winning streak for the industry as an upswing in capital markets alleviated a hit from weaker loan demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-mid-sized-banks-ride-industry-upswing-robust-fee-income-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3OLHJFGDVIDFD3PCMZMX2MZBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛将首席执行官薪酬提高至 3,900 万美元，准备再执掌高盛五年]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份文件显示，高盛去年将首席执行官大卫-所罗门的薪酬提高了 26%，达到 3900 万美元，董事会还为他准备了 8000 万美元的股票留用奖金，这预示着他将继续执掌高盛 5 年。【原文：Goldman Sachs raised CEO David Solomon's compensation 26% to $39 million for last year, according to a filing, and its board lined up an $80 million stock retention bonus that signals he will stay at the helm for another 5 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-boosts-ceo-pay-39-million-lines-up-five-more-years-helm-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQGSNB4PENIZJNBUPCU5B4XH5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）上调美国经济展望，警告各国反对保护主义和补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五将其对2025年全球经济增长的预测上调了十分之一个百分点，其中美国的增长强于预期，抵消了德国、法国和其他主要经济体下调的预测。【原文：The International Monetary Fund on Friday raised its forecast for global growth in 2025 by one-tenth of a percentage point, with stronger-than-expected growth in the U.S. offsetting downward revisions in Germany, France and other major economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/imf-lifts-us-outlook-warns-countries-against-protectionism-subsidies-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUKBTA7YLZMBLAKH4LEG4YO2J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国的 TikTok 禁令可能与印度的混乱相呼应，因为用户正在寻求各种选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 即将关闭，美国的 TikTok 粉丝们正争先恐后地寻找替代品，保护自己的数字王国，这让人想起印度 2020 年的禁令，一夜之间，该应用从 2 亿用户的生活中消失。【原文：TikTok fans in the U.S. are racing to secure alternatives and safeguard their digital empires ahead of a looming shutdown, evoking the chaos of India's 2020 ban that erased the app from the lives of 200 million users overnight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-tiktok-ban-could-echo-india-chaos-users-seek-options-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4Q2Q2WKVVJT7JJW3ZEASDDIRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月独户住宅新开工面积增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[12 月份，美国单户住宅建设稳健增长，但由于抵押贷款利率上升和市场上新房供应过剩，进一步增长受到限制。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding increased solidly in December, but further gains were seen limited by rising mortgage rates and a glut of new homes on the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-single-family-housing-starts-increase-december-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72WUSUMKZVJ3PCIUDDQP3LIN7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亨廷顿银行因资本市场强劲和利息收入增长而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[亨廷顿银行（Huntington Bancshares）周五公布的第四季度利润增长了两倍多，主要得益于资本市场部门的强劲表现和更高的利息收入。【原文：Huntington Bancshares on Friday reported a more than two-fold rise in its fourth-quarter profit, helped by robust performance in its capital markets unit and a higher interest income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/huntington-bancshares-profit-surges-strong-capital-markets-interest-income-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDRGRP44YFPQDJFKM2WCCJ5M4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bumble 首席执行官莉迪亚妮-琼斯辞职，创始人将担任首席执行官一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[约会应用运营商 Bumble 周五表示，在利迪亚娜-琼斯（Lidiane Jones）辞去首席执行官一职后，其创始人兼执行主席惠特尼-沃尔夫-赫德（Whitney Wolfe Herd）将从 3 月中旬起担任公司首席执行官。【原文：Dating app operator Bumble said on Friday its founder and executive chair, Whitney Wolfe Herd, will become the chief executive of the company from mid-March after Lidiane Jones resigned as CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bumble-ceo-lidiane-jones-resigns-executive-chair-fill-role-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YSIEMCBYJJPPCUKIXYU3NPLJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:38:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私募股权 "二次 "销售创纪录，Ardian 完成 300 亿美元基金募集]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，私募股权基金二级市场的交易量创下历史新高，因为在交易低迷的情况下，收购公司的老板和他们的投资者都在想方设法获取现金。【原文：The secondary market for private equity funds saw record transaction volumes last year as buyout bosses and their investors looked for ways to generate cash amid a downturn in dealmaking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/private-equity-secondary-sales-hit-record-ardian-closes-30-bln-fund-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7BGPXF635J75DZKOL3MQLQ35M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:36:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美 RedNote 用户找到难得的坦诚交流空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[从经济悲观主义到对马克思主义的愤世嫉俗，再到对潜在战争的恐惧，红笔记的中美用户本周进行了罕见的坦诚交流，测试了中国社交媒体平台审查制度的极限。【原文：From economic pessimism to cynicism about Marxism and fears over the potential for war, Chinese and American users of RedNote took part this week in rare candid exchanges that tested the limits of censorship on the Chinese social media platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-us-users-rednote-find-rare-space-candid-exchanges-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIT7MTIBCNIM7JJG7SC5S6OPCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈里王子将与默多克报社对簿公堂]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈里王子对鲁珀特-默多克（Rupert Murdoch）的英国报业集团提起的诉讼于本周二在伦敦高等法院正式开庭，查尔斯国王的小儿子将在下个月的庭审中亲自出庭作证。【原文：Prince Harry's lawsuit against Rupert Murdoch's British newspaper group officially begins at the High Court in London on Tuesday, with King Charles' younger son set to appear as a witness himself at the trial next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/prince-harry-set-court-battle-with-murdoch-papers-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQON62FJ7RNGTMKXDBPGFCRWXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工业安全产品需求低迷，Fastenal业绩未达预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，Fastenal 公布的第四季度利润低于分析师预期，原因是建筑行业的持续放缓抑制了对其紧固件和其他安全产品的需求。【原文：Fastenal posted fourth-quarter profit below analysts' estimates on Friday, as a sustained slowdown in construction sector dented demand for its fasteners and other safety products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fastenal-misses-estimates-amid-sluggish-demand-industrial-safety-products-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFGUJ5E3T5IIZF7TUPL3VLSKRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场押注特朗普上台后中国会让人民币贬值，但幅度不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融市场押注，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）第二任总统任期内，中国将不会把人民币作为抵消美国关税预期的政策工具，因为有人认为，像第一任总统任期内那样的大幅贬值对陷入困境的经济弊大于利。【原文：Financial markets are betting China will not use the yuan as a policy tool to offset expected U.S. tariffs in a second Donald Trump presidency, based on a view that sharp depreciation like that seen in his first term will be more harmful than helpful to the struggling economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/markets-are-betting-china-will-let-yuan-fall-trump-takes-power-not-much-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLBUKQSIQRKBXOTGI72YO3B5TQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Truist 因投资银行业务收益而实现超预期的季度利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于资本市场走强，投资银行和交易活动更加活跃，特里斯特金融公司周五公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Truist Financial on Friday exceeded Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit, helped by stronger investment banking and trading activity as capital markets strengthened.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/truist-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-investment-banking-gains-2025-01-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APKSSZ4YSRJRJONSDMANHGJ4IA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:32:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>