<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 06:08:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 06:08:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[新任首席执行官努诺-马托斯（Nuno Matos）清理门户，澳新银行投资者做好短期阵痛的准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳新银行集团（ANZ Group）的投资者愿意支持新任首席执行官努诺-马托斯（Nuno Matos）重振这家澳大利亚银行颓势的战略，但他们正准备应对近期的打击，包括可能的股息削减。【原文：ANZ Group investors are willing to back new CEO Nuno Matos' strategy to resuscitate the Australian bank's flagging fortunes, but they are gearing up for near-term hits, including a possible dividend cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/anz-investors-brace-short-term-pain-new-ceo-nuno-matos-clears-decks-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOPA4HOCYBPOVEYAGKT62TKDEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:55:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行高层表示，随着规模扩大，澳大利亚养老基金将扩大外汇套期保值的使用范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行的一位高级官员周二表示，澳大利亚养老基金将不得不扩大外汇对冲的使用范围，因为该行业的规模可能会扩大，成为全球第二大行业，海外投资的份额也会增加。【原文：Australian pension funds will have to expand the use of foreign exchange hedging as the sector is likely to grow in size to become the second-largest globally with a larger share of investments going abroad, a top central banker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-pension-funds-expand-use-forex-hedging-size-grows-top-central-banker-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AS33CSSARFMD3KM5QHAOSRJTAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:48:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国钢材出口有望再创新高，面临关税进一步反弹的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年，中国的钢铁出口量将创下历史新高，打破了前所未有的贸易壁垒将导致出货量下降的预测，并有可能引发针对世界主要生产国的更激烈的保护主义反弹。【原文：China's steel exports are set to hit an all-time high this year, defying predictions that unprecedented trade barriers would drive down shipments, and threaten to provoke an even fiercer protectionist backlash against the world's dominant producer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-steel-exports-poised-record-high-risking-further-tariff-backlash-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBFSERSRB5KWPGX6W4Q2JMGPEQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:43:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，中国征收关税后，越南饲料制造商购买加拿大菜籽粕]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位贸易商周二表示，在中国（加拿大菜籽粕的传统买家）今年早些时候征收高额反倾销税以抑制采购后，越南的饲料加工厂正在利用加拿大菜籽粕的低价优势。【原文：Feed millers in Vietnam are taking advantage of bargain prices for Canadian canola meal after China, the product's traditional buyer, curbed purchases by imposing hefty anti-dumping duties earlier this year, three traders said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/vietnamese-feed-makers-buying-canadian-canola-meal-after-china-duties-sources-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MKGSXF6R5K4XIMWGHDMJ4LZMA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:26:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南要求美国重新考虑海产品出口禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南已要求美国重新考虑一项可能导致从明年起禁止越南部分海产品出口到美国市场的决定，这对已经受到美国关税打击的越南经济是一个潜在的打击。【原文：Vietnam has asked the United States to reconsider a decision that could lead to a ban on some Vietnamese seafood exports to the American market starting next year, a potential blow to an economy already hit by U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vietnam-asks-united-states-reconsider-seafood-export-ban-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSNYFJXTGBIZDGMZXOHP7Z7RHY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金上行趋势保持不变，但在 2026 年突破 4,000 美元之前将出现修正]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易商和业内专家表示，黄金连续创下历史新高的强劲涨势显示出今年下半年仍将持续的迹象，但在2026年突破每盎司4000美元的里程碑之前，黄金将出现健康的修正。【原文：Gold's stellar rally to successive record highs shows every sign of continuing for the rest of the year, but a healthy correction is on the cards before breaching the $4,000 per ounce milestone in 2026, traders and industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/gold-uptrend-intact-due-correction-before-topping-4000-2026-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3C5Z7KD45NAFKC2FKHHTOH3RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:10:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 19 万亿美元的股票市场曾被称为不可投资的市场，如今再次吸引了外国人的目光]]></title><description><![CDATA[外国投资者在撤出中国股市并认为中国股市不可投资三年后，正计划大举重返中国股市，他们受到了中国股市所提供的科技机会的鼓舞，以及对美国资产以外的多元化需求的增长。【原文：Foreign investors are plotting a return to China's stock markets in a big way three years after pulling back and terming them uninvestable, encouraged by the tech opportunities on offer, and a growing demand for diversification beyond U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-19-trillion-stock-market-once-called-uninvestable-lures-foreigners-again-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZAVNM52G5NU3IYF3M5SLXUE64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：美国在全面的海事任务中瞄准中国对全球港口的控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉该计划的消息人士透露，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府正致力于削弱中国的全球港口网络，并将更多战略码头置于西方控制之下。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is on a mission to weaken China's global network of ports and bring more strategic terminals under Western control, according to three sources familiar with the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-targets-chinas-grip-global-ports-sweeping-maritime-mission-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GFZUYDFGA5OKXOJEEP6PC7MILQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源机构称全球油气田衰退率正在上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际能源机构周二表示，由于更加依赖页岩和深海资源，全球油气田产量的自然下降速度正在加快。这意味着企业需要加快投资步伐，才能保持产量持平。【原文：The natural rate of decline in output from the world's oil and gas fields is speeding up, owing to more reliance on shale and deep offshore resources, the International Energy Agency said on Tuesday. That means companies will need to step up the pace of investment just to keep output flat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/global-oil-gas-field-decline-rates-are-increasing-iea-says-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXMC4E7LTVKZVP2IYPHNUULUQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 聘请前 xAI 首席财务官 Mike Liberatore 担任业务财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 公司发言人周二告诉路透社，该公司已聘请埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）旗下 xAI 公司的前财务总监迈克-利伯拉托里（Mike Liberatore）担任这家人工智能初创公司的业务财务官，负责监督其人工智能基础设施。【原文：OpenAI has hired Mike Liberatore, former finance chief at Elon Musk's xAI, to be the artificial intelligence startup's business finance officer, responsible for overseeing its AI infrastructure, a company spokesperson told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-hires-former-xai-cfo-mike-liberatore-business-finance-officer-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLWJP2D5FBKBHMO4OS2JPMX4IA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 04:48:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 美联储 9 月会议开幕，独立性受到威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFNQAQTLORLHFG4FEBZSWP2VNM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 04:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智能手机制造商 Nothing 以 13 亿美元的估值融资 2 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于伦敦的智能手机制造商Nothing周二以13亿美元的估值从老虎环球（Tiger Global）为首的一批投资者手中融资2亿美元，以寻求在其产品中整合人工智能。【原文：London-based smartphone maker Nothing on Tuesday raised $200 million from a group of investors led by Tiger Global at a valuation of $1.3 billion as it seeks to integrate artificial intelligence in its products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/smartphone-maker-nothing-raises-200-million-13-billion-valuation-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQ2CBX5FQ5M5HKM5STMRWYYMTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 04:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌计划未来两年在英国投资 50 亿英镑]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/google-sets-out-plan-invest-5-bln-pounds-britain-over-next-two-years-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CR2OTSGQZOM7JTZA7OXW2W5OE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 04:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将对《纽约时报》提起 150 亿美元的诽谤和中伤诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他将对《纽约时报》提起价值 150 亿美元的诽谤和中伤诉讼。【原文：U.S President Donald Trump said on Monday that he will be filing a $15 billion defamation and libel lawsuit against The New York Times .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-file-15-billion-defamation-libel-lawsuit-against-new-york-times-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKTRB5BHVBL5PEW5XIETVETCRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 03:54:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，越南航空公司 Vietjet 将在订购 9 年多后的本周日接收首架波音 737 max 喷射机]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietnamese-airline-vietjet-set-take-delivery-first-boeing-737-max-jet-sunday-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPKGFIR4UZN67ILIAWHXF6VR3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 03:46:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CBS 新闻报道，甲骨文是帮助 TikTok 在美国继续运营的公司之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[据哥伦比亚广播公司（CBS）周一报道，如果中美之间的框架协议最终达成，甲骨文公司将成为使 TikTok 能够在美国继续运营的企业集团之一。【原文：Oracle is among a consortium of firms that would enable TikTok to continue operations in the United States if a framework deal between the U.S. and China is finalized, CBS News reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/oracle-among-firms-enable-tiktok-continue-operations-us-cbs-news-reports-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CTDUPBSH5P7VHDCNIBLEK34SM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 03:40:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优衣库创始人柳井正表示美国可能受关税影响最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[时装品牌优衣库的日本创始人周一表示，美国可能会在关税对全球贸易的影响中付出最大的代价。【原文：The Japanese founder of fashion brand Uniqlo said on Monday the U.S. may bear the highest price from the impact of tariffs on global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/uniqlo-founder-yanai-says-us-may-suffer-most-tariffs-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V24PGJIZ3BKMRBNPIJHMP34L2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 03:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚希望在青少年社交媒体禁令下进行 "侵入性最小 "的年龄检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚周二敦促社交媒体平台采用 "侵入性最小 "的方法来检查其世界首创的青少年社交媒体禁令所涵盖的用户年龄，这些方法考虑到了人工智能（AI）和行为数据。【原文：Australia urged social media platforms on Tuesday to employ "minimally invasive" methods to check the age of users covered by its world-first teen social media ban, which take into account artificial intelligence (AI) and behavioural data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australia-wants-minimally-invasive-age-checks-under-teen-social-media-ban-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYY5PDV2XZK6HNVXJMEOQQSNSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 03:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者关注美联储减息，亚洲股市再创新高，美元徘徊不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市攀升，美元走低，因为投资者押注美国联邦储备委员会将在本周恢复宽松周期，并可能为进一步降息敞开大门。【原文：Asia stocks climbed on Tuesday while the dollar was on the back foot as investors bet the U.S. Federal Reserve would resume its easing cycle this week and potentially leave the door open to further rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGRR6TL2RVMWHLHBKNU4QAAPHI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 02:18:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场权衡俄罗斯炼油厂遭袭带来的供应风险，石油市场保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，油价在上一交易日上涨后持稳，因为市场参与者考虑到乌克兰无人机袭击俄罗斯炼油厂后，俄罗斯可能会中断供应。【原文：Oil prices held steady in early trade on Tuesday after rising in the previous session, as market participants contemplated potential supply disruption from Russia after Ukrainian drone attacks on its refineries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-steady-market-weighs-supply-risk-attacks-russian-refineries-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PO3NTJ4OW5J5DATGSL3OUL2KWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:47:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府命令达美航空公司和墨西哥航空公司在 1 月 1 日前终止合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周一晚些时候表示，它正在命令达美航空公司和墨西哥航空公司在 1 月 1 日前解散一家合资企业，该合资企业允许它们在美国-墨西哥航班的调度、定价和运力决策方面进行协调。【原文：The Trump administration said late on Monday it is ordering Delta Air Lines and Aeromexico to unwind a joint venture by January 1 that lets them coordinate on scheduling, pricing and capacity decisions for U.S.–Mexico flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-administration-orders-delta-aeromexico-end-joint-venture-by-january-1-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHXBNXVH2JOGNDSCEQOHH455ZA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:31:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普经济顾问米兰获参议院批准加入美联储董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院周一以微弱优势确认斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）为美联储理事会成员，扩大了唐纳德-特朗普总统对世界上最重要的中央银行的影响力，并在一次关键的政策会议召开前夕，将 12 票中决定利率的一票交给了他的最高经济顾问。【原文：The U.S. Senate on Monday narrowly confirmed Stephen Miran to the Federal Reserve's Board of Governors, expanding President Donald Trump's influence over the world's most important central bank and handing his top economic adviser one of 12 interest-rate-setting votes on the eve of a key policy meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-economic-adviser-miran-gets-senate-nod-join-fed-board-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2SL6QIPI5I5XPOIU6AX3K5RYM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:22:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员关注美联储一系列降息举措，美元走势受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美元兑欧元汇率接近两个半月低点，兑风险敏感的澳元汇率接近10个月低点，原因是投资者巩固了对美联储本周降息以及随后更多降息的押注。【原文：The dollar traded near a 2-1/2 month low against the euro and close to a 10-month trough versus the risk-sensitive Aussie on Tuesday as investors cemented bets for a Federal Reserve interest rate cut this week and more to follow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-back-foot-traders-eye-series-fed-rate-cuts-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5MGQ4YLLNOAHPSXIXLXGZIIWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上诉法院拒绝让特朗普解除美联储理事库克的职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周一拒绝允许唐纳德-特朗普解雇美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）--这是美联储自1913年成立以来首次由总统采取此类行动--这是一场威胁到美联储长期独立性的法律战的最新一步。【原文：A U.S. appeals court declined on Monday to allow Donald Trump to fire Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook - the first time a president has pursued such action since the central bank's founding in 1913 - in the latest step in a legal battle that threatens the Fed's longstanding independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/appeals-court-declines-let-trump-remove-fed-governor-cook-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z22EUUHSAFMPFM63GELJEMH2TI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:13:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：中美嘀嘀打车交易面临哪些障碍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国周一宣布达成一项框架协议，将短视频应用 TikTok 转为美国控制的所有权，该协议存在诸多问题和潜在障碍，包括任何交易是否符合 2024 年的一项法律。【原文：Questions and potential hurdles surround a framework agreement announced on Monday between the U.S. and China that would switch short-video app TikTok to U.S.-controlled ownership, including whether any deal will comply with a 2024 law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/what-hurdles-lie-ahead-any-us-china-tiktok-deal-2025-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZS3SUH77JOA7PYW5RZYBO2FJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在线市场 Fiverr 将裁员 30% 以推动人工智能发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于以色列的 Fiverr International 公司发言人周一表示，该公司正在裁员 30%，因为这家在线服务市场正在加倍努力利用人工智能来实现系统自动化和业务精简。【原文：Israel-based Fiverr International is laying off 30% of its workforce, a company spokesperson said on Monday, as the online services marketplace doubles down on artificial intelligence to automate systems and streamline operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/online-marketplace-fiverr-lay-off-30-workforce-ai-push-2025-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKBJQIB2SRIELK33IAVLIJH6UY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:45:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示，Reddit 在短暂中断后已恢复运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据追踪网站 Downdetector.com 报道，美国社交媒体平台 Reddit 在周一短暂宕机后，影响成千上万用户的故障情况有所缓解。【原文：An outage affecting thousands of users of social media platform Reddit in the U.S. had eased after a brief downtime on Monday, according to tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/reddit-back-up-after-brief-outage-downdetector-shows-2025-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">77JUBHMYRJNZ7H6LHOXBADSJPU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:37:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工部统计机构为 CPI 报告招聘兼职经济学家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工部劳工统计局最近因大幅下调美国非农就业人数和减少通胀数据收集工作而备受指责，该局正在招聘约25名兼职助理经济学家。【原文：The Labor Department's Bureau of Labor Statistics, under fire for recent sharp downward revisions to U.S. nonfarm payrolls and reductions to inflation data collection, is hiring about 25 part-time assistant economists, job postings showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-labor-department-statistical-agency-hiring-part-time-economists-cpi-report-2025-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6CJO2424VMV5O5UQAHEFDFLGE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美国联邦贸易委员会调查 Ticketmaster 是否采取了足够措施阻止机器人转售]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一报道，美国联邦贸易委员会正在调查 Live Nation 旗下的 Ticketmaster 是否采取了足够措施来防止机器人在其平台上非法转售门票。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is investigating whether Live Nation's Ticketmaster is doing enough to prevent bots from illegally reselling tickets on its platform, Bloomberg News reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/ftc-probes-whether-ticketmaster-does-enough-stop-resale-bots-bloomberg-news-2025-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWJJULEKAFMU5O2VIFXQXLHHKU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:21:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰 8 月房价下跌，购房者仍持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰房地产协会（REINZ）周二表示，尽管央行积极降息以刺激经济，但由于潜在购房者仍持谨慎态度，8月份新西兰房价有所下跌。【原文：New Zealand home prices edged lower in August, the Real Estate Institute of New Zealand (REINZ) said on Tuesday, as prospective buyers remained cautious despite aggressive interest rate cuts from the central bank to spur the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealand-home-prices-dip-august-buyers-remain-cautious-2025-09-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCVFGHM4ZVJLNKHTZRSWPUOMHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>