<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 18:36:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 18:36:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士选民拒绝赋予房东更多转租权力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日，瑞士举行了一场全民公投，对 Airbnb 在租房市场中的作用进行了审查，公投的初步结果显示，瑞士选民以微弱优势否决了一项赋予房东更多权力限制租客转租的法律改革。【原文：Swiss voters narrowly rejected a change in the law giving landlords more powers to restrict subletting by tenants, according to preliminary results of a referendum on Sunday that scrutinized Airbnb's role in the rental market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/swiss-voters-reject-more-powers-landlords-subletting-2024-11-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFYEYGH2GRJG7GGGGLCESXOQAE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 17:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国石油公司前老板卢尼将担任美国数据公司 Prometheus Hyperscale 主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[石油巨头英国石油公司（BP）前首席执行官伯纳德-卢尼（Bernard Looney）将担任 Prometheus Hyperscale 公司董事长。【原文：Oil major BP's former CEO Bernard Looney is set to chair Prometheus Hyperscale, the U.S.-based data company said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/former-bp-boss-looney-chair-us-data-company-prometheus-hyperscale-2024-11-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7RI2DZHJNO3ZCYJNGYOWGPD6Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 16:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度监管机构拒绝苹果公司搁置反垄断报告的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司否认有不当行为。【原文：Apple has denied wrongdoing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indian-regulator-rejects-apple-request-put-antitrust-report-hold-2024-11-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUOK7ICYCJIPNINVCMQK6AUFUU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 15:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[媒体称巴西肉类供应商停止向当地家乐福零售商供货]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体援引匿名行业消息人士的话报道，在家乐福全球首席执行官誓言将南美肉类从法国的货架上撤下以声援法国农民之后，巴西肉类包装商据说已经停止了向家乐福集团在巴西的肉类供应。【原文：Brazilian meatpackers have reportedly stopped supplying meat to the Carrefour group in Brazil after the retailer's global CEO vowed to keep South American meat off its shelves in France in solidarity with French farmers, according to local media reports that cited anonymous industry sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/brazilian-meat-suppliers-stop-deliveries-local-carrefour-retailers-media-say-2024-11-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEXNVEXALBI7RAZFGU7MDASAA4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 14:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会因贿赂指控对高塔姆-阿达尼及其侄子发出传票]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦检察官对高塔姆和萨加尔-阿达尼发出了逮捕令，指控他们参与了一项价值 2.65 亿美元的计划，通过贿赂印度官员来获得电力供应交易。【原文：Federal prosecutors issued arrest warrants for Gautam and Sagar Adani, alleging they participated in a $265 million scheme to bribe Indian officials to secure power-supply deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-sec-issues-summons-indias-adani-nephew-bribery-allegations-2024-11-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMPW5L7ELFMARJHUV7TVMKSVXM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 10:26:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[明镜》报道：专家对蒂森克虏伯钢铁公司给予积极评价]]></title><description><![CDATA[据德国《明镜》杂志周日报道，调查蒂森克虏伯钢铁业务财务需求的独立专家对该公司作为持续经营企业继续经营的能力持肯定态度。【原文：Independent experts looking into the financial needs of Thyssenkrupp's steel business have taken a positive view on its ability to continue as a going concern, Germany's Der Spiegel magazine reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/experts-give-positive-update-thyssenkrupp-steel-reports-spiegel-2024-11-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PONQZA4R4RNDXE62EFVGNQHUJ4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 09:53:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，特朗普选中的卢特尼克的公司正在与 Tether 就价值 20 亿美元的比特币借贷项目进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周日报道，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的商务部长人选霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）正在商谈与全球最大的稳定币Tether公司加深金融联系，启动一个价值20亿美元的项目，以比特币为抵押向客户提供美元贷款。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's pick for Commerce Secretary, Howard Lutnick is in talks to deepen his financial ties with the company operating the world's largest stablecoin, Tether, by launching a $2 billion project to lend dollars to clients against bitcoin, Bloomberg News reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-pick-lutnicks-firm-talks-with-tether-2-billion-bitcoin-lending-project-2024-11-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CW5NWK2GWVMOJGPIBXSRUOH33M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 09:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，高盛基金将在 Northvolt 上损失 9 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周六报道，瑞典锂离子电池生产商 Northvolt 在本周早些时候申请破产保护后，高盛管理的基金将注销近 9 亿美元。【原文：Funds managed by Goldman Sachs will write off nearly $900 million after Swedish lithium-ion battery producer Northvolt filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy earlier this week, Britain's Financial Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-funds-take-900-million-hit-northvolt-ft-reports-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XPM74PSQZN3HJJTDQFOLBXGUI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 17:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿达尼能源解决方案公司称肯尼亚能源交易取消不会造成重大影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿达尼能源解决方案公司（Adani Energy Solutions）周六表示，肯尼亚取消一个价值 7.36 亿美元的输电线路项目不需要根据印度证券交易所规则进行任何监管披露，因为这属于其正常业务范围。【原文：Adani Energy Solutions said on Saturday that Kenya's cancellation of a $736 million transmission line project did not require it to make any regulatory disclosure under Indian stock exchange rules as it was within its ordinary course of business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/adani-energy-solutions-says-no-material-impact-kenya-energy-deal-cancellation-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VLBN5PEXRJ6JDLLZXYIZC4OJQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 16:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，TikTok 首席执行官在特朗普执政前征求马斯克意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周六援引知情人士的话报道称，字节跳动旗下的 TikTok 已就美国事务向当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的亲密顾问埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）征求意见。【原文：ByteDance-owned TikTok has sought input on U.S. matters from Elon Musk, a close adviser to President-elect Donald Trump, the Wall Street Journal reported on Saturday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/tiktok-ceo-sought-musks-input-ahead-trump-administration-wsj-reports-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEQWBCTXKJKO3BMORF5SRF4WL4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 16:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博世将削减德国 10,000 名员工的工作时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[这家全球最大的汽车零部件供应商在一天前宣布裁员数千人。【原文：The world's largest car-parts supplier announced thousands of job cuts a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bosch-cut-hours-10000-workers-germany-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOFBO3HAERLU3CFQ7WRCBZOQAE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 15:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国阿斯达请回行业资深人士莱顿领导业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[陷入困境的英国超市阿斯达（Asda）周六表示，资深零售商艾伦-莱顿（Allan Leighton）将重新担任执行董事长，在他担任首席执行官二十多年后，阿斯达在出售给沃尔玛（Walmart）之前扭转了经营局面。【原文：Struggling British supermarket Asda said on Saturday veteran retailer Allan Leighton would return as executive chairman, more than two decades after he served as CEO when he turned around the business before selling it to Walmart .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-asda-brings-back-industry-veteran-leighton-chair-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOCBKVMNABIMXFHX7AI324LNSQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 11:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国华为的目标是在 6-12 个月内在 Harmony 操作系统上开发 10 万个应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[被美国列入黑名单的中国华为公司周六表示，在寻求广泛帮助以实现自力更生的过程中，华为将在未来几个月内为其和谐操作系统开发 10 万个应用程序。【原文：China's Huawei, blacklisted by the U.S., said on Saturday it is targeting 100,000 applications for its Harmony operating system in coming months as it seeks widespread help to achieve self-reliance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-huawei-aims-100000-apps-harmony-os-6-12-months-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQTCKLCYNNOPLFCU7N2C7TSE54</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 10:41:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西冻结 33.3 亿美元支出以遵守财政规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西政府周五晚些时候加强了支出控制，将支出冻结在 193 亿雷亚尔（33.3 亿美元），以遵守今年的财政规定。【原文：Brazil's government tightened spending controls late on Friday, freezing expenditure at 19.3 billion reais ($3.33 billion) to comply with this year's fiscal rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-freezes-spending-333-bln-comply-with-fiscal-rules-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OIDFGNJPSRNTVP33R4BTD77G4U</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 10:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称，Seven & i 创始家族就收购事宜与 KKR 等公司进行了接触]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周六报道，日本 Seven &amp; i 控股公司的创始家族已与 KKR &amp; Co 和其他投资公司接洽，希望参与对该零售商的潜在收购。【原文：The founding family of Japan's Seven &amp; i Holdings has approached KKR &amp; Co and other investment firms about participating in the potential buyout of the retailer, the Nikkei newspaper reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/seven-i-founding-family-sounded-out-kkr-others-about-buyout-nikkei-says-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SM7EM32WAZKGFK637JYMUXZSNE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 09:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿达尼首席财务官就美国指控进行辩护，称与一份商业合同有关]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）在美国受到的贿赂起诉与阿达尼绿色能源公司（Adani Green Energy）的一份合同有关，该合同约占其业务的 10%，该集团的首席财务官周六表示，该集团的其他公司均未被指控有不当行为。【原文：A U.S. bribery indictment of Indian billionaire Gautam Adani is linked to one contract of Adani Green Energy comprising some 10% of its business, and none of the conglomerate's other companies are accused of wrongdoing, the group's CFO said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/adani-cfo-defends-against-us-charges-says-linked-one-business-contract-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4M3JZMTVZPVTITJ7DOQ5Q2YCU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国指控墨西哥汽车零部件工厂违反北美贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国指控墨西哥一家法资汽车零部件工厂的工人被剥夺了集体谈判权，这违反了北美贸易协定，并要求墨西哥进行调查。【原文：The U.S. has alleged workers at a French-owned auto parts plant in Mexico were denied the right to collective bargaining in violation of a North America trade agreement and asked Mexico to investigate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-alleges-car-parts-factory-mexico-violates-north-america-trade-pact-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCPWEYKI2JJGFBA5M5Q4UDJSEE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众品牌老板：裁员、关闭工厂是解决汽车制造商问题的必要手段]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与工人的争端不断升级之际，大众汽车首席执行官在接受报纸采访时表示，大众汽车认为没有机会避免裁员和关闭工厂，以削减 40 亿欧元（42 亿美元）的成本。【原文：Volkswagen sees no chance of avoiding layoffs and plant closures in order to cut 4 billion euros ($4.2 billion) in costs, the brand's chief executive said in a newspaper interview, amid an escalating dispute with workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-brand-boss-layoffs-plant-closures-needed-fix-carmakers-problems-2024-11-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJW4WXWZT5IH5NX5RROTTGWYZU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官驳回证交会制裁埃隆-马斯克的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周五驳回了美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的制裁请求，原因是他今年早些时候在监管机构对其斥资 440 亿美元收购推特（Twitter）的调查中未能按法庭要求出庭作证。【原文：A federal judge on Friday rejected the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's request to sanction Elon Musk over his failure to appear earlier this year for court-ordered testimony in the regulator's probe of his $44 billion takeover of Twitter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-judge-rejects-sec-request-sanction-elon-musk-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7GXPII5RFJZ3CBLAQQUTDKEQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 23:56:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产说服美国法院取消刹车缺陷集体诉讼的资格]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车公司周五说服联邦上诉法院取消了10起集体诉讼的资格，这些集体诉讼指控这家日本汽车制造商销售的汽车和越野车的自动紧急制动系统存在缺陷，导致车辆无故突然停车。【原文：Nissan persuaded a federal appeals court on Friday to decertify 10 class actions accusing the Japanese automaker of selling cars and SUVs with defective automatic emergency braking systems that caused vehicles to stop suddenly for no reason.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/nissan-persuades-us-court-decertify-brake-defect-class-actions-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5GUYIQX3NIFHMAASHRM5SROOI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，博雅银行在印度的三名银行家因股票销售调查而离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士称，美国银行在印度的三名投资银行家已经离职，因为该公司正在调查有关股票销售不当行为的指控。【原文：Three Bank of America investment bankers in India have left the company as it probes allegations of wrongdoing over stock sales, a source familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/three-bofa-bankers-india-leave-amid-probe-into-stock-sale-source-says-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKDZ6V3ADZKT3GSWCN7ED4WSUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:40:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，沙特阿美石油公司正在洽谈向美国软件制造商 Mavenir 投资 10 亿美元事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周五告诉路透社，沙特阿美石油公司（Saudi Aramco）的数字部门正在洽谈收购 Mavenir 公司的少数股权，这笔交易可能会给这家美国电信软件制造商带来约 30 亿美元的价值。【原文：Saudi Aramco's digital arm is in talks to take a significant minority stake in Mavenir, in a deal that is likely to value the U.S. telecommunications software maker at about $3 billion, people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-aramco-unit-talks-invest-1-billion-us-software-maker-mavenir-sources-say-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">277ZWTIBMFP25AHFYFRCJI7ETY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 黑色星期五消费支出成为市场关注焦点，股市接近历史纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[未来一周，美国消费者和零售业的健康状况将成为焦点，因为黑色星期五拉开了假日购物季的序幕，这可能会揭示出买家是如何应对价格上涨的。【原文：The health of the U.S. consumer and the retail sector will be in focus in the coming week, as Black Friday kicks off a holiday shopping season that could shed light on how buyers are grappling with higher prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-black-friday-puts-consumer-spending-markets-glare-with-stocks-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4DFRSS3KFJ3DMQD7FITXIRWTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普财政部长人选的猜谜游戏加剧了美国债券市场的负面情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者希望当选总统唐纳德-特朗普能尽快任命一位财政部长，以缓解他们对共和党人政策承诺的担忧，这些政策承诺已经拖累了本已低迷的美国政府债券市场。【原文：Investors are hoping President-elect Donald Trump will name a Treasury secretary soon who will assuage their concerns about the Republican's policy promises that have weighed on an already sagging U.S. government bond market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/guessing-game-over-trumps-treasury-pick-adds-us-bond-markets-negative-mood-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EW33KB2BO5MZTMJUL2T3GJ3SMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，CoreWeave 2025 年美国 IPO 目标估值超过 350 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周五告诉路透社，人工智能云平台 CoreWeave 预计将于明年在美国首次公开募股，目标估值超过 350 亿美元。【原文：Artificial intelligence cloud platform CoreWeave, is aiming for a valuation of more than $35 billion in its U.S. initial public offering that is expected to occur next year, people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/coreweave-targets-valuation-over-35-billion-2025-us-ipo-sources-say-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFSJJ7CI2FMXVK336SH6Y7WJMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星因侵犯 Netlist 专利被判赔偿 1.18 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，德克萨斯州马歇尔市的一个联邦陪审团裁定，计算机内存公司 Netlist 在一起关于改进高性能内存产品数据处理技术的专利诉讼案中，应向三星电子赔偿 1.18 亿美元。【原文：A federal jury in Marshall, Texas, on Friday awarded computer memory company Netlist $118 million in damages from Samsung Electronics in a patent lawsuit over technology for improving data processing in high-performance memory products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/samsung-ordered-pay-118-million-infringing-netlist-patents-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXT76Y2KGVI75E4IJ3L6KME7AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 21:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称沃尔玛健康与保健主管离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份内部备忘录显示，沃尔玛价值 550 亿美元的健康和保健部门负责人在任职不到两年后即将离职，他曾负责监督该公司进军诊所的失败。【原文：The head of Walmart's $55-billion health and wellness division, who oversaw the company's failed push into clinics, is leaving after less than two years in the role, an internal memo seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmarts-health-wellness-head-departs-memo-says-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELV6EIBDW5JAJPHMAIMBJR7HXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 21:36:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储调查发现，除债务和贸易战外，通胀风险正在消退]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美联储周五公布的一项最新调查显示，当选总统唐纳德-特朗普可能在竞选时极力反对高通胀，但在他11月5日赢得大选时，金融专业人士已经不再关注物价上涨，而是开始担心美国债务增加、可能出现的经济衰退以及全球贸易风险，这些都是金融业稳定性面临的最大威胁。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump may have campaigned hard against high inflation, but by the time of his Nov. 5 election victory financial professionals had moved on from rising prices and begun worrying about rising U.S. debt, possible recession, and risks to global trade as among the top threats to the stability of the financial sector, according to a new Federal Reserve survey released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-survey-finds-inflation-fading-risk-next-debt-trade-wars-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAV5XZAU65O2JLKNE7XVGGWLT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 21:06:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邮件称商会看到美国对华出口打压新动向]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商会在周四的一封电子邮件中告诉会员们，拜登政府最快将于下周公布新的对华出口限制措施。【原文：The Biden administration is set to unveil new export restrictions on China as soon as next week, the U.S. Chamber of Commerce told members in a Thursday email.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chamber-commerce-sees-new-us-export-crackdown-china-email-says-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2OHXYKYYJKFPGBOQ7XIJZPI5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 20:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称 2024 财年获得创纪录的金融补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）周五在一份声明中表示，该机构在 2024 财年获得了 82 亿美元的金融赔偿，创下历史最高纪录。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) obtained $8.2 billion in financial remedies, the highest amount in its history, in fiscal 2024, the agency said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-sec-obtained-record-financial-remedies-fiscal-2024-agency-says-2024-11-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FY2P7V247RP4HDOFPLRH5RQAGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 20:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>