<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:11:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:11:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子旗下哈曼公司将以 15 亿欧元收购采埃孚集团的 ADAS 业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子（Samsung Electronics）周二表示，该公司旗下的哈曼国际（Harman International）已同意以 15 亿欧元（17.7 亿美元）的价格收购德国汽车供应商采埃孚（ZF Friedrichshafen）的高级驾驶辅助系统（ADAS）业务。【原文：Samsung Electronics said on Tuesday its unit Harman International has agreed to acquire German automotive supplier ZF Friedrichshafen's advanced driver assistance system (ADAS) business for 1.5 billion euros ($1.77 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-elec-unit-harman-acquire-zf-groups-adas-business-15-bln-euros-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUY5YJX4PROODKG2A6WX7GE4NQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街担忧泡沫，全球投资者转向中国人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着华尔街对人工智能行业投机泡沫的担忧与日俱增，全球投资者正在加大对中国人工智能公司的投注，押注下一个 DeepSeek，并寻求多元化发展。【原文：Global investors are increasing their wagers on Chinese artificial intelligence companies, betting on the next DeepSeek and seeking to diversify, with concerns growing about a speculative bubble in the sector on Wall Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-investors-turn-chinese-ai-wall-street-fears-bubble-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBABIR7AGRNB7DEWWCUTDLG5Z4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 07:28:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国批准减肥药后，诺和诺德在法兰克福上涨近 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国食品和药物管理局批准诺和诺德公司生产减肥药后，该公司在法兰克福上市的股票周二早盘高开近10%。【原文：Novo Nordisk's Frankfurt-listed shares opened nearly 10% higher in early trading on Tuesday after the U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved its weight-loss pill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-up-nearly-10-frankfurt-after-us-approves-weight-loss-pill-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUMP7S4PZFIL5PLBLTAVOKODUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 07:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德的 Wegovy 药片将测试消费者对现金的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）新近获批的减肥药Wegovy将成为快速增长的现金支付消费市场的一个试验案例，计划于1月初直接进入美国自费渠道。【原文：Novo Nordisk's newly approved weight-loss pill version of Wegovy will be a test case for the fast-growing cash-paying consumer market, with plans for the first highly effective oral treatment to go straight to U.S. self-pay channels in early January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novos-wegovy-pill-test-demand-consumers-with-cash-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMKUACFSEBOXJCH6PNEE52ZMPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 06:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年的市场：黄金、金发姑娘和美元熊]]></title><description><![CDATA[大多数投资者都知道，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普重新掌权，这个世界上最大的经济体今年会有所不同，但很少有人预测到今年的走势会有多疯狂，或者最终的结果会如何。【原文：Most investors knew this year would be different given U.S. President Donald Trump's return to power in the world's biggest economy, but few predicted how wild the ride would get, or the end results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-performance-pix-graphics-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNJT5VJ3IBJM3KFWAFRL7WARBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 06:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车助力欧洲新车销量连续第五个月增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲汽车游说组织ACEA周二发布的数据显示，受德国、意大利和西班牙等市场电动汽车注册量增加的推动，11月份欧洲新车销量连续第五个月同比增长。【原文：New car sales in Europe rose year-on-year in November for a fifth consecutive month, helped by an increase in EV registrations in markets including Germany, Italy and Spain, data from the European auto lobby ACEA showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/new-car-sales-europe-rise-fifth-month-helped-by-evs-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGCKZ6KRPJINVMY76B24EXT6YQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:08:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲建筑股在创下历史新高后面临现实考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲建筑股是 2025 年涨幅最突出的股票之一，原因是围绕德国基础设施刺激政策、乌克兰重建希望和人工智能相关热潮的主题交易受到热捧。【原文：European construction shares have been among 2025's standout gainers, lifted by enthusiasm for thematic trades around Germany's infrastructure stimulus, hopes of Ukraine's rebuild and the AI-related boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/european-construction-stocks-face-reality-check-after-record-run-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTB5464D2NOGTLQWQHI4YEWDPM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度经济增长可能保持强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[在稳健的消费支出和企业投资的推动下，美国经济在第三季度可能实现了快速增长，但在生活成本上升和政府近期停摆的影响下，增长势头似乎有所减弱。【原文：The U.S. economy likely grew at a brisk clip in the third quarter, driven by solid consumer spending and business investment, but momentum appears to have since faded amid the rising cost of living and recent government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-economic-growth-likely-remained-strong-third-quarter-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4CSIJHOCJK6ROJBDVQTQHFMZM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚退休基金将购买悉尼 Westfield 购物中心 5.76 亿澳元的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚退休信托基金（ART）周二表示，将以 8.64 亿澳元（5.7568 亿美元）的价格收购 Scentre 集团旗下悉尼标志性购物中心 Westfield 近 20% 的股份。【原文：The Australian Retirement Trust (ART) will acquire a near 20% stake in Scentre Group's iconic Westfield Sydney shopping mall for A$864 million ($575.68 million), the shopping centre owner said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australian-retirement-fund-buy-576-million-stake-westfield-sydney-mall-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMWONXVKTZN77E3LVI6ABVXUTQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 04:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前日本央行决策者称，日本财政困境可能导致更多日元下跌和收益率上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[前央行决策者足立诚司告诉路透社，由于市场对政府扩张性财政政策的担忧，日本可能面临日元进一步下跌和债券收益率持续上升的局面。【原文：Japan may face further yen declines and a relentless rise in bond yields driven by market concern over the government's expansionary fiscal policy, former central bank policymaker Seiji Adachi told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-fiscal-woes-may-cause-more-yen-falls-yield-rises-says-ex-boj-policymaker-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APJZMFJCMVJ5BKPXVXFXHAQHR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 04:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[直播网络攻击后，中国瓜子网股价跌至近五周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一晚间，中国短视频平台酷爱秀遭遇网络攻击，周二股价下跌多达 6%，至 62.70 港元（8.06 美元），为 11 月 21 日以来最低。【原文：Shares of Kuaishou dropped by as much as 6% on Tuesday to HK$62.70 ($8.06), their lowest since November 21, after the Chinese short video platform was hit by a cyberattack on Monday night.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-kuaishou-shares-fall-near-five-week-low-after-livestreaming-cyberattack-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6E4PZKVGQFLLNIFHLWOKK3YMEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:59:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受网络攻击报告影响，中国瓜子网跌至近五周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，中国短视频平台周一遭遇网络攻击，导致露骨内容突然激增，瓜子二手车股价周二下跌多达 6%，至 62.70 港元（8.06 美元），创 11 月 21 日以来新低。【原文：Shares of Kuaishou Technology dropped by as much as 6% on Tuesday to HK$62.70 ($8.06), their lowest since November 21, after media reported that the Chinese short video platform experienced a sudden surge of explicit content because of a cyberattack on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-kuaishou-falls-near-five-week-low-report-cyberattack-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWQNBP3GJM2TN46Q7W6RRG5GA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市、贵金属上涨；日元受到干预观察]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市与贵金属齐涨，原因是投资者在节日假期前延续了买盘势头，预计当天晚些时候将公布美国国内生产总值（GDP）的预估数据。【原文：Asia shares rose alongside precious metals on Tuesday as momentum buying from investors extended ahead of the festive holidays, with an advanced reading on U.S. GDP expected later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGWUTPU52VM27GIUZ4V5QWOBP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 02:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[干预威胁席卷而来，日元岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在美元广泛走软的背景下，日元小幅上扬，此前东京当局发出了迄今为止最严厉的警告，表明东京准备采取干预措施，日元兑主要同业货币在近期低点附近徘徊。【原文：The yen perked up slightly on Tuesday amid broad U.S. dollar weakness after the severest warning yet from authorities signalled Tokyo's readiness to intervene as the Japanese currency hovered near recent lows against major peers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/frail-yen-whipped-around-intervention-threat-swirls-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3CKXV52CJLF3NZUYMKHYE53QM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 02:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场权衡委内瑞拉和俄罗斯供应风险，石油价格下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，油价在上一交易日上涨超过2%后有所回落，原因是美国表示可能出售其扣押的委内瑞拉原油，而乌克兰对俄罗斯船只和码头的袭击加剧了市场对供应中断的担忧。【原文：Oil prices eased in early trade on Tuesday after rising more than 2% in the previous session as the U.S. said it might sell Venezuelan crude it has seized, while Ukraine's attacks on Russian vessels and piers heightened supply disruption fears.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-slips-market-weighs-venezuela-russia-supply-risks-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AICGIAFNX5OQPNEYC7WEFCQIYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 01:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，字节跳动计划在 2026 年斥资 230 亿美元建设人工智能基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周一援引知情人士的话报道称，TikTok 的所有者字节跳动已初步计划在 2026 年投入 1600 亿元人民币（约合 227.4 亿美元）的资本支出，用于建设人工智能基础设施。【原文：TikTok owner ByteDance has made preliminary plans for capital expenditure of 160 billion yuan ($22.74 billion) in 2026 to build artificial intelligence infrastructure, the Financial Times reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bytedance-plans-spend-23-billion-towards-ai-infrastructure-2026-ft-reports-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LOUDIIMEZLLBPXYAGRVNMILJE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 01:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，萨克斯全球公司正考虑将破产作为最后手段]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道，高端连锁百货公司萨克斯第五大道（Saks Fifth Avenue）的母公司萨克斯全球公司（Saks Global）正在考虑将破产保护作为最后的手段。【原文：Saks Global, parent of high-end department store chain Saks Fifth Avenue, is weighing Chapter 11 bankruptcy as a last resort, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/saks-global-is-considering-bankruptcy-last-resort-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QMZOUM3K5PGDKOUTF3ZA7TWOM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》记者就聊天机器人培训问题起诉谷歌、xAI 和 OpenAI]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位因揭露硅谷血液检测初创公司Theranos欺诈行为而闻名的调查记者周一起诉埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的xAI、Anthropic、谷歌、OpenAI、Meta Platforms和Perplexity，指控它们未经许可使用受版权保护的书籍来训练人工智能系统。【原文：An investigative reporter best known for exposing fraud at Silicon Valley blood-testing startup Theranos sued Elon Musk's xAI, Anthropic, Google , OpenAI, Meta Platforms and Perplexity on Monday for using copyrighted books without permission to train their artificial intelligence systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/new-york-times-reporter-sues-google-xai-openai-over-chatbot-training-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TVTQ4HQ7J5I55E62WB3SVPJ3UU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:06:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德减肥药获美国批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周一批准了诺和诺德公司的减肥药，使这家丹麦制药商在销售一种强效减肥口服药物的竞争中占得先机，并希望从竞争对手礼来（Eli Lilly）手中夺回失地。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved Novo Nordisk's weight-loss pill on Monday, giving the Danish drugmaker a leg up in the race to market a potent oral medication for shedding pounds as it looks to regain lost ground from rival Eli Lilly .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novo-nordisk-wins-us-approval-weight-loss-pill-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFSOGEWWHBN7PIM5GVRTF6UWMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump to press defense giants on delays, mulls curbs on executive pay]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he will meet major defense contractors next week to address production delays and cost overruns while the administration plans an executive order to limit dividends, buybacks and executive pay.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-press-defense-giants-delays-mulls-curbs-executive-pay-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4ONL5J2NBKX7NHPWE7WWL47DI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goodman Group, Canada's CPPIB strike $9.3 bln deal for Europe data centres]]></title><description><![CDATA[Australian data centre landlord Goodman Group said on Tuesday it had signed a A$14 billion ($9.32 billion) partnership agreement with Canada Pension Plan Investment Board to develop data centre projects in Frankfurt, Amsterdam and Paris.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/goodman-group-canada-pension-plan-establish-93-billion-european-data-center-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRXVDU4CTVP53NFC2F67YSQIIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democratic-led states sue to block US consumer watchdog's defunding under Trump]]></title><description><![CDATA[A coalition of Democratic-led states filed a lawsuit on Monday seeking to prevent President Donald Trump's administration from defunding the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau by refusing to request money from the Federal Reserve.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/democratic-led-states-sue-block-us-consumer-watchdogs-defunding-under-trump-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3QTGDEFRRNERBSRWFDODBRDH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US farm agency lost 20,000 staff in first five months of Trump administration]]></title><description><![CDATA[More than 20,300 employees left the U.S. Department of Agriculture in the first five months of the administration of President Donald Trump, about a fifth of staff, according to a report from the agency's inspector general.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-farm-agency-lost-20000-staff-first-five-months-trump-administration-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PDMWNWN4JJ6HKHETDDBFC6KHQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:59:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil oil union set to accept Petrobras labor offer, end strike]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian oil workers union FUP said on Monday it plans to accept a counteroffer from state-run company Petrobras for a labor deal, paving the way to end a week-long strike.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/brazil-oil-union-set-accept-petrobras-labor-offer-end-strike-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMWWVG3IKZKPJCWOUSMLZZ2UX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:42:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US business equipment borrowings down more than 4% y/y in November, ELFA says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. companies borrowed 4.4% less to finance equipment investments in November compared with the same period a year earlier, the Equipment Leasing and Finance Association (ELFA) said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-business-equipment-borrowings-down-more-than-4-yy-november-elfa-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIT4BOHD4ZNVHCNZD2H4JVB7IM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US adds DJI, other foreign drones to national security list]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Communications Commission said on Monday it is adding China's DJI and all foreign made drones and components to a list of companies determined to pose unacceptable risks to U.S. national security and will bar approvals of new types of drones for import or sale in the United States.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-adds-dji-other-foreign-drones-national-security-list-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4YO45F3KNLKXGXBOBPORBW3YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[South Korea online retailer Coupang faces US securities class action over massive data breach]]></title><description><![CDATA[South Korean e-commerce company Coupang has been sued in a U.S. court in an investor class action alleging violations of securities laws after a cybersecurity breach exposed personal information of more than 33 million customers.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/south-korea-online-retailer-coupang-faces-us-securities-class-action-over-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHNYYG5WQFNAFBOKHEHGJWDSOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FanDuel, CME Group launch prediction markets in five US states]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sports betting firm FanDuel and derivatives exchange heavyweight CME Group on Monday announced the launch of their prediction markets platform in five U.S. states, as the red-hot asset class continues to draw in new entrants.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fanduel-cme-group-launch-prediction-markets-five-us-states-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KQOHEC6JJI75BGALSUELFO3YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[United Launch Alliance CEO Tory Bruno resigns]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tory Bruno has resigned as United Launch Alliance's chief executive officer after leading the space venture for nearly 12 years, the firm said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/united-launch-alliance-ceo-tory-bruno-resigns-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MJSZAB2MBOCJJ65DV4L3OXVKA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lawmakers want US to disclose any approvals of Nvidia H200 China licenses]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two senior Democratic lawmakers on Monday asked the U.S. Commerce Department to disclose details and any approvals of ongoing license reviews for potential sales to Chinese firms of Nvidia's second-most powerful AI chips.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/lawmakers-want-us-disclose-any-approvals-nvidia-h200-china-licenses-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJGRIXTZJZNWFFTX75LBKYXB5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>