<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:34:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:34:04 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[市场评估英伟达业绩，纳斯达克、标准普尔期货收平]]></title><description><![CDATA[科技股重镇纳斯达克指数和基准 S&amp;P 500 指数周四收平，此前人工智能领军企业英伟达（Nvidia）的季度业绩预测未能给投资者留下深刻印象，但营收和盈利均好于预期，表明需求仍有弹性。【原文：Futures tracking the tech-heavy Nasdaq and the benchmark S&amp;P 500 were flat on Thursday, after AI-darling Nvidia's quarterly forecast failed to impress investors but a beat on both revenue and earnings expectations signaled resilient demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-sp-futures-flat-markets-assess-nvidias-results-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YS6S4ORXQBKH5OV3A4VBVLFH6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国不会对欧盟白兰地实施临时反倾销措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周四表示，尽管 1 月份开始的反倾销调查认定存在倾销行为，但不会对从欧盟进口的白兰地征收关税，这为双方在紧张的贸易谈判中提供了喘息的空间。【原文：China said on Thursday it would not impose tariffs on brandy imported from the European Union despite an anti-dumping investigation it opened in January determining dumping had taken place, giving both sides room to breathe in tense trade talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/china-wont-impose-provisional-anti-dumping-measures-eu-brandy-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRM7UMEHPRNWHCNS76MGJMQCII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:10:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者减少消费，Birkenstock销售额略有下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，Birkenstock 第三季度营收略低于预期，原因是在生活成本高企的情况下，顾客不愿购买价格昂贵的鞋类产品，如这家德国砂器制造商生产的软木鞋。【原文：Birkenstock marginally missed expectations for third-quarter revenue on Thursday as customers held back from spending on pricey footwear, such as the German sandalmaker's cork-based shoes, amid high costs of living.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/birkenstock-misses-sales-estimates-consumers-cut-back-spending-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXMFU3FAEBPL5OOWX4YJWRMJXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国取消白兰地临时措施后，欧洲烈酒生产商大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国商务部表示不会对从欧盟进口的白兰地实施临时反倾销措施后，法国烈酒制造商人头马君度和保乐力加的股票周四早盘大涨。【原文：Shares in French spirit makers Remy Cointreau and Pernod Ricard rallied early on Thursday after China's commerce ministry said it will not impose provisional anti-dumping measures on brandy imported from the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/european-spirits-makers-jump-after-china-drops-provisional-brandy-measures-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFK5RVJPXNLXXGNZNB4FQX7AEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 15 个月来首次上调经济评估]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于出现了消费改善的迹象，日本政府一年多来首次上调了对经济的评估，这使人们对更广泛的经济复苏持乐观态度。【原文：The Japanese government has upgraded its economic assessment for the first time in more than a year on signs of improved consumption, fostering optimism for a broader recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-raises-economic-assessment-first-time-15-months-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UNZM4TMPFIBRK4DMQGZVPTVUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国六个州通胀率下降，表明全国通胀率下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的初步数据显示，8 月份德国六个重要州的通胀率有所下降，这表明本月全国通胀率可能会明显下降。【原文：Inflation fell in six important German states in August, preliminary data showed on Thursday, suggesting that national inflation could decline noticeably this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/inflation-down-six-german-states-pointing-national-decline-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7A3H566HROMVH2USCO3SLM27M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:17:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Huawei sees first-half earnings surge on smartphone renaissance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chinese tech giant Huawei (HWT.UL) reported hefty jumps in first-half revenue and net profit on Thursday, with smartphone sales robust and its smart car components business also doing well despite U.S. sanctions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/huawei-sees-first-half-earnings-surge-smartphone-renaissance-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBNBJ5ZL4ZPDHDSAKRIHUGBRRQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:11:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，谷歌考虑在越南建立大型数据中心，这是美国大型科技公司在越南建立的首个数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士透露，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司正在考虑在越南建设一个大型数据中心，这将是美国大型科技公司在东南亚国家的首次此类投资。【原文：Alphabet's Google is considering building a large data centre in Vietnam, a person briefed on the plans said, in what would be the first such investment by a big U.S. technology company in the Southeast Asian nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-weighs-large-data-centre-vietnam-source-says-nations-first-by-us-big-tech-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YL5ULIVU4BMRPMBEO4UWSPAOWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 06:35:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债券市场在夏季的辉煌表现后面临清算]]></title><description><![CDATA[政府债券市场经历了一个价格稳健上涨的夏天，现在面临着对央行快速降息和通胀放缓押注的清算，更不用说紧锣密鼓的美国总统大选了。【原文：Government bond markets, which have enjoyed a summer of solid price gains, now face a reckoning with their bets for speedy central bank rate cuts and slowing inflation, not to mention a tight U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bond-markets-face-reckoning-after-stellar-summer-run-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFKY6ZW4BNLQ7O3A6GJ534L2OY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 06:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保乐力加年销售额下降 1%，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国保乐力加集团（Pernod Ricard）周四公布的全年有机销售额下降了 1%，基本符合预期和该集团的指导目标，因为该集团成功地抵消了其在美国和中国的主要业务所面临的严重问题。【原文：France's Pernod Ricard reported a 1% fall in full-year organic sales on Thursday, largely in line with forecasts and its own guidance, as it managed to mostly offset deep problems in its key U.S. and Chinese businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pernod-ricards-annual-sales-fall-1-line-with-estimates-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5M43PANBINKNJCUIRRSFIC27TE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 05:34:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国地区性银行投资收益激增，贷款却乏善可陈]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于经济衰退和货币政策传导缓慢，迫使银行转而从事债券交易，中国几家地区性银行报告称，今年上半年投资收入大幅增长，即使其主要贷款业务也出现了下滑。【原文：Several Chinese regional banks have reported a jump in their investment income in the first half of the year, even as their primary lending businesses faltered, as the flailing economy and slow monetary transmission forces banks into bond trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-regional-banks-investment-revenues-surge-even-lending-falters-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GEQOWQCACBOOZF2KZNEYLJPLQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 05:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[遏制投资浪费，中国担忧经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国地方政府的发债计划已经落后，因为对潜在浪费性基础设施投资的审查日益增多，这加剧了关于这些资金可用于其他领域以刺激经济增长回归目标的讨论。【原文：China's local governments have fallen behind on their debt issuance plans as scrutiny mounts over potentially wasteful infrastructure investment, fuelling talk that such funds could be used in other areas to stimulate growth back towards target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/it-reins-wasteful-investment-china-frets-over-growth-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OIDSWIQPFJ4RMWB6GZXNZZFLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 05:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价英伟达观摩会结束，重回通胀警戒线]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HI75DQBGMBLLPPSZS6M476UE4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:33:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片业大放异彩，亚洲企业盈利前景改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于该地区的半导体公司受益于人工智能的蓬勃发展，一个重要的亚洲股票指数获得了三年多来最大的盈利预测提升。【原文：A key Asia stock index has gained its biggest lift in earnings projections in more than three years, as the region's semiconductor firms benefit from the boom in generative artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asian-firms-earnings-outlook-improves-chip-sector-shines-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5SOFGFWSFKZVGKTWKXROSDZAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:25:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业机构 ACEA 称，由于电池电动汽车销量下滑，7 月份欧盟新车销量持平]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲汽车工业组织周四公布的数据显示，7月份欧盟新车销量增长0.2%，但因法国和德国的销量下降而放缓，同时电池电动汽车的市场份额继续下降。【原文：New car sales in the European Union rose 0.2% in July, slowed by declines in France and Germany, while battery-electric vehicles continued to lose market share, data from Europe's auto industry body showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-new-car-sales-flat-july-battery-electric-slumps-industry-body-acea-says-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6EC4BOKT5PUNCVGIF72PTHG7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 CBA 首席执行官抨击国会议员对银行卡支付费用的 "误导]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚最大的贷款机构澳大利亚联邦银行首席执行官周四指责一名议员散布错误信息，称银行对购物者的借记卡和信用卡支付收费不公平。【原文：The CEO of Commonwealth Bank of Australia , the country's biggest lender, accused a member of parliament of spreading misinformation on Thursday by saying banks were charging shoppers unfairly for debit and credit card payments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-cba-chief-blasts-mp-misinformation-card-payment-charges-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZOM7TJ5LJOIDHEWRLEO2B36I4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 02:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩令人失望，亚洲股市追随华尔街期货走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于英伟达（Nvidia）的业绩令一些看涨的投资者感到失望，亚洲股市周四跟随华尔街期货走低，同时美元走稳，国债收益率曲线也险些转正。【原文：Asian shares followed Wall Street futures lower on Thursday as Nvidia's results disappointed some bullish investors, while the dollar steadied and the Treasury yield curve came within a whisker of turning positive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZRTKBEHONL7TG7P4XMHH2ZJPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 02:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ONEOK 以 59 亿美元收购 Medallion 和 GIP 在 EnLink 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[Oneok Inc 周三表示，它将收购 Medallion 和 GIP 在 EnLink Midstream 的全部股份，交易价值为 59 亿美元。【原文：Oneok Inc said on Wednesday that it would acquire Medallion and GIP's entire stake in EnLink Midstream in a deal valued at $5.9 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/oneok-buy-medallion-gips-stake-enlink-59-bln-deal-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2NGUMR6Y5OFNBSJ6NNXHXHJME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 02:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各国都在打造自己的人工智能模型，英伟达的芯片需求与日俱增]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高管周三表示，随着生成式人工智能（Generative AI）成为企业和政府的中心工作，各国正在转向使用英伟达（Nvidia）的芯片，用自己的语言构建人工智能模型，从而增加了本已蓬勃发展的需求。【原文：Nations building artificial intelligence models in their own languages are turning to Nvidia's chips, adding to already booming demand as generative AI takes center stage for businesses and governments, a senior executive said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nations-building-their-own-ai-models-add-nvidias-growing-chip-demand-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXTDONCZNVKBNKXL2AJ4XUVR7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 01:35:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀测试前美元保持涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美元走稳，收复了前几个交易日的部分跌幅，交易员们期待着本周末美国的一项关键通胀数据，该数据可能会为美国的利率前景提供进一步的线索。【原文：The dollar steadied on Thursday as it nursed some of its steep losses from previous sessions, with traders looking ahead to a key U.S. inflation reading at the end of the week that could offer further clues on the outlook for rates there.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-holds-gains-ahead-us-inflation-test-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJGTKQZE2RL3VGOTGVCQRU6TGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 01:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁将对美国钢铁厂追加投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大的钢铁制造商新日铁公司周四表示，作为其即将收购美国钢铁公司的一部分，该公司计划向美国钢铁公司的两家钢厂追加约 13 亿美元的投资。【原文：Japan's biggest steelmaker Nippon Steel said on Thursday it plans to make an additional investment of about $1.3 billion in U.S. Steel's two mills as part of its pending acquisition of the U.S. company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steel-make-additional-investment-us-steels-mills-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNTXTORDC5KZNLUHSCAO5S3VYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 01:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国库存减少抵消利比亚供应中断影响，石油价格持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四基本持稳，原因是美国原油库存降幅小于预期，以及对中国需求的持续担忧抵消了利比亚的供应中断。【原文：Oil prices held mostly steady on Thursday as a smaller-than-expected draw in U.S. crude inventories and continued worries over China demand countered supply disruptions out of Libya.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-steady-smaller-than-expected-us-stock-draw-counters-libya-supply-disruption-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULEOCUH4UVNY5JE4K6VLV6AFNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[增长放缓，J.D. Power 将美国电动汽车销量预期下调至 9]]></title><description><![CDATA[咨询公司J.D. Power周三在一份报告中称，今年美国电动汽车（EV）销量预计将仅占市场份额的9%，下调了此前12%的预期。【原文：U.S. electric vehicle (EV) sales are expected to reach just 9% of the market this year, consulting firm J.D. Power said in a report on Wednesday, lowering its previous forecast of 12%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jd-power-cuts-us-ev-sales-forecast-9-growth-slows-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW6AK37D3JKX7BUAWKF472EPDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:34:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SK Hynix 开发出功耗更低的第六代 DRAM 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球第二大内存芯片制造商 SK Hynix 周四表示，该公司已开发出业界首款第六代 10 纳米动态随机存取内存（DRAM）芯片，其功耗比旧款芯片更低。【原文：SK Hynix , world's second-largest memory chip maker, said on Thursday it had developed the industry's first sixth-generation 10-nanometre dynamic random access memory (DRAM) chip with reduced power consumption than older models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sk-hynix-says-it-has-developed-6th-gen-dram-chip-that-uses-less-power-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4OQSC6C6MZIKHKBDWLQ7FPG5KM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示：中国对非洲的贷款七年来首次增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项独立研究周四显示，中国贷款机构去年向非洲批准了价值46.1亿美元的贷款，这是自2016年以来的首次年度增长。【原文：Chinese lenders approved loans worth $4.61 billion to Africa last year, marking the first annual increase since 2016, an independent study showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/chinas-lending-africa-rises-first-time-seven-years-study-shows-2024-08-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HK2FSE2G2VLLPL2SYEVHPVYGEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:14:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西最高法院威胁在周四晚前暂停 X 在该国的使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西最高法院法官亚历山大-德-莫赖斯（Alexandre de Moraes）周三命令亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）在24小时内为其信息平台X在巴西指定一名法律代表，否则将面临该网站在巴西被暂停服务的命运。【原文：Brazilian Supreme Court Justice Alexandre de Moraes ordered billionaire Elon Musk on Wednesday to name a legal representative for his messaging platform X in Brazil within 24 hours or face the site's suspension in the country, a court decision showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazilian-court-suspend-x-brazil-if-musk-does-not-name-new-country-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PZSDBMXV5KNRIKYO4ZCLBEAJU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 23:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储博斯蒂克：现在是降息的 "行动时机"，但要确保万无一失]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周三表示，随着通胀率的进一步下降以及失业率的上升超出了他的预期，现在可能是 "行动起来 "实施降息的时候了，但他希望在扣动扳机之前能够确定这一点。
博斯蒂克说，他希望在美联储 9 月 17-18 日会议之前看到月度就业报告和两份通胀报告确认【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic on Wednesday said that with inflation down farther and the unemployment rate up more than he anticipated, it may be "time to move" on rate cuts, but he wants to be sure before pulling that trigger.
Bostic said he will want to see confirmation from the monthly jobs report and two inflation reports due before the Fed's Sept. 17-18 meeting that】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bostic-it-is-time-move-rate-cuts-wants-be-sure-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXXAANO3ENMGPESFPA6LLSMIQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 23:14:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[有争议的加州人工智能法案获得立法机构通过，正等待州长签署]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州立法者周三通过了一项备受争议的人工智能安全法案，之后还需要进行一次程序投票，其命运才会掌握在州长加文-纽森（Gavin Newsom）手中。【原文：California lawmakers passed a hotly contested artificial-intelligence safety bill on Wednesday, after which it will need one more process vote before its fate is in the hands of Governor Gavin Newsom, who has until Sept. 30 to decide whether to sign it into law or veto it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/contentious-california-ai-bill-passes-legislature-awaits-governors-signature-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6B7XRPDDZICDGTDTC355OKYIQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 23:08:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，7 月份英国汽车产量连续第五个月下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的行业数据显示，受制造商转向新车型和供应链临时中断的影响，英国 7 月份的汽车产量连续第五个月下降。【原文：Britain's car production fell for the fifth consecutive month in July, hurt by manufacturers shifting to new models and temporary disruptions in supply chain, industry data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uk-car-output-drops-fifth-straight-month-july-data-shows-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YRF6ZAR6RJCVBG247UWF3YHLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 23:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，折扣零售商 Big Lots 因销售额下降而酝酿申请破产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周三援引熟悉该计划的人士的话报道，折扣家居用品零售商 Big Lots 正在考虑申请破产，并可能在几周内寻求法院保护。【原文：Discount home goods retailer Big Lots is considering a potential bankruptcy filing and may seek court protection within weeks, Bloomberg reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/discount-retailer-big-lots-mulling-bankruptcy-filing-sales-decline-bloomberg-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OVYXY4YXWZPR7KSH76YLUGTCT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 22:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>