<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:38:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:38:55 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥总统表示墨西哥考虑对中国征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆周四表示，墨西哥政府正在考虑对来自与墨西哥没有贸易协定的国家（包括中国）的进口商品征收关税。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Thursday that her government is considering imposing tariffs on imports from countries that do not have trade agreements with Mexico, including China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/mexico-considering-imposing-tariffs-china-president-says-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GH362KDEKBMIHETAEQMLS2TZTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:19:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国生物柴油和可再生柴油进口量在税收抵免政策调整后出现下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（U.S. Energy Information Administration）周四称，在生物柴油和可再生柴油税收抵免政策生效后，2025 年上半年美国生物柴油和可再生柴油的进口量降至十年来的最低点。【原文：U.S. imports of biodiesel and renewable diesel slumped to a decade low in the first half of 2025 after a change in tax credits for the fuels went into effect, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-biodiesel-renewable-diesel-imports-slump-after-changes-tax-credits-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEYDH4Q2YRND5BX47VDVW4IZFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:15:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就 2022 年野火起诉南加州爱迪生公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周四起诉南加州爱迪生公司，要求该公司就 2022 年的一场野火赔偿损失，该公司将野火归咎于该公司运营的一条下垂的输电线。【原文：The U.S. government sued Southern California Edison on Thursday, seeking damages for a 2022 wildfire it blamed on a sagging power line operated by the utility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-sues-southern-california-edison-over-2022-wildfire-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BX7X6XIIC5IZZOJ4RRASNAQ5PA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:11:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国放弃要求航空公司为航班中断支付赔偿的拜登计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周四表示，将放弃其前任要求航空公司在美国航班中断时向乘客支付现金赔偿的计划。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration said on Thursday it will drop a plan by his predecessor to require airlines to pay passengers cash compensation when U.S. flight disruptions are caused by carriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-drops-biden-plan-require-airlines-pay-compensation-disrupted-flights-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3D3MHW7HT5KAFAG346G6OJY52I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯认为，如果经济表现符合他的预期，将逐步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周四表示，如果明年经济达到他目前预测的失业率小幅上升和通胀趋势走软的目标，那么就有理由在一段时间内逐步降低短期借贷成本。【原文：New York Federal Reserve President John Williams said on Thursday a gradual lowering in short-term borrowing costs is warranted over time if the economy meets his current forecast of modest gains in unemployment and a softening of inflation trends next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-williams-sees-gradual-rate-cuts-if-economy-performs-he-expects-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBRI5QD3JFO5NG3OF6KSCD5X7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司在贸易紧张局势中追随美国的新 "里程碑]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周四表示，将于下周在华盛顿宣布巴西飞机制造商的一个 "里程碑"。【原文：Embraer said on Thursday it would announce what it described as a "milestone" for the Brazilian planemaker in Washington next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-trails-new-us-milestone-amid-trade-tensions-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCVTPVGSYRMXLGFPGJG4H7DOHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:24:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德州仪器标明四月后增长放缓，关税导致增长飙升；不存在与《CHIPS 法案》相关的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国芯片制造商德州仪器（Texas Instruments）周四表示，由于客户在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）所谓的 "解放日"（Liberation Day）关税之前订购，需求在 4 月份激增后有所降温，导致其股价下跌 5%。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Texas Instruments said on Thursday demand cooled after a spike in April as customers ordered ahead of President Donald Trump's so-called "Liberation Day" tariffs, sending its shares down 5%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/texas-instruments-flags-post-april-slowdown-after-tariff-driven-spike-no-chips-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIN5EFVZANPIVANITZ7ONFACDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西淡水河谷重开关键矿山，计划在米纳斯吉拉斯州投资 120 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷周四表示，到2030年，该公司将向米纳斯吉拉斯州的采矿业务投资670亿雷亚尔（123.6亿美元）。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale said on Thursday it will invest 67 billion reais ($12.36 billion) in its mining operations in Minas Gerais state by 2030, as it held a ceremony to mark the reopening of a key mine in the city of Ouro Preto.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/brazils-vale-reopens-key-mine-plans-invest-12-billion-minas-gerais-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKJ2MYRUHRKLFOK6NHUSXAY4VA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:59:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：美国陡峭的收益率曲线对银行和经济意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国债收益率曲线是衡量经济状况的重要晴雨表，由于人们担心公共债务不断增加、唐纳德-特朗普总统试图对美联储施加控制以及他的激进关税政策，美国国债收益率曲线已经变得陡峭。【原文：The U.S. Treasury yield curve, a crucial barometer of how the economy is doing, has steepened on fears of mounting public debt, President Donald Trump's attempts to exert control over the Federal Reserve and his aggressive tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/what-does-steep-us-yield-curve-mean-banks-economy-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPTK5RDFQRIBDMHXC7O3P6OLK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，美国联邦贸易委员会准备就对儿童的影响问题对人工智能公司进行质询]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国联邦贸易委员会计划研究人工智能聊天机器人对儿童心理健康的影响，并要求科技公司提供相关文件。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission plans to study the impact of artificial intelligence chatbots on children's mental health and request documents from tech companies, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ftc-prepares-grill-ai-companies-over-impact-children-wsj-reports-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPICBLAAZBKRJITBVQOIKT7UCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理阿尔巴内斯与特朗普就重要矿产和安全问题进行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞的办公室称，澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞周四晚间在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普通电话时讨论了澳美两国在关键矿产方面的合作机会。【原文：Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese discussed opportunities for Australia and the United States to cooperate on critical minerals in a phone call with President Donald Trump on Thursday evening, his office said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-pm-albanese-spoke-trump-about-critical-minerals-security-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSGL34QAJFPTVG7RXLDUVSCNTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关税紧张局势下，印度制药出口的目光不再局限于美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府支持的一个贸易机构的官员周四告诉路透社，印度正在寻求加强对非洲、拉丁美洲和东南亚半管制市场的药品出口，以减少对美国的依赖，因为美国的关税问题会带来风险。【原文：India is seeking to boost drug exports to semi-regulated markets in Africa, Latin America and Southeast Asia to reduce its dependence on the U.S., where tariff concerns pose risks, officials from a government-backed trade body told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/india-looking-beyond-us-pharma-exports-amid-tariff-tensions-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXNMDZCV3RMABD45L7ZFB34G5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫官员称特朗普就俄罗斯石油采购问题向欧洲领导人施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四告诉欧洲领导人，欧洲必须停止购买俄罗斯石油，他说俄罗斯石油正在帮助莫斯科为其对乌克兰的战争提供资金。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump told European leaders on Thursday that Europe must stop purchasing Russian oil that he said is helping Moscow fund its war against Ukraine, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-put-pressure-european-leaders-over-russian-oil-purchases-white-house-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIAF433QZVN6TMMQ6XRH53Q2K4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，作为对美联储理事丽莎-库克调查的一部分，司法部发出传票]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引熟悉此事的官员的话报道，美国司法部已对美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）展开刑事调查，并发出传票，作为调查她是否在抵押贷款申请中提交欺诈信息的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department has opened a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook, issuing subpoenas as part of an inquiry into whether she submitted fraudulent information on mortgage applications, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing officials familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/doj-issues-subpoenas-part-probe-into-fed-governor-lisa-cook-wsj-reports-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKOSCZCIHZPUZBE65OOPEINDCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:22:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯雷融资 200 亿美元收购二手私募股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯雷投资集团（Carlyle Group）周四表示，该公司已融资 200 亿美元，用于从投资者手中购买二手私募股权，这些投资者希望卸下在上市和收购交易低迷时期积累的资产。【原文：Carlyle Group said on Thursday it had raised $20 billion to buy second-hand private equity stakes from investors looking to offload assets that built up during a downturn in public listings and acquisition deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyle-raises-20-billion-buy-second-hand-private-equity-stakes-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUIEJC7BTNOX5BE37ZE4D4RM6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[T-Mobile 预计 UScellular 交易将为第三季度带来 4 亿美元的服务收入增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[T-Mobile 周四表示，随着这家美国无线运营商整合最近收购的地区性竞争对手 UScellular 的客户，预计本季度的服务收入将增加约 4 亿美元。【原文：T-Mobile said on Thursday it expects to generate about $400 million more in service revenue this quarter as the U.S. wireless carrier integrates customers of the recently acquired regional rival UScellular.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/t-mobile-expects-400-million-service-revenue-boost-q3-uscellular-deal-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZG6GTX4RJOOTFTXL2AACGSRHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月服务业恢复增长；就业疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国服务业活动在 8 月份有所回升，但由于劳动力市场状况有所缓解，就业依然低迷。【原文：U.S. services sector activity picked up in August, but employment remained subdued as labor market conditions ease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-service-sector-regains-speed-august-employment-weak-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7OL4SHCIJIYZMHVGOZ4OIIC5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乔治-阿玛尼之后，继承人和基金会掌舵时尚帝国]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利设计师乔治-阿玛尼（Giorgio Armani）创立了世界上最著名的时装公司之一，他的去世不可避免地引发了人们对这家他珍视独立的公司未来的疑问。【原文：Italian designer Giorgio Armani established one of the world's most famous fashion businesses, his death inevitably raises questions about the future of a company whose independence he cherished.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/after-giorgio-armani-heirs-foundation-steer-fashion-empire-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2W6RW2KRN5MLFHOK35CCHMCYHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储：迄今为止，人工智能对就业市场影响不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储纽约地区联储银行周四在一篇博客中说，到目前为止，美联储纽约地区企业对人工智能技术的采用率不断上升，但并没有对就业造成太大影响。【原文：Rising adoption of artificial intelligence technology by firms in the Federal Reserve's New York district has not been much of a job-killer so far, the regional Fed bank said in a blog on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-not-affecting-job-market-much-so-far-new-york-fed-says-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMARTTZ6ANOPZJI3JFW2FS3EMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gap 将于今秋推出美容和个人护理产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gap 周四表示，今年秋季将进军快速增长的美容和个人护理领域，其中包括以 Old Navy 品牌销售的一些产品。【原文：Gap said on Thursday it would expand into the fast-growing beauty and personal care segment this fall season, including some sold under the Old Navy brand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gap-offer-beauty-personal-care-products-this-fall-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZRFKTLANVLMBKQIQM2HNJYDOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:57:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Orsted 的 Revolution Wind 公司就项目停工问题起诉特朗普政府]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份法庭文件显示，丹麦风电场开发商 Orsted 的 Revolution Wind 合资企业已就美国政府阻止在罗德岛附近建造该项目的决定对唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府提起诉讼。【原文：Danish wind farm developer Orsted's Revolution Wind joint venture has filed a lawsuit against the administration of President Donald Trump over the U.S. government's decision to block construction of the project off Rhode Island, a court filing showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/orsteds-revolution-wind-sues-trump-administration-over-project-halt-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2PU2FHEU5J2ZE3KE4PJOBA3U4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:47:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月贸易逆差因进口飙升而扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于创纪录的资本和其他商品的流入推动了进口，美国 7 月份的贸易赤字急剧扩大。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit widened sharply in July as record inflows of capital and other goods boosted imports, a trend that if sustained could see trade subtracting from gross domestic product in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-trade-deficit-widens-july-soaring-imports-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CP6NH7MRGVLQJGEXA3UPHPHO5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:46:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会公布改革加密货币规则和放宽华尔街规则的议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周四公布了其未来几个月的规则制定议程，其中可能包括修改加密货币法规和减少华尔街谴责的过于繁琐的规则的广泛建议。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Thursday unveiled its rulemaking agenda for the upcoming months, which could see broad proposals to revamp cryptocurrency regulations and reduce rules that Wall Street has decried as being overly burdensome.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-sec-unveils-agenda-revamp-crypto-rules-ease-wall-street-rules-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L64WF7O3CFM6FA5XATS77JYPZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团向贝莱德转移 800 亿美元资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周四表示，将把 800 亿美元的资产从其财富管理部门转移到贝莱德公司（BlackRock Inc）。【原文：Citigroup will transfer $80 billion in assets from its wealth management unit to BlackRock Inc , the bank said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/citigroup-transfers-80-billion-assets-blackrock-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMGB7BV3ZJKURASRQAO5QGPRNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:26:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国小盘股爆发，但能持续多久？]]></title><description><![CDATA[长期落后的美国小盘股正迎来阳光灿烂的时刻，但利率前景、盈利实力和经济健康状况将有助于确定它们是迎来了新的曙光，还是又一个错误的开始。【原文：Long-lagging U.S. small-cap stocks are having a moment in the sun, but the interest rate outlook, the strength of their earnings and the health of the economy will help determine whether they are experiencing a new dawn or another false start.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-small-cap-stocks-break-out-how-long-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFGKZM3JYBOEFGSBBOCV5CVIKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:19:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利时装设计师乔治-阿玛尼去世]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利时装设计师乔治-阿玛尼（Giorgio Armani）公司周四表示，乔治-阿玛尼已经去世。【原文：Italian fashion designer Giorgio Armani has died, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/italian-fashion-designer-giorgio-armani-has-died-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DZFLQ7SCBOBJJPJSPNB7EUQSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:18:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Atlassian 6.1 亿美元收购浏览器公司，押注人工智能浏览器]]></title><description><![CDATA[Atlassian 周四表示，将以 6.1 亿美元现金收购总部位于纽约的初创公司 The Browser Company，进军快速拥挤的人工智能驱动型浏览器市场。【原文：Atlassian said on Thursday it will acquire New York-based startup The Browser Company for $610 million in cash, moving into the fast‑crowding market for AI‑driven browsers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/atlassian-bets-ai-browsers-with-610-million-deal-browser-company-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DY5XLQXCHRJQHPW4GQFW7ER4VA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:13:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第二季度工人生产率大幅提高]]></title><description><![CDATA[第二季度美国工人生产率的增长速度超过了最初的预期，从而抑制了劳动力成本的上升。【原文：U.S. worker productivity grew faster than initially thought in the second quarter, curbing the rise in labor costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-second-quarter-worker-productivity-revised-sharply-higher-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4KC7GCHDFKTNAF5ENNFYGMI5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 12:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数上升，劳动力市场趋于缓和]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，新申请失业救济金的美国人数量增幅超过预期，这与劳动力市场状况疲软一致。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for jobless benefits increased more than expected last week, consistent with softening labor market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-weekly-jobless-claims-rise-labor-market-eases-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3MQ4TNQ4RJHLKKHTXOK436T3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 12:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼泊尔封杀包括 Facebook 在内的部分社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼泊尔周四表示，由于包括 Facebook 在内的多个社交媒体平台未能在当局打击滥用行为的行动中进行登记，该国将阻止这些平台的访问。【原文：Nepal said on Thursday it would block access to several social media platforms, including Facebook, after they failed to register with authorities in a crackdown on misuse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/nepal-block-some-social-media-including-facebook-2025-09-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIDHE7JTSNNCVCNYKDNGZEHOJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 12:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>