<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 18:04:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 18:04:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：在美国禁令的不确定性下，TikTok 母公司字节跳动的估值达到 3000 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周六报道，TikTok 的中国母公司字节跳动（ByteDance）在最近提出回购要约后，对自身的估值约为 3000 亿美元。【原文：TikTok's Chinese parent company ByteDance is valuing itself at about $300 billion after a recent buyback offer, the Wall Street Journal reported on Saturday, even as the tech giant's popular TikTok app faces the prospect of a looming ban in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-parent-bytedances-valuation-hits-300-billion-amid-us-ban-uncertainty-wsj-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HB27VFBNLROFTLKLB5IY7ESGMI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 16:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱迪生公司首席执行官称，美国公用事业公司希望特朗普和共和党人拯救通胀法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱迪生国际公司（Edison International）首席执行官佩德罗-皮萨罗（Pedro Pizarro）周六表示，美国公用事业行业希望即将上任的特朗普政府和共和党领导的国会保留《通货膨胀削减法案》中的清洁能源和电动汽车税收减免政策。【原文：The U.S. utility industry wants the incoming Trump administration and Republican-led Congress to preserve clean energy and EV tax credits in the Inflation Reduction Act, Pedro Pizarro, the CEO of utility Edison International said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-utilities-want-trump-republicans-save-inflation-act-edison-ceo-says-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCWKFVK4QROBLGKLIL5KGP2SII</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 13:51:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其因亚马逊 Twitch 数据泄露事件罚款 200 万里拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[据土耳其官方通讯社（Anadolu Agency）周六报道，土耳其个人数据保护委员会（KVKK）对亚马逊网站旗下游戏平台 Twitch 的数据泄露事件处以 200 万里拉（约合 5.8 万美元）的罚款。【原文：Turkey's Personal Data Protection Board (KVKK) has fined Amazon.com's gaming platform Twitch 2 million lira ($58,000) over a data breach, the official Anadolu Agency reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/turkey-fines-amazons-twitch-2-mln-lira-data-breach-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SB5FKINQNOYXM5Y33IZ5KYKRM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 10:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OMV 称已停止从俄罗斯供应天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥地利能源公司 OMV 称，来自俄罗斯的天然气供应已于周六早上 6 点（格林尼治标准时间 5 点）结束，但监管机构称，尽管进入奥地利的天然气流量有所下降，但对客户的供应是稳定的。【原文：Austrian energy company OMV said gas deliveries from Russia had ended at 6 a.m. (0500 GMT) on Saturday, but the regulator said supplies to customers were stable despite a drop in flows into Austria.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/omv-says-its-gas-deliveries-russia-have-stopped-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7CHOTF4B5LJPGD6UPJE2E6CZU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 10:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普助手称，英国应在贸易问题上与美国保持一致，而不是追求欧盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的一位高级经济顾问表示，英国应在贸易方面与美国保持一致，而不是寻求与欧盟建立更紧密的关系。【原文：A senior economic adviser to U.S. President-elect Donald Trump has said Britain should align itself with the United States on trade rather than pursue closer ties with the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/britain-should-align-with-us-trade-rather-than-pursue-eu-says-trump-aide-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPHSWO4ZBZITTCKX74S5CK2HVU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 09:18:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国气候主管要求二十国集团（G20）领导人助其一臂之力，因为融资谈判进展缓慢]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国气候主管周六呼吁全球最大经济体的领导人在下周于里约热内卢举行会议时发出支持全球气候融资努力的信号。【原文：The U.N.'s climate chief called on leaders of the world's biggest economies on Saturday to send a signal of support for global climate finance efforts when they meet in Rio de Janeiro next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/un-climate-chief-asks-g20-leaders-boost-finance-talks-lag-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FB4VXP5C5MN3MA7IVBWZ57PVM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 09:14:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管奥地利削减天然气出口，但俄罗斯通过乌克兰向欧洲的天然气出口保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯天然气生产商俄罗斯天然气工业股份公司（Gazprom）表示，尽管预计对奥地利的天然气供应将因合同纠纷而削减，但该公司周六将通过乌克兰向欧洲输送 4240 万立方米天然气，与周五的输送量持平。【原文：Russian gas producer Gazprom said it would send 42.4 million cubic metres of gas to Europe via Ukraine on Saturday, the same volume as on Friday, despite expectations of gas supplies cuts to Austria over a contractual dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russian-gas-exports-via-ukraine-europe-stable-despite-austria-cuts-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWQYXE5SCNM6ZGMSATSBBCS2E4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 08:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称 Archegos 公司的 Bill Hwang 应被判处 21 年监禁]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦检察官周五表示，Archegos Capital Management 的创始人 Bill Hwang 应在监狱服刑 21 年，因为他实施了一项市场操纵计划，导致其价值 360 亿美元的公司破产，并使其贷款人损失了 100 多亿美元。【原文：Bill Hwang, the founder of Archegos Capital Management, should spend 21 years in prison for running a market manipulation scheme that wiped out his $36 billion firm and cost its lenders more than $10 billion, federal prosecutors said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/archegos-bill-hwang-deserves-21-years-prison-us-says-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MU7IFDTW2VJIPFLGU4EXCQ4AAA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 04:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 称美国数以千计的用户无法使用 Netflix]]></title><description><![CDATA[据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 称，周五晚些时候，美国有数千名用户的 Netflix 出现故障。【原文：Netflix was down for thousands of users in the U.S. late on Friday, according outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-down-thousands-users-us-downdetector-says-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TRVQ72CSFOBXMVBHVO7LVD6DQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 02:28:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，T-Mobile 在中国大规模电信网络入侵事件中遭到黑客攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，T-Mobile 的网络是在一次破坏性的中国网络间谍行动中被黑客入侵的系统之一，这次行动进入了多家美国和国际电信公司。【原文：T-Mobile's network was among the systems hacked in a damaging Chinese cyber-espionage operation that gained entry into multiple U.S. and international telecommunications companies, The Wall Street Journal reported on Friday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/t-mobile-hacked-massive-chinese-breach-telecom-networks-wsj-reports-2024-11-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INYI5ZXSV5LEHHX7Y7XRICJ3OI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:21:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉下调精神航空长期信用评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周五将美国精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）的长期信用评级从 "CCC "下调至 "CC"，使其低于北美同类低成本航空公司的评级，并警告称该公司近期可能出现违约。【原文：Fitch Ratings on Friday downgraded the long-term credit rating of Spirit Airlines to 'CC' from 'CCC', bringing it below the low-cost carrier's North America peers and warning that a near-term default appears probable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-downgrades-spirit-airlines-long-term-credit-rating-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55PG43E6GBKWXJ4LTUYM3DARSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 23:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普传媒大股东出售几乎全部股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普媒体与科技集团的主要股东 ARC Global Investments 在周四提交的一份监管文件中称，该公司已将其持有的媒体公司股份几乎全部出售。【原文：Trump Media &amp; Technology Group's key shareholder, ARC Global Investments, has unloaded nearly all its stake in the media company, it said in a regulatory filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/major-trump-media-shareholder-sells-nearly-entire-stake-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4U4TEVMTRJJCHIFIJGGQCC4TE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 22:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的政治上位激起了 X 银行的救赎希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，华尔街的一些银行希望很快就能卸下这位亿万富翁收购社交媒体平台 X 的 130 亿美元债务。【原文：Some Wall Street banks are hoping they may soon be able to offload $13 billion of debt that backed the billionaire's purchase of the social media platform X, sources say】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/musks-political-ascendancy-stirs-hopes-redemption-x-banks-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOD6IYSNBJLAVCBAHUURJ4ME4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 22:24:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intrum 在美国申请破产重组 45 亿美元债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的收债公司 Intrum 周五表示，它已在美国申请破产保护，以重组其债务。【原文：Intrum , Europe's biggest debt collector, on Friday said it had filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in the United States in a bid to restructure its debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/intrum-files-bankruptcy-us-restructure-45-billion-debt-pile-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRTIQCVBOJKERK7SB6F7LGX5IE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 21:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提高效率后，美国国防股和政府承包商下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，国防公司和政府承包商股价走低，延续了近期的跌势，原因是当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提议成立的政府效率部存在不确定性。【原文：Shares of defense companies and government contractors were lower on Friday, extending recent losses amid uncertainty surrounding President-elect Donald Trump's proposed Department of Government Efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-defense-shares-government-contractors-fall-after-trump-efficiency-picks-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6V7HYTFCTFOLRI2W3GY6HPYC5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 21:20:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[千禧年、Capula、Tudor 将比特币 ETF 纳入投资组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[证券文件显示，包括千禧管理公司（Millennium Management）、卡普拉管理公司（Capula Management）和帝舵投资公司（Tudor Investment）在内的对冲基金在第三季度增加了对美国现货比特币交易所交易基金的投资，因为一种流行的选举驱动套利交易正在增加。【原文：Hedge funds including Millennium Management, Capula Management and Tudor Investment increased their exposure to U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds in the third quarter, securities filings showed, as a popular election-driven arbitrage trade ramped up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/millennium-capula-tudor-pile-bitcoin-etfs-into-portfolios-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JRG7DSAT7ZKZVFPOEBAJLXX25A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 20:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游说团体要求特朗普全面修订投资规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封信，一个行业组织要求即将上任的特朗普政府考虑更新美国证券交易委员会对投资公司监管框架的 "全面计划"。【原文：A trade group has asked the incoming Trump administration to consider a "comprehensive plan" for updating the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's regulatory framework for investment companies, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/lobby-group-asks-trump-investment-rules-overhaul-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWQP2CT7B5IMZBFFYZSVRNCVDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 19:50:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比认为到 2025 年底将再降息 125 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，他认为美国央行很可能会像美联储决策者在 9 月份预测的那样，在今年将政策利率再下调四分之一个百分点，并在明年再下调整整一个百分点。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago President Austan Goolsbee on Friday signaled he feels the U.S. central bank will likely end up cutting the policy rate by another quarter of a percentage point this year and a full percentage point further next year, as Fed policymakers projected in September .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-sees-another-125-bps-rate-cuts-by-end-2025-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CS3QUD3WYNPL7NETWTN42QQY5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 19:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 英伟达业绩受关注，股市受大选提振停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司（Nvidia Corp）下周的财报可能会指引美国股市的下一步走势，因为在大选推动的涨势停滞之后，投资者将目光转向了科技行业和人工智能交易。【原文：Nvidia Corp's results in the coming week could guide the U.S. stock market on its next path, as investors turn their focus to the technology sector and artificial intelligence trade after an election-fueled rally stalled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-nvidia-results-focus-stock-markets-election-boost-stalls-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZKIPTUDYVIATJFX7P2AJA64DE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 18:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车公司和电池制造商敦促特朗普不要取消汽车税收减免政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表主要电动汽车和电池制造商的一个团体周五敦促当选总统唐纳德-特朗普不要取消电动汽车销售和生产的税收减免，理由是这将对投票支持共和党的主要州产生影响。【原文：A group representing major electric vehicle and battery manufacturers on Friday urged President-elect Donald Trump not to kill tax credits for electric vehicle sales and production, citing the impact on key states that voted for the Republican.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-companies-battery-makers-urge-trump-not-kill-vehicle-tax-credits-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IC4J2MO6WFJ5VHGKRCZQIB3X7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 18:17:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在亚马逊和 SpaceX 案件中，美国劳工委员会的权力岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会的执法权力在一系列诉讼中受到挑战，该委员会将在美国一家保守的上诉法院为自己辩护，以抵御埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）和亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）的攻击。【原文：A U.S. labor board whose enforcement powers are being challenged in a series of lawsuits is set to defend itself from attacks by Elon Musk's SpaceX and Amazon.com in a conservative U.S. appeals court, as the agency also braces for a potential overhaul under President-elect Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/amazon-spacex-will-test-us-labor-boards-powers-conservative-appeals-court-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCVWJUFMJ5JDLCUZJF67RN4LGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音任命前先锋集团首席执行官巴克利为董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国波音公司周五表示，波音董事会已选举前 Vanguard 集团首席执行官蒂姆-巴克利（Tim Buckley）为其最新成员，自 1 月 1 日起生效。【原文：Boeing board has elected former Vanguard Group CEO Tim Buckley as its newest member, effective Jan. 1, the U.S. planemaker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-names-ex-vanguard-ceo-buckley-board-member-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBG3XOLHRNJXJCJCXWS2T3ACBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FanDuel 与 MLB 工会就使用球员肖像的诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国职业棒球大联盟（Major League Baseball）球员工会就一起诉讼达成和解，该诉讼指控体育博彩巨头 FanDuel 未经许可在其博彩平台上使用数百名 MLB 球员的姓名和肖像。【原文：Major League Baseball's players union settled a lawsuit that accused sports betting giant FanDuel of using the names and likenesses of hundreds of MLB players on its betting platform without permission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/fanduel-settles-mlb-union-lawsuit-over-use-player-likenesses-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GI2YQP335NJ3JC4JLKKP3AJS6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强劲的美国数据继续重塑美联储对降息步伐和幅度的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，强劲的美国经济和通胀数据继续重塑美联储决策者关于降息步伐和幅度的争论，投资者进一步下调了对央行在12月会议上降息的预期。【原文：Strong U.S. economic and inflation data on Friday continued reshaping the debate among Federal Reserve policymakers over the pace and extent of interest rate cuts as investors further downgraded their expectations for a rate reduction at the central bank's December meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/strong-us-data-continues-reshaping-fed-views-pace-extent-rate-cuts-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPUP4ULLNZNHFDJSFRHCNQIVUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯在彭博电视上表示不排除 12 月降息的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周五表示，她希望看到更多数据，然后再决定央行是否应在下个月的政策会议上再次降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said Friday she wants to see more data before deciding whether the central bank should cut rates again at its policy meeting next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-collins-wont-rule-out-december-rate-cut-bloomberg-tv-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3O5OU6DOJJODFFH5K56BPCMJWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:26:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃利奥特的 50 亿美元霍尼韦尔赌局：分拆是否会成功？]]></title><description><![CDATA[长期以来，多元化企业集团一直是美国股市的一大特色，3M、通用电气（General Electric）、联合技术（United Technologies）等大公司为道琼斯工业指数（Dow industrials）提供了支撑。但其中许多公司后来分崩离析，其分拆公司的股价也一路飙升。【原文：Diversified conglomerates were long a fixture of the U.S. stock market landscape, with the Dow industrials bolstered by big names such as 3M, General Electric, United Technologies and others. But many of those companies have since broken apart, and shares of their spinoffs have surged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/elliotts-5-billion-honeywell-gambit-would-split-pay-off-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5AWT7JYXBK6RMPK6UCORJJMCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:22:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新闻机构称苹果公司从俄罗斯应用程序商店删除了美国资助的 RFE/RL 新闻应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[自由欧洲电台/自由电台周五表示，应俄罗斯国家通信监管机构Roskomnadzor的要求，苹果公司已从俄罗斯应用商店删除了自由欧洲电台/自由电台的一款俄语新闻应用程序。【原文：Apple has deleted one of U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty's Russian-language news apps from the Russian App Store at the request of state communications regulator Roskomnadzor, the news outlet said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-deletes-us-funded-rferl-news-app-russian-app-store-news-outlet-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2Y52T7KAVJLDNLKJ7MWA2TI3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克扩大对 OpenAI 的诉讼范围，增加微软和反垄断指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁企业家埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）扩大了对聊天软件制造商 OpenAI 的诉讼范围，增加了联邦反垄断和其他索赔，并将 OpenAI 最大的财政支持者微软公司列为被告。【原文：Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk expanded his lawsuit against ChatGPT maker OpenAI, adding federal antitrust and other claims and adding OpenAI's largest financial backer Microsoft as a defendant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/musk-expands-lawsuit-against-openai-adding-microsoft-antitrust-claims-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUFFOZKH6JMMDASLJWXMH5Q27Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir计划登陆纳斯达克，股价再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[Palantir Technologies Inc 周四晚些时候宣布将在纳斯达克上市，并有望获得加入纳斯达克 100 指数的资格，该公司股价周五上涨超过 6%，创下历史新高。【原文：Shares in Palantir Technologies Inc were up more than 6% on Friday, hitting a record high, after it announced late on Thursday that it would list on the Nasdaq and expects eligibility to join the Nasdaq 100 index .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/palantir-shares-rally-fresh-record-plans-move-nasdaq-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWR3NDDR3ZIVPI7MQQIZBMFASQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 15:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[曼哈顿美国检察官称将缩减加密货币案件数量]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高级检察官周五表示，在包括 FTX 创始人山姆-班克曼-弗里德（Sam Bankman-Fried）在内的几起重大定罪之后，曼哈顿的美国检察官办公室将减少用于监管加密货币犯罪的资源。【原文：The U.S. Attorney's Office in Manhattan will devote fewer resources to policing cryptocurrency crimes after securing several major convictions, including that of FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried, a senior prosecutor said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/manhattan-us-attorney-scale-back-crypto-cases-prosecutor-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIQ262AEBNKDTLDFT44UZTFM4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 15:45:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>