<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 01:39:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 01:39:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[默多克的新闻集团进军西部，推出《加州邮报》]]></title><description><![CDATA[《加州邮报》本周正式创刊，这是鲁珀特·默多克旗下新闻集团出版的保守派日报，以纸质版和网络版形式发行，标志着《纽约邮报》向西海岸媒体版图的扩张。【原文：The California Post, a conservative daily tabloid published by Rupert Murdoch's News Corp in print and online, made its debut this week, marking the New York Post’s expansion into the West Coast media landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/murdochs-news-corp-goes-west-with-launch-california-post-2026-01-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2LBMNTBVVICPCXEEMHTP7MS2A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 01:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻报道，Bumble、Match、Panera Bread和CrunchBase遭遇网络攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周三援引受影响公司发言人的消息报道称，Bumble、Match Group和CrunchBase遭遇了网络攻击。【原文：Bumble , Match Group , and CrunchBase were hit by cyberattacks, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing spokespersons of the impacted companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bumble-match-panera-bread-crunchbase-hit-by-cyberattacks-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYDTXIPLMFPQ7GVVVBGV67RWPU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌破坏大型住宅代理网络，使运营商使用的设备减少"数百万台"]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌周三表示，已采取行动移除全球最大住宅代理网络之一IPIDEA的域名，旨在保护数百万消费者设备免遭网络犯罪分子和国家支持的黑客利用。【原文：Google said on Wednesday it has taken action to remove domains belonging to one of the largest residential proxy networks in the world, called IPIDEA, in an effort to protect millions of consumer devices from being exploited by cybercriminals and state-sponsored hackers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-disrupts-large-residential-proxy-network-reducing-devices-used-by-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXIDIXGZLRMI5BTTITS2QBEBFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:51:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席鲍威尔新闻发布会关键引语]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔周三花了45分钟回答记者提问，解释了美国央行在白宫施加巨大降息压力下仍决定维持短期借贷成本不变的决定。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell spent 45 minutes on Wednesday answering reporter questions about the U.S. central bank's decision to keep short-term borrowing costs unchanged despite tremendous pressure from the White House to cut them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/key-quotes-fed-chair-powells-news-conference-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIYCG76IRJM3ZGOI4WQ46CV5UU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:51:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉斯维加斯金沙集团季度利润因澳门需求强劲而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉斯维加斯金沙集团周三公布，受澳门业务强劲需求推动，其第四季度利润实现增长。【原文：Las Vegas Sands on Wednesday reported a rise in ​fourth-quarter profit on strong demand ‌from its Macau operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/las-vegas-sands-quarterly-profit-rises-strong-macau-demand-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QFKLTMQ7LRL5XLPLGW2G3HMOVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:51:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星利润翻三倍创历史新高，人工智能热潮加剧芯片短缺]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子表示，其第四季度营业利润增长逾三倍，创下历史新高。人工智能建设竞赛加剧了芯片短缺，导致价格飙升。【原文：Samsung Electronics said its operating profit more than tripled to a record high in the fourth quarter, as the race to build artificial intelligence exacerbated a chip shortage and sent prices surging.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-profit-triples-record-high-ai-boom-exacerbates-chip-shortage-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BD7JMRRNGZJELITO6WLT3MQ3RU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称美国放弃关键矿产价格下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[多位消息人士向路透社透露，特朗普政府正逐步放弃为美国关键矿产项目设定最低价格保障的计划，这实际上承认了国会资金短缺以及制定市场定价机制的复杂性。【原文：The Trump administration is stepping back from plans to guarantee a minimum price for U.S. critical minerals projects, a tacit acknowledgment of a lack of congressional funding and the complexity of setting market pricing, multiple sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-moves-away-critical-mineral-price-floors-sources-say-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HWF2PAYCB5L27KW3NMEVRU2IQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:45:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗预计油价将维持高位，尽管存在供应过剩风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗周三表示，尽管市场年初预期将出现大量供应过剩，但受地缘政治风险上升、美国限制购买俄罗斯石油以及中国持续采购等因素影响，油价可能维持高位。【原文：Citi said on Wednesday that oil prices may stay elevated due to rising geopolitical risks, U.S. restrictions on Russian oil purchases and continued Chinese buying, even as markets entered the year expecting a large oversupply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/citi-expects-oil-prices-stay-elevated-despite-oversupply-risks-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUX6VP57VVIE5JPZLUXVKES6BI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：议员称英伟达曾协助DeepSeek完善人工智能模型，该模型后被中国军队使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国芯片制造商英伟达曾协助中国企业深思求助公司优化人工智能模型，这些模型后来被中国军队使用。美国众议院一个委员会的主席在周三被路透社看到的信函中表示。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Nvidia helped China's DeepSeek hone artificial intelligence models that were later used by the Chinese military, the chairman of a U.S. House of Representatives committee said in a letter seen by Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-helped-deepseek-hone-ai-models-later-used-by-chinas-military-lawmaker-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GPK4H5DHBNEJIHWSDHRWDRGFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:19:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lam Research预测芯片制造设备需求将推动季度业绩强劲增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉姆研究公司周三预测第三季度营收将超出华尔街预期，因企业对其芯片制造设备的订单量持续攀升。【原文：Lam Research forecast third-quarter revenue above Wall Street expectations on Wednesday, as enterprises ramped up orders of its chipmaking tools.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lam-research-forecasts-strong-quarterly-results-chipmaking-tool-demand-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWQVQH7HUFOLTL3MUYQKHWHTUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:18:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 美联储几乎与市场动荡无关]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三美元汇率急剧攀升，华尔街股市震荡波动。此前，在美联储维持利率不变并警示通胀风险上升后，标普500指数首次突破7000点大关。【原文：The dollar snapped higher and Wall Street wobbled on Wednesday, but not before the S&amp;P 500 broke above 7,000 points for the first time, after the Federal Reserve kept interest rates on hold and flagged rising inflation risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3P7IYBODRJMNL6SCSTB76L2IM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金价延续创纪录涨势，突破每盎司5400美元大关]]></title><description><![CDATA[现货黄金周四延续创纪录涨势，突破每盎司5400美元大关，因投资者在经济与地缘政治不确定性加剧之际寻求避险资产。【原文：Spot gold extended its record‑setting rally on Thursday, marching above the $5,400 per ounce mark as investors sought safety amid deepening economic and geopolitical uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/gold-extends-record-run-races-past-5400oz-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q77SFXCPMROGBN75XKJIJPCKQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，黑石旗下规模最大的对冲基金业务在2025年实现了12%的回报率。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周三透露，黑石旗下规模最大的对冲基金平台——绝对回报组合基金（AR）去年收益率接近12%，超越基准HFRX全球对冲基金指数7.1%的涨幅。【原文：Blackstone's biggest hedge fund platform, Absolute Return Composite (AR), returned nearly 12% last ​year, beating the benchmark HFRX Global Hedge Fund Index's 7.1% gain, two ‌people familiar with the numbers said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackstones-biggest-hedge-fund-business-returned-12-2025-sources-say-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDBR7UAH3BIA3KVXSNYRUOA62A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得宝将在其亚特兰大门店支持中心裁减800个企业岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[家得宝周三宣布，将裁减其亚特兰大门店支持中心800个岗位，并要求公司员工每周五天返回办公室工作。【原文：Home Depot said on Wednesday it is cutting 800 jobs associated with its Atlanta store support center, and is calling on its corporate employees to return to the office five days a week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/home-depot-cut-800-corporate-jobs-its-atlanta-store-support-center-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEGF6NHRWJJ5JHL5NZ7U4MXQCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空2026年盈利预期超出市场预期，因业务重组成效渐显]]></title><description><![CDATA[西南航空周三预测2026年盈利将超出预期，并表示尽管上周末席卷美国的冬季风暴造成运营中断，但今年开局稳健，其业务重组已初见成效。【原文：Southwest Airlines on Wednesday forecast a stronger-than-expected profit in 2026 and signaled a solid start to the year despite disruptions from the winter storm that swept the U.S. last weekend, saying its overhaul is beginning to gain traction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/southwest-forecasts-2026-profit-above-estimates-overhaul-gains-traction-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5HRIBZGC7RKC7ER6SKZXATJ74U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威主权财富基金持有的美国国债在2025年下半年有所增加。]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威2.2万亿美元主权财富基金持有的美国国债价值在2025年下半年持续增长，延续了长期趋势，该基金周三公布的数据显示。【原文：The value of U.S. Treasuries held by Norway's $2.2 trillion sovereign wealth fund increased during the second half of 2025, continuing a long-term trend, fund data showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/norway-wealth-funds-us-treasuries-holding-rose-second-half-2025-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRSMS53OIRJVHLRO7UG4HVAJTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:24:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[李维斯季度业绩超预期，得益于强劲的牛仔需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[李维斯周三公布的第四季度销售额和利润超出华尔街预期，尽管面临美国提高进口关税的压力以及国内消费支出疲软，但其牛仔裤的强劲需求仍支撑了业绩。【原文：Levi Strauss beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter sales and profit on Wednesday, buoyed by ​strong demand for its denim jeans despite pressure from higher U.S. import ‌tariffs and dampened consumer spending in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-beats-quarterly-results-estimates-strong-denim-demand-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZKZT63IT5MURJXKBJMKJOOJRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，自2019年与委内瑞拉母公司断绝关系以来，雪佛龙旗下Citgo公司首次购入委内瑞拉原油货运]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周三向路透社透露，美国炼油商雪佛龙石油公司（Citgo Petroleum）自2019年初与母公司委内瑞拉国家石油公司（Petroleos de Venezuela SA）断绝关系以来，首次购入委内瑞拉原油。【原文：U.S. refiner Citgo Petroleum has bought Venezuelan crude oil for the first time since it severed ties with its parent, state-run oil firm Petroleos de Venezuela SA, in early 2019, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/citgo-buys-first-venezuelan-oil-cargo-since-ending-ties-with-venezuelan-parent-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3AZGOE6MZIBZOIXGUO7FUDOMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:18:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ServiceNow年度订阅收入超预期，彰显人工智能实力]]></title><description><![CDATA[-【原文：-】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/servicenow-projects-annual-subscription-revenue-above-estimates-signals-ai-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7B7X2ULYFNIHFB4ILY763HJDPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBM第四季度营收超预期，人工智能推动软件需求增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[IBM周三公布的第四季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，人工智能的快速普及推动了对该公司软件服务的需求，这些服务涵盖从海量数据管理到IT流程自动化等多个领域。【原文：IBM beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter revenue and profit on Wednesday, as the rapid adoption of artificial intelligence boosts demand for its software services, ranging from managing swaths of data to automating IT processes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ibm-beats-fourth-quarter-revenue-estimates-ai-boosts-software-demand-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JLBQACUDJN6HGXHNZMGHU5NJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:13:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉营收超预期，尽管汽车交付量疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周三公布的第四季度营收超出华尔街预期，尽管这家由埃隆·马斯克领导的汽车制造商在假日季度交付的车辆数量低于预期。【原文：Tesla beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter revenue on Wednesday despite the Elon Musk-led automaker delivering fewer-than-expected vehicles in the holiday quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-revenue-beats-estimates-despite-weaker-vehicle-deliveries-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G742GPI6ENO6NIZ5G3WN2HX7L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta预计年度资本支出将因超级智能计划而增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta周三预测其年度资本支出将大幅增加，这家社交媒体巨头正致力于构建人工智能基础设施，以追求超级智能。【原文：Meta on Wednesday forecast its annual capital expenditure to increase sharply, as the social media giant builds artificial intelligence infrastructure in the pursuit of superintelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-expects-annual-capital-expenditures-rise-superintelligence-push-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ESRVSR6A5IFXCDXZ6TVOWXKQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软云业务增长超预期，引发对人工智能回报的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周三公布的季度营收略超市场预期，但其关键的云计算业务表现平平，这加剧了投资者对其巨额人工智能投资回报的疑虑，同时也凸显出该行业日益激烈的竞争态势。【原文：Microsoft delivered a marginal beat on quarterly revenue expectations for its crucial cloud-computing business on Wednesday, amplifying investor doubts about the payoff ​from its hefty artificial intelligence spending and highlighting growing competition in ‌the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/microsoft-edges-past-cloud-growth-expectations-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DINL275P2ZMDVI4GKPKYDICFKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[若特朗普限制信用卡利率，航空公司忠诚度计划或面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普提出的限制信用卡利率的提案若得以实施，可能对美国航空公司利润丰厚的忠诚度计划产生重大影响，行业顾问周三表示。【原文：A proposal by U.S. President Donald Trump to cap credit-card interest rates, if implemented, could have a big impact on the profitable loyalty programmes of the country's airlines, industry advisers said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/airline-loyalty-programs-seen-risk-if-trump-caps-credit-card-interest-rates-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUDKYC445BL2TNYTSVOOTHYDSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:51:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[真相社交基金计划收购上帝保佑美国ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[约克维尔美国股票有限责任公司（Yorkville America Equities, LLC）——这家管理着五只新推出的"真相社交"品牌ETF的投资顾问公司，其投资主题聚焦于"美国优先"理念——周三宣布已同意收购"上帝保佑美国"ETF。【原文：Yorkville America ​Equities, LLC, the investment adviser that manages the five just-launched Truth Social-branded ETFs focusing ‌on "America first" investment themes, said on Wednesday it has agreed to acquire the God Bless America ETF .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/truth-social-funds-plans-acquisition-god-bless-america-etf-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MHUGBI2EJM5BPC6S6PAGSTMX4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊、香奈儿获任代表萨克斯百货债权人处理破产事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[电商巨头亚马逊与奢侈品集团LVMH、香奈儿已被任命加入萨克斯全球公司新组建的债权人委员会，这将使它们在该奢侈品零售商的破产重组过程中拥有更大话语权。【原文：Ecommerce giant Amazon and high-end brands LVMH and Chanel have been appointed to Saks Global's newly formed creditors committee, which will give them a stronger voice in the luxury ​retailer's bankruptcy restructuring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/amazon-chanel-appointed-represent-saks-creditors-bankruptcy-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNGEDXF7WFN4FP673JVM55TA6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国自动驾驶出租车公司Waymo计划于2026年第四季度进军伦敦市场。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国无人驾驶出租车公司Waymo周三表示，计划于2026年第四季度在伦敦推出其全自动无人驾驶网约车服务。【原文：U.S. robotaxi company Waymo said on Wednesday it was aiming to launch its fully driverless ride-hailing service in London by the fourth quarter of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/us-robotaxi-group-waymo-aims-launch-london-by-fourth-quarter-2026-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MF5C2OOY5LXRFHJCHN2MC7WF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法警局调查政府数字资产遭黑客攻击事件，彭博社报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法警局表示正在调查一起可能针对美国政府数字资产账户的黑客攻击事件，彭博新闻周三援引该机构的一封电子邮件报道称。【原文：The U.S. Marshals Service said it is investigating a possible hack of ​U.S. government digital-asset accounts, Bloomberg News ‌reported on Wednesday, citing an email from the agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-marshals-probe-possible-government-digital-asset-hack-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MBYNKHGSBKYBFAVX23PUYASBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储按预期维持利率不变，但认为通胀水平居高不下]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三如市场普遍预期般维持利率不变，称通胀水平依然居高不下，同时经济增长势头强劲。在最新政策声明中，美联储几乎未透露何时可能再次降息。【原文：The Federal Reserve held interest rates steady on Wednesday, as was widely expected, citing still-elevated inflation alongside solid economic growth, and giving little indication in its latest policy statement of when borrowing costs might fall again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-fed-holds-rates-steady-expected-sees-elevated-inflation-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3MAPWNUYFN2BBBGAFNT3ZH4LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储维持利率不变后，美元兑欧元和日元汇率保持涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元兑欧元和日元汇率维持升势。此前美国联邦储备委员会维持利率不变，称通胀率仍居高不下，经济增长稳健，且在最新政策声明中未透露何时可能再次降息。【原文：The U.S. dollar held gains against the euro and the yen on Wednesday after the U.S. Federal Reserve kept interest rates steady, citing still-elevated inflation alongside solid economic growth, and gave little indication in its latest policy statement of when borrowing costs might fall again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-holds-gains-against-euro-yen-after-fed-stands-pat-rates-2026-01-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4MQ426RRFOZLF25H5CWFQFGWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>