<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:33:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:33:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[越南公安部入股互联网公司 FPT Telecom]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南公安部周三表示，为加强国家网络安全，越南最大的互联网服务提供商之一--越南 FPT 电信公司的多数股权已从一家国营投资公司移交给公安部。【原文：A majority stake in Vietnam's FPT Telecom, one of the country's largest internet providers, has been transferred to the Ministry of Public Security from a state-run investment corporation in an effort to boost national cybersecurity, the ministry said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/vietnams-public-security-ministry-takes-stake-internet-firm-fpt-telecom-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4J643ZUODNN2JHHNNZAQPR4TLM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际航空运输协会称，关税不确定性可能导致航空公司不愿交付飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际航空运输协会总干事威利-沃尔什（Willie Walsh）周三表示，由于美国关税及其对飞机成本影响的不确定性，航空公司可能不愿接收飞机。【原文：Airlines may be reluctant to take delivery of aircraft due to the ongoing uncertainty around U.S. tariffs and their impact on the cost of the planes, International Air Transport Association Director-General Willie Walsh said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airlines-may-be-reluctant-take-aircraft-deliveries-tariff-uncertainty-iata-says-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNL3E44M6FOGZBX2P3XPTNZ5LQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易商赶在特朗普征收 50%关税前将巴西咖啡运抵美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，大宗商品贸易商们表示，他们正在争分夺秒，在特朗普于8月1日对巴西产品征收50%新关税之前，尽可能多地在美国卸载巴西咖啡。【原文：Commodities traders are racing against time to unload as much Brazilian coffee as possible in the United States before Trump's new 50% tariff on Brazilian products is implemented on August 1, they said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/traders-rush-land-brazilian-coffee-us-before-trumps-50-tariff-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UX6V4TNQ7VODNKGSRFKXBCERV4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息押注下调，亚洲股市挣扎，美元飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，亚洲股市承压，美元兑日元汇率攀升至4月初以来最坚挺水平，此前美国通胀表明关税正在推动物价上涨，从而抑制了美联储放松政策的预期。【原文：Asian stock markets were under pressure on Wednesday while the dollar climbed to its firmest against the yen since early April, after U.S. inflation suggested tariffs are pushing prices up, dampening expectations for Federal Reserve policy easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGC6ZW4B3JIYFCXSX4JVQQMJEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 02:40:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴林王储宫廷表示，巴林与美国私营企业签署了价值 170 亿美元的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴林王储宫（Court of the Crown Prince）周三在 X 上发布消息称，巴林首相萨勒曼-本-哈马德-阿勒哈利法王储在访问华盛顿期间见证了巴林与美国私营部门公司之间价值约 170 亿美元的多项协议的签署仪式。【原文：Bahrain's prime minister, Crown Prince Salman bin Hamad Al Khalifa, witnessed the signing ceremony of several agreements between Bahraini and U.S. private-sector companies valued at around $17 billion during a visit to Washington, the Court of the Crown Prince said on Wednesday in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/bahrain-us-private-firms-sign-17-billion-worth-agreements-says-court-bahraini-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T33NQMWY3RNAXC42B4CCHEUOJY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 02:39:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因经济改善带来的需求预期而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，油价上涨，原因是经济前景改善，人们预期全球两大石油消费国美国和中国的需求将保持稳定。【原文：Oil prices rose on Wednesday on expectations of steady demand in the U.S. and China, the world's two largest oil users, amid an improving economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-gain-demand-expectations-amid-improving-economy-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYROIDKNURO5RGJXPOJDY2LWBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 01:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税影响开始显现，美元带动国债收益率走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元与国债收益率同时上涨，这反过来又对日元构成压力，因为最新的美国通胀报告显示，有迹象表明唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税正开始影响物价。【原文：The U.S. dollar rose alongside Treasury yields on Wednesday, which in turn kept pressure on the yen after the latest U.S. inflation report showed signs that President Donald Trump's tariffs were beginning to feed into prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-rides-treasury-yields-higher-trumps-tariffs-begin-bite-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPIQ47SU2RJLFBMRHQMZOJEAZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:59:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 Aura Minerals 公司计划在美国首次公开募股中筹资超过 1.96 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大金铜矿商 Aura Minerals 周二表示，该公司计划从美国首次公开募股中筹集约 1.964 亿美元。【原文：Canadian gold and copper miner Aura Minerals said on Tuesday it plans to raise about $196.4 million from its U.S. initial public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-aura-minerals-plans-raise-over-196-million-us-ipo-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRTM5XTQN5K5TEOVD4GSTVDBCE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:53:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称越南贸易协议 "已基本确定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，与越南的贸易协定已接近完成。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that a trade agreement with Vietnam was nearly complete.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-vietnam-trade-deal-is-pretty-well-set-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V77CWNNPKBNDNEBZANQ2I65D3M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[原住民团体要求智利法院暂停对 Codelco-SQM 锂交易的社区审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的法律文件显示，智利北部的两个原住民团体要求当地法院暂停国家主导的社区审查程序，该程序是铜业巨头 Codelco 与锂矿商 SQM 之间的锂矿合作所必需的。【原文：Two Indigenous groups in northern Chile have asked a local court to suspend a state-led community review process that is required for a lithium partnership between copper giant Codelco and lithium miner SQM , according to legal documents reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/indigenous-groups-ask-chile-court-pause-community-review-codelco-sqm-lithium-2025-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5HBZCF4I5O3ZFL6QS7YZUQHOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根表示，她的基本预期是再维持一段时间利率稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周二表示，面对特朗普政府关税带来的上行压力，美国央行可能还需要在一段时间内维持利率不变，以确保通胀率保持在较低水平。【原文：The U.S. central bank will probably need to leave interest rates where they are for a while longer to ensure inflation stays low in the face of upward pressure from the Trump administration's tariffs, Dallas Federal Reserve Bank President Lorie Logan said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-says-her-base-case-calls-holding-rates-steady-while-longer-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYOOXFKD5JIPPGMJ2SGUPKNTMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 23:54:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普贝森特是接替美联储主席的一个选择，"但我喜欢他的工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，财政部长斯科特-贝森特可能成为接替美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的候选人，但他也暗示这可能不会发生。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent could be a candidate to replace Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, but suggested that might not happen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-bessent-an-option-replace-fed-chair-but-i-like-job-hes-doing-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHXPN35YXBIHRDR2JSLHHTCJZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 23:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府起诉驱逐公共广播公司董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周二对公共广播公司的三名董事会成员提起诉讼，尽管特朗普试图解雇他们，但他们仍未离职。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration filed a lawsuit on Tuesday against three board members of the Corporation for Public Broadcasting who have not left their posts despite Trump's attempt to fire them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-administration-sues-oust-corporation-public-broadcasting-board-members-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WL57QQZFVVKLNBAXTR4AV2NVV4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 23:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国经济的韧性之下，是减薪和副业的生活]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国有企业员工张金明每天晚上下班后和周末送三个小时的外卖，以弥补工资减少 24% 的损失--他希望这样可以避免与同事发生尴尬。【原文：Chinese state firm employee Zhang Jinming makes up for a 24% cut to his salary by delivering food for three hours every night after work and on weekends - and hopes he can avoid awkward encounters with colleagues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/beneath-chinas-resilient-economy-life-pay-cuts-side-hustles-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SVRYU5BFFMHBBVNXANFG36EKM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 23:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓第二季度铁矿石产量环比增长 13]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓（Rio Tinto）周三报告称，第二季度铁矿石发货量连续增长 13%，从今年早些时候与极端天气有关的中断中反弹。【原文：Rio Tinto , reported a 13% sequential rise in second-quarter iron ore shipments on Wednesday, rebounding from extreme weather-related disruptions earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rio-tintos-second-quarter-iron-ore-output-rises-13-sequentially-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZDTFK2L4VNQXGH6NZHZVGFY6A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 22:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：特朗普下令帮助向私人市场开放退休计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周二援引知情人士的话报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普预计将在未来几天内签署一项行政命令，旨在帮助美国退休计划更多地利用私人市场投资。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is expected to sign an executive order in the coming days designed to help make private-market investments more available to U.S. retirement plans, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-order-help-open-up-retirement-plans-private-markets-wsj-reports-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZT4FAU64RMUJAQVXFC5WBVPE4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 22:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，美国国民警卫队在 2024 年遭到 "盐台风 "的 "大范围 "黑客攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据国土安全部的一份备忘录，美国一个州的陆军国民警卫队网络被一个绰号为 "盐台风 "的中国网络间谍组织彻底入侵。【原文：A U.S. state's Army National Guard network was thoroughly hacked by a Chinese cyberespionage group nicknamed "Salt Typhoon," according to a Department of Homeland Security memo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-national-guard-unit-was-extensively-hacked-by-salt-typhoon-2024-memo-says-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2YIVIWOWBMH7AJ774KJRXDPTQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 22:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会终结 Cognizant 贿赂案，司法部也放弃了该案]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）决定停止执行一项重要的反腐败法律后，美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）结束了对两名前科知技术解决方案公司（Cognizant Technology Solutions）高管的民事贿赂案。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission ended a civil bribery case against two former Cognizant Technology Solutions executives, after President Donald Trump decided to stop enforcing a key anti-corruption law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-sec-ends-cognizant-bribery-case-that-justice-department-also-abandoned-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVBAIXRU35JYBIVITRASGF65IU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 21:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业机构终止支持小企业的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部周二表示，将削减对一个全国性中心网络的资助，该网络为数千家中小型农场和食品企业提供了支持。【原文：The U.S. Department of Agriculture said on Tuesday it would cut funding for a national network of centers that have supported thousands of small- and mid-sized farm and food businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-farm-agency-ends-program-support-small-businesses-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AK4M6TMLYBKWJLAXMAE4QWASPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 21:13:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 债券低迷股市低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJ6YHT3PCNKUROYHAMDOXCNIXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 21:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称美国证交会罢免会计监督机构负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封发给员工的电子邮件，美国证券交易委员会已将负责监督上市公司审计师的美国监察机构的负责人推了出去。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has pushed out the head of the U.S. watchdog that oversees public company auditors, according to an email to staff seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-audit-watchdog-chief-tells-staff-she-has-been-asked-resign-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4AI7OVD25LI3JIAQFNEXNLBEQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:48:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[广告部门增长强劲，奥姆尼康收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[广告公司宏盟集团（Omnicom）周二公布的第二季度业绩超出华尔街预期，主要得益于广告和媒体业务的增长。【原文：Advertising firm Omnicom on Tuesday beat Wall Street estimates for the second quarter, fueled by growth in its advertising and media segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/omnicom-tops-revenue-estimates-strong-growth-advertising-unit-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3M32RU2EEVOW7IIMEMYBDVPZOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:43:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西希望在最后期限前解决美国关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西副总统杰拉尔多-阿尔克明（Geraldo Alckmin）周二表示，巴西将努力争取美国在对巴西商品征收50%的关税于8月1日生效之前撤销该关税。【原文：Brazil will work to get the United States to reverse 50% tariffs on Brazilian goods before they are set to take effect on August 1, Vice President Geraldo Alckmin said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-looks-solve-us-tariff-issue-before-deadline-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMQZHBRTDNNDPJHOEZC2G4BN6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英格兰银行贝利支持国际货币基金组织帮助解决全球经济问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[英格兰银行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）周二表示，国际货币基金组织在应对世界经济中风险失衡的积累方面可以发挥关键作用，其中许多风险失衡来自美国和中国。【原文：Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey said on Tuesday the International Monetary Fund had a key role to play in tackling the buildup of risky imbalances in the world economy, many of them coming from the United States and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bank-englands-bailey-backs-imf-help-fix-problems-global-economy-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CEAOKR65RNPFHXH7FZ7EYW3YY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币法案在国会遭遇程序性障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，国会对期待已久的加密货币立法的命运产生了疑问，因为审议这些措施的程序性投票被立法者否决了。【原文：The fate of long-awaited cryptocurrency legislation in Congress was cast into doubt Tuesday, as a procedural vote to consider the measures was shot down by lawmakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/crypto-bills-hit-procedural-snag-congress-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITK2W5ETXRPSFKWGWCOIXMTGM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车安全提名人称机构不能等待自动驾驶汽车问题的解决]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统提名的美国最高汽车安全监管机构负责人将于周三告诉美国参议员，该机构必须在监督自动驾驶汽车和其他新技术方面发挥积极作用。【原文：President Donald Trump's nominee to serve as the nation's top auto safety regulator will tell U.S. senators Wednesday that the agency must take an active role in overseeing self-driving vehicles and other new technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-auto-safety-nominee-says-agency-cannot-wait-self-driving-vehicle-issues-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPG4YRYTQ5NV5NDM27HKC36CLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:37:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，墨西哥监管机构对受美国制裁的金融机构处以罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体周二报道，墨西哥银行监管机构在 6 月份对三家因涉嫌洗钱而受到美国制裁的金融机构处以超过 1.85 亿比索（约合 981 万美元）的罚款。【原文：Mexico's banking regulator slapped three financial institutions, which had been sanctioned by the U.S. for alleged money laundering, with more than 185 million pesos ($9.81 million) in fines in June, local media reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mexico-regulator-fines-financial-institutions-sanctioned-by-us-local-media-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3546MLY3ZKFPEYYBDKJ3V7VME</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 与美国公用事业公司 PPL 建立合资公司，合作建设天然气发电厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州电力和天然气公用事业公司 PPL 与 Blackstone Infrastructure 周二表示，两家公司已成立一家合资企业，根据长期能源服务协议建设天然气发电站，为数据中心供电。【原文：Pennsylvania electric and gas utility PPL and Blackstone Infrastructure have formed a joint venture to build natural gas generation stations to power data centers under long-term energy services agreements, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/blackstone-us-utility-ppl-build-gas-power-plants-jv-partnership-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57TT45K2CRMM7C6DRIHYGD4UAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:14:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国防部官员称五角大楼将继续与美国稀土项目合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位国防部官员周二告诉路透社记者，美国国防部计划继续与稀土公司合作，以确保美国在整个经济中使用的关键矿物的多样化供应。【原文：The U.S. Department of Defense plans to continue working with rare earths companies to ensure diverse American supply of the critical minerals used across the economy, a defense official told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/pentagon-keep-working-with-us-rare-earths-projects-us-defense-official-says-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLW6PHH3XBNURE6WG7V5ISB6TI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯敦促对利率保持耐心，并称关税冲击可能较小]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联储主席苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周二表示，在当前经济不确定的情况下，她并不急于改变美国央行的基准利率，因为数据显示，虽然进口关税将推高通胀，但总体影响可能并不像人们曾经担心的那样糟糕。【原文：Boston Federal Reserve President Susan Collins said on Tuesday she's in no rush to change the U.S. central bank's benchmark interest rate amid current economic uncertainty, as data suggest that while import tariffs will drive up inflation, it's possible the overall impact may not be as bad as once feared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-collins-urges-patience-rates-says-tariff-hit-may-be-more-modest-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AOTVJW5AHVKNVGAJRR2LLR77DY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:47:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>