<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:07:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:07:41 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税令印度市场动荡不安，经济增长前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对印度商品征收高于预期的关税后，印度卢比周四跌至历史新低，股指下跌，分析师警告称印度经济增长将面临持续压力。【原文：India's rupee plunged toward a record low and equity indexes declined on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump slapped steeper-than-expected tariffs on Indian goods, with analysts warning of sustained pressure on the country's growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/trump-tariffs-rattle-indias-markets-cloud-growth-outlook-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXW6V4XS6JPHDCOHKPGFXJSTVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:56:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aixtron 第二季度销售额高于市场预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国芯片系统制造商 Aixtron 周四公布的季度收入好于预期，原因是对数据通信激光器的需求不断增长，尤其是对人工智能中心的需求。【原文：German chip systems manufacturer Aixtron reported a better than expected quarterly revenue on Thursday, citing increasing demand for datacom lasers particularly for AI centers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/aixtron-posts-q2-sales-above-market-expectations-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57Q6AGEXMNJ6NLWFNRU3GLKUGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据中心推动增长，乐可兰上调 2025 年利润率展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电气和数字楼宇基础设施集团罗格朗（Legrand）周四公布的上半年核心盈利高于市场预期，并上调了年度营业利润率展望。【原文：French electrical and digital building infrastructure group Legrand on Thursday increased its annual operating margin outlook as it reported first-half core earnings above market expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/legrand-lifts-2025-margin-outlook-data-centres-fuel-growth-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJ6IDCFN5NPABNIYDTJIV6VHHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:42:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据中心推动增长，施耐德电气确认 2025 年展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电气设备制造商施耐德电气周四公布了第二季度收入增长报告，受数据中心产品持续强劲需求的推动，施耐德电气确认了 2025 年的业绩展望。【原文：French electrical equipment maker Schneider Electric confirmed its 2025 outlook on Thursday after reporting second-quarter revenue growth, buoyed by continued strong demand for its data centre offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/schneider-electric-confirms-2025-outlook-data-centres-drive-growth-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PEZRBHFYFLGTMCAGGOVXX5KJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲国防开支增加，卫星集团 SES 收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲卫星公司 SES 周四公布的第二季度营收高于市场预期，这主要得益于其积压的大量政府合同，该公司还重申了 2025 年的发展目标。【原文：European satellite company SES reported second-quarter revenue above market expectations on Thursday, buoyed by its strong backlog of government contracts, and reiterated its guidance for 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/satellite-group-ses-beats-revenue-forecast-defence-spending-rises-europe-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3G5X7XYEVLEXKCOIL6TJ4LK74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:39:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马维持指导，但预计关税将打击汽车盈利能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商宝马（BMW）周四维持了其全年业绩指导，在美国关税威胁面前表现坚挺，因为该公司在美国的强大制造实力使其在竞争中占据优势。【原文：German carmaker BMW maintained its full-year guidance on Thursday, holding strong against the threat of U.S. tariffs as the company's strong manufacturing presence in the country gives it an edge on competitors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-maintains-guidance-forecasts-tariff-blow-auto-profitability-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIMVSJUZLJJMTFIOC3CCBLLH2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔第二季度核心利润略有增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界第二大钢铁制造商安赛乐米塔尔公司周四公布的季度核心利润略高于市场预期，主要得益于欧洲积极的价格成本效应和印度较高的贡献率。【原文：ArcelorMittal , the world's second largest steelmaker, reported quarterly core profit slightly above market expectations on Thursday, helped by a positive price-cost effect in Europe and a higher contribution from India.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/arcelormittal-posts-slight-core-profit-beat-second-quarter-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RS2Q5CZOQ5IVRJ6DRWJACHEW74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:21:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[啤酒生产商百威英博第二季度利润超出预期，但销量受到拖累]]></title><description><![CDATA[啤酒巨头安海斯-布希英博公司（Anheuser-Busch InBev）周四公布的第二季度利润超出预期，尽管受中国和巴西销售疲软的拖累，啤酒销量有所下滑。【原文：Beer giant Anheuser-Busch InBev on Thursday reported forecast-beating second-quarter profits even as beer volumes slipped, dragged back by weak sales in China and Brazil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/brewer-ab-inbev-beats-second-quarter-profit-forecasts-volumes-drag-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXIAZFAY55KI7A5QU3IUJKWJWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:18:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国网络空间监管机构就 H20 芯片风险传唤英伟达公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国网络空间监管机构周四在一份声明中表示，因英伟达公司的H20芯片存在安全风险，该机构传唤了英伟达公司。【原文：China's cyberspace regulator summoned Nvidia on Thursday over security risks related to its H20 chips, it said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-cyberspace-regulator-summons-nvidia-over-h20-chip-risks-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DN3Y7TVXHJN53OL3M4GYP3GRMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:12:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费企业面临关税定价困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[从玩具到运动鞋和纸尿裤，消费品是一系列公司战略的重点，以减弱美国关税的影响--这取决于客户钱包的大小。【原文：From toys to sneakers and diapers, consumer goods are the focus of a range of company strategies to blunt the impact of U.S. tariffs - depending on the size of their customers' wallets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/consumer-companies-confront-tariff-pricing-dilemma-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTO2XC7PTBIHROBPGLFCOGX7WQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺上半年亏损 112 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷诺周四公布了上半年归属于集团的净亏损为 111.9 亿欧元（127.8 亿美元），其中包括本月早些时候一次性减记对合作伙伴日产的投资所产生的 93 亿欧元亏损。【原文：Renault reported a first-half net loss attributable to the group of 11.19 billion euros ($12.78 billion) on Thursday, including a one-off 9.3 billion euros from writing down its investment in partner Nissan flagged earlier this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-reports-first-half-loss-112-billion-euros-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSHXCR264BKLTNJ6TDL6IJL4TI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空第二季度盈利高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[汉莎航空周四公布的第二季度业绩好于预期，这主要得益于低油价和货币效应的推动，汉莎航空还确认了全年业绩指导。【原文：Lufthansa on Thursday reported better second-quarter results than expected, boosted by low oil prices and currency effects, and confirmed its full-year guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lufthansa-reports-higher-than-expected-q2-earnings-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67RA7P2IK5JMJOILXYGFRYVL4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国与印度业务往来极少，与俄罗斯几乎没有业务往来]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普说，美国与印度的业务往来很少，俄罗斯和美国几乎没有业务往来。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said that the United States has done very little business with India, and that Russia and the U.S. do almost no business together.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/trump-says-us-does-very-little-business-with-india-almost-none-with-russia-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQOKAYIL6BLZDLNTTD2U5HLRNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:52:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对韩国与特朗普达成贸易协议的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国和美国表示，他们达成了一项协议，将美国对大部分韩国商品征收的关税定为 15%，以换取美国 3500 亿美元的投资。【原文：South Korea and the United States said they reached a deal that would set U.S. tariffs on most South Korean goods at 15% in return for $350 billion in investment in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/reaction-south-koreas-trade-deal-with-trump-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWO4S6KQSBIHPO3EFIHBIAPR7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:47:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标截稿日前危险重重]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔-斯图尔特-亨特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4ME5ATURJKUZBV5P4GKQWCT3E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[StanChart 确定 13 亿美元回购计划，上半年利润大幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行（StanChart）周四报告称，由于财富、市场和全球银行业务的强劲表现提高了该银行的收入，其上半年税前利润增长了 26%，超过了分析师的预期。【原文：Standard Chartered (StanChart) reported on Thursday its first-half pretax profit rose 26%, beating analysts' estimates, as a strong performance in the wealth, markets and global banking businesses boosted revenue at the lender.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stanchart-sets-13-billion-buyback-after-h1-profit-beats-handily-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUG3TE3M6RI4PLNTJQM2COLH2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片设计公司瞄准智能眼镜，Ambiq Micro 上市后股价收盘上涨 60]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，芯片设计公司 Ambiq Micro 在纽约证券交易所的首个交易日结束时，股价上涨了 60% 以上，因为该公司在首次公开募股中筹集了 9,600 万美元。【原文：Shares of chip designer Ambiq Micro ended their first trading day on the New York Stock Exchange up more than 60% on Wednesday after the firm raised $96 million in an initial public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ambiq-micro-shares-close-up-60-after-ipo-chip-designer-targets-smart-glasses-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKWCXUDQU5OWPFIWVDLH7BNC3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行维持利率稳定，上调通胀预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周四维持利率稳定，并上调了本财年的通胀预期，表明对日本与美国达成的贸易协议将有助于日本经济避免急剧下滑持谨慎乐观态度。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady on Thursday and raised its inflation forecast for the current fiscal year, signalling cautious optimism that Japan's trade deal with the U.S. would help the economy avert a steep downturn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-keeps-rates-steady-revises-up-inflation-forecast-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLSIXCFK4NI4RJT6VAU72CP3V4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国数据疲软导致亚洲股市下滑，日本央行决议后日元走强]]></title><description><![CDATA[受中国经济活动数据不及预期和铜价暴跌的影响，周四亚洲股市下滑，而日元则在日本央行上调本财年通胀预期并维持利率不变后走强。【原文：Asian equities slipped on Thursday, weighed down by weaker-than-expected Chinese activity data and a plunge in copper prices, while the yen firmed after the Bank of Japan raised its inflation forecast for the fiscal year and held rates steady.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-2-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDRS2NYHHRP7LLRDBRJIMBGYZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 6 月零售额大幅增长，原因是折扣和任天堂 Switch 吸引了购物者]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于任天堂 Switch 2 的推出和财政年度末的打折活动吸引了消费者重返商店，澳大利亚 6 月份的零售销售额激增，尽管整个第二季度的销售量并不乐观。【原文：Australian retail sales surged in June as the launch of Nintendo's Switch 2 and discounting at the end of the financial year drew consumers back to the shops, though sales volumes for the second quarter as a whole were subdued.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/australia-june-retail-sales-jump-discounts-nintendo-switch-lure-shoppers-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUOFJPLYPVKB3IHGPKFWMBD2NU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田供应商电装的季度利润因关税和日元走强而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国关税和日元走强的影响，丰田汽车的主要汽车零部件供应商日本电装公司周五公布的第一季度利润下降 11%，降幅高于预期。【原文：Japan's Denso , a leading auto parts supplier to Toyota , posted a bigger-than-expected 11% decline in first-quarter profit on Friday, hit by U.S. tariffs and a stronger yen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/toyota-supplier-densos-quarterly-profit-falls-tariffs-strong-yen-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBZG763DT5PORE52CMYJBNYMOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:32:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出口疲软，中国工厂活动降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一项官方调查显示，7月份中国制造业活动连续第四个月萎缩，这表明在美国提高关税之前出口激增的势头已开始减弱，而国内需求依然低迷。【原文：China's manufacturing activity shrank for a fourth straight month in July, an official survey showed on Thursday, suggesting a surge in exports ahead of higher U.S. tariffs has started to fade while domestic demand remained sluggish.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-factory-activity-cools-exports-weaken-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTDLNAIDX5L7DOVUV73BGLW2RQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子称韩美贸易协议减少了不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子周四表示，韩美贸易协议将减少不确定性。【原文：Samsung Electronics said on Thursday that the South Korea-U.S. trade deal would reduce uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/samsung-electronics-says-korea-us-trade-deal-reduces-uncertainty-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WG4SMP6LUFIODINJVP46VWTACM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，OpenAI 的年化收入达到 120 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《信息》周三援引消息人士的话报道，聊天软件制造商 OpenAI 在今年前七个月的收入翻了一倍，年化收入达到 120 亿美元。【原文：ChatGPT-maker OpenAI roughly doubled its revenue in the first seven months of the year, reaching $12 billion in annualized revenue, the Information reported on Wednesday citing a source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-hits-12-billion-annualized-revenue-information-reports-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUKIQGPTKBN3HAM266IBE4GN3E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩美达成贸易协议后韩国汽车股下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，作为贸易协议的一部分，美国将对包括汽车在内的韩国进口产品征收15%的关税，此后韩国现代汽车（Hyundai Motor）和起亚汽车（Kia Corp）股价周四下跌。【原文：Shares of South Korean automakers Hyundai Motor and Kia Corp fell on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said the U.S. will charge a 15% tariff on imports from South Korea, including autos, as part of a trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-korean-auto-shares-dip-after-korea-us-trade-deal-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXFZWRZZDRNO5E2PO64BFZOISM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，7月份中国工厂活动连续第四个月萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一项官方调查显示，中国制造业活动在7月份连续第四个月萎缩，这表明在美国提高关税之前出口激增的势头已开始减弱，而国内需求依然低迷。【原文：China's manufacturing activity shrank for a fourth month in July, an official survey showed on Thursday, suggesting that a surge in exports ahead of higher U.S. tariffs has started to fade while domestic demand remains sluggish.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-factory-activity-shrinks-fourth-month-july-pmi-shows-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWESTQFSWBJO3NDZQEZSXKT6VA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:38:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储不急于放宽利率，美元迎来年内首次月度上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在备受关注的政策决定中坚持对利率采取耐心的态度，并对何时可能下调利率没有提供什么见解之后，美元周四一度触及两个月高点。【原文：The dollar flirted with a two-month peak on Thursday after Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell stuck to his patient approach on rates in a closely watched policy decision and offered little insight on when they could be lowered.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-eyes-first-monthly-gain-year-fed-no-hurry-ease-rates-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGQCR6XFBZPAXAHKH6SF626ANA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普掺水的铜关税几乎压垮 Comex 溢价]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦金属交易所的基准铜价在周四开盘时上涨，因为市场继续回吐美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）缩减美国对铜征收关税后一度高涨的铜价溢价。【原文：Benchmark copper prices on the London Metals Exchange rose at the open on Thursday as markets continued to claw back the once-mighty U.S. copper price premium in response to the scaled-down U.S. copper tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-watered-down-copper-tariffs-almost-crush-comex-premium-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEBDQK5E4NILXFJSJAACTRU7BQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:15:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税威胁引发供应担忧，油价连续第四天上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四连续第四天上涨，原因是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普推动迅速解决乌克兰战争，并威胁对购买俄罗斯石油的国家征收关税，投资者担心供应短缺。【原文：Oil prices gained for a fourth straight day on Thursday, as investors worried about supply shortages amid U.S. President Donald Trump's push for a swift resolution to the war in Ukraine and threats of tariffs on countries buying Russian oil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-gain-fourth-day-supply-fears-trump-tariff-threats-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHQ3PRLLANNHVLKAB2XWUOMUDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:49:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储对降息保持缄默迫使市场重新审视前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管政治压力无情，美联储仍决定避免发出即将降息的信号，这凸显了其普遍的谨慎态度，并迫使投资者降低了对下一次政策会议上放松政策的预期。【原文：The Federal Reserve's decision to avoid signaling imminent rate cuts despite relentless political pressure underscores its prevailing caution and has forced investors to dial back expectations for an easing at the next policy meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-reticence-rate-cuts-forces-market-rethink-outlook-2025-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKJHLRIVTVPNZHZ7AKURCVZJQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:17:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>