<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:20:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:20:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[萨克斯全球将在破产程序中再关闭九家门店]]></title><description><![CDATA[萨克斯全球公司周二宣布将再关闭九家门店，这家高端百货集团正致力于聚焦盈利能力更强的门店。【原文：Saks Global said on Tuesday it is closing nine more stores as the high-end department store conglomerate looks to focus on more profitable locations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/saks-global-close-nine-more-stores-amid-bankruptcy-proceedings-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKH3THOZXZN55POKYIS7ZUBLVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:49:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，随着电动汽车业务亏损加剧，Stellantis正寻求退出与三星的电池合资企业。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周二报道，知情人士透露，随着这家汽车制造商缩减其电动汽车计划，Stellantis NV正寻求退出与韩国三星SDI公司的美国电池合资企业。【原文：Stellantis NV is looking to exit its U.S. battery joint venture with South Korea's Samsung SDI Co. as the automaker scales back its electric-vehicle ambitions, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-seeks-exit-battery-venture-with-samsung-ev-losses-mount-bloomberg-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ECJT6Q5OFOK5B2W66ZVXZSSAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西Agibank大幅缩减美国IPO规模逾50%，下调发行价区间]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西金融科技公司Agibank周二在监管文件中披露，已将其在美国首次公开募股（IPO）的规模缩减逾50%，并大幅下调了拟定价格区间。【原文：Brazilian fintech Agibank has downsized its U.S. initial public offering by more than 50% and slashed the proposed price range, according to a regulatory filing on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/brazils-agibank-slashes-us-ipo-size-by-over-50-slices-price-range-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGXP7V4Z6ZKFDDKEMDJ4MFBPPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:34:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音计划于盛夏时节开通第四条737生产线]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司一位高管周二在航空航天供应商大会上表示，波音计划于今夏中旬在华盛顿州埃弗雷特市开通第四条737 MAX生产线。【原文：Boeing plans to open fourth 737 MAX production line in Everett, Washington, in mid-summer, a Boeing executive said Tuesday at an aerospace suppliers' conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-plans-open-fourth-737-production-line-mid-summer-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJROFN6VQRIBRCR7DCIQVQHE7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国调查未发现中国电源逆变器存在间谍软件]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的美国能源部报告显示，美国能源官员未发现中国制造的逆变器中存在恶意通信设备的证据，这些逆变器被用于该国的电力基础设施。【原文：U.S. energy officials found no evidence of malicious communication equipment embedded in Chinese-made inverters in the nation's power infrastructure, according to a Department of Energy report viewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-probe-finds-no-evidence-spyware-chinese-power-inverters-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOP4Q3OCBBMINLJZPUAPJHWQ2E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:25:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，Citgo在出售进程停滞之际，正为长期发展方向而苦恼]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，美国炼油商雪佛龙石油公司正艰难推进关键投资与财务决策，其委内瑞拉母公司出售给埃利奥特投资管理公司旗下关联企业的交易，在获得美国法官批准数月后仍处于冻结状态。【原文：U.S. refiner Citgo Petroleum is struggling to make key decisions about investments and finances as the sale of its Venezuela-owned parent to an affiliate of Elliott Investment Management remains frozen months after a U.S. judge signed off on the process, two sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/citgo-struggles-with-long-term-direction-sale-process-remains-frozen-sources-say-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SL7XYUOIMRO4HOTLY6KUZIXKUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:02:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[米莱的劳工改革计划引发与阿根廷工会的冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷总统哈维尔·米莱领导的自由主义政府将全面劳动改革置于吸引投资、重振经济的核心位置，此举引发了与该国强大工会组织的激烈冲突。【原文：Argentine President Javier Milei's libertarian government has put sweeping labor reforms at the center of its push to attract investment and revive growth, setting up a clash with the country's powerful unions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/mileis-labor-reform-drive-sets-up-clash-with-argentina-unions-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHREIWXAURM3BBW6LTYDEZLZOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟称科技巨头或需加大打击网络欺凌力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周二表示，网络平台可能需要采取更多措施来打击网络欺凌。该机构宣布了一系列应对措施，以解决这一影响六分之一儿童的问题，该问题引发了人们对其心理健康的日益担忧。【原文：Online platforms may have to do more to fight cyberbullying, the European Commission said on Tuesday as it announced a slew of measures to tackle a problem that affects one in six children and sparked mounting concerns about their mental health.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/big-tech-may-have-do-more-combat-cyberbullying-eu-says-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KHIDWSHQBLBBIJ5UG4R6KEOHY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储洛根：对当前利率政策效果持"谨慎乐观"态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里·洛根周二表示，她对美联储当前的政策利率设定能使通胀率回归2%目标并保持就业市场稳定持"谨慎乐观"态度，未来数月的经济数据将验证这一预期是否成立。【原文：Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan said on Tuesday she's "cautiously optimistic" that the Fed's current policy rate setting will get inflation headed to its 2% goal while keeping the job market stable, and that economic data in coming months will show if that hope bears out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-cautiously-optimistic-that-current-rate-setting-will-do-job-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPTDRVK3D5LFZEFLXDXJPEUKLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰涅维亚多夫公司与诺斯罗普·格鲁曼公司签署155毫米弹药生产框架协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰军工集团涅维亚多夫-PGM周二宣布，已与美国国防供应商诺斯罗普·格鲁曼公司签署框架协议，将在波兰生产炮兵弹药。【原文：Polish arms group Niewiadow-PGM said on Tuesday it had signed a framework deal with U.S. defence supplier Northrop Grumman on producing artillery ammunition in Poland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/polands-niewiadow-signs-framework-deal-with-northrop-grumman-155-mm-ammo-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VCXMZWUTJLLZGUX7V7U52X4PY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Telegram创始人杜罗夫在俄罗斯实施新限制之际重申对隐私保护的承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[Telegram创始人帕维尔·杜罗夫周二表示，Telegram将继续致力于保护言论自由和用户隐私，"无论面临多大压力"。【原文：Telegram founder Pavel Durov said on Tuesday that Telegram remains committed to protecting freedom of speech and user privacy "no matter the pressure".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/telegrams-durov-reaffirms-commitment-privacy-amid-new-russian-curbs-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z7U5YNVD7NIDBLKEXQVBF34D3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:54:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多伦多证券交易所首席执行官表示，采矿业和外国企业正推动加拿大首次公开募股热度持续高涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[多伦多证券交易所运营商TMX集团首席执行官表示，尽管美国软件股抛售引发北美市场震荡，但加拿大IPO渠道依然强劲，约有1600家企业处于不同上市阶段。【原文：Toronto Stock Exchange operator TMX's CEO said the IPO pipeline in Canada remains strong with about 1,600 companies at varying stages to list, despite a U.S. software selloff that created ripples in the North American market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/tmx-ceo-says-mining-foreign-firms-keeping-canada-ipo-interest-strong-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWYOAJ7SURNFLCPLQT4ZSA5UCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:51:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列金融科技公司FINQ推出由人工智能独家管理的美国ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列基金管理公司FINQ周二宣布，将携两只完全由人工智能管理的基金进军美国交易所交易基金市场。在这一新兴子领域，人工智能迄今仅作为辅助工具使用。【原文：Israel fund manager FINQ said on Tuesday it was entering the U.S. Exchange-Traded Funds market with two funds that will be solely managed by artificial intelligence, a nascent sub-sector where so far AI has only been used as a supporting tool.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/israels-finq-launches-us-etfs-managed-solely-by-ai-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVTFX4EV6FOTDCLGJ2AAVEGEZU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:49:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长称美元汇率处于更符合贸易规律的水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德·卢特尼克周二表示，他认为美元走弱处于"更自然"的水平，这有助于促进美国出口并扩大经济增长。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said on Tuesday that he views the weaker dollar as being at a "more natural" level to promote U.S. exports and expand economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-commerce-chief-says-dollar-more-natural-level-trade-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Y2D3PS4D5NX7HHIVZWSEWCSJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:42:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[策略师称，对人工智能颠覆的担忧为美国软件股创造了买入机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通策略师表示，近期软件股因市场担忧人工智能发展将颠覆该行业而遭遇重挫，这为投资者布局优质股反弹创造了机会。【原文：The severity of the pullback in software stocks in recent days, driven by fears of advances in artificial intelligence disrupting the industry, has created opportunities for investors to position for a rebound in higher-quality stocks, strategists at JP Morgan said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-disruption-fears-create-buying-chance-us-software-stocks-strategists-say-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RG3CULKNLBK2HHYJQJ53GVPHYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国券商股下跌，因人工智能驱动的抛售蔓延至金融板块]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国券商股价下跌，此前财富管理初创企业Altruist推出人工智能赋能的税务规划功能。这项尚处萌芽阶段的技术持续加剧了市场对传统券商面临颠覆性冲击的担忧。【原文：Shares of U.S. brokerages fell on Tuesday after wealth management startup Altruist introduced AI-enabled tax planning features, as the still-nascent technology continues to fuel disruption fears for the incumbents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-brokerages-fall-ai-driven-rout-extends-financials-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5R56HDWLRK7HMFMYO5REXIG4U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国飞行员工会呼吁周四在汉莎航空核心航线发起罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国飞行员工会VC周二呼吁，因养老金争议问题，将于2月12日对汉莎航空集团旗下核心德国航空公司及其货运子公司汉莎货运发起24小时罢工。【原文：German pilots' union VC called on Tuesday for a 24-hour strike on February 12 at Lufthansa Group's core German airline and its freight group Lufthansa Cargo in a dispute over pensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/german-pilots-union-calls-strike-lufthansas-core-airline-thursday-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LO5LU4NIPRJGVADPN35T2PEENY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:34:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白银协会称，投资增长将使2026年全球白银需求保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球白银需求预计在2026年保持稳定，零售投资的增长将抵消工业、珠宝和银器需求的大部分损失，白银协会周二表示。【原文：Global silver demand is expected to remain steady in 2026 with gains in retail investment offsetting most of the losses across industrial, jewellery and silverware demand, the Silver Institute industry association said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/rising-investment-keep-global-silver-demand-steady-2026-silver-institute-says-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFSE36TYGFKBBDO2NILS56TPAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢特尼克表示，英伟达必须接受其向中国销售人工智能芯片时设置的限制措施。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德·卢特尼克周二在听证会上表示，人工智能芯片公司英伟达在向中国销售其第二先进的AI芯片时，"必须遵守"许可条款。【原文：AI chip company Nvidia "must live with" the licensing terms on sales of its second most advanced AI chip to China, Commerce Department Secretary Howard Lutnick said at a hearing on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nvidia-must-live-with-guardrails-around-its-ai-chip-sales-china-lutnick-says-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNLT6M7OPFKWJJTMU2A64Y6KEQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:08:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉任命欧洲高管执掌全球销售，彭博社报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，知情人士透露，特斯拉已任命其欧洲业务负责人全面负责公司全球销售业务。【原文：Tesla has named its head of European operations to oversee the company's sales globally, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tesla-names-europe-executive-head-global-sales-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5FIWQX7NFLBLCP43JQN5RUK5Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员哈马克表示，利率可能在"相当长一段时间内"维持不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长贝丝·哈马克周二表示，鉴于经济活动前景"谨慎乐观"，美国央行今年没有必要急于调整利率政策。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack said on Tuesday the U.S. central bank faces no urgency to change the setting of interest rates this year amid a “cautiously optimistic” outlook for economic activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-hammack-says-interest-rates-could-be-hold-for-quite-some-time-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3PKGSLWTJPAVAQ5WGUJ7DA3MI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼亚萨法瑞科姆公司开始在其M-Pesa平台上提供股票交易服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯尼亚电信运营商Safaricom周二在其M-Pesa手机金融平台上推出股票交易服务，此举有望为该国证券交易所引入数百万新的小额投资者。【原文：Kenyan telecoms operator Safaricom on Tuesday launched stock trading for investors on its M-Pesa mobile phone financial platform, a move that could bring millions of new small investors into the bourse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/kenyas-safaricom-starts-offering-stock-trading-its-m-pesa-platform-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2MLSH7W6ROFFNSHBJ6E34JQCY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:54:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉因工会成员秘密录制员工代表会议而提起诉讼，备忘录显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一份员工备忘录显示，特斯拉已对德国金属工会（IG Metall）的一名成员提起刑事诉讼，指控其在周二柏林附近工厂举行的员工代表会议上进行秘密录音。【原文：Tesla has filed a criminal complaint against a member of Germany's IG Metall trade union for secretly recording a works council meeting that took place at its plant near Berlin on Tuesday, according to a memo to staff seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/tesla-files-complaint-against-union-member-secretly-recording-works-council-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIY4LKMNUJNLVNA65MJJLVPPLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟议会支持数字欧元，与理事会就线上线下兼容货币达成一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲议会周二首次对数字欧元给予重大支持，认可了欧洲理事会关于发行兼具线上线下功能的央行数字货币的谈判立场。【原文：The European Parliament gave its first major backing to the digital euro on Tuesday, endorsing the European Council's negotiating stance for a central bank digital currency with both online and offline functionality.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eu-parliament-backs-digital-euro-aligns-with-council-online-offlineready-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOLPLPNOYZPKLNXJTVJ5F6MO24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:23:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步在迪拜推出百度自动驾驶出租车服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步和百度周二宣布，将于下月在迪拜推出自动驾驶网约车服务，这是这家中国科技公司推进全球扩张的最新举措。【原文：Uber and Baidu said on Tuesday they would launch autonomous ride-hailing services in Dubai in the coming month, the latest step in the Chinese tech firm's push toward global expansion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uber-rolls-out-baidus-self-driving-taxis-ride-hailing-dubai-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNFWEMF6KBP7HC5MBWXI3AXFL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:22:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛起诉沃尔玛涉嫌销售假冒香水]]></title><description><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛周一在加州联邦法院起诉沃尔玛，指控这家零售巨头销售其旗下香水及护肤品牌的仿冒品，涉及品牌包括倩碧、汤姆·福特和Le Labo。【原文：Estee Lauder sued Walmart in California federal court on Monday, accusing the retail giant of selling knockoffs of Estee Lauder fragrance and skin care brands including Clinique, Tom Ford and Le Labo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/estee-lauder-sues-walmart-over-alleged-counterfeit-fragrances-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6V2S7LONC5J5NJJP6VDXYRVAUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:17:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙为华纳兄弟竞购案增添甜头]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙天空舞影业公司已提升其对华纳兄弟探索公司的收购报价，承诺若交易未能在今年内完成，将按季度追加现金补偿，并同意承担HBO母公司若退出交易需向网飞支付的违约金。【原文：Paramount Skydance has enhanced its Warner Bros Discovery bid by offering extra cash for each quarter the deal fails to close beyond this year and agreeing to cover the breakup fee the HBO owner would owe Netflix if it walked away.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/view-paramount-adds-sweeteners-warner-bros-bid-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRFGWRVLCVK25KUNOEHHISDZUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国提议提高政府资助的电动汽车充电站"购买美国产品"要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部周二表示，拟将联邦资助的电动汽车充电站中美国本土零部件比例从55%提高至最高100%，此举可能对资金使用构成重大障碍。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department said Tuesday it is proposing to boost American-content in federally funded electric vehicle charging stations from 55% to up to 100%, which could pose significant hurdles to use of the funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-proposes-boosting-buy-america-requirements-government-funded-ev-charging-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZT2QQZN3JPFZH5J5NFQRRYXNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储称美国家庭信贷问题在2025年末加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周二发布的一份报告称，美国整体信贷问题在第四季度小幅加剧，部分抵押贷款市场加速恶化，同时学生贷款借款人持续面临困难。【原文：Overall credit troubles in the U.S. increased modestly during the fourth quarter as some parts of the mortgage market saw accelerated fraying, amid ongoing difficulties for student loan borrowers, the New York Federal Reserve said in a report released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/us-household-credit-troubles-worsened-end-2025-new-york-fed-says-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGYDZUNFWRP7LAVCYBM5YLKZKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国人工智能初创企业Wrtn计划进军美国市场，目标最早于2028年实现首次公开募股（IPO）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国初创企业Wrtn创始人表示，该公司已在韩国和日本推出人工智能娱乐服务，预计今年将实现逾1亿美元的年化营收，计划于6月前进军美国市场，并瞄准最早2028年上市。【原文：South Korean startup Wrtn expects to generate more than $100 million of annualised revenue this year after launching its AI entertainment service in South Korea and Japan, with plans to expand to the U.S. by June and eyeing an IPO as early as 2028, its founder said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-ai-startup-wrtn-aims-enter-us-market-targets-ipo-early-2028-2026-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFVNNR7JTVMIJDH6JA2VOUWO6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>