<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:05:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:05:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构称，吉普车主应将车停在室外，等待召回修复]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局表示，15.4 万辆吉普插电式混合动力电动 SUV 的车主应将车停在室外，远离建筑物或其他车辆，直到完成召回维修。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said owners of 154,000 Jeep plug-in hybrid electric SUVs should park outside and away from buildings or other vehicles until they get recall repairs completed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jeep-owners-should-park-outside-pending-recall-fix-us-agency-says-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQ6CZRI2CNJU3CWT3HLMGBGGB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:53:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田称因预计美国港口罢工而增加库存]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车北美分公司周二表示，在当天早些时候开始的美国港口罢工之前，该公司已经建立了额外的汽车和零部件库存。【原文：Toyota Motor North America said on Tuesday it had built extra inventory of vehicles and parts ahead of the U.S. port strikes, which began earlier in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-says-built-extra-stock-anticipation-us-port-strikes-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NS2DRKAXYJLLVN5X6EFZHGT7FU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监察机构向医疗债务催收者发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高消费者金融监督机构周二警告医疗债务催收者，如果他们非法试图催收不准确或法律上无效的医疗债务，他们将面临联邦监管机构的执法行动。【原文：The top U.S. consumer financial watchdog on Tuesday warned medical debt collectors they face enforcement action by federal regulators if they illegally attempt to collect on inaccurate or legally invalid medical debts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-watchdog-issues-warning-medical-debt-collectors-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KLI235U2BOEJOBWW7ABKQRBAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:41:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称欧洲汽车制造商受美国码头工人罢工影响最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，欧洲汽车制造商最有可能受到美国东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸港口码头工人罢工的影响，因为他们严重依赖这些港口，但如果供应商受到影响，时间更长的罢工可能会对汽车行业造成更广泛的冲击。【原文：European automakers are most likely affected by the dockworkers strike at U.S. East Coast and Gulf Coast ports because they rely heavily on those locations, but a longer walkout could hit the industry more broadly if suppliers suffer, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-automakers-most-risk-us-dockworkers-strike-analysts-say-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSGE6CMO4JP6FAO4PRUZEMXOYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美谈判有助于避免中国对加征关税的报复--财政部官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部最高经济外交官在周二接受采访时说，中国没有对美国提高中国进口商品关税进行报复，部分原因是世界上最大的两个经济体之间继续进行对话。【原文：China has not retaliated against U.S. tariff increases on Chinese imports partly because of continued dialogue between the world's two largest economies, the U.S. Treasury's top economic diplomat said in an interview aired on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-china-talks-helping-avoid-chinese-retaliation-against-tariff-hikes-treasury-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCT3EBHB7FOZJOCAC33A4FHKDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车第三季度美国销量下降约 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，通用汽车公司（General Motors）发布报告称，其第三季度在美国的新车销量下降了 2.2%，这主要是受三个月内销售天数减少以及通货膨胀导致客户支出减少的影响。【原文：General Motors reported a 2.2% fall in third-quarter sales of its new vehicles in the United States on Tuesday, pressured by fewer sales days in the three-month period and lower customer spending due to inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gms-third-quarter-us-sales-fall-about-2-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRZFIKGNABNLHKRKJVNC626E6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）推出付费墙，对部分用户每月收费 3.99 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）周二表示，该新闻网站已推出付费墙，并要求部分用户每月支付 3.99 美元来访问其内容，以寻求数字收入来源。【原文：CNN has rolled out a paywall and is asking some of its users to pay $3.99 a month for access to its content, the news website said on Tuesday, as it looks to generate a digital revenue stream.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cnn-launches-paywall-charge-399-month-some-users-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXVBIEQZR5PQNNZVD6XYFZJHLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金反弹削弱了主要市场的实物需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士和分析师表示，随着黄金价格持续上涨，主要市场对黄金的实物需求急剧下降，一些零售消费者选择出售所持黄金并将利润入账。【原文：Physical demand for gold across key markets has tumbled as prices continue to rise, with some retail consumers opting to sell their holdings and book the profit, industry players and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-rally-cripples-physical-demand-key-markets-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEYXCSPXLVKRRA2I52XYUQ3AN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司被美国劳工委员会指控实施非法工作场所规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会发出投诉，指控苹果公司通过维持一系列非法的工作场所规定，侵犯了员工组织和争取更好工作条件的权利。【原文：A U.S. labor board issued a complaint accusing Apple of violating employees' rights to organize and advocate for better working conditions by maintaining a series of unlawful workplace rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-accused-by-us-labor-board-imposing-illegal-workplace-rules-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7P27CBJ2UFLRVHN5PNMOMFWKKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:59:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月建筑支出因单户住宅建设而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于独户住宅项目支出大幅下降，8 月份美国建筑支出意外下降，但借贷成本的下降可能会刺激未来几个月的建筑活动。【原文：U.S. construction spending unexpectedly fell in August amid a sharp drop in outlays on single-family housing projects, but declining borrowing costs could stimulate activity in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-construction-spending-falls-august-single-family-homebuilding-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OT7PXSQJVRPJLJVQBZFFTIIKWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，凯雷支持的标准航空（StandardAero）将把首次公开募股定价定在区间之上]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周二表示，美国飞机维修服务提供商标准航空（StandardAero）在美国的首次公开募股定价将高于预期范围，这将使其成为今年股市首次公开募股规模最大的公司之一。【原文：StandardAero, a U.S. aircraft maintenance services provider, is set to price its U.S. initial public offering above its indicated range, setting it up for one of the biggest stock market debuts this year, people familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/carlyle-backed-standardaero-set-price-ipo-above-range-sources-say-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2QQTHOIZFO3VAPNEBSUUUXMPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月职位空缺反弹；招聘疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 8 月份的职位空缺在连续两个月下降后意外增加，但招聘情况疲软，与劳动力市场放缓的趋势一致。【原文：U.S. job openings unexpectedly increased in August after two straight monthly decreases, but hiring was soft and consistent with a slowing labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-rebound-august-hiring-soft-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X7QWXNKLSZIIDAX2ZZ5HKRVRKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:20:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[能源价格下跌，大石油公司的巨额派息面临压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，在经历了两年多的丰厚利润之后，面对油价下跌，大型能源公司将借款数十亿美元以维持股东派息或降低股票回购速度。【原文：Major energy companies are set to borrow billions to maintain shareholder payouts or cut the rate of share repurchases in the face of a drop in oil prices after more than two years of bumper profits, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/big-oils-big-payouts-under-strain-energy-prices-fall-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3EIWF2ZKBZORFL7EZWJGC5JYF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[9 月份美国制造业保持稳定；支付价格为 9 个月来最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[9 月份，美国制造业在疲软的水平上保持稳定，但新订单有所改善，投入品的价格降至 9 个月来的最低点，再加上利率下降，预示着未来几个月制造业活动将出现反弹。【原文：U.S. manufacturing held steady at weaker levels in September, but new orders improved and prices paid for inputs declined to a nine-month low, which together with falling interest rates bode well for a rebound in activity in the coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-steady-september-prices-paid-measure-lowest-nine-months-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJZCE5XRFNKOVP66JGPUKPCCEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软改进人工智能 Copilot，新增语音和推理功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软（Microsoft）在最新的更新中为其消费者人工智能助手 Copilot 赋予了更亲切的声音，该聊天机器人还能在用户浏览网页时为感兴趣的用户分析网页。【原文：Microsoft has given its consumer Copilot, an artificial intelligence assistant, a more amiable voice in its latest update, with the chatbot also capable of analyzing web pages for interested users as they browse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/microsoft-revamps-ai-copilot-with-new-voice-reasoning-capabilities-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXFYHGVJUJL7PJQAW7JHSZLHSQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行支付 400 万美元了结美国商品期货交易委员会关于掉期报告的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会周二表示，巴克莱银行（Barclays Bank PLC）将支付 400 万美元，以了结与掉期报告相关的指控。【原文：The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission on Tuesday said Barclays Bank PLC will pay $4 million to settle charges related to swap reporting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-pay-4-mln-settle-us-cftc-charges-over-swap-reporting-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJULR47BKNMWPIA35TAUI7T33Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦收购其能源部门的全部控制权]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的企业集团伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）同意支付 23.7 亿美元，收购已故亿万富翁慈善家沃尔特-斯科特（Walter Scott）家族持有的伯克希尔-哈撒韦能源公司（Berkshire Hathaway Energy）8% 的股份，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司将完全控股该公司。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway will take full ownership of Berkshire Hathaway Energy, after the unit of Warren Buffett's conglomerate agreed to pay $2.37 billion for the 8% stake owned by the family of late billionaire philanthropist Walter Scott.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/berkshire-hathaway-buys-full-control-its-energy-unit-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRVCCYLI2JO4HCTIY5LMQSHBI4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:45:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，CVS 正在探索包括潜在分拆在内的各种方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，CVS Health 正在探索各种方案，其中可能包括拆分公司，将其零售和保险部门分开，因为这家陷入困境的医疗服务公司希望在投资者的压力下扭转颓势。【原文：CVS Health is exploring options that could include a break-up of the company to separate its retail and insurance units, as the struggling healthcare services company looks to turn around its fortunes amid pressure from investors, people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/cvs-explores-options-including-potential-break-up-sources-say-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFEYT3V43VKZLHE6ZGCRHUEFWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Equinix 签订价值 150 亿美元的合资协议，建设美国数据中心基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据中心公司 Equinix 周二表示，该公司正在与新加坡主权财富基金 GIC 和加拿大养老金计划投资委员会组建一家合资企业，目标是筹集超过 150 亿美元的资金。【原文：Data center firm Equinix is forming a joint venture with Singapore's sovereign wealth fund GIC and Canada Pension Plan Investment Board with goals to raise more than $15 billion in capital, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/equinix-signs-15-bln-joint-venture-build-us-data-center-infrastructure-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I436SPNALBPO5LSPCVH76WUTXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:42:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特降低免提驾驶服务的年度和月度价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司周二表示，将降低免提驾驶技术的年费和月费价格。【原文：Ford Motor Co said on Tuesday it will lower the annual and monthly subscription prices for its hands-free driving technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-slashes-annual-monthly-prices-hands-free-driving-service-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKNHSNGKR5IYXN2PADHINJN65M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:38:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+不太可能在 10 月 2 日的小组会议上改变产量政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[来自欧佩克+组织的五位消息人士告诉路透社，尽管近期油价大幅下跌，但欧佩克+组织的一个小组本周不太可能建议对目前的减产协议做出任何修改，并从12月开始解除部分减产协议。【原文：An OPEC+ panel is unlikely this week to recommend any changes to its current deal to reduce production and to start unwinding some cuts from December, despite recent sharp declines in oil prices, five sources from the producer group told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-unlikely-change-output-policy-oct-2-panel-meeting-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6BG4V42VRJCTCD642J7XFJXDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百事公司将以 12 亿美元收购玉米片生产商 Siete 食品公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事公司周二表示，将以 12 亿美元的价格收购玉米片生产商 Siete Foods，作为 Frito-Lay 的所有者，百事公司希望扩大其零食产品组合。【原文：PepsiCo said on Tuesday it would acquire tortilla-chip maker Siete Foods for $1.2 billion, as the Frito-Lay owner looks to expand its snacking portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/pepsico-acquire-garza-food-ventures-12-billion-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJGDVSC7U5MCPJJK5JHESAKGHA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zoom 聘请微软资深员工 Chang 担任财务总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zoom Video Communications 周二任命微软公司高管 Michelle Chang 为公司首席财务官，10 月 7 日生效。【原文：Zoom Video Communications on Tuesday named Microsoft executive Michelle Chang as its chief financial officer, effective Oct. 7.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/zoom-taps-microsoft-veteran-chang-finance-chief-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REKWEQ7VMVJVFFIWVCHYZR2NYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车公司前总裁因健康问题暂停柴油门审判]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国不伦瑞克一家法院周二表示，对大众汽车前首席执行官马丁-温特科恩（Martin Winterkorn）就所谓的柴油门丑闻进行的刑事审判因其健康状况不佳而暂停。【原文：The criminal trial of former Volkswagen Chief Executive Martin Winterkorn over the so-called dieselgate scandal has been suspended due to his poor health, a court in Braunschweig said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/dieselgate-trial-former-vw-chief-suspended-due-ailing-health-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4GNLXHW2BIQ3LVWUEUHYFZ6H4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:47:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）和美国石油管理局（APA）为苏里南价值 100 亿美元的油气项目开绿灯]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）和美国 APA 公司周二宣布，对苏里南最有前途的油气项目--58 号区块--作出了积极的投资决定，该项目有望为南美国家的近海产出揭开序幕。【原文：France's TotalEnergies and U.S. APA Corp on Tuesday announced a positive investment decision for Suriname's most promising oil and gas project, Block 58, which is expected to inaugurate the South American country's offshore output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/totalenergies-apa-greenlight-10-bln-oil-gas-project-suriname-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GK6JG4TWLVJEZE3OHZMF2ITVTU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:37:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉信理财首席执行官沃尔特-贝廷格将退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经纪公司嘉信理财（Charles Schwab）周二表示，首席执行官沃尔特-贝廷格（Walt Bettinger）将于今年年底退休。【原文：U.S. brokerage firm Charles Schwab said on Tuesday CEO Walt Bettinger will retire at the end of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/charles-schwab-ceo-walt-bettinger-retire-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXJ6DM2HXBNEFKPX5JJJ2SPOKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CVS 和 Cigna 推出 2025 年医疗保险优势计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 和 Cigna 周二公布了明年由政府支持的 65 岁及以上老年人医疗保险计划的详情，称部分会员每月将支付 0 美元的处方药保费。【原文：CVS Health and Cigna on Tuesday released details on their government-backed health insurance plans for next year for people aged 65 and above, saying some members would pay $0 premium monthly for prescription drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-cigna-unveil-medicare-advantage-plans-2025-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZRASQIKKVMQDNGD5SL6IZZATI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度塔塔工厂起火后，苹果可能需要转向中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位行业观察家和一位消息人士称，塔塔集团位于印度南部的苹果 iPhone 部件工厂发生火灾，造成大面积损坏，可能会在节日销售旺季到来之前阻碍生产，迫使这家美国公司的供应商从中国或其他地方安排关键部件。【原文：Extensive damage from a fire at Tata Group's Apple iPhone component plant in southern India could hamper production ahead of a festive season sales surge, an industry watcher and a source said, forcing the U.S. firm's suppliers to arrange critical parts from China or elsewhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-may-need-turn-china-after-indian-tata-plant-fire-sources-say-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUHJ7TKWORMSPOP4XMQRCJSLAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:36:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰跻身全球十大避税天堂排行榜]]></title><description><![CDATA[税收正义网络（Tax Justice Network）是一个致力于提高税收透明度的压力组织，根据该组织的一项排名，爱尔兰已超过巴哈马，成为全球第九大避税天堂。【原文：Ireland has leapfrogged the Bahamas to become the world's ninth most significant tax haven, according to a ranking by pressure group the Tax Justice Network, which campaigns for tax transparency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ireland-edges-into-top-10-global-tax-haven-ranking-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOWAJEAQZRJTPIIFL2RERV6PAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:27:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着需求复苏，香料制造商麦考密克上调了年度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[辣酱生产商麦考密克周二发布了好于预期的第三季度财报，并上调了全年盈利预期。【原文：Hot sauce maker McCormick raised its annual earnings forecast on Tuesday after posting better-than-expected third-quarter results, banking on consumers choosing to make meals at home to curb discretionary spending amid sticky inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spice-maker-mccormick-lifts-annual-forecast-demand-recovers-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIGB64X7U5IEXC6XN3UTL2W43U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>