<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 04:09:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 04:09:13 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌在台湾成立新的人工智能工程中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周四在台湾开设了美国以外最大的人工智能（AI）基础设施硬件工程中心，台湾总统称这是对台湾作为值得信赖的技术合作伙伴的信任。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Thursday opened in Taiwan its biggest artificial intelligence (AI) infrastructure hardware engineering centre outside of the U.S., in what Taiwan's president said was a show of confidence in the island as a trustworthy technology partner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/google-opens-new-ai-engineering-centre-taiwan-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFVQA3G53FNR3OII4VCWLP2HR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:51:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中金公司计划收购两家竞争对手，中资券商股价攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国国际金融有限公司（中金公司）表示将收购两家竞争对手之后，中国券商股价周四上涨，这激起了人们对中国 1.6 万亿美元证券业进一步整合的预期。【原文：Shares in Chinese brokerages gained on Thursday after China International Capital Corp (CICC) said it would acquire two rivals, stoking expectations of further consolidation in the country's $1.6 trillion securities industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/shares-chinese-brokerages-climb-ciccs-plan-acquire-two-rivals-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNVF4GLJNFPEVGHJKVDF3U33I4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩亮眼带动科技股上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，科技公司股价在亚洲大涨，此前芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）的丰厚收益平息了投资者对人工智能泡沫的担忧，并为科技股带动的涨势注入了新的活力，推动全球股指在今年创下历史新高。【原文：Shares of technology companies surged in Asia on Thursday, after bumper earnings from chipmaker Nvidia quelled investor fears of an AI bubble and breathed new life into a tech-led rally that has propelled global stock indexes to record highs this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tech-shares-turbocharged-by-nvidias-stellar-earnings-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GJPTYNJQVJXRK4IZ6DPPV54DU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[转折点还是泡沫？英伟达首席执行官看好人工智能变革，怀疑论者却在计算风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋说，他没有看到人工智能泡沫，而是看到了一个转折点。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang says he does not see an AI bubble, but rather a tipping point.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tipping-point-or-bubble-nvidia-ceo-sees-ai-transformation-while-skeptics-count-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUHIREA3RNOKBMZ2INTXJRPAYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰任命史蒂夫-休斯（Steve Hughes）为行政总裁兼澳大利亚和新西兰银行业务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行发言人周四表示，该行已任命史蒂夫-休斯（Steve Hughes）为澳大利亚和新西兰地区首席执行官兼银行业务主管，任期自 2026 年 1 月 1 日起。【原文：HSBC has appointed Steve Hughes as CEO and head of Banking for Australia and New Zealand, effective January 1, 2026, a company spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hsbc-appoints-steve-hughes-ceo-head-australia-new-zealand-banking-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOGYQIX34BPCFAULLZO6GGXQYA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国连续两个月未进口美国大豆，巴西到货量增长 29]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，中国连续第二个月没有从美国进口大豆，尽管总进口量因从南美的采购而飙升至历史新高，买家的目的是在与华盛顿的贸易紧张局势中避免供应中断。【原文：China imported no soybeans from the U.S. for a second straight month in October even as total imports surged to a record high on purchases from South America, with buyers aiming to avert supply disruptions amid trade tensions with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-imports-no-us-soybeans-second-month-brazil-arrivals-up-29-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCREHO5IAJOL7K4PVC2TT2B4DQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:31:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国会要求澳大利亚互联网监管机构提供证词]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会一个委员会要求澳大利亚互联网监管机构就该国的互联网法律作证，称她是 "著名的全球网络攻击狂热分子"，"威胁到美国公民的言论"。【原文：A U.S. congressional committee called on Australia's internet regulator to testify about the country's laws governing the internet, calling her a "noted zealot for global takedowns" who "threatens speech of American citizens."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-congress-seeks-testimony-australias-internet-regulator-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24CKACYENFP55IPXSIML5NBTIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行仔细研究可能左右政策的三个因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚一位高级官员周四表示，澳大利亚央行正在研究三个可能影响政策的问题，包括企业是否改变了定价方式以及货币政策的传导渠道是否发生了变化。【原文：Australia's central bank is examining three issues that could influence policy, including whether firms have changed how they set prices and whether the transmission channels for monetary policy have changed, a senior official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-scrutinising-three-factors-that-could-sway-policy-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVMEK7EBQBKCFBVSCO3CSDTL6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:58:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁豁免期限临近，石油反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四走高，从上一交易日的跌势中回升，原因是市场评估了美国提出的结束乌克兰战争的最新建议，并准备在美国规定的最后期限前停止与俄罗斯两大石油公司的业务往来。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Thursday, recovering from losses in the previous session, as markets assessed the latest U.S. proposals to end the war in Ukraine and prepared for a U.S. deadline to cease operations with two major Russian oil firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rebounds-deadline-us-sanctions-waiver-looms-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQUNH7WM3ZJTXFN6DARGTCTZNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息押注减退，日元下滑，美元跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美联储会议纪要显示美国 12 月降息的可能性较小，美元在周四创下六周来最大涨幅后一路走高，而日元则因押注日本不会立即出手阻止日元走软而暴跌。【原文：The dollar was riding high on Thursday after notching its sharpest gain in six weeks as Fed minutes made a December U.S. rate cut seem less likely, while the yen tumbled on bets that Japan would not immediately step in to stem its weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-slumps-dollar-jumps-rate-cut-bets-recede-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCNEVRHAIJMFJHPKHOLXM6ZGZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:46:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Netflix 对华纳兄弟的竞购将包括影院发行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，Netflix 已通知华纳兄弟 Discovery 管理层，如果收购成功，将继续在影院上映该公司的电影。【原文：Netflix has informed Warner Bros. Discovery management that it would continue releasing the studio's films in theaters if its acquisition of the company succeeds, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflixs-warner-bros-bid-will-include-theater-releases-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Y2JKQ4PR5PBTP7YVNYRIOZHC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩超预期，就业数据可期，股市大幅反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四早盘，由于投资者对英伟达（Nvidia）创下市场最高收益欢呼雀跃，一股宽松的反弹席卷亚洲市场，并提振了股市，而美元则因交易员为推迟公布的就业数据做好准备而上涨。【原文：A relief rally swept across Asian markets and lifted stocks in early trading on Thursday as investors cheered Nvidia's market-topping earnings, while the dollar rose as traders braced for the release of delayed jobs data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6SLKIEBJNOAHKWZD5HFM6CH5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:13:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，各大音乐唱片公司与人工智能流媒体初创公司 Klay 达成许可协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三援引熟悉交易的人士的话报道称，环球音乐集团、索尼音乐集团和华纳音乐集团已将其产品目录授权给人工智能音乐流媒体初创公司Klay，该公司将让用户利用人工智能重制歌曲。【原文：Universal Music Group , Sony Music and Warner Music Group have licensed their catalogs to Klay, an AI-powered music streaming startup that will let users remake songs using artificial intelligence, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/major-music-labels-strike-licensing-deals-with-ai-streaming-startup-klay-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2V754JX7ROINEFVJONN2UVMAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃及副国务卿兰道表示，埃及选择哈特里合作伙伴公司进行 40 亿美元的天然气交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃及副国务卿克里斯托弗-兰道（Christopher Landau）周三宣布，埃及已选择美国能源公司哈特里合伙公司（Hartree Partners）进行一项价值 40 亿美元的天然气交易。【原文：Egypt has selected U.S. energy firm Hartree Partners for a $4 billion natural gas deal, Deputy Secretary of State Christopher Landau announced Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/egypt-selects-hartree-partners-4-billion-natural-gas-deal-deputy-secretary-state-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XY2UQ5DARMTFFUYU2SFATIHOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trafigura 的 Nyrstar 公司在南澳大利亚工厂铸造了第一批锑产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[Trafigura 旗下的 Nyrstar 公司周四表示，该公司已开始在其位于南澳大利亚的皮里港（Port Pirie）金属设施的试点工厂铸造金属锑，该项目被列为美国-澳大利亚关键矿物和稀土框架的一部分。【原文：Trafigura unit Nyrstar said on Thursday it had started casting antimony metal in a pilot plant at its Port Pirie metals facility in South Australia, a project listed as part of the U.S.-Australia Critical Minerals and Rare Earths Framework.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trafiguras-nyrstar-casts-first-antimony-south-australia-plant-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXBTIEQXGROCPIO4TK6JSEH2TU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:42:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能者特朗普-MBS会晤带来人工智能资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[本文最初发表于每周三发行的《人工智能者》时事通讯。在此注册，了解人工智能和科技领域的最新突破。【原文：This was originally published in the Artificial Intelligencer newsletter, which is issued every Wednesday. Sign up here to learn about the latest breakthroughs in AI and tech.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligencer-trump-mbs-meeting-brings-ai-money-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X65BXNOIXNNZZG6KMBYY7EQ4EU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联想第二季度利润下降 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国联想集团周四公布的第二季度利润下降了 5%。【原文：China's Lenovo on Thursday reported a 5% drop in second-quarter profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/lenovo-reports-5-fall-q2-profit-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGTMYKJPEZPXRGK44EU7YRPKDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行上调目标，预计到 2026 年底标准普尔 500 指数将上涨 11]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）的策略师们上调了对 S&amp;P 500 指数在 2026 年年底的预期，这意味着该指数将比周三收盘时上涨 11.4%，理由是尽管经济低速增长，但超级大盘股科技股表现强劲，而且货币和财政背景也在改善。【原文：Barclays strategists raised their year-end 2026 expectation for the S&amp;P 500 , implying an 11.4% gain from the benchmark's Wednesday close, citing strength in megacap technology along with an improving monetary and fiscal backdrop despite low growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/barclays-raises-target-estimates-11-gain-sp-500-by-end-2026-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPCDM7ZQTZPVLL7QC3TLBQI5FE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中央银行在美国首次公开募股中融资 3.73 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中央银行公司（Central Bancompany）周三在美国首次公开发行股票，募集资金 3.7333 亿美元，在私人信贷紧缩、投资者重新审视地区性银行的时期，为其首次公开发行奠定了基础。【原文：Central Bancompany raised $373.33 million in its U.S. initial public offering on Wednesday, positioning the lender for its debut during a period of renewed investor scrutiny of regional banks amid private credit jitters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/central-bancompany-raises-373-million-us-ipo-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IX7WOPLMOZPADP25E6CWOKSLVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[APM 码头将在秘鲁卡亚俄港投资 5.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰港口运营商 APM 码头公司秘鲁分公司首席商务官 Fernando Fauche 周三表示，该公司将投资 5.5 亿美元，从 1 月份开始扩建秘鲁卡亚俄港。【原文：Dutch port operator APM Terminals will invest $550 million to expand Peru's Callao port starting in January, chief commercial officer for the company's Peru unit, Fernando Fauche, said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apm-terminals-invest-550-mln-perus-callao-port-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WROV35OTQROGPNI62V4N3BJGMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最大电网运营商推进数据中心管理计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[覆盖全球最大数据中心市场的美国电网运营商周三表示，他们计划推进一项计划，以管理巨型服务器仓库的连接，这些服务器仓库正将美国的用电量推向创纪录的高点，并增加了供应短缺的风险。【原文：Operators of the U.S. electric grid covering the world's largest data center market on Wednesday said they planned to move forward with a plan to manage the connection of the giant server warehouses that are propelling the country's power use to record highs and raising the risk of supply shortfalls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/biggest-us-power-grid-operator-moving-forward-with-plan-manage-data-centers-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GZQ33AN65LFDDNJO6SY2O45YE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国授权向沙特和阿联酋公司出口先进的美国半导体产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周三表示，它已授权向沙特阿拉伯和阿拉伯联合酋长国的两家公司出口先进的人工智能芯片，相当于35,000枚英伟达（Nvidia）Blackwell芯片。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Wednesday it has authorized the export of advanced artificial intelligence chips, the equivalent of up to 35,000 Nvidia Blackwell chips, to two companies in Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-authorizes-export-advanced-american-semiconductors-companies-saudi-uae-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEBVUMMZHNMJHOSW4FKVEWUP3M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:16:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院下令对 First Brands 欺诈指控进行独立调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国破产法官周三下令对汽车零部件制造商 First Brands 展开独立调查，并划拨了 700 万美元预算，用于调查该公司利用第三方融资开具客户发票的欺诈指控。【原文：A U.S. bankruptcy judge on Wednesday ordered an independent investigation into auto parts maker First Brands, allocating a $7 million budget to probe allegations of fraud involving the company's use of third-party financing for customer invoices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/court-orders-independent-probe-into-first-brands-fraud-allegations-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MY2UUM33FKAVM5Z3NTHTBBFKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amkor 股价尾盘回升，将与 Nvidia 合作开发封装产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在英伟达（Nvidia）的电话会议上，Amkor Technology 的股价在盘后交易中上涨超过 8%，因为这家人工智能芯片领导者的首席财务官把 Amkor 列为其计划在芯片封装方面合作的公司之一。【原文：Shares in Amkor Technology rose more than 8% in after-the-bell trading on Wednesday during Nvidia's conference call after the AI chip leader's chief financial officer named Amkor among companies it plans to work with on chip packaging.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/amkor-shares-rally-late-trade-work-with-nvidia-packaging-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDVJQNABNNJ5DAIRXWNUXWBGBY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普考虑颁布行政命令，禁止各州制定人工智能法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份行政命令草案，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正在考虑一项行政命令，该命令将通过诉讼和扣留联邦资金的方式，寻求优先适用各州有关人工智能的法律。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is considering an executive order that would seek to preempt state laws on artificial intelligence through lawsuits and by withholding federal funding, according to a draft of the order seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/urgent-trump-considering-executive-order-preempt-state-ai-laws-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFPQH7TBCJPMBEAEBMS2MDWRSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为摊牌后，美国参议员推出防止出口垄断法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参众两院两党议员周三公布了一项法案，要求商务部在发放出口许可证时创造公平竞争的环境，不得做出对一家美国公司有利而对另一家美国公司不利的决定。【原文：A bipartisan duo of U.S. senators unveiled a bill on Wednesday that directs the Commerce Department to create a level playing field when issuing export licenses and not make decisions that benefit one U.S. company over another.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-senators-unveil-bill-prevent-export-monopolies-after-huawei-showdown-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMMM52LCTVNONKNHK7UK5SGM74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:19:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Axalta 投资方 Artisan Partners 敦促拒绝阿克苏诺贝尔的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者 Artisan Partners 对 Axalta Coating Systems 与阿克苏诺贝尔的合并计划表示不满，该合并计划将通过全股票交易打造一个企业价值 250 亿美元的涂料行业巨头。【原文：Investor Artisan Partners is unhappy with Axalta Coating Systems' plans to combine with AkzoNobel in an all-stock deal that will create a paint industry giant with an enterprise value of $25 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/axalta-investor-artisan-partners-urges-rejection-akzonobel-deal-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37SFOYAEWVJZ5BT23DZX3ZG3JE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：市场低迷，英伟达发布报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者在等待美国芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）的最新财报，周三全球股市总体平静，更广泛的波动幅度也有所缓和，但日本货币和债券的抛售压力进一步加大。【原文：Global stock markets were generally calm on Wednesday and wider measures of volatility eased as investors awaited U.S. chipmaker Nvidia's latest earnings, although selling pressure on Japan's currency and bonds intensified further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDJHHUSPLJI6JMO4JJRYBPQK4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yann LeCun 将离开 Meta，创办专注于高级机器智能的人工智能初创公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yann LeCun 是现代人工智能的创始人之一，也是 Meta Platforms 公司的关键人物，他在周三表示，他计划在今年年底离开公司，创办一家新的人工智能初创公司。【原文：Yann LeCun, one of the founding figures of modern artificial intelligence and a pivotal force at Meta Platforms , said on Wednesday he plans to leave the company at the end of the year to launch a new AI startup.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/yann-lecun-leave-meta-launch-ai-startup-focused-advanced-machine-intelligence-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLCKWSVYINIH7JXQSHEP4X65VY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:52:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能领军企业英伟达预测第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周三预测第四季度营收将高于华尔街预期，在人工智能泡沫引发广泛担忧的背景下，该公司押注于云服务提供商对其人工智能芯片的蓬勃需求。【原文：Nvidia forecast fourth-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, betting on booming demand for its AI chips from cloud providers against the backdrop of widespread concerns of an artificial-intelligence bubble.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ai-leader-nvidia-forecasts-fourth-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2025-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5XFCF5KRBOTZHV4NTVR3WWQSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:22:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>