<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:46:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:46:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月单户住宅开工量和建筑许可量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[在未售出的新房过剩和劳动力市场疲软的影响下，美国 8 月份的独栋住宅建设和未来建设许可出现下降，但抵押贷款利率却在下降。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding and permits for future construction dropped in August amid a glut of unsold new houses and a softening labor market, shrugging off falling mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-single-family-housing-starts-building-permits-drop-august-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VOD4CHNLEJOQDDJKSUQ7V7ONI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构建议加密货币公司免于遵守 "诚信 "和其他规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据英国金融行为监管局（Financial Conduct Authority）周三提出的新建议，英国的加密货币公司可以不受确保金融服务公司诚信经营和维护客户利益的规则的约束。【原文：Crypto firms in Britain could be exempted from rules that ensure financial services companies act with integrity and in the interests of customers, under new proposals outlined by the Financial Conduct Authority on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uk-regulator-proposes-exempting-crypto-firms-integrity-other-rules-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIQBJ4MIMVNWBJ4JBVBSES7HJU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:25:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊投资逾 10 亿美元提高员工薪酬并降低医疗成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[科技巨头亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周三表示，该公司将投资超过 10 亿美元，用于提高美国执行和运输员工的薪酬并降低医疗保健成本。【原文：Amazon.com is investing over $1 billion to raise pay and lower health care costs for U.S. fulfillment and transportation employees, the tech giant said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/amazon-investing-over-1-billion-raise-employee-pay-lower-health-care-costs-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSXNQCJSRNLWFH4GX7APYK5DZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司工人开始无限期罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣若泽多斯坎波斯金属工人工会在一份声明中说，巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司的金属工人周三举行了无限期罢工，要求增加工资和签署集体劳动协议。【原文：Metalworkers at Brazilian planemaker Embraer went on strike on Wednesday for an indefinite time, demanding wage increases and the signing of a collective labor agreement, the Metal Workers Union from Sao Jose dos Campos said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/workers-brazils-embraer-begin-indefinite-strike-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4N3RW7VSNMIDFCW4Q4WODZDYQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾略特透露 20 亿美元入股并支持领导层后，Workday 公司股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在激进投资者埃利奥特管理公司（Elliott Management）宣布持有该公司超过 20 亿美元的股份并支持其领导层之后，Workday 的股价在周三收盘前上涨了近 10%。【原文：Shares of Workday rose nearly 10% before the bell on Wednesday, after activist investor Elliott Management unveiled a stake of more than $2 billion in the company and backed its leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/workday-rises-after-elliott-reveals-2-billion-stake-endorses-leadership-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBE6GJ7TCFIOFF2JLP24L73XPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:11:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前英国央行副行长警告特朗普可能打开金融支付 "致命开关]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行的一位前高级官员说，那些视自己为美国盟友的国家现在正在考虑，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府是否有一天会破坏它们的支付系统，以施加外交压力。【原文：Countries that see themselves as U.S. allies are now considering whether President Donald Trump's administration could one day disrupt their payments systems to exert diplomatic pressure, a former top Bank of England official has said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ex-boe-deputy-governor-warns-trump-could-flick-financial-payments-kill-switch-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHJIBG4MJBMDBHOGO3EDEMX5L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉姆-宾为 F1 首次亮相的凯迪拉克增添美国精神]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯塔基波本威士忌品牌吉姆-宾（Jim Beam）和一级方程式赛车新军凯迪拉克于本周三宣布建立合作伙伴关系，以彰显双方的历史渊源，并为车队增添美国精神。【原文：Kentucky bourbon brand Jim Beam and Formula One newcomers Cadillac announced a partnership on Wednesday highlighting their historic ties and adding to the team's American spirit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jim-beam-adds-american-spirit-f1-debutants-cadillac-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROCX4NYM4VJS5NJWOT4EX6GA5M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾展示与美国军火制造商联合制造的首枚导弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾周三公布了与一家美国公司联合制造的首枚导弹，标志着台北与华盛顿为应对中国军事威胁而快速发展的防务合作迈出了重要一步。【原文：Taiwan unveiled its first missile to be jointly manufactured with a U.S. company on Wednesday, marking a major step in the fast-growing defence cooperation between Taipei and Washington to counter China's military threat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/taiwan-shows-off-first-missile-be-jointly-manufactured-with-us-arms-maker-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2JQWWJF6NNIZA46SABZ7O5PRY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rithm Capital 拟以 16 亿美元收购房地产投资信托公司派拉蒙集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球资产管理公司 Rithm Capital 周三表示，已同意以 16 亿美元现金收购房地产投资信托公司派拉蒙集团。【原文：Global asset management company Rithm Capital on Wednesday said it had agreed to acquire real estate investment trust Paramount Group for $1.6 billion in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/rithm-capital-acquire-reit-paramount-group-16-billion-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PDRT34P5RI7BLYJQNZFBV6LII</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博鳌亚洲论坛将美国最低时薪提高至 25 美元，兑现 2021 年承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周三表示，已将全美最低时薪提高至每小时 25 美元，兑现了其 2021 年达到这一门槛的承诺。【原文：Bank of America raised its minimum hourly wage to $25 per hour across the United States, the lender said on Wednesday, fulfilling its 2021 pledge to meet the threshold.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/bofa-raises-us-minimum-hourly-wage-25-delivering-2021-commitment-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2UWWQATDBNOPKCFK5Q64FQXWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:48:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片初创企业 Groq 以 69 亿美元估值融资 7.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能芯片初创公司 Groq 周三表示，该公司新融资 7.5 亿美元，融资后估值 69 亿美元。【原文：Artificial intelligence chip startup Groq said on Wednesday it has raised $750 million in new financing at a post-money valuation of $6.9 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/chip-startup-groq-raises-750-million-69-billion-valuation-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKB3PONDHRMSHJRTVJNU6LM7CM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[曼联连续第六年亏损，预计收入下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[曼彻斯特联队（Manchester United）周三连续第六年报告年度净亏损，并预测本财年收入将减少，这凸显了这家足球俱乐部持续的财务困境。【原文：Manchester United reported an annual net loss for the sixth consecutive year on Wednesday and forecast lower revenue for this fiscal year, highlighting the football club's ongoing financial struggles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/manchester-united-posts-sixth-straight-annual-loss-forecasts-revenue-dip-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVBAYJJRAVOXXH72LZWY72LPCM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MBA 数据显示，美国 30 年期抵押贷款利率下降，再融资大幅增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着就业增长放缓和美联储降息预期推动基准国债收益率下降，美国最受欢迎的住房贷款利率上周降至一年来的最低点，房主们竞相锁定更低的借贷成本。【原文：The interest rate on the most popular U.S. home loan dropped last week to its lowest in a year, sending homeowners racing to lock in cheaper borrowing costs as slowing jobs growth and expectations for a Federal Reserve interest-rate cut drive down yields on benchmark Treasuries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-30-year-mortgage-rate-drops-refinances-jump-mba-data-shows-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5FVF7UEVVJONG5SEK2RZ6Z6DE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用磨坊公司季度销售额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用磨坊周三的季度销售额超出预期，原因是部分产品降价刺激了需求。【原文：General Mills beat quarterly sales estimates on Wednesday, as price cuts on select products lifted demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/general-mills-beats-quarterly-sales-estimates-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MU2IAEZE7NLQPLVP7ZUD6562LI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行将 2026 年黄金预期上调至 4,000 美元，金银屡创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行（Deutsche Bank）周三将明年的金价预期上调了 300 美元，平均预期为每盎司 4,000 美元，原因是央行需求强劲、美元可能走软以及美联储重启加息周期。【原文：Deutsche Bank raised its gold price forecast by $300 for next year to an average of $4,000 per ounce on Wednesday, due to strong central bank demand, potential U.S. dollar weakness and a resumed Federal Reserve rate-easing cycle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-raises-2026-gold-forecast-4000-bullion-hits-record-highs-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TN6JDY6HSZKTTL5AXB4PB6GATU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美联储翘首以盼，疲软美元获得支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGNYSYB3ZRLHVBCGKEBSGCAGRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:38:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[非洲制造商为延长美国贸易计划做最后努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位参与游说活动的肯尼亚工厂主告诉路透社，非洲制造商正在游说美国国会，希望能将将于 9 月底到期的免税贸易计划最后延长一到两年。【原文：African manufacturers are lobbying U.S. Congress to grant a last-ditch extension of one or two years to a duty-free trade programme due to expire at the end of September, a Kenyan factory owner involved in the campaign told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/african-manufacturers-last-ditch-bid-extend-us-trade-programme-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSZJOXQRRVOEZGB5RQFIL7P2OU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息可能为美股更广泛的上涨奠定基础]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者表示，美国央行恢复宽松货币政策可能会增加并扩大华尔街的涨势，尽管这种提振可能已经被定价，而且可能取决于较低的利率是否有助于经济避免大幅下滑。【原文：The resumption of monetary easing by the U.S. central bank could add to and broaden Wall Street's rally, investors say, though such a boost might already be priced in and could depend on whether lower interest rates help the economy avoid a significant downturn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-rate-cuts-could-set-stage-broader-us-stock-gains-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNVMJMZ4YRL7NAVXIVNOCD7AC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储有望降息，并通过新预测更新对特朗普经济计划的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[多年来政治色彩最浓厚的美国联邦储备委员会会议将于本周三结束，人们普遍预期这次会议将降息四分之一个百分点，但这可能会引发一些决策者的异议，他们认为降息幅度太小、为时过晚，而另一些决策者则认为根本没有必要降息。【原文：The most politically charged U.S. Federal Reserve meeting in years wraps up on Wednesday with broad expectations for a quarter-percentage-point interest rate cut that may spark dissents from some policymakers who feel it is too small and too late and others who feel it is not warranted at all.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-expected-cut-rates-update-views-trump-economic-plan-with-new-projections-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGXOS4FTLVM2RB3ZRJUCVFEYJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递利润将受美国对此前豁免的包裹征收关税拖累]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递（FedEx）周四发布的财报显示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）决定终止对流行的直接面向消费者的货运免征关税待遇，这家全球快递公司的季度利润将受到冲击。【原文：FedEx will report a quarterly profit hit from President Donald Trump's decision to end tariff-exempt treatment for popular direct-to-consumer shipments when the global delivery firm reports results on Thursday, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fedex-profit-be-dragged-down-by-us-tariffs-previously-exempt-parcels-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BJ4TP4X3VPLXHFZWYCQD7J5GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行可能降息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[受疲软的就业报告和第二季度经济萎缩的刺激，加拿大央行预计将于周三降息 25 个基点。【原文：The Bank of Canada is expected to cut interest rates by 25 basis points on Wednesday, spurred by weak job reports and economic contraction in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-likely-cut-interest-rate-by-25-basis-points-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAY2DQXKUFMEBLASHHUDNPAHIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储新预测将考虑动荡时期，米兰参与辩论]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三政策会议的结束将向投资者传递三方面的信息，显示官员们为应对就业市场疲软而重新调整展望的程度、美国央行在利率路径问题上的分歧有多大，以及行长斯蒂芬-米兰的上任是否让这一切有了党派倾向。【原文：The end of the Federal Reserve's policy meeting on Wednesday will convey a three-part message for investors, showing how much officials have reshuffled their outlooks to account for a weakening job market, how divided the U.S. central bank is becoming over the interest rate path and whether the arrival of Governor Stephen Miran has given it all a partisan tilt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/feds-new-projections-account-turbulent-period-miran-joins-debate-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GW7GTVFLZZML3BBWDNPAK66ZWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:05:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国媒体行业新领军者 YouTube 将人工智能视为内容创作的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[在其 20 岁生日之际，YouTube 已无法辨认出当初那个由年轻的业余用户发布未经加工的低成本短片的零散视频网站。【原文：On its 20th birthday, YouTube is unrecognizable as the scrappy video site that began as the domain of young amateur users publishing unpolished, low-budget clips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/youtube-new-leader-us-media-industry-bets-ai-key-creating-content-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52VK6KPUQNJHJEEXGZAJEZPU44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储将于 2025 年首次降息，美国各行业值得关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美联储有望在今年首次降低借贷成本，对利率敏感的美国企业部门将成为关注焦点，在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）上个月暗示将下调借贷成本后，大多数部门已经实现了上涨。【原文：U.S. corporate sectors that are sensitive to interest rates will be in focus as the Federal Reserve looks poised to lower borrowing costs for the first time this year, with most having already notched up gains after Chair Jerome Powell hinted at cuts last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-sectors-watch-fed-lines-up-first-rate-cut-2025-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFIUGRJ5QVJ5HL4USB75HJESEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储做出降息决定前谨慎情绪挥之不去，美国股指期货走势低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国股指期货变化不大，因为投资者在等待美联储为期两天的货币政策路径评估会议之后发布公告的同时，暂缓了大额押注。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were little changed on Wednesday as investors held back on big bets while awaiting an announcement after the Federal Reserve's two-day meeting to assess the monetary policy path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-stock-futures-muted-caution-lingers-ahead-feds-rate-cut-decision-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4YM6UKBNVNJRIAF4EU746KMDU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:57:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来制定以消费者为中心的战略，肥胖症药物领导地位将超越美国本土]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司国际总裁周三告诉路透社，礼来已在欧洲、亚洲和中东成为肥胖症药物市场的领导者，并希望在全球复制其在美国的主导地位。【原文：Eli Lilly has established itself as the market leader in obesity drugs in Europe, Asia and the Middle East and expects to replicate its U.S. dominance globally, the company's international president told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-sees-obesity-drug-leadership-beyond-us-it-leans-consumer-focused-strategy-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSQCPCUUHZIYPHULDCOOI3Y2AY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界贸易组织报告称，人工智能将改变全球贸易]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织周三的一份新报告警告说，到2040年，人工智能可将商品和服务贸易额提高近40%，但如果没有适当的政策，人工智能也可能加剧经济鸿沟。【原文：Artificial intelligence could boost the value of trade in goods and services by nearly 40% by 2040, but without adequate policies it could also exacerbate economic divides, a new World Trade Organization report warned on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-set-transform-global-trade-says-world-trade-organization-report-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXCSTDCDT5IN5G4GL7PIOKIXLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行首席执行官认为 "不友好 "的联合信贷银行交易可能导致收入减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行首席执行官贝蒂娜-奥尔洛普（Bettina Orlopp）周三称，联合信贷银行（UniCredit）对潜在合并的态度 "不友好"，并表示任何交易都可能损害收入。【原文：Commerzbank CEO Bettina Orlopp on Wednesday labelled UniCredit's approach for a potential merger as "unfriendly" and said that any deal would likely hurt revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commerzbank-ceo-sees-likely-revenue-hit-unfriendly-unicredit-deal-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMHCR7Z7IJLPHJBGQ6TGR6TYWA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚要求联合国航空机构制定保护飞机上宠物的全球标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[在发生狗在飞机上死亡的高调事件后，哥伦比亚要求联合国航空机构支持宠物跨境空运的全球标准。【原文：Colombia is asking the U.N.'s aviation agency to support global standards for transporting pets by air across borders, following high-profile cases of dogs dying on planes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-asks-un-aviation-agency-global-standards-protect-pets-planes-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEIWE6DXSNL5XKOLU6PGSDJY44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国要求科技公司停止购买英伟达的所有人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，中国互联网监管机构已指示中国最大的科技公司停止购买英伟达（Nvidia）的所有人工智能芯片，并终止现有订单。【原文：China's internet regulator has instructed the nation's biggest technology firms to stop buying all of Nvidia's artificial intelligence chips and terminate their existing orders, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/china-tells-tech-firms-stop-buying-all-nvidias-ai-chips-ft-reports-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRYUMDBCNBIGPJQBMXKV3D7Y5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 08:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>