<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:36:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[智利监管机构：中美贸易战迫在眉睫，铜价可能已见顶]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利国家铜业委员会（Cochilco）周一表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要进一步提高对中国的关税，在贸易战不断升级的情况下，红色金属的价格很可能已经在今年达到顶峰。【原文：Chile's state copper commission Cochilco on Monday said that prices for the red metal have likely already peaked this year amid an escalating trade war, as U.S. President Donald Trump threatened to further increase tariffs on China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chile-regulator-copper-prices-have-likely-peaked-us-china-trade-war-looms-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSRHWQVMHRJ5NCNWD4AEB6ETNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希腊股市可能重获梦寐以求的 "发达市场 "徽章]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊股票本周可能重新获得指数提供商富时罗素（FTSE Russell）梦寐以求的发达市场地位--这是该国在长达十年的债务危机后恢复正常的关键一步，此举可能刺激数百万美元的资金流入。【原文：Greek equities could regain the coveted developed market status by index provider FTSE Russell this week - a key step on the country's return to normalcy following a decade-long debt crisis and a move that could spur millions of dollars in inflows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/greek-stocks-could-regain-coveted-developed-market-badge-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYJYPGWZOBLQFHPOTVV5JR2WXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官称股市跌幅可能扩大 20%，经济可能陷入衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）周一表示，由于美国征收巨额关税，股市可能会扩大20%的跌幅，并指出经济很可能已经陷入衰退。【原文：BlackRock CEO Larry Fink on Monday said stock markets could extend their decline by 20% as the U.S. imposes steep tariffs, noting the economy is probably already in a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackrock-ceo-says-stocks-could-extend-fall-by-20-economy-probably-recession-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRJ57ZYQLVMEFOHAEQOT2Z5UGA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:44:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球市场陷入崩溃：图表为证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税对经济造成破坏的担忧不断升温，一场规模空前的股市暴跌席卷全球，主要市场损失超过 10 万亿美元。【原文：A stock market rout, historic in scale, has swept across the globe wiping more than $10 trillion off major markets, as concerns about the economic damage unleashed by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs spiral.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/breakingviews/global-markets-selloff-graphic-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEGA47OOPRMGHIQNCTVAKXFJRY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒：确保通胀率不上升是首要任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周一表示，近期商品和市场服务通胀的部分上升可能是对特朗普政府当前政策效果的 "预期"，并补充说，控制通胀是美联储的 "首要任务"。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler on Monday said that some of the recent rise in goods and market-services inflation may be "anticipatory" of the effect of the Trump administration's current policies, adding that it's a "priority" for the Fed to keep inflation in check.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-making-sure-inflation-doesnt-rise-is-priority-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSKEYSAQHVJT3OTK7Y2YW625RY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DailyPay 在纽约提起诉讼，以挫败因工人薪资产品而面临的诉讼威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[DailyPay公司提供了一种让工人更快地领取工资以换取费用的产品，该公司周一起诉了纽约州总检察长莱蒂西亚-詹姆斯（Letitia James），以阻止一项声称该产品是非法贷款的潜在诉讼。【原文：DailyPay, which offers a product that lets workers collect paychecks faster in exchange for a fee, sued New York Attorney General Letitia James on Monday to thwart a potential lawsuit claiming the product is an illegal loan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/dailypay-sues-new-york-thwart-threatened-lawsuit-over-worker-pay-product-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4RCC22FQFKI5BDQKNUKP44ONE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼日利亚法院延期至 4 月 30 日审理 Binance 高管逃税案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Binance 的一名律师周一表示，尼日利亚一家法院已将针对 Binance 的逃税案延期至 4 月 30 日，以允许当地税务机关回应该加密货币交易所提出的一项请求，即废除通过电子邮件向其送达法庭文件的命令。【原文：A Nigerian court has adjourned a tax evasion case against Binance to April 30 to allow the local tax authority to respond to a request by the cryptocurrency exchange to annul an order for court documents to be served on it by email, a lawyer for Binance said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/nigerian-court-adjourns-binance-executives-tax-evasion-trial-april-30-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2VQDXMKVBMIVPRSQYPFPFDACQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称银行业高层就特朗普关税影响举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士称，包括摩根大通和美国银行在内的一些全球顶级银行的首席执行官周日举行了一次电话会议，讨论美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）公布的巨额关税所带来的影响。【原文：The CEOs of some of the top global banks, including JPMorgan Chase and Bank of America , held a call on Sunday to discuss the repercussions of the hefty tariffs unveiled by President Donald Trump, sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-banking-chiefs-held-talks-over-trump-tariff-fallout-sources-say-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H46FQIRFT5PB3KXJSVUZD2JWYQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:41:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国商务部长卢特尼克在关税宣布一天后与银行首席执行官讨论了关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉此次会议的消息人士透露，美国最大银行的负责人周四与商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）举行了会晤，讨论了唐纳德-特朗普总统在关税计划宣布一天后提出的全面关税计划。【原文：The heads of the U.S.'s largest banks met with Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick on Thursday to discuss President Donald Trump's sweeping tariff plans a day after they were announced, according to a source familiar with the meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-discussed-tariffs-with-bank-ceos-one-day-after-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEQRLWTHRNKZ5ABV5DS4WDG2JM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德准备提前在印度推出减肥药 Wegovy]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉诺和诺德计划的消息人士告诉路透社，丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司正在考虑提前在印度推出其减肥药 Wegovy，以便在这个人口众多的国家与竞争对手礼来公司展开更好的竞争。【原文：Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk is looking at an early launch of its blockbuster weight-loss drug Wegovy in India to better compete with rival Eli Lilly in the populous nation, two sources familiar with the plans told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-preparing-early-launch-weight-loss-drug-wegovy-india-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXC3VQLHUVNOBE6PTNJDRXM7EI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塞夫科维奇表示，欧盟将以价值不到 260 亿欧元的美国进口为目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易委员马罗斯-塞夫科维奇（Maros Sefcovic）周一告诉记者，考虑到成员国的意见，欧盟针对特朗普政府征收钢铝关税的美国进口商品清单的反制措施将少于260亿欧元（约合284.6亿美元）。【原文：The European Union's countermeasures targeting a list of U.S. imports in response to the Trump's administration steel and aluminum tariffs will be less than 26 billion euros' ($28.46 billion) worth after taking in account member states' remarks, EU trade commissioner Maros Sefcovic told reporters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-will-target-less-than-26-bln-worth-us-imports-sefcovic-says-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XARTUNOVBL6FMWDBENYRS7GXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:23:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰资产管理公司英国首席执行官斯图尔特-怀特离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行一位发言人告诉路透社，汇丰资产管理公司英国首席执行官斯图尔特-怀特（Stuart White）在这家银行业巨头任职超过 14 年后即将离职，该公司已开始寻找接替他的人选。【原文：HSBC Asset Management's UK CEO Stuart White is leaving the company after more than 14 years at the banking giant, which had started a search for his replacement, a spokesperson told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-asset-managements-uk-ceo-stuart-white-leaving-company-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4QJ7FC7XRIE7H2MIRJPCSL3PI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街 "恐惧指数 "闪红，股市延续跌势]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街最受关注的投资者焦虑指数周一跃升至八个月来的新高，原因是对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关税政策后果的担忧导致美国股市延续了上周的跌势。【原文：Wall Street's most watched gauge of investor anxiety jumped to a new eight-month high on Monday as U.S. stocks extended their selloff from last week on worries over the fallout from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-fear-gauge-flashes-red-stocks-extend-selloff-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TF7DOPDR5JZXANGIYUEYBNNMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星展银行供应商勒索软件攻击可能导致 8,200 份客户账单曝光]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡星展集团周一表示，其数据供应商 Toppan Next Tech (TNT) 遭到勒索软件攻击，约 8200 名星展客户的客户账单可能受到影响。【原文：Singapore's DBS Group said on Monday its data vendor, Toppan Next Tech (TNT), had suffered a ransomware attack, potentially compromising customer statements of around 8,200 DBS customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/dbs-vendor-ransomware-attack-potentially-exposes-8200-customer-statements-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMZZ5MMSI5KRRD7JZ6ZM64FYFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令重新审查日邦钢铁对美国钢铁公司的竞购--声明]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周一指示美国外国投资委员会审查买家对美国钢铁公司的收购，"以协助我决定是否应就此采取进一步行动"。【原文：President Donald Trump on Monday directed the Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States to review the acquisition of U.S. Steel by the buyers "to assist me in determining whether further action in this matter may be appropriate."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-orders-fresh-review-nippon-steels-bid-us-steel-statement-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQX3WLEXKRKPLCBGCUX6L7E2EE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:49:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司与两起 737 MAX 坠机事故受害者家属达成诉讼和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国飞机制造商波音公司与埃塞俄比亚航空公司一架波音737 MAX客机于2019年3月坠毁事件中两名遇难者的家属在庭审前夕达成和解。【原文：U.S. planemaker Boeing settled lawsuits with the families of two victims killed in the March 2019 crash of an Ethiopian Airlines Boeing 737 MAX on the eve of trial, lawyers for the families said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/boeing-settles-lawsuits-with-two-737-max-crash-victims-families-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXASI2V7GZKIDP6PZAB4KDKV7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税风暴肆虐 "华丽七重奏"，苹果逼近一年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全球关税战会带来金融后果，"华丽七国 "股票周一下挫，延续了市场的颓势，其总价值已减少约 2 万亿美元。【原文：The "Magnificent Seven" stocks sank on Monday, extending a market rout that has wiped off around $2 trillion from their combined value as investors worry about the financial fallout of U.S. President Donald Trump's global tariff war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tariff-storm-ravages-magnificent-seven-apple-nears-one-year-low-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFBHQQGNBBMGVM4X6HMPQIKCWE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:17:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国信贷息差继续扩大，未宣布新债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税战可能导致经济衰退，信用利差或发行成本继续上升，美国投资级和高收益债券市场连续第三天没有宣布新的债券发行。【原文：No new offerings were announced in the U.S. investment-grade and high-yield bond markets for the third consecutive day as credit spreads or the cost of issuance continued to increase on worries that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff war could lead to a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-credit-spreads-continue-widen-no-new-bonds-announced-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Z72BUCMHZO6DO2WF6UV542MAI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:11:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工程软件初创公司 Rescale 从应用材料公司和英伟达公司融资 1.15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rescale 是一家位于旧金山的初创公司，主要生产用于设计赛车和计算机芯片的工程软件，该公司周一获得了 1.15 亿美元的风险融资。【原文：Rescale, a San Francisco-based startup that makes engineering software used to design race cars and computer chips, raised $115 million on Monday in venture financing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/engineering-software-startup-rescale-raises-115-million-applied-materials-nvidia-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7KSZJTHOJKTDCLNXMX534BP4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街最新下调标准普尔 500 指数年度目标的是美国银行和奥本海默公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[博雅全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）和奥本海默资产管理公司（Oppenheimer Asset Management）周一成为最新一批下调美国 500 指数（S&amp;P 500 index）年底目标至 6000 点以下的华尔街研究公司，以应对全球贸易战深化带来的风险。【原文：BofA Global Research and Oppenheimer Asset Management on Monday became the latest Wall Street research firms to cut their year-end targets for the S&amp;P 500 index to below the 6,000 mark in response to risks from a deepening global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bofa-oppenheimer-latest-wall-st-slash-sp-500s-annual-target-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7HYJJVGA5NEVO42BR7TN3T2NY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普顾问纳瓦罗在发表关税言论后斥责马斯克为 "汽车组装商]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的最高贸易顾问彼得-纳瓦罗（Peter Navarro）周一驳斥了科技亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）推动美国和欧洲之间 "零关税 "的主张，称这位特斯拉首席执行官是一个依赖其他国家零部件的 "汽车组装商"。【原文：Peter Navarro, President Donald Trump's top trade adviser, on Monday dismissed tech-billionaire Elon Musk's push for "zero tariffs" between the United States and Europe, calling the Tesla CEO a "car assembler" reliant on parts from other countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-adviser-navarro-dismisses-musk-car-assembler-after-tariff-comments-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BV6QR3PYNVLGVGM4VZBHBVZIXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币创 2025 年新低，美国加密货币类股大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于关税紧张局势升级和对全球贸易战的担忧引发了风险资产的广泛撤退，在美国上市的加密公司股价在周一开盘前暴跌，与比特币的大幅下跌如出一辙。【原文：U.S.-listed shares of crypto companies tumbled before the markets opened on Monday, mirroring a sharp drop in bitcoin as escalating tariff tensions and fears of a global trade war triggered a broad retreat from risk assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/us-crypto-stocks-plunge-bitcoin-hits-new-2025-low-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOIP37KBJBOA3MT2TUXQHPWK74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:30:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亨廷顿-英格尔斯公司与现代重工签署造船合作谅解备忘录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国军用造船厂亨廷顿-英格尔斯公司（Huntington Ingalls）和韩国现代重工公司（HD Hyundai Heavy Industries）周一表示，两家公司已签署协议，探讨增加商业和国防项目生产的机会。【原文：U.S. military shipbuilder Huntington Ingalls and South Korea's HD Hyundai Heavy Industries have signed an agreement to explore opportunities to increase production in commercial and defense projects, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/huntington-ingalls-hd-hyundai-heavy-industries-sign-mou-shipbuilding-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJAX2XRSSRII5KE6UEK7I4ITRY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:26:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济衰退风险加剧，欧洲央行利率可能加速下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税计划引发的全球市场溃败巩固了欧洲央行下周再次降息的理由，并支持了世界第二大央行更快放宽政策的论点。【原文：A global market rout induced by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs scheme has solidified the case for another ECB rate cut next week and supports arguments for even quicker policy easing from the world's second largest central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecb-rates-could-fall-faster-recession-risk-mounts-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y2EWZ3PKN5JEJBWTVAHBPAJZ54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:17:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大就美国汽车关税向世贸组织提起争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织周一表示，加拿大已就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普决定对来自加拿大的汽车和汽车零部件征收25%的关税一事请求与美国进行世贸组织争端磋商。【原文：Canada has requested WTO dispute consultations with the United States over President Donald Trump's decision to impose a 25% duty on cars and car parts from Canada, the World Trade Organization said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-initiates-wto-dispute-over-us-duties-cars-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWN3SF3BRFOGZESRKOEMXVNKW4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:11:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，在美国关税影响下，德国可能面临第三个经济萎缩年]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析人士说，美国宣布的关税将对德国经济造成重大打击，推迟经济复苏，并可能使欧洲最大的经济体历史上首次步入第三年衰退的轨道。【原文：The tariffs announced by the United States will deal a major blow to the German economy, delaying a recovery and possibly putting Europe's biggest economy on track for a third year of recession for the first time in history, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/germany-faces-third-possible-year-contraction-amid-us-tariffs-analysts-say-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTC3FBBAIRL4FEJVDAUTLL2DQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:10:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车咨询公司预测，关税将导致今年美国汽车销量减少 200 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[据底特律地区一家汽车咨询公司预测，如果全球贸易战升级，美国和加拿大今年的汽车销量可能会减少180万辆，并在未来十年停滞不前。【原文：U.S. and Canada auto sales could decline by 1.8 million vehicles this year and be stagnant over the next decade if the global trade war escalates, a Detroit-area automotive advisory firm forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tariffs-will-lead-2-million-fewer-auto-sales-us-this-year-auto-advisory-firm-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYD4V33DTRMLTGSKOLRGCYJVBA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:06:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪在欧洲推出高端品牌 Denza 以支持业务扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪周一在欧洲推出高端品牌Denza，旨在支持其在该地区的扩张，并与宝马和奔驰等高端德国制造商竞争。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle giant BYD launched on Monday its premium Denza brand in Europe, aiming to support its expansion in the region and compete with top-end German manufacturers such as BMW and Mercedes .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-launches-denza-premium-brand-europe-support-expansion-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPX532SUJVM35FYRMY4TYUKVBE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 12:42:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[商品 石油跌至四年低点，金属因经济衰退担忧而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中美贸易战愈演愈烈，引发了对原材料需求的担忧，包括金属和咖啡在内的大多数大宗商品市场下跌。【原文：Oil slid around 3% on Monday to its weakest since 2021, while most commodity markets including metals and coffee declined as the intensifying trade war between the United States and China triggered worries over demand for raw materials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/commodities-oil-drops-four-year-low-metals-fall-recession-fears-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2C3CM47FFLXNOEIYDVEWGXCQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 12:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tinder 母公司 Match 拒绝 Anson Funds，任命电子商务资深人士为董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tinder 母公司 Match Group 回击了激进分子 Anson Funds 对其董事会的提名，并于周一任命经验丰富的电子商务高管达雷尔-卡文斯（Darrell Cavens）为新董事。【原文：Tinder parent Match Group pushed back against activist Anson Funds' nominees to its board, and appointed seasoned e-commerce executive Darrell Cavens as a new director on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/match-group-appoints-seasoned-e-commerce-executive-darrell-cavens-director-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALZ447SLHRL5LC5D262MQOFGTU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 12:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>