<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:16:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:16:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国研究人员利用 Meta's Llama 开发出军用人工智能模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[据学术论文和分析人士称，与中国人民解放军有关联的中国顶级研究机构已经使用 Meta 公开的 Llama 模型开发了一种人工智能工具，用于潜在的军事应用。【原文：Top Chinese research institutions linked to the People's Liberation Army have used Meta's publicly available Llama model to develop an AI tool for potential military applications, according to academic papers and analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinese-researchers-develop-ai-model-military-use-back-metas-llama-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INNW65CMXZMV7LR4QEBCXQOZJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲市场谨慎开启重要月份，美国非农就业值得期待]]></title><description><![CDATA[在投资者等待美国非农就业数据的同时，尽管下周降息已成定局，但亚洲市场在这个可能意义重大的月份一开始就持谨慎态度，周五股市大多走低，国债收益率接近三个月高点。【原文：Asian markets started a likely momentous month on the cautious side, with shares mostly lower and Treasury yields near three-month highs on Friday, while investors wait for U.S. payrolls data, although a rate cut next week is largely baked in.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NOHYOGLWZJPLOZJDKC45AJ3OA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新PMI显示，中国10月工厂活动恢复扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五进行的一项私营部门调查显示，由于新订单的扩大带动了生产增长的回升，中国制造业活动在10月份恢复了增长，这标志着该行业在最后一个季度开始时有所改善。【原文：China's manufacturing activity swung back to growth in October as an expansion in new orders led to a pick-up in production growth, signalling an improvement in the sector at the start of the final quarter, a private-sector survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-oct-factory-activity-returns-expansion-caixin-pmi-shows-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5OXYQGW5VIQLDUULT6NIBNK6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:49:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织警告贸易紧张局势和中国经济增长疲软将给亚洲经济带来风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）周五表示，随着贸易紧张局势的升级、中国房地产行业的困境以及市场进一步动荡的可能性，亚洲经济面临的风险已经增加。【原文：Risks to Asia's economy have increased with escalating trade tensions, China's property sector woes and the potential for further market turbulence clouding the outlook, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/imf-warns-risks-asias-economy-trade-tensions-soft-china-growth-bite-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGGGCTYEIBKTFB7CTZ2CR4QO6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民间调查显示，10月份中国新房价格增长略有加快]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项民间调查显示，在传统的购房旺季--10月份，中国新房价格上涨速度加快，这表明近期的支持措施可能会对受到危机冲击的市场产生一些早期影响。【原文：Prices of new homes in China rose at a faster pace in October, traditionally a peak season for house hunting, a private survey showed on Friday, suggesting that recent support measures could be having some early impact in a crisis-hit market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-new-home-prices-grow-slightly-faster-oct-private-survey-shows-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UEECQFIQNRPYRHIPVILNJ7H46I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊解决 Temu、Shein 的计划？销售更多牙膏]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊推出牙膏等更多日常生活必需品的举措损害了其平均销售价格，但这也是对特姆和Shein等竞争对手的一种防范，因为它们从中国发货的商品价格低得惊人。【原文：Amazon's push to offer more everyday essentials like toothpaste is hurting its average selling prices, but it is also a guard against rivals such as Temu and Shein who offer rock bottom prices on goods they ship from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazons-plan-tackle-temu-shein-sell-more-toothpaste-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZICGKYQJ5IAJNJRYWBN6DE5EE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:17:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民意调查：乘着经济增长的东风，大多数亚洲国家央行的降息步伐将慢于美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的民意调查显示，大多数亚洲国家央行未来一年的降息速度将慢于美国联邦储备委员会，原因是稳健的经济增长缓解了维持货币稳定以对抗美元持续走强的压力。【原文：Most Asian central banks will cut interest rates slower than the U.S. Federal Reserve over the coming year, Reuters polls showed, as solid growth has eased pressure to maintain currency stability against a persistently strong dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/poll-riding-growth-wave-most-asian-central-banks-go-slower-than-fed-rate-cuts-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELWOCNVS5ZJ23M4LBEHR7QJEB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:13:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者关注美国就业报告和大选，美元持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元兑主要货币汇率持稳，投资者在等待美国就业报告，以确认经济在美联储货币政策会议和下周美国总统大选前的韧性。【原文：The dollar steadied against major peers on Friday, as investors awaited the U.S. jobs report to confirm economic resiliency heading into the Federal Reserve's monetary policy meeting and a close-call U.S. presidential election next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-steady-investors-eye-us-jobs-report-election-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXDAC6JADFLO7GVK34NMBZ4WYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，10 月份韩国工厂活动再次萎缩，产出下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项民间调查显示，韩国 10 月份的工厂活动连续第二个月萎缩，产量降幅为 16 个月来最大，这加剧了近期全球需求放缓的迹象。【原文：South Korea's factory activity shrank for a second straight month in October, with output falling by the most in 16 months, a private survey showed on Friday, adding to recent signs of a slowdown in global demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/skorea-factory-activity-shrinks-again-oct-output-drops-pmi-shows-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4XK2R5DOJIQ5KAUXF2YSHYY6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:39:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示：需求下滑，日本工厂加速倒闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项私营部门调查显示，由于国内外需求疲软损害了销售和产出，日本 10 月份的工厂活动以三个月来最快的速度萎缩。【原文：Japan's factory activity shrank at the fastest pace in three months in October as weak domestic and overseas demand hurts sales and output, a private-sector survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-factory-declines-accelerate-demand-sags-pmi-shows-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XY45VCOXHZIXDL6LVYBS2MNDJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行今年将维持现金利率不变，首次降息可能在二月份：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社对经济学家的调查显示，澳大利亚央行将在本周二和今年余下的时间里把关键利率维持在 4.35% 的水平，因为强劲的经济活动和胶着的核心通胀仍然需要采取谨慎的态度。【原文：Australia's central bank will hold its key interest rate at 4.35% on Tuesday and for the rest of the year, according to a Reuters poll of economists, as strong economic activity and sticky core inflation still warrant a cautious approach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/rba-hold-cash-rate-this-year-first-cut-seen-february-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KRMPAN6FVLYNNAO5RDLS4ZLPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国出口增长放缓至 7 个月低点，经济复苏受到打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国 10 月份的出口增长放缓至七个月来的最低点，低于市场预期，这是全球需求降温的一个迹象，给步履蹒跚的经济复苏带来了进一步的压力。【原文：South Korea's export growth slowed to a seven-month low in October, missing market expectations, in a sign of cooling global demand that puts further pressure on a stuttering economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/south-korea-oct-export-growth-slows-seven-month-low-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXXEGCV5PJNBBJ3BDSCUX7HRBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经济表现优异，美元保持强势：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于强劲的国内经济数据以及对美联储降息押注的持续缩减，美元在未来几个月将保持近期的强势。【原文：The U.S. dollar will hold on to its recent strength over coming months on robust domestic economic data and continued scaling back of bets for Federal Reserve interest rate cuts, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/us-economic-outperformance-keep-dollar-strong-2024-11-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDD5SXHI4FLJDFRHACRERU5NY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:16:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官将在年底前对埃隆-马斯克 560 亿美元的特斯拉薪酬做出裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据特拉华州法官致该案律师的信，特拉华州法官正在考虑特斯拉股东的投票是否恢复了埃隆-马斯克 560 亿美元的薪酬方案，该方案已被法院宣布无效，法官将争取在今年做出裁决。【原文：The Delaware judge considering whether a vote by Tesla shareholders reinstated Elon Musk's $56 billion pay package which the court had voided will try to issue a ruling this year, according to the judge's letter to the lawyers in the case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-aims-rule-elon-musks-56-bln-tesla-pay-by-year-end-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IQB6NUXQZP3RNTYC44XGI347Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 23:27:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油涨幅扩大，因有报道称伊朗准备打击以色列]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚市早盘，油价延续涨势，此前有报道称伊朗正准备在未来几天内从伊拉克境内对以色列实施报复性打击。【原文：Oil prices extended gains in early Asian trade on Friday, following reports that Iran was preparing a retaliatory strike on Israel from Iraqi territory in the coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-extends-gains-reports-iran-preparing-strike-israel-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUIEFSCJRZOSPKYBVQC6J2GV54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 22:39:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道工会称波音向罢工工人提出加薪 38% 的改进方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位工会发言人告诉路透社，波音公司周四向美国西海岸的罢工工人提出了一份改进后的合同，其中包括在四年内加薪 38%。【原文：Boeing made an improved contract offer to striking workers on the U.S. West Coast on Thursday, including a 38% pay increase over four years, a union spokesperson told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-makes-improved-38-pay-raise-offer-striking-workers-union-says-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OP4KB3KAJVKLLHHCC7TO53GHVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 22:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称波音公司将提高工资以结束罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉此事的消息人士告诉路透社记者，波音公司预计将于周四向代表该飞机制造商美国西海岸工厂33000多名罢工工人的工会提出一份改进后的工资方案。【原文：Boeing is expected to make an improved wage offer on Thursday to the union representing over 33,000 of the planemaker's striking U.S. West Coast factory workers, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-due-make-improved-wage-offer-bid-end-strike-sources-say-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YVU3GZAOVJB5ORWJDGGS6L5D4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 22:12:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲 邦德义警大显身手，科技滋补品依然炙手可热]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-pix-graphic-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPKE7FQNEJI3PAKP5JELEBHYYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，波音公司解散多元化部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四援引知情人士的话报道，波音公司已经解散了其全球多元化、公平和包容部门。【原文：Boeing has dismantled its global diversity, equity and inclusion department, Bloomberg news reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-dismantles-diversity-department-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENBIIKIPOJNDLMEZWVEK2BVGQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[能源贸易低迷，澳大利亚麦格理上半年利润不及预期；股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚资产规模最大的投资银行麦格理集团（Macquarie Group）周五公布的上半年利润低于分析师预期，原因是稳定的能源市场挤压了其主要盈利部门--大宗商品交易部门，导致其股价大幅下跌。【原文：Macquarie Group , Australia's biggest investment bank by assets, posted first-half profit on Friday that fell short of analyst estimates as stabilising energy markets squeezed the commodities trading unit, its main earner, sending its share price sharply lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/macquarie-group-half-year-profit-misses-estimate-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHEJREYOCVKPNFGMEE2GNM5SCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉加密货币公司 Gotbit 创始人涉嫌电信诈骗]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，加密货币做市商 Gotbit 的创始人因涉嫌代表客户加密货币公司操纵加密货币市场而被起诉。【原文：The founder of cryptocurrency market maker Gotbit was indicted for his alleged role in a wide-ranging conspiracy to manipulate cryptocurrency markets on behalf of client cryptocurrency companies, the U.S. Justice Department said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-indicts-founder-crypto-firm-gotbit-alleged-market-manipulation-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TN7FCMU3ZZNEHFXKZI7VTDXAME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环保人士就美国批准 ioneer 内华达州锂矿提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，环保和原住民团体提起诉讼，质疑美国内政部批准离子公司在内华达州 Rhyolite Ridge 开采锂矿，这是民主党总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）政府批准的首个国内电池金属矿。【原文：Environmental and Indigenous groups on Thursday filed a lawsuit challenging the U.S. Interior Department's approval of ioneer's Rhyolite Ridge lithium mine in Nevada, the first domestic source of the battery metal to be permitted by Democratic President Joe Biden's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/environmentalists-sue-over-us-approval-ioneers-nevada-lithium-mine-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">II6DKTLO2FK6ZP7542WXPA6Y3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:28:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瞻博网络季度业绩超预期，网络设备需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[瞻博网络公司（Juniper Networks）正在被惠普企业公司（Hewlett Packard Enterprise）收购，受网络设备需求的推动，该公司周四公布的第三季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Juniper Networks , which is being bought by Hewlett Packard Enterprise , beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue and profit on Thursday, aided by demand for its networking equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/juniper-beats-quarterly-estimates-networking-gear-demand-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEGADPQQHJNXRGXYWGPWJ7DKCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通就信息披露问题与美国证券交易委员会达成 1 亿美元和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的银行摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）将支付 1 亿美元，以了结美国证券交易委员会对其披露信息误导客户投资 "导管 "产品的指控。【原文：JPMorgan Chase , the largest U.S. bank, will pay $100 million to settle U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charges its disclosures misled customers who invested in "conduit" products, which pooled customer money to invest in private equity or hedge funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-chase-reaches-100-million-settlement-with-sec-over-disclosures-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3VQMG7QYVOSZJC6GGBXX5TH6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:54:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受 iPhone 销售支撑，苹果业绩超出华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四公布的第四财季销售额和利润超出华尔街预期，这主要得益于 iPhone 16 的强劲提前销售。【原文：Apple beat Wall Street sales and profit expectations on Thursday for its fiscal fourth quarter, bolstered by strong early sales of iPhone 16, a set of phones designed for new AI features that was released near the end of the quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-beats-wall-street-estimates-supported-by-iphone-sales-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDC6I42ZRNJ2RAHI3LQUNT76MY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:30:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科特拉能源公司季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[受天然气价格疲软的影响，美国石油和天然气生产商科特拉能源公司（Coterra Energy）周四公布的第三季度利润下降了 22%。【原文：U.S. oil and gas producer Coterra Energy posted a 22% decline in third-quarter profit on Thursday, hurt by weak prices of natural gas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/coterra-energy-posts-lower-quarterly-profit-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVZXZMXKXNLNFPTWYKCMZEOZIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:11:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊公司季度利润、营收均超华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周四公布的第三季度利润和销售额均超出华尔街预期，股价在常规交易时段下跌后，收盘后上涨达 6%。【原文：Amazon.com on Thursday posted third quarter profit and sales that beat Wall Street estimates, sending shares up as much as 6% after the closing bell after they fell during the regular trading session.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazoncom-beats-estimates-quarterly-revenue-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPO2JKXHGRO7XHOSGP4CND7LAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔公布第三季度亏损，但预计第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受减值和重组费用的影响，英特尔周四公布了巨额净亏损，但预计第四季度营收高于预期。【原文：Intel reported a massive net loss on Thursday, weighed down by impairment and restructuring charges, but forecast fourth-quarter revenue above estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-reports-third-quarter-loss-forecasts-q4-revenue-above-estimates-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNV54RQ6MJKYPMT23WNPCOYLBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德成为寻求批准 ETF 股份类别的最新、最大公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德公司（BlackRock Inc.【原文：BlackRock Inc. on Wednesday filed an application with the U.S. Securities &amp; Exchange Commission seeking approval to create exchange-traded fund classes for its mutual funds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-becomes-latest-largest-firm-seek-approval-etf-share-class-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLB5Z4QTARPOVG3R47BOUIOLTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 19:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州男子被控与 CVS 收购案有关的内幕交易罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦检察官周四指控一名宾夕法尼亚州男子涉嫌内幕交易，他利用其家庭伴侣提供的线索，在 CVS Health 去年以 95 亿美元收购初级保健提供商 Oak Street Health 之前进行非法交易。【原文：Federal prosecutors charged a Pennsylvania man on Thursday with insider trading for using tips from his domestic partner to trade illegally ahead of CVS Health's $9.5 billion purchase last year of primary care provider Oak Street Health.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/pennsylvania-man-charged-with-insider-trading-related-cvs-takeover-2024-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJX4WG23NJMXTDEBMIZ4EBGQHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>