<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:38:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:38:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 弗里波特公司认为，如果特朗普宣布铜为关键资源，每年将增加 5 亿美元的收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[Freeport-McMoRan 公司首席执行官凯瑟琳-奎克（Kathleen Quirk）周一表示，希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在宣布其促进美国采矿业发展的计划时，将铜宣布为关键矿产。【原文：Freeport-McMoRan hopes U.S. President Donald Trump declares copper to be a critical mineral when he announces his plan to boost American mining, CEO Kathleen Quirk said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ceraweek-freeport-sees-500-million-annual-boost-if-trump-declares-copper-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFTI7Q426NLVFKCGRGLEC4IWAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:27:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，CoreWeave 在上市前与 OpenAI 签订了价值 120 亿美元的合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周一告诉路透社，由英伟达（Nvidia）支持的人工智能初创公司 CoreWeave 已与 OpenAI 签订了一份为期五年、价值 119 亿美元的合同，将在其上市前提供云计算服务。【原文：CoreWeave, an artificial intelligence startup backed by Nvidia , has signed a five-year contract worth $11.9 billion with OpenAI to provide cloud computing services ahead of its hotly anticipated stock market launch, people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/coreweave-strikes-12-billion-contract-with-openai-ahead-ipo-sources-say-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWXNTLXF3RL33IRRHYUKOGFCEM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽油运输商与殖民地管道公司就条款修改建议发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[至少有四家美国汽油营销商正准备对殖民地管道公司提出法律和监管挑战，因为这些公司认为，拟议中的燃料运输条款变化将损害他们的利润，并推高加油站的燃料价格。【原文：At least four U.S. gasoline marketers are preparing legal and regulatory challenges to the Colonial Pipeline over proposed changes in fuel shipping terms which the companies say will hurt their margins and drive up fuel prices at the pump, sources familiar with the discussions said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/gasoline-shippers-clash-with-colonial-pipeline-proposed-changes-terms-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62IGF2YLFRKGPHYOZ43IHC34QM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 美国液化天然气出口商寻求重新谈判交易，以弥补不断上涨的成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的消息来源和公司声明称，由于建筑、劳动力和借贷成本上升，几家美国液化天然气生产商正试图与买家重新谈判更高的价格。【原文：Several U.S. LNG producers are trying to renegotiate higher prices with buyers as a result of rising construction, labor and borrowing costs, according to sources and company statements reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-us-lng-exporters-seek-renegotiate-deals-cover-rising-costs-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTKHKG27SZJ23L6Q7JCA73HQJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员押注美联储将在经济下滑时快速降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储不会在下周的政策会议上降低利率，但如果对贸易战引发经济衰退的担忧升温成真，美联储可能会在 6 月份快速降低借贷成本。【原文：The Federal Reserve won't lower interest rates at its policy meeting next week, but could deliver the first of a set of rapid-fire reductions in borrowing costs in June if rising fears of an economic downturn triggered by a trade war materialize.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/fed-deliver-rapid-fire-rate-cuts-if-economic-downturn-happens-traders-bet-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CK44HVPNYVILHNPW2KM6KOA2FE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会主席表示，美国证券交易委员会将不再要求加密货币公司注册为交易系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）代理主席周一表示，他已指示工作人员研究如何放弃一项计划，该计划将扩大另类交易系统的定义，把一些加密货币公司包括在内。【原文：The acting chief of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Monday he has directed staff to look at ways to abandon a plan that would have widened the definition of alternative trading systems to include some cryptocurrency firms.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/us-sec-move-away-requiring-crypto-firms-register-trading-systems-chief-says-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMCMOBRVPBM57AGEQLOTNUQKFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，欧盟可能对苹果和 Meta 违反 DMA 规定处以适度罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的人士周一表示，欧盟反垄断监管机构预计将对苹果公司和 Meta Platforms 公司处以适度罚款，因为这两家公司涉嫌违反了旨在约束其权力的具有里程碑意义的规定。【原文：EU antitrust regulators are expected to hand out modest fines to Apple and Meta Platforms for allegedly breaching landmark rules aimed at reining in their power, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/eu-likely-impose-modest-fines-apple-meta-over-dma-breaches-sources-say-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOPWLO57ZNOEBGXMPE5N5Z55KM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行就陷入困境的 4.81 亿美元房地产贷款起诉摩根大通]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）周一起诉摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase），要求为一笔 4.81 亿美元的商业房地产贷款的投资者追回损失。【原文：Wells Fargo sued JPMorgan Chase on Monday to recover losses for investors in a $481 million commercial real estate loan that was allegedly based on a fraudulently inflated financial metric.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/wells-fargo-sues-jpmorgan-over-troubled-481-million-real-estate-loan-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4GKTQO4O5O23PFPWJR4OPLYDQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:45:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦敦劳合社预计洛杉矶野火将造成 23 亿美元净损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦劳合社（Lloyd's of London）周一表示，预计近期的洛杉矶野火将造成 23 亿美元的净损失，该保险市场去年的承保利润也有所下降。【原文：Lloyd's of London said on Monday it expected $2.3 billion in net losses caused by the recent Los Angeles wildfires, as the insurance marketplace reported a dip in underwriting profit for last year.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/lloyds-london-expects-23-billion-net-losses-los-angeles-wildfires-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPMXQWI5HVM4HKJD4K4H2YS5NY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:43:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月份集装箱进口量接近历史最高水平，关税风险迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[供应链技术提供商笛卡尔周一表示，2月份美国集装箱进口量同比增长4.7%，但随着美国与中国和其他主要贸易伙伴的贸易战占据上风，未来几个月可能会降温。【原文：U.S. container import volumes increased 4.7% year-on-year in February, but could cool in coming months as the U.S. trade war with China and other key trading partners takes hold, supply chain technology provider Descartes said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-container-imports-near-record-level-february-tariff-risks-loom-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZTKZOVIXVPFHC4VA6NBQOYKDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普引发的不确定性引发经济担忧，投资者逃离股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[对贸易关税的不确定性将引发经济衰退的担忧正导致投资者逃离股市，这对曾因唐纳德-特朗普总统的议程前景而火热的华尔街来说是一个重大转变。【原文：Fears that uncertainty over trade tariffs will spark an economic downturn are causing investors to flee equities, in a major shift for Wall Street which had been fired-up by the prospect of President Donald Trump's agenda.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-flee-equities-trump-driven-uncertainty-sparks-economic-worry-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSTUGJEA2FIZJDORUN2GKYU4GU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的 DeepSeek 解决了短暂影响其人工智能推理模型的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的 DeepSeek 周一表示，影响其高级 R1 人工智能推理模型的一个问题在短暂中断后已得到解决。【原文：China's DeepSeek said on Monday an issue impacting its advanced R1 artificial intelligence reasoning model was resolved after a brief outage.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chinas-deepseek-says-advanced-ai-reasoning-model-currently-unavailable-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMFDOAKKHFI65H5THHLJTLWTGU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metinvest 首席执行官：乌克兰钢铁产能重建取决于安全保障]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰钢铁巨头 Metinvest 的负责人告诉路透社记者，重建被战争严重破坏的业务将取决于美国和欧洲在与俄罗斯达成的任何停火协议中是否提供强有力的安全保障。【原文：The head of Ukrainian steel giant Metinvest told Reuters that rebuilding its heavily war-damaged operations will hinge on the robustness of U.S. and European security guarantees in any ceasefire deal with Russia.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/rebuilding-ukraine-steel-capacity-hinges-security-guarantees-metinvest-ceo-says-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUCR6GQ2ZNIQFESUMKD75BJEUE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咖啡豆价格飙升，美国咖啡盗窃案激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[据运输公司称，由于去年咖啡豆的价格升至历史最高点，世界上最大的咖啡豆进口国美国的卡车装载绿咖啡豆的盗窃案正在激增。【原文：Theft of truck loads of green coffee beans is surging in the United States, the world's largest importer of the commodity, as prices for the beans increased to all-time highs in the last year, according to transportation companies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/coffee-theft-surges-us-prices-beans-soar-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWDEAPPIFOOZGZJOIRXTCEYWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咖啡豆价格飙升，美国咖啡盗窃案激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[据运输公司称，由于去年咖啡豆的价格升至历史最高点，世界上最大的咖啡豆进口国美国的卡车装载绿咖啡豆的盗窃案正在激增。【原文：Theft of truck loads of green coffee beans is surging in the United States, the world's largest importer of the commodity, as prices for the beans increased to all-time highs in the last year, according to transportation companies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/coffee-theft-surges-us-prices-beans-soar-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWDEAPPIFOOZGZJOIRXTCEYWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱主席告诉 FCA Epstein-Staley 的关系不需要在 2019 年接受董事会审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据法庭文件显示，巴克莱银行董事长奈杰尔-希金斯（Nigel Higgins）认为，在英国金融监管机构对此事进行询问后，该行前首席执行官杰斯-斯塔利（Jes Staley）与已故失宠金融家杰弗里-爱泼斯坦（Jeffrey Epstein）的关系不值得在 2019 年夏天的董事会上讨论。【原文：Barclays chairman Nigel Higgins believed the bank's former CEO Jes Staley's ties with the late disgraced financier Jeffrey Epstein did not warrant a board discussion in the summer of 2019 after Britain's financial regulator inquired over the matter, according to court documents.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-chair-told-fca-epstein-staley-ties-did-not-need-board-review-2019-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNCOPNZRQROJTPI346BDPSDQ5A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：欧盟在特朗普首轮关税中面临哪些挑战？]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，欧盟正准备迎接美国的首轮关税，对铝和钢材进口征收25%的关税，受影响的欧盟进口商品价值超过美国总统唐纳德-特朗普2018年对欧盟金属进口征收的关税。【原文：The European Union is bracing for its first round of U.S. tariffs on Wednesday, 25% tariffs on aluminium and steel imports, affecting more EU imports in value than duties U.S. President Donald Trump imposed on EU metal imports in 2018.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/europe/what-challenges-face-eu-first-round-trump-tariffs-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWKJEOXGGNOSZGOK5P7XTVZ33M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普引发经济衰退担忧，华尔街抛售加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普拒绝预测其关税政策是否会导致经济衰退后，美国主要股指周一下挫，投资者情绪受到影响。【原文：Major U.S. stock indexes sank on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump declined to predict whether his tariff policies could lead to a recession, roiling investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/wall-street-selloff-deepens-trump-sparks-recession-concerns-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGEWS2GEGNKZLI6CIXQQJW4B7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:53:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安大略省对出口到美国的电力征收 25% 的附加费]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大安大略省省长道格-福特（Doug Ford）周一表示，该省将对出口到纽约州、密歇根州和明尼苏达州的电力征收25%的附加费，以抗议美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对加拿大征收关税。【原文：The Canadian province of Ontario is imposing a 25% surcharge on electricity exports to New York state, Michigan and Minnesota to protest against U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on Canada, Premier Doug Ford said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ontario-imposes-25-surcharge-electricity-exports-us-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDB7IR3QYBMLJJKOKMP7NIPBXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Northvolt 股东斯堪尼亚已获得更多电池芯供应商]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典卡车制造商斯堪尼亚（Scania）是陷入困境的电池制造商 Northvolt 的股东和客户，该公司周一告诉路透社，它已找到了另一家电池供应商。【原文：Swedish truckmaker Scania, a shareholder and customer of struggling battery maker Northvolt, told Reuters on Monday it had secured an additional supplier of battery cells.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/northvolt-shareholder-scania-has-secured-additional-supplier-battery-cells-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBBBXCJ3KNNHBKZDUMXT2WQDQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:13:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储：通胀预期稳定，对前景的担忧加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周一发布的一份报告称，尽管美国人对未来通胀路径的预期变化不大，但他们在二月份对经济前景的担忧却有所增加。【原文：Americans grew more worried about the economic outlook in February even as their expectations of the future path of inflation were little changed, a report on Monday from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/ny-fed-worry-over-outlook-increases-amid-stable-inflation-expectations-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3SNWQWUVVODFHGQ6DX44A5DSU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:06:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府推出新的 "自我驱逐 "应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周一推出了一款新的应用程序，允许在美国非法居留的移民 "自行递解出境"，而不是面临可能的逮捕和拘留。【原文：The Trump administration rolled out a new app on Monday that will allow immigrants in the United States illegally to "self deport" rather than face possible arrest and detention, building on President Donald Trump's deportation push.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-launches-new-self-deportation-app-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHOZXSMTUZLALEZJ4P4JC3SEX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街券商开始报道 SailPoint，普遍看好，但认为存在竞争风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街券商周一开始对帆点科技公司（SailPoint Technologies）进行报道，普遍看好该公司，但一些分析师警告说，这家身份安全供应商可能面临更激烈的竞争。【原文：Wall Street brokerages on Monday started coverage on SailPoint Technologies with broadly bullish views, but some analysts warned that the identity security provider could face increased competition.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-brokerages-start-sailpoint-coverage-with-broadly-bullish-view-see-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4ZTXWVNPJOXDPQ3RT2P4Q6JHY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称石油生产商今年不太可能增加支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝克休斯公司（Baker Hughes BKR.O）首席执行官洛伦佐-西蒙内利（Lorenzo Simonelli）周一表示，美国油气生产商今年不太可能增加支出，产量的增加将主要来自效率的提高，而不是新的钻井。【原文：U.S. oil and gas producers are unlikely to increase spending this year and output increases will primarily come from improved efficiencies rather than new drilling, Baker Hughes BKR.O Chief Executive Lorenzo Simonelli said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-baker-hughes-says-oil-producers-unlikely-increase-spending-this-year-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOZ3TAFCARKOJD72EQVWCMOBAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 阿美石油公司首席执行官称，猫王演讲比能源转型计划成功的几率更大]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特国家石油巨头沙特阿美石油公司（Saudi Aramco 2222.SE）首席执行官周一表示，政策制定者和能源高管需要重新思考能源转型计划，停止加倍执行已经失败的转型内容，并强调需要投资化石燃料以满足全球需求。【原文：Policymakers and energy executives need to rethink energy transition plans and stop doubling down on elements of the transition that have failed, the CEO of state oil giant Saudi Aramco 2222.SE said on Monday, stressing the need for investment in fossil fuels to meet global demand.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-more-chance-elvis-speaking-than-energy-transition-plans-succeeding-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47DOAJYKXZNNHCIORWWUGSCA6U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:23:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约州就数据泄露和安全漏洞起诉全州保险公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州周一起诉 Allstate 公司，指控该保险公司的 National General 部门未报告数据泄露事件，暴露了驾驶执照号码，也未制定合理的保障措施来保护投保人的私人信息。【原文：New York state sued Allstate on Monday, accusing the insurer's National General unit of failing to report a data breach that exposed drivers' license numbers, and not developing reasonable safeguards to protect policyholders' private information.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/new-york-sues-allstate-over-data-breach-security-lapses-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T564EKFMZZKDTNQAI4NFU32TOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 美国能源部长称全球变暖是现代经济的副作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）周一表示，全球变暖是建设现代世界的副作用，并誓言结束前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）的气候政策。【原文：US Energy Secretary Energy Secretary Chris Wright said on Monday that global warming is a side effect of building the modern world and vowed to end former President Joe Biden's climate policies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-us-energy-secretary-says-global-warming-side-effect-modern-economy-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGFHQ6EYPJLC3LZURUCZYH4FDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:01:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔暂时停止法国两家主要工厂的生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔公司（ArcelorMittal）周一宣布了一项超过 2.7 亿欧元（2.754 亿美元）的维护计划，其中包括在法国敦刻尔克（Dunkirk）和滨海福斯（Fos-sur-Mer）的工厂停工数月。【原文：ArcelorMittal on Monday announced a more than 270 million euro ($275.4 million) maintenance programme that would include the halt of activities at its plants in Dunkirk and Fos-sur-Mer, France, for several months.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/arcelormittal-temporarily-halt-production-its-two-main-french-plants-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4E2E3F25YJKNTP4YHRFELMOERI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK-加拿大总理阿勒塔表示，加拿大可以增加对美国的石油供应，但也需要新的市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿尔伯塔省省长丹尼尔-史密斯（Danielle Smith）周一表示，该省将继续向美国供应原油，但美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税威胁也凸显了对新市场的需求。【原文：Alberta Premier Danielle Smith said on Monday that the Canadian province would continue to supply crude oil to the United States but that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats also underscored the need for new markets.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ceraweek-canada-could-boost-oil-supplies-us-also-needs-new-markets-alerta-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTYI5QUTKVM5PM5TBYYRB63NAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟贸易首脑称美国不寻求达成避免关税的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国即将对所有进口钢铁和铝征收关税的前两天，欧盟贸易部长周一表示，特朗普政府似乎没有参与避免与欧盟贸易冲突的谈判。【原文：The Trump administration does not seem to be engaging in talks to avert trade conflict with the European Union, the EU's trade chief said on Monday, two days before the United States is set to impose tariffs on all steel and aluminium imports.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/eu-trade-chief-says-us-not-seeking-deal-avert-tariffs-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I76GEFUGAFMF3NGZNUE7MSTP5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:25:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>