<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 03:10:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 03:10:31 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，8月份中国新房价格涨势放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日的一项民间调查显示，8月份中国新房价格涨幅放缓，受危机影响的房地产行业在一系列扶持政策之后正努力寻找底部。【原文：Prices of new homes in China rose at slower pace in August, a private survey showed on Sunday, as the crisis-hit property sector struggles to find its bottom after a slew of supportive policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-new-home-prices-rise-more-slowly-august-survey-shows-2024-09-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BL3J3SPS3NKKNKKFPHGAUA66XQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 02:11:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国出口连续第 11 个月增长，但增速放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国 8 月份出口连续第 11 个月增长，但增长速度低于上个月和市场预期，原因是计算机芯片需求放缓，而汽车销售依然低迷。【原文：South Korea's exports rose an 11th straight month in August, but the pace of growth was weaker than the previous month and market expectations as demand for computer chips slowed, while auto sales remained sluggish.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/south-korea-exports-extend-gains-11th-month-growth-slows-2024-09-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TFZL2I3VJPFJJ7RSHRNEUCE7E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构称福特将因发动机气门问题召回90736辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周六表示，福特将召回90736辆汽车，因为这些汽车的发动机进气阀可能在行驶过程中破裂。【原文：Ford will recall 90,736 vehicles as engine intake valves in the vehicles may break while driving, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-90736-vehicles-over-engine-valve-issue-us-regulators-say-2024-08-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3F4N5ZXKZL35GQMG6JUO23JPM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 09:50:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[硅谷银行中方合作伙伴收购合资企业股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国金融监管部门周五晚些时候表示，硅谷银行在中国的合资企业将成为上海浦东发展银行的全资子公司，并获准更名为上海创新银行。【原文：Silicon Valley Bank's Chinese joint venture will become a wholly owned unit of Shanghai Pudong Development Bank, following approval to change its name to Shanghai Innovation Bank, a Chinese financial regulator said late on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/silicon-valley-banks-chinese-partner-buys-out-stake-joint-venture-2024-08-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJ7IU72ENJN35CINQCIVINR36U</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 04:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Artisan 敦促 Seven&i 在 9 月 19 日前更新收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国基金 Artisan Partners Asset Management 加大了对日本 Seven and i 控股公司的压力，要求董事会在 9 月 19 日前就加拿大 Alimetation Couche-Tard (ACT) 公司的收购要约提供最新信息。【原文：U.S. fund Artisan Partners Asset Management ramped up pressure on Japan's Seven and i holdings , calling on the board to provide an update on a takeover bid from Canada's Alimetation Couche-Tard (ACT) by Sept. 19.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/artisan-urges-seveni-takeover-bid-update-by-sept-19-2024-08-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQUH7ZEFOJPXJJ736P6KFONVRM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 03:00:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 8 月制造业下滑至 6 个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六的一项官方工厂调查显示，中国制造业在8月份放缓至六个月低点，这使人们更加期待决策者将公布新的计划，加大对家庭的刺激力度，减少对基础设施项目的刺激。【原文：China's manufacturing slowed to a six-month low in August, an official factory survey showed on Saturday, raising expectations policymakers will unveil fresh plans to direct more stimulus to households and less to infrastructure projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-august-manufacturing-activity-falls-fourth-month-2024-08-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TX275MLCXBNLHNV4Q5IVIAMGVQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 01:39:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州发布自动驾驶卡车运营法规草案]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州机动车辆管理局周五发布了关于自动驾驶汽车在高速公路上行驶的法规草案，为自动驾驶卡车开始长途运输铺平了道路。【原文：The California Department of Motor Vehicles on Friday issued draft regulations on the operation of autonomous vehicles on highways, paving the way for self-driving trucks to commence long-haul deliveries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/california-issues-draft-regulations-operating-autonomous-trucks-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R54FHH6X65I6RPF3HIGY63QNPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 23:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁巴菲特再次出售价值约 8.45 亿美元的美国银行股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一份监管文件显示，亿万富翁沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）再次减持美国银行股份，出售价值约为 8.45 亿美元的股票。【原文：Billionaire Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway has once again cut its stake in Bank of America with a share sale worth roughly $845 million, a regulatory filing showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/billionaire-buffett-again-sells-bofa-shares-worth-about-845-mln-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QB4XYU4WVVJNFPKNCNKMEQT5VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 23:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局称 SpaceX 猎鹰 9 号运载火箭可在进行探测时恢复飞行作业]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周五表示，在对 "星链 "8-6组飞行任务中出现的异常情况进行全面调查的同时，SpaceX公司的猎鹰9号飞行器可能会恢复飞行。【原文：The SpaceX Falcon 9 vehicle may return to flight operations while the overall investigation of the anomaly during the Starlink Group 8-6 mission remains open, the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/faa-says-spacex-falcon-9-vehicle-may-return-flight-operations-while-probe-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS7AIBBBUBO3DGNA5S6OAUAIHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 22:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美国股市涨势扩大，投资者等待美联储的到来]]></title><description><![CDATA[在市场等待关键就业数据和美联储 9 月份降息预期之际，美国股市涨势扩大，为担心科技股集中度的投资者提供了一个令人鼓舞的信号。【原文：A broadening rally in U.S. stocks is offering an encouraging signal to investors worried about concentration in technology shares, as markets await key jobs data and the Federal Reserve's expected rate cuts in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-us-stock-rally-broadens-investors-await-fed-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUNXJQTCTZMTBETF34AXBTXIIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[药品经销商与美国医疗计划达成 3 亿美元阿片类药物和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的法庭文件显示，美国三大药品分销商已同意支付 3 亿美元，以解决医疗保险公司和福利计划提出的索赔，即它们助长了美国阿片类药物的流行。【原文：The three largest U.S. drug distributors have agreed to pay $300 million to resolve claims by health insurers and benefit plans that they helped fuel the U.S. opioid epidemic, according to court papers filed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drug-distributors-strike-300-mln-opioid-settlement-with-us-health-plans-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YW4SIAD3G5LSBA6ILSPML5YHUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康泰伦特推迟提交年度报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[康泰伦特周五表示，由于需要更多时间完成 "某些流程"，公司无法按时向监管机构提交年度报告。【原文：Catalent said on Friday it was unable to file its annual report with regulators on time as it requires additional time to complete "certain processes".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/catalent-delays-filing-annual-report-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHZ6HZDZLJL6HAE5W25FZFPZJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:33:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称中国中化计划退出与埃克森的美国页岩油气合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，中国国有石油和化工企业中化集团正计划出售其与石油巨头埃克森美孚（Exxon Mobil）在美国一家页岩合资企业中持有的 40% 股份，价值高达 20 亿美元。【原文：Chinese state-backed oil and chemicals company Sinochem is planning to sell its 40% stake in a U.S. shale joint venture with oil major Exxon Mobil , valued upwards of $2 billion, people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/chinas-sinochem-plans-exit-us-shale-jv-with-exxon-sources-say-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGDYY73PIBODZBNGEZSUYOQ4FM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:01:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，罢工迫在眉睫，加拿大不愿介入加航飞行员争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府的一位消息人士本周告诉路透社，如果加拿大航空公司的飞行员罢工，加拿大不愿强迫他们复工，尽管渥太华在本月早些时候采取了这一措施来结束该国两家铁路公司的停工。【原文：Canada is reluctant to force Air Canada's pilots back to work if they go on strike, a government source told Reuters this week, even though Ottawa took that step to end a work stoppage at the country's two railroads earlier this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/strike-looms-canada-unwilling-wade-into-air-canada-pilot-dispute-source-says-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWWN4OZCOFN63O7YRB76SY37EQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 20:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加密货币高管将在华盛顿为哈里斯举办筹款活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币投资者和行业高管呼吁副总统卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）对该行业采取更柔和的监管立场，他们计划在 9 月 13 日的华盛顿筹款活动上为这位民主党提名人筹集至少 10 万美元。【原文：Cryptocurrency investors and industry executives calling on Vice President Kamala Harris to pursue a softer regulatory stance on the industry are planning to raise at least $100,000 for the Democratic nominee at a Sept. 13 Washington fundraiser.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-crypto-executives-throw-washington-fundraiser-harris-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLWAR5E6MJORJJSTNZGLSHWRG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 20:43:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音新任首席执行官与 FAA 局长举行首次会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司新任首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）本周早些时候会见了美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）负责人。【原文：New Boeing CEO Kelly Ortberg met earlier this week with the head of the Federal Aviation Administration as the planemaker faces numerous regulatory issues and increased scrutiny, an agency official confirmed Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/new-boeing-ceo-holds-first-meeting-with-faa-chief-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LV7HQ46ZJ5K5RNN2KNFE6LMOVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 19:52:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西在所得税增税法案中针对银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西政府周五向国会提交了一份法案，作为增加收入努力的一部分，该法案增加了部分所得税，包括对银行进行更明显的加息。【原文：Brazil's government submitted a bill to Congress on Friday that increases some income taxes as part of a revenue-raising effort, including a more pronounced rate hike for banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/brazil-targets-banks-income-tax-hike-bill-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNCYMSVYONMALGYH7A7CBM42XY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 19:49:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：高盛将裁员 1300 多人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，高盛计划在其全球员工队伍中裁减 1300 多名员工，作为裁减绩效低下员工的年度审查程序的一部分。【原文：Goldman Sachs plans to cut more than 1,300 employees from its global workforce as part of an annual review process to cull low performers, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-lay-off-over-1300-workers-wsj-reports-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOSIYYVNBJPMFNAUB3W3POB4GU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 19:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西财政部长表示，巴西政府将在 2024 年底实现财政目标容忍范围内的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西财政部长费尔南多-哈达德（Fernando Haddad）周五表示，如果国会批准对工资税减免的补偿，政府今年的财政收支应在财政目标的容忍范围内。【原文：Brazil Finance Minister Fernando Haddad said on Friday that the government should close this year within the tolerance band of its fiscal target if Congress approves the compensation for payroll tax waivers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/brazils-government-end-2024-within-fiscal-target-tolerance-band-finance-minister-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WE7HXHM4EBNENJLRNZUAP7IY2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 18:31:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国要求就新数字服务税与加拿大进行贸易争端磋商]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登-哈里斯政府周五表示，美国已要求与加拿大就其新数字服务税进行贸易争端解决磋商，并补充说这一 "歧视性 "税收似乎不符合加拿大的北美贸易协议义务。【原文：The U.S. has requested trade dispute settlement consultations with Canada over its new digital services tax, the Biden-Harris administration said on Friday, adding that the "discriminatory" tax appears inconsistent with Canada's North American trade deal obligations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-requests-trade-dispute-consultations-with-canada-over-new-digital-services-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVTK5Y7KEFPK7ASOYR23BNCKGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 18:09:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普会如何试图瓦解拜登的气候遗产？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在总统竞选中提出了一项能源政策纲领，其核心是最大限度地提高美国的燃料和电力产出，部分手段是废除拜登政府应对气候变化的核心努力。【原文：Donald Trump’s presidential campaign has laid out an energy policy platform centered around maximizing U.S. fuel and power output, in part by dismantling the Biden administration’s centerpiece efforts to fight climate change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/how-trump-would-seek-dismantle-bidens-climate-legacy-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUODV7ECUROLVMD732MUYSNXUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马自达北美任命大村达郎为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[马自达周五任命大村达郎（Tatsuro Omura）为其北美业务的首席财务官。【原文：Mazda on Friday named Tatsuro Omura as the chief financial officer of its North American operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mazda-north-america-names-tatsuro-omura-cfo-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQRZ5KGZLZPERERWBLXZCDCR3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:11:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 "假新闻 "肆虐之际，巴西法官起诉马斯克的 X 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西法官亚历山大-德-莫赖斯（Alexandre de Moraes）威胁要关闭亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体平台 "X"（X），这只是他对被认为是对民主的攻击和在政治上利用虚假信息的无情讨伐的最新一章。【原文：Brazilian judge Alexandre de Moraes' threats to shut down billionaire Elon Musk's social media platform X are just the latest chapter in a no-holds-barred crusade against perceived attacks on democracy and the political use of disinformation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-judge-takes-musks-x-fake-news-crusade-ramps-up-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WT5L7RXUUBI6LOJUPWY33IDIAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CrowdStrike 公司高管将就 IT 故障向国会作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[9 月 24 日，CrowdStrike 公司的一名高级管理人员将在美国众议院小组委员会上就该公司软件更新错误导致全球 IT 故障一事作证。【原文：A senior executive at CrowdStrike will testify before a U.S House of Representatives subcommittee on Sept. 24 on the company's faulty software update that caused a global IT outage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/crowdstrike-exec-testify-before-congress-it-outage-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIPALWG4R5K6TI22S3USXG6LRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：巴西航空工业公司寻求奥利弗-怀曼公司帮助其开拓美国防务市场，并对 C-390 的销售虎视眈眈]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）已聘请咨询公司奥利弗-怀曼（Oliver Wyman）帮助其开拓美国国防市场，这家巴西飞机制造商国防部门的负责人表示，该公司正着眼于向世界头号经济体出售其 C-390 军用货机。【原文：Embraer has hired consultancy firm Oliver Wyman to help it explore the U.S. defense market, the head of the Brazilian planemaker's defense unit said, as it eyes selling its C-390 military cargo aircraft to the world's No. 1 economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/embraer-taps-oliver-wyman-help-it-us-defense-market-eyeing-c-390-sales-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJFJGLJKHFOXLDTVBVRTORXFXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥迪销售主管离职，由保时捷欧洲区负责人接任]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥迪公司周五表示，奥迪销售主管希尔德加德-沃特曼（Hildegard Wortmann）已选择退居二线，她的职位将由保时捷公司欧洲区负责人马尔科-舒伯特（Marco Schubert）接替。【原文：Audi's sales chief Hildegard Wortmann has chosen to step back from her role and will be replaced by Marco Schubert, head of Europe at Porsche AG, Audi said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/audi-sales-chief-steps-back-be-replaced-by-porsche-europe-head-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JA2PWC2HMNNQRB2TVMR3D47JRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[密歇根大学数据显示，美国消费者近期通胀预期为2020年以来最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者认为明年的通胀将继续放缓，周五公布的8月份物价增长预期指数为2020年底以来的最低水平。【原文：U.S. consumers see inflation continuing to moderate in the next year, with a gauge of price growth expectations published on Friday at the lowest level in August since late 2020.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumers-near-term-inflation-expectation-lowest-since-2020-umich-data-shows-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IW43PHQU3FPP5LRNFNHTGDQNRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺福克南方公司与另外五个工会达成临时协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铁路运营商诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern）周五表示，该公司已与五个工会达成了为期五年的临时劳资协议。【原文：Norfolk Southern has reached tentative, five-year labor agreements with five unions, the U.S. railroad operator said on Friday, at a time when thousands of employees in the industry are negotiating for better pay and working conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/norfolk-southern-reaches-tentative-agreements-with-five-more-labor-unions-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7W7DX4XORPVLDZRG6URYWFKSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度法庭批准迪士尼与 Reliance 媒体资产合并案]]></title><description><![CDATA[信实公司周五表示，印度公司法庭已批准信实工业公司和迪斯尼公司以 85 亿美元合并印度媒体资产。【原文：An Indian company tribunal has approved the $8.5 billion merger of Reliance Industries and Disney's Indian media assets, Reliance said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/indian-tribunal-approves-disney-reliance-media-assets-merger-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJZHG4Y6URPO3PENYOC3WXL6DM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:10:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国务院称 RTX 将因出口错误支付 2 亿美元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院周四的记录显示，RTX 公司将支付 2 亿美元的罚款，以了结其违反出口法，与包括中国在内的违禁国家交换数据和产品的指控。【原文：RTX Corp will pay a $200 million fine to settle allegations it violated export laws by exchanging data and products with prohibited countries including China, State Department records dated Thursday said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtx-pay-200-million-fine-export-mistakes-state-department-says-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPDXS5L56RNZFJPHODSPJINNBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>