<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:04:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:04:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：看到低收入消费者受到挤压，零售商瞄准 10 美元及以下的礼品]]></title><description><![CDATA[塔吉特（Target）和沃尔玛（Walmart）等零售商正在货架上摆放更多价格低于 10 美元的玩具和礼物，如芭比娃娃，这一策略旨在吸引手头拮据的购物者。【原文：Retailers including Target and Walmart are stocking shelves with more toys and gifts such as Barbies that cost less than $10 this holiday season, a strategy aimed at attracting cash-strapped shoppers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/seeing-low-income-consumers-squeezed-retailers-target-10-under-gifts-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZV37Q7NZVK7HCLN7EWJP6H5SQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WiWo 报道：诺华关闭 Morphosys，约 330 个工作岗位受影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[据德国新闻媒体 WirtschaftsWoche 周四报道，瑞士制药集团诺华正在对其年初收购的德国生物技术公司 Morphosys 进行清盘，称将有 330 个工作岗位受到影响。【原文：Swiss pharmaceutical group Novartis is winding up the German biotech company Morphosys, which it acquired at the beginning of the year, German news outlet WirtschaftsWoche reported on Thursday, saying 330 jobs would be affected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/some-330-jobs-hit-novartis-closes-morphosys-wiwo-reports-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXQBRRYIWRKANFZDAJDLPHFEP4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 10:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储认为降息次数将减少，华尔街大跌后期货持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周四走高，原因是投资者消化了美联储关于明年降息幅度低于预期和通胀率上升的预测。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Thursday as investors digested the Federal Reserve's projections of fewer-than-expected interest rate cuts and higher inflation next year that pummeled Wall Street a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-steady-after-wall-street-swoons-fed-view-fewer-rate-cuts-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VHD35DMVJN6BIFGE4PXYP7JCY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 10:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普的推动下，交易商预计 2025 年并购总额将超过 4 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家们预计，受美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺减少监管、降低企业税和广泛亲商立场的影响，明年全球交易额将超过 4 万亿美元，达到四年来的最高水平。【原文：Bankers expect global deal volumes to surpass $4 trillion next year, the highest in four years, buoyed by U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's promise of less regulation, lower corporate taxes and a broadly pro-business stance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/dealmakers-eye-4-trillion-plus-ma-haul-2025-trump-boost-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3G5UTZOHRNE3BYUJ2WBJ37VOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 10:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敲定向 SK Hynix 提供 4.58 亿美元的美国芯片封装厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周四敲定向 SK Hynix 发放高达 4.58 亿美元的政府补助金，用于资助其在印第安纳州的先进芯片封装厂和人工智能产品研发机构。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department on Thursday finalized an award to SK Hynix of up to $458 million in government grants to help fund an advanced chip packaging plant and research and development facility for artificial intelligence products in Indiana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-finalizes-458-million-award-sk-hynix-us-chips-packaging-facility-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYIM6H4S5JLJ7KSIRDJ4D2EBHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 10:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上台后印美贸易会是什么样子]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度正在为可能与美国进行的贸易谈判做准备，目的是在当选总统唐纳德-特朗普上台后增加美国公司的投资和提高出口。【原文：India is preparing for possible trade talks with the United States, aiming for increased investments from U.S. companies and higher exports once President-elect Donald Trump takes office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/what-india-us-trade-could-look-like-after-trump-takes-office-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OB2HJGV7GVJYNH2IGBIZLV42PE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:49:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本田与日产潜在合作的背后，是中国电动汽车带来的生存威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[有些联合是迫不得已，有些则是出于方便。就本田和日产的潜在合并而言，在中国竞争对手席卷全球之际，这主要是为了防御。【原文：Some unions are born of necessity, others from convenience. In the case of Honda and Nissan's potential merger, it is mostly defensive as Chinese rivals take the world by storm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/behind-potential-honda-nissan-tie-up-existential-threat-posed-by-chinese-evs-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3SHU4CUMVMWVO2AGJ6EY7LFT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾华航将价值 119 亿美元的飞机交易分给波音和空客]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾的中华航空公司（China Airlines）将在波音和欧洲竞争对手空中客车公司（Airbus）之间平分其长途机队的更新订单，并从美国飞机制造商那里购买货机，这笔交易受到密切关注，价值近 120 亿美元。【原文：Taiwan's China Airlines will split an order for its long-haul fleet renewal between Boeing and European rival Airbus and buy freighters from the U.S. planemaker in a closely watched deal worth almost $12 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/taiwans-china-airlines-orders-119-bln-boeing-airbus-jets-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SYSVMF4TBIRRAY6EFZ5LJUUPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 将日本富士软的要约收购期延长至 1 月 9 日]]></title><description><![CDATA[KKR 周四将其对富士软的要约收购期延长至 1 月 9 日，以与竞争对手美国私募股权公司贝恩资本争夺这家日本软件制造商的控制权。【原文：KKR extended on Thursday its tender offer period for Fuji Soft to Jan. 9 as it battles rival U.S. private equity firm Bain Capital for control of the Japanese software maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-extends-tender-offer-period-japans-fuji-soft-jan-9-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJ765D7IAJJ4DESL4YUAWEZV4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的鹰派倾向令新兴市场急于挽救货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美联储表示明年可能不会大幅降息令市场震惊数小时后，从巴西到印尼的各国央行争相捍卫其陷入困境的货币。【原文：Central banks from Brazil to Indonesia scrambled to defend their struggling currencies on Thursday, hours after the Federal Reserve jolted markets by indicating it may not cut rates by much next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/feds-hawkish-tilt-has-emerging-markets-scurrying-save-currencies-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAYQLEBVLBPDHNGZQHAIVR7KKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 08:50:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田在新闻发布会上的讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周四维持利率不变，但一位持反对意见的董事会成员提议提高借贷成本，这表明该央行仍将在明年初收紧政策。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates unchanged on Thursday but one dissenting board member's proposal to push up borrowing costs showed the central bank remains on track to tighten policy early next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/boj-governor-uedas-comments-news-conference-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N37EQNYOLBL4XB2HEYEZUAX3QY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 06:41:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高管表示，RTX 的目标是在 3 年内将印度员工人数增加 14]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空航天和国防巨头 RTX 公司的高层管理人员告诉路透社，该公司计划在 2027 年之前为其在印度的 7000 多名员工增聘 1000 人，因为该公司正在寻找更多的工程师和数据科学家来支持其全球业务。【原文：U.S. aerospace and defence giant RTX Corp plans to hire 1,000 more people to its 7,000-strong workforce in India by 2027, its top executives told Reuters, as it looks for more engineers and data scientists to power its global operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtx-aims-boost-india-headcount-by-14-3-years-execs-say-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YDDSRD3AFJFPMHYFOVIXPPXQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 06:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利债券有望在 2025 年获得收益，而德国和法国的收益将受到影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，由于德国和法国的不确定性削弱了投资者对意大利政府债券的信心，意大利一反常态的政治稳定很可能在明年提振其政府债券。【原文：Italy's uncharacteristic political stability is likely to boost its government bonds next year, analysts say, as uncertainty over Germany and France undermines investor confidence in them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/italys-bonds-poised-gains-expense-germany-france-2025-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTCNYQBBQNPI5PKZ7O23AI5RXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据中央社报道，富士康高管在法国讨论从雷诺手中收购日产股份事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 "中央社 "周四报道，台湾合同制造商富士康的一名高级主管正在法国讨论从日本汽车制造商最大股东雷诺手中收购日产汽车股份的可能性。【原文：A senior executive of Taiwan-based contract manufacturer Foxconn is in France to discuss a potential stake purchase in Nissan Motor from the Japanese automaker's biggest shareholder Renault , Central News Agency reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/foxconn-exec-france-discuss-nissan-stake-purchase-renault-central-news-agency-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXTSB3WMFFJTJBYXTVY7K2LIVA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储发出减少降息信号后，美股面临收益率上升的不利因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市的反弹遇到了新的障碍--随着美联储发出 2025 年降息次数减少的信号，国债收益率的上升可能会带来问题。【原文：The rally in U.S. stocks is encountering a fresh hurdle -- a potentially problematic rise in Treasury yields as the Federal Reserve signals fewer interest rate cuts for 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-stocks-face-headwind-rising-yields-after-fed-signals-fewer-rate-cuts-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJ7NMHEM3RIDXFU5JOMATYSKEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 05:34:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 日本按兵不动，英国央行下一步行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4T3IC2X2JRIZHFYRZCYVTJG73Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 05:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易商预计 2025 年并购总额将超过 4 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）承诺减少监管、降低企业税和广泛支持商业立场的影响，顶级交易商预计明年全球并购（M&amp;A）规模将超过 4 万亿美元，达到四年来的最高水平。【原文：Top dealmakers expect global mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A)volumes to surpass $4 trillion next year, the highest in four years, buoyed by U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's promise of less regulation, lower corporate taxes and a broadly pro-business stance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/dealmakers-eye-4-trillion-plus-ma-haul-2025-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7NHVMJUPNKBRAGV2KF5PMFZOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 05:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ACEA 称 11 月欧洲汽车销量下降，法国和意大利居首]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的行业数据显示，受法国和意大利大幅下滑以及德国停滞不前的影响，欧洲新车销量继 10 月份出现微弱增长后，11 月份再次转为负增长。【原文：New car sales growth in Europe turned negative again in November, after showing a meagre growth in October, weighed by sharp declines in France and Italy, and a stagnation in Germany, industry data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-car-sales-fall-november-led-by-france-italy-acea-says-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SQ5WGFHOVJ2RBO75SL6UEK53U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 05:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，苹果正与腾讯和字节跳动洽谈在中国推出人工智能功能的事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟知内情的消息人士透露，苹果公司正在与腾讯和 TikTok 的所有者字节跳动洽谈将其人工智能模型整合到在中国销售的 iPhone 中的事宜。【原文：Apple is in talks with Tencent and TikTok owner ByteDance about integrating their artificial intelligence models into iPhones sold in China, according to three sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/apple-talks-with-tencent-bytedance-roll-out-ai-features-china-sources-say-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJ7WF7RGJFKRHA65S5IYCCVS64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 04:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，大众汽车与工会仍在就工厂关闭和减薪问题进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，由于双方仍未达成协议，大众汽车与工会就工厂关闭和减薪问题的谈判预计将持续到本周四。【原文：Talks between Volkswagen and labour unions over plant closures and pay cuts are expected to last well into Thursday as both sides have still not reached a deal, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-unions-still-locked-talks-over-plant-closures-pay-cuts-sources-say-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHVUE4YATBMRXAZ3KCVQC752KE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 03:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[发生安全事故后，美国联邦航空局结束对西南航空公司的审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周三表示，已完成对西南航空公司（Southwest Airlines）的安全审查，该公司是在一系列事件（包括一些引起严重关切的事件）之后于 7 月份开业的。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said Wednesday it had completed a safety review of Southwest Airlines it opened in July after a series of incidents including some that raised serious concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-ends-review-southwest-airlines-after-safety-incidents-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SX53X3BJ5JI7JG4DLOVUAXEEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 03:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社称，大众汽车接近与工会达成协议，以维持汽车工厂的运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四援引知情人士的话报道，大众汽车和工会即将达成一项协议，在不关闭德国工厂的情况下重组大众汽车品牌。【原文：Volkswagen and labour unions are nearing an agreement to restructure the brand without closing factories in Germany, Bloomberg reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-nears-deal-with-unions-keep-car-plants-open-bloomberg-says-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AB4PBXPHJBK7ZF7YG2HQ6MN564</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 03:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行以 8-1 的投票结果维持利率稳定，董事会成员田村表示反对]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周四维持利率稳定，凸显出决策者倾向于花更多时间仔细研究工资上涨是否会扩大范围，并使通胀率持久保持在2%的目标附近。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady on Thursday, underscoring policymakers' preference to spend more time scrutinising whether wage hikes will broaden and keep inflation durably around its 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/boj-keeps-rates-steady-by-8-1-vote-board-member-tamura-dissents-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74YRV4MB2FLSBLHYS43R6YH33Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 03:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美联储鹰派影响，韩元创 2009 年 3 月以来最弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）对更多降息采取谨慎立场所引发的避险情绪以及国内政治不确定性的影响，韩元周四跌至15年来的最弱水平。【原文：The South Korean won dropped to its weakest level in 15 years on Thursday, weighed down by risk-averse sentiment sparked by the U.S. Federal Reserve's cautious stance on more interest rate cuts, on top of domestic political uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/south-korean-won-hits-weakest-since-march-2009-hawkish-fed-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBDVY2PPVRJNRDV2JHY6PJVDBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储发出放缓宽松信号后，石油因需求担忧而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）表示将在 2025 年放慢降息步伐，从而可能影响燃料需求之后，周四早盘油价下跌。【原文：Oil prices fell in early trading on Thursday after the U.S. Federal Reserve signalled that it would slow the pace of interest rate cuts in 2025, potentially impacting fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-falls-demand-concerns-after-fed-signals-slower-easing-ahead-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKSJJUP3CJNPPFLQLBSC6XPCME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储放缓降息步伐，亚洲股市大幅下挫，日本央行尚未做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）警告未来一年将放缓降息步伐，以及投资者为日本央行的政策决定做好准备之后，亚洲股市下滑，债券收益率上升，美元徘徊在两年高点附近。【原文：Asian stocks slid, bond yields rose and the dollar was perched near a two-year high on Thursday after the U.S. Federal Reserve cautioned it would ease the pace of rate cuts in the coming year and investors braced for a Bank of Japan policy decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNCKW37GMJLZJESP2WRFRNQNV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:27:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊工人将在繁忙假期期间在美国多个仓库举行罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[数以千计的亚马逊公司（Amazon.com AMZN.O）员工将于美国东部时间周四上午 6 点（格林尼治标准时间 11 点）在圣诞节前的最后几天离开工作岗位，因为工会官员称该零售商未能坐到谈判桌前。【原文：Thousands of Amazon.com AMZN.O workers will walk off the job on Thursday at 6 a.m. ET (1100 GMT), in the crucial final days before Christmas, after union officials said the retailer failed to come to the bargaining table.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-workers-strike-multiple-us-warehouses-during-busy-holiday-season-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPXH7LI6GZJLBPWF23HJJXJN4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因美联储鹰派前景而大幅走高，日元等待日本央行出手]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储发出放缓2025年降息步伐的信号后，美元周四一度触及两年高点，而在日本央行（BOJ）当天晚些时候做出政策决定前，日元则跌至一个月低点。【原文：The dollar flirted with a two-year peak on Thursday after the Federal Reserve signalled a slower pace of rate cuts in 2025, while the yen slid to a one-month low ahead of a policy decision by the Bank of Japan (BOJ) later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-charges-ahead-hawkish-fed-outlook-yen-awaits-boj-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBKQF3HVRJPEDKREE2HKDAGILQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士软公司创始家族确认支持贝恩 20 亿美元的恶意收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本 IT 公司富士软的创始家族周三与贝恩联合发表声明称，重申支持私募股权公司贝恩资本的收购要约，但遭到富士软董事会的反对。【原文：The founding family of Japanese IT firm Fuji Soft on Wednesday reiterated its support for a takeover bid by private equity firm Bain Capital that is opposed by Fuji Soft's board, it said in a statement jointly released with Bain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/fuji-soft-founding-family-affirms-support-bains-2-bln-hostile-takeover-bid-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GFOR53P3Q5N7FJLBLH2OSCPYBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普尚未上任，已成为全球经济政策的风云人物]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）即将上任，本周全球开始认真对待这届政府的经济问题，一些美联储官员预计通胀率将上升，利率将受到限制，加拿大官员因未来关税预算而意外辞职，比特币的潜在地位升级受到高度关注。【原文：The world's economic reckoning with the incoming administration of U.S. President-elect Donald Trump began in earnest this week, with some Federal Reserve officials penciling in estimates for higher inflation and restrictive interest rates, a surprise resignation in Canada over budgeting for prospective tariffs and a hyper focus on a potential status upgrade for bitcoin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-not-yet-office-already-figure-global-economic-policy-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2ZUQVKX4ZJKXIIUI67WUYTXPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>