<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:40:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:40:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[硅谷银行前所有者获准结束破产程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[倒闭的硅谷银行的前所有者 SVB 金融集团周五获得美国法官的许可，将其资产移交给债权人并结束破产。【原文：SVB Financial Group, the former owner of failed Silicon Valley Bank, received a U.S. judge's permission on Friday to turn over its assets to creditors and end its bankruptcy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/silicon-valley-banks-former-owner-gains-approval-end-bankruptcy-2024-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GTBMD5LWRK5FOLHYTFLSCB2KQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:39:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴尔金在公共广播公司节目中表示，他不会预先判断下一次会议将采取什么行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）表示，在周五公布了意外疲软的美国就业数据后，他还不准备改变其货币政策前景，即使华尔街转向了积极降息的预期。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said he is not ready to change his monetary policy outlook after the release of unexpectedly weak U.S. jobs data on Friday, even as Wall Street shifted toward expectations of aggressive interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-barkin-tells-pbs-program-he-wont-prejudge-what-do-next-meeting-2024-08-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LORMRUA5Y5O35I3GE5DYBZXISM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，对冲基金在经济放缓的忧虑中逐渐看跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）在给客户的一份说明中说，截至8月1日的一周里，全球对冲基金继续在投资组合中增加看跌股票的押注，因为新的数据引发了对美国经济放缓速度超过预期的担忧。【原文：Global hedge funds continued to add bearish equity bets to portfolios in the week to Aug. 1 when fresh data sparked fears the U.S. economy is slowing faster than anticipated, Goldman Sachs said in a note to clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-grow-bearish-amid-economic-slowdown-jitters-goldman-says-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKJUT26EHNJZLAAGWVFUB2IUBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[50 多名美国议员和 21 个州在 TikTok 诉讼案中支持司法部]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 21 个州和 50 多名立法者周五支持司法部为一项法律辩护，该法律要求总部位于中国的字节跳动公司在 1 月 19 日前出售 TikTok 在美国的资产，否则将面临禁令。【原文：A group of 21 states and more than 50 U.S. lawmakers on Friday backed the Justice Department in its defense of a law that requires China-based ByteDance to sell TikTok's U.S. assets by Jan. 19 or face a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/more-than-50-us-lawmakers-21-states-back-doj-tiktok-lawsuit-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBFZJFN4BNK6XLRSZFTHCAVJAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚央行技术团队将 2024 年通胀展望上调至 5.7]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚中央银行技术小组在周五公布的一份季度报告中称，该行将今年的通胀预期从之前的 5.5% 下调至 5.7。【原文：The technical team of Colombia's central bank revised its inflation outlook for the year to 5.7, from a previous 5.5%, it said in a quarterly report published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-central-bank-technical-team-raises-2024-inflation-outlook-57-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SY3HVC2RCJLRNE4K3XNQFWHPPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:46:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通考虑就 Zelle 起诉消费者监督机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周五表示，正在考虑是否就对 Zelle 支付应用的调查起诉美国政府消费者监督机构。【原文：JPMorgan Chase said on Friday it is considering whether to sue a U.S. government consumer watchdog over inquiries into the Zelle payment app.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/jpmorgan-considers-suing-consumer-watchdog-over-zelle-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTDRTXQPQVIWNA4O366NAFVJG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:57:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受疲软电影阵容影响，AMC 娱乐公司第二季度转入亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[AMC Entertainment Holdings 第二季度出现亏损，而去年同期则实现盈利，原因是去年好莱坞双罢工的影响仍未消除，导致主要影院上映的影片数量有限。【原文：AMC Entertainment Holdings posted a loss for the second quarter compared to a profit in the same period last year hurt by the lingering impact of last year's dual Hollywood strikes, which led to a limited number of major theatrical releases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/amc-entertainment-swings-loss-second-quarter-hurt-by-weak-movie-lineup-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAGXXBKPTJPMFKWRJ4QXCXXQDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业报告疲软，华尔街认为 2024 年美联储将加大宽松力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份出人意料地疲软的美国 6 月份就业报告，使华尔街对经济软着陆的信心转变为对经济衰退迫在眉睫的近乎恐慌，促使各大公司改变了对美联储今年宽松政策的预测，转而采取更激进的降息措施。【原文：A surprisingly weak U.S. employment report for June has turned Wall Street confidence on a soft landing into near panic that a recession is looming, prompting major firms to change forecasts for Federal Reserve easing this year to more aggressive interest rate cutting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-sees-bigger-2024-fed-easing-after-soft-jobs-report-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAGG4ZC76VM3PHLEQLRRYOZ73U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:57:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经济衰退恐慌助推债券飙升，收益率曲线翻转在望]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国降息预期的急剧重新定价可能会给因经济数据疲软而引发的债券大涨火上浇油，因为投资者正在努力应对美联储可能需要以比预期快得多的速度放松对经济的严格控制，以避免经济衰退。【原文：A sharp repricing in U.S. interest rate cut expectations could give more fuel to a searing bond rally triggered by weakening economic data, as investors grapple with the possibility the Federal Reserve may need to loosen its tight grip on the economy much faster than anticipated to avoid a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-recession-scare-fuels-searing-rally-bonds-yield-curve-flip-view-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHWVCIRQDRNDHGUVZDJUFA6OEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储古尔斯比：不希望 "击穿 "充分就业]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，美国央行应该以 "稳健 "的方式行事，这是对市场匆忙下注美联储将在9月份对7月份疲软的就业数据报告做出比通常幅度更大的半点降息反应的温和回击。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee said on Friday the U.S. central bank should move in a "steady" way, a mild pushback against the rush of market bets that the Fed will react to a report of weak July jobs data with a bigger-than-usual half-point rate cut in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-dont-want-blow-through-full-employment-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGMTOMLWKVIYZCPZJ4CYOU5KCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就业报告发布后，我们有四个理由喘口气]]></title><description><![CDATA[令人失望的美国 7 月份就业报告引发了金融市场的 "疯狂星期五"，并引发了对美联储下月降息幅度预期的全面重置。【原文：The disappointing U.S. employment report for July unleashed a "Freakout Friday" moment in financial markets and triggered a wholesale resetting of expectations for how much the Federal Reserve might cut interest rates next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/four-reasons-take-breath-after-us-jobs-report-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2FZ2H3QAFICLEKAFRPEYHE2GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 称礼来公司所有剂量的减肥和糖尿病药物现已上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周五更新的短缺药品清单显示，礼来公司的减肥药Zepbound和糖尿病药Mounjaro的所有剂量现在都有供应。【原文：All doses of Eli Lilly's weight-loss drug Zepbound and diabetes drug Mounjaro are now available, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's updated shortage list showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-says-all-doses-lillys-weight-loss-diabetes-drug-now-available-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZCLGXA3JBJA7AUGNWTQHXDJNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与 Character.AI 签订许可协议，并聘用其联合创始人]]></title><description><![CDATA[聊天机器人制造商 Character.AI 表示，它已与 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌达成协议，允许谷歌获得 Character.AI 当前大型语言模型技术的非独家许可。【原文：Chatbot maker Character.AI said it has entered into an agreement with Alphabet's Google, allowing it a non-exclusive license for Character.AI's current large language model technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/google-hires-characterai-cofounders-licenses-its-models-information-reports-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YP6HJQMMXVKCXDZRLE35AMAGNU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:22:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，巴西国家石油公司对 Galp 纳米比亚勘探区的竞标将包括至少一个合作伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士告诉路透社，巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）在竞购 Galp Energia 公司位于纳米比亚的 Mopane 石油勘探区 40% 的股份时，将至少包括一个合作伙伴。【原文：Brazil's Petrobras will include at least one partner in its bid for a 40% stake in Galp Energia's Mopane oil prospect in Namibia, two sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/petrobras-bid-galps-namibia-prospect-include-least-one-partner-sources-say-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YM22YVGQIRMS3C6XA2FUEMIEPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:18:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，数据提供商邓白氏正在探索出售事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据和分析服务提供商邓白氏公司（Dun &amp; Bradstreet）市值近 80 亿美元（包括债务），该公司正在探索包括潜在出售在内的各种选择，熟悉此事的人士周五表示。【原文：Data and analytics provider Dun &amp; Bradstreet , which has a market value of nearly $8 billion including debt, is exploring options including a potential sale, people familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/data-provider-dun-bradstreet-explores-sale-sources-say-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPGLMWSESRKH3NVL2IX5MYADIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道伊坎支持的炼油厂与债权人集团在 Citgo 拍卖会上一决雌雄]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟知内情的人士透露，一家由激进投资者卡尔-伊坎（Carl Icahn）支持的炼油企业和一群持有对委内瑞拉债权的债权人正在美国法院拍卖 Citgo Petroleum 的最后一公里展开竞争。【原文：An oil refiner backed by activist investor Carl Icahn and a group of creditors holding claims against Venezuela are competing in the last mile of a U.S. court auction for Citgo Petroleum, according to three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/citgo-auction-pits-icahn-backed-oil-refiner-creditor-group-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIY5WP5TWVKQ5HZSL27MEHGLBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:50:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家回应股市抛售，纳斯达克指数走向修正]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于对经济的担忧以及亚马逊和英特尔公司的下调预测，全球股市遭到抛售，美国国债收益率也创下了数月来的新低，这对估值颇高的科技公司造成了冲击。【原文：Global equities sold off on Friday and U.S. Treasury yields were at multi-month lows on concerns about the economy and downbeat forecasts from Amazon and Intel, which hit richly-valued technology firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/equities-sell-off-nasdaq-down-3-bond-yields-sink-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZLFXPW4BBOMNM4PFZGFT2NT2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波动率挂钩基金抛售美股，加剧股市下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市的急剧下跌引发了对波动性敏感的基金的抛售，加剧了纳斯达克综合指数（Nasdaq Composite）已经进入调整区间的抛售。【原文：A sharp drop in U.S. stocks is provoking selling from volatility-sensitive funds, exacerbating a selloff that has already brought the Nasdaq Composite into correction territory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/volatility-linked-funds-dump-us-stocks-exacerbating-selloff-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTJOJGZFSRJG3PQZXH7STKZF4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:49:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部面临周五 TikTok 儿童隐私权诉讼的最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部将在周五的最后期限内决定是否起诉 TikTok 和母公司 ByteDance，指控其未能保护儿童在社交媒体应用程序上的隐私。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department faces a Friday deadline to decide whether to sue TikTok and parent company ByteDance for failing to protect children's privacy on the social media app.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/doj-faces-friday-deadline-tiktok-children-privacy-suit-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHXHZN37NJOM3K4LN6HCRMKKXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第二季度盈利增长率预期从周四的 13.3% 下调至周五的 12.9% - LSEG]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 LSEG 的数据，截至周五，S&amp;P 500 指数公司第二季度的盈利增长预期已从周四的 13.3% 降至 12.9%。【原文：The earnings growth estimate for S&amp;P 500 companies for the second quarter has dipped to 12.9% as of Friday from 13.3% on Thursday, according to LSEG data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-q2-earnings-growth-estimate-dips-129-fri-133-thurs-lseg-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBVFHBYZU5LHXGMXTBJUUBKVCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国巴黎银行收购 AXA 基金业务为更多交易带来希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家们表示，法国巴黎银行（BNP Paribas）收购保险公司安盛（AXA）投资业务的谈判将引发更多交易，因为欧洲的资金管理公司正试图抵御美国竞争对手的冲击，而且客户需要廉价的技术驱动型投资。【原文：BNP Paribas' talks to buy the investment business of insurer AXA will trigger more deals, bankers say, as European money managers seek to fend off U.S. rivals and as customers demand cheap technology-driven investing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bnp-paribas-swoop-axa-fund-business-fuels-hopes-more-deals-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZUAX47AORMCBI3OGNXX2HHOLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，对冲基金投资者的胃口受到高收费和私人信贷的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五看到的高盛（Goldman Sachs）在给客户的一份报告中称，全球投资者对最昂贵的多策略对冲基金的偏好有所下降，尽管有更多投资者计划将对冲基金纳入其投资组合。【原文：Global investor appetite for the most expensive multi-strategy hedge funds has fallen, Goldman Sachs said in a report to clients seen by Reuters on Friday, though more investors plan to add hedge funds to their portfolios.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hedge-fund-investor-appetite-hit-by-high-fees-private-credit-says-goldman-sachs-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKTH6YTMSJMSXOIU7XYHJZPGHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:38:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 预计无论大选结果如何，美国都将对加密货币友好]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase 首席执行官布莱恩-阿姆斯特朗（Brian Armstrong）周四晚些时候表示，无论哪个政党获胜，下一届美国政府都将对加密货币采取 "建设性 "态度，这凸显了该行业在 11 月大选前日益增长的政治影响力。【原文：The next U.S. administration will be "constructive" on crypto regardless of which party wins, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong said late on Thursday, underscoring the industry's growing political influence ahead of the November election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/coinbase-expects-us-be-crypto-friendly-irrespective-election-outcome-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDRDVTPBTRPJNN4K7IXQ6RQBKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:29:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月份工厂订单降幅超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周五公布的数据显示，6 月份美国制成品新订单降幅超过预期，但企业设备支出与最初估计的一样稳健。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods fell more than expected in June, but business spending on equipment was solid as was initially estimated, government data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-factory-orders-fall-more-than-expected-june-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KOMPECK7RJLTIQ7YNHE5ZAZE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:18:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克指数从历史高点下跌 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克综合指数周五下跌 2.2%，使其有望确认自己正处于调整期，因为人们担心大型科技公司的估值过高和经济降温。【原文：The Nasdaq Composite index fell 2.2% on Friday, putting it on track to confirm it is in a correction following concerns about pricey Big Tech valuations and a cooling economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-falls-10-record-high-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXB2ZCMD35OCBJ4Z67SSXNMKCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[截至 7 月 31 日当周，美国股票基金在降息预期下继续流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 7 月 31 日的一周内，投资者将资金投入美国股票基金，因为他们预计美联储将在政策会议后发出降息信号，但科技股的持续抛售抑制了购买热情。【原文：Investors put money into U.S. equity funds in the week through July 31 as they anticipated the Federal Reserve would signal interest rate cuts following its policy meeting, though an extended sell-off in tech stocks tempered purchases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-fund-inflows-continued-week-july-31-amid-rate-cut-hopes-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYGBVDO6IBNITNDGVFQF3OOVQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金连续第六周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 7 月 31 日，全球投资者连续第六周保持股票基金净买入，原因是市场预期美国联邦储备委员会最早将在 9 月份发出降息信号，这可能会降低企业借贷成本。【原文：Global investors remained net buyers of equity funds for a sixth successive week through July 31, driven by expectations that the U.S. Federal Reserve would signal a rate cut as early as September, which could reduce corporate borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRVPICTPFRNDJMLSE3UL6RWBQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:57:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国就业人数疲软为美联储9月减息敞开大门]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份的就业增长放缓幅度超过预期，失业率上升至 4.3%，这可能加剧人们对劳动力市场正在恶化的担忧，并可能使经济容易陷入衰退。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed more than expected in July, while the unemployment rate increased to 4.3%, which could heighten fears that the labor market is deteriorating and potentially making the economy vulnerable to a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/view-soft-us-payrolls-number-opens-door-september-fed-cut-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NQSNPK5CNLNRJ5CD4G37LJAQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:52:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业数据疲软，美联储 9 月将降息半点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，交易商押注美联储将在9月份开始放松政策，大幅降息半个百分点，此前政府数据显示，上个月雇主增加的工人数量远低于预期，失业率上升。
利率期货合约目前反映出，下个月降息半个百分点的可能性约为 70%，而《纽约时报》之前的预测为 70%。【原文：Traders bet on Friday that the Federal Reserve will start easing policy in September with a big half-percentage-point interest rate cut, after government data showed employers added far fewer workers than expected last month, and the jobless rate rose.
Interest rate futures contracts now reflect about a 70% chance seen of a half-percentage-point rate cut next month, versus what was seen before the】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-seen-cutting-rates-by-half-point-sept-after-weak-jobs-data-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYNGK3E745JQ3J3TRAH6JO2SWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月就业增长不及预期；失业率升至 4.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份的就业增长放缓幅度超过预期，失业率上升至 4.3%，这可能加剧人们对劳动力市场正在恶化的担忧，并可能使经济容易陷入衰退。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed more than expected in July, while the unemployment rate increased to 4.3%, which could heighten fears that the labor market is deteriorating and potentially making the economy vulnerable to a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-growth-misses-expectations-july-unemployment-rate-rises-43-2024-08-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44F23RHCNNIZHPWFXPOOQFTDIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>