<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:36:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:36:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[百时美施贵宝与武田将汇集数据进行人工智能药物研发]]></title><description><![CDATA[百时美施贵宝公司、武田制药公司和阿斯泰克斯制药公司将共同分享用于训练人工智能模型的专有数据，以协助药物发现和开发。【原文：Bristol Myers Squibb , Takeda Pharmaceuticals and Astex Pharmaceuticals are coming together to share proprietary data for training an artificial intelligence model to assist drug discovery and development.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bristol-myers-takeda-pool-data-ai-based-drug-discovery-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7FELWNAJBN7NNPEAPIC3B33VM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:31:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宜家家居斥资 2.13 亿美元购入曼哈顿大楼，在美国开设新店]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的宜家零售商英卡集团（Ingka Group）周三表示，该集团已经收购了曼哈顿的一处房产，计划在那里开设一家新店，作为该家具集团在美国扩张的一部分。【原文：Ingka Group, the biggest global IKEA retailer, has acquired a Manhattan property where it plans to open a new store as part of the furniture group's expansion in the United States, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ikea-buys-213-million-manhattan-building-new-store-us-push-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCILRT7YMNOU7FCJUTIW2QKYG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大型制药公司宣布在美国开展直接面向消费者的销售和降价活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普呼吁降低药价并剔除药店、保险公司和药房福利管理公司等 "中间商 "后，多家制药公司表示将直接向美国患者销售药品并提供折扣。【原文：Several pharmaceutical companies have said they will sell drugs direct to patients in the U.S. and offered discounts following President Donald Trump's calls to bring down drug prices and cut out "middlemen" like pharmacies, insurers and pharmacy benefit managers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/big-pharma-firms-announce-direct-to-consumer-sales-price-cuts-us-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZGYP4LZFJINBEFGUJ5URDVI4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年特斯拉在法国和丹麦的月销量首次上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[当地行业数据周三显示，特斯拉上个月在法国和丹麦的销量今年首次出现增长，美国电动汽车制造商特斯拉的改款车型Y成为丹麦最畅销的车型。【原文：Tesla's sales rose in France and Denmark last month for the first time this year, local industry data showed on Wednesday, with the U.S. electric car maker's revamped Model Y coming in as the best-selling model in Denmark.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-monthly-sales-rise-france-denmark-first-time-2025-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JH32QK7RTRPELAPLOIYKFFVYVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府停摆使美联储加息路径复杂化，华尔街期货下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周三下跌，原因是投资者评估了联邦政府关门的影响，这有可能扰乱关键经济数据的发布，并使美联储的政策路径复杂化。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Wednesday as investors assessed the implications of the federal government shutdown, which threatens to disrupt the release of key economic data and complicate the Federal Reserve's policy path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-slip-government-shutdown-complicates-fed-rate-path-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKL6I7SO25NR5BZZ6TYC57EIAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼有望很快与自由港-麦克莫兰公司就撤资计划达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼投资部长周三表示，印尼预计将很快与自由港麦克莫兰公司就该公司剥离其印尼子公司 PT Freeport Indonesia 12% 股份的计划签署协议。【原文：Indonesia expects to sign a deal with Freeport-McMoRan soon regarding a plan for the firm to divest a 12% stake in its Indonesian unit PT Freeport Indonesia, the investment minister said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-expects-deal-soon-with-freeport-mcmoran-divestment-plan-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHVEB7ADYJJOPNIMNCFMA66RAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:47:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果、OpenAI要求美国法官驳回马斯克就人工智能竞争、应用商店排名提起的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司和 ChatGPT 所有者 OpenAI 周二请求美国联邦法官驳回亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克的 xAI 提起的诉讼，后者指控苹果公司和 OpenAI 非法合谋阻碍人工智能领域的竞争。【原文：Apple and ChatGPT owner OpenAI on Tuesday asked a U.S. federal judge to dismiss a case filed by billionaire Elon Musk's xAI, which had accused them of illegally conspiring to thwart competition in the field of artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-openai-ask-us-judge-dismiss-musks-suit-over-ai-competition-app-store-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T345CTQ3KNKIBELZSKIUPC3CZU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:22:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网站显示，随着 7500 美元电动汽车税收抵免到期，特斯拉提高了所有美国车型的租赁价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[据特斯拉网站周三报道，在促进电动汽车销售的7500美元税收减免政策到期后，特斯拉提高了其在美国所有汽车的租赁价格。【原文：Tesla has raised lease prices for all its vehicles in the U.S. after a $7,500 tax credit that boosted EV sales expired, according to its website on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-hikes-lease-price-all-us-models-7500-ev-tax-credit-expires-website-shows-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NCRNB3NRBPT5H3HVCYMLHNY6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 07:34:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马因起动机缺陷召回逾 14.5 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，宝马公司将在美国召回超过14.5万辆汽车，因为过热的起动机可能会增加起火的风险。【原文：BMW is recalling over 145,000 vehicles in the U.S. as an overheated starter could increase the risk of a fire, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-recall-over-145000-us-vehicles-citing-starter-motor-defect-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TA5Z2YTBTBOMTCN2HD6SLJS3DA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 07:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界自由金融公司最早将于今年推出借记卡]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界自由金融公司（World Liberty Financial）首席执行官扎克-威特科夫（Zach Witkoff）周三在一次会议上表示，该公司是一家由美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）家族支持的加密风险投资公司，计划推出一种借记卡，将 "加密资产与日常消费连接起来"。【原文：World Liberty Financial, a crypto venture backed by the family of U.S. President Donald Trump, plans to launch a debit card that would "bridge crypto assets with everyday spending", its CEO Zach Witkoff told a conference on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/world-liberty-financial-launch-debit-card-early-this-year-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYNGXAJA7VLSREAXZBAMTDMBUM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 07:15:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LG 化学将出售价值 14 亿美元的 LG 能源解决方案股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国 LG 化学公司周三表示，计划出售其电池部门 LG Energy Solution 价值 2 万亿韩元（14.3 亿美元）的股份，以帮助改善财务状况并提升公司价值。【原文：South Korea's LG Chem said on Wednesday it plans to sell 2 trillion Korean won ($1.43 billion) worth of shares in its battery unit LG Energy Solution to help improve finances and boost its corporate value.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/lg-chem-sell-14-bln-worth-shares-lg-energy-solution-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CKMYMHTPNMXXDDLGA4K23FSR4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 06:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，奥地利莱费森银行出售俄罗斯股份的新努力失败了]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士称，莱法森国际银行（Raiffeisen Bank International）试图出售其俄罗斯业务股份的又一次尝试失败了，因为俄罗斯正努力维持一座通往西方的重要金融桥梁。【原文：Raiffeisen Bank International has failed in another attempt to sell a stake in its Russian business, two people familiar with the situation said, as Russia seeks to maintain a key financial bridge to the West.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/austrias-raiffeisen-fails-new-effort-sell-stake-russia-sources-say-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALWXO4FICJID7PIYTYUGWB2D7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 06:32:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森预计到 2027 年底将在新加坡裁员 10%-15%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil Corp）周三表示，为进行全球重组，该公司预计将削减 10%至 15%的新加坡员工人数，并在 2027 年底前将其办公室从市中心迁至裕廊工厂所在地。【原文：Exxon Mobil Corp expects to cut the number of its employees in Singapore by 10% to 15% and move its office to the site of its Jurong plant from downtown by the end of 2027, in global restructuring efforts, the company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/exxon-expects-cut-singapore-staff-by-10-15-by-end-2027-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHVQMLVRZBMNFD45NNYF5VKMNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 06:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉九月份在丹麦的注册量增长 20.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦移动通信公司（Mobility Denmark）周三提供的数据显示，9月份丹麦的特斯拉新车注册量同比增长了20.45%，达到2232辆。【原文：Registrations of new Tesla cars in Denmark rose by 20.45% in September from a year earlier, to 2,232 vehicles, data from Mobility Denmark showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/tesla-registrations-denmark-rise-205-september-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQO7EZPEOVJITBZ3RYEAYMVVQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 06:21:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受到人工智能的惊吓，宝莱坞明星将谷歌拖入 "人格权 "之争]]></title><description><![CDATA[在印度，宝莱坞明星要求法官在人工智能时代保护他们的声音和形象。其中一对知名夫妇的最大目标是谷歌的视频部门YouTube。【原文：In India, Bollywood stars are asking judges to protect their voice and persona in the era of artificial intelligence. One famous couple's biggest target is Google's video arm YouTube.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/spooked-by-ai-bollywood-stars-drag-google-into-fight-personality-rights-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWUHJCY5AZJHBNLPYT2PZCMQAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 06:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易倡议失效，非洲出口面临直接损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国与非洲的旗舰贸易倡议一夜之间失效，使非洲大陆的数十家企业和数十万个工作岗位面临风险，让人担心即使承诺延期也可能为时已晚。【原文：The lapse of a flagship U.S. trade initiative with Africa that expired overnight is putting scores of businesses on the continent and hundreds of thousands of jobs at risk, raising fears that even a promised extension may come too late.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/african-exports-face-immediate-damage-lapse-us-trade-initiative-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REXON4T5WZJ47JCZACNVCOLLSQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 05:58:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛集团高管称，随着美国以外投资者的多元化，亚洲吸引了 1,000 亿美元的资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）亚太地区（日本除外）总裁凯文-斯耐德（Kevin Sneader）周三表示，随着全球投资者在美国以外地区进行多元化投资，除中国以外的亚洲地区在过去九个月里吸引了约1000亿美元的资本流入。【原文：Asia excluding China has attracted about $100 billion in capital inflows over the past nine months as global investors diversify beyond the U.S., said Kevin Sneader, Goldman Sachs' president for Asia-Pacific ex-Japan, on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/asia-draws-100-billion-capital-investors-diversify-beyond-us-goldman-executive-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTTG67CLBJJJJOSBOG7ZFM7OGA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 05:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify 创始人丹尼尔-艾克（Daniel Ek）的下一步行动：在欧洲防务和健康领域下长线赌注]]></title><description><![CDATA[当丹尼尔-艾克（Daniel Ek）在 2006 年创立 Spotify 时，一款可行的音乐产品还只是 "登月之作"。当时，全球音乐产业正苦苦挣扎，销量连年下滑，在线音乐盗版猖獗，而苹果公司的 iTunes 等服务价格昂贵。【原文：When Daniel Ek founded Spotify in 2006, a viable music product was a "moon shot." The global music industry was struggling with years of declining sales, online music piracy was rampant, and services like Apple's iTunes were pricey.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/spotify-founder-daniel-eks-next-act-long-bets-european-defence-health-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TPB47HETNMQBAU5QR2CQL7DHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 05:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓斥资 5.55 亿美元提高南澳大利亚铜产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[必和必拓（BHP）周三表示，该公司将向其位于南澳大利亚州的奥林匹克大坝铜矿业务投资超过8.4亿澳元（5.5516亿美元），因为该矿商准备在2027年中期做出投资决定，将该州的铜矿产量翻一番。【原文：BHP said on Wednesday it would invest more than A$840 million ($555.16 million) in its Olympic Dam copper operations in South Australia as the miner prepares to make an investment decision by mid-2027 to double output from the state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bhp-earmarks-555-million-boost-copper-production-south-australia-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQ6XQXU3SVINVMUWBQIIWTB244</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:37:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标华盛顿陷入黑暗]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5S4QFGNSXZKPVMKCSIUS7VQZ7I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Variety 报道，NBC 环球与 YouTube TV 签订短期续约协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Variety 周三援引谷歌发言人的话报道称，谷歌和 Comcast 旗下的 NBCUniversal 已就现有的 YouTube TV 运营协议达成短期续约。【原文：Google and Comcast-owned NBCUniversal have entered a short-term extension on their existing carriage deal for YouTube TV, Variety reported on Wednesday, citing a Google spokesperson.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nbcuniversal-youtube-tv-ink-short-term-deal-extension-variety-reports-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MKINATJUZMCTBV3S6QZEQIDZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:24:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[野村将加强利率和外汇交易部门，市场波动加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本野村控股公司（Nomura Holdings）的一位高级管理人员表示，该公司计划在全球范围内加强利率和货币交易业务，因为他相信市场波动的加剧将提升需求。【原文：Japan's Nomura Holdings plans to beef up its interest rate and currency trading operations globally, believing increased market volatility will lift demand, a senior executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nomura-boost-rates-fx-trading-units-sees-more-market-volatility-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJRKK3PPURORXAMBUTWX3UIZBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:23:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长詹姆斯就交通资金冻结问题起诉国土安全部，索赔近 3400 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长莱蒂西亚-詹姆斯（Letitia James）周二提起诉讼并提出紧急动议，要求对美国国土安全部部长克里斯蒂-诺姆（Kristi Noem）和国土安全部下达临时限制令，指控他们非法扣留了纽约州大都会运输局（MTA）申请的近3400万美元资金。【原文：New York Attorney General Letitia James on Tuesday filed a lawsuit and an emergency motion seeking a temporary restraining order against U.S. Secretary of Homeland Security Kristi Noem and the department, accusing them of unlawfully withholding nearly $34 million in funding requested by the state's Metropolitan Transportation Authority (MTA).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/new-york-ag-james-sues-homeland-security-nearly-34-million-over-transit-funding-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWKOOT34Z5KITAA6PAD372EA7U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:22:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国会未能推进拨款法案，美国政府开始关闭大部分业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-government-begins-shut-down-most-operations-after-congress-fails-advance-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWMQLGSSI5KMZMUIQASYVXBSIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球经济 中国和美国需求疲软，亚洲工厂举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的民间调查显示，9月份亚洲大多数主要经济体的工厂活动萎缩，原因是有迹象表明美国经济增长放缓，而且美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税预期影响加大了中国需求疲软带来的压力。【原文：Factory activity shrank in most of Asia's major economies in September, private surveys showed on Wednesday, as signs of a slowdown in U.S. growth and the expected impact of President Donald Trump's tariffs added to pressure from weak Chinese demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-economy-asian-factories-struggle-soft-china-us-demand-takes-toll-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNFWVDC4PJPEFLA4QP3H2ZASGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 03:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本最高贸易谈判代表称美国 5500 亿美元投资计划不会对外汇产生影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最高贸易谈判代表赤泽亮世周三表示，日本将在不影响外汇市场的情况下执行东京与华盛顿达成的关税协议中商定的对美投资 5500 亿美元的一揽子计划。【原文：Japan will run a $550 billion U.S.-bound investment package agreed in Tokyo's tariff deal with Washington without any impact on the foreign exchange market, its top trade negotiator Ryosei Akazawa said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/japans-550-billion-us-investment-package-have-no-fx-impact-top-trade-negotiator-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUAFNPA2NRJIRNHEWKRJQVBLMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 03:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示：中国 9 月新房价格上涨，转售市场下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项民间调查显示，尽管采取了一系列支持措施，但中国市场仍在努力寻找立足点。【原文：China's new home prices rose at a slower pace in September, traditionally a peak buying month, while resale home prices fell again, as the market struggled to find its footing despite a raft of support measures, a private survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-september-new-home-prices-edge-up-resale-market-falls-survey-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BWTDE4SORKR3NGRNEASEOJYQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arm计划就高通纠纷终审裁决提起上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arm Holdings 周二表示，它计划就法官在与高通公司的许可纠纷中做出的裁决提起上诉，该裁决使芯片制造商在陪审团中的胜利保持不变。【原文：Arm Holdings said on Tuesday it planned to appeal a judge's ruling in a licensing dispute against Qualcomm that left the chipmaker's jury victory intact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/arm-plans-appeal-final-ruling-qualcomm-dispute-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSFE424BPJII7CY3YRVMK5C2KM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:17:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府关门在即，华尔街期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国政府关门时间的临近，华尔街期货周三下滑，这将推迟关键就业数据的公布，并使利率前景变得模糊。【原文：Wall Street futures slipped on Wednesday as the clock ticked down to a U.S. government shutdown that would delay the release of crucial jobs data and muddy the interest rate outlook, while Asian markets hesitated after a solid quarter of gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CHVU5D6LNMVPIMEVBODWNEY7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，贝莱德的 GIP 接近以 380 亿美元收购公用事业集团 AES]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周二援引知情人士的话报道称，黑石集团旗下的全球基础设施合作伙伴公司（GIP）即将以 380 亿美元（含债务）的价格收购公用事业集团 AES。【原文：BlackRock-owned Global Infrastructure Partners (GIP) is nearing a $38 billion deal, inclusive of debt, to acquire utility group AES , the Financial Times reported on Tuesday, citing people briefed on the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/blackrocks-gip-nears-38-billion-takeover-utility-group-aes-ft-reports-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNME2M3ZIZKGJJJO7IJAPTCH7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 01:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>