<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:09:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:09:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[劳动力市场忧虑引发 11 月美国住宅建筑商情绪低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对劳动力市场和家庭财务状况的担忧拖累了需求，导致建筑商为减少新房库存而降价的比例激增，11 月份美国住宅建筑商的情绪依然低迷。【原文：U.S. homebuilder sentiment remained subdued in November as concerns about the labor market and household finances weighed on demand, contributing to a surge in the share of builders slashing prices to reduce new housing inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-home-builder-sentiment-subdued-november-amid-labor-market-worries-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMDRTJZGRBM43CLOCB6NNMIOZM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格关闭部分自动化设施，将产生 26 亿美元费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国杂货商克罗格（Kroger）周二表示，该公司将在 2025 年第三财季关闭某些自动履行设施，并计提约 26 亿美元的减值费用。【原文：U.S. grocer Kroger said on Tuesday it would close certain automated fulfillment facilities and incur an impairment charge of about $2.6 billion in the third fiscal quarter of 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kroger-close-some-automated-facilities-incur-26-billion-charge-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXRURZMW2JOZ5FIRSAT5QS4YNE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intuit 达成 1 亿美元协议，将 OpenAI 模型整合到金融工具中]]></title><description><![CDATA[Intuit 周二表示，它已与 OpenAI 签订了一份价值超过 1 亿美元的多年期协议，将使用这家 ChatGPT 制造商的人工智能模型为其应用程序（如报税软件 TurboTax）中的人工智能代理提供支持。【原文：Intuit said on Tuesday it has signed a multi-year deal worth more than $100 million with OpenAI to use the ChatGPT maker's artificial intelligence models to power AI agents across its apps such as tax-preparation software TurboTax.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intuit-strikes-100-million-deal-integrate-openai-models-into-financial-tools-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJKKUENWZFML5I5C2ZLQV6WXUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:24:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ocado 因美国合作伙伴 Kroger 表示将关闭三个机器人仓库而下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国在线超市和技术集团 Ocado 周二股价暴跌，此前其美国合作伙伴克罗格（Kroger）表示将在一月份关闭三个自动化仓库。【原文：Shares in British online supermarket and technology group Ocado slumped on Tuesday after U.S. partner Kroger said it would close three automated warehouses in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ocado-get-250-million-krogers-planned-closure-some-automated-facilities-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJXFMT4LGRJLDKMQP6V772T3XE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:23:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工部称，10 月中旬美国失业救济人数创 8 月份以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月中旬，领取失业救济金的美国人数创下了两个月来的新高，当时劳工部正在对美国家庭进行调查。【原文：The number of Americans receiving unemployment benefits stood at a two-month high in mid-October at the time when the Labor Department would have been conducting its survey of U.S. households.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-jobless-benefits-rolls-mid-october-were-highest-since-august-labor-dept-says-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Y4PYTRNC5PRTEMLVODKPUBMJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Autonomy 诉讼案后，惠普向迈克-林奇的遗产索赔 18 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技巨头惠普公司的律师周二在伦敦高等法院表示，惠普公司正就惠普收购已故英国科技公司 Autonomy 事宜向已故迈克-林奇的遗产索赔近 18 亿美元。【原文：Hewlett Packard Enterprise is seeking nearly $1.8 billion from the estate of the late Mike Lynch over HP's acquisition of his British tech firm Autonomy, the U.S. technology giant's lawyers told London's High Court on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hp-seeking-18-billion-mike-lynchs-estate-after-uk-autonomy-lawsuit-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P53C6BKJCNPJ7O6DNPOHQ77B3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PVH's finance chief Zac Coughlin to step down, insider named interim replacement]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tommy Hilfiger and Calvin Klein's parent company PVH said on Tuesday that its Chief Financial Officer Zac Coughlin will be leaving at the end of the year, to be replaced by company veteran Melissa Stone as interim CFO.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pvhs-finance-chief-zac-coughlin-step-down-insider-named-interim-replacement-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VC6DP6ANZBOIJLZYAU64HSFI2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:51:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK measures to counter China's threat to lawmakers, business, universities]]></title><description><![CDATA[Britain's domestic intelligence service, MI5, warned lawmakers and parliamentary staff on Tuesday about Chinese agents who were targeting democratic institutions, including through networking sites.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-measures-counter-chinas-threat-lawmakers-business-universities-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHB5U3BUE5LDBFJ6BHRCPXFTJE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:44:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Italy considers 5G telecoms licence extensions with lower costs tied to investment pledges]]></title><description><![CDATA[Italy is considering extending 5G licences while limiting costs for operators in return for investment pledges, a cabinet undersecretary said on Tuesday, as the telecom sector contends with falling revenue and lower margins.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italy-considers-5g-telecoms-licence-extensions-with-lower-costs-tied-investment-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTGYAYMY2RI3NPAZUTHY76RGIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:37:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Klarna strikes $6.5 bln loan deal with Elliott funds to boost US push]]></title><description><![CDATA[Klarna said on Tuesday it will sell up to $6.5 billion of loans to funds managed by Elliott Investment Management over a two-year period, as part of efforts to expand its buy-now-pay-later business in the U.S.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/klarna-strikes-65-bln-loan-deal-with-elliott-funds-boost-us-push-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV7TCJGTXNLCZITCY57WM3FQ5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bosch struggling with production snags despite hopes of chip supply detente]]></title><description><![CDATA[German automotive supplier Bosch (ROBG.UL) is struggling with disruption at three production sites despite signs of movement in a trade dispute around the chipmaker Nexperia, with thousands of workers impacted, the company said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bosch-struggling-with-production-snags-despite-hopes-chip-supply-detente-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RI5S7QM2GNNFLBK6YNW263ZRKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI accounting startup Maxima raises $41 million in Kleiner Perkins-backed round]]></title><description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence startup Maxima has raised about $41 million from investors including Redpoint Ventures and Kleiner Perkins as it looks to automate accounting for businesses, the company said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-accounting-startup-maxima-raises-41-million-kleiner-perkins-backed-round-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSRXIKOPI5IFVP4HC26M5JA6GY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Klarna Q3 revenue beats estimates in first earnings report after IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[Swedish fintech Klarna on Tuesday reported a 26% jump in third-quarter revenue, beating expectations in its first report as a public company, and forecast revenue to cross $1 billion in the current quarter, backed mainly by growth in U.S. markets.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/klarna-q3-revenue-beats-estimates-first-earnings-report-after-ipo-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SN7UYN46JBJJZJWJYIUYRX4YSI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Nissan to cut more output at Kyushu plant on chip supply troubles]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's Nissan will cut production by another 1,400 vehicles at its Kyushu plant next week, as the fallout from chip supply disruptions linked to Chinese-owned Nexperia continues to affect its domestic operations, a person familiar with the matter said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-cut-more-output-kyushu-plant-chip-supply-troubles-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ID6WWF52RNLMFCBWLTCH3EIHLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:31:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cash allocation strategies across US companies could be missing out on millions, report shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Corporations across the U.S. could potentially be leaving millions on the table depending on their cash management strategies, according to research published by Clearwater Analytics on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cash-allocation-strategies-across-us-companies-could-be-missing-out-millions-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PJLM4NGW5M4FOW4LLBCIDDOA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:17:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币跌破 90,000 美元，交易者日趋谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，比特币七个月来首次跌破 90,000 美元，这是整个金融市场投资者风险偏好正在枯竭的最新迹象。【原文：Bitcoin fell below $90,000 for the first time in seven months on Tuesday in the latest sign that investor appetite for risk is drying up across financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-drops-below-90000-sign-souring-mood-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWTRLIBE4FJL3NKZKR2DHWDEH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:13:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示，数以千计的美国用户无法使用埃隆-马斯克的 X 系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 的数据，埃隆-马斯克的 X 系统周二在美国有数千名用户出现故障。【原文：Elon Musk's X was down for thousands of users in the U.S. on Tuesday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/elon-musks-x-down-thousands-us-users-downdetector-shows-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXVMF3TZENIVRIUP6TLBZPN2I4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:05:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行调查显示，美国中小企业预计 2026 年将更加强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行的一项调查显示，大多数美国中小型企业主预计明年的业绩将更加强劲，其中 74% 的企业主预计收入将增长，近 60% 的企业主计划扩大经营规模。【原文：A majority of small and mid-sized business owners in the U.S. expect stronger performance next year, with 74% forecasting revenue growth and nearly 60% planning to expand operations, a Bank of America survey showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-small-mid-sized-businesses-expect-stronger-2026-bofa-survey-shows-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2G74PBIZJNJXJKT7LG6CQH6NGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roblox 将要求使用平台聊天功能的用户接受年龄检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[游戏平台 Roblox 将要求用户在与其他玩家聊天时使用面部识别软件验证自己的年龄，该公司的一位高管表示，这样做的目的是限制平台上儿童与成年人之间的交流。【原文：Gaming platform Roblox will require users to verify their age using facial recognition software to chat with other players, a company executive said, with the goal of limiting communication between kids and adults on the platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/roblox-require-age-checks-use-platforms-chat-features-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWNDLZPDFFL57M5Z3IVM56VOVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前 FDA 委员斯科特-戈特利布加入 UnitedHealth 董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）周二表示，美国食品和药物管理局前局长斯科特-戈特利布（Scott Gottlieb）已加入该公司董事会。【原文：UnitedHealth Group said on Tuesday former U.S. Food and Drug Administration commissioner Scott Gottlieb has joined the company's board of directors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/former-fda-commissioner-scott-gottlieb-joins-unitedhealth-board-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRJH3JTOZROKZIFAWSA7BWIPBM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:53:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关税推动的涨势之后，嘉能可将世纪铝业的股份削减至 33]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国对进口铝征收关税和当地铝冶炼厂利润大增引发股价大涨之后，嘉能可已将其在世纪铝业公司（Century Aluminum）的股份削减了 10%，降至 33%，从而获得了数百万美元的收益。【原文：Glencore has cut its stake in Century Aluminum by 10% to 33%, raking in millions following a share price rally triggered by U.S. tariffs on aluminium imports and a profit bonanza for local aluminium smelters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/glencore-cuts-century-aluminum-stake-33-after-tariff-driven-rally-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5JPIMIM6NOQZGT2XYU4MKP4QI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：科技股震荡加剧波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQORTJEQHRMB5B6VERP2BQ4NFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:37:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国同意加入阿联酋星际之门人工智能数据中心项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[首尔周二表示，韩国已同意与阿拉伯联合酋长国就美国支持的 "星际之门"（Stargate）项目开展合作，在这个海湾国家新建一个大型人工智能数据园区。【原文：South Korea has agreed to work with the United Arab Emirates on the U.S.-backed Stargate project to build a massive new artificial intelligence data campus in the Gulf country, Seoul said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/south-korea-agrees-join-uaes-stargate-ai-project-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH6KLJZK45PSNEEO6BJHAPDL4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:27:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泡沫还是突破？英伟达财报将人工智能热潮置于显微镜下]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，英伟达（Nvidia）将公布财报，华尔街对人工智能的惊人押注将完全取决于这家芯片制造商的命运。【原文：The fate of Wall Street's staggering bets on artificial intelligence will rest squarely on Nvidia on Wednesday when the chipmaker reports results, with investors seeking signs that bubble worries are overblown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/bubble-or-breakout-nvidia-earnings-put-ai-boom-under-microscope-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQIYKLAJANLRPBN46ARXVPRLUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[创纪录的反向拆分揭示了小盘股与巨型股之间日益扩大的鸿沟]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年，全球反向拆股创下新高，这凸显了小市值公司在人工智能推动的涨势将科技权重股推向新高之际，仍在为继续上市而苦苦挣扎的压力。【原文：Reverse stock splits globally have climbed to a record this year, underscoring the strain on small-cap companies struggling to stay listed even as an AI-fueled rally lifts technology heavyweights to fresh highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/record-reverse-splits-expose-growing-divide-between-small-caps-megacaps-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFD3PA53WFPJBNFUAREWLAR5YE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息希望减弱，估值担忧持续，美股期货下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周二下跌，原因是对股票估值过高和降息前景黯淡的担忧打压了市场情绪，尽管人们仍在关注英伟达（Nvidia）的财报和本周晚些时候公布的关键政府数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Tuesday as concerns over lofty equity valuations and diminishing prospects for an interest rate cut weighed on sentiment, though attention remained on Nvidia's earnings and key government data due later this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-slip-rate-cut-hopes-fade-valuation-worries-persist-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AO7LP6QBYJNMJPJHOQM3L6IM3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:07:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得宝季度销售额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于专业建筑商和承包商的强劲需求帮助抵消了 DIY 项目的放缓，家得宝周二公布的第三季度销售额超出预期。【原文：Home Depot topped third-quarter sales estimates on Tuesday, as robust demand from professional builders and contractors helped offset a slowdown in do-it-yourself projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/home-depot-beats-quarterly-sales-estimates-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUXET5SD2FLBNARTT6NYWVQHMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着数据流的复苏，美联储仍面临深刻的政策分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[分裂的美国联邦储备委员会本周开始从现已重新开放的联邦政府接收最新的经济报告，政策制定者们希望在三周多后的会议上就是否降息的争论做出澄清。【原文：A divided U.S. Federal Reserve begins receiving updated economic reports from the now-reopened federal government this week as policymakers hope for clarity in their debate over whether to cut interest rates when they meet in just over three weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/data-flow-revives-fed-still-faces-deep-policy-divide-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGREOMU4HRNFRBBXA6D2AEXS7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[目标公司投资者为市场份额下降和美国停摆导致的销售疲软做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[塔吉特周三公布的第三季度财报预计将暴露出该零售商在经济不确定性日益加剧的情况下所面临的困境，因为在政府长期停摆期间，资金紧张的美国人削减了可自由支配的开支。【原文：Target's third‑quarter results on Wednesday are expected to lay bare the retailer’s struggles amid mounting economic uncertainty, and as cash-strapped Americans slashed discretionary spending during the prolonged government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/target-investors-brace-market-share-drop-weak-sales-due-us-shutdown-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJZAI4ROWJKURNGYCEEFBWYFSE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期权显示，财报发布后英伟达股价将波动 3,200 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周三发布的财报可能会引发这家芯片制造商市值出现 3200 亿美元的波动--这是这家人工智能巨头有史以来最大的财报后波动--因为投资者在寻找有关人工智能热潮是加速还是降温的信号。【原文：Nvidia's earnings report on Wednesday could trigger a $320 billion swing in the chipmaker's market value — the largest post-earnings move ever for the AI giant — as investors seek signals about whether the artificial intelligence boom is accelerating or cooling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-set-320-billion-price-swing-after-earnings-options-indicate-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QB6Q72GQH5JSBELTSNOC3TBUMM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:01:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>