<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 20:34:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 20:34:25 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[比特币最后下跌 5%，报 78892.92 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币是全球市值最大的加密货币，格林尼治标准时间周日18时55分，比特币下跌约5%，报78892.92美元。【原文：Bitcoin, the world's largest cryptocurrency by market value, was down by around 5% at $78,892.92 at 1855 GMT on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-last-down-5-7889292-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTX2XTQCGNKK3AQ46OOO6RB34Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 19:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[周一开盘前美国投资者将面临更多波动和颠簸]]></title><description><![CDATA[在上周华尔街因特朗普政府宣布加征关税而大跌之后，投资者紧张地等待着美国股市开盘，预计随着其他国家做出反应，本周又将出现动荡。【原文：Investors were nervously awaiting the open of U.S. trading after Wall Street's selloff last week following the Trump administration's tariffs announcement, anticipating another week of turbulence as other nations react.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-investors-braced-more-volatility-bumps-ahead-monday-trading-open-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSA7V4QVL5P7FE4W3RHJFNBT34</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 18:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航运巨头达飞轮船公司（CMA CGM）与法国人工智能初创企业合作，瞄准客户服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[航运巨头法国达飞海运集团（CMA CGM）与科技初创公司 Mistral AI 周日公布了一项价值 1 亿欧元的合作计划，预计将迅速提高生产力。【原文：Shipping giant CMA CGM and tech startup Mistral AI expect rapid productivity gains from a 100 million euro partnership unveiled on Sunday, which the French firms also touted as a commitment to their home country amid the global trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/shipping-giant-cma-cgm-french-ai-startup-target-customer-service-tie-up-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLOS7SR4M5KRTDWFCHTDMLOMTM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普顾问称50多个国家已与白宫联系开始贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的一位高级经济顾问周日表示，在美国官员试图为引发全球动荡的全面新关税辩护之际，已有50多个国家与白宫接触，希望开始贸易谈判。【原文：More than 50 countries have reached out to the White House to begin trade talks, a top economic adviser to U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday as U.S. officials sought to defend sweeping new tariffs that have unleashed global turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/more-than-50-countries-have-contacted-white-house-start-trade-talks-trump-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GD2GAAVWPJKWTEDCVVMXELHJFI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 14:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普征收 20% 关税为意大利葡萄酒在美国的前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对欧洲进口商品征收 20% 的关税后，生产商和进口商表示，普罗塞克、布鲁内罗-蒙塔尔奇诺和其他意大利葡萄酒在美国的前景越来越暗淡。【原文：The outlook for Prosecco, Brunello di Montalcino and other Italian wines in the United States is increasingly gloomy, producers and importers said, following President Donald Trump's imposition of a 20% tariff on European imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-20-tariff-clouds-future-italian-wines-us-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2FAEUJYMNI2ZPLEGJBTAITS5U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 13:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[内塔尼亚胡表示将在与特朗普的会晤中寻求关税减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列总理本雅明-内塔尼亚胡周日表示，他希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普本周在华盛顿会晤时能放宽对以色列征收的关税。【原文：Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said on Sunday he hopes U.S. President Donald Trump will ease tariffs imposed on Israel when the two meet in Washington this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/netanyahu-says-will-seek-relief-tariffs-meeting-with-trump-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FX5J32FORFJKPHTSYL6XO4GZ6Y</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 12:56:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着协议谈判取得进展，印度不太可能对特朗普的关税进行报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位印度政府官员表示，印度不打算对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对来自亚洲国家的进口商品征收 26% 的关税进行报复，并引述了两国正在进行的协议谈判。【原文：India does not plan to retaliate against U.S. President Donald Trump's 26% tariff on imports from the Asian nation, an Indian government official said, citing ongoing talks for a deal between the countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india-unlikely-retaliate-against-trumps-tariffs-deal-talks-progress-sources-say-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3PZT2ZU4ZMNPN4ZXZLAZHARDE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 12:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利梅洛尼承诺支持受特朗普关税影响的企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利总理乔治亚-梅洛尼（Giorgia Meloni）周日承诺保护因美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税而遭受损失的企业。【原文：Italian Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni pledged on Sunday to shield businesses that suffered damage from the tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/italys-meloni-pledges-support-businesses-hurt-by-trump-tariffs-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ3WTSJM4NNNBFHHYXRUKHCD3M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯下调亚洲油价至四个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在欧佩克+石油组织周四做出增加供应的令人震惊的决定之后，世界头号石油出口国沙特阿拉伯周日将亚洲买家 5 月份的原油价格降至四个月来的最低点。【原文：Saudi Arabia, the world's top oil exporter, on Sunday lowered crude oil prices for Asian buyers in May to their lowest in four months, after a shock decision by the OPEC+ oil group to increase supply on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/saudi-arabia-cuts-oil-prices-asia-four-month-low-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7CW35RRTJOOBE572DQ6MOAPXY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾不会对美国征收对等关税，将消除贸易壁垒]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾总统赖清德周日表示，台湾不会对美国征收对等贸易关税，但会消除贸易壁垒，台湾企业将逐步增加在美国的投资。【原文：Taiwan President Lai Ching-te said on Sunday that Taiwan will not impose reciprocal trade tariffs against the United States, but will remove trade barriers and Taiwanese companies will gradually increase their investments in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/taiwan-wont-take-reciprocal-tariffs-against-us-will-remove-trade-barriers-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEYYWCSU7NLPZPPS6RWKQMNDFY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，普拉达将于本周就范思哲交易做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日，一位接近此事的消息人士称，随着谈判进入最后阶段，意大利奢侈品集团普拉达（Prada）将于本周就收购规模较小的竞争对手范思哲（Versace）一事做出决定。【原文：Italian luxury group Prada is set to make a decision this week about a potential takeover of smaller rival Versace, a source close to the matter said on Sunday, as the negotiations enter a final phase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/prada-make-decision-versace-deal-this-week-source-says-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKX573GPYNNBVCINL4TWOMGMB4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 10:39:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼官员称印尼不会对特朗普关税进行报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚高级经济部长周日在政府对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对东南亚最大经济体征收贸易关税的首次回应中表示，印尼不会对这一关税进行报复。【原文：Indonesia will not retaliate against U.S. President Donald Trump's trade tariff on Southeast Asia's largest economy, its senior economic minister said on Sunday in the government's first response to the levy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/indonesia-will-not-retaliate-against-trump-tariff-official-says-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOOPEZT6G5IERBOXWSTGIPSH7Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 09:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟寻求团结，首次反击特朗普关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责协调欧盟贸易政策的欧盟委员会将于周一晚些时候向成员国提出一份美国产品清单，针对特朗普的钢铝关税征收额外关税，而不是更广泛的对等征税。【原文：The European Commission, which coordinates EU trade policy, will propose to members late on Monday a list of U.S. products to hit with extra duties in response to Trump's steel and aluminium tariffs rather than the broader reciprocal levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/eu-seeks-unity-first-strike-back-trump-tariffs-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQMUA4CXKZJNHBHD6WBH52ESEI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 08:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和越南企业要求特朗普推迟对越南征收 46%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和越南企业要求特朗普政府推迟对越南商品征收46%关税的计划，称这一征税将损害他们的利益和双边商业关系。【原文：U.S. and Vietnamese businesses have asked the Trump administration to delay its planned 46% tariff on Vietnamese goods, saying the levy will hurt them and bilateral commercial relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-vietnamese-businesses-ask-trump-delay-46-tariffs-vietnam-2025-04-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZMEGFRFDZLJ3FSSDZQ7QVGWPY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 07:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司建成离岸许可证所需的动物护理中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国营石油公司（Petrobras）周六表示，该公司已经完成了亚马逊地区一个兽医中心的建设工作，这是该公司获得近海钻井项目环境许可证的必要条件。【原文：Brazilian state-run oil company Petrobras has completed work on a veterinary center in the Amazon region that is required for it to obtain an environmental permit for an offshore drilling project, the company said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/petrobras-completes-animal-care-center-required-offshore-license-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7P5ANBHVNNJCZNZB3EBXCS2DBM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:29:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 发布新型人工智能模型 Llama 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周六发布了最新版本的大型语言模型（LLM）Llama，称为 Llama 4 Scout 和 Llama 4 Maverick。【原文：Meta Platforms on Saturday released the latest version of its large language model (LLM) Llama, called the Llama 4 Scout and Llama 4 Maverick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-releases-new-ai-model-llama-4-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVET5TBL5NIKBHJDD6UCM33EMI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:09:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州就健康声明对 WK Kellogg 公司展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[得克萨斯州周六表示，已开始对 WK Kellogg 公司进行调查，称这家早餐麦片生产商将其产品宣传为 "健康"，可能违反了该州的法律。【原文：The state of Texas on Saturday said it opened a probe into WK Kellogg , saying the breakfast cereal maker could be violating state laws by advertising its products as "healthy."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/texas-opens-probe-into-wk-kellogg-over-health-claims-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3THAW6ZBHNMWDGJBF7MWRMJL24</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行施纳贝尔称不确定性 "急剧上升 "可能会恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）决策者伊莎贝尔-施纳贝尔（Isabel Schnabel）周六表示，欧元区经济长期存在的结构性不利因素因不确定性的激增而加剧，而美国贸易关税可能会使情况变得更糟。【原文：The euro zone economy's long standing structural headwinds have been exacerbated by a surge in uncertainty which may get even worse in the wake of U.S. trade tariffs, European Central Bank policy maker Isabel Schnabel said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecbs-schnabel-says-dramatic-surge-uncertainty-may-get-worse-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DK2EPXPLRZIVNPH6YE46WJVL3U</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 11:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰晤士报》称，英国捷豹路虎公司将因关税问题暂停向美国发货]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《泰晤士报》报道，捷豹路虎公司将暂停向美国运送英国制造的汽车一个月，因为该公司正在考虑如何减轻唐纳德-特朗普总统征收 25% 关税的成本。【原文：Jaguar Land Rover will pause shipments of its Britain-made cars to the United States for a month, as it considers how to mitigate the cost of President Donald Trump's 25% tariff, according to a report in the Times newspaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uks-jaguar-land-rover-pause-shipments-us-over-tariffs-times-says-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGDDKRFDCZI6DPX6WU4D7TMR4A</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:39:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对美国：在关税刺激大跌之后，"市场说了算]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周六表示，"市场已经发出声音"，反对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税，并呼吁华盛顿进行 "平等协商"，此前全球市场因美国征收贸易关税而暴跌，并招致中国的报复。【原文：China said on Saturday "the market has spoken" in rejecting U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, and called on Washington for "equal-footed consultation" after global markets plunged in reaction to the trade levies that drew Chinese retaliation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-market-has-spoken-after-tariffs-spur-selloff-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7R43DLPUNID7FLWFZSSRMKNK4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾总统与科技企业高管讨论美国关税对策]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾总统赖清德周六会见了科技高管，讨论如何应对美国新关税，并承诺确保台湾的全球竞争力，维护岛内利益。【原文：Taiwan President Lai Ching-te met tech executives on Saturday to discuss how to respond to new U.S. tariffs, promising to ensure Taiwan's global competitiveness and safeguard the island's interests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/taiwan-president-discusses-us-tariff-response-with-tech-execs-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIY4ZVLRXVOKTEMIC4PTSDBFZI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国人工智能视频中的机器人和焦虑的消费者嘲笑关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的国营媒体在互联网上发布了人工智能生成的视频，其中有跳舞的机器人和焦虑不安的消费者，以斥责美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和他们所说的威胁到美国人的高通胀和经济困境的关税。【原文：China's state-run media has taken to the internet with AI-generated videos, featuring dancing robots and fraught consumers, to chide U.S. President Donald Trump and tariffs they say threaten high inflation and economic distress for Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/robots-fraught-consumers-star-china-ai-videos-mocking-tariffs-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LNNHCFVO55KMJNWOH6P3DIVGIQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:13:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南越捷航空公司将从 4 月中旬起在国内航线上运营中国制造的飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社查阅的越南廉价航空公司 VietJet 的一份声明，该公司将从 4 月中旬起首次在国内航线上运营中国制造的中国商飞 ARJ21-700 飞机（也称为 C909）。【原文：Vietnamese budget airline VietJet is set to operate Chinese-made COMAC ARJ21-700 aircraft, also branded as C909, on domestic routes for the first time from mid-April, according to a company statement reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietnams-vietjet-operate-chinese-made-aircraft-domestic-routes-mid-april-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVLIBAEORVJ3NNS7YNAKSC53NM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:12:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税让美国和加拿大农机制造商陷入混乱]]></title><description><![CDATA[在最近于加拿大举行的一次农场展上，设备销售人员竭力与担心关税的农民达成交易。【原文：All around a recent farm show in Canada, equipment salespeople struggled to swing deals with farmers worried about tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/tariffs-throw-us-canadian-farm-machinery-manufacturers-into-turmoil-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XU6N6OXMRJPG7LRJQHF7L2G66I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称日产考虑将部分国内生产转移至美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周六报道，随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）加大对全球各国征收贸易关税的力度，日产汽车公司正在考虑将部分美国本土生产的汽车转移到美国。【原文：Nissan Motor is considering shifting some domestic production of U.S.-bound vehicles to the U.S., the Nikkei reported on Saturday, as President Donald Trump ramps up trade tariffs on nations worldwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-considers-transferring-some-domestic-production-us-nikkei-says-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NEXCVN2V3JJQ7BU6ITWEDSMRLU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 08:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康第一季度收入创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约电子生产商、苹果公司最大的 iPhone 组装商台湾富士康周六公布，其第一季度收入增长 24.2%，创下历史新高。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker and Apple's biggest iPhone assembler, reported on Saturday that its first-quarter revenue jumped 24.2% to a record high for the quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-reports-record-first-quarter-revenue-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INPMTQR5SNJFVAEASITY4H2LKU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 07:42:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受贸易战影响的法国干邑制造商因特朗普的关税政策而陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[克里斯托夫-菲柳（Christophe Fillioux）的家族酒庄位于法国西南部的干邑地区，历经五代人的努力，经历了战争和金融危机的洗礼。不过现在，他已经开始将一些葡萄园连根拔起。【原文：Christophe Fillioux's family estate in the cognac region of southwest France has survived for five generations, through wars and financial crises. Now, though, he has started to tear up some of his vineyards by the roots.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/frances-cognac-makers-buffeted-by-trade-wars-reel-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJMHSIQWNBLFNOFOEUJRY7X3YU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税引发股市大跌，中国称 "市场已经发声]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周六表示，"市场已经发出声音"，反对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税，并呼吁华盛顿在全球市场对贸易征税做出剧烈反应后进行 "平等协商"，因为贸易征税招致了中国的报复。【原文：China said on Saturday "the market has spoken" in rejecting U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, and called on Washington for "equal-footed consultation" after global markets' dramatic reaction to the trade levies, which drew Chinese retaliation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-says-market-has-spoken-after-us-tariffs-spark-selloff-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTL56PON5BIIZFJM6ZQ5MCHB6Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 04:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国开始征收特朗普新的 10%关税，打破全球贸易准则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国海关人员周六开始对来自许多国家的所有进口商品征收唐纳德-特朗普总统单方面提出的10%的关税，并将于下周开始对来自57个较大贸易伙伴的商品征收更高的关税。【原文：U.S. customs agents began collecting President Donald Trump's unilateral 10% tariff on all imports from many countries on Saturday, with higher levies on goods from 57 larger trading partners due to start next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-starts-collecting-trumps-new-10-tariff-smashing-global-trade-norms-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCO3UH532VMZ3FYCVXKWQMZDF4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 04:25:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软人工智能首席执行官的讲话被支持巴勒斯坦的抗议者打断]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软人工智能首席执行官穆斯塔法-苏莱曼（Mustafa Suleyman）在周五举行的科技公司 50 周年庆典上的发言被一名亲巴勒斯坦的员工抗议打断，原因是该公司与以色列的关系。【原文：Microsoft AI CEO Mustafa Suleyman's remarks were interrupted by a pro-Palestinian protesting employee during the technology company's 50th anniversary celebration on Friday over the firm's ties with Israel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/microsoft-ai-ceos-remarks-interrupted-by-pro-palestinian-protester-2025-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IIJ25SKINMNBF6HW4X53OSUDM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>