<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:33:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:33:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[EQT 计划减少开支，同时在 2025 年生产更多美国天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国第二大天然气生产商、美国能源公司 EQT 计划减少资本支出，但在 2025 年生产更多能源；而竞争对手 Range Resources 则表示，将从 2024 年起保持支出和产量相对稳定。【原文：U.S. energy company EQT , the country's second-biggest natural gas producer, plans to reduce capital spending but produce more energy in 2025, while rival Range Resources said it would hold expenditures and output relatively steady from 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eqt-plans-spend-less-while-producing-more-us-natgas-2025-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQDDFBTQX5JDZKYSM2P3625R64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球圆桌会议认为，随着不确定性增加，低收入国家的债务风险也在上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球债务圆桌会议主席周三表示，需要做更多的工作来改进主权债务重组进程，并帮助面临日益严峻的偿债挑战的国家，他们同时还发布了一本新的手册来帮助这些努力。【原文：More work is needed to improve the sovereign debt restructuring process and help countries facing mounting debt service challenges, the chairs of a global debt roundtable said on Wednesday, as they released a new playbook to aid those efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-roundtable-sees-rising-debt-risks-low-income-countries-uncertainty-mounts-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QWJ6GZGCNNUTEUNNJRDLYUDNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国央行行长称美国可能因贸易战陷入衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国央行行长弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周三表示，美国可能会因全球贸易战的影响而陷入衰退，但包括欧元区在内的所有人都会受到影响，即使影响较小。【原文：The United States could dip into recession on the fallout from a global trade war but everyone will suffer, including the euro zone, even if to a lesser effect, French central bank chief Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-could-dip-into-recession-trade-war-french-central-banker-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5DWGTKG4VJ2ZNY23YSGPBZSYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:50:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国财政部长表示迫切需要降低关税的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国财政部长约尔格-库基斯（Joerg Kukies）周三在谈到与美国的贸易关税谈判时说，减少不确定性对经济和企业来说都是当务之急。【原文：Reducing uncertainty is urgent for economies and businesses, German Finance Minister Joerg Kukies said on Wednesday, talking about negotiations on trade tariffs with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/german-finance-minister-says-it-is-urgent-reduce-tariffs-uncertainty-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQIX7RU7TZIJTOPGX5D2HUBPY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电展示拼接更大、更快芯片的新技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾积体电路制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co on Wednesday unveiled technology for making faster chips and putting them together in dinner-plate sized packages that will boost performance needed for artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tsmc-shows-off-new-tech-stitching-together-bigger-faster-chips-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4WPK27TSVMLLJTDPI7NOH2FMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国和美国试图在联合国将对方描绘成恶霸]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国和美国周三在联合国安理会非正式会议上相互指责对方的不公平贸易做法，试图将对方描绘成贸易战升级中的全球恶霸。【原文：China and the United States accused each other of unfair trade practices at an informal United Nations Security Council on Wednesday, seeking to portray each other as global bullies amid their escalating trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-us-seek-portray-each-other-bullies-un-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3Z3IW564LZOQNOW2S6ANVIRLI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国排除在与日本贸易谈判中设定货币目标的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）在本周预计与日本财务大臣加藤胜信（Katsunobu Kato）举行会谈之前于周三表示，美国在与日本的双边贸易谈判中没有特定的货币目标。【原文：The U.S. does not have specific currency targets in mind as part of bilateral trade talks with Japan, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday, ahead of an expected meeting with Japanese Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-rules-out-setting-currency-targets-trade-talks-with-japan-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPWZHJ5PKRPCVEZDYIJSWN6XF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储称最近几周美国经济活动稳定，但不确定性普遍存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三在一份报告中称，自3月份以来，美国大部分地区的物价上涨，经济活动和就业情况变化不大，这份报告反映了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普反复无常地推出旨在重塑全球贸易的全面关税措施所带来的一些早期影响。【原文：U.S. prices are up and economic activity and employment have changed little since March across most of the nation, the Federal Reserve said on Wednesday in a report that captures some of the early fallout from U.S. President Donald Trump's erratic rollout of sweeping tariffs aimed at reshaping global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economic-activity-steady-recent-weeks-uncertainty-pervasive-fed-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W67OLFFURFNETBL7TM3BGE5XZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥 Banorte 公司再次权衡收购 Banamex 公司事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥银行 Banorte 的首席执行官周三告诉分析师，Banorte 将再次考虑收购 Banamex。【原文：Mexican lender Banorte will again consider a potential purchase of Banamex, Citi's one-time retail unit in the country which it split off last year, Banorte's CEO told analysts on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mexicos-banorte-once-again-weighs-banamex-purchase-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BORY7SG3WVIFXIXFEJEUZN6MYE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:55:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，马斯克的 Neuralink 公司估值可达 85 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克的大脑植入公司 Neuralink 计划以 85 亿美元的投前估值融资约 5 亿美元。【原文：Elon Musk's brain implant company Neuralink is planning to raise about $500 million at a pre-money valuation of $8.5 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-neuralink-could-fetch-85-billion-valuation-bloomberg-reports-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MAQFINEMJPCBCIXRXDEGJ4IDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢旺达称正与美国就可能的矿产交易进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[卢旺达周三表示，它正在与美国就潜在的矿产交易进行谈判，这是继华盛顿与卢旺达的邻国刚果民主共和国正在进行类似谈判之后的又一进展。【原文：Rwanda said on Wednesday it was in talks with the U.S. over a potential minerals deal, a development that follows similar ongoing talks between Washington and Rwanda's neighbour Democratic Republic of Congo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/rwanda-says-it-talks-with-us-possible-minerals-deal-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7UKFTHHDBMV7H7PWH2VCEH7TI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:50:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称中国关税不可持续，美国释放缓和信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，美国和中国之间的高关税是不可持续的，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府对缓和世界两大经济体之间的贸易战持开放态度，这场贸易战已引发了对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that high tariffs between the United States and China are not sustainable, as President Donald Trump's administration signaled openness to de-escalating a trade war between the world's two largest economies that has raised fears of recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-china-tariffs-are-not-sustainable-us-signals-willingness-de-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNOS264ZPVITVEIUKLUCQTJI6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:39:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行将拜耳、凯悦和其他首席执行官纳入私营部门倡议]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行（World Bank）周三增添了四位高层管理人员，其中包括拜耳公司（Bayer AG）首席执行官比尔-安德森（Bill Anderson）和凯悦酒店集团（Hyatt Hotels）首席执行官马克-霍普拉马齐安（Mark Hoplamazian）。【原文：The World Bank on Wednesday added four top executives, including Bayer AG CEO Bill Anderson and Hyatt Hotels CEO Mark Hoplamazian, to an initiative working to address barriers to private sector investment in developing countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/world-bank-adds-bayer-hyatt-other-ceos-private-sector-initiative-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFEADIFB2VOOTA2VRLSAE3EOZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:04:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管受到关税影响，EssilorLuxottica 仍确认前景展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷朋（Ray-Ban）制造商依视路（EssilorLuxottica）周三确认了其到2026年的业绩预测，但同时表示正在采取措施控制美国进口关税的影响，此前该公司公布的第一季度收入按不变汇率计算增长了7.3%。【原文：Ray-Ban maker EssilorLuxottica on Wednesday confirmed its forecasts through 2026 but also said it was implementing measures to manage the impact of U.S. import duties, after it reported a 7.3% increase in first-quarter revenue at constant rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/essilorluxottica-confirms-outlook-despite-tariff-impact-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDTNKCRBIRKIDHEAUTLPESZZ5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长拉加德：美国关税可能对欧洲产生通货紧缩影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）周三表示，如果欧洲不采取反制措施，但美国关税会促使中国改变对该地区的出口路线，那么美国关税可能会对欧洲产生通货紧缩的影响。【原文：European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde said on Wednesday U.S. tariffs could have a disinflationary impact in Europe if there are no European countermeasures but they prompt China to reroute exports to the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ecbs-lagarde-us-tariffs-could-have-disinflationary-impact-europe-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEGHVL5QCNNHRCQIDXPJEF4IKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:54:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citadel的格里芬称特朗普需谨慎对待国债品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citadel 的创始人兼首席执行官肯尼斯-格里芬（Kenneth Griffin）周三表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府需要小心美国国债信用可能受到的损害。【原文：Citadel's founder and CEO Kenneth Griffin said on Wednesday that U.S. President Donald Trump's administration needs to be careful about potential damage to the creditworthiness of U.S. Treasuries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/citadels-griffin-says-trump-needs-be-careful-about-treasuries-brand-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCQ4RQPJTFKZNNN5STLUV2DOFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯第一季度销售额增长 13]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿迪达斯周三公布，第一季度销售额增长 13%，达到 61.5 亿欧元（69.8 亿美元）。【原文：Adidas on Wednesday reported a 13% rise in sales to 6.15 billion euros ($6.98 billion) in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/adidas-sales-rise-by-13-first-quarter-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BR2ECB77CBJSFMHKDLBZVU6SBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储处于政策和政治的十字路口，带来全球风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[将美国联邦储备局视为稳定之源的全球央行行长们现在面临着一个难以预测的时期，美联储的货币政策决策正朝着相互冲突的方向发展，该机构的独立性可能面临风险。【原文：Global central bankers who have come to view the U.S. Federal Reserve as a source of stability now face an unpredictable period where the Fed's monetary policy decisions are being pulled in conflicting directions and the institution's independence could be at risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-policy-political-crossroads-poses-global-risks-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKMQCDUYIRKFJEDZQLV2GKJPOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉高管因安全问题取消罗马会议之旅]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉公司的一位高管取消了出席在罗马举行的一次会议，因为她担心该汽车制造商会因首席执行官埃隆-马斯克的右翼活动而遭到抗议。【原文：A Tesla senior executive has cancelled her attendance at a conference in Rome over fears of protests surrounding the carmaker in response to CEO Elon Musk's right-wing activism.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-exec-cancels-rome-conference-trip-over-security-concerns-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PN4WKYAT3BOE7J54TU7MD4BY7I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新泽西州起诉 RealPage，称其与房东串通抬高租金]]></title><description><![CDATA[新泽西州周三起诉物业管理软件公司 RealPage，指控其与该州一些大房东非法合谋抬高住宅租金。【原文：New Jersey sued the property management software company RealPage on Wednesday, accusing it of illegally conspiring with some of the state's largest landlords to drive up residential rents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/new-jersey-sues-realpage-says-collusion-with-landlords-drives-up-rents-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTNKBP7N2FODVIPMIKSCJHDGBA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:33:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 向全球广告商开放 Threads]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周三表示，它正在将其社交网络 Threads 上的广告扩展到全球所有符合条件的广告商，因为它希望在品牌关税的不确定性中创造新的收入来源。【原文：Meta Platforms said on Wednesday it is expanding advertising on its social network Threads to all eligible advertisers globally, as it looks to generate new revenue streams amid brand uncertainty over tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/meta-opens-threads-advertisers-globally-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ID7WSOV36NPF7HBN7DK3XP3KBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行下调拉美和加勒比地区增长预期，强调不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行周三将其对拉丁美洲和加勒比地区2025年经济增长的预测从1月份的2.5%下调至2.1%，称该地区经济体必须进行调整，以应对日益加剧的全球不确定性。【原文：The World Bank on Wednesday cut its 2025 economic growth forecast for Latin America and the Caribbean to 2.1% from its January forecast of 2.5%, saying regional economies must adapt to navigate increasing global uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/world-bank-cuts-latin-american-caribbean-growth-view-highlights-uncertainties-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CS4SNEIYKJJORGVLJS7NFHAD3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官制定新战略，Worldline推迟发布盈利指引]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国数字支付公司 Worldline 周三表示，由于新管理层上任和全球经济波动加剧，该公司将把年度财务前景更新推迟到 7 月份。【原文：French digital payments company Worldline will postpone its annual financial outlook update until July, it said on Wednesday, citing its new management and increased global economic volatility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/worldline-postpones-earnings-guidance-ceo-works-new-strategy-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDA3JJVGO5NAXALN4ZGLUWW25E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：国际货币基金组织的格奥尔基耶娃和世界银行的班加需要赢得特朗普政府的信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）和世界银行行长阿贾伊-班加（Ajay Banga）都是很好的领导者，但他们必须赢得特朗普政府的信任，使这些机构重新专注于其核心使命。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva and World Bank President Ajay Banga are both good leaders but they will have to earn the Trump administration's trust refocusing the institutions on their core missions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/imfs-georgieva-world-banks-banga-need-earn-trump-administrations-trust-bessent-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3ZB7OVSHBN7LGYUA3NR6DRNF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:57:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯预测关税抑制需求将导致生产商支出下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国油田服务供应商贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周三预测，由于关税削弱了需求预期并推低了原油价格，全球石油生产商的支出将大幅下降。【原文：U.S. oilfield service provider Baker Hughes on Wednesday forecast steeper drops in spending by global oil producers as tariffs dent demand expectations and push down prices for crude.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/baker-hughes-forecasts-drop-producer-spending-tariffs-pinch-demand-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDACQEUEMVIL3E5HOAWSQA6T5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:52:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kering 公布第一季度销售额下降 14%，Gucci 销售额进一步下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[开云集团（Kering）周三公布的第一季度营收降幅超过预期，这是该奢侈品集团最新公布的一组令人失望的业绩，因为其明星品牌古驰（Gucci）在日益恶化的经济环境中继续挣扎。【原文：Kering reported on Wednesday a bigger-than-expected decline in first-quarter revenue, the latest set of disappointing results from the luxury group as its star label Gucci continues to struggle amid a worsening economic environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kering-reports-14-sales-drop-first-quarter-gucci-sales-slide-further-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">374KG6HZSNO65A2ZRBPIPBII4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:49:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：中美关税必须下降才能启动贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，他认为中美之间过高的关税必须先降下来，然后才能进行贸易谈判。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that he believes that excessively high tariffs between the U.S. and China will have to come down before trade negotiations can proceed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-china-tariffs-need-fall-trade-talks-start-bessent-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5VGQSCBXWVNLDDV5NS3WHDNTBI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:43:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：欧盟罚款后，苹果和 Meta 会怎样？]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构周三对苹果公司 AAPL.O 和 Meta 分别处以 5 亿欧元（5.7 亿美元）和 2 亿欧元的罚款，要求这两家公司遵守《数字市场法案》，该法案旨在允许较小的竞争对手进入由最大公司主导的市场。【原文：European Union antitrust regulators on Wednesday fined Apple AAPL.O 500 million euros ($570 million) and Meta 200 million euros to make the companies comply with the Digital Markets Act, which seeks to allow smaller rivals into markets dominated by the biggest companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/what-happens-apple-meta-after-eu-fine-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HERZUQ2BSBPZHLPDO6B4UKHSYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:42:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，因竞争问题，司法部正在调查迪斯尼与 FuboTV 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周三援引熟悉该计划的人士的话报道称，美国司法部官员正在调查迪士尼收购流媒体公司 FuboTV 控股权的交易。【原文：Officials at the U.S. Department of Justice are probing Disney's deal to take a controlling stake in streaming company FuboTV , Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/doj-probing-disney-fubotv-deal-over-competition-concerns-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGG3GDS6NVPOZPEF6DGGDUDT6I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:27:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称，美国原油库存意外增加，进口量猛增]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周三表示，由于进口量猛增，上周美国原油库存意外增加，而汽油和馏分油库存的降幅均超过预期。【原文：U.S. crude oil stockpiles rose unexpectedly last week as imports jumped, while both gasoline and distillate inventories fell more than expected, the Energy Information Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-stockpiles-post-surprise-build-imports-jump-eia-says-2025-04-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HV7GOMR7RLTBAWINQFXSRUAOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:18:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>