<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:22:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:22:52 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将审理埃克森美孚与太阳石油公司要求驳回博尔德市气候诉讼案的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一同意受理埃克森美孚和太阳石油公司提出的申请，该申请旨在驳回科罗拉多州博尔德市官员提起的诉讼。该诉讼要求石油公司为助长气候变化承担责任。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court agreed on Monday to hear a bid by ExxonMobil and Suncor Energy to scuttle a lawsuit brought by officials in Boulder, Colorado that seeks to hold the oil companies liable for helping to fuel climate change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-supreme-court-hear-exxon-suncor-bid-toss-boulders-climate-suit-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZJNOX5VZOVINHDL3EFVHM4N3JE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:42:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟议员因关税风波推迟对美贸易协定投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟议会一直在讨论取消对美国商品多项进口关税的提案。【原文：The EU assembly has been debating proposals to remove many import duties on U.S. goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-lawmakers-postpone-vote-us-trade-deal-after-tariff-upheaval-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZRWAFCUW5MMBCBDUZHJD6PDTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:41:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMC娱乐公司票房收入超预期，影院票房持续复苏]]></title><description><![CDATA[AMC娱乐公司周一公布的第四季度营收超出华尔街预期，表明市场对影院客流量从疫情低谷缓慢回升持乐观态度。【原文：AMC Entertainment beat Wall Street expectations for fourth-quarter revenue on Monday, offering a sign of confidence in the slow recovery of cinema traffic from pandemic-era lows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/amc-entertainment-beats-revenue-estimates-box-office-recovers-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P64UCMZVHNOI7B4QNP66UH4TTM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:31:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，诺沃农业公司CagriSema项目受挫或将使投资者关注点转向并购战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德新一代减肥药CagriSema在与礼来公司Zepbound的直接对比试验中效果逊色，这对这家丹麦制药商试图在蓬勃发展的肥胖症药物市场重夺早期领先地位的努力又是一记重击。【原文：Novo Nordisk's next-generation weight-loss drug CagriSema was less effective than Eli Lilly's Zepbound in a head-to-head trial, a fresh blow to the Danish drugmaker's efforts to reclaim its early lead in the booming obesity drug market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/view-novos-cagrisema-setback-may-shift-investor-focus-ma-strategy-analysts-say-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5SPQZE6WZP7NIROM7BXFI3IKI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IQM量子计算机公司将在美国上市，初始估值达18亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于芬兰的IQM量子计算机公司周一宣布，计划通过与特殊目的收购公司Real Asset Acquisition Corp合并的方式，在美国股市上市。【原文：Finnish-headquartered IQM Quantum Computers is aiming to list its shares on the U.S. stock market via a merger with a special purpose acquisition company Real Asset Acquisition Corp , the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/iqm-quantum-computers-list-shares-us-initial-18-billion-valuation-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGZLHVLJGZK6ZAU4OXCDJB5VKA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：ASML揭示EUV光源技术突破，有望在2030年前提升50%芯片产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[ASML控股公司的研究人员表示，他们已找到一种方法，可提升关键芯片制造设备光源的功率，使芯片产量在本世纪末前增加50%，从而帮助这家荷兰企业保持对新兴的美国和中国竞争对手的优势。【原文：Researchers at ASML Holding say they have found a way to boost the power of the light source in a key chip making machine to turn out up to 50% more chips by decade's end, to help retain the Dutch company's edge over emerging U.S. and Chinese rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asml-unveils-euv-light-source-advance-that-could-yield-50-more-chips-by-2030-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNGG34MDYFOMFGOEKO4H62ZN2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来将在美国推出多剂量减肥药物装置]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周一宣布，其减肥药物泽普邦（Zepbound）的四剂量速效笔（KwikPen）已获美国食品药品监督管理局批准上市。该装置可提供整月的治疗剂量，实现单次注射完成整月疗程。【原文：Eli Lilly said on Monday it received the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's approval to launch a four-dose KwikPen for its weight-loss drug Zepbound, delivering a full month of the treatment in a single device.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-launch-multi-dose-weight-loss-drug-device-us-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PM5WKVFDQBO5TMYRVUPUPADTPM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多米尼恩能源公司年度利润预测低于预期，上调支出计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[多米尼能源公司周一公布的年度利润预测低于华尔街预期，但该公司将五年资本支出计划上调近30%，以加大努力满足激增的电力需求。【原文：Dominion Energy forecast annual profit below Wall Street expectations on Monday, but raised its five-year capital spending plan by nearly 30% as the utility ramps up its efforts to meet soaring electricity demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/dominion-energy-forecasts-annual-profit-below-estimates-raises-spending-plan-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKZJYUEHEBIP3BRYUWQSBSRCIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI深化与咨询巨头的合作，推动企业人工智能突破试点阶段]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI正通过与全球四大顶级咨询公司合作，加速进军企业市场。该公司押注更务实的合作模式，将助力企业客户突破试点项目阶段，实现人工智能的全面部署。【原文：OpenAI is expanding its push into the enterprise market by teaming up with four of the world’s largest consulting firms, betting that a more hands-on approach will help corporate clients move beyond pilot projects to full-scale AI deployments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-deepens-partnerships-with-consulting-giants-push-enterprise-ai-beyond-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCUZHTJILVNP5MLURJOWPQ447U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储委员沃勒：1月就业数据表现强劲，若此趋势延续，暂停政策调整或为明智之举]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗·沃勒表示，若即将公布的2月就业数据显示美国劳动力市场在2025年疲软后已"转向更稳固的基础"，他愿意在美联储3月会议上维持利率不变。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Christopher Waller said he was open to leaving interest rates on hold at the Fed's March meeting if upcoming February jobs data indicates the U.S. labor market had "pivoted to a more solid footing" after a weak 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-waller-january-jobs-data-an-upside-surprise-if-it-continues-policy-pause-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IY4ONA5TRVI3VNVJFUPC62PUF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰国际集团报告称，美元已丧失部分避险货币地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰国际集团周一在一份报告中指出，自2024年以来，美元作为避险货币的部分价值已有所减弱，但并非全部丧失。不过该机构同时表示，尚未观察到全球对美元需求的普遍恶化。【原文：The dollar has lost some, but not all, of its safe-haven value since 2024, ING said in note on Monday, adding however, that it saw no broad deterioration in global demand for the US currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dollar-has-lost-some-its-safe-haven-status-ing-report-says-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IVB4W5L5G5N27G52YAHPJVELEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德将以最高78亿美元收购癌症疗法开发商Arcellx]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司周一宣布，将斥资高达78亿美元收购其合作伙伴Arcellex，这是该公司自2020年以来规模最大的交易，旨在强化其抗癌药物产品线。【原文：Gilead Sciences will pay as much as $7.8 billion to acquire its partner Arcellex in its largest deal since 2020, the biopharma company said on Monday, as it looks to strengthen its lineup of cancer treatments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/gilead-acquire-cancer-therapy-developer-arcellx-up-78-billion-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJ263JE2ZRNVFOFBUYLD53YSZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再度抨击美国最高法院，誓言加征关税并限制许可证发放]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普在最高法院上周裁定其大规模关税计划违宪后，再次谴责该法院，并誓言将动用其他关税权力和许可，但未透露具体细节。【原文：President Donald Trump renewed his condemnation of the U.S. Supreme Court after it ruled against his sweeping tariff program last week, vowing to turn to other tariff powers and licenses but giving no details.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-renews-attack-us-supreme-court-vows-other-tariffs-licenses-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALW5WEC3JRLJVO2CWFFJUL5ZRI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:18:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将就印度、印尼和老挝产太阳能电池板作出关税决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部将于周一公布初步裁决，决定是否对从印度、老挝和印度尼西亚进口的太阳能电池及组件征收反补贴税。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department on Monday will reveal a preliminary decision on whether to impose anti-subsidy duties on solar cells and panels imported from India, Laos and Indonesia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-make-tariff-decision-solar-panels-india-indonesia-laos-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFMGMLIYKZJ27ADVCNHLNEHMPI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞标：至高不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDW2ENMTLVLOTAG3RKISMKJI54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据Axios报道，美国国防部长赫格塞斯召见Anthropic公司首席执行官，就克劳德人工智能在军事领域的应用展开严厉交涉。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Axios周一援引消息人士报道，美国国防部长皮特·赫格塞斯已于周二召见人工智能公司Anthropic首席执行官达里奥·阿莫代至五角大楼，预计将就该公司克劳德人工智能工具的军事用途展开可能较为严厉的会谈。【原文：U.S. Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has summoned artificial intelligence company Anthropic's CEO Dario Amodei to the Pentagon on Tuesday for what is expected to be potentially tough talks over the military use of Anthropic's Claude artificial intelligence tool, Axios reported on Monday, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-defense-secretary-hegseth-summons-anthropic-ceo-tough-talks-over-military-use-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROHK5GCNDZMEHHANZVJEWE66P4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:51:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德股价暴跌，试验受挫令韦戈维时代最后涨幅化为乌有]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德股价周一暴跌逾15%，抹去了此前Wegovy上市带来的全部涨幅。此前这家制药公司表示，其新一代减肥药CagriSema在临床试验中表现逊于礼来公司的tirzepatide。【原文：Novo Nordisk shares fell more than 15% on Monday, wiping away the last gains Wegovy's launch had brought, after the drugmaker said its next-generation obesity drug CagriSema underperformed Eli Lilly's tirzepatide in a trial.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-slump-wipes-out-last-wegovy-era-gains-after-trial-setback-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7M3CDIIELJJTRMDMHTTXBFKOBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国隐私监管机构在联合声明中对人工智能生成的图像发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国隐私监管机构周一与数十个国际监管机构发表联合声明，对人工智能生成的图像表示担忧——这些图像未经当事人同意便描绘了可识别身份的个体。【原文：Britain's privacy watchdog published a joint statement with dozens of international authorities on Monday, setting out concerns over images generated by artificial intelligence which depict identifiable individuals without their consent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-privacy-watchdog-warns-over-ai-generated-images-joint-statement-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6ATNGHS3ZJHFINC4TOBY4FJ44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克将设立独立癌症业务部门以弥补Keytruda专利到期损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司周一宣布，将把人类健康业务拆分为两个部门，将其由Keytruda主导的重磅抗癌业务与非肿瘤药物业务分开。【原文：Merck said on Monday it will split its human-health business into two divisions, separating its blockbuster cancer franchise led by Keytruda from its non-oncology medicines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-create-separate-cancer-business-offset-keytruda-patent-loss-wsj-reports-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4M7SNEKDOFLNPDUWLTMOGKHI6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士表示仍致力于与美国达成具有法律约束力的贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政府周一表示，该国仍计划通过与美国的谈判促成一项具有法律约束力的协议，旨在最终敲定2025年底达成的初步协议——该协议将美国对瑞士商品的关税从39%降至15%。【原文：Switzerland still plans to broker a legally-binding agreement from talks with the United States aimed at finalising a preliminary deal struck in late 2025 that cut U.S. tariffs on Switzerland to 15% from 39%, the government said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/switzerland-says-still-aiming-legally-binding-trade-deal-with-us-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4E4KDLF5BKKBGFX5AU76VKPL4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:21:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度电信公司巴蒂电信将投资22亿美元扩大数字贷款业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度第二大移动运营商巴蒂电信周一宣布，未来几年将向旗下金融部门投资2000亿卢比（约合22亿美元），以加速推进数字贷款业务。【原文：Bharti Airtel will invest 200 billion rupees ($2.2 billion) in its financial arm over the next few years, India's second-largest mobile carrier by number of users said on Monday, as it steps up its push into digital lending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-telecom-firm-bharti-airtel-invest-22-billion-expand-digital-lending-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISTRJGTK5JLK7ORRE67E52X4SM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必胜客美国销售额超预期，优惠活动吸引精打细算的顾客]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美乐披萨周一公布的美国第四季度同店销售额超出华尔街预期，这家快餐连锁企业以价值驱动的促销活动和新菜品推动了需求增长。【原文：Domino's Pizza beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter U.S. same-store sales on Monday, as the fast-food chain's value-driven promotions and new menu items fueled demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dominos-beats-us-sales-estimates-deals-attract-budget-conscious-customers-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4B6M2YD4FLF5BCNY4SK3PST3A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利德以78亿美元收购Arcellx]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉利德科学公司周一宣布将收购癌症疗法开发商Arcellx，交易隐含股权价值达78亿美元，推动Arcellx股价在盘前交易中飙升77.8%至113.99美元。【原文：Gilead Sciences said on Monday it will buy cancer therapy developer Arcellx for an implied equity value of $7.8 billion, sending shares of Arcellx climbing 77.8% to $113.99 in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/gilead-acquire-arcellx-78-billion-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SONFG3J7AFLSBHL47CB3UJ6CEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：人工智能威胁企业生存，软件公司面临更高借贷成本和更严格审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业消息人士称，软件公司正推迟债务融资交易，因借贷成本上升及贷款方审查趋严给该行业带来压力，而人工智能带来的日益增长的压力则威胁着其商业模式。【原文：Software companies are delaying debt deals as higher borrowing costs and tougher scrutiny from lenders weigh on the sector, at a time when mounting pressure from artificial intelligence threatens their business models, industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/software-companies-face-higher-borrowing-costs-tougher-scrutiny-ai-threatens-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSWKHZIQLVM23F7KI7M4LDG7CA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商正推动实现"无需注视"的驾驶技术，引发安全与责任归属的争议]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商正朝着实现完全无人驾驶汽车的漫长征程中一个关键里程碑全力冲刺：开发出允许驾驶员将视线移离道路——无论是发短信还是敲击笔记本电脑——的系统，除非车辆发出警报要求其重新接管控制权。【原文：Automakers are racing toward a key milestone on the long road to fully driverless cars: systems that let drivers take their eyes off the road – to shoot a text or peck away on a laptop – unless the car alerts them to retake control.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carmakers-push-toward-eyes-off-driving-raising-questions-safety-liability-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7BFKMSR3BKUJJF7N3LHF3YX3M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将审理埃克森公司向古巴索赔案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院将于周一审议一项法律的适用范围，该法律允许美国企业就古巴没收财产寻求赔偿。此案涉及埃克森美孚公司和邮轮运营商，正值特朗普政府加大对古巴政府施压之际。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court will consider on Monday the scope of a law that lets American companies seek compensation for property seized by Cuba in cases involving ExxonMobil and cruise operators being argued at a time when President Donald Trump's administration is ramping up pressure on the Cuban government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-supreme-court-hear-exxon-bid-compensation-cuba-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTS4SCHUGJM3TAL3RI6YLKHFSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货下跌，关税疑虑打击风险偏好]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周一走低，因关税不确定性再度升温令投资者感到不安。此前尽管最高法院裁定推翻了特朗普总统更广泛的关税措施，但特朗普仍宣布将对部分商品加征15%的关税。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Monday as renewed tariff uncertainty unnerved investors after President Donald Trump announced a new 15% duty despite a Supreme Court ruling that struck down his broader levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-dip-tariff-doubts-hit-risk-appetite-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JT7JFICHZLU5OONVXDRY3SWLY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威普罗首席技术官表示人工智能是机遇而非威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度威普罗公司高管表示，人工智能的快速普及将推动软件服务供应商需求增长而非萎缩，此言反驳了该技术将威胁行业外包模式的担忧。【原文：India's Wipro expects rapid AI adoption to boost rather than shrink demand for software service providers, a top executive said, countering concerns that the technology threatens the industry's outsourcing model.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/wipros-cto-says-ai-is-an-opportunity-not-threat-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSQE7JVTENOLPADQXTY24WOXII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士工业团体称特朗普最新关税上调加剧混乱局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普上周末宣布将所有国家对美出口商品的临时关税从10%提高至15%，此举引发了更多混乱。瑞士工业协会Swissmem周一表示，全球不确定性正在抑制投资活动。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's weekend announcement that he would increase a temporary tariff on U.S. imports from all countries to 15% from 10% has created more chaos, and the global uncertainty is dampening investment activity, Swiss industry association Swissmem said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/swiss-industry-group-says-trumps-latest-us-tariff-hike-creates-more-chaos-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJLMBQHQ7FLFNIJVON6DF3LPMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德减肥药CagriSema在临床试验中逊于礼来公司产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德周一表示，其新一代减肥药CagriSema在直接对比试验中效果逊于礼来公司的tirzepatide，这标志着在减肥药市场主导权争夺战中遭遇挫折。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Monday its next-generation obesity drug CagriSema was less effective than Eli Lilly's tirzepatide in a head-to-head trial, a setback in the race for dominance in the weight-loss drug market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisks-obesity-drug-falls-short-against-eli-lillys-copenhagen-trial-2026-02-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INUR3NIW45P7FG5HKCOVF2GYFI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>