<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:19:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:19:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能公司Eightfold因协助企业秘密评分求职者而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[由风险投资支持的人工智能招聘平台Eightfold AI正面临加州诉讼，该公司服务于微软、PayPal等众多《财富》500强企业，被指控在求职者不知情的情况下编写用于筛选应聘者的报告。【原文：Eightfold AI, a venture capital-backed artificial intelligence hiring platform ​used by Microsoft , PayPal and many other Fortune 500 companies, is being sued in California for ‌allegedly compiling reports used to screen job applicants without their knowledge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ai-company-eightfold-sued-helping-companies-secretly-score-job-seekers-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVPQA6EQY5KNVBG6RKW7VJ2H6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝索斯的蓝色起源公司将部署数千颗卫星，用于建设全新的"TeraWave"通信网络。]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰夫·贝索斯的太空公司蓝色起源周三宣布，计划在太空部署5408颗卫星构建通信网络，为数据中心、政府及企业提供服务，由此进军由埃隆·马斯克的SpaceX主导的卫星星座市场。【原文：Jeff Bezos' space company Blue Origin on Wednesday announced a plan to deploy 5,408 satellites in space for a communications network that will serve data centers, governments and businesses, jumping into a satellite constellation market dominated by Elon Musk's SpaceX.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/bezos-blue-origin-deploy-thousands-satellites-new-terawave-communications-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CRJXP2U5BKJZKOODXTR27LB5A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，欧盟将同时评估奈飞与派拉蒙对华纳兄弟的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周三报道，欧盟反垄断监管机构预计将同时审查奈飞与派拉蒙天空舞影业对华纳兄弟探索公司的竞购提案，这将形成一场不同寻常的正面交锋式并购审查。【原文：The European Union's antitrust regulators are expected to scrutinize rival bids by Netflix and Paramount Skydance for Warner Bros. Discovery at the same time, setting up an unusual head-to-head competition review, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eu-weigh-netflix-paramount-bids-warner-bros-same-time-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PO6ZMJYEQZJXNMY62F7BMQPDBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车推出EX60电动SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车周三表示，其新款电动中型SUV EX60的定价将与同款插电式混合动力车型持平。这家瑞典车企同时驳斥了外界担忧——即任何与格陵兰相关的美国关税措施都可能打乱其计划。【原文：Volvo Cars said on Wednesday that its new electric mid-sized SUV, the EX60, will have a similar price tag to the plug-in hybrid version of the same model, as the Swedish automaker dismissed concerns that any Greenland-linked U.S. tariffs could disrupt its plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-unveils-its-ex60-electric-suv-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTSRTBFLBBPUHHWOYMIV6KU4LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[育碧宣布大规模重组，更新目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电子游戏发行商育碧周三宣布将进行重组，公司将拆分为五个创意部门，同时修订其财务展望。【原文：French video game publisher Ubisoft will undergo a reorganization, splitting the company into five creative divisions, it said on Wednesday while also revising its financial outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ubisoft-unveils-sweeping-restructuring-updates-targets-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2EPXN3ICRNKXLDIBBXKPXWEYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康集团将为其奥巴马医改计划客户提供返利]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团首席执行官斯蒂芬·赫姆斯利在周三发布的书面证词中表示，该公司将于2026年向其奥巴马医改计划参保人提供返利。【原文：UnitedHealth Group Inc. will provide rebates to its Obamacare plan members in 2026, company CEO Stephen Hemsley said in a prepared testimony released Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-offer-rebates-its-obamacare-customers-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEM2HEU3AVPV7INXOXCHPEDAAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英杰华集团高管在达沃斯表示，公司避开数据中心投资，专注于服务领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[另类投资公司英仕集团周三表示，其副总裁兼首席投资官称，该公司正回避对数据中心的大规模投资，认为该领域竞争过于激烈，转而选择能提供更高回报且能规避地缘政治风险的领域。【原文：Alternative investment firm Investcorp is eschewing big investments in data centres, a space it considers too crowded, its vice president and CIO said on Wednesday, opting instead for sectors offering better returns and shelter from geopolitical risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/investcorp-shies-away-data-centre-investment-focuses-services-executive-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2RQGPSBJBKKNEWF5NQ5QR63X4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田关联公司就叉车发动机排放作弊指控达成4.36亿美元和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[三家丰田关联公司就一起美国集体诉讼达成和解，涉及金额约4.36亿美元。该诉讼指控其在九款叉车发动机中存在排放作弊行为。【原文：Three Toyota affiliates reached a settlement worth an estimated $436 million of a proposed U.S. class action accusing them of emissions cheating in nine engines for forklift trucks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/toyota-affiliates-436-million-settlement-over-alleged-forklift-engine-emissions-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNSP5AAIFRIX7GKHHHZUKQIQRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普引发的市场动荡冲击新兴市场债券销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[据投资者透露，在特朗普总统强力推动收购格陵兰岛引发市场广泛恐慌后，贝宁计划发行的政府债券已被搁置，而格鲁吉亚债券发行的时机也悬而未决。【原文：Benin's planned government bond sale has been put on hold while the timing for one from Georgia is also in flux, according to investors, after U.S. President Donald ​Trump's aggressive push to take control of Greenland caused widespread market jitters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-market-jitters-hit-emerging-market-bond-sales-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYDEGUQESVL4TPFQ5ESCU4XEOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储主席候选人都很棒，直到他们上任为止]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普表示，他已面试了多位实力雄厚的美联储主席候选人，但抱怨称提名人选一旦上任往往会改变立场。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said he has interviewed several strong candidates for Federal Reserve chair, but complained that nominees tend to change once they take office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trump-says-fed-chair-candidates-are-great-until-they-get-job-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWLJNFDVFVJTVDRUQJ3B6J2GSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国10月建筑支出因翻修工程而反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国10月建筑支出增幅超预期，这可能反映了房屋翻修活动的增长，而其他领域的建筑活动则表现疲软。【原文：U.S. construction spending increased more than expected in October, likely reflecting home renovations, with activity elsewhere weak.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-construction-spending-rebounds-october-amid-renovations-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQWRZOD7ZRPVBLBXE3LPMBZWVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:33:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动空中出租车制造商Archer与塞尔维亚合作，共同开拓全球市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿彻航空周三宣布，已与塞尔维亚达成合作，成为该国首选的电动垂直起降飞机合作伙伴，此举旨在拓展全球市场。【原文：Archer Aviation said on Wednesday it had partnered with Serbia as the country's preferred electric vertical take-off and landing aircraft partner, in a move to expand into global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/electric-air-taxi-maker-archer-partners-with-serbia-global-markets-push-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIWWRI5DRZKONPKNQ4WO7OCPHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟议员因格陵兰问题抗议而搁置美欧贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲议会决定暂停审议欧盟与美国的贸易协定，以抗议美国总统唐纳德·特朗普要求收购格陵兰岛的行径，以及对反对其计划的欧洲盟友实施关税威胁的举动。【原文：The European Parliament has decided to suspend its work on the European Union's trade deal with the United States in protest at U.S. President Donald Trump's demands to acquire Greenland and threats of tariffs on European allies who oppose his plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-parliament-suspends-work-eu-us-trade-deal-after-trumps-repeated-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQ7TACHH6VOSFIVHRWQJHRGMTY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：高盛晋升消费零售银行家，本·弗罗斯特出任投行主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[据内部备忘录显示，高盛已将顶级消费零售银行家本·弗罗斯特晋升为投资银行部主席，此前他主导了该行去年在该领域两笔最大交易的运作。【原文：Goldman Sachs has elevated top consumer retail banker Ben Frost to chairman of investment banking, according to an internal memo, after leading the bank's work on two of the biggest deals in the sector last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-promotes-consumer-retail-bankers-ben-frost-named-chairman-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53CIBYBGBBJUHMZJFWX4V62CEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:17:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月待售房屋签约量跌至五个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[12月美国二手房购买合同意外下滑，跌至五个月低点，这可能是因为对劳动力市场的担忧以及持续的入门级住房短缺抵消了抵押贷款利率的下降。【原文：Contracts to purchase previously owned U.S. homes unexpectedly fell in December, hitting a five-month low, likely as worries over the labor market and a persistent shortage of entry-level houses offset lower mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-pending-home-sales-slump-five-month-low-december-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEGLDTMU6JIFXJIGPIJ4RHYRBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:01:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SAP股价跌至17个月低点，人工智能驱动抛售潮蒸发1300亿美元市值]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国SAP公司股价周三延续数月跌势，跌至2024年8月以来最低点，自去年创纪录高点以来市值蒸发约1300亿美元。【原文：Shares in Germany's SAP extended a months-long downtrend on Wednesday, falling to their lowest since August 2024 and bringing the loss in market value since last year's record high to around $130 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sap-shares-hit-17-month-low-ai-driven-selloff-burns-130-bln-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCVVB46F4FKR3MI5H4Z5GRRXSQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗人工智能初创公司OpenEvidence在最新融资轮估值翻倍至120亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司OpenEvidence周三宣布，在获得英伟达和谷歌风投支持后，以120亿美元估值完成2.5亿美元新一轮融资，其估值在短短三个月内翻了一番。该公司开发的工具已被美国医生广泛使用。【原文：OpenEvidence, an AI startup whose tools are used by U.S. physicians, has raised $250 million in fresh funding at a $12 billion valuation, the ​Nvidia and Google Ventures-backed company said on Wednesday, doubling its ‌value in just three months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/medical-ai-startup-openevidence-doubles-valuation-12-billion-latest-round-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMCQFDXOP5KSJPMF3WM54FTOZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《商报》报道：特斯拉在柏林裁员1700人]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国《商报》周三报道称，特斯拉位于柏林郊外的超级工厂员工数量已减少约1700人。【原文：Tesla's workforce at its gigafactory outside Berlin has shrunk by some 1,700 employees, the Handelsblatt business daily reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tesla-reduces-berlin-staff-by-1700-handelsblatt-reports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGDLENH3GFLF5PEL3EAF75PRAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[查尔斯·施瓦布公司利润因利息收入和交易收入增加而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经纪公司嘉信理财周三公布第四季度利润增长，在动荡的市场环境中，其利息收入增加和交易收入强劲成为主要支撑因素。【原文：U.S. brokerage firm Charles Schwab posted a rise in fourth-quarter profit on Wednesday, ​buoyed by higher interest income and ‌strong trading revenue amid a volatile market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/charles-schwabs-profit-rises-higher-interest-income-trading-revenues-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJRFK7DH3FIOLOFU7C6KWPORQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:42:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将通过软件助手实现按里程计费的保险方案，保费可减半]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国保险公司Lemonade周三宣布，当特斯拉电动汽车启用全自动驾驶（FSD）辅助系统时，将为车主提供50%的保费折扣。该公司表示，数据显示该系统能有效降低事故发生率。【原文：U.S. insurer Lemonade said on Wednesday it would offer a 50% rate cut for drivers of Tesla electric vehicles when the automaker's Full Self-Driving (FSD) driver assistance software is steering because it had data showing it reduced accidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lemonade-halve-tesla-insurance-rates-miles-driven-with-software-assistant-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CRP6V4L4ZPO7AGUXVVBMQP7MY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[天哪！史密斯菲尔德食品公司收购了标志性的纳森斯美食店]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国猪肉加工企业史密斯菲尔德食品公司周三宣布，将以4.5亿美元收购拥有百年历史的纳森热狗品牌，此举使其旗下品牌组合新增了美国最具标志性的热狗品牌。【原文：U.S. pork processor Smithfield Foods will buy century-old Nathan's Famous in a $450 million deal that adds the most iconic U.S. hot dog name to its portfolio of brands, the company said Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hot-diggity-dog-smithfield-foods-acquires-iconic-nathans-famous-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSDYBBBSMZIUBP2NTYZXGAZX5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:18:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰雷兹季度业绩超预期，得益于强劲的国防业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字成像产品制造商泰雷兹科技公司周三公布的第四季度利润和营收超出华尔街预期，其航空航天与国防电子业务板块的强劲需求是主要推动力。【原文：Digital imaging products maker Teledyne Technologies on Wednesday beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit and revenue, led by robust demand in its aerospace and defense electronics segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/teledyne-quarterly-results-beat-estimates-strong-defense-business-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4Z2YTAH4FNFTKCDCG2TYZDTCM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:04:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院委员会将就赋予国会人工智能芯片出口监管权的法案进行投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管白宫人工智能事务主管戴维·萨克斯等人反对，一位关键共和党议员仍于周三安排委员会对一项法案进行投票，该法案将赋予国会对人工智能芯片出口的监管权。【原文：A key Republican lawmaker scheduled a committee vote on Wednesday for a bill that would give Congress power over artificial intelligence chip exports, despite pushback from White House AI czar David Sacks, among others.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-house-panel-vote-bill-give-congress-authority-over-ai-chip-exports-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZW2A6TAWBJ7ZF4LXVJAIWQLDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利称美国政策因素对去美元化程度至关重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普在债务、贸易、制裁、安全及国家关键机构方面的政策，很可能对美元地位的动摇程度起到决定性作用——华尔街投行摩根士丹利如是表示。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's policies around debt, trade, sanctions, security and the country's key institutions are likely to be critical in determining the extent ​of a shift away from the dollar, Wall Street bank Morgan ‌Stanley has said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-policy-factors-critical-extent-de-dollarisation-shift-morgan-stanley-says-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WJOFDG7YJNYPL7LBSXX4PB4GE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:57:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官戴蒙警告称，信用卡利率上限将引发经济灾难]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席执行官杰米·戴蒙周三表示，特朗普政府提议将信用卡利率上限设定为10%将引发经济灾难，但他同时补充称该行能够承受这一冲击。【原文：JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon said on Wednesday a proposed 10% cap on credit card interest rates by the Trump ​administration would be an economic disaster, but added that the bank would ‌survive the impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/jpmorgan-ceo-dimon-says-credit-card-rate-cap-will-be-an-economic-disaster-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GROIAT25LRILVCXNMTZ7T2XVKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:46:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix与华纳兄弟的协议或能缓解观众的订阅疲劳]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼克·拉弗勒是众多美国人中的一员，他们认为奈飞与华纳兄弟的合作或许能缓解"订阅疲劳"。【原文：Nick LaFleur is one of many Americans who think a Netflix-Warner Bros tie-up might provide some relief from "subscription fatigue."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/netflix-warner-bros-deal-could-offer-viewers-relief-subscription-fatigue-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMRYF3ZZEBLMXN7XWLXULJ4L64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行清算万事达银行，万事达卡暂停发卡业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行周三下令清算陷入困境的贷款机构Banco Master旗下子公司Will Financeira SA，这是针对该集团旗下流动性枯竭机构采取的最新严厉措施。【原文：Brazil's central bank ordered on Wednesday the liquidation of Will Financeira SA, a unit of ​troubled lender Banco Master, in the latest drastic step involving ‌illiquid institutions tied to the conglomerate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-central-bank-liquidates-banco-masters-will-mastercard-suspends-cards-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KI3JT3JWJJHXGDXHUYKKJPRLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国的里夫斯表示，对英美经济协议将得以维持充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国财政大臣瑞秋·里夫斯周三表示，尽管特朗普总统与欧洲因格陵兰问题引发的紧张局势不断升级，她仍确信去年与美国签署的经济协议将保持不变。【原文：British finance minister Rachel Reeves said ​on Wednesday she was confident that the economic deal signed ‌with the United States last year will stay intact, despite escalating tensions between President Donald Trump and Europe over Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/uks-reeves-says-confident-uk-us-economic-deal-will-hold-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEFMFSUT2JJFDLN5QLCRJ6C5IU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，赖特向石油公司高管表示委内瑞拉产量可提升30%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯·赖特周三向石油公司高管表示，委内瑞拉的石油产量可在短期至中期内从当前每日90万桶的水平提升30%。三位与会高管透露了这一消息。【原文：U.S. Energy Secretary Chris Wright told oil company executives on Wednesday that Venezuela's output can rise 30% from its current level of 900,000 barrels per day in the short- to medium-term, three executives who attended the meeting said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/wright-tells-oil-executives-that-venezuelas-output-can-rise-30-sources-say-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MBIFTZMQZOPTCEWUZWKAFMX7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔业绩将凸显转型成效，人工智能数据中心推动芯片需求增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔股东对公司业绩的乐观程度已达数个季度之最，他们押注首席执行官陈立武承诺的业务转型正在落地生根，同时数据中心快速扩张正推动其传统服务器芯片需求强劲增长。【原文：Intel shareholders are optimistic about the company's results like they have not been for many quarters, betting the turnaround CEO Lip-Bu Tan promised was taking root and that rapid data center build outs were fueling strong demand for its traditional server chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/intel-results-spotlight-turnaround-efforts-ai-data-centers-boost-chip-demand-2026-01-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RQGU4CM3RMERDAYDHPMVHH3DA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>