<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:40:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:40:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次批评美联储鲍威尔不降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四再次批评美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔，抱怨美联储拒绝降息。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump renewed his criticism on Thursday of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, complaining the Fed is refusing to lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-renews-criticism-feds-powell-not-cutting-rates-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2WGEAJ3KNIGDDRHTGOKTGR2CI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:29:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国交通部长呼吁全面改革空中交通管制系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）周四将敦促国会批准数十亿美元，用于更换老化的雷达、电信设备、塔台和其他设施，对摇摇欲坠的空中交通管制系统进行大修。【原文：U.S Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy will urge Congress on Thursday to approve billions of dollars to replace aging radar, telecommunications equipment, towers and other facilities in an overhaul of the crumbling air traffic control system, airline officials said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transportation-chief-call-overhaul-air-traffic-control-system-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPX2SD7BE5IABENPGCIJTMT2CU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:27:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易协定和英国央行降息抚平英国资产伤痕]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国贸易协议、降息以及与欧洲重新建立联系的希望刺激了投资者对英国市场长期低迷的乐观情绪，他们正在寻找替代动荡的华尔街和摇摇欲坠的美元的市场。【原文：Investors are betting on long-depressed UK markets as a U.S. trade deal, rate cuts and hopes for renewed links with Europe spur optimism for a revival as they search for alternatives to a volatile Wall Street and flailing dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/global-markets-britain-analysis-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZFET6Z6ZROBBMTNMSF6UFKD6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:25:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 特朗普宣布与英国达成 "突破性 "协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）和英国首相基尔-斯塔默（Keir Starmer）周四宣布就贸易问题达成 "突破性协议"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump and British Prime Minister Keir Starmer on Thursday announced a "breakthrough deal" on trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/view-trump-heralds-breakthrough-deal-with-uk-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJRUIPZXAZIBPDPDWGS2BHR3SI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金巴利第一季度收入和营业利润低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利烈酒集团坎帕里（Campari）公布的第一季度收入和调整后营业利润均有所下降，远低于分析师的预期，但集团确认了今年和中期的前景。【原文：Italian spirits group Campari posted a decline in revenue and adjusted operating profit in the first quarter, well below analysts expectations, but confirmed its outlook for this year and the medium term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/campari-posts-revenues-below-analysts-expectations-down-4-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6XIAQHMGVLMBNDOXU3OCF6I3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币因贸易协议乐观而突破 100,000 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币周四突破 100,000 美元，这是自 2 月初以来的首次，美国和英国之间达成的一项广泛协议为比特币提供了支撑，表明美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与世界其他国家的贸易战可能正在缓和。【原文：Bitcoin topped $100,000 on Thursday for the first time since early February, bolstered by a wide-ranging deal between the United States and the United Kingdom in a sign that perhaps U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war with the rest of the world is easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/bitcoin-tops-100000-trade-deal-optimism-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REEZUUDODZOU3BCUJCFOWZ76QQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:59:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FTX 对汤姆-布雷迪、斯蒂芬-库里、大谷翔平等人的诉讼范围缩小]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官缩小了投资者要求体育明星汤姆-布雷迪（Tom Brady）、斯蒂芬-库里（Stephen Curry）和大谷翔平（Shohei Ohtani）等名人为推广倒闭的加密货币交易所 FTX 而承担责任的诉讼范围，但并未驳回该诉讼。【原文：A federal judge narrowed but stopped short of dismissing a lawsuit by investors seeking to hold celebrities like sports stars Tom Brady, Stephen Curry and Shohei Ohtani liable for promoting the collapsed cryptocurrency exchange FTX.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ftx-lawsuit-against-tom-brady-stephen-curry-shohei-ohtani-others-is-narrowed-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNMOPDIWGRJMTPFHNAITRWK5XI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:57:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿波罗支持的阿斯彭保险公司估值 30 亿美元，股价在纽约证券交易所回归时大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，Aspen Insurance 的股票在纽约证券交易所的回报中比发行价上涨了 10.8%，这家总部位于百慕大的专业保险公司的估值达到 30.5 亿美元。【原文：Shares of Aspen Insurance rose 10.8% above the offer price in their New York Stock Exchange return on Thursday, valuing the Bermuda-based specialty insurer at $3.05 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/apollo-backed-aspen-insurance-valued-3-billion-shares-jump-nyse-return-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTRKIGHBGZP4DALEISXRHSMVUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:53:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 中心立即在内部部署人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四表示，其所有中心都必须立即在内部部署人工智能，并于 6 月 30 日实现全面整合。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Thursday all its centers will have to be deploy artificial intelligence internally immediately, with full integration on June 30.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-centers-deploy-ai-internally-immediately-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZME7PLIAFMD3CDYJR4JJTA76I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:48:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美英经济协议有哪些内容？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和英国周四宣布了一项降低部分商品关税的协议，美国削减了对汽车和钢铁的征税，双方都获得了更好的农产品市场准入。【原文：The United States and Britain announced a deal to lower tariffs on some goods on Thursday, with U.S. levies on cars and steel being cut and both sides gaining better access to agriculture markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/whats-us-uk-economic-deal-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4X3PPR6ZBOEFFLNPWXPR4XO4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国对 "大科技 "征收数字税不受贸易协议影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国政府表示，根据两国周四达成的贸易协议条款，英国对亚马逊、谷歌和 Meta 等美国公司征收的数字服务税将不会改变。【原文：Britain's digital services tax, imposed on U.S. companies like Amazon , Google and Meta , will not be changed under the terms of the trade deal agreed between the two countries on Thursday, the British government said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-digital-tax-big-tech-not-impacted-by-trade-deal-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETCFD2E2OFNFBJAJBBKQNOD2YQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长表示，英国将宣布以 100 亿美元收购波音公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周四在白宫宣布英美双边贸易协议时表示，英国将购买 100 亿美元的波音飞机。【原文：The United Kingdom will purchase $10 billion of Boeing planes, U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said at the White House on Thursday during the announcement of a bilateral trade deal between the UK and the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/uk-announce-10-billion-boeing-purchase-us-commerce-secretary-says-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UK7H32ME2ZO3FJWYEE6UCGPRDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:26:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国表示，美国将把对英国的汽车关税降至 10%，钢铁关税降至零]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国政府周四表示，作为与美国达成的经济协议的一部分，美国将立即把对英国汽车业的关税从27.5%降至10%，而对钢铁和铝的征税将降至零。【原文：Britain's car industry will see U.S. tariffs immediately slashed to 10% from 27.5%, while levies on steel and aluminium will reduce to zero, the British government said on Thursday, as part of an economic deal with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-will-slash-car-tariffs-uk-10-steel-levies-zero-says-uk-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33TY5IJTRFP63CKR7GSI44OH64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储调查发现家庭财务状况恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行（Federal Reserve Bank of New York）周四表示，由于对通胀前景的看法不一，4月份美国人对其当前和未来财务状况的看法以及对未来收入和收益的预期都有所下降。【原文：Americans’ views on their current and future financial situations, as well as their expectations for future earnings and income, soured in April, amid mixed views on the outlook for inflation, the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ny-fed-survey-finds-deteriorating-views-household-financial-situation-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RY4M3IGTRNPMRL3TOD6FBFOV6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:19:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在监管机构的反对声中，Talen Energy 考虑进行替代数据中心电力交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国大型电力公司塔伦能源公司（Talen Energy）的高管周四表示，该公司正在考虑为数据中心提供电力的替代安排，此前监管机构对直接从塔伦公司宾夕法尼亚州核电厂为亚马逊数据中心供电的计划进行了回击。【原文：Talen Energy is considering alternative arrangements to supply electricity to data centers, executives with the major U.S. power company said on Thursday, after regulators pushed back on a plan to fuel an Amazon data center directly from Talen's Pennsylvania nuclear power plant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/talen-energy-considers-alternative-data-center-power-deals-after-regulator-push-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUYAFPLDGJLNHHPSHRODRQIDIA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:55:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管关税对销售构成威胁，啤酒商仍对增长充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国关税对销售构成了一定的威胁，但欧洲啤酒制造商对其增长潜力仍充满信心，投资者也将这些公司视为全球贸易战愈演愈烈情况下相对安全的避风港。【原文：European beer makers remain confident about their growth potential despite U.S. tariffs posing some threat to sales and investors see the companies as a relatively safe haven in an intensifying global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/brewers-confident-growth-despite-tariffs-threat-sales-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIQBS5O2KROUVOQ7MDGDEI23NE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:49:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，雀巢为出售水务部门与罗斯柴尔德集团牵线]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，雀巢公司已聘请罗斯柴尔德集团（Rothschild）为今年晚些时候出售其水业务部门提供建议，因为这家瑞士食品巨头希望重新专注于更大的品牌。【原文：Nestle has hired Rothschild to advise on the sale of its water division later this year, four people familiar with the matter told Reuters, as the Swiss food giant looks to refocus on bigger brands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/land-use-biodiversity/nestle-lines-up-rothschild-water-unit-sale-sources-say-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNQGNLDJWVPKFPWNYMMJ6UYELM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月份批发库存略有下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于电器、木材、服装和农产品库存减少，3 月份美国批发库存增幅略低于初步估计。【原文：U.S. wholesale inventories increased slightly less than initially estimated in March amid decreases in the stocks of electrical, lumber, apparel and farm products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-wholesale-inventories-revised-slightly-lower-march-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4CZJBES45I37KREHKGYQGVEZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:20:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特高管称不计划回购或分拆商用车]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司高管周四在年度股东大会上回答有关这两个话题的提问时告诉股东，目前没有计划回购股票或分拆利润丰厚的商用车业务。【原文：Ford Motor executives told shareholders Thursday that there are no plans to offer stock buybacks or spin off its lucrative commercial vehicle operations, in response to questions on both topics at its annual shareholder meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-executives-say-no-buybacks-or-commercial-vehicle-spinoff-planned-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRSACF2XZFL65FCCCZVVRZI4GA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:44:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国企业排队出售 "创新债券"，利用中国政府的技术推动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的银行、券商和私募股权公司等公司周四启动了销售所谓的科技创新债券的计划。【原文：Chinese banks, brokerages and private equity firms are among companies kicking off plans on Thursday to sell so-called sci-tech innovation bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-companies-line-up-sell-innovation-bonds-capitalising-beijings-technology-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOPNUBEPJFMPBMF7CVS36EUNG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软件供应商 EPAM 提高年度预期，宣布更换首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[受企业对其 IT 咨询服务稳定需求的推动，EPAM Systems 周四上调了年度收入和利润预期，使其股价在盘前交易中上涨了约 10%。【原文：EPAM Systems raised its annual revenue and profit forecasts on Thursday, helped by steady enterprise demand for its IT consulting services, sending its shares up around 10% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/software-provider-epam-raises-annual-forecasts-announces-ceo-change-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOH3KNQQNNIUNEJDAWBGKOXLY4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:30:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税风险阻碍美国联储，全球央行出现分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着白宫关税威胁到美国通胀率的上升，以及美元贬值引发其他地区货币走强，各大央行正在出现分歧。【原文：Big central banks are diverging as White House tariffs threaten to raise U.S. inflation and a dash out of the dollar sparks disinflationary currency strength elsewhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-central-banks-graphic-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEHQMJ4F7BNJBHBJQJVX4PLK4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通新设绿色银行领导职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通在欧洲设立了一个新的部门主管，为可再生能源和绿色技术领域的客户提供支持，从而加强了其在欧洲的绿色金融和咨询业务。【原文：JP Morgan has bolstered its green finance and advisory offering in Europe with a new division head to support clients across renewable energy and green technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/jp-morgan-creates-new-green-banking-leadership-role-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U35WRIAPBPC3JO6C4V3KX7NVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:09:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，美国和俄罗斯正在探索恢复俄罗斯天然气流向欧洲的途径]]></title><description><![CDATA[八位熟悉会谈情况的消息人士告诉路透社，随着欧洲与俄罗斯能源关系的霜冻，华盛顿和莫斯科的官员就美国帮助恢复俄罗斯对欧洲大陆的天然气销售进行了讨论。【原文：With a frost covering Europe's energy relations with Russia, officials from Washington and Moscow have held discussions about the U.S. helping to revive Russian gas sales to the continent, eight sources familiar with the talks have told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-russia-explore-ways-restore-russian-gas-flows-europe-sources-say-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSPW47H2JBMDFMHAI7KEZF3P54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：Coinbase 将以 29 亿美元收购 Deribit]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引公司高管的话报道，最大的上市加密货币交易所 Coinbase 将以 29 亿美元的现金和股票收购 Deribit。【原文：Coinbase , the largest publicly traded cryptocurrency exchange, will acquire Deribit for $2.9 billion in cash and stock, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing company executives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/coinbase-acquire-deribit-29-billion-deal-wsj-reports-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBGI2OWDL5PQHHWXKTE5UKV5OU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:56:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第一季度工人生产率下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[第一季度美国工人的生产率出现了近三年来的首次下降，导致劳动力成本激增，在企业面临关税带来的成本上升之际，这可能会挤压企业的利润空间。【原文：U.S. worker productivity dropped in the first quarter for the first time in nearly three years, resulting in a surge in labor costs that could squeeze margins for businesses at a time when they are facing rising costs from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-worker-productivity-declines-first-quarter-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNENVVJ33BJXPOFDZ2E2LJSMTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:51:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱茵金属与 ICEYE 达成制造军用卫星的初步协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国莱茵金属公司（Rheinmetall）已同意与芬兰 ICEYE 公司组建一家合资企业，生产军用卫星。【原文：Rheinmetall has agreed with Finland's ICEYE to form a joint venture to make military satellites, part of a drive to repurpose automotive factories to serve the booming defence sector instead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rheinmetall-iceye-initial-deal-make-military-satellites-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAXJUX5PPVMW7DQV2MKOVTDG6Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:46:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数降幅超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济的美国人数量降幅超过预期，表明劳动力市场继续保持良好态势，但关税带来的风险正在增加。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell more than expected last week, suggesting the labor market continued to chug along, though risks are mounting from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-more-than-expected-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYAOLBRRWBJXBGOI44GR6GY2OA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:37:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查发现，尽管计划上调产量，欧佩克四月石油产量仍走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项调查显示，尽管原定的增产计划已经生效，但欧佩克 4 月份的石油产量仍有所下降，原因是美国再次试图遏制石油流动，导致委内瑞拉的供应量减少，而伊拉克和利比亚的石油产量降幅较小。【原文：OPEC oil output edged lower in April despite a scheduled output hike taking effect, a Reuters survey found, led by a cut in Venezuelan supply on renewed U.S. attempts to curb the flows and smaller drops in Iraq and Libya.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-april-oil-output-edges-lower-despite-plans-hike-survey-finds-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCZFYVLWJVJ7JLB2FCO3ATWO5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:33:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储继续按兵不动，欧洲各国央行仍将宽松政策提上日程]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲各国央行周四与美国央行形成鲜明对比，纷纷降息或暗示将采取宽松政策，即使美联储隔夜保持稳定，也让投资者猜测其下一步行动。【原文：Europe's central banks stood in stark contrast to their U.S. counterpart on Thursday, cutting interest rates or hinting at policy easing to come, even as the Federal Reserve kept a steady hand overnight and left investors guessing about its next move.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/central-banks-europe-keep-easing-agenda-even-fed-stays-firmly-hold-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XX53ONWURVML3ELY2XHVNIKSBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>