<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:08:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:08:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[供应紧张之际，欧盟技术负责人表示，欧盟将寻求与耐克森的外交解决方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟技术事务主管亨娜-维尔库宁（Henna Virkkunen）周五在与荷兰芯片制造商耐克斯佩里亚公司（Nexperia）举行虚拟会议后表示，由于担心供应紧张，欧盟决心与该公司寻求外交解决方案。【原文：The European Union is determined to find a diplomatic solution with Dutch chipmaker Nexperia amid concerns about a supply squeeze, EU tech chief Henna Virkkunen said on Friday after a virtual meeting with the Chinese-owned company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-seeks-diplomatic-solution-with-nexperia-eu-tech-chief-says-amid-supply-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKD5SDOOQ5KGDBEXF6LCK6XD2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:47:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西淡水河谷公司首席财务官称可能很快宣布特别股息]]></title><description><![CDATA[淡水河谷首席财务官马塞洛-巴奇（Marcelo Bacci）周五在巴西矿业公司第三季度财报发布后与分析师的电话会议上表示，淡水河谷很可能在未来几个月内宣布特别股息。【原文：Vale is likely to announce extraordinary dividends in the coming months, Chief Financial Officer Marcelo Bacci said during a call with analysts on Friday, following the release of the Brazilian miner's third-quarter results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-vale-likely-announce-extraordinary-dividends-soon-cfo-says-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNJ53OLU2BMW7MVDX3XFJN2OCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》称，巴菲特将发表致子女和股东的信，并将年度信件交给阿贝尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周四援引巴菲特助手的话称，沃伦-巴菲特将于 11 月 10 日发表致其三个子女和伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司股东的信，而格雷格-阿贝尔将在担任首席执行官后于 2 月份撰写伯克希尔公司的年度股东信。【原文：Warren Buffett will release a letter to his three children and Berkshire Hathaway shareholders on November 10, while Greg Abel will write Berkshire's annual shareholder letter in February after becoming chief executive, the Wall Street Journal said on Thursday, citing Buffett's assistant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/buffett-issue-letter-children-shareholders-hand-off-annual-letter-abel-wsj-says-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3P7DI3VVAVK25LXZIDVGL5TO3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:33:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车从巴西国家开发银行（BNDES）获得信贷额度，以推动混合动力汽车的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车周五表示，该公司已从巴西国家开发银行（BNDES）获得 23 亿雷亚尔（约合 4.2562 亿美元）的信贷额度，以促进混合动力汽车的开发并扩大巴西业务的出口。【原文：Volkswagen said on Friday it has secured 2.3 billion reais ($425.62 million) in credit lines from Brazil's state development bank BNDES to boost the development of hybrid vehicles and expand exports from its Brazilian operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/volkswagen-secures-credit-lines-brazils-bndes-boost-hybrids-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZBPWT6MHVKOJD3XHTVLS7DC3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:20:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美加不会重启贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，美国和加拿大不会重启贸易谈判，一周前他曾因加拿大安大略省播出的一则广告而叫停谈判。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday the United States and Canada will not restart trade talks, a week after he called off negotiations over an advertisement aired by the Canadian province of Ontario.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-says-us-canada-will-not-restart-trade-talks-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWVAKRE4ZFIBZMDDG7QAS5C6XU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:01:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受汽车零部件破产影响，First Guaranty Bancshares 转为季度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[First Guaranty Bancshares 周五表示，该公司第三季度出现亏损，原因是该公司计提了减值费用，并增加了与一家汽车零部件制造商破产有关的不良贷款准备金。【原文：First Guaranty Bancshares on Friday said it has swung to a third-quarter loss, as the lender booked an impairment charge and increased reserves for bad loans linked to an auto parts manufacturer bankruptcy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/first-guaranty-bancshares-swings-quarterly-loss-exposure-auto-parts-bankruptcy-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMY22PFF6VLKBIR4JOUFLOU2TA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:23:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府关门进入第 31 天，美国预计航班将受到更多干扰]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）周五表示，随着政府关门进入第31天，他预计未来几天将有更多航班延误。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said Friday he expects more flight delays in the coming days as a government shutdown hits its 31st day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-expects-more-flight-disruptions-government-shutdown-enters-day-31-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOWBYJFHXNKSPBNJWDDFVXFAFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:06:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德支持的 TXSE 集团新增美国银行业巨头摩根大通为投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[德州证券交易所集团周五表示，华尔街巨头摩根大通（J.P. Morgan）已对该公司进行了战略投资，成为德州证券交易所母公司的主要支持者之一。【原文：TXSE Group said on Friday Wall Street behemoth J.P. Morgan had made a strategic investment in the company, becoming the latest to join a roster of marquee backers of the Texas Stock Exchange-parent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackrock-backed-txse-group-adds-us-banking-giant-jp-morgan-investor-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A72RXFN3SRO7DOBD3GJYFAGHIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:14:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Acerinox 对欧盟最近采取的措施表示欢迎，并敦促立即予以采纳]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙钢铁制造商 Acerinox 的老板周五称赞了欧盟委员会最近宣布的钢铁进口配额，但表示该公司正在努力争取更快地通过这些措施。【原文：The boss of Spanish steelmaker Acerinox praised on Friday recently announced steel import quotas by the European Commission but said the company was working to get the measures adopted more quickly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/acerinox-hails-recent-eu-measures-urges-urgent-adoption-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTIKX7CKTNKEZFYCX66S7OHDLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称欧佩克+可能同意在 12 月小幅增加石油产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉会谈情况的消息人士称，欧佩克+将有可能在周日同意再次小幅上调12月份的石油产量目标，因为在预测明年将出现供应过剩的情况下，该组织将缓和其夺回市场份额的努力。【原文：OPEC+ will likely agree on Sunday another small hike in oil output targets for December, three sources familiar with the talks said, as the group moderates its drive to regain market share amid predictions of a supply glut next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-likely-agree-small-oil-output-increase-december-sources-say-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFBRK6LSFFLVLEUZJSZ3KWVIFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:56:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储洛根称本周无需降息，反对 12 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周五表示，美国央行本周不应降息，12 月份也不应再次降息，理由是劳动力市场 "平衡"，不需要立即给予支持，而且通胀率看起来有可能长期保持在决策者 2% 的目标之上。【原文：The U.S. central bank should not have cut interest rates this week and should not do so again in December, Dallas Federal Reserve President Lorie Logan said on Friday, citing a 'balanced' labor market in no immediate need of support and inflation that looks likely to stay above policymakers' 2% goal for too long.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-says-this-weeks-rate-cut-was-not-needed-opposes-one-december-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKLEOETLJJNSVPJYYAYDQ7SQYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:25:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储国债中枢有望缓解供应，但利率期货显示资金紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三决定开始逐步缩减其长期资产负债表，但这并没有缓解人们对约 4 万亿美元的美国隔夜回购市场近期流动性紧张的担忧。【原文：The Federal Reserve's decision on Wednesday to begin winding down its long-running balance sheet runoff has done little to ease concerns about near-term liquidity strains in the roughly $4 trillion U.S. overnight repurchase market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-t-bill-pivot-expected-ease-supply-rate-futures-flag-tight-funding-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAMKHHDXF5OSNPQ46JBEI7L77I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：华尔街 "不给糖就捣蛋]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克-多兰（Mike Dolan）和投资回报率团队周末兴奋地阅读、观看和收听的所有内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-corrected-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TICNHANFS5PX7PZ2V4KOCNRRCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德通胀风险犹存，经济仍显动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储主席杰弗里-施密德（Jeffrey Schmid）周五表示，他反对本周降息，因为他担心持续的高通胀和经济中价格压力蔓延的迹象可能会使人们对央行实现2%通胀目标的承诺产生怀疑。【原文：Kansas City Fed president Jeffrey Schmid said on Friday that he dissented against cutting interest rates this week out of concern that continued high inflation and signs of price pressures spreading in the economy could raise doubts about the central bank's commitment to its 2% inflation target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-schmid-inflation-risks-remain-economy-still-showing-momentum-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7DO7HPF45M7XN3V7MTZMGZZM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储决议和科技巨头财报公布前，美国股票基金流入量有所减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 29 日的一周内，美国股票基金的资金流入量大幅下降，原因是在美联储降息预期和大型科技公司公布一系列财报之前，投资者没有进行大举下注。【原文：U.S. equity fund inflows cooled significantly in the week to October 29 as investors refrained from taking major bets in the lead-up to an anticipated Federal Reserve rate cut and a batch of earnings reports from big technology companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-fund-inflows-eased-before-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZ67Q2AQHFKSJLHF5OFJIGAWQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美联储降息和中美达成贸易协议之前，投资者纷纷涌入股票基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 29 日的一周内，全球股票基金在美国联邦储备委员会降息预期和美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与中国国家主席习近平达成贸易协议之前吸引了大量投资。【原文：Global equity funds attracted massive investments in the week to October 29 ahead of an anticipated interest rate cut by the U.S. Federal Reserve and a trade deal between U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Z2FMACW6NNRVGZ5DB34XXGWYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Perplexity 签订多年协议，使用盖蒂图片进行人工智能搜索]]></title><description><![CDATA[盖蒂图片公司（Getty Images）和 Perplexity 周五签署了一项全球多年期许可协议，允许这家人工智能初创公司在其搜索和发现工具中显示图片发行商的编辑和创意图片。【原文：Getty Images and Perplexity signed a global multi-year licensing agreement on Friday, allowing the AI startup to display the photo distributor's editorial and creative images across its search and discovery tools.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/getty-perplexity-sign-multi-year-licensing-deal-boost-ai-powered-search-visuals-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5IYRFSZIFJMXJVLDENDXPT6YQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:18:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高露洁-棕榄公司因需求低迷迹象下调年度销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[牙膏生产商高露洁-棕榄公司周五下调了年度销售预期，这表明经济不确定性的增加正在挤压消费者的消费欲望，即使是在必需品方面，他们也不愿意在价格较高的商品上消费。【原文：Toothpaste maker Colgate-Palmolive cut its annual sales forecast on Friday, in a sign that rising economic uncertainty is squeezing consumer appetite to spend on higher-priced items even in essential categories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/colgate-palmolive-cuts-annual-sales-forecast-signs-sluggish-demand-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGCLSZOLGBLD7OZFBIUN46XKLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:14:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾伯维上调年度盈利预期，因新型免疫学药物需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯维周五上调了 2025 年的利润预期，此前较新的免疫学药物 Skyrizi 和 Rinvoq 的销售强劲，使第三季度业绩高于华尔街预期。【原文：AbbVie raised its 2025 profit forecast on Friday, after strong sales of newer immunology drugs Skyrizi and Rinvoq helped boost third-quarter results above Wall Street estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/abbvie-lifts-annual-profit-forecast-resilient-demand-newer-immunology-drugs-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASCDLYBTZJNDLCPM5526BESTKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[竞争白热化，Charter 宽带用户流失超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Charter Communications 周五报告称，该公司第三季度宽带用户下降幅度超过预期，因为这家美国宽带和有线电视服务提供商正在努力应对来自无线运营商的激烈竞争。【原文：Charter Communications reported a larger-than-expected decline in broadband subscribers for the third quarter on Friday, as the U.S. broadband and cable TV provider grapples with intense competition from wireless carriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/charter-sheds-more-broadband-customers-than-expected-competition-heats-up-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYGXJ7BLGRLHVOQHABUZ7WJ2N4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:54:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据存储公司西部数据和希捷因人工智能驱动的需求激增而飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[希捷（Seagate）和西部数据（Western Digital）等数据存储公司的股价今年大幅跑赢大盘，原因是全球竞相扩大人工智能相关基础设施的规模，对硬盘的需求惊人。【原文：Shares of data storage companies such as Seagate and Western Digital have sharply outperformed the broader market this year, powered by the staggering demand for hard drives in the global race to scale up AI-related infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/data-storage-firms-western-digital-seagate-soar-ai-driven-demand-spike-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OEC4G72RRKXFNF72F3OTHBBK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[风险管理需求强劲，保险经纪公司 Aon 盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，保险经纪公司 Aon 的第三季度利润超出华尔街预期，原因是市场对其风险管理解决方案的需求强劲。【原文：Insurance brokerage firm Aon beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter profit on Friday, amid robust demand for its risk-management solutions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/insurance-broker-aon-profit-beats-estimates-strong-demand-risk-management-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHQZZVDJXJMGDN5JRFDCYNCT6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:08:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管存在地缘政治风险，但供应充足、需求低迷将抑制油价]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，由于欧佩克+产量目标的提高和需求不振抵消了供应方面的地缘政治风险，分析师们对油价的预测基本保持不变。【原文：Analysts are holding their oil price forecasts largely unchanged as rising OPEC+ output targets and lacklustre demand offset geopolitical risks to supply, a Reuters poll showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ample-supply-subdued-demand-curb-oil-prices-despite-geopolitical-risks-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZL3VRMTHVM4FODZ3W7QKN76TE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员要求特朗普政府帮助马来西亚打击芯片走私]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封信，一名美国共和党参议员要求美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府帮助马来西亚政府防止美国人工智能芯片通过该国走私到中国。【原文：A U.S. Republican senator is asking U.S. President Donald Trump's administration to help the Malaysian government prevent U.S. artificial intelligence chips from being smuggled through the country to China, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-lawmaker-asks-trump-administration-to-help-malaysia-crack-down-chip-smuggling-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ABMGQENANKFNDKAPRGSFPW5BM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[iPhone 假期销售预期缓解供应困境，苹果股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，苹果公司股价盘前上涨约 2%，原因是对利润丰厚的假日季度的乐观预测显示，尽管向关键市场中国发货出现延误，但最新的 iPhone 17 机型推动了销售反弹。【原文：Apple shares rose about 2% premarket on Friday after upbeat forecasts for the lucrative holiday quarter suggested the latest iPhone 17 models were driving a sales rebound despite delays in shipping to key market China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/apple-shares-rise-iphone-holiday-sales-forecast-soothes-supply-woes-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MG7ZJWXBEZOQRJ3ZGKAFSUD5W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产与巨石公司扩大人工智能合作，以缩短汽车开发时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车公司和英国软件公司Monolith周五表示，他们已扩大合作，利用人工智能减少汽车物理测试，因为日本汽车制造商正努力缩短新车的开发时间。【原文：Nissan and UK software firm Monolith said on Friday they have extended their partnership using artificial intelligence to reduce vehicle physical testing as the Japanese automaker pushes to slash development times for new cars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nissan-monolith-expand-joint-ai-efforts-cut-car-development-time-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCX4NYHPVVLWPDIYZGGQLVQJKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:31:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司第三季度利润超出预期，原因是圭亚那和二叠纪产量增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚周五公布的第三季度盈利超出华尔街预期，主要得益于圭亚那和二叠纪盆地石油和天然气产量增加，抵消了油价下跌的影响。【原文：Exxon Mobil beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter earnings on Friday, underpinned by higher oil and gas production in Guyana and the Permian Basin, which offset lower oil prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-beats-q3-profit-estimates-higher-guyana-permian-production-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZU2W6FQ7FLVNN462YZOVVIWJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾联发科目标到 2027 年人工智能加速芯片收入达数十亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾顶级芯片设计公司联发科技（MediaTek）首席执行官周五表示，随着该公司进一步推进数据中心业务，预计到2027年，其人工智能加速器ASIC芯片将带来数十亿美元的收入。【原文：Taiwan's top chip design company, MediaTek , expects to earn revenue of billions of dollars from its AI accelerator ASIC chips by 2027, the chief executive said on Friday, as the company pushes further into the data centre business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/taiwans-mediatek-targets-billions-ai-accelerator-chip-revenue-by-2027-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQN525ERCRP35PFZVV645ULMII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙第三季度盈利超出预期，赫斯交易后产量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，雪佛龙公司的业绩超过了分析师的预期，创纪录的石油和天然气产量、550亿美元收购赫斯公司（Hess）所带来的推动力以及炼油利润率的增长，都提升了这家美国第二大石油生产商第三季度的业绩。【原文：Chevron beat analyst estimates on Friday as record oil and gas production, boosted by its $55 billion acquisition of Hess, and stronger refining margins lifted the No. 2 U.S. oil producer's results for the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-tops-q3-earnings-estimates-with-record-production-after-hess-deal-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACUMEZFISVI5RP3W4SQ3623RKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 在人工智能和美联储动荡之后，股市反弹面临盈利浪潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市的反弹势头在进入繁忙的企业财报周后有所恢复，但投资者对人工智能交易的力度以及美联储降息的力度感到担忧。【原文：A resilient U.S. stocks rally heads into a busy week of corporate results, with investors concerned about the strength of the artificial intelligence trade and about how aggressively the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-resilient-stocks-rally-faces-earnings-wave-after-ai-fed-2025-10-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ID2MSFQ2MVILVJFGYMRSH7UT5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>