<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:27:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:27:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[体育联盟质疑广播公司 Diamond 能否在没有康卡斯特的情况下生存下去]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国职业棒球大联盟、国家冰球联盟和国家篮球协会周三表示，如果不与有线电视分销商康卡斯特公司（Comcast）达成新协议，破产的广播公司钻石体育可能无法生存。【原文：Major League Baseball, the National Hockey League and the National Basketball Association said on Wednesday that bankrupt broadcaster Diamond Sports may not survive without a new deal with cable distributor Comcast .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/sports-leagues-question-whether-broadcaster-diamond-can-survive-without-comcast-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6P3GR3HFZLWHIS55ERJFPUUFA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:14:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢拉责成巴西国家石油公司新任首席执行官玛格达-尚布里亚特大力创造就业机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士说，巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）的下一任首席执行官玛格达-尚布里亚特（Magda Chambriard）的履历和任务是让这家巴西国营石油公司重现工人党政府执政时期的辉煌：成为创造就业机会和推动工业发展的引擎。【原文：The next chief executive of Petrobras , Magda Chambriard, arrives with the résumé and mandate to make Brazil's state-run oil firm what it was under prior Workers Party governments: an engine of job creation and industrial development, said people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/magda-chambriard-new-petrobras-ceo-charged-by-lula-with-firing-up-job-creation-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWTDBT4HP5KVXLSA2VGT535QPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大自称 "加密货币之王 "的人及其同伙被控欺诈罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大警方周三表示，一名自称加拿大 "加密货币大王 "的人和一名从投资者那里获得 4000 多万加元（2940 万美元）资金的同伙已被逮捕，并被指控犯有欺诈罪。【原文：A self-proclaimed Canadian "Crypto King" and an associate who received more than C$40 million ($29.4 million) from investors have been arrested and charged with fraud, police said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadian-self-proclaimed-crypto-king-associate-charged-with-fraud-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRT5UGE6CBKHXJ2DTOUYKP37OY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AT&T 与 AST SpaceMobile 合作提供天基宽带网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[电信巨头 AT&amp;T 公司周三表示，已与 AST SpaceMobile 公司达成协议，为手机提供天基宽带网络。【原文：Telecom giant AT&amp;T has entered an agreement with AST SpaceMobile to provide a space-based broadband network direct to cell phones, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/att-ast-spacemobile-tie-up-provide-space-based-broadband-network-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GGMCORZHZMLBCT5HJLDCE7KAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔披露以 67.2 亿美元入股保险公司 Chubb]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周三透露，将以 67.2 亿美元的价格新入股保险公司 Chubb，从而结束了数月来外界对该公司进行大笔新投资的猜测。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway on Wednesday revealed a new, $6.72 billion stake in the insurer Chubb , ending months of speculation that it had made a big new investment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-reveals-672-billion-stake-insurer-chubb-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43SIYAPSSVMINPIZMC6BVJTZSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:32:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[思科预测第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[思科系统公司（Cisco Systems）周三预测第四季度营收将高于华尔街预期，原因是这家网络设备制造商受益于企业支出的回升和供应链限制的缓解。【原文：Cisco Systems forecast fourth-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday as the network equipment maker benefits from a pick up in enterprise spending and easing supply chain constraints.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cisco-forecasts-fourth-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAUTGC7AGBJGFDL5RK6QHCA5TU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普发现全球企业违约从 3 月到 4 月翻了一番]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据S&amp;P全球评级公司的一份报告，4月份全球企业债务违约比3月份增加了一倍多，创下了2020年10月以来的最高月度记录。【原文：Global corporate debt defaults more than doubled in April from March to their highest monthly tally since October 2020, according to a report from S&amp;P Global Ratings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-corporate-defaults-doubled-march-april-sp-finds-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2J3KDJF6UJMLXKQI2MQOTYXVKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:58:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布里奇沃特第一季度大举投资 Mag Seven 股票，但拒绝了特斯拉 - 文档]]></title><description><![CDATA[证券文件显示，桥水联合公司（Bridgewater Associates）第一季度在所谓的 "七大巨头 "美股中的六只股票上投入了 8 亿美元，押注谷歌母公司 Alphabet，同时避开了陷入困境的电动汽车制造商特斯拉（Tesla）股票。【原文：Bridgewater Associates piled into six of the so-called Magnificent Seven megacap U.S. stocks in the first quarter, making an $800 million bet on Google-parent Alphabet while avoiding struggling shares of electric car-maker Tesla , securities filings showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bridgewater-piled-into-mag-seven-stocks-q1-spurned-tesla-filings-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FN6BHCFJNPL7COIQBHTJNXSXQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:48:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼将大幅削减传统电视网络支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼首席执行官鲍勃-艾格（Bob Iger）周三表示，随着消费者转向流媒体，公司将大幅削减对传统电视网络节目的投资。【原文：Walt Disney will cut its investment in programming for traditional television networks pretty dramatically as the company navigates the consumer shift to streaming, Chief Executive Bob Iger said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-dramatically-cut-spending-traditional-tv-networks-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5BU3IO5YZKMNJD62Q5VQ4ZWBY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森称代理顾问格拉斯-刘易斯应回避提出建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油巨头埃克森公司（Exxon）周三表示，由于 "利益冲突"，代理顾问格拉斯-刘易斯公司（Glass Lewis）应回避就其即将召开的股东大会提出建议。【原文：U.S. oil giant Exxon said on Wednesday proxy advisor Glass Lewis should recuse itself from making recommendations on its upcoming shareholder meeting due to "conflicts of interest."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/exxon-says-proxy-advisor-glass-lewis-should-recuse-itself-making-recommendations-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47OJRBRFJRKBVMZG2KNRPDLCJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将于今年秋季发布针对中国联网汽车的法规]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长吉娜-雷蒙多（Gina Raimondo）周三表示，商务部计划在今年秋天发布针对中国联网汽车的拟议规则，理由是美国人的数据面临国家安全风险。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo said on Wednesday that her department plans to issue proposed rules on Chinese connected vehicles this fall, citing national security risks to Americans' data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-issue-rules-chinese-connected-vehicles-this-fall-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKBI7HILTNJNBL43SXVPRSZGI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 的广告支持计划用户达到 4000 万]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 周三表示，其广告支持层级的全球月活跃用户已从一年前的 500 万增至 4000 万，这表明其通过更便宜的计划吸引新用户的努力正在取得成效。【原文：Netflix said on Wednesday its ad-supported tier has reached 40 million global monthly active users, from 5 million a year earlier, a sign that its push to attract new users with the cheaper plan is paying off.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-hits-40-million-users-ad-supported-plan-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTUULRE6FBNWHEX2J3JVLB53LQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品公司首席执行官称不确定美国紧张的牛供应何时会扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）首席执行官唐尼-金（Donnie King）周三表示，泰森食品公司无法准确预测美国牧场主何时会开始以有意义的方式重建牛群，因为供应紧张正在挤压这家肉类食品公司的牛肉业务。【原文：Tyson Foods cannot predict exactly when U.S. ranchers will start rebuilding the cattle herd in a meaningful way, CEO Donnie King said on Wednesday, as tight supplies squeeze the meatpacker's beef business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/tyson-foods-unsure-when-tight-us-cattle-supplies-will-expand-ceo-says-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4M52OWEOJLRPMPH3KKYBKKKZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:14:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文艺复兴科技公司和 Two Sigma 是第一季度抛售波音公司的基金之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周三公布的证券文件显示，文艺复兴科技公司（Renaissance Technologies）、Two Sigma Investments和Arrowstreet Capital等大型公司在第一季度出售了其持有的陷入困境的飞机制造商波音公司的全部股票。【原文：Renaissance Technologies, Two Sigma Investments and Arrowstreet Capital were among large firms that sold all their shares of embattled aircraft maker Boeing Co in the first quarter, according to securities filings released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/renaissance-technologies-two-sigma-among-funds-that-dumped-boeing-first-quarter-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6P5DKW5MRPEVJEB6NWPWLOI44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:45:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国指控两兄弟参与价值 2500 万美元的新型加密货币抢劫案]]></title><description><![CDATA[曾就读于麻省理工学院的两兄弟于周三在美国被捕，罪名是他们实施了一项尖端计划，利用以太坊区块链的完整性窃取了价值 2500 万美元的加密货币。【原文：Two brothers who studied at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology were arrested on Wednesday on U.S. charges that they carried out a cutting-edge scheme to exploit the Ethereum blockchain's integrity and steal $25 million worth of cryptocurrency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-charges-two-brothers-with-novel-25-million-cryptocurrency-heist-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4LNFXEEYFKRBMNBSFPYROUXZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:39:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国会通过内容广泛的航空安全和消费者法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院周三以压倒性多数通过了一项内容广泛的航空法案，该法案旨在增加空中交通管制员的人手，增加资金以避免跑道关闭事件的发生，并加快取消航班的退款速度。【原文：The U.S. House of Representatives on Wednesday overwhelmingly passed a broad aviation bill to boost air traffic controller staffing, increase funding to avert runway close-call incidents, and speed refunds for canceled flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-congress-passes-broad-aviation-safety-consumer-bill-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HK6BBYOIVFLANFZ3UCVAGL6PAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:28:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：奥地利莱费森银行因俄罗斯业务遭美国怒斥]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部已警告奥地利莱弗森国际银行（RBI），由于其与俄罗斯的交易，该银行进入美国金融系统可能会受到限制。【原文：The U.S. Treasury has warned Austria's Raiffeisen Bank International (RBI) that its access to the U.S. financial system could be restricted because of its Russian dealings, according to a person who has seen a letter detailing the threat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/austrias-raiffeisen-faces-us-wrath-over-russian-business-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWYL4DW4L5JBPF7XXFEJ3KTOXM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典投资者 AP7 支持对蒙代尔俄罗斯业务的研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[至少有一家 Mondelez 公司的投资者--瑞典养老基金 AP7 将支持一项决议，该决议要求奥利奥饼干制造商对继续在俄罗斯开展业务的风险进行独立研究。【原文：At least one Mondelez investor, Swedish pension fund AP7, will back a resolution calling for the Oreo cookie maker to conduct an independent study of the risks of continuing to do business in Russia, which faces a vote at the company's annual meeting this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/swedish-investor-ap7-back-study-mondelez-russia-business-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IAQ5EGET5I73MPMA6AV6FCOAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:18:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储卡什卡利：利率应 "再按兵不动 "一段时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周三重申了他的观点，即他不确定目前的货币政策有多严格，在美国央行行长们对通胀进行评估之际，借贷成本应保持在目前的水平。
"在我看来，最大的不确定性是货币政策对经济造成了多大的下行压力？这是一个未知数。【原文：Minneapolis Federal Reserve Bank President Neel Kashkari on Wednesday reiterated his view that he is unsure how restrictive monetary policy is right now, and that borrowing costs should stay where they are as U.S. central bankers take stock of inflation.
"The biggest uncertainty in my mind is how much downward pressure is monetary policy putting on the economy? That's an unknown," Kashkari told th】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kashkari-rates-should-stay-hold-for-while-longer-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIEFEPOJWVOW5KZJ6QS25J5HYU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储在通胀进展方面获得一些好消息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美联储政策制定者在降低借贷成本之前等待看到通胀率的新进展，他们得到了一些令人鼓舞的数据，一份政府报告显示 4 月份通胀略有缓解。
消费者价格指数比去年同期上升了 3.4%，比 3 月份上升了 0.3%，这表明美联储在实现其 2% 的通胀目标方面仍有一段距离。【原文：Federal Reserve policymakers waiting to see renewed progress on inflation before reducing borrowing costs got some encouraging data on Wednesday with a government report showing inflation eased a bit in April.
The 3.4% rise in the consumer price index from a year earlier, and the 0.3% increase from March, shows the Fed still has some distance to go before it achieves its 2% target for inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-gets-some-good-news-inflation-progress-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWPKID7D4VK53CLCE3GC2K5HM4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：波音公司如何在 2021 年面临它所避免的刑事起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部称，波音公司违反了 2021 年协议规定的义务，该协议规定波音公司在 2018 年和 2019 年 737 MAX 飞机坠毁造成 346 人死亡后免于刑事起诉。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department said Boeing breached its obligations under a 2021 agreement that kept the planemaker from criminal prosecution following fatal 737 MAX crashes in 2018 and 2019 that killed 346 people.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/how-boeing-could-face-criminal-prosecution-it-avoided-2021-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJEL6EHMOFK3VKX37IJIF6SZQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，KKR 预计将于下周就意大利电信交易做出补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟知内情的人士周三表示，美国投资公司 KKR 很可能在下周提出补救措施，试图获得欧盟的反垄断批准，以收购意大利电信公司（TIM）的固网接入网络。【原文：U.S. investment firm KKR will likely offer remedies next week in an attempt to secure EU antitrust approval to buy Telecom Italia's (TIM) fixed-line access network, a person familiar with the matter said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-remedies-telecom-italia-deal-expected-next-week-source-says-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APSJ5OQDERPMXIJ5GTPNMMBMW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Comex铜价创下新高，Trafigura和IXM陷入空头挤压]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位直接了解情况的消息人士称，大宗商品交易商 Trafigura 和 IXM 正在寻求实物铜，以弥补芝加哥商品交易所（CME）的大量看跌头寸，周三美国铜价飙升至历史新高。【原文：Commodity traders Trafigura and IXM are seeking physical copper to cover large bearish positions on the CME, where U.S. copper prices surged to record highs on Wednesday, five sources with direct knowledge of the situation said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trafigura-ixm-caught-comex-copper-short-squeeze-prices-hit-record-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3J5U2WD52JLEHAGSNWSBRDQ4FU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:38:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[视频游戏制造商育碧全年营业利润创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国视频游戏集团育碧（Ubisoft）周三表示，截至 3 月底的全年业绩转为营业利润，创纪录的预订额帮助该公司扭转了去年同期 5 亿欧元的亏损，这是该公司有史以来最大的亏损。【原文：French video games group Ubisoft swung to an operating profit for its full-year to end-March, it said on Wednesday, as record bookings helped it reverse a year earlier loss of 500 million euros, its biggest ever.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/video-game-maker-ubisoft-swings-full-year-operating-profit-record-bookings-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMDBML56RJIKJBD3KPQRRNNHYI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:44:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic 聘用 Instagram 联合创始人担任产品总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Anthropic周三表示，该公司已任命Instagram联合创始人迈克-克里格（Mike Krieger）为首席产品官，希望借此完善其人工智能产品并领先于竞争对手。【原文：Artificial intelligence startup Anthropic has appointed Instagram co-founder Mike Krieger as its chief product officer, the company said on Wednesday, it looks to spruce up its AI offerings and get ahead of rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/anthropic-taps-instagram-co-founder-product-chief-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2AJQSRAXFLZTEK3VJN3Q3RTTU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:41:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber 推出美国班车服务，扩大与好市多的合作以吸引价格敏感型用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步（Uber Technologies）将在美国推出班车服务，并扩大与会员制零售商好市多的送货合作，这是优步周三公布的一系列举措的一部分，目的是在竞争对手 Lyft 的竞争中吸引注重价格的消费者。【原文：Uber Technologies is introducing a shuttle service in the U.S. and widening a delivery tie-up with membership-only retailer Costco as part of a series of initiatives unveiled on Wednesday to attract price-conscious consumers amid competition from rival Lyft .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uber-unveils-us-shuttle-service-expands-costco-tie-up-woo-price-conscious-users-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OV67YB77NRIWLHEPFMAJIBOMYI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:58:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官驳回声称优步藏匿荷兰避税港的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官驳回了一项集体诉讼提议，该诉讼指控优步科技公司隐瞒其荷兰子公司作为避税天堂的事实，欺骗股东。【原文：A U.S. judge has dismissed a proposed class action lawsuit accusing Uber Technologies of defrauding shareholders by concealing its use of its Netherlands subsidiary as a tax haven.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/lawsuit-claiming-uber-hid-dutch-tax-haven-is-dismissed-by-us-judge-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5VDFZN2INITDMIONS6MC6KXLQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因违反停机坪延误规定，美国对沃乐瑞公司罚款 30 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部周三表示，已对墨西哥航空公司 Volaris Airlines 罚款 30 万美元，原因是该公司违反了有关机场停机坪延误的联邦法律。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department said Wednesday it had fined Mexican carrier Volaris Airlines $300,000 for violating federal law on airport tarmac delays.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-fines-volaris-300000-violating-tarmac-delay-rules-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYVTNP65MFIZVD5DPZRPG24YBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:47:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称美国原油、汽油和馏分油库存下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（EIA）周三称，在截至5月10日的一周内，美国原油库存、汽油库存和馏分油库存均有所下降。【原文：U.S. crude stocks, gasoline and distillate inventories fell in the week ending May 10, the Energy Information Administration (EIA) said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-crude-stocks-gasoline-distillate-inventories-fall-eia-says-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PDNPNPXJVNGZNCZPQU2EJWBXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月份商业库存下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份美国企业库存下降，但这可能为企业重建库存和支持第二季度经济增长奠定基础。【原文：U.S. business inventories fell in March, but this could lay the ground for businesses to rebuild stocks and support economic growth in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-inventories-fall-march-2024-05-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2J4ANGHRPZOSVCYLIRNE223J7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>