<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:06:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:06:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Squishmallows 制造商与 Build-A-Bear 在毛绒玩具官司中休战]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据向洛杉矶联邦法院提交的一份文件，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的 Squishmallows 制造商 Jazwares 已同意结束对 Build-A-Bear Workshop 的诉讼，因为该公司涉嫌山寨流行的毛绒玩具。【原文：Jazwares, the Berkshire Hathaway-owned maker of Squishmallows, has agreed to end a lawsuit against Build-A-Bear Workshop over its alleged knockoffs of the popular plush toys, according to a filing in Los Angeles federal court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/squishmallows-maker-build-a-bear-call-truce-plush-toy-legal-battle-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XI7BVXEKZZMPDN7VZAPLXNSPUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的 xAI 就人工智能竞争和应用商店排名起诉苹果和 OpenAI]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁企业家埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的人工智能初创公司 xAI 周一在美国得克萨斯州联邦法院起诉苹果公司和 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI，指控它们非法合谋阻挠人工智能竞争。【原文：Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence startup xAI sued Apple and ChatGPT maker OpenAI in U.S. federal court in Texas on Monday, accusing them of illegally conspiring to thwart competition for artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/elon-musks-xai-sues-apple-openai-over-ai-competition-app-store-rankings-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DC6MCVW5MRNHFLK6ZWWZEPFLNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔将 Keurig Dr Pepper 列入负面信用观察名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国软饮料巨头 Keurig Dr Pepper 周一宣布将收购荷兰咖啡集团 JDE Peet's 之后，评级机构 S&amp;P Global 将该公司的信用展望定为负面。【原文：Ratings agency S&amp;P Global put a negative credit outlook on U.S. soft drinks giant Keurig Dr Pepper after the company announced Monday it will buy Dutch coffee group JDE Peet's .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/sp-puts-keurig-dr-pepper-negative-credit-watch-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOZA5MXZ55M4NNV3N7NAZW42KU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月新屋销售下降；6 月销售修正为上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[继上月销售速度大幅上调之后，7 月份美国新建独户住宅的销售量有所下降，总体趋势仍然是住房市场在高抵押贷款利率的环境中苦苦挣扎。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell in July following a sharp upward revision to the prior month's sales pace, and the overall trend remained consistent with a housing market struggling in an environment of high mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-july-june-sales-revised-higher-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LH6HTVIRFFPTJJBTLZMHRUZENU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将继续达成类似英特尔的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他将与其他公司达成类似于上周宣布的与英特尔公司（Intel）的交易。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he would make deals with other companies similar to the one he announced last week with Intel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-continue-make-deals-like-intel-one-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2R3AJ3OB2RJLVNBQFLRAEE4XX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇率飙升和特朗普关税影响欧洲业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国关税和美元疲软导致的欧洲货币升值削弱了企业在第二季度的业绩表现，增加了企业将业务迁往美国或将工作岗位迁往美国的压力。【原文：U.S. tariffs and an appreciation in European currencies caused by dollar weakness have eroded companies' top line performance in the second quarter, increasing pressure on them to relocate operations or put jobs into the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/currency-spikes-trump-tariffs-take-bite-out-european-results-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIQOIBDYNVKPBEE7O67QNXLIXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，皮纳尔家族正在探索出售彪马公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道称，Pinault 家族正在权衡 Puma SE 的各种选择，包括出售。【原文：The Pinault family is weighing options for Puma SE , including a sale, Bloomberg News reported on Monday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pinault-family-explores-sale-puma-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPLEWCTLMNLE3DHWUZTJFESFJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拥有优质信用的美国消费者在付款方面开始出现滑坡]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评分公司 VantageScore 在周一发布的一份报告中称，信用评分最高的美国消费者在偿还债务方面开始落后，这表明美国人的财务健康状况可能正在更广泛地恶化。【原文：U.S. consumers with the highest credit scores are starting to fall behind in debt repayments, credit scoring company VantageScore said in a report published on Monday, in a sign that Americans' financial health may be deteriorating more broadly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumers-with-prime-credit-are-starting-slip-payments-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APIJM3WJQRLSVGIPDTJQV764M4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoma Bravo 拟斥资 20 亿美元收购 Verint，软件并购步伐加快]]></title><description><![CDATA[客户参与平台 Thoma Bravo 周一表示，将以包括债务在内的 20 亿美元收购 Verint Systems，这标志着私募股权公司越来越多地押注于人工智能，以应对不确定的经济形势，这也是最新的软件收购交易。【原文：Thoma Bravo will acquire Verint Systems in a $2 billion deal, including debt, the customer engagement platform said on Monday, marking the latest software buyout as private equity firms increasingly bet on AI to navigate an uncertain economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/thoma-bravo-buy-verint-2-billion-deal-software-acquisitions-ramp-up-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWNI5I2HOZIIHIS6XM4LZ5WEUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔警告称美国股份可能损害国际销售和未来拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司周一表示，美国政府持有这家芯片制造商 10% 的股份可能会给其业务带来风险，从可能损害国际销售到限制其未来获得政府拨款的能力。【原文：Intel said on Monday that the 10% stake by the U.S. government in the chipmaker could pose risks to its business, from potentially harming international sales to limiting its ability to secure future government grants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/intel-warns-us-stake-could-hurt-international-sales-future-grants-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2QM5P4DTRLHTM3EPTVN6RCAJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫哈塞特称美国可参股其他行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[继入股英特尔（Intel）之后，白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）周一在接受 CNBC 采访时表示，联邦政府可能会入股其他美国半导体公司，甚至转向其他行业。【原文：The federal government could take stakes in other U.S. semiconductor companies or even move to other industries, White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett told CNBC in an interview on Monday following its stake in Intel .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/white-houses-hassett-says-us-could-take-stakes-other-industries-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCULR7H76BKTZBPQCVHYSDJPYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法律修改后，Flutter 关闭了印度的付费在线游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线博彩公司 Flutter 上周修改法律后关闭了其在印度的货币在线游戏，该公司首席执行官彼得-杰克逊（Peter Jackson）表示，他对事态发展 "极为失望"。【原文：Online betting company Flutter , has shut down its money-based online games in India following a law change last week, with CEO Peter Jackson saying he was "extremely disappointed" by the development.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/flutter-shuts-down-money-based-online-games-india-following-law-change-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZH3F6FSDBZJ2HBKZ4DN26TAACA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:32:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper 180 亿美元收购 JDE Peet's 的内幕交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper 周一宣布将以 157 亿欧元（184 亿美元）的现金收购荷兰 JDE Peet's，以打造全球咖啡巨头。【原文：Keurig Dr Pepper on Monday announced it would buy Dutch company JDE Peet's for 15.7 billion euros ($18.4 billion) in cash, in a bid to create a global coffee heavyweight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/inner-workings-keurig-dr-peppers-18-billion-move-jde-peets-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH4MKP5RARMYXPSWLWQOALPQB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Figma 获得 "中性 "评级，华尔街认为估值过高、竞争加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街券商周一开始给予 Figma 中性评级，因为他们权衡了这家设计软件制造商在激烈竞争中的高估值和人工智能驱动的增长潜力。【原文：Wall Street brokerages on Monday started their coverage of Figma with neutral ratings, as they weighed the design software maker's lofty valuation amid stiff competition against its potential for artificial intelligence-driven growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/figma-draws-neutral-ratings-wall-street-flags-lofty-valuation-rising-competition-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZS6GL4QXWRMNLE4Z5S2VMV7F6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[信心增强刺激交易反弹，华尔街增聘高级银行家]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几个月，华尔街银行招聘了数十名高级管理人员，因为在今年早些时候由于担心美国关税的影响而陷入低迷之后，经济景气的改善刺激了兼并和首次公开募股。【原文：Wall Street banks have hired dozens of senior executives in recent months, as improved economic sentiment has spurred mergers and IPOs after a lull earlier in the year due to concerns over the effect of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/wall-street-hires-more-senior-bankers-growing-confidence-spurs-deal-rebound-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKINH3KGQRINRNKYPVER7K3ZZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特木公司所有者 PDD 季度收入超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子商务公司点点客控股公司（PDD Holdings）周一公布的季度收入超出市场预期，表明尽管全球贸易存在不确定性，但国内需求反弹，国际业务增长也有所改善。【原文：E-commerce firm PDD Holdings beat market estimates for quarterly revenue on Monday, signaling a rebound in domestic demand and improved growth in its international business despite global trade uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/temu-owner-pdd-tops-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCMSUH722FN7XFFOXRWHI6UQRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国立法者和工会反对铁路自动化轨道安全检查计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铁路行业计划更多地依靠技术而不是人力来进行日常轨道安全检查，这一计划引起了劳工团体和立法者的反弹，他们担心自动检查会导致更多事故。【原文：A U.S. railroad industry plan to rely more heavily on technology instead of humans to conduct routine track safety inspections has drawn a backlash from labor groups and lawmakers who voiced worry that automated inspections will result in more accidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-lawmakers-unions-oppose-railroad-plan-automate-track-safety-inspections-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OK7PGHASI5PTVKGY5OLSHPURDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:34:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Royalty Pharma 拟以高达 9.5 亿美元的价格收购安进公司肺癌药物的特许权使用费权益]]></title><description><![CDATA[Royalty Pharma 公司周一表示，它已与 BeOne Medicines 公司签署协议，将以最高 9.5 亿美元的价格收购安进公司治疗小细胞肺癌药物的特许权使用权。【原文：Royalty Pharma said on Monday it has signed a deal with BeOne Medicines to acquire a royalty interest in Amgen's drug for small cell lung cancer for up to $950 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/royalty-pharma-buy-royalty-interest-amgens-lung-cancer-drug-up-950-million-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SG7EHOYBB5I5VOOI5XK2UTCYUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔带动美国股市反弹，9 月减产预期升温，美股期货下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）暗示下个月的央行会议上可能会降息，美国股指期货周一下滑，在前一交易日强劲上涨后暂停。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Monday, pausing after strong gains in the previous session, when Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell hinted that an interest-rate cut could be on the table at the central bank's meeting next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-dip-after-powell-led-rally-september-cut-expectations-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXG7RQXHSFJTRFLIXMGOBRQCEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅赛德斯-奔驰退休金信托基金拟出售 3.46 亿美元日产汽车股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份条款书显示，梅赛德斯-奔驰的养老信托基金将出售其持有的陷入困境的日本汽车制造商日产汽车价值约 3.46 亿美元的股份。【原文：Mercedes-Benz's Pension Trust will sell around $346 million worth of shares it holds in beleaguered Japanese automaker Nissan Motor , a term sheet showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-benz-pension-trust-sell-346-million-stake-nissan-motor-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC4SCVXFMZIGHIXQ2Z4TV2IOEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:10:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大银行在最新财报中回避最糟糕的关税情景]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计加拿大大型银行第三季度的贷款损失准备金将比上一季度有所下降，因为美国关税对其贷款组合造成的损害可能比人们担心的要小。【原文：Canada's big banks are expected to have lowered loan-loss provisions in the third quarter from the prior quarter as U.S. tariffs have likely hurt their loan portfolios less than feared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadian-banks-dodge-worst-case-tariff-scenario-latest-earnings-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DXEVQBIONLTDMOGNKHD4DUPVM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:06:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：宝洁出售中国产豪华 "邦宝 "牌纸尿裤，市场份额岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝洁公司（Procter & Gamble）正在零售商塔吉特（Target）销售中国制造的添加芦荟的 "bumbum "牌豪华纸尿裤，因为其最畅销的帮宝适（Pampers）和Luvs品牌被越来越多标榜类似功能的进口竞争对手所击败。【原文：Procter & Gamble is selling luxury aloe-infused “bumbum” brand diapers made in China at retailer Target as its top-selling Pampers and Luvs brands lose ground to a growing number of imported rivals touting similar features.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pg-selling-china-made-luxury-bumbum-brand-diapers-market-share-falters-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VA6IUHHFDFPO7OKUSMV4T3RJOM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰消费者监督机构指控 Netflix 擅自提高收费标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰消费者监督机构竞争和消费者保护办公室（UOKiK）周一表示，该机构指控 Netflix 在未征得用户明确同意的情况下提高订阅费用。【原文：Poland's consumer watchdog the Office of Competition and Consumer Protection (UOKiK) has accused Netflix of raising subscription fees without securing explicit user consent, the regulator said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/polish-consumer-watchdog-accuses-netflix-unauthorised-fee-hikes-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOIF36NK75P5PJNDS3ZH5RWVAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[紧张的瑞士准备好接受特朗普的关税减免甜言蜜语]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟知内情的人士表示，瑞士希望尽快敲定一项新的商业提议，以减轻华盛顿的关税负担，其中可能包括增加国防开支和扩大美国能源利益的准入。【原文：Switzerland soon hopes to finalise a new business offer for Washington to ease its tariff burden, which will likely include more defence spending and greater access for U.S. energy interests, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/nervous-swiss-ready-trump-sweetened-offer-tariff-pain-relief-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2O2BK6XTHRP6VH3JVY3HI7NFCI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 09:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷取消 Cellforce 部门的电池生产计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车制造商保时捷公司（Porsche AG）取消了其高性能电池部门 Cellforce 的生产计划，称由于电动汽车需求放缓以及中国和美国的情况发生变化，该公司将专注于研发。【原文：German carmaker Porsche AG scrapped production plans at its high-performance battery unit Cellforce, saying it would focus on development because of slow demand for electric vehicles and changed conditions in China and the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-scraps-battery-production-plans-cellforce-unit-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNUXACHC2RP3FF6NB6ZULE77BQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:56:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球负债最多的开发商恒大从违约到退市]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国恒大集团周一从香港证券交易所退市，这是近年来按市值和交易量计算的最大退市事件之一。【原文：China Evergrande Group was delisted from the Hong Kong stock exchange on Monday, in one of the largest removals by market value and volume in recent years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/default-delisting-evergrande-worlds-most-indebted-developer-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2KEXWII7ZLANO72JIZXID5HFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:48:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对 140 多万辆本田汽车发动机故障进行调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局正在对在美国销售的 140 多万辆本田汽车展开调查，因为人们担心本田汽车发动机连杆轴承故障可能导致发动机完全失效。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration is opening a probe into more than 1.4 million Honda vehicles sold in the United States over concerns that connecting rod bearing failures in their engines could lead to complete engine failure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-probes-into-more-than-14-million-honda-vehicles-over-engine-failure-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEWSGBQO2VLELDNUMJMJ5FQIY4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[证券交易所敦促监管机构打击 "代币化股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个代表全球最大证券交易所的组织正在敦促证券监管机构取缔所谓的代币化股票，认为基于区块链的代币给投资者带来了新的风险，并有可能破坏市场诚信。【原文：A group representing the world's biggest stock exchanges is urging securities regulators to clamp down on so-called tokenised stocks, arguing that the blockchain-based tokens create new risks for investors and risk damaging market integrity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/stock-exchanges-urge-regulators-crack-down-tokenised-stocks-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6ZVJE2NYVOZNBYKX5AY5Q53K4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国 7 月出口超预期，但受关税影响增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国商务部周一表示，泰国7月份的出口增长放缓，但好于预期，因为在美国加征关税之前出货量加速增长。【原文：Thailand's export growth slowed in July but beat forecasts as shipments accelerated ahead of U.S. tariffs, but growth is set to slow over the rest of the year after those tariffs took effect, the commerce ministry said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thai-exports-beat-forecast-july-growth-slow-due-tariffs-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIDSLSR66NP2BMEVC7FCJ4I534</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度将在通胀改革中直接利用亚马逊和 Flipkart 的数据，并推出服务指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度统计部负责人表示，印度将开始直接从亚马逊和沃尔玛旗下的 Flipkart 等电商巨头处获取价格数据，以全面调整其基准通胀率指标，旨在捕捉不断变化的消费习惯，并消除人们对当前数据已经过时的担忧。【原文：India will start sourcing price data directly from e-commerce giants including Amazon and Walmart-owned Flipkart to overhaul its benchmark inflation gauge, aiming to capture shifting consumption habits and address concerns that current data is outdated, the head of the statistics ministry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-tap-amazon-flipkart-data-directly-inflation-revamp-roll-out-services-index-2025-08-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SX5R54RKHZMORN35Y5W4SFSGGA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>