<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:14:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:13:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Palmer Luckey-backed Erebor receives US national banking charter, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Crypto-focused Erebor Bank became the first bank to receive a national bank charter during the second term of the Trump administration, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/palmer-luckey-backed-erebor-receives-us-national-banking-charter-wsj-reports-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUYV6UIAXZND7FNI6ZNH3IRODI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Judge bans Kalshi from offering sports-events contracts in Massachusetts in 30 days]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Massachusetts judge on Friday rejected a request by prediction-markets operator Kalshi to allow it to keep offering sports-events contracts in the state while it appeals an injunction that will lead to it being banned from operating there without a state gaming license in 30 days.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/judge-bans-kalshi-offering-sports-events-contracts-massachusetts-30-days-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VPFCAHGDNKM7INNAJRRAZK43M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US, India release framework for an interim trade deal]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United States and India on Friday released a framework for an interim trade agreement that the countries said affirms their commitment to negotiations towards a broader bilateral trade deal.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-india-release-framework-an-interim-trade-deal-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HGLYBWMRFJEVDVJFBKT4WBYRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFL to talk with partners outside of core media for live games, CNBC reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[The National Football League plans to hold discussions with non-traditional media outlets about the possible sale of rights to a live game, its media chief Hans Schroeder told CNBC Sport on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nfl-talk-with-partners-outside-core-media-live-games-cnbc-reports-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKWDIMQFNZO7FBV5KVZT3QWZ5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FDA to restrict GLP-1 ingredients used in non‑approved compounded drugs]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Friday it plans to restrict GLP-1 ingredients used in non-approved compounded drugs that companies such as Hims & Hers and other compounding pharmacies have been marketing as alternatives to authorized treatments, citing concerns over quality, safety and potential violations of federal law.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/fda-restrict-glp1-ingredients-used-nonapproved-compounded-drugs-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OCNJQ4EZBLO3KLNZX37SMQPWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:59:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senator Warren presses Trump over DOJ probe of Fed Chair Powell]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren on Friday challenged President Donald Trump's denial of involvement in a Justice Department investigation of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell that has heightened concerns about the Fed's independence and complicated the president's plan to install a rate-cut friendly Fed chair.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/senator-warren-presses-trump-over-doj-probe-fed-chair-powell-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYHDK6Y27FLALALL6EEKH7ZNCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla executives say hiring is ramping up to support Musk’s expanded solar strategy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tesla is hiring to support founder Elon Musk's recently announced plan to become what would be the biggest U.S. manufacturer of solar energy components, according to online posts by senior executives at the company.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/tesla-executives-say-hiring-is-ramping-up-support-musks-expanded-solar-strategy-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TU4AZ2AUKBLZTEPBSJWDEO5ISE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump signs proclamation on increasing certain types of beef imports, White House says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday signed a proclamation on increasing certain types of beef imports, the White House said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-signs-proclamation-increasing-certain-types-beef-imports-white-house-says-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLSZNOR5RVJZTAAFP3SSKZMNPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pentagon poised to curb some defense contractors' payouts under Trump order]]></title><description><![CDATA[Defense contractors are bracing for the Pentagon to release, as soon as Friday, a list of companies who would be subject to potential restrictions on stock buybacks and dividend payments, nearly a month after President Donald Trump signed an executive order linking shareholder payouts to weapons delivery schedules.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/pentagon-poised-curb-some-defense-contractors-payouts-under-trump-order-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4UB7KBL75OW5MASF4CTOILMNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:21:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Vista Equity Partners and Intel to lead investment in AI chip startup Samba Nova, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Private equity firm Vista Equity Partners is leading a new funding round of over $350 million in artificial intelligence chip startup SambaNova Systems, marking a rare departure from its traditional focus on enterprise software, according to people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/vista-equity-partners-intel-lead-investment-ai-chip-startup-samba-nova-sources-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPMKYG6HEBPBHBMHP5OSPMNVTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Fed's Daly sees labor market vulnerabilities, room to cut interest rates]]></title><description><![CDATA[San Francisco Federal Reserve President Mary Daly on Friday said she thinks one or two more interest rate cuts may be needed to counteract weakness in the labor market, where workers are "walking a knife's edge" with higher prices eating into their wages and scarce opportunities for new jobs.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-sees-labor-market-vulnerabilities-room-cut-interest-rates-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AC73T7EQCRJZTM2SH5TCMN42OM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:48:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apple plans to allow external voice-controlled AI chatbots in CarPlay, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing to allow voice-controlled artificial intelligence apps from other companies in CarPlay, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-plans-allow-external-voice-controlled-ai-chatbots-carplay-bloomberg-news-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3X6YD5TUNPDRHNW7EBPCTJPGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Union approves national agreement negotiated with marathon for 30,000 oil industry workers]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United Steelworkers union (USW) adopted a national agreement negotiated with Marathon Petroleum for use in contracts between 30,000 oil industry workers and their refineries and chemical plants, the union said in a statement posted on-line.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/union-approves-national-agreement-negotiated-with-marathon-30000-oil-industry-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CC4EZMKXXNK2PD2EF44QFY3U3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dow Jones Industrial Average hits record 50,000 points]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged above 50,000 points for the first time on Friday, a historic moment for the blue-chip index, which was up more than 2% in afternoon trading.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dow-jones-industrial-average-hits-record-50000-points-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJWF3BUDBVODFBZLOSLCLJUHCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:11:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ripple effects of software rout felt through asset managers]]></title><description><![CDATA[Asset managers and private equity firms found themselves at the sharp end of the AI‑driven shock hitting the software sector as investors fretted over exposure to loans and leverage tied to the industry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ripple-effects-software-rout-felt-through-asset-managers-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQCJFBVN7ZLSZFWOOGFTYWW2FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:47:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Justice Department casts wide net on Netflix's business practices in merger probe, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice is investigating whether Netflix engaged in anti-competitive tactics as part of the streaming giant's proposed acquisition of Warner Discovery's studios and streaming service, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/justice-department-casts-wide-net-netflixs-business-practices-merger-probe-wsj-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVMSHKHLXJKAVONWNGABTQCQKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs teams up with Anthropic to automate banking tasks with AI agents, CNBC reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs is working with technology startup Anthropic to develop AI-powered agents aimed at automating a widening range of internal functions, CNBC reported on Friday, citing the bank’s chief information officer.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-teams-up-with-anthropic-automate-banking-tasks-with-ai-agents-cnbc-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZTIGQD5CBPE7DJ34VWMRZUNN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[White House considers antitrust probe into homebuilders, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Trump administration officials are exploring opening an antitrust investigation into U.S. homebuilders as the White House ramps up efforts to address the housing affordability crisis in the country, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-considers-antitrust-probe-into-homebuilders-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KW3VAFV6UNNJDE2X2BBL54FMDA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:27:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil's Inpasa ramps up exports of dried distillers grains to China]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian corn ethanol producer Inpasa will quickly ramp up exports of dried distillers grains with solubles (DDGS) to China this year, Gustavo Mariano Oliveira, the company's vice president of trading, said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/brazils-inpasa-ramps-up-exports-dried-distillers-grains-china-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJIQOT7YTVI37H2DXEQOB5EEMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:26:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称特朗普关于起诉其美联储主席提名人选的言论是玩笑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五强调，特朗普总统上周末称若美联储主席提名人凯文·沃什不降息就起诉他的言论纯属玩笑。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Friday stressed that President Donald Trump was joking when he said over the weekend that he could sue Kevin Warsh, his nominee to lead the Federal Reserve, if he doesn't lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bessent-says-trumps-comment-about-suing-his-fed-chair-nominee-was-joke-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2TLFMREQJLLVFY4HY7EFDGGYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:20:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hims公司49美元减肥药动摇投资者对现金支付肥胖市场的信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hims & Hers公司推出诺和诺德Wegovy减肥药49美元复合版本的策略，正引发肥胖治疗股的剧烈震荡。此举不仅引发对该行为合法性的争议，更威胁到制药商在美国蓬勃发展的自费医疗市场中的收益。【原文：Hims & Hers' gambit to sell a $49 compounded version of Novo Nordisk's Wegovy pill is rattling obesity shares, sparking debate about the legality of the move and threatening drugmaker returns in the burgeoning U.S. cash-pay market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/hims-49-weight-loss-pill-rattles-investor-case-cash-pay-obesity-market-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIXPNKRDYNPVTNDPOJU7R4ETQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[詹妮弗·加纳创立的Once Upon a Farm公司于纽约证券交易所上市首日估值达8.45亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由演员詹妮弗·加纳联合创立的儿童有机食品公司"童话农场"，周五在纽约证券交易所首次公开募股时，其股价较发行价上涨16.7%，公司估值达到8.449亿美元。【原文：Once Upon a Farm , the children's organic food company co-founded by actor Jennifer Garner, fetched an $844.9 million valuation as its shares opened 16.7% above the offer price in its New York Stock Exchange debut on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jennifer-garners-once-upon-farm-valued-845-million-nyse-debut-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORW7OPJ5RBM4VEAHO5M3H6B6HM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:56:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉能可将专注短期资产处置，因力拓交易仍无定论]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘉能可与力拓的合并谈判破裂，这家总部位于瑞士的矿业集团很可能将专注于资产出售，以强化其铜业务组合。【原文：Glencore's failed merger talks with Rio Tinto , have left the Swiss-based mining group likely to focus on asset sales as it works to strengthen its copper portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/glencore-focus-short-term-disposals-rio-deal-remains-elusive-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVVQWECCDZKBJN2H5V33OPN63Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:51:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比利时Agomab Therapeutics公司估值达7.16亿美元，纳斯达克首日上市股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Agomab Therapeutics公司估值达7.164亿美元，其股票周五上市首日下跌约8%，因投资者对新股仍持审慎态度。【原文：Agomab Therapeutics secured a valuation of $716.4 million, after its shares fell about 8% in their debut on Friday, as investors remain selective about new offerings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/belgiums-agomab-therapeutics-valued-716-million-shares-fall-nasdaq-debut-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OR36DN4DVBPXVCX524CM5YGTCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:48:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Williams weighs buying gas-producing assets to enhance AI energy supply to hyperscalers, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，威廉姆斯公司正考虑收购美国天然气生产资产，这对能源基础设施运营商而言实属罕见举措。此举旨在确保天然气供应，以支持其面向超大规模企业及数据中心客户的一站式服务。【原文：Williams Companies is exploring buying natural gas production in the United States, a rare foray for an energy infrastructure operator, as it aims to secure natural gas supplies to support its one-stop-shop offering to hyperscalers and data center clients, three people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/williams-weighs-buying-gas-producing-assets-enhance-ai-energy-supply-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JA6HYPJG5FKIJPESPWI37FV6RM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:44:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷贸易部长称与美国的贸易协议不会排挤中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷外交部长帕布罗·基尔诺周五表示，本周签署的阿根廷与美国关键矿产协议并不排除中国对该国矿业领域的投资。【原文：A deal on critical minerals between Argentina and the United States signed this week does not rule out Chinese investment in the country's mining sector, Argentine Foreign Minister Pablo Quirno said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/argentinas-minerals-deal-with-us-does-not-rule-out-chinese-investment-minister-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZJWYSCKKWVPMBNFM3DLHAO6OQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:37:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[四大图表解读科技巨头季度业绩：人工智能投资激增与云计算业务增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技巨头预测今年支出将激增，因其正加倍押注人工智能领域，这加剧了投资者对这些高成本投资能否产生足够回报以支撑该行业高估值的审视。【原文：U.S. tech giants have predicted their spending would surge this year as they double down on artificial intelligence, sharpening investor scrutiny over whether these costly bets would generate enough returns to justify the sector's high valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/big-techs-quarter-four-charts-ai-splurge-cloud-growth-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32WGZHPBR5MYZGDDUQEAKOBEWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储杰斐逊对经济持谨慎乐观态度，认为就业市场趋稳，通胀率下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储副主席菲利普·杰斐逊周五表示，他对2026年的经济前景持"谨慎乐观"态度，预计经济增长将略高于趋势水平，劳动力市场趋于稳定，通胀率将重新回落至美联储2%的目标水平。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair Philip Jefferson said on Friday he was "cautiously optimistic" about the 2026 economic outlook, with growth expected to remain slightly above trend, the labor market stabilizing, and inflation resuming a decline to the U.S. central bank's 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-jefferson-cautiously-optimistic-about-economy-sees-job-market-stabilizing-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4HAJP4U7FMGLGJJQZG2H7R45Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官驳回Compass公司针对Zillow在线房屋挂牌信息提出的禁令申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一名联邦法官驳回了美国最大住宅房地产经纪公司Compass要求Zillow在其房地产平台上增加房源的禁令申请。【原文：A federal judge on Friday rejected a bid by Compass , the largest U.S. residential real estate brokerage, for an injunction requiring Zillow to list more homes on its real estate platforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-judge-rejects-compass-bid-injunction-over-zillow-online-home-listings-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">776OMY5UYRIHNDJOIN6E5NMTBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:45:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TPG收购电力基础设施企业Sabre Industries多数股权，交易额达35亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司TPG已同意从黑石集团手中收购Sabre Industries的多数股权，两家公司周五宣布了这一消息。据两位知情人士透露，这笔交易对这家电力基础设施公司的估值约为35亿美元。【原文：Private markets firm TPG has agreed to buy a majority stake in Sabre Industries from Blackstone , the companies said on Friday, in a deal two people familiar with the matter said valued the power infrastructure company at around $3.5 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/tpg-buys-majority-stake-35-billion-power-infrastructure-firm-sabre-industries-2026-02-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEE44UKZEVO6VJEX5WY77F62EE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:45:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>