<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 22:36:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 22:36:40 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[报道称，巴菲特将在 2026 年伯克希尔会议上与董事会成员并排而坐，但不会登台亮相]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《奥马哈世界先驱报》周日报道，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）创始人兼董事长沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）将放弃在 2026 年公司股东大会上按惯例登台亮相。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway founder and chairman Warren Buffett is going to forego his usual stage appearance at the 2026 company shareholders' meeting, the Omaha World-Herald reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/buffett-sit-alongside-board-members-2026-berkshire-meeting-wont-appear-stage-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKGZALJAOBINZCAUUQHW2KHIIU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 20:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大总理卡尼表示联邦预算将于秋季公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周日表示，联邦政府将在秋季提交一份预算案，而在此之前几天，加拿大财政部长曾表示，新的自由党政府将在今年晚些时候提交一份最新的经济报告。【原文：Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney said on Sunday the federal government will present a budget in the autumn, days after the finance minister had said the new Liberal government will have an economic update later in the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-pm-carney-says-federal-budget-will-come-autumn-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WDHVWA6NZI5VFOMRWI7DHN2S4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Telegram 创始人称拒绝接受 "压制 "罗马尼亚保守派声音的要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[Telegram 消息应用程序的创始人帕维尔-杜罗夫（Pavel Durov）周日表示，他拒绝了一个西方国家提出的 "压制 "罗马尼亚保守派声音的要求。【原文：The founder of the Telegram messaging app, Pavel Durov, said on Sunday he had refused a request by a Western country, which he did not name, to "silence" conservative voices in Romania, which was holding a presidential election run-off.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/telegram-founder-says-he-rejects-request-silence-conservative-voices-romania-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IG7SYXLEJKUVARS6HH2WBINGI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长在特朗普减税辩论中驳斥穆迪下调评级]]></title><description><![CDATA["斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）说："我不太相信穆迪下调评级的说法。【原文："I don't put much credence in the Moody's" downgrade, Scott Bessent said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasury-chief-dismisses-moodys-downgrade-amid-trump-tax-cut-debate-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22B7X3P7KNOONMG2JMULW6OOUI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[犯罪"：埃尔顿-约翰谴责英国的人工智能版权计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃尔顿-约翰（Elton John）周日指责英国政府 "偷窃"，因为英国政府建议科技公司在不保证适当补偿的情况下对英国的音乐和创意产出进行人工智能模型训练。【原文：Elton John on Sunday accused the British government of "committing theft" by proposing that tech firms could train artificial intelligence models on the UK's music and creative output without guaranteeing proper recompense.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/criminal-elton-john-condemns-uks-ai-copyright-plans-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEVCAD2KOBNCFAUEUZOWHIB2PY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 11:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国对来自美国、欧盟、日本和台湾的塑料制品征收反倾销税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周日宣布对从美国、欧盟、日本和台湾进口的工程塑料 POM 共聚物征收高达 74.9% 的反倾销税。【原文：China on Sunday announced anti-dumping duties as high as 74.9% on imports of POM copolymers, a type of engineering plastic, from the United States, the European Union, Japan and Taiwan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-announces-anti-dumping-duties-plastics-us-eu-japan-taiwan-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPTOY2RNNBORFPUR5WKFDEMR5U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CATL 称，到 2028 年，中国重型卡车销量的一半可能是电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，电池制造商 CATL 董事长周日表示，到 2028 年，中国重型卡车销量的一半可能是电动汽车，而 2024 年仅为 10%。【原文：Half of China's sales of heavy trucks could be electric vehicles by 2028, up from 10% in 2024, the chairman of battery maker CATL said on Sunday, according to a media report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/half-chinas-heavy-truck-sales-could-be-evs-by-2028-catl-says-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JITFUZN6DBI7FL232XUMQDBTCA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪下调评级加剧投资者对美国财政之路的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪（Moody's）下调美国主权评级加剧了投资者对迫在眉睫的债务定时炸弹的担忧，这可能会刺激债券市场的警惕者，他们希望看到华盛顿加强财政约束。【原文：A U.S. sovereign downgrade by Moody's has exacerbated investor worries about a looming debt time-bomb that could spur bond market vigilantes who want to see more fiscal restraint from Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/moodys-downgrade-intensifies-investor-worry-about-us-fiscal-path-2025-05-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VRD53KP5YJKETGQFV76FWODDPE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道贸易战中，一些中国公司着眼于在新加坡上市以拓展市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[四名消息人士称，至少有五家来自中国大陆或香港的公司正计划在未来 12 至 18 个月内在新加坡进行首次公开募股、两地上市或配股，因为在全球贸易紧张局势下，中国企业正寻求在东南亚扩张。【原文：At least five companies from mainland China or Hong Kong are planning IPOs, dual listings, or share placements in Singapore in the next 12 to 18 months, four sources said, as Chinese firms look to expand in Southeast Asia amid global trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/some-chinese-companies-eye-singapore-listings-expand-markets-amid-trade-war-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WBKEAPWIBM3XKM46JYOSR2MXY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[737 MAX 空难遇难者家属反对允许波音公司免于起诉的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名律师周六表示，在两起致命的波音 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故中遇难的 346 人中的一些人的家属计划反对该飞机制造商与美国司法部达成的暂定不起诉协议。【原文：Families of some of the 346 people killed in two fatal Boeing 737 MAX crashes plan to object to a tentative nonprosecution agreement between the planemaker and the U.S. Justice Department, a lawyer said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/families-737-max-crash-victims-object-deal-allowing-boeing-avoid-prosecution-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RH7H34B5DBPNFA232UFGPPX35A</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:59:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国目前不希望联合信贷银行全面竞购德国商业银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希-梅尔茨（Friedrich Merz）周六表示，德国目前不希望意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）全面竞购德国商业银行（Commerzbank）。【原文：Germany does not expect Italy's UniCredit to launch a full bid for German rival Commerzbank at present, German Chancellor Friedrich Merz said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/germany-does-not-expect-unicredit-go-full-commerzbank-bid-present-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EVSETT5WZLCPMSA4ZM3RUSOPU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共和党人对美国信用评级下调意见不一，党内税收法案问题久拖不决]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪下调美国主权信用评级在国会共和党人中引起了不同的反响，一些人质疑这一变化背后的动机，另一些人则认为这是一个警告，立法者在处理一项全面的税收和预算法案时应该注意到这一点。【原文：Moody's downgrade of the U.S. sovereign credit rating has elicited mixed responses among Republicans in Congress, with some questioning the motive behind the change and others depicting it as a warning that lawmakers should heed as they wrestle with a sweeping tax and budget bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/republicans-split-us-credit-downgrade-partys-tax-bill-lingers-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E445X63GNBJQDOA6JXXMLZJKGY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:28:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普力促美联储降息并批评鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六在社交媒体上发文称，美国联邦储备委员会应该 "宜早不宜迟 "地降息。【原文：President Donald Trump on Saturday said in a social media post the U.S. Federal Reserve should cut rates "sooner, rather than later."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-pushes-us-federal-reserve-rate-cuts-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FW5PNXMWRFPFXEAWVINAP3ZPOA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:27:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普让沃尔玛 "吃掉关税 "而不是提高价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六表示，沃尔玛（WMT.N）应该 "吃掉关税"，而不是把零售商涨价的责任归咎于对进口商品征收的关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Saturday that Walmart (WMT.N) should "eat the tariffs" instead of blaming duties imposed on imported goods for the retailer's increase prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-tells-walmart-eat-tariffs-instead-raising-prices-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3BAE4JNGNJJ3KHV3VGTLW4BCQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，特朗普政府对将阿里巴巴人工智能应用于 iPhone 的交易表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周六报道，白宫和国会官员一直在仔细审查苹果公司与阿里巴巴达成交易的计划，以便在中国的 iPhone 手机上使用中国公司的人工智能。【原文：The White House and congressional officials have been scrutinizing Apple's plan to strike a deal with Alibaba to make the Chinese company's AI available on iPhones in China, The New York Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-administration-is-concerned-by-deal-put-alibabas-ai-iphones-nyt-reports-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3EFNFQFCJJOTLWBBZXJ3YT7TU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:36:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲投资银行正在制定人工智能和半导体投资计划，以提高欧盟竞争力]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲投资银行（European Investment Bank）负责人周六表示，该银行正在制定一个新项目，以增强欧洲在人工智能和半导体方面的能力，目标是到2027年筹集700亿欧元（780亿美元）资金。【原文：The European Investment Bank is working on a new project to enhance European capabilities on artificial intelligence and semiconductors, with the aim of raising 70 billion euros ($78 billion) by 2027, its head said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eib-work-ai-semiconductor-investment-plan-boost-eu-competitiveness-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3NXXYQ5SJLUNMLSH6YOCR3PNA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:16:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TBS 称，日本在关税谈判中考虑为特斯拉电动汽车充电站提供补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 TBS 广播公司周六报道，日本正在考虑一项计划，在与美国的关税谈判中为特斯拉电动汽车充电站的建设提供补贴。【原文：Japan is considering a plan to offer subsidies for building charging stations for Tesla electric vehicles in tariff talks with the United States, broadcaster TBS reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japan-mulls-subsidies-teslas-ev-charging-stations-tariff-talks-tbs-says-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAS6A3LK2JOONHAUATPRAQWIZA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 08:29:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达首席执行官称中国市场 H20 之后的下一款芯片不会来自 Hopper 系列]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）周六表示，在美国政府限制其Hopper H20芯片在中国的销售后，英伟达正在评估如何应对中国市场，但不会推出另一版本的Hopper芯片。【原文：Nvidia is evaluating how to address the China market after the U.S. government placed limits on sales of its Hopper H20 chip there but it will not put out another version of the Hopper chip, CEO Jensen Huang said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-ceo-says-next-chip-after-h20-china-wont-be-hopper-series-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VD2XXC4UTZISHMH3RQRFBBXF5U</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国电信接近达成向华纳兄弟探索公司出售 TNT 体育股份的交易，英国金融时报报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周六报道，英国电信正在就向美国合资伙伴华纳兄弟发现公司出售其在英国广播公司 TNT 体育公司所持的 50%股份进行深入谈判。【原文：BT is in advanced talks to sell its 50% stake in British broadcaster TNT Sports to U.S. joint venture partner Warner Bros Discovery , the Financial Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/bt-nears-deal-sell-tnt-sports-stake-warner-bros-discovery-ft-reports-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWM3A2BFLJJK7AYY7UNLKSV54Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 04:55:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南加强与美国谈判以降低高额关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国即将对从东南亚国家进口的商品征收 46% 的关税，这可能会严重影响越南的经济增长，在此背景下，越南和美国于周五举行了首次部长级直接谈判。【原文：Vietnam and the United States held their first direct ministerial-level negotiations on Friday against the backdrop of an impending U.S. tariff of 46% on imports from the Southeast Asian nation, which could significantly impact its growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/vietnam-steps-up-talks-with-us-reduce-hefty-tariff-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGBN7JREPJNYZIRBCCGLVGADAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 04:13:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北京官员：中国的仿人机器人不会取代人类工人]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的仿人机器人不会取代人类工人，也不会造成大规模失业，一位负责监管北京科技中心的中国官员说。【原文：China's humanoid robots will not replace human workers and cause mass unemployment, according to a Chinese official who oversees a tech hub in Beijing, amid a rapid expansion of the sector and state funding for it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-humanoid-robots-will-not-replace-human-workers-beijing-official-says-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AH7LTJGJYNLKHC3OEU5O3P2YSI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:11:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国撤销对西南航空公司长期航班延误的起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五晚些时候撤销了拜登政府在其任期最后几天对西南航空公司提起的诉讼，该诉讼指控西南航空公司非法运营长期延误的航班。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice dropped a lawsuit late on Friday against Southwest Airlines , filed by the Biden administration in its final days, that accused the carrier of illegally operating chronically delayed flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-drops-suit-against-southwest-airlines-over-chronically-delayed-flights-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMAIPYQETBKS7AHJRC6EZY232I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 01:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉禁止持股不足 3% 的股东代表公司起诉高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五提交的一份监管文件显示，特斯拉禁止持有其不到 3% 股份的股东代表这家电动汽车制造商起诉其董事或高管违反职责。【原文：Tesla blocked shareholders who own less than 3% of its shares from suing its directors or officers on behalf of the electric vehicle maker for breach of duties, according to a regulatory filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/tesla-blocks-stockholders-with-less-than-3-shares-suing-officers-its-behalf-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEAZCSTNRZIANBONUTL7K4ZK24</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[发表 "白人种族灭绝 "言论后，马斯克的 xAI 更新了 Grok 聊天机器人]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）旗下的xAI公司回应了有关其Grok聊天机器人宣称对南非白人公民实施种族灭绝的广泛报道，称该人工智能机器人曾发生过未经授权的更改。xAI 周四在 X 上发文称，它将更新系统以解决这一问题。【原文：Elon Musk's xAI responded to widespread reports that its Grok chatbot made claims about a genocide against white citizens in South Africa, saying there had been an unauthorized change to the artificial intelligence bot. In a post on X on Thursday, xAI said it would update the system to address the problem.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-xai-updates-grok-chatbot-after-white-genocide-comments-2025-05-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EV45BWHUCVKU7HFGJMGAHCQZBM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Capital One 将支付 4.25 亿美元解决储蓄账户诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Capital One 同意支付 4.25 亿美元，以了结全国范围内的诉讼，该诉讼指控 Capital One 欺骗储蓄账户储户，不告诉他们可以把钱转到收益更高的账户，从而使他们无法获得更高的利率。【原文：Capital One agreed to pay $425 million to settle nationwide litigation accusing it of cheating savings account depositors out of much higher interest rates by not telling them they could move their money to higher-yielding accounts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/capital-one-pay-425-million-settle-litigation-over-savings-accounts-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BNG7KL5PFNDVDXP72E5CDYVVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 23:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顶级投资人库恩表示，汉莎航空管理层应对工会更加强硬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六，德国汉莎航空公司（Lufthansa）的顶级投资人克劳斯-迈克尔-库恩（Klaus-Michael Kuehne）在谈到该公司的股价时说，汉莎航空的管理层应该更加积极地抵制劳工代表的阻力。【原文：Lufthansa's management should be more vigorous in fending off resistance from labour representatives, top investor Klaus-Michael Kuehne was quoted as saying on Saturday, pointing to the airline group's share price.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/lufthansa-management-should-be-tougher-with-unions-says-top-investor-kuehne-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GDCMF4YG5ME7NBAX3DCNVVMPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 23:05:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将在航空公司会议后宣布临时削减纽瓦克机场航班数量]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周五表示，计划在与美国主要航空公司会面后宣布暂时削减纽瓦克机场航班的建议，以解决拥堵造成的影响。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said Friday it plans to announce proposed temporary cuts to flights at Newark after meetings with major U.S. airlines to address congestion impacts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-faa-announce-temporary-flight-cuts-newark-after-airline-meetings-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7D3CORKN5KP7K7SGODZZAMD3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称日产考虑关闭日本及海外工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士周六透露，日产汽车公司正在考虑关闭日本的两家汽车组装厂和包括墨西哥在内的海外工厂，这也是该公司本周早些时候提出的成本削减计划的一部分。【原文：Nissan is considering plans to shut two car assembly plants in Japan and overseas factories, including in Mexico, sources said on Saturday, as part of a cost-cutting plan the company flagged earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/nissan-plans-shut-japans-oppama-shonan-plants-under-restructuring-yomiuri-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RO435YXHNMVTF72WL2QXDY3EU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上诉法官就 CFPB 清盘问题敦促特朗普政府和工会]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿联邦上诉法院的法官们周五就他们能在多大程度上指示特朗普政府运营政府的消费者金融监督机构展开了争论。【原文：Federal appeals court judges in Washington wrestled Friday with the extent to which they could instruct the Trump administration to operate the government's consumer finance watchdog agency, which the White House this year has sought to decimate if not shut down entirely.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/appeals-judges-prod-trump-admin-union-over-cfpb-wind-down-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LNPFSTKUBICDF5ZZUTH4UKEAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，3月份外国持有的美国国债高达9万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五公布的数据显示，3月份外国持有的美国国债飙升至历史新高，连续第三个月上升，原因是在唐纳德-特朗普总统上台几个月后，对美国国债的需求依然强劲。【原文：Foreign holdings of U.S. Treasuries soared to a record high in March, data from the Treasury Department showed on Friday, rising for a third straight month, as demand for U.S. government debt remained robust a few months after President Donald Trump took office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/foreign-holdings-us-treasuries-top-9-trillion-march-data-shows-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZ3ST62FTRNLVLTLKSKFJOLM2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 22:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>