<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:33:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:33:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普分享视频后，伯克希尔驳斥有关巴菲特言论的 "不实 "报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周五表示，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的 "真理社交"（Truth Social）账户分享了一段视频，暗示沃伦-巴菲特支持美国总统的经济政策之后，社交媒体上有关该公司董事长涉嫌发表言论的报道是 "虚假的"。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway said on Friday that reports on social media regarding comments allegedly made by its chairman are "false," after Donald Trump's account on Truth Social shared a video suggesting that Warren Buffett endorsed the U.S. president's economic policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-dismisses-false-reports-buffett-comments-after-trump-shares-video-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKBNVG2FGRLYFOOIVWJZ6SCA2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:17:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税动荡冻结全球并购交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[从华尔街到以色列和瑞典，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的新关税及其引发的全球股市抛售迅速阻碍了收购和首次公开募股。【原文：From Wall Street to Israel and Sweden, U.S. President Donald Trump's new tariffs -- and the global equities sell-off they sparked -- have rapidly scuttled acquisitions and IPOs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/tariff-turmoil-puts-freeze-global-ma-dealmaking-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O36CGKF32VJRHPO3VT5WSDH5HA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部的贝森特市场下跌是 "Mag 7 "的问题，而不是 MAGA 的问题 - 塔克-卡尔森访谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）在周五接受塔克-卡尔森（Tucker Carlson）采访时表示，股市暴跌与今年早些时候中国出人意料地推出 DeepSeek 人工智能工具有关，而不是与唐纳德-特朗普总统的政策有关。【原文：The stock market plunge has more to do with the surprise emergence of China's DeepSeek artificial intelligence tool earlier this year than it does with President Donald Trump's policies, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said in an interview with Tucker Carlson released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/treasurys-bessent-market-drop-mag-7-problem-not-maga-one-tucker-carlson-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KX3WP7UTQJID3IJQLH6NOCMEOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者称，拉美资产可能会受到贸易战的提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉美股票和债券可能不会成为赢家，因为到目前为止，特朗普政府的贸易战大多没有波及该地区，而贸易战却引发了华尔街市场的溃败，使投资者开始追逐非美国资产。【原文：Latin American stocks and bonds could be unlikely winners as the Trump administration's trade war so far mostly spared the region, while it triggered a market rout on Wall Street that has sent investors on a hunt for non-U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/latam-assets-may-receive-trade-war-boost-investors-say-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GWPBHJ5YBJCTLHU5UUBKCOS5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税刺激需求担忧，炼油股跌至近两年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统特朗普宣布征收新关税后，美国炼油企业的股价周五跌至两年来的最低点，因为投资者担心石油和燃料需求放缓以及炼油利润率下降。【原文：Shares of U.S. refiners fell to two-year lows on Friday in the wake of U.S. President Trump's announcement of new tariffs, as fears of slower oil and fuel demand and weakening refining margins rattled investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/refining-stocks-plunge-near-two-year-lows-trump-tariffs-spur-demand-worries-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5PYITIR4VODHKLAY23EPMAEKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国石油服务公司将受到特朗普关税和油价下跌的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和金融公司周五表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策使供应链陷入混乱，油价暴跌又为钻探活动下降埋下伏笔，美国油田服务公司正准备迎接打击。【原文：U.S. oilfield service firms are bracing for a hit as President Donald Trump's tariffs throw supply chains into disarray and tumbling oil prices set the stage for a drop in drilling activity, analysts and financial firms said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-service-firms-set-hit-trump-tariffs-tumbling-oil-prices-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LFHOCO2ARJ6ZORTFA3PF3BABA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国高等级债券发行市场出现自大流行病以来从未有过的态势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策导致美国投资级债券的发行在本周戛然而止，但一些银行家表示，在过去的一个月里，市场压力已经显现，因为焦虑不安的投资者推低了定价。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs brought U.S. investment-grade bond issuance to a screeching halt this week, but market stress had already been apparent over the past month as jittery investors pushed back on pricing, some bankers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-high-grade-bond-issuance-market-teeters-ways-not-seen-since-pandemic-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XT7GJUDW7VLETGJHFVQOA5LYUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将把 TikTok 的最后期限延长 75 天]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五延长了 ByteDance 出售短视频应用 TikTok 美国资产的最后期限，并表示已经取得了 "巨大进展"，但还需要做更多的工作以获得批准。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday extended the deadline for the sale of ByteDance's U.S. assets of short video app TikTok, saying "tremendous progress" had been made but more work was needed to secure approvals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-says-he-will-extend-tiktok-deadline-75-days-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBNJOKCLU5PLFJZCFZT5W4TBLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:46:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的沃勒稳定币为支付系统带来好处]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）周五表示，稳定币对国家支付系统来说是件好事，但他怀疑金融系统能否支持大量此类资产。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Christopher Waller said on Friday that stablecoins are a good thing for the nation’s payment system, but he doubts the financial system can support a large number of these assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/feds-waller-stablecoins-bring-benefits-payment-system-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FINIUDT4RNNSTKBU7FRFQRYCDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:28:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国石油钻井平台数量升至 6 月以来最高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周连续第二周削减了石油和天然气钻井平台的作业数量，尽管石油钻井平台数量已升至 6 月份以来的最高点。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating for a second week in a row, even as the number of oil rigs rose to the highest since June, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-rig-count-rises-highest-since-june-baker-hughes-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KP7RQSRBCNJDLD3ALWB7X44HCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国广播公司新闻记者称，沃尔玛考虑加入投资者集团收购 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国广播公司新闻记者 Selina Wang 周五在 X 上发帖称，沃尔玛正在考虑加入一个投资者团体，收购短视频应用 TikTok。【原文：Walmart is considering joining a group of investors to buy short video app TikTok, ABC News reporter Selina Wang said in a post on X on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/walmart-considers-joining-investor-group-buy-tiktok-abc-news-reporter-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KCQT6WUCVPNVEBSXEVFVKHRC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISS 建议对美国银行首席执行官薪酬投反对票]]></title><description><![CDATA[代理顾问机构股东服务公司（Institutional Shareholder Services）建议投资者对包括首席执行官布莱恩-莫伊尼汉（Brian Moynihan）在内的美国银行高管的薪酬投反对票，理由是对薪酬制定过程的担忧。【原文：Proxy adviser Institutional Shareholder Services has recommended that investors cast advisory votes against the pay of top Bank of America executives including CEO Brian Moynihan, citing concerns about the process used to set the compensation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/iss-recommends-votes-against-bank-americas-ceo-pay-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JH3JO4OKGNKEHOUGRRL7LGFC3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:41:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府将在墨西哥湾举行石油和天然气租赁销售活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国内政部周五表示，美国将按照前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）政府的计划，在墨西哥湾举行一次石油和天然气租赁销售活动，并将于六月份发布拟议通知。【原文：The U.S. will hold an oil and gas lease sale in the Gulf of Mexico, as planned by the administration of former President Joe Biden, and will release a proposed notice of it in June, the Interior Department said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-administration-hold-oil-gas-lease-sale-gulf-mexico-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WOBY2JGPJI4FKLN24BS2FS7HY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[年届 50 岁的微软加大了 Copilot 行动的力度，以保持在人工智能领域的领先地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[当微软公司的产品经理演示该公司的最新功能时，数千人在昏暗的会议大厅里如痴如醉，感觉更像是在举行一场摇滚音乐会：如何在 Excel 中通过点击一个按钮来计算数字的总和。【原文：Thousands of people swooned in a dark conference hall that felt more like a rock concert when a Microsoft product manager demonstrated the company's latest feature: how to sum numbers in Excel, with the click of a button.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/microsoft-turning-50-dials-up-copilot-actions-stay-ai-game-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYLG3S5EDBP6HGG2HMT3RYXAHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:32:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关税不确定的情况下，现代汽车将在 6 月前保持汽车价格稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车（Hyundai Motor）周五表示，该公司将在未来两个月内保持现有车型系列的贴纸价格稳定，以缓解消费者对关税影响经销商销售的担忧。【原文：Hyundai Motor is keeping sticker prices on its current model lineup steady for the next two months, the company said Friday, in an effort to ease shoppers' concerns that fallout from tariffs will affect dealer lots.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-keep-vehicle-prices-steady-until-june-amid-tariff-uncertainty-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75QOSTI2M5OQTA4V3Y6LAAFFJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称对冲基金抛售的股票数量为 2010 年以来最多]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）周五在给客户的一份说明中说，在市场崩溃的背景下，全球对冲基金周四净抛售全球股票，创下自2010年以来最大单日抛售量。【原文：Hedge funds across the world on Thursday sold global equities on a net basis at largest 1-day amount since 2010 amid a market meltdown, Goldman Sachs said in a note to clients on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/hedge-funds-sell-largest-amount-stocks-since-2010-goldman-sachs-says-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2M2HOW7TVPPDAKTLBHTPOPDAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税冲击后，市场警示灯闪烁黄灯]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收关税之后，全球市场陷入了下行通道，投资者的警示灯在闪烁，但尚未亮起红灯。【原文：Global markets have been sucked into a down-draft after U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs, setting investors' go-to warning lights flickering but not yet flashing red.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-stress-graphic-pix-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FHB3Y7VJ5N4DBF23CR6C4TE54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，日本 Rapidus 公司正与苹果和谷歌洽谈大规模生产芯片事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周五援引该公司首席执行官小池敦义的话报道，日本芯片制造商 Rapidus 正在与苹果、谷歌和其他数十家潜在客户谈判，以便在 2027 年之前大规模生产先进芯片。【原文：Japanese chipmaker Rapidus is negotiating with Apple , Google and dozens of other potential clients to mass-produce advanced chips by 2027, the Nikkei business daily reported on Friday, citing the company's CEO Atsuyoshi Koike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/japans-rapidus-talks-with-apple-google-mass-produce-chips-nikkei-reports-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZEMOKCRJNJOBIH6AYIELJ34SU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列官员称内塔尼亚胡已与特朗普谈及关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名以色列高级官员周五表示，以色列总理本雅明-内塔尼亚胡已与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普就其新关税政策进行了交谈，以色列正努力将美国威胁采取的措施的影响降至最低。【原文：Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has spoken with U.S. President Donald Trump about his new tariff policy, two senior Israeli officials said on Friday, as Israel seeks to minimise the impact of the threatened U.S. measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israels-netanyahu-has-spoken-trump-about-tariffs-officials-say-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDAJU7SXCJLDPFAJ3EBI5KGCWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国司法部正在审查企业监控制度]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟知内情的消息人士透露，美国司法部已经暂停了企业监督员制度，这是对设立此类公司来监督已解决错失行为指控的公司的做法进行非正式审查的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department has paused corporate monitorships as part of an informal review into the practice of installing such firms to oversee companies that have resolved accusations of wrongdoing, according to two sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-justice-department-is-reviewing-corporate-monitorships-sources-say-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXOKU5EUHRMTRBUUUZ7X2NUVGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：关税动荡，Klarna暂停美国上市计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，在美国最新关税引发的动荡中，瑞典金融科技公司Klarna暂停了首次公开募股计划。【原文：Swedish fintech company Klarna has paused plans for an initial public offering amid turmoil sparked by the latest U.S. tariffs, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/klarna-pauses-us-ipo-plans-amid-tariff-turmoil-wsj-reports-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDMBCCQMXZMRDEL4UWD6B3OCGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国部长呼吁坚定应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国工业部长呼吁对美国的关税做出适度但坚定的回应，并表示欧洲仍愿意就解决方案进行谈判。【原文：France's industry minister called for a proportionate but firm response to US tariffs and said Europe remained open to negotiate a solution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/french-minister-calls-firm-response-us-tariffs-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSMYVBMUOVOEBAYFWREPLBYOOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储降息的 "最佳时机]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五呼吁美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔降息，称现在是降息的 "最佳时机"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday called on Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell to cut interest rates, saying it was the "perfect time" to do so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-perfect-time-fed-cut-interest-rates-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZVXTDWMN5NQ5OMKVZJL7SCZT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:17:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，ProSiebenSat.1 将与摩根士丹利合作抵御 MFE 的竞购]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，ProSiebenSat.1 在收到其最大投资者 MFE-MediaForEurope 的收购要约后，已经聘请了包括摩根士丹利在内的辩护律师，MFE-MediaForEurope 是由意大利贝卢斯科尼家族控制的电视集团。【原文：ProSiebenSat.1 has lined up defence advisers, including Morgan Stanley , after receiving a takeover bid from its largest investor MFE-MediaForEurope , the TV group controlled by Italy's Berlusconi family, two people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/prosiebensat1-lines-up-morgan-stanley-defence-against-mfes-bid-sources-say-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4PO6YH5ARNINMMTLGDO4IJWOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:11:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Information 报道，Meta 公司即将在本月发布新的人工智能模型 Llama 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Information 周五报道，Meta Platforms 计划在本月晚些时候发布其最新版本的大型语言模型，在此之前至少推迟了两次。【原文：Meta Platforms plans to release the latest version of its large language model later this month, after delaying it at least twice, the Information reported on Friday, as the Facebook owner scrambles to lead in the AI race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/meta-nears-release-new-ai-model-llama-4-this-month-information-reports-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72JY7SHT2VIRXGCXN36RMQORK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯里兰卡表示致力于大幅削减与美国的关税和非关税壁垒]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯里兰卡周五表示，已准备好与美国加强贸易关系，并承诺大幅削减阻碍贸易和投资的关税和非关税壁垒。【原文：Sri Lanka is ready to engage with the United States in strengthening trade relations, the island nation said on Friday, committing to substantially reduce tariff and non-tariff barriers that hinder trade and investment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/sri-lanka-says-it-is-committed-substantially-reduce-tariff-non-tariff-barriers-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OO75OY4BFLJVDTP3SOSLDL7W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:53:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[无处藏身：特朗普关税让贸易伙伴走投无路]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易战中，美国的贸易伙伴们几乎没有什么好的选择，除了起诉求和。【原文：U.S. trading partners have few good options in their trade war with President Donald Trump, other than to sue for peace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/nowhere-hide-trump-tariffs-leave-trading-partners-cornered-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6I24W24XYFNOVEG2FMO3ZF2DNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛峰集团18亿美元柯林斯交易获欧盟反垄断批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国发动机和飞机设备制造商赛峰集团周五获得欧盟反垄断监管机构的批准，以 18 亿美元收购柯林斯宇航公司的飞行控制业务，此前该公司承诺出售北美的执行器业务。【原文：French engine and aircraft equipment maker Safran on Friday secured the green light from EU antitrust regulators for its $1.8 billion bid for Collins Aerospace's flight controls business after pledging to sell a North American actuator business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/safran-wins-eu-antitrust-approval-18-billion-collins-deal-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BGSZBP62ZL6DD4M2JGVULGS5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税推动汽车销售，Stellantis 将员工折扣扩大至公众]]></title><description><![CDATA[克莱斯勒母公司斯泰兰特公司周五证实，该公司将在部分新车型上向更广泛的市场推出员工折扣计划。【原文：Chrysler-parent Stellantis is extending its employee-discount program to the wider market on some new models, the company confirmed Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-extends-employee-discount-public-tariffs-drive-car-sales-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMWJZO7RDBPNTJLV64JZPQILZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市抛售，华尔街 "恐惧指数 "跃升至 8 个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，华尔街最高 "恐惧指数 "跃升至八个月来的新高，美国股市大幅低开，此前中国对所有美国商品征收新的关税，以回应特朗普政府的全面征税。【原文：Wall Street's top 'fear gauge' jumped to a fresh eight-month high on Friday as U.S. stocks opened sharply lower after China imposed fresh tariffs on all U.S. goods in response to the Trump administration's sweeping levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wall-street-fear-gauge-jumps-8-month-high-stocks-sell-off-2025-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMN4Z3CSENJPNPYDPHD5GC255Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:38:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>