<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:05:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:05:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[韩国部长在格里尔会议上要求豁免美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国贸工部长安德根（Ahn Deuk-geun）周五表示，他会见了美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer），并再次要求免除华盛顿的关税措施。【原文：South Korea's minister of trade and industry Ahn Deuk-geun said on Friday that he met U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer and asked again for a waiver from Washington's tariff measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-minister-asks-exemption-us-tariffs-greer-meeting-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WILWIK5KJ5OKZGHE5BUDTUNFGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:03:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普：阿联酋和美国就阿布扎比购买最先进人工智能芯片的途径达成一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，阿拉伯联合酋长国和美国已同意为海湾国家从美国公司购买一些最先进的人工智能半导体开辟一条道路。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday the United Arab Emirates and the United States have agreed to create a path for the Gulf country to buy some of the most advanced artificial intelligence semiconductors from U.S. companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/uae-us-agree-path-abu-dhabi-buy-most-advanced-ai-chips-trump-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H26YZ6PH2NNP3KDMLMOFHHJTYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大幅抛售后资金回流美国上市的中国 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中美关税休战提振了市场情绪，跟踪中国股市的主要美国上市交易所交易基金（ETF）在 5 月份录得资金流入。【原文：Major U.S.-listed exchange-traded funds (ETFs) that track Chinese stocks recorded inflows in May as a U.S.-China tariff truce boosted sentiment, following a heavy sell-off in the previous month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/capital-flows-back-us-listed-china-etfs-post-big-sell-off-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRPJBGX5BZKSFIMHPAN35KOTDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Charter 就与考克斯合并进行深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，宽带和有线电视服务提供商 Charter 正在与考克斯通信公司（Cox Communications）就合并事宜进行深入谈判，该交易对考克斯的估值超过 300 亿美元。【原文：Broadband and cable TV provider Charter is in advanced talks to combine with Cox Communications in a deal that values Cox at more than $30 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/charter-advanced-talks-combine-with-cox-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVZQ5SXFDRJKNOWYHCZE2OSQII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗地亚《权力的游戏》拍摄地面临特朗普关税威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[克罗地亚古城杜布罗夫尼克的堡垒和鹅卵石铺就的街道上经常挤满了游客，他们都渴望参观《权力的游戏》电视剧或《星球大战：最后的绝地武士》电影中的取景地。【原文：The fortresses and cobbled streets of the ancient Croatian town of Dubrovnik are often crowded with tourists eager to visit the locations from the Game of Thrones television series or the Star Wars: The Last Jedi film.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/croatias-game-thrones-filming-sites-face-threat-trump-tariffs-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZUP3EOB3VLVXA2D4DQVXCWORQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Patria 公司推出数据中心平台，首期投资 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着云计算和人工智能在拉丁美洲的应用加速，巴西投资公司 Patria Investimentos 周五宣布推出超大规模数据中心平台 Omnia，该公司将在未来 18-24 个月内为其首个项目投资约 10 亿美元。【原文：Brazilian investment firm Patria Investimentos on Friday announced the launch of Omnia, a hyperscale data center platform that will invest about $1 billion in its first project in the next 18 to 24 months, as cloud computing and artificial intelligence adoption accelerates in Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-patria-launches-data-center-platform-with-initial-investment-1-billion-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVS2U32DONNA5DWD3EOKIKJ5LU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工资谈判陷入僵局，新泽西公交公司铁路四十年来首次罢工开始]]></title><description><![CDATA[新泽西州通勤铁路工程师周五提前下班，因为马拉松式的合同谈判在其工会为满足工资要求而设定的午夜最后期限前陷入僵局，从而引发了 40 多年来席卷美国第三大交通系统的首次罢工。【原文：New Jersey's commuter rail engineers walked off the job early on Friday after marathon contract talks stalled ahead of a midnight deadline their union set for meeting its wage demands, igniting the first strike to engulf the third-largest U.S. transit system in more than 40 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/new-jersey-transit-rail-strike-first-four-decades-begins-wage-talks-stall-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGGWGEHV7BKMHP2JGUW3JAKSKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球时报》：应延长中美90天关税休战期]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家支持的《环球时报》周五称，上周末中美两国在瑞士贸易谈判期间达成的为期90天的关税休战协议太短，因为世界上最大的两个经济体的特使正在韩国重新集结。【原文：The 90-day tariff truce agreed by the United States and China during trade talks in Switzerland last weekend is too short, China's state-backed Global Times said on Friday, as envoys from the world's two biggest economies regrouped in Korea.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-us-90-day-tariff-truce-should-be-extended-global-times-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NXPPGK47VJEDMKXCXT3URC2UE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:27:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纬创称美国新工厂将于明年为 Nvidia 服务器生产做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾电子制造商纬创（Wistron）周五表示，其为客户英伟达（Nvidia）在美国新建的生产设施将于明年完工，该公司正在与其他潜在客户进行谈判。【原文：Taiwanese electronics manufacturer Wistron said on Friday that its new U.S. manufacturing facilities for its customer Nvidia would be ready next year and the firm was in talks with potential other customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/wistron-says-new-us-plants-will-be-ready-nvidias-server-production-next-year-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIK3IDKXIFLZ5P23MKVRI6Q7YM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业巨变后，中国主动型基金以全新产品蓄势待发]]></title><description><![CDATA[本月公布的中国主动型基金新规将彻底改变中国股市的资金流向，这促使业内一些大公司立即行动起来，推出新产品。【原文：New rules for Chinese active funds unveiled this month that are set to drastically change fund flows in the country's stock markets have prompted immediate action from some of the biggest players in the industry to introduce fresh products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/chinese-active-funds-gear-up-with-fresh-products-after-dramatic-industry-reforms-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPYGN4GCZNJY7MAI66BLC2KEIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的邻国为何希望与特朗普达成货币交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着韩国、台湾和日本的货币升值，有关这些经济体可能在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易谈判中利用汇率重估作为筹码的传言也甚嚣尘上。【原文：As the currencies of South Korea, Taiwan and Japan rise, so too is chatter that these economies could use exchange rate revaluation as a carrot in trade talks with U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/why-chinas-neighbours-may-want-currency-deals-with-trump-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZANQUVMCBICFBZEQCUNT6ERRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉凯恩汽车公司交易后，美国车桥公司计划在伦敦二次上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于底特律的美国车桥与制造公司周五表示，在斥资 14 亿美元收购吉凯恩汽车公司（GKN Automotive）所有者 Dowlais 之后，该公司计划寻求在伦敦进行股票二次上市。【原文：Detroit-based American Axle and Manufacturing said on Friday it plans to seek a secondary listing of its shares in London after its $1.4 billion acquisition of GKN Automotive owner Dowlais .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/american-axle-plans-secondary-london-listing-after-gkn-automotive-deal-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QL7566PISJJGPJVHZWIPRDJIRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行：贸易休战后美国不再可能出现经济衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）在周四晚些时候发布的一份报告中称，鉴于中美贸易紧张局势出现缓和迹象，该行不再预计美国经济将在今年晚些时候陷入衰退，并上调了经济增长预期。【原文：Barclays no longer expects the U.S. economy to slip into a recession later this year and has revised up its growth forecasts, given signs of a de-escalation in U.S.-China trade tensions, the bank said in a note released late Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-recession-no-longer-likely-after-trade-truce-says-barclays-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SE42SGSLNK45D26FTT34CTP2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 4 月份核心通胀率可能升至两年来最快水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于能源补贴减少和食品成本上升，日本 4 月份的核心通胀率可能创下两年来的最快增速，这增加了央行加息的压力。【原文：Japan's April core inflation probably rose at its fastest pace in two years on the reduction of energy subsidies and higher food costs, a Reuters poll showed, adding to pressure on the central bank to raise interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-april-core-inflation-likely-sped-up-fastest-pace-two-years-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYGAFDBQK5LYBMYJO6IZWNJ6KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡地亚珠宝大放异彩，历峰集团销售额增长 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡地亚的所有者历峰集团（Richemont）周五报告称，该集团季度销售额增长了7%，略好于预期，原因是美国富裕的购物者摆脱了经济的不确定性，继续在奢侈珠宝上挥金如土，从而抵消了亚洲需求的疲软。【原文：Cartier owner Richemont on Friday reported a slightly better-than-expected 7% rise in quarterly sales as weaker demand in Asia was offset by brisk business in the United States where wealthy shoppers shrugged off economic uncertainty and continued to splash out on luxury jewellery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cartier-owner-richemont-sales-up-7-jewellery-shines-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXQETUUOMRKFTOLL52YSZ3YZGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾与美国在韩国举行关税会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾副总理郑丽群周五表示，台湾和美国的主要贸易代表在韩国举行了贸易谈判，双方对进一步谈判将导致美国降低对台湾出口产品的关税表示乐观。【原文：The main Taiwan and U.S. trade representatives met in South Korea for trade negotiations, yielding optimism that further talks would lead to reduced U.S. tariffs on Taiwan exports, the island's Vice-Premier Cheng Li-chiun said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-meets-with-us-tariff-talks-south-korea-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAMGKNGROJJORGIHWPXR22T54U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:22:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡航空公司高管表示，最近飞往中国的航班需求有所增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡航空公司首席商务官李力新周五表示，最近几个月进入中国的客流量激增，但出境游仍未恢复到大流行前的水平。【原文：Singapore Airlines has seen a surge in passenger traffic into China in recent months, but outbound travel has still not recovered to pre-pandemic levels, Chief Commercial Officer Lee Lik Hsin said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/demand-flights-china-has-risen-recently-singapore-airlines-exec-says-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC32NBSLLNO7PBMZ62UFF2B6EY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价贸易推动的本周反弹戛然而止]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5K7BU4YPVJL3ISUJXPK5UNL24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行中村呼吁因美国关税不确定性暂停加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行董事会成员中村丰明（Toyoaki Nakamura）周五表示，央行目前必须暂缓加息，以仔细研究美国提高关税的不确定性会如何影响企业利润、资本支出和工资。【原文：Bank of Japan board member Toyoaki Nakamura said on Friday the central bank must hold off raising interest rates for the time being to scrutinise how uncertainty over higher U.S. tariffs could affect corporate profits, capital expenditure and wages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bojs-nakamura-calls-pause-rate-hikes-us-tariff-uncertainty-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXHMPDQBXJNBHPUHHCHVODFYQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，英伟达计划在上海建立研究中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，英伟达正在寻求在中国建立一个研发中心，该公司的最高负责人黄仁勋在四月份与上海市市长龚正会面时讨论了这一计划。【原文：Nvidia is seeking to build a research and development center in China, and the company's top boss Jensen Huang discussed the plan with Shanghai's mayor Gong Zheng when they met in April, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-plans-shanghai-research-center-ft-reports-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4HXKN44VVJH7DUXYGGD2XEKTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称中国佛山海天将在香港上市融资约 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位直接知情人士透露，中国佛山海天调味食品公司已获得香港联交所批准在港上市，该公司的目标是融资约 10 亿美元。【原文：China's Foshan Haitian Flavouring and Food Company has received approval from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange to list in the city and it aims to raise about $1 billion, according to two sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-foshan-haitian-raise-about-1-billion-hong-kong-listing-sources-say-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMGKU2UBGNIOZCDL6JC3MBB34Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇率飙升，惠誉下调台湾寿险公司评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用评级机构惠誉（Fitch）周四对五家台湾寿险公司进行了评级下调的审查，因为本月台币的大幅飙升给这些公司的资产负债表带来了压力。【原文：Credit ratings agency Fitch on Thursday placed five Taiwanese life insurers under review for potential downgrades after a sharp surge in the Taiwanese dollar this month put stress on their balance sheets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fitch-puts-taiwan-life-insurers-downgrade-watch-after-currency-surge-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FU2MSFG7SZOAZEMZLNVI6LLJUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GlobalWafers 在美国开设新工厂；计划追加 40 亿美元投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾硅晶圆制造商环球晶圆公司（GlobalWafers）周五表示，将在美国追加投资 40 亿美元，以满足美国客户日益增长的需求，同时该公司在得克萨斯州新建的价值 35 亿美元的晶圆厂正式开业。【原文：Taiwanese silicon wafer manufacturer GlobalWafers said on Friday it would invest an additional $4 billion in the United States to meet growing customer demand there, as it officially opened its new $3.5 billion wafer facility in Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/globalwafers-opens-new-us-factory-plans-additional-4-bln-investment-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHXEUA422VMWFMFRYXHGPAEDAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税下调缓解了中国大规模裁员的威胁，但就业市场的痛苦依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国进口关税在 4 月份飙升至三位数，迫使广东一家照明产品工厂和一家鞋类制造商减少产量，中国工人刘胜尊在短短一个月内失去了两份工作。【原文：Chinese worker Liu Shengzun lost two jobs in just one month as U.S. import tariffs shot up to triple digits in April, forcing a Guangdong lighting products factory, and then a footwear maker, to reduce output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/tariff-cuts-ease-mass-china-layoffs-threat-job-market-pain-persists-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJYPBN2I6VMKZD44QIWIM2XMG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普实施 100% 关税计划后，新西兰加强了电影制作激励措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对美国境外制作的电影征收 100%关税之后，新西兰将拨出更多预算资金，为在该国拍摄电影的外国电影公司提供回扣。【原文：New Zealand will allocate more budget funds to give rebates to foreign studios for filming movies in the country - a move which follows U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of 100% tariffs on films made outside the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/new-zealand-boosts-movie-production-incentives-after-trumps-100-tariff-plan-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZIX3NZXVZM43EH7C5N4VXR3XI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:25:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市本周将以疲软态势强势收官，债券则将迎来缓解性反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，随着中美贸易谈判的喜悦逐渐消退，亚洲股市以疲软的走势结束了本周的强劲走势，而对美国宽松政策的押注重燃，引发了跌势乏力的债券市场的反弹。【原文：Asian stocks were ending a strong week on a softer note on Friday as the euphoria over U.S.-China trade talks faded, while revived bets for policy easing in the United States sparked a rally in beaten-down bond markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDGRR4BIPVKQXKHPPNUKIFIQBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国数据向好，美元追随国债收益率走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五与美国国债收益率同步下跌，此前本周美国经济数据意外下行，巩固了美联储今年将进一步降息的预期。【原文：The dollar fell in tandem with U.S. Treasury yields on Friday after downside surprises on U.S. economic data this week cemented bets of more Federal Reserve rate cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-tracks-treasury-yields-lower-benign-us-data-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIFPFAWZXNNFJP2YWAIG5CZ2RM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:50:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易缓和，油价有望实现 1%的周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美中贸易的乐观情绪超过了伊朗供应重返市场的前景，周五油价在前一交易日大幅下跌后上扬，周涨幅超过1%。【原文：Oil prices edged up on Friday following a sharp drop in the previous session, heading for a weekly gain of more than 1% as U.S.-China trade optimism outweighed the prospects of Iranian supply returning to the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-heading-1-weekly-gain-us-china-trade-detente-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2KPZKYST5K6ZHWUECWHYMXJWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Third Point 在提交的文件中详细说明了其在美国钢铁公司和 Kenvue 公司的股份情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资者丹尼尔-勒布（Daniel Loeb）的对冲基金Third Point周四详细公布了其在美国钢铁公司和Kenvue公司的持股规模，股东们希望这两家公司不久将因被收购而受益。【原文：Billionaire investor Daniel Loeb's hedge fund Third Point on Thursday detailed the size of its stakes in U.S. Steel and Kenvue , companies that shareholders hope will soon benefit from being bought by someone.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/third-point-details-stakes-us-steel-kenvue-filing-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BBQKD6YLBLLPM6ETCCN7RTNF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:12:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税冲击迫在眉睫，日本经济出现萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，日本经济在 3 月份出现了一年来的首次萎缩，这凸显了日本经济复苏的脆弱性质，目前正受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普贸易政策的威胁。【原文：Japan's economy shrank for the first time in a year in the March quarter, data showed on Friday, underscoring the fragile nature of its recovery now under threat from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-economy-shrinks-us-tariff-hit-looms-2025-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AITFYEREFNOOBNEJWQUILQJJMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>