<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:35:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:35:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Novo Nordisk sues Hims & Hers over patent infringement]]></title><description><![CDATA[Novo Nordisk said on Monday it has filed a lawsuit against U.S. telehealth company Hims & Hers for infringing on the Danish group's patents.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/novo-nordisk-sues-hims-hers-over-patent-infringement-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYV2UGC75ZP4VNQ3L763RTYBCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:08:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lilly to buy Orna Therapeutics for up to $2.4 billion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Eli Lilly will buy therapy developer Orna Therapeutics for up to $2.4 billion in cash, the companies said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/lilly-buy-orna-therapeutics-up-24-billion-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3UZVZPEBBMDFJ5YHOOZBWF3IY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:06:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Morning Bid: Tokyo takes off]]></title><description><![CDATA[What matters in U.S. and global markets today]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3G5OLOMNYZLT3FT5DREHKBXHEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Freedom Holding considers HK share offering as part of growth plans, CEO says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Freedom Holding , a Kazakhstan-based financial services company, is considering a secondary public offering of shares in Hong Kong to help fund expansion plans, its CEO Timur Turlov told Reuters.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/freedom-holding-considers-hk-share-offering-part-growth-plans-ceo-says-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76B6SX3D4JJQZON63DI6CTUKAI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apollo's fourth-quarter profit rises on strong inflows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Apollo Global Management reported a 13% rise in fourth-quarter profit on Monday, buoyed by inflows of fresh client money and strong debt origination.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apollos-fourth-quarter-profit-rises-strong-inflows-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVK3TZDFPVLJXEHFB7CWCC4C34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:31:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Imec opens 2.5 bln euros chip pilot line as Europe looks to strengthen AI hand]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲周一在加强其在全球芯片竞赛中的地位方面迈出重要一步。比利时研究机构imec启动了耗资25亿欧元（约合29.5亿美元）的"NanoIC"试点生产线，该项目旨在根据欧盟《芯片法案》开发超先进半导体。【原文：Europe took a step to strengthen its hand in the global chip race on Monday as Belgian research firm imec opened "NanoIC", a 2.5 billion euros ($2.95 billion) pilot line aimed at developing ultra-advanced semiconductors under the EU's Chips Act.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imec-opens-25-bln-euros-chip-pilot-line-europe-looks-strengthen-ai-hand-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4P4XWH22VRKGHAB24FFXHTUNEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Symrise称美国司法部终止反垄断调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[西玛瑞斯公司周一表示，美国司法部对其在美国反垄断诉讼中的调查已撤销。【原文：Symrise AG said on Monday that investigations against it in U.S. antitrust proceedings by the Department of Justice have been dropped.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/symrise-says-us-department-justice-drops-antitrust-probe-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYHXFO4MHRJ4TFD2RJL2O743FI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛杉矶首例Instagram与YouTube成瘾诉讼案开庭审理]]></title><description><![CDATA[加州州法院周一开庭审理一起诉讼，该案聚焦Instagram和YouTube是否通过令人上瘾的应用设计损害了一名女性的精神健康。此案将检验科技巨头平台是否应为伤害儿童的行为承担法律责任。【原文：A California state court case over whether Instagram and YouTube harmed a woman's mental health through addictive app design kicks off on Monday with opening statements, in a test of whether Big Tech platforms can be held liable for harming kids.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/instagram-youtube-addiction-trial-kicks-off-los-angeles-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULYQU5EPXNO6XMM354H4D7MZ7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国软件股暴跌引发担忧：人工智能交易正在重塑市场格局]]></title><description><![CDATA[软件与服务行业的近期暴跌引发担忧，人们担心人工智能热潮可能正以意想不到的方式重塑市场格局，这不禁让人质疑：科技股的轮换是否预示着人工智能交易领域即将面临困境。【原文：The software and services industry's recent plunge has ignited fears that the artificial intelligence boom may be reshaping markets in unexpected ways, raising questions about whether a rotation out of technology stocks signals trouble ahead for the AI trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-software-stocks-tumble-sparks-concerns-that-ai-trade-is-reshaping-markets-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MH5AVF2F7ZOZ3CJRLHX6A3YKDA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格股价上涨，因有报道称前沃尔玛高管将出任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shares of Kroger rose about 6% in premarket trading on Monday after a Wall Street Journal report said the grocery chain has picked former Walmart executive Greg Foran as its CEO, a year after the ouster of Rodney McMullen.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/kroger-shares-rise-after-report-ex-walmart-executive-become-ceo-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PG22A4Y7T5IFHPOOEJEYYM2PNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货走势平淡，市场静候关键经济数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，华尔街期货走势趋稳。此前一周，受人工智能担忧拖累科技股下跌，市场整体承压。投资者正等待关键经济数据，同时关注美国央行对潜在降息的信号。【原文：Wall Street futures steadied on Monday, after a week marred by tech stock declines amid AI concerns that dragged the market lower, as investors awaited crucial economic data as well as hints from the U.S. central bank on potential rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-muted-markets-await-key-economic-data-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IIFCQ5RE5NITO7OH7PPUP3KXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:28:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国1月集装箱进口量下降6.8%，但笛卡尔公司表示，这一结果表明贸易正趋于正常化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. seaports in January handled 6.8% less container import volume than the year-ago month, when U.S. companies rushed in goods to front-run President Donald Trump's tariffs and sent imports soaring to a record high for the month, supply chain technology provider Descartes Systems Group said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-container-imports-fell-68-january-result-points-more-normalized-trade-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4L2W3ST3ARPKJIGGXHLW7UDSLA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度古吉拉特邦与马斯克的星链公司签署协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度古吉拉特邦周一宣布，已与埃隆·马斯克的星链公司签署意向书，将在该邦西部偏远及服务不足地区提供基于卫星的高速互联网接入服务。【原文：India's Gujarat state said on Monday that it had signed a letter of intent with Elon Musk's Starlink to provide high-speed, satellite-based internet connectivity across remote and underserved regions of the western state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-gujarat-state-signs-agreement-with-musks-starlink-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNGLYLAY2ZMOPEDGCXYWTQHIXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta批评欧盟针对WhatsApp封杀人工智能竞争对手的反垄断举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms周一抨击欧盟监管机构，此前欧盟指控这家美国科技巨头违反反垄断法规，并威胁要解除其在即时通讯服务WhatsApp上对人工智能竞争对手的封锁。【原文：Meta Platforms on Monday criticised EU regulators after they charged the U.S. tech giant with breaching antitrust rules and threaten to halt its block on AI rivals on its messaging service WhatsApp.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-criticises-eu-antitrust-move-against-whatsapp-block-ai-rivals-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ6TWVEMU5JFDHSF25GY6FZZZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:18:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，随着并购交易复苏，2026年美国IPO募资额将激增至创纪录的1600亿美元，增幅达四倍。]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛分析师表示，美国股市将在2026年迎来首次公开募股（IPO）的强劲反弹，预计募资规模将翻四倍至创纪录的1600亿美元，因为SpaceX、OpenAI和Anthropic等知名企业正逐步接近公开上市。【原文：U.S. equity markets are set for a sharp rebound in IPOs in 2026, Goldman Sachs analysts said, forecasting proceeds quadrupling to a record $160 billion as marquee names such as SpaceX, OpenAI and Anthropic edge closer to public listings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-ipo-proceeds-quadruple-record-160-billion-2026-dealmaking-rebounds-says-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJC7H6CVWVMWPMJKQIYZOALH6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:18:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟威胁对Meta采取临时措施，因其封锁WhatsApp上的AI竞争对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟竞争监管机构周一指控Meta Platforms违反反垄断法规，通过封锁其即时通讯服务WhatsApp中的人工智能竞争对手，并威胁将对这家美国科技巨头采取临时措施。【原文：EU competition regulators on Monday charged Meta Platforms with breaching antitrust rules by blocking artificial intelligence rivals from its messaging service WhatsApp and threatened to impose interim measures against the U.S. tech giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eu-threatens-meta-with-interim-measure-blocking-ai-rivals-whatsapp-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BCWK6RTDTRP2JEBIQ353ERVK2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:04:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[渣打银行任命前瑞银银行家拉扎·贾弗里为全球私人客户销售主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周一宣布任命拉扎·贾弗里为全球私人客户销售主管，该行正推动企业与投资银行部门与财富管理业务部门建立新合作关系，以服务单一家族办公室及超高净值客户。【原文：Standard Chartered said on Monday it had appointed Raza Jafree as global head of private client sales, as it sets up a new partnership between its corporate and investment bank and wealth unit to serve single-family offices and ultra-high net worth clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/standard-chartered-appoints-ex-ubs-banker-raza-jafree-global-head-private-client-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTZIBUQRWRKONEPGC6TIPSMDFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:33:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道达尔能源将为谷歌得克萨斯州数据中心提供太阳能电力]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国石油巨头道达尔能源公司周一签署两项长期协议，将为谷歌位于得克萨斯州的数据中心供应太阳能电力，此举旨在满足人工智能驱动的电力需求增长。【原文：French oil major TotalEnergies on Monday signed two long-term deals to supply solar power to Google’s data centres in Texas, as it looks to tap rising electricity demand driven by artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/totalenergies-provide-solar-power-googles-texas-data-centres-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHKIKRGEU5PMNOMJEYGML5X5XE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:31:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德股价上涨，因Hims放弃售价49美元的减肥药]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德在法兰克福上市的股票周一上涨4.5%，此前远程医疗公司Hims & Hers在周末撤回了其49美元复合减肥药的上市计划，该计划因诺和诺德和美国食品药品监督管理局的法律威胁而受阻。【原文：Novo Nordisk's Frankfurt-listed shares rose 4.5% on Monday after telehealth firm Hims & Hers reversed its launch of a $49 compounded weight-loss pill over the weekend, following legal threats from Novo and the U.S. Food and Drug Administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novo-nordisk-shares-rise-hims-abandons-49-weight-loss-pill-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z7CANYB7NRKKJBSQ2E35OXB6KM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:45:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴超负荷运转的AI聊天机器人暂停发放优惠券，请求消费者耐心等待]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴旗下人工智能聊天机器人Qwen因用户量过载，已暂停发放优惠券服务，这阻碍了其推广新功能的计划——该功能旨在突破单纯答疑的局限，进一步提升购物辅助能力。【原文：Alibaba's artificial intelligence chatbot Qwen has temporarily stopped issuing coupons due to customer overload, hampering a new campaign to promote the tool's capabilities beyond simply answering questions to assist shopping.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alibabas-overloaded-ai-chatbot-stops-issuing-coupons-asks-shoppers-patience-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JERHSRBKORNV5AK6525BJPLGFY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国吸尘器制造商Dreame通过超级碗广告宣传其计划中的电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国机器人吸尘器制造商 Dreame Technology 雄心勃勃地计划打造电动超跑，其在超级碗期间投放的30秒广告展示了即将推出的电动豪华轿车。【原文：Dreame Technology, a Chinese maker of robot vacuum cleaners with an audacious goal to build electric supercars, ran a 30-second Super Bowl commercial showcasing its planned electric luxury car.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-vacuum-maker-dreame-pushes-its-planned-ev-with-super-bowl-ad-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTNO4JUURZMULO6BKYWOEQUGIY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:27:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国机器人制造商蓄势待发，准备在春节娱乐活动中大放异彩]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国，人形机器人正作为春节娱乐项目亮相，其制造商向公众、潜在客户、投资者及政府官员展示了它们的歌舞才艺。【原文：In China, humanoid robots are serving as Lunar New Year entertainment, with their manufacturers pitching their song-and-dance skills to the general public as well as potential customers, investors and government officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinese-robot-makers-ready-lunar-new-year-entertainment-spotlight-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M36T5ONNN5JODJPVO4JH52ASKU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:47:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[裕信银行上调盈利预期，因收购竞争对手股权及税收抵免助力2025年收入增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利第二大银行裕信银行表示，今年目标将利润提升至110亿欧元（约合130亿美元）。此前该行2025年盈利已超出分析师预期，这得益于首席执行官安德烈亚·奥尔塞尔扩张战略下收购竞争对手股权带来的收益增长。【原文：Italy's second-largest bank UniCredit said it aimed to lift its profit to 11 billion euros ($13 billion) this year, after topping analysts' forecasts for 2025 with earnings boosted by stakes in rivals bought under CEO Andrea Orcel's expansion strategy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-hikes-profit-outlook-after-stakes-rival-tax-credits-help-2025-income-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCDWC3SWKFLVBBXBLVQPSIKJ54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Advent与联邦快递牵头的财团以92亿美元收购包裹柜公司InPost]]></title><description><![CDATA[由控股公司Advent和联邦快递牵头的财团已同意以每股15.60欧元的价格收购InPost，该包裹柜公司估值达78亿欧元（约合92亿美元）。相关企业周一宣布，此举旨在进一步扩大其在欧洲的业务覆盖范围。【原文：A consortium led by holding firm Advent and FedEx has agreed to buy InPost for 15.60 euros per share, valuing the parcel locker company at 7.8 billion euros ($9.2 billion) and aiming to further expand its reach across Europe, the companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/advent-fedex-led-consortium-buy-parcel-locker-company-inpost-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZSIW7P2NP5LPLESF4QVUUAMESQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:19:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国监管机构称400亿美元赠款事件表明需制定新规应对加密货币风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国金融市场监管机构负责人周一表示，当地交易所Bithumb无意中向客户赠送价值逾400亿美元的比特币，这凸显出亟需完善监管以应对加密货币的脆弱性。【原文：The chief of South Korea's financial market watchdog said on Monday local exchange Bithumb's unintentional giveaway of more than $40 billion worth of bitcoins to customers raises the need for improved regulations to address the vulnerabilities of cryptocurrencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/south-korea-watchdog-says-40-billion-giveaway-shows-new-rules-needed-tackle-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEKCMJO2I5KGXJSF6ZDQ4FEARQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡称网络间谍组织瞄准电信基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡网络安全局周一表示，该国四家电信公司——新电通、星和、M1和Simba电信——去年遭到网络间谍组织UNC3886的攻击。【原文：Singapore's four telecom companies, Singtel , StarHub , M1 and Simba Telecom , were targeted by cyber espionage group UNC3886 in attacks last year, Singapore's Cyber Security Agency said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/singapore-says-cyber-espionage-group-targeted-telco-infrastructure-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAL4FYHIOVJIJHX5QUSSAUG3N4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早盘竞价：日本市场欢迎首相长期留任的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩·科尔为您解析欧洲及全球市场今日展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBO2MSMLGVPCJPGH3772NEI7ZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓高管称，旗下Vicuña项目或将投资额翻倍，2026年阿根廷铜矿项目投资达8亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在安第斯山脉海拔4200多米的高处，阿根廷与智利边境线上，矿业公司Vicuña Corp.的一位高管表示，该公司计划在今年将投资额翻倍，押注全球最大的铜矿项目之一。【原文：High in the Andes Mountains, more than 4,200 meters above sea level on the Argentina–Chile border, mining company Vicuña Corp. aims to double its investment this year in one of the world’s biggest copper bets, a company executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bhps-vicua-could-double-investment-argentina-copper-project-800-mln-2026-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRRLXWVKBFMQ3J6VIQXJWJAF6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本表示企业可拒绝非邀约收购要约以应对收购风险担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本产业省官员向路透社表示，日本企业即使收到大幅溢价收购要约，也无义务接受未经请求的收购要约。此番表态正值市场日益担忧激进投资者和外国收购方瞄准日本龙头企业之际。【原文：Japanese companies are not obliged to accept unsolicited takeover bids even when offered large premiums, an industry ministry official told Reuters, amid growing concern about the targeting of leading firms by activist investors and foreign acquirers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/japan-says-companies-can-rebuff-unsolicited-bids-amid-takeover-risk-concerns-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYCPSD7DVBIJNACFUGB4DEH5DA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾称40%芯片产能转移至美国"不可能"]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾首席关税谈判代表表示，将台湾40%的半导体产能转移至美国"不可能实现"，此言是对近期美国官员呼吁大规模转移生产所作回应。【原文：It would be "impossible" to move 40% of Taiwan's semiconductor capacity to the U.S., the island's top tariff negotiator said, pushing back against recent comments by American officials who called for a major production shift.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-says-40-shift-chip-capacity-us-is-impossible-2026-02-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JBQOO55ORNC5KIHC6LDQADN6M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>