<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:38:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:38:34 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[阿布拉航空集团将提交美国 IPO 注册声明草案]]></title><description><![CDATA[控制着巴西戈尔航空公司（Gol）和哥伦比亚阿维安卡航空公司（Avianca）的阿布拉集团（Abra Group）周三表示，打算秘密提交一份拟在美国首次公开发行股票的注册声明草案。【原文：Abra Group, which controls Brazilian airline Gol and Colombia's Avianca, intends to confidentially submit a draft registration statement for a proposed initial public offering in the United States, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/airline-group-abra-submit-draft-registration-statement-us-ipo-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBFAMLG7MNL7LGD4Y7J4TWS2KY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:26:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受高端旅行需求拉动，美国联合航空公司预计第四季度利润强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周三预测，由于高端旅行需求强劲和定价能力提高，第四季度利润将高于预期。【原文：United Airlines on Wednesday forecast a higher-than-expected profit in the fourth quarter on the back of robust demand for premium travel and improved pricing power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/united-airlines-predicts-strong-q4-profit-driven-by-premium-travel-demand-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QU7KVY6M75IWHLGIAU5ZLDCB6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国合众银行为数字资产和资金流动成立专门部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国合众银行（U.S. Bancorp）周三表示，该公司已成立了一个专注于数字资产和资金流动的新部门，以加快发展并增加新兴数字产品和服务的收入。【原文：U.S. Bancorp said on Wednesday it had formed a new unit focused on digital assets and money movement to speed up development as well as grow the revenue from emerging digital products and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bancorp-forms-dedicated-unit-digital-assets-money-movement-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXUA6BJDL5JSFDASDVVY7QHNDA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空集团以航空风险为由敦促政府结束关门]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家航空公司贸易集团的负责人敦促政府结束为期 15 天的停摆，理由是他担心停薪留职的空中交通管制员面临越来越大的压力。【原文：The head of a U.S. airline trade group urged an end to the 15-day government shutdown, citing concerns about rising pressure faced by air traffic controllers who are working without pay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-airline-group-urges-end-government-shutdown-citing-aviation-risks-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SLO6KRB7FPFLFYJSSSG764OW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约梅隆银行因涉嫌与杰弗里-爱泼斯坦有财务关系而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名自称受到已故金融家和性犯罪者杰弗里-爱泼斯坦虐待的妇女周三起诉纽约梅隆银行，指控该银行向他的性交易受害者支付了 3.78 亿美元。【原文：A woman who says she was abused by the late financier and sex offender Jeffrey Epstein sued Bank of New York Mellon on Wednesday, alleging the bank processed $378 million in payments to victims of his sex trafficking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bny-mellon-sued-over-alleged-financial-ties-jeffrey-epstein-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFPOIZJD6NK6TH6PYF6FXBWA44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥国家石油公司与强大的工会达成加薪 4.5% 的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥国家能源公司 Pemex 周三表示，作为修订 2025-2027 年集体谈判协议的一部分，该公司已与强大的 STPRM 石油工人工会就加薪 4.5% 达成一致。【原文：Mexican state energy company Pemex said on Wednesday it had agreed with the powerful STPRM oil workers union on a 4.5% salary increase as part of the revision of the 2025-2027 collective bargaining agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/mexicos-pemex-powerful-union-agree-45-pay-increase-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZSLCVU2XOJNMBENSXMMGRS6JOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国监管机构准备为社区银行提供资本减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道称，美国监管机构将发布一项计划，通过放宽一系列资本要求来鼓励小型银行增加贷款。【原文：US regulators are set to release a plan to encourage small banks to lend more by easing a set of capital requirements, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/us-regulators-poised-offer-capital-relief-community-banks-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4NTUBVYBJMJVKLSZFXWED7WLQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:55:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通和高盛留在中国，但业务有所转移]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）和高盛（Goldman Sachs）银行高管周三表示，随着与美国的紧张关系升级，全球市场笼罩在紧张气氛中，摩根大通和高盛将坚持在中国开展业务。【原文：JPMorgan Chase and Goldman Sachs are sticking with their businesses in China as escalating tensions with the U.S. loom over global markets, bank executives said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-goldman-sachs-stay-china-businesses-shift-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VZNCKZ2ZBKZBDKLCHDXKR3MD4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:35:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储称最近几周美国经济活动变化不大，就业稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三表示，最近几周美国经济活动变化不大，就业基本稳定，尽管有更多企业报告称裁员，这加剧了人们对劳动力市场疲软的担忧。【原文：U.S. economic activity was little changed and employment was largely stable in recent weeks even as more businesses reported headcount reductions, the Federal Reserve said on Wednesday, reinforcing concerns about labor market softening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-economic-activity-little-changed-employment-stable-recent-weeks-fed-says-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2T2STKMWTJJKTJSIF634PFQ4LM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行因涉嫌与杰弗里-爱泼斯坦有经济往来而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名自称受到已故金融家和性犯罪者杰弗里-爱泼斯坦（Jeffrey Epstein）虐待的妇女周三起诉美国银行，称该银行在知情的情况下提供金融服务，使其多年来的性交易活动得以进行。【原文：A woman who says she was abused by the late financier and sex offender Jeffrey Epstein sued Bank of America on Wednesday, alleging the bank knowingly provided financial services that enabled his sex trafficking operation for years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-sued-over-alleged-financial-ties-jeffrey-epstein-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4MXUSAKJNL2HK2NZYZOQC75TQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Volatility Shares 申请美国首个潜在 5 倍杠杆 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[Volatility Shares 是一家交易所交易基金发行商，该公司周三申请推出总共 27 种高杠杆 ETF，其中包括首次提议在美国市场推出的 5 倍杠杆 ETF。【原文：Volatility Shares, an issuer of exchange-traded funds, filed on Wednesday to launch a total of 27 highly leveraged ETFs, including the first-ever proposed 5x ETF for the U.S. market, at a time of rising caution over inflated asset prices as markets continue their upward swing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/volatility-shares-files-first-ever-potential-5x-leveraged-etf-us-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UH3DZJDUYJORDFYTDADZ7E5AH4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街顶级银行强调消费者的适应力]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街最大的银行在第三季度财报中强调了美国消费者的韧性，并补充说，尽管利率上升和经济存在不确定性，但迄今为止信贷并未出现裂痕。【原文：Wall Street's biggest banks kicked off third-quarter earnings by highlighting the resilience of U.S. consumers and added that credit has shown no cracks so far despite higher rates and economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-top-banks-highlight-consumer-resilience-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHWXRKWPUFLZZPQFEUEAMIQE3A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:04:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫预算主管计划在数月内关闭美国消费者金融监督机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫预算主任拉塞尔-沃尔特（Russell Vought）周三表示，他希望关闭美国消费者金融保护局，并预计在未来两三个月内关闭该机构。【原文：White House budget director Russell Vought said on Wednesday he wants to close the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau and expects to do so within the next two to three months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/white-house-budget-director-vought-says-over-10000-federal-workers-could-be-laid-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCDV5B32IZJFNFOR4QPGUVERQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:59:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主经纪业务蓬勃发展为华尔街银行带来第三季度巨额暴利]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街价值数十亿美元的大宗经纪业务正在全面启动。【原文：Wall Street's multibillion-dollar prime brokerage machinery is firing on all cylinders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/prime-brokerage-boom-generates-big-third-quarter-windfall-wall-street-banks-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZI7WZZBAIFOT7JZ22FTEW5BLHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:38:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vantage 数据中心投资 3.5 亿欧元建设第二个意大利站点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国数字基础设施供应商 Vantage Data Centers 周三表示，将投资超过 3.5 亿欧元（4.07 亿美元）在意大利建设第二个园区。【原文：Vantage Data Centers will invest more than 350 million euros ($407 million) to build a second campus in Italy, the U.S.-based digital infrastructure provider said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/vantage-data-centers-invests-350-million-euros-second-italy-site-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AM3B2IUUABLPTDNYVHRJQLUBTU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行只有在确信不存在威胁时才会取消计划中的稳定币上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[英格兰银行只有在确信稳定币不会对金融稳定构成威胁时，才会取消对个人和企业持有稳定币数量的限制。【原文：The Bank of England will only remove proposed caps on the quantity of stablecoins individuals and businesses can hold when it is confident they do not pose a threat to financial stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/boe-will-only-lift-planned-stablecoin-cap-when-confident-no-threat-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMHW34FQBVM7LKWI3ZKHBRGHDM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[竞争对手称将驳回申诉，微软将避免法国反垄断调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国搜索引擎竞争对手 Qwant 周三表示，由于监管机构计划驳回 Qwant 的投诉，美国科技巨头微软有望避免法国对其搜索业务的反垄断调查。【原文：U.S. tech giant Microsoft looks set to avoid a French antitrust investigation into its search operations because regulators are planning to dismiss a complaint by Qwant, the French rival search engine said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/microsoft-avoid-french-antitrust-investigation-rival-says-its-complaint-will-be-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYLIBI4WFJIXJJPJMZC2KWRCHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国科技初创公司 Anthropic 推出更便宜的模型，以扩大人工智能的吸引力]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Anthropic对其最小的人工智能模型 "Haiku "进行了全面改造，因为越来越多的公司开始选择人工智能系统，这些系统的能力几乎不亚于最先进的工具，但成本却很低。【原文：Artificial intelligence startup Anthropic has overhauled its smallest AI model, Haiku, as companies increasingly opt for AI systems that are nearly as capable as the most advanced tools – but come at a fraction of the cost.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-tech-startup-anthropic-unveils-cheaper-model-widen-ais-appeal-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ26X36QMVKBBIFRU4FKZEWXQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，Anthropic 的目标是在 2026 年将年化收入提高近三倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，人工智能初创公司Anthropic预计明年的年化营收将增长一倍多，甚至可能增长近两倍。【原文：Artificial intelligence startup Anthropic is projecting to more than double and potentially nearly triple its annualized revenue run rate next year, fueled by the rapid adoption of its enterprise products, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/anthropic-aims-nearly-triple-annualized-revenue-2026-sources-say-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXGDK4KSWJLUZJT2RGHHKR32BA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特说，如果日本央行采取 "适当 "政策，日元将找到自己的水平线]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，如果日本央行遵循 "适当的货币政策"，日元将找到自己的汇率水平。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday the yen will find its own level if the Bank of Japan follows "proper monetary policy."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bessent-says-yen-will-find-its-own-level-if-bank-japan-follows-proper-policy-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XF76NCBY5FKYJCWKUJ455B6S3M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:52:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HPE 140 亿美元收购瞻博网络可能面临国家挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一些州表示，他们可能会寻求阻止惠普企业以 140 亿美元收购瞻博网络，并已请求法官允许他们介入美国司法部提议和解并允许交易继续进行的案件。【原文：A group of U.S. states said they may seek to block Hewlett-Packard Enterprise's $14 billion acquisition of Juniper Networks and have asked a judge for permission to intervene in a case where the U.S. Department of Justice has proposed to settle and let the deal move forward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hpes-14-billion-juniper-acquisition-could-face-state-challenge-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIQVTOQUMFNR5LY3GJ3K7JM6LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 成立部门，引导退休储蓄用于私人投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[领先的资产管理公司 Blackstone 周三表示，已成立一个部门，将全球更多的退休基金引入私募市场投资，仅在美国就可能有数十亿美元的机会。【原文：Leading asset manager Blackstone has launched a unit to channel more retirement funds globally into private market investments, a potentially multi-trillion-dollar opportunity in the United States alone, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/blackstone-launches-unit-channel-retirement-savings-private-investments-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RH4UCMCQZZMBLB32EMQPJ66MGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示美国将购买更多阿根廷比索，并正在筹划 200 亿美元的债务机制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三告诉记者，美国再次在公开市场上购买阿根廷比索，并补充说，美国财政部正在与私营部门投资基金合作，建立一个 200 亿美元的基金，用于投资阿根廷的主权债务。【原文：The U.S. again purchased Argentine pesos in the open market on Wednesday, Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told reporters, adding that the department was working with private sector investment funds to create a $20 billion facility to invest in Argentina's sovereign debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bessent-says-us-buys-more-argentine-pesos-working-20-billion-debt-facility-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZMVJ7VWPBM4XFIVP7ATQ6VBEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席米兰对CNBC表示，中美贸易紧张局势对经济增长前景构成新风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周三表示，美中贸易紧张局势再起给经济前景带来了新的下行风险，这使得美国央行下调基准利率变得更加重要。【原文：Renewed U.S.-China trade tensions pose new downside risks to the economic outlook, making it more important that the U.S. central bank cut its benchmark interest rate, Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-trade-tensions-pose-new-risk-growth-outlook-feds-miran-tells-cnbc-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SQAPZ3ASKNKO5NS4AVGRKQMDOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，沃尔玛美国首席执行官称，购物者仍在以健康的速度消费]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三报道，沃尔玛美国负责人表示，尽管经济存在不确定性，且美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税导致价格上涨，但购物者仍在以健康的速度消费，且具有很强的抵御能力。【原文：Walmart's U.S. head said shoppers were spending at a healthy rate and were resilient despite economic uncertainty and inflationary prices due to President Donald Trump's tariffs, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-us-ceo-says-shoppers-still-spending-healthy-rate-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVTF4C3LCJPPDBTMXY6WLYFXDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:08:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 借助 Arm Holdings 在 Facebook 和 Instagram 上进行人工智能推荐]]></title><description><![CDATA[各家公司正急于升级其服务所依赖的芯片技术。【原文：Companies are rushing to upgrade the chip technology underpinning their services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/meta-taps-arm-holdings-power-ai-recommendations-across-facebook-instagram-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K733BORZKNPF3KWLA3QUPQSAYM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 承诺出资 15 亿美元在得克萨斯州建设人工智能数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体巨头 Meta Platforms 周三表示，将投资 15 亿美元在德克萨斯州建造一个数据中心，这是该公司在全球破土动工的第 29 个数据中心，该公司将扩大基础设施，以支持人工智能工作负载。【原文：Meta Platforms said on Wednesday it would invest $1.5 billion in a data center in Texas, breaking ground at its 29th such facility globally, as the social media giant expands infrastructure to support artificial intelligence workloads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-commits-15-billion-ai-data-center-texas-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYZL4NZNLZNLLGRKR476GRKTPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员抨击中国在稀土问题上的行为，敦促中国政府让步]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国高级官员周三抨击中国大幅扩大稀土出口管制对全球供应链构成威胁，但表示中国政府仍有可能改变路线，避免华盛顿采取与世界第二大经济体脱钩的措施。【原文：Top U.S. officials on Wednesday blasted China's major expansion of rare earth export controls as a threat to global supply chains, but said Beijing could still change course and avoid steps by Washington to decouple from the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-officials-blast-chinas-actions-rare-earths-urge-beijing-back-down-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPTRNM4Y4NI2XLL6KP3LXJTZTY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西将于周四与美国商讨关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦周三表示，巴西和美国将于周四举行关税谈判会谈。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Wednesday that Brazil and the U.S. will hold negotiation talks on tariffs on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/brazil-us-hold-tariff-talks-thursday-says-lula-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTHIRMDY6RPCPNPI3BA3IARKWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:31:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官将批准力拓 1.3875 亿美元的蒙古矿山和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官周三表示，他已准备好批准力拓集团（Rio Tinto）支付 1.3875 亿美元的和解协议，该诉讼指控这家英澳矿业巨头在蒙古奥尤陶勒盖（Oyu Tolgoi）铜金矿耗资 70 亿美元的地下扩建工程中隐瞒问题，欺骗投资者。【原文：A U.S. judge on Wednesday said he was ready to approve Rio Tinto's , agreement to pay $138.75 million to settle a lawsuit that accused the Anglo-Australian mining giant of defrauding investors by concealing problems with its $7 billion underground expansion of the Oyu Tolgoi copper and gold mine in Mongolia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-judge-set-approve-rio-tintos-13875-million-mongolia-mine-settlement-2025-10-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FEGWYFUZXVOJ3AR34K4GW5RVUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:28:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>