<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:04:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:04:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[《The Information》报道称，安杜瑞尔公司正就新融资进行讨论，公司估值已突破600亿美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《信息》周五报道，知情人士透露，美国国防公司安杜瑞尔正就以至少600亿美元估值筹集数十亿美元新资金进行谈判。【原文：U.S. defense firm Anduril is in talks to raise billions in new funding at a valuation of at least $60 billion, The Information reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/anduril-discusses-new-funding-60-billion-plus-valuation-information-reports-2026-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFU5IGLADVIMRNGQG3DWXQ5ANU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 01:19:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府发布《海事行动计划》旨在重振美国造船业]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周五公布了重建美国造船业及其他海事产业的计划，部分资金将来自对中国制造船舶运抵美国的货物征收港口费——这项税费已被中美双方同意暂停一年。【原文：The Trump administration on Friday released its plan to rebuild U.S. shipbuilding and other maritime businesses, paid for in part by port fees on cargo delivered to the United States on ships made in China - levies the U.S. and China agreed to pause for one year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-releases-maritime-action-plan-aimed-resurrecting-us-2026-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVN3H2YDV5N4XDROMM6SVVOVFM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA["Swift Home"商标遭弃用，因泰勒·斯威夫特提出异议]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家申请联邦"Swift Home"商标的床上用品公司，在流行歌手泰勒·斯威夫特施压后已放弃申请。该公司律师周五向路透社透露了这一消息。【原文：A bedding company that applied for a federal "Swift Home" trademark has abandoned its application following pressure from pop star Taylor Swift, an attorney for the company told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/swift-home-trademark-abandoned-after-taylor-swift-opposition-2026-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHI2FW5TORLQLLJQE5BYVKZ5FQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:22:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加强石油封锁，古巴人转向电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[1959年款雪佛兰汽车的轰鸣声，曾是哈瓦那有节奏的心跳，如今随着古巴遭遇多年来最严重的燃油短缺，正逐渐消逝在电动汽车的近乎寂静中。【原文：The rumble of 1959 Chevrolets, once the rhythmic heartbeat of Havana, is fading to the near silence of electric vehicles as the island faces its worst fuel shortage in years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/cubans-turn-electric-vehicles-us-tightens-oil-blockade-2026-02-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZZWP5XHL5OF5AQEGOEBIHHHQM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，美国在突袭委内瑞拉行动中使用了Anthropic公司的Claude系统。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，知情人士透露，美国军方在抓捕委内瑞拉前总统尼古拉斯·马杜罗的行动中使用了Anthropic公司的人工智能模型Claude。【原文：Anthropic's artificial-intelligence model Claude was used in the U.S. military's operation to capture former Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-used-anthropics-claude-during-the-venezuela-raid-wsj-reports-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVNC5GC4XRM5JCQZIZTZ4MN3IM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:42:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称美国炼油商瓦莱罗3月将进口多达650万桶委内瑞拉原油]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士周五透露，瓦莱罗能源公司计划在3月采购最多650万桶委内瑞拉原油运往其墨西哥湾沿岸炼油厂，这使其成为自1月美国逮捕尼古拉斯·马杜罗总统以来，该欧佩克国家原油的最大海外炼油商。【原文：Valero Energy is set to buy up to 6.5 million barrels of Venezuelan crude in March bound for its Gulf Coast refineries, making it the top foreign refiner of the OPEC country's oil since the United States captured President Nicolas Maduro in January, sources said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refiner-valero-import-up-65-million-barrels-venezuelan-crude-in-march-sources-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3O5236N7VLIRFASUCPWRF4DNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司第四季度遭遇激进投资者萨切姆·海德增持股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司上周五提交的监管文件显示，这家媒体娱乐巨头在第四季度同意将其流媒体和影视制作业务出售给奈飞公司，此举引起了激进投资者萨切姆海德资本管理公司的关注。【原文：Warner Bros. Discovery attracted the attention of activist investor Sachem Head Capital Management in the fourth quarter when the media and entertainment giant agreed to sell its streaming and studios business to Netflix, according to a regulatory filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/warner-bros-discovery-sees-activist-sachem-head-increase-stake-q4-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2AATH7M7JLVFILF2MYOY4MS6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:12:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院民主党人要求CFIUS调查阿联酋在特朗普家族加密货币公司持股的报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院银行委员会两名民主党成员周五致函财政部长斯科特·贝森特，要求其调查阿联酋国家安全顾问收购特朗普家族加密货币企业5亿美元股权一事可能引发的国家安全问题。【原文：Two Democratic members of the U.S. Senate Banking Committee on Friday asked Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent to examine the potential national security implications of a reported purchase of a $500 million stake in the Trump family’s cryptocurrency venture by the United Arab Emirates' national security adviser.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/senate-democrats-seek-cfius-probe-reported-uae-stake-trump-familys-crypto-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4YCRFMTKNLMJAPNEYA3IQXTRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局称，美国航空公司必须证明其采用基于实绩的飞行员招聘制度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局周五表示，所有美国航空公司必须证明其飞行员招聘基于能力，否则将面临联邦调查。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said on Friday that all U.S. airlines must certify they are conducting merit-based hiring for pilots or face a federal investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-airlines-must-certify-use-merit-based-hiring-pilots-faa-says-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKOKPJZFBNLBXJQPENUNLM2L5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙任命前特朗普政府官员为公共政策副总裁，正值华纳兄弟收购案之际]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的公司备忘录显示，派拉蒙天空舞影业已任命特朗普政府前任律师雷内·奥古斯丁担任全球公共政策高级副总裁。此举正值华纳兄弟探索公司收购战持续进行之际。【原文：Paramount Skydance has named Rene Augustine, a former Trump administration attorney, as its senior vice president of global public policy, according to a company memo seen by Reuters, amid an ongoing takeover battle for Warner Bros Discovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-taps-ex-trump-official-public-policy-vp-amid-warner-bros-bid-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B45Y3YRJ6BOZVKALVSDFL6DEPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行首席执行官布莱恩·莫尼汉薪酬升至4100万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周五宣布，已批准首席执行官布莱恩·莫尼汉2025年总薪酬为4100万美元，较去年增长逾17.1%。【原文：Bank of America said on Friday it had approved $41 million for CEO Brian Moynihan's total compensation for 2025, reflecting a more than 17.1% rise from last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/bofa-ceo-brian-moynihans-pay-rises-41-million-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32V5EG4KFNOUNN7JTHGBCIU56M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，劳氏公司裁减600个企业及支持岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，劳氏公司正裁撤约600个企业及支持岗位，占这家北卡罗来纳州零售商总员工数的不到1%。【原文：Lowe's is eliminating about 600 corporate and support roles, representing less than 1% of the North Carolina-based retailer's total workforce, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lowes-cuts-600-corporate-support-roles-wsj-reports-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RESK6KBO5VKUNLJY36U3PFQIY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:55:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，马斯克旗下AI聊天机器人Grok在美国市场份额激增，尽管其因发布性化图像引发争议]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据显示，过去数月间，埃隆·马斯克的人工智能聊天机器人Grok在美国市场持续扩张，尽管该系统因生成大量未经同意的女性及未成年人性化图像而引发全球谴责及监管审查。【原文：Grok, Elon Musk's AI chatbot, has been gaining ground in the U.S. over the past months, data showed, even as it draws global censure and regulatory scrutiny after being used to generate a wave of non-consensual sexualized images of women and minors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/musks-ai-chatbot-groks-us-market-share-jumps-amid-sexualized-images-backlash-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRFJWBLRMNKX5LQZYJXV5TG6TI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党人抨击特朗普搁置对华科技措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党议员抨击特朗普政府在中美领导人四月会晤前搁置针对北京的关键科技安全措施，称此举危及美国国家安全。【原文：Democratic lawmakers slammed the Trump administration for shelving key tech security measures aimed at Beijing ahead of an April meeting between the American and Chinese leaders, arguing the moves threaten U.S. national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/democrats-take-aim-trump-shelving-china-tech-measures-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKRMURVZPZL4DNGD5KPS6D5VLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗尔斯·罗伊斯发动机纠纷令美联航搁置的A350订单前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联航披露与发动机制造商罗尔斯罗伊斯存在纠纷后，为其长期延迟的空客A350订单注入了新的不确定性。这成为航空业持续时间最长的喷气式飞机采购风波中的最新转折。【原文：United Airlines has injected new uncertainty into its long-delayed Airbus A350 order after disclosing a dispute with engine maker Rolls-Royce , the latest twist in one of the industry's longest-running jet procurement sagas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/uniteds-stalled-a350-order-thrown-into-doubt-by-rolls-royce-engine-row-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5G6MIH6HJFK4ZHK7AE5SGI3CNI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:46:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宾夕法尼亚州陪审团裁定强生公司对滑石粉致癌案负有责任]]></title><description><![CDATA[据全国范围内针对强生公司滑石粉诉讼的原告律师称，宾夕法尼亚州法院陪审团周五裁定，强生公司需向一名女性的家人赔偿25万美元。该女子起诉强生公司，指控其含滑石粉的婴儿爽身粉是导致她患上卵巢癌的元凶。【原文：A jury in Pennsylvania state court on Friday awarded $250,000 to the family of a woman who sued Johnson & Johnson alleging its talc-based baby powder was to blame for her ovarian cancer, according to an attorney for plaintiffs in nationwide talc litigation against the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/pennsylvania-jury-finds-johnson-johnson-liable-cancer-latest-talc-trial-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTCP3N6YTBLMNMPIXRAXMRNHGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:43:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[字母债券缺乏保护措施凸显投资者信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌母公司Alphabet本周发行的全球债券凸显了投资者对主要人工智能超大规模企业的强烈需求，但同时也引发了对债券缺乏对现有及未来债券持有者保护措施的担忧。【原文：Alphabet Inc's global bond sale this week underscored the high level of investor demand for the major AI hyperscalers, but raised concerns about the debt's lack of protections for existing and future bondholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/alphabet-bonds-lack-guardrails-highlights-investor-confidence-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O24SNVTJ7VLBHCWWDXHZZOCE3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:34:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道称，SpaceX正考虑在首次公开募股中采用双重股权结构]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周五援引知情人士消息报道称，埃隆·马斯克旗下的SpaceX公司正考虑在今年计划中的首次公开募股（IPO）中采用双层股权结构。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX is considering a dual-class share structure in its planned IPO this year, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/spacex-considering-dual-class-shares-ipo-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3TWSA4DFJLWDBNSBN5U4L5G6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行监管机构正逐步推进针对大型银行的新版《巴塞尔协议》规则提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据本周公布的监管文件显示，美国银行监管机构似乎正逐步推进所谓"巴塞尔终局"规则的新版本提案，该规则将规定大型银行必须如何衡量其风险。【原文：U.S. bank regulators appear to be moving closer to proposing a new version of the so-called "Basel endgame" rules dictating how large banks must measure their risk, according to regulatory filings posted this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-bank-regulators-move-closer-proposing-new-basel-rules-large-banks-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNIWWXNP75PPZHM6TAFE675OHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司寻求运营美国至委内瑞拉航班的批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司周五向美国交通部提交文件称，该公司正寻求批准，计划通过其全资拥有的地区性航空公司Envoy，开通从迈阿密飞往委内瑞拉首都加拉加斯和马拉开波的美国境内航班。【原文：American Airlines said Friday it was seeking approval to operate U.S. flights to Caracas and Maracaibo in Venezuela from Miami through its wholly owned regional carrier Envoy, according to a filing with the U.S. Transportation Department.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/american-airlines-seeks-approval-operate-us-flights-venezeula-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMLHAKCV3FMPJBGVFQEU7OSUBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普环保署取消美国车企排放限值；各州法规及诉讼或将接踵而至]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统废除联邦气候监管基础的举措，将立即使汽车制造商摆脱昂贵的尾气排放标准束缚。但此举可能引发诉讼，并迫使企业面对各州及地区规则纷繁复杂的不确定未来。【原文：President Donald Trump's repeal of the foundation for federal climate regulation will immediately free automakers from costly tailpipe emissions standards, but the move could spark lawsuits and force businesses to navigate an uncertain future of multiple state and regional rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-epa-ends-emissions-limits-us-automakers-state-rules-lawsuits-could-follow-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWTZ47IHHNL77FWCBVZ75XLP2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:07:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航空公司和旅游集团警告称，政府部分停摆将影响机场安检人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[主要航空公司和旅游集团周五敦促国会避免政府部分停摆，否则在繁忙的美国春假旅行季来临前，约5万名机场安检人员将无法获得薪资。【原文：Major airlines and travel groups on Friday urged Congress to avoid a partial government shutdown, which would result in about 50,000 airport security officers not getting paid ahead of the busy U.S. spring break travel period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/airlines-travel-groups-warn-impact-partial-government-shutdown-airport-screeners-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYR23G6H6JLO5PA5VAUR2L4AHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软、爱立信牵头组建全球科技联盟，共筑数字信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[由微软和爱立信牵头的15家公司于周五联合发起"可信技术联盟"，该联盟围绕五大原则构建，旨在确保技术无论在何处开发都能安全使用。【原文：A group of 15 companies, led by Microsoft and Ericsson , launched on Friday the “Trusted Tech Alliance,” built around five principles to safely use technology regardless of where it is developed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-ericsson-lead-global-tech-alliance-digital-trust-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNR2IMGO7NNYRK3CM4UA26RTPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称委内瑞拉国家石油公司仅向获得单独许可的企业出售石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[委内瑞拉国有石油公司PDVSA过去两周拒绝向未获得美国单独许可的企业出售石油，四家寻求购买货物的公司消息人士向路透社透露。此举限制了该国石油出口，阻碍了其加快清空满溢储油罐的进程。【原文：Venezuela's state-run oil company PDVSA has refused to sell oil to companies without individual U.S. licenses in the past two weeks, four sources from companies seeking to buy cargoes told Reuters, limiting exports and preventing the country from draining brimming storage tanks faster.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuelas-pdvsa-selling-oil-only-individually-licensed-companies-sources-say-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKHTCWFKZVNUPDJC4DWMKCKNOI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026年企业缩减规模、推迟IPO，市场波动考验估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[2026年，多家公司缩减或推迟了在美国市场的首次公开募股计划，市场波动、估值审查以及同行表现疲软等因素共同影响了新股上市进程。【原文：Several companies have downsized or postponed their U.S. initial public offerings in 2026, as market volatility, valuation scrutiny and weak peer performance weighed on the new listings pipeline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/companies-trim-delay-ipos-2026-volatility-tests-valuations-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26B4LCOPJBJLVP3ZF57LXU3T3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:58:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，美国联邦贸易委员会正加强对微软人工智能和云计算业务的审查，并向竞争对手展开问询。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周五报道，美国联邦贸易委员会正加强对微软的审查力度，并已向该科技巨头的竞争对手征询有关其许可协议及其他商业行为的意见。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is escalating scrutiny of Microsoft and has sought answers from the company's rivals on the tech giant's licensing and other business practices, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-ftc-ramps-up-scrutiny-microsoft-over-ai-cloud-practices-questions-rivals-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SCFO4SIL5JYFATPAJMUSCG2ZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行称，该行客户对美元风险敞口的对冲规模创2023年以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大托管机构之一纽约梅隆银行的客户正以逾两年最高幅度对冲美元风险敞口，该行高级策略师周五向路透社透露，这反映出投资者今年对美元的谨慎态度有所增强。【原文：Clients of BNY, one of the world's biggest custodians, are hedging their exposure to the dollar by the most in over two years, a senior strategist told Reuters on Friday, reflecting an increase in investor caution towards the U.S. currency this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-clients-hedge-dollar-exposure-by-most-since-2023-bank-says-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRRL2JZXDBPQZGOUG5RRDMYBDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:22:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官裁定摩根大通客户可就现金清算利率过低提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通必须面对部分拟议集体诉讼，联邦法官裁定，该诉讼指控这家美国最大银行向经纪账户和退休账户持有人支付接近零利率的闲置现金利息，而非市场利率。【原文：JPMorgan Chase must face part of a proposed class action lawsuit accusing the largest U.S. bank of paying brokerage and retirement account holders near-zero interest rates instead of market rates on their idle cash, a federal judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/jpmorgan-customers-can-sue-over-low-rates-cash-sweeps-us-judge-rules-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NY2PFBW3RIH3LKATLOPFTBWE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instacart股价飙升，乐观预测缓解市场对竞争的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线杂货配送公司Instacart周五股价一度飙升19%，这家数百万美国人的首选购物平台发布了乐观的一季度业绩预期，缓解了市场对其面临日益激烈竞争的担忧。【原文：Instacart's shares surged as much as 19% on Friday after the online grocery delivery company, a go-to for millions of Americans, issued an upbeat first-quarter forecast that eased worries about growing competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/instacart-shares-soar-upbeat-forecast-tempers-competition-fears-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3RRSAONTVIUJC7ALD26AP4YB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅首席执行官称，在开云集团与科蒂公司推进交易之际，欧莱雅倾向于优先获得古驰美妆授权。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅首席执行官尼古拉·希罗尼穆斯周五表示，公司希望能在2028年前获得古驰美妆品牌授权，并补充称该问题正在古驰母公司开云集团与现任授权方科蒂公司之间进行磋商。【原文：L'Oreal would welcome gaining access to the Gucci beauty licence earlier than 2028, CEO Nicolas Hieronimus said on Friday, adding that the issue was being discussed between Gucci-owner Kering and current licence holder Coty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/loreal-favours-early-access-gucci-beauty-licence-kering-coty-work-towards-deal-2026-02-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXGTW73RHBOHHHSCC3PSKZ7GBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>