<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:34:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:34:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[爱荷华州总检察长称，好市多就共和党推动终止多元化政策进行了 "富有成效 "的会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据伯德办公室和另一位熟悉谈判的人士透露，好市多与爱荷华州总检察长布伦娜-伯德（Brenna Bird）就该零售商的多元化政策进行了富有成效的讨论，因为唐纳德-特朗普总统对这些计划发起了法律攻势。【原文：Costco has had productive discussions with Iowa Attorney General Brenna Bird over the retailer's diversity policies amid a legal onslaught against those programs launched by President Donald Trump, according to Bird's office and another person familiar with the talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/costco-had-productive-talks-republican-push-end-diversity-policies-iowa-ag-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C43NEMLIZFKZHIMW6NINHSPFUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国宣布为受美国关税影响的汽车行业采取紧急措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国周三宣布对其汽车行业采取紧急支持措施，以减轻美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税措施对这个多年来对美出口大幅增长的行业的打击。【原文：South Korea on Wednesday announced emergency support measures for its auto sector, seeking to reduce the blow of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on a sector that has seen years of sharply rising exports to the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-korea-announces-emergency-measures-auto-industry-hit-by-us-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZGJNGANPRLIFKKBW3KG62IAOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球影城将在伦敦附近开设首个欧洲主题公园]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国政府周三表示，美国媒体巨头康卡斯特公司（Comcast Corp）将在伦敦北部的贝德福德（Bedford）建造其在欧洲的首个环球主题公园和度假村，并于 2031 年开业。【原文：U.S. media giant Comcast Corp will build its first Universal theme park and resort in Europe in Bedford, north of London, opening in 2031, the British government said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/universal-studios-open-first-european-theme-park-near-london-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZVCVR7ZLZMWVOX2JPMGMSREFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:08:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部长称本周末可能就关税问题达成新协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部长布鲁克-罗林斯（Brooke Rollins）周二表示，本周结束前可能与其他国家就贸易关税问题达成新的协议。【原文：U.S. Agriculture Secretary Brooke Rollins said on Tuesday that new deals could be struck with other countries over trade tariffs by the end of this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-agriculture-chief-says-new-deals-may-be-struck-over-tariffs-by-end-week-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PLVANIBRZOSNMADYA3SX4G7CM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中国，一些公司要求员工减少工作，变革的呼声不绝于耳]]></title><description><![CDATA[家电制造商美的等少数几家中国大公司今年有了新的荣誉徽章：强制员工打卡下班，禁止下班后开会。【原文：A handful of major Chinese companies like home appliance maker Midea have new badges of honour this year: mandatory clock-off times for staff and bans on after-hours meetings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-whispers-change-some-companies-tell-staff-work-less-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQMBULIGPJMIDIBYH2XZHV6OA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:05:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大公司前高级律师谴责特朗普针对律师事务所的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软、英特尔和礼来等大公司的前法务高管周二提交了一份法律简报，指责美国总统唐纳德-特朗普破坏法治，并以针对律师事务所的行政命令威胁美国企业。【原文：Former top legal executives at large companies including Microsoft , Intel and Eli Lilly submitted a legal brief on Tuesday accusing U.S. President Donald Trump of undermining the rule of law and threatening American businesses with his executive orders targeting law firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/former-top-lawyers-major-companies-decry-trump-orders-against-law-firms-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BTTYG2CRBLKPIWBS4W4RLRF6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 22:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上午反弹失败后，华尔街关税溃败重现]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 500 指数近一年来首次收盘跌破 5000 点，扭转了上午的强劲涨势，因为在午夜最后期限到来之前，人们对美国即将推迟关税或做出让步的希望逐渐破灭。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 closed below 5,000 points for the first time in almost a year, reversing a strong morning rally as hopes faded for any imminent U.S. delays or concessions on tariffs ahead of a midnight deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-stocks-quotes-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6D5QTNUQNI3ZHRTAHM5E4CQH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 22:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战迫使韩国更快更大幅度地降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国贸易战不断升级，亚洲第四大经济体正努力应对经济衰退的风险，韩国央行今年可能被迫提前或加深降息。【原文：South Korea's central bank may be forced to bring forward or deepen interest rate cuts this year as Asia's fourth-largest economy grapples with the risk of recession due to the escalating U.S. trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/trade-war-pressures-south-korea-cut-rates-faster-deeper-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOCXJFYDZJMIRIIHXYNF3DY354</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 22:09:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车第一季度欧洲电动汽车销量增长一倍多]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车集团（Volkswagen Group）周三表示，第一季度该集团在欧洲的电池电动汽车交付量增加了一倍多，从去年同期的7.44万辆增至15万辆以上，这是电动汽车需求回升的又一迹象。【原文：The Volkswagen Group more than doubled its deliveries of battery-electric cars in Europe in the first quarter to over 150,000 from 74,400 in the same period last year, the carmaker said on Wednesday, in another sign that EV demand is picking up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagens-europe-ev-sales-more-than-double-first-quarter-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUZGXIT5BNPSLNSAIV6PBH7GCI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 22:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会将与产业界讨论贸易和美国关税战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一封邀请信显示，欧盟委员会已邀请受美国关税影响最严重的部门参加周四的面谈，委员会正在权衡新的贸易伙伴关系和进一步的反制措施。【原文：The European Commission has invited the sectors most impacted by U.S. tariffs to an in-person meeting on Thursday, an invitation letter seen by Reuters showed, as the commission weighs new trade partnerships and further countermeasures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-commission-discuss-trade-us-tariff-strategy-with-industries-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QT4ZCWR635NT3OQ6IHUATPONVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 21:43:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普政策影响，伍德麦肯兹将 5 年期美国风能展望下调 40]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一家著名的能源研究公司以特朗普政府的政策和对经济的担忧为由，将其对美国新风能项目的五年展望下调了 40%。【原文：A prominent energy research firm slashed its five-year outlook for new U.S. wind energy projects by 40% on Tuesday, citing Trump administration policies and concerns about the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/wood-mackenzie-cuts-5-year-us-wind-energy-outlook-40-trump-policies-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOLJMPK7RBNVREQHJAF3RLDOOM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 21:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西咖啡出口商在美国加征关税之际看到机遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西咖啡出口商将美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收全球关税视为一个机会，在国际竞争对手被征收更重的关税后，他们将更多的罗布斯塔咖啡豆运往美国。【原文：Brazilian coffee exporters see U.S. President Donald Trump's global tariffs as an opportunity to send more robusta beans to the United States after international rivals were hit with even heavier charges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazil-coffee-exporters-glimpse-opportunity-amidst-us-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4PHMPUZJJL5DPAQAVTBK76BYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 20:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[当局称华盛顿特斯拉超级充电站受损]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地警方和联邦调查局称，本周二，华盛顿州莱西的一个特斯拉超级充电站遭到破坏。【原文：A Tesla Supercharger station was damaged in Lacey, Washington, on Tuesday, according to local police and the Federal Bureau of Investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-supercharger-station-damaged-washington-authorities-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKEMAGUJ65JVFBG3LSQUQVTK5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 20:50:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国每天从关税中获利 20 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二表示，美国每天从关税中获得 20 亿美元的收入。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday the United States is taking in $2 billion per day from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-us-taking-2-billion-day-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSWPK5CMQJOIJLYOS4C7GM33LI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 20:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，英国财政大臣里夫斯将与高层管理人员举行关税危机会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻周二报道，在全球金融市场持续动荡之际，英国财政大臣雷切尔-里夫斯（Rachel Reeves）将与哈格里夫斯-兰斯当（Hargreaves Lansdown）、法律与通用公司（Legal & General）、劳埃德银行集团（Lloyds Banking Group）和M&amp;G等公司的老板举行会谈。【原文：British finance minister Rachel Reeves will hold talks with bosses from companies including Hargreaves Lansdown, Legal & General , Lloyds Banking Group and M&amp;G amid ongoing volatility in global financial markets, Sky News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/british-finance-minister-reeves-hold-tariff-crisis-talks-with-top-executives-sky-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WW3W4TKT35OIXEJYS6YRAFDFLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 20:28:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[啤酒制造商 Constellation Brands 撤回 DEI 计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[科罗娜（Corona）啤酒制造商星座品牌公司（Constellation Brands）周二废除了其多元化、公平和包容计划，加入了越来越多的企业在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）反对后削减其多元化、公平和包容目标的行列。【原文：Corona beer maker Constellation Brands scrapped its diversity, equity and inclusion programs on Tuesday, joining an increasing number of corporations curbing their DEI goals after U.S. President Donald Trump's opposition to them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/beer-maker-constellation-brands-pulls-back-dei-initiatives-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFDN5VYGFVNYXLE5Y3HQUI6YGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 20:20:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯迪拉克终止生产三排座汽油动力 XT6 SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（GM.N）周二表示，将于2025年底停产凯迪拉克XT6汽油动力三排座SUV。【原文：General Motors GM.N is discontinuing the Cadillac XT6 gasoline-powered three-row SUV at the end of 2025, the automaker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/cadillac-ending-production-three-row-gasoline-powered-xt6-suv-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ESODAVM5BLPPBESFMZHZ3T2CQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 19:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构 OCC 向国会通报重大安全漏洞事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部货币监理署（OCC）周二表示，已向国会通报了涉及其电子邮件系统的重大信息安全漏洞。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department's Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) said on Tuesday it had notified Congress of a major information security breach involving its email system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-regulator-occ-notifies-congress-major-security-breach-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWZIBPMTIBJHLAYLBQFODJF7VU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 19:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税将于周三生效，美国葡萄酒销售商忧心忡忡]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大安斯利葡萄酒商行（Ansley Wine Merchants）的老板、57 岁的亚当-威廉姆斯（Adam Williams）说，他周三已经做好了最坏的打算，因为唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税即将生效，这将使他销售的进口葡萄酒和烈酒的成本飙升。【原文：Adam Williams, 57, owner of Ansley Wine Merchants in Atlanta, said he was bracing for the worst on Wednesday, as President Donald Trump's tariffs are set to kick in, which will spike costs of the imported wines and liquors he sells.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-wine-sellers-worry-trump-tariffs-set-hit-wednesday-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZMZSHYPTNFLGHCL2GVJ5TZRFSA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 19:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美两国就阿根廷主要货币互换额度发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国寻求与总部设在华盛顿的国际货币基金组织（IMF）达成新协议的同时，中国与阿根廷达成的一项重要货币互换协议缓冲了南美国家枯竭的外汇储备水平。【原文：China is on a crash course with the United States over a major Chinese currency swap deal with Argentina that has buffered the South American country's depleted foreign reserve levels even as it seeks a new deal with the Washington-based IMF.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/china-us-clash-over-major-argentina-currency-swap-line-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TR4ISU4FZI75PMA3FJSOI7QVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 19:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席戴利：现在是缓慢、谨慎地制定政策的时候了]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周二表示，在经济强劲、特朗普政府的新政策效果尚不明朗的情况下，央行不应急于调整利率。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly on Tuesday said with the economy strong and a lot still unclear on the effect of new policies of the Trump administration, the central bank should not rush to adjust interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-daly-theres-time-tread-slowly-carefully-policy-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGA2TCKPFZLZTGIAIN6ZMAWHLA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西监管机构授权星链公司为其本地运营增加 7,500 颗卫星]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西电信监管机构 Anatel 周二在一份声明中说，该监管机构授权埃隆-马斯克的 Starlink 公司增加 7500 颗新卫星，以便在这个拉美国家运营。【原文：Brazil's telecommunications regulator Anatel authorized Elon Musk's Starlink to add 7,500 new satellites to operate in the Latin American nation, the watchdog said in a statement on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/brazil-regulator-authorizes-starlink-add-7500-satellites-its-local-operation-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXW2QDS665JPTB35H6S3IX2BA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大称将从 4 月 9 日起对部分美国产汽车征收反关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大联邦财政部周二表示，加拿大上周表示将对部分美国制造的汽车征收25%的反关税，该反关税将于4月9日生效。【原文：The 25% counter-tariffsCanada said last week it would impose on some U.S.-made vehicles will go into effect on April 9, the federal finance ministry said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/canada-says-counter-tariffs-against-some-us-made-autos-will-start-april-9-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45JXKXTVIRKKLI76E5HT7ZALTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NRF 称，美国复活节消费将增长，因为节日的欢乐气氛与经济阴霾背道而驰]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国全国零售联合会周二发布的一份报告显示，尽管人们对高通胀和经济不确定性感到担忧，但由于美国人抢购糖果和礼物来庆祝复活节，预计今年美国复活节的消费支出将增长约5%。【原文：U.S. consumer spending for Easter is expected to rise about 5% this year as Americans snap up candy and gifts to celebrate despite concerns around high inflation and economic uncertainty, a National Retail Federation report showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-easter-spending-rise-holiday-cheer-defies-economic-gloom-nrf-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIQOS2TGIROOLEZYQWPHXMH6VY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员加大对美联储将于五月开始降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，交易员们加大了对美联储最快将于下月开始下调政策利率的押注，因为白宫表示，对从中国进口的商品征收的额外关税将于周三生效，贸易敌对行动进一步升级，可能会拖累经济。【原文：Traders boosted bets on Tuesday the Federal Reserve will start cutting its policy rate as soon as next month, as the White House said additional tariffs on imports from China will go into effect on Wednesday in a further escalation of trade hostilities that could slow the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-boost-bets-fed-will-start-cutting-rates-may-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4IX4BJMFRJTBCSSP5LLOWFSIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:59:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，在遭到反对后，美国考虑调整针对中国船只的港口费计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据六位消息人士透露，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑软化其对访问美国港口的与中国有联系的船只征收费用的提议，因为来自各行业的大量负面反馈称这一提议可能会造成经济破坏。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering softening its proposed fee on China-linked ships visiting U.S. ports after a flood of negative feedback from industries that said the idea could be economically devastating, according to six sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-considers-adjusting-port-fee-plan-chinese-vessels-after-pushback-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BNO23GFFWZKA5NG64QMZWCIRDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表格里尔称，并非所有中国船舶收费都将实施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周二向立法者表示，美国贸易代表办公室提出的向停靠美国港口的中国船只征收数百万美元费用的建议并不会全部实施，而且这些费用可能不会累积。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer told lawmakers on Tuesday that not all of the agency's proposed multimillion-dollar fees for Chinese-built ships to dock at U.S. ports will be implemented, and they may not be cumulative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/not-all-chinese-ship-fees-will-be-implemented-ustr-greer-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGDDCXFWMNI4XHTH65ES3VEG6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社/益普索民意调查显示，73%的美国人预计特朗普关税将导致物价飞涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社/益普索（Reuters/Ipsos）的一项最新民意调查显示，在唐纳德-特朗普总统对来自世界大多数国家的进口商品征收全面新关税之后，大多数美国人都在为各种消费品的价格上涨做准备。【原文：Most Americans are bracing for higher prices on a wide range of consumer goods following President Donald Trump's move to impose sweeping new tariffs on imports from most of the world, a new Reuters/Ipsos poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/73-americans-expect-price-surge-under-trump-tariffs-reutersipsos-poll-finds-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGVG6ICNTBOSVOGWHCENQAMWZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司称美国新关税将增加喷气机的复杂性和成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）推出的关税措施将增加这家巴西喷气机制造商在美国的业务和客户的复杂性和成本。【原文：Embraer said on Tuesday that tariffs introduced by U.S. President Donald Trump would add complexity and costs for the Brazilian jet maker’s business and customers in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-says-new-us-tariffs-will-add-complexity-costs-jets-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24PUKUKOWRKKHH6JL7I7PIW2DU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表在关税范围和期限问题上面临两党质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周二告诉美国参议员们，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的政府没有计划在短期内改变全球关税计划的策略。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer told U.S. senators on Tuesday that President Donald Trump's administration has no plans to change tactics on the global tariff program in the near term, prompting some light push back from Republican lawmakers as Democrats excoriated the approach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-trade-rep-faces-bipartisan-questions-scope-duration-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2V7B2FR6FNKTBH3TFROKGF4FDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>