<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 10:35:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 10:35:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[空客公司高管称，空客、泰雷兹和莱昂纳多今年可能签署首份卫星合作协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲航空航天集团莱昂纳多（Leonardo）、泰雷兹（Thales）和空中客车公司（Airbus）防务与航天部门负责人周日在接受采访时说，它们最早可能在今年签署合并卫星业务的初步协议，这证实了路透社早些时候的报道。【原文：European aerospace groups Leonardo , Thales and Airbus could sign an initial agreement to combine their satellite businesses as early as this year, the head of Airbus' defence and space division said in an interview on Sunday, confirming an earlier Reuters report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-thales-leonardo-could-sign-first-deal-this-year-satellite-tie-up-airbus-2025-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPSP6YDOOBNQ3LYRKHWSBHQW3A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 09:10:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利将在即将出台的预算计划中确认 GDP 增长预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利经济部长吉安卡洛-乔盖蒂（Giancarlo Giorgetti）周日表示，意大利计划在即将于本月晚些时候公布的预算计划中确认其国内生产总值（GDP）增长预期。【原文：Italy plans to confirm its GDP growth estimates in the upcoming budget plan to be unveiled later this month, Economy Minister Giancarlo Giorgetti said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italy-confirm-gdp-growth-estimates-upcoming-budget-plan-2025-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLAYA4QYGBLCVMPYGU6DGVLI3Y</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 08:38:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行伦敦塔改造账单高达 15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街银行花旗集团（Citigroup）告诉路透社，该公司对其伦敦大楼的改建费用已上升至 15 亿美元（11 亿英镑），这凸显了在企业寻求吸引员工重返办公室的同时，对过时的工作场所进行大修的高昂成本。【原文：Wall Street bank Citigroup's bill for refitting its tower in London has risen to $1.5 billion (1.1 billion pounds), the company told Reuters, highlighting the high costs of overhauling outdated workplaces as businesses seek to attract staff back into the office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citis-bill-london-tower-revamp-hits-15-billion-2025-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GY6NFHQRENOGZJZ5ZCTKKIT6ZA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 08:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道刚果-卢旺达协议草案概述了美国等国在矿产部门改革中的作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份经济框架草案，卢旺达和刚果民主共和国将致力于与包括美国在内的第三方合作，改造其矿产供应链并进行改革，以寻求在华盛顿达成和平协议后刺激投资。【原文：Rwanda and the Democratic Republic of Congo will commit to working with third parties, including the U.S., to revamp their mineral supply chains and develop reforms, according to a draft of an economic framework seen by Reuters, as they seek to spur investment following a peace deal reached in Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/congo-rwanda-draft-deal-outlines-role-us-others-revamp-minerals-sector-2025-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2HZKZW6IZPPZKP63JMZCLWEWI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 08:03:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美官员将在西班牙就贸易摩擦、TikTok 截止日期等问题展开会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美两国官员周日在马德里举行会晤，就长期存在的贸易摩擦、中国短视频应用 TikTok 即将到来的资产剥离期限以及华盛顿要求七国集团（G7）和欧洲盟国对中国征收关税以阻止其购买俄罗斯石油等问题进行讨论。【原文：U.S. and Chinese officials meet in Madrid on Sunday to hash over longstanding trade irritants, a looming divestiture deadline for Chinese short video app TikTok and demands by Washington that G7 and European allies impose tariffs on China to halt its purchases of Russian oil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-chinese-officials-launch-talks-spain-trade-irritants-tiktok-deadline-2025-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVJXIKUNWRJWXAJNAHZ2TPV74U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 04:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[滚石》、《公告牌》所有者彭斯克就人工智能概述起诉谷歌]]></title><description><![CDATA[滚石》（Rolling Stone）、《公告牌》（Billboard）和《综艺》（Variety）的所有者周五起诉谷歌，称这家技术巨头的人工智能摘要未经同意使用了其新闻报道，并减少了其网站的流量。【原文：The owner of Rolling Stone, Billboard and Variety sued Google on Friday, alleging the technology giant's AI summaries use its journalism without consent and reduce traffic to its websites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/rolling-stone-billboard-owner-penske-sues-google-over-ai-overviews-2025-09-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6X6UNEGAMNO5PDK45GCUX5W6XU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 02:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英美将在特朗普访问期间签署数十亿美元科技协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国驻华盛顿大使馆周六表示，作为唐纳德-特朗普总统访问英国的一部分，英美两国准备在未来几天内签署一项具有里程碑意义的技术协议。【原文：The United Kingdom and the U.S. are preparing to sign a landmark technology agreement in the coming days as part of President Donald Trump’s visit to the UK, the British Embassy in Washington said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-us-sign-multibillion-dollar-tech-deal-during-trumps-visit-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5OD7O3WWRL4VH2BXXYZ3UNLBI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国金融巨头促进英国投资和就业]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国政府周六宣布了总额超过 12.5 亿英镑（16.9 亿美元）的美国私人对英国金融服务业的投资，其中包括 PayPal、美国银行、花旗集团和 S&amp;P Global。【原文：The UK government on Saturday announced a total of over 1.25 billion pounds ($1.69 billion) of private U.S. investment in the UK's financial services sector including PayPal , Bank of America , Citigroup and S&amp;P Global .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-financial-giants-boost-uk-investments-jobs-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYMVWURSJZPLPB5RJBIFIHKWIY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰和美国将寻找矿产交易投资项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰经济部长周六表示，作为基辅与华盛顿矿产交易的一部分，乌克兰官员和美国国际开发金融公司的一个团队将进行实地考察，以确定投资项目。【原文：Ukrainian officials and a team from the U.S. International Development Finance Corporation will carry out site visits to identify investment projects as part of Kyiv's minerals deal with Washington, Ukraine's economy minister said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ukraine-us-scout-minerals-deal-investment-projects-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKKEYHZDKNMM5PTR65LEDS3JQA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 17:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表格里尔将在马德里与中国官员就贸易、嘀嗒出行等问题举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位美国贸易代表办公室官员周六表示，美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）将出席周日在马德里举行的与中国官员的新一轮会谈，讨论贸易和其他经济问题，包括嘀嗒出行（TikTok）剥离美国资产的最后期限（周三）。【原文：U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer will attend a new round of talks with Chinese officials due to start on Sunday in Madrid on trade and other economic issues including a Wednesday deadline for TikTok to divest its U.S. assets, a USTR official said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ustr-greer-attend-talks-with-chinese-officials-madrid-trade-tiktok-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2L3DTOO3JJ35FS7EDLNAYAG24</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在贸易谈判前对美国芯片发起歧视和倾销调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在西班牙举行新一轮中美贸易谈判前一天，中国商务部于周六启动了对美国芯片贸易政策的反歧视调查，以及对倾销的单独调查。【原文：China's Ministry of Commerce initiated an anti-discrimination investigation into U.S. trade policy over chips on Saturday, as well as a separate investigation into dumping, a day ahead of a new round of U.S.-China trade talks in Spain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-launches-discrimination-dumping-probes-into-us-chips-ahead-trade-talks-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFGO3L2QYNOQTCMNMPZACCNO6Y</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 14:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Sainsbury's 正洽谈将 Argos 出售给中国的 JD.com]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国超市集团塞恩斯伯里（Sainsbury's）周六表示，正在就向中国电子商务巨头京东商城出售旗下 Argos 日用百货业务的可能性进行谈判。【原文：British supermarket group Sainsbury's is in talks regarding a potential sale of its Argos general merchandise business to Chinese e-commerce giant JD.com , it said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uk-sainsburys-talks-sell-argos-chinas-jdcom-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKSTPSIFKNKMJIB7EYMNBLULVM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 14:04:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[裕信银行首席执行官告诉德国报纸：裕信银行可能向非欧盟银行出售德国商业银行股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据德国一家报纸周六报道，意大利联合信贷银行首席执行官安德烈亚-奥塞尔（Andrea Orcel）表示，如果该银行收到了股东们想要的好报价，可能会考虑将其持有的德国商业银行股份出售给欧盟以外的一家银行。【原文：UniCredit CEO Andrea Orcel said the Italian lender may consider the sale of its stake in Germany's Commerzbank to a bank outside the European Union if it received a good offer that shareholders wanted, a German newspaper reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-could-sell-commerzbank-stake-non-eu-bank-ceo-tells-german-paper-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJXQ3F4KPBKC7KZSRW7DYTXORE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 12:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，贝莱德将在特朗普访问期间向英国数据中心投资 6.78 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻（Sky News）周六报道，贝莱德计划通过与 Digital Gravity Partners 成立一家新的合资企业，向英国数据中心基础设施投资 5 亿英镑（约合 6.78 亿美元），这是将于下周美国总统唐纳德-特朗普进行国事访问期间宣布的一系列交易之一。【原文：BlackRock plans to invest 500 million pounds ($678 million) in British data centre infrastructure through a new joint venture with Digital Gravity Partners, one of a string of deals to be announced next week during U.S. President Donald Trump's state visit next week, Sky News reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/blackrock-invest-678-million-uk-data-centres-during-trump-visit-sky-news-reports-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GIK3LWLPFOSHDLCAOJCF22RRM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 05:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，雀巢投资者呼吁董事长下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周六报道，雀巢公司的投资者呼吁董事长保罗-布尔克（Paul Bulcke）下台，因为在短短一年多的时间里，又有一位首席执行官离职。【原文：Nestle investors have called for Chairman Paul Bulcke to step down over the departure of a second chief executive in just over a year, the Financial Times reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nestle-investors-call-chairman-step-down-ft-reports-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FVT6SZKLMBIDXHLTHAIWKH7XFQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 04:12:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国设定的 2025 年汽车销量目标低于协会预测，并誓言加强监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国工业部表示，2025 年中国汽车销量目标为 3230 万辆，低于中国汽车工业协会（CAAM）预计的 3290 万辆。【原文：China is targeting 32.3 million in vehicle sales in 2025, the country's industry ministry said, below the 32.9 million units projected for the year by the China Association of Automobile Manufacturers (CAAM).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-sets-2025-auto-sales-target-below-association-forecast-vows-tighter-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LXYDNBI2ZNY5EQECDQMZLZV6I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 04:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Business Insider 报道，马斯克的 xAI 裁员数百名数据注释员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》（Business Insider）周五报道，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 xAI 数据注释团队裁员至少 500 人。【原文：Elon Musk's xAI laid off at least 500 workers from its data annotation team, Business Insider reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-xai-lays-off-hundreds-data-annotators-business-insider-reports-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VESPULGU4RJRZFNINR6PCRVY6I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 02:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，OpenAI 将与商业合作伙伴分享 8%的收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周五报道，OpenAI 预计到本十年末将与商业合作伙伴（即微软）分享约 8% 的收入，低于目前的 20%。【原文：OpenAI has projected to share about 8% of its revenue with commercial partners, namely Microsoft , by the end of the decade, down from the current 20%, The Information reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-share-8-its-revenue-with-commercial-partners-information-reports-2025-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCRYDEANEFLA5C5LYR6YDECQ5M</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 02:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄亥俄州和肯塔基州工厂的 UAW 工人与通用电气航空航天公司达成临时协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用电气航空航天公司（GE Aerospace）俄亥俄州埃文代尔（Evendale）和肯塔基州埃兰格（Erlanger）工厂的联合汽车工人工会成员周五表示，已与该公司达成临时协议。【原文：Members of the United Auto Workers union at GE Aerospace's Evendale, Ohio, and Erlanger, Kentucky, facilities have reached a tentative agreement with the company, the union said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/uaw-workers-reach-tentative-deal-with-ge-aerospace-ohio-kentucky-plants-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMBOMBEHWFMMXDIGXQYQN57PCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:59:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国处罚为芯片制造商中芯国际收购工具的两家中国公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府发布公告称，美国周五对为中国顶级芯片制造商中芯国际收购美国芯片制造设备的两家中国公司进行了处罚，将其列入商务部限制贸易名单的32家实体之一。这 32 家公司中有 23 家在中国。【原文：The United States on Friday penalized two Chinese firms that acquired U.S. chipmaking equipment for China's top chipmaker SMIC, including them among 32 entities that were added to the Commerce Department's restricted trade list, according to a U.S. government posting. Twenty-three of the 32 were in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-penalizes-two-chinese-companies-that-acquired-tools-chipmaker-smic-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CP462KFC5FMKHMYYGUXESKDRVA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:28:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥拟对中国征收关税，比亚迪和特斯拉损失最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥拟对从中国进口的汽车征收 50% 的关税，电动汽车竞争对手比亚迪和特斯拉将成为最大的输家，这可能会对墨西哥快速增长的电动汽车市场造成打击，而美国传统的 "三大 "汽车制造商则不会受到影响。【原文：Electric car rivals BYD and Tesla are set to be the biggest losers from Mexico’s proposed 50 percent tariff on autos imported from China, triggering a likely blow to the fast-growing electric car market in Mexico while sparing the traditional "Big Three" U.S. car manufacturers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-tesla-set-lose-most-mexicos-proposed-tariffs-china-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2NUABDXBJN63LVNFTPPCQIWZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合太平洋公司首席执行官与特朗普就 850 亿美元收购诺福克的计划举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合太平洋公司首席执行官吉姆-维纳（Jim Vena）在椭圆形办公室会见了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump），讨论了该公司拟以 850 亿美元收购诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern Corp）的事宜。【原文：Union Pacific Corp CEO Jim Vena met with U.S. President Donald Trump in the Oval Office to discuss the railroad's proposed $85 billion buyout of Norfolk Southern Corp , the company said on Friday, as it seeks regulatory approval for the biggest U.S. rail merger in decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/union-pacific-ceo-held-talks-with-trump-85-billion-plan-buy-norfolk-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HUV72N3ZZMZ3CM5IFTLUKTR6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alliance Laundry 在提交的美国首次公开募股文件中披露收入大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着 IPO 市场的持续火热，这家洗衣设备制造商周五在其美国首次公开募股文件中披露，Alliance Laundry 的收入在 2025 年上半年增长了近 15%，该公司的目标是在纽约证券交易所上市。【原文：Alliance Laundry's revenue rose nearly 15% in the first half of 2025, the laundry equipment maker disclosed on Friday in its U.S. initial public offering paperwork, aiming to list on the New York Stock Exchange as the IPO markets continue to run hot.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/alliance-laundry-reveals-revenue-jump-us-ipo-filing-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIZEEU6YY5MY3BCNTHWH3WCALU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:18:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空要求在登机前取下移动设备的电池]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国西南航空公司周五表示，将以火灾风险为由，要求乘客在登机前取出电动轮椅和代步车上的可拆卸锂电池。【原文：Southwest Airlines said on Friday it will require passengers to take out removable lithium batteries from powered wheelchairs and scooters before boarding, citing fire risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/southwest-requiring-removal-batteries-mobility-devices-before-boarding-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXZDUHFNVRPDNFEVDAA2PO7UOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，贝森特与贝莱德的里德尔会面，继续物色下任美联储主席人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士称，在特朗普政府继续为美联储物色新主席之际，美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五在纽约会见了贝莱德公司（BlackRock Inc）高管里克-里德尔（Rick Rieder）。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent met with BlackRock Inc executive Rick Rieder in New York on Friday, as the Trump administration continued its search for a new chair for the Federal Reserve, a source familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-met-with-blackrocks-rieder-search-next-fed-chair-continues-source-says-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QS5YQFR5L5P45H2OD3K42NAWHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博雅银行任命联席总裁，首席执行官莫伊尼汉表示将任职十年]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周五表示，任命迪安-阿塔纳西亚（Dean Athanasia）和吉姆-德马雷（Jim DeMare）为联席总裁，首席执行官布莱恩-莫伊尼汉（Brian Moynihan）加强了他在本十年末领导这家美国第二大银行的承诺。【原文：Bank of America appointed Dean Athanasia and Jim DeMare as co-presidents, the U.S. lender said on Friday, as CEO Brian Moynihan reinforced his commitment to lead the second-largest bank in the country through the end of the decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bofa-appoints-co-presidents-ceo-moynihan-says-he-will-serve-through-decade-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NHGVIC4GNLPLA5VEP7WYGMHSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:26:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Corteva 探索分拆为两家独立公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，农业公司 Corteva 正在探索将其种子和农药业务拆分为两家独立公司。【原文：Agriculture company Corteva is exploring a breakup that would separate its seed and pesticide businesses into two separate companies, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/corteva-explores-breaking-up-into-two-separate-companies-wsj-reports-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAISBA3UA5OKBHUZ5YW3J4MHZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:18:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院驳回谷歌在 Epic Games 案中要求进一步暂停 Play 商店全面改革的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周五未能说服美国一家上诉法院进一步冻结一项命令，该命令要求谷歌对其应用程序商店 Play 进行全面改革，同时谷歌在 "堡垒之夜"（Fortnite）视频游戏制造商 Epic Games 的诉讼中对这一决定提出质疑。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Friday failed to persuade a U.S. appeals court to further freeze an order forcing it to make sweeping reforms to its app store Play while it challenges the decision in a lawsuit by "Fortnite" video game maker Epic Games.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-appeals-court-declines-google-bid-further-pause-play-store-overhaul-epic-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YULZTTREXFONVHDDFQ43WEEQAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果公司人工智能和搜索高管罗比-沃克将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，苹果公司最资深的人工智能高管之一罗比-沃克（Robby Walker）即将离职。【原文：Robby Walker, one of Apple's most senior artificial intelligence executives, is leaving the company, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apples-ai-search-executive-robby-walker-leave-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVJQH52Q4ZNI3LCM2TFDNXMAI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州指控卡尔希经营非法体育博彩业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州总检察长周五提起诉讼，要求阻止 Kalshi 在该州运营其体育预测平台，称这家纽约衍生品交易公司正在经营非法体育博彩业务。【原文：Massachusetts' attorney general filed a lawsuit on Friday seeking to block Kalshi from operating its sports prediction platform in the state, alleging the New York derivatives trading company was operating an illegal sports wagering business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/massachusetts-accuses-kalshi-running-illegal-sports-wagering-operation-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4QF77ARVVIZ5LLA5DKLLCTRRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>