<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 15:04:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 15:04:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥总统表示，无需财政改革，墨西哥仍有提高税收的空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）周五表示，墨西哥明年还有增加税收的空间，无需进行深入的财政改革。【原文：Mexico has room to boost tax revenues next year without turning to a deep fiscal reform, President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Friday, as her government is expected to present its budget proposal later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-has-room-boost-tax-revenues-without-fiscal-overhaul-president-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSIRYBBRAJNUNDX5OUFTE2TRWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:49:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称 Northvolt 已考虑在美国寻求破产保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士告诉路透社，瑞典电池制造商 Northvolt 一直在讨论在美国寻求破产保护的可能性，这也是这家资金短缺的公司生存下去的几种选择之一。【原文：Swedish battery maker Northvolt has been discussing the possibility of bankruptcy protection in the United States as one of several options for the cash-strapped company to survive, two people with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/northvolt-has-considered-us-bankruptcy-protection-sources-say-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJ7NV4GYJFPSXDAQ6WR3MMUVUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安巴尼的信实公司要求印度审查马斯克的 "星链 "和亚马逊的覆盖范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一封信显示，亿万富翁穆克什-安巴尼（Mukesh Ambani）的信实公司（Reliance）要求印度电信监管机构在授予卫星频谱之前，审查埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的星链（Starlink）和亚马逊的Kuiper的潜在覆盖范围，因为他们担心本地企业可能会受到影响。【原文：Billionaire Mukesh Ambani's Reliance has asked India's telecom regulator to review the potential reach of Elon Musk's Starlink and Amazon's Kuiper before awarding satellite spectrum amid concerns local players could suffer, a letter showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ambanis-reliance-asks-india-review-reach-musks-starlink-amazon-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KE7S5TQXJIGXEDIEORHBUITXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:41:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，摩根大通在权衡伦敦总部的各种选择，因为金丝雀码头大厦已无法容纳它的规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，摩根大通正在评估其伦敦欧洲总部的选择方案，因为这家快速扩张的华尔街银行已经超出了其位于伦敦金丝雀码头金融区的现有大楼。【原文：JPMorgan is assessing options for its European headquarters in London as the fast-expanding Wall Street bank outgrows its existing tower in London's Canary Wharf financial district, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-weighs-london-hq-options-it-outgrows-canary-wharf-tower-sources-say-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CKOVXSMOWZNAZKTFB54H3VBDZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:32:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯 Sovcomflot 公司将盈利下降归咎于西方制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯领先的油轮集团 Sovcomflot 周五表示，西方对俄罗斯油轮的制裁限制了其财务业绩，因为该公司报告的收入和核心盈利都在下降。【原文：Russia's leading tanker group Sovcomflot said on Friday that Western sanctions on Russian oil tankers were limiting its financial performance, as it reported falling revenues and core earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russias-sovcomflot-blames-earnings-drop-western-sanctions-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYBHFGY2JVMNREC4VSFPUS4DX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:32:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯称技术变革可改善金融体系]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周五表示，美国中央银行需要密切关注金融系统的技术发展。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said Friday the U.S. central bank needs to keep a close watch on technological developments in the financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-collins-says-tech-changes-can-improve-financial-system-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNWZBX7Z6ZMINAP3CVDFW742G4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份进口价格意外上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于燃料和其他商品价格上涨，10月份美国进口价格意外上涨，这是近几个月来美国在降低通胀方面缺乏进展的最新迹象。【原文：U.S. import prices unexpectedly rose in October amid higher prices for fuels and other goods, the latest indication of lack of progress lowering inflation in recent months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-import-prices-unexpectedly-rise-october-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3LH4EIYX2VL3TN5WMB7JTGQTU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:01:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，马斯克的 SpaceX 公司准备在 12 月以每股 135 美元的价格发起要约收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，埃隆-马斯克的 SpaceX 公司准备在 12 月发起要约收购，以每股 135 美元的价格出售现有股份。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX is preparing to launch a tender offer in December to sell existing shares at a price of $135 per share, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people with knowledge of the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/musks-spacex-preparing-launch-tender-offer-dec-135share-ft-reports-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDQJXRKX7BL35DTGTVT2C2W6YY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 13:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份零售销售略高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 10 月份的零售额增幅略高于预期，但消费者支出的基本势头在第四季度初似乎有所放缓。【原文：U.S. retail sales increased slightly more than expected in October, but underlying momentum in consumer spending appeared to slow at the start of the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-retail-sales-slightly-above-expectations-october-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQIRTC5YJ5KAXMA3JOTZVWJAZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 13:40:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称通用汽车裁员近千人，其中大部分在美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周五告诉路透社，通用汽车公司正在全球范围内裁员近1000人，其中大部分在美国，因为该公司希望精简业务。【原文：General Motors is laying off nearly 1,000 workers worldwide, most in the U.S., as it looks to streamline operations, a source told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-laying-off-nearly-1000-workers-most-us-source-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NGC2LZ3PBNEZJZ3IJEQHGUDHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 13:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业盈利乐观，美国股票基金资金流入强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月13日的一周内，投资者对美国股票基金的需求大幅增加，原因是人们对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）重新上台将改善美国企业盈利前景持乐观态度。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed a significant boost in investor demand in the week through Nov. 13, fueled by optimism that Donald Trump’s return to office would enhance the outlook for U.S. corporate earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-robust-inflows-corporate-earnings-optimism-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6EI6BCLVBN3ROQ5GQWFFFLAH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼接近临界点，流媒体利润开始抵消有线电视的下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[2022 年，鲍勃-艾格重返华特迪士尼担任首席执行官，并大胆承诺要让流媒体盈利。【原文：Bob Iger returned to Walt Disney as CEO in 2022 with a bold promise of making streaming profitable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-nears-tipping-point-streaming-profits-start-offset-cable-decline-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CUNW7YSCVMJ5NNZOISMQ47GJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:41:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[格兰霍姆称，取消美国电动汽车税收抵免将让位于中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长詹妮弗-格兰霍尔姆（Jennifer Granholm）周五在巴库举行的COP29气候大会上对记者说，取消美国电动汽车税收抵免将适得其反，并将把市场拱手让给中国的汽车制造商。【原文：Cancelling the U.S. electric vehicle tax credit would be counterproductive and cede ground to car-makers in China, U.S. Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm told reporters on Friday at the COP29 climate conference in Baku.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rescinding-us-ev-tax-credit-would-cede-ground-china-granholm-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6K5OZXSVBNHHLAOYJAZR5ZPKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:30:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大手笔预算和特朗普获胜后，英国通胀忧虑升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在英国似乎要摆脱通胀问题时，新政府的大肆挥霍以及美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税计划引发的全球贸易战风险却威胁着通胀问题的延续。【原文：Just when Britain seemed to be moving beyond its inflation problem, the new government's spending splurge and the risk of a global trade war triggered by U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's tariff plan are threatening to extend it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-inflation-worries-tick-up-after-big-spending-budget-trump-win-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4UJMDRCRRLABBIAHREYOPUTR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道联合利华将欧洲裁员预期减半，部分员工转至冰淇淋部门--工厂委员会]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华欧洲工作委员会负责人告诉路透社，联合利华在欧洲的裁员数量将比最初预计的少约 1500 人，并将为其即将分拆的冰淇淋业务招聘约 1000 人，主要是那些受其成本削减行动影响的员工。【原文：Unilever is cutting about 1,500 fewer jobs in Europe than initially anticipated and hiring about 1,000 people, primarily those affected by its cost-cutting drive, for its soon-to-be spun off ice cream business, the head of the company's European Works Council told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-nearly-halves-expected-european-job-cuts-switching-some-staff-ice-cream-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AD5KEXTSXFNTXCR2BBIHPMWZB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国阿里巴巴季度营收不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴集团周五公布的季度销售额不及分析师预期，原因是经济不确定性持续存在，削弱了中国消费者的支出，并拖累了这家电子商务巨头的国内业务。【原文：Alibaba Group Holding missed analysts' estimates for quarterly sales on Friday, as lingering economic uncertainty sapped consumer spending in China and weighed on the e-commerce giant's domestic business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinas-alibaba-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ASQLJKRGJLYNGS2DIRYZQTM4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标美联储为大选后的宽松政策披上面纱]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBI4TJCWMFIF5EZVETVYCPEZI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小肯尼迪誓言肃清食品及药物管理局，与大药厂碰撞出火花]]></title><description><![CDATA[小罗伯特-肯尼迪希望做出的任何改变都将面临制药业的反对，而制药业为美国食品和药物管理局支付了大量费用。【原文：Any changes Robert F. Kennedy Jr. wants to make will come up against a pharmaceutical industry that pays much of the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's bills.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/rfk-jr-vow-purge-fda-sets-up-collision-with-big-pharma-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVFAWBRTMBNRBMJO6XGH7VMXLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔发出不急于降息的信号，期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）表示没有必要急于降息之后，美国股指期货周五下跌，从而推高了债券收益率，并对利率敏感的股市构成压力。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Friday after Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said there was no need to reduce interest rates in a hurry, pushing up bond yields and pressuring rate-sensitive equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-drop-powell-signals-no-hurry-rate-cuts-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USNBP753CJKXJKGOM7MRZELYYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：波士顿联储主席称 12 月降息并非 "板上钉钉]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）在接受《华尔街日报》采访时表示，12 月再次降息已经摆在桌面上，但并非 "板上钉钉"。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said in an interview with the Wall Street Journal that another rate cut in December is on the table, but it is not a "done deal".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/boston-fed-president-says-december-rate-cut-not-done-deal-wsj-reports-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4ECU7JAYBOYVJV5RC5Q5OSSTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会称美国保护主义对美欧极为有害]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲经济专员保罗-真蒂洛尼（Paolo Gentiloni）周五表示，美国贸易政策保护主义的加剧将对美国和欧洲都极为不利。【原文：Increased protectionism of U.S. trade policy would be extremely harmful to both the United States and to Europe, European Economic Commissioner Paolo Gentiloni said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/us-protectionism-would-be-extremely-harmful-us-europe-says-eu-commission-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2S6YGP6GJKTLKCSKK47YQ354U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[疫苗生产商巴伐利亚北欧公司表示，特朗普执政后美国有望增加生物防御开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[疫苗生产商巴伐利亚北欧公司首席执行官周五表示，尽管对疫苗持怀疑态度的小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：Vaccine maker Bavarian Nordic expects the incoming Trump administration to boost biodefence funding despite the nomination of Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a vaccine sceptic, as health secretary, the company's CEO said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bavarian-nordic-ceo-says-kennedy-nomination-could-fuel-vaccine-scepticism-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIHHEUZKF5LQNLCTN2OLOSMAWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:40:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 提高收购富士软的要约收购价]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司 KKR 周五表示，已将收购日本软件开发商 Fuji Soft 的要约收购价从之前的每股 8,800 日元提高到 9,451 日元（60.86 美元）。【原文：Private equity firm KKR has raised its tender offer price for the acquisition of Japanese software developer Fuji Soft to 9,451 yen ($60.86) a share from 8,800 yen previously, the Japanese company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-raises-tender-offer-price-fuji-soft-acquisition-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTSTUGN33RPMNCRGDES3EJN5O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:40:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金创十多年来最大单周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月13日的一周内，全球股票基金创下了十多年来最大的单周净购买量，原因是投资者乐观地认为，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）决定性的连任将促进企业盈利并推动美国经济增长。【原文：Global equity funds saw the largest weekly net purchases in over a decade in the week to Nov. 13, driven by investor optimism that a decisive second-term mandate for Donald Trump would bolster corporate earnings and fuel U.S. economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JH6CSPKARO7VCPNNNV4N3WPQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在特朗普回国前敲定授予台积电 66 亿美元芯片合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五表示，已敲定向台湾积体电路制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Friday it has finalized a $6.6 billion government subsidy for Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co's U.S. unit for semiconductor production in Phoenix, Arizona.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-finalizes-66-billion-chips-award-tsmc-ahead-trump-return-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEOT3RK6ANOQPKQLGHOYKZIFGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团警告特朗普的政策可能会减缓新兴市场的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团分析师预计，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最近赢得美国总统大选后，新兴市场股票的表现将逊于全球同行，尽管中国最近采取了一些政策措施，全球经济也在增长。【原文：Citigroup analysts anticipate that emerging market stocks will underperform compared to global peers following Donald Trump's recent victory in the U.S. presidential election, despite China's recent policy initiatives and global economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/citigroup-warns-trumps-policies-may-slow-growth-emerging-markets-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIX6RPY6OJJTRND7TEUQ75WF3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:59:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者围观特朗普贸易的全球市场受害者]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球大型投资者正在退出那些押注美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的税收和关税政策将提振华尔街并给海外市场造成破坏的热门交易，转而投向 11 月 5 日大选中一些最大的市场受害者。【原文：Big global investors are exiting popular trades that bet on U.S. President-elect Donald Trump’s tax and tariff policies boosting Wall Street and wreaking damage abroad and swooping in on some of the Nov. 5 election's biggest market victims.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-circle-trump-trades-global-market-victims-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UXLG5IFQJP7RMBF2LGQIP5UAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子计划回购 72 亿美元以提升股东价值]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子在周五收盘后提交的一份监管文件中表示，该公司计划在一年内回购价值 10 万亿韩元（71.7 亿美元）的股票，以提升股东价值。【原文：Samsung Electronics plans to buy back shares worth 10 trillion won ($7.17 billion) over a one-year period to boost shareholder value, it said in a regulatory filing submitted after the market closed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-electronics-plans-72-bln-buyback-boost-shareholder-value-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOA2ZTIVVFNCDLVUWFGXC75XGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：信中称，脆弱国家将在 COP29 上推动 200 亿美元的气候融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一封信显示，一些受冲突影响的国家正在COP29会议上推动将财政援助增加一倍，达到每年200多亿美元，以应对这些国家的人民所面临的自然灾害和安全危机。【原文：A group of conflict-affected countries is pushing at COP29 to double financial aid to more than $20 billion a year to combat the natural disaster and security crises facing their populations, a letter seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/fragile-countries-make-20-bln-climate-finance-push-cop29-letter-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZOICYZUGZI5TNGE2SQBIO46RE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普选择疫苗怀疑论者小肯尼迪担任美国卫生职务，制药商股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）挑选曾散布错误疫苗信息的小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：Shares in global vaccine makers and drugmakers fell on Friday after U.S. President-elect Donald Trump picked Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who has previously spread misinformation on vaccines, to lead the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/europe-vaccine-makers-fall-trump-picks-rfk-jr-lead-top-us-health-agency-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SH3VVC2ONP5HBVDHR5PK57T3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>