<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:04:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:04:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[在人工智能竞赛中，"数据基础设施 "这个不光彩的世界推动了热门科技并购市场的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[受关税和地缘政治不确定性的拖累，大多数行业的交易都放缓了脚步，只有一个行业例外，那就是并不光彩的数据基础设施领域。【原文：Weighed down by tariffs and geopolitical uncertainty, dealmaking has slowed to a crawl across most industries except one: the unglamorous world of data infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/unglamorous-world-data-infrastructure-driving-hot-tech-ma-market-ai-race-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQMKM6GGWBIPLNEVM6GXFYRXH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 16:53:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西称越南被接纳为金砖国家 "伙伴国]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西政府周五表示，越南已被正式接纳为由主要新兴经济体组成的金砖国家集团的 "伙伴国"。【原文：Brazil's government said on Friday that Vietnam has been formally admitted as a "partner country" of the BRICS group of major emerging economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/vietnam-admitted-brics-partner-country-brazil-says-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAL3WHHU3VJWDH3ZDHS37XM76A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 15:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国海关允许从部分美国工厂进口符合条件的猪肉和家禽产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国海关在其网站上发布通知称，中国已批准一些新的美国猪肉和家禽工厂出口 6 月 12 日或之后生产的合格产品。【原文：China has approved some new U.S. pork and poultry plants to export eligible products produced on or after June 12, Chinese Customs said in a notice on its website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-customs-allows-import-eligible-pork-poultry-products-some-us-plants-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WDJWCHN4RL55EMTGI5VBRNV3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 15:25:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际金融公司将为巴基斯坦 Reko Diq 铜金矿提供 4 亿美元贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据国际金融公司周五披露，该公司将为巴基斯坦 Reko Diq 铜金矿提供 4 亿美元的次级贷款。【原文：The International Finance Corporation will provide a $400 million subordinated loan for Pakistan’s Reko Diq copper-gold mine, according to an IFC disclosure on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/ifc-provide-400-million-loan-pakistans-copper-gold-reko-diq-mine-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XUR3PLT5VLD3PGGUS3SUXPHN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 15:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[担心中东出现最坏情况的投资者缩手缩脚]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者最坏的设想是中东冲突全面爆发，这使得大量资金从风险资产流出，转而投向典型的避险资产，其中美元再次居首。【原文：Investors' worst-case scenario of a full-blown Middle East conflict is coming into view, unleashing a flood of capital out of risk assets and into classic safe-havens, topped once more by the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/global-markets-investors-pix-graphic-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHSXKSQJWZPUVPH3U2QEQMSPXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 15:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe 股价下滑，投资者对人工智能的快速应用回报持怀疑态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[Adobe 的股价在周五早盘交易中下跌了 7%，原因是投资者担心该公司在软件工具中采用人工智能可能需要更长的时间才能获得回报，这给上调的年度营收预期蒙上了阴影。【原文：Adobe's shares dropped 7% in early trading on Friday as investors' concern that the company's AI adoption into its software tools could take longer to fetch returns, overshadowed a raised annual revenue forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/adobe-shares-slide-investors-skeptical-quicker-ai-adoption-returns-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAYBMEJXLFOEZJZR5QXTX4UK7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称以色列袭击伊朗后石油供应不太可能出现大的中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[两家主要银行的分析师表示，以色列对伊朗的袭击不太可能导致石油供应出现重大中断，但高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）表示，如果出现霍尔木兹海峡被封锁的最坏情况，石油价格可能会被推高到每桶 100 美元以上。【原文：Israel's attack on Iran is unlikely to cause a major disruption to oil supply, analysts at two major banks said, but a worst-case scenario involving blockades in the Strait of Hormuz could push prices above $100 per barrel, Goldman Sachs said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/big-disruption-oil-supply-unlikely-after-israels-attack-iran-say-analysts-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRQB2EIYVVMRHLXSTJZSJ5BGWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源署表示随时准备动用紧急石油库存，欧佩克认为没有必要]]></title><description><![CDATA[西方能源监管机构周五表示，如果市场在以色列袭击伊朗后出现短缺，该机构准备释放石油库存，这招致了竞争对手欧佩克（OPEC）的批评，称这一声明只会给市场带来恐慌。【原文：The West's energy watchdog said on Friday it was ready to release oil stocks should the market experience shortages following Israel's attack on Iran, drawing criticism from rival OPEC which said the statement would only create fear in the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/iea-says-it-stands-ready-tap-emergency-oil-stocks-opec-sees-no-need-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NN6S7HCL2VJKXDEPX6BHJKMX5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:25:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月消费者信心指数上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[6 月份，美国消费者情绪出现六个月来的首次好转，但这可能只是暂时的，因为以色列对伊朗发动了导弹袭击，从而提振了油价。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment improved for the first time in six months in June, but that could be temporary after Israel launched missile strikes against Iran, boosting oil prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-improves-june-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVVRO4LA6RJZFHSDLU52VL3CWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特首席执行官告诉彭博新闻社，福特在稀土磁铁供应方面遇到困难]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司首席执行官吉姆-法利（Jim Farley）周五在接受彭博新闻社采访时表示，福特汽车公司正在努力解决稀土磁铁的供应问题。【原文：Ford Motor Co is struggling with supplies of rare earth magnets, the automaker's CEO Jim Farley told Bloomberg News in an interview on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-struggles-with-supply-rare-earth-magnets-ceo-tells-bloomberg-news-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4N7PGI2ZRZI4FBYZ7PUGCYAICQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 交易后，OpenAI 将继续与 Scale AI 合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 的首席财务官莎拉-弗里尔（Sarah Friar）在巴黎举行的 VivaTech 会议上表示，在竞争对手 Meta 周五同意以 148 亿美元的价格收购人工智能初创公司 Scale AI 49% 的股份后，OpenAI 计划继续与 Scale AI 合作。【原文：OpenAI plans to continue working with Scale AI after rival Meta on Friday agreed to take a 49% stake in the artificial intelligence startup for $14.8 billion, OpenAI's CFO Sarah Friar told the VivaTech conference in Paris.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-continue-working-with-scale-ai-after-meta-deal-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSWA3QTRHJL65PV5IXNX6KDGTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁面临特朗普控制权障碍，美国钢铁股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示将对美国钢铁制造商实施 "完全控制 "后，新日铁公司的一位高管告诉日本《日经新闻》，新日铁收购美国钢铁公司的计划需要 "一定程度的管理自由 "才能进行，美国钢铁公司的股价在盘前交易中下跌。【原文：Shares of U.S. Steel dipped in premarket trading after a Nippon Steel executive told the Japanese Nikkei newspaper that its planned acquisition of the company required "a degree of management freedom" to go ahead, after President Donald Trump said he would exercise "total control" over the U.S. steelmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-steel-shares-slip-nippon-steel-faces-trumps-hurdle-over-control-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJCH4A7YE5PQTGEQSKXDRQXDJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:30:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会任命市场部门主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周五表示，杰米-塞尔维（Jamie Selway）将从 6 月 17 日起担任该机构交易与市场部主任。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday said Jamie Selway will become director of the agency's Trading and Markets division, effective June 17.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-securities-exchange-commission-names-markets-unit-chief-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7G7UCUDVPFK2TL4PTMZEWPDZQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典养老基金 AP7 将特斯拉列入黑名单，并已出售全部股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典养老基金 AP7 周五表示，它已将美国电动汽车制造商特斯拉列入黑名单并出售了所有股份，理由是特斯拉在美国侵犯了工会权利。【原文：Swedish pension fund AP7 said on Friday it has blacklisted and sold all its shares in U.S. electric vehicle maker Tesla , citing violations of union rights in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/swedish-pension-fund-ap7-blacklists-tesla-has-sold-entire-stake-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTLOMJBNPJPSBIHX2XT476TWSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法航荷航首席执行官表示对波音 787 充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，一架飞往伦敦的客机在艾哈迈达巴德坠毁，法航荷航负责人在向印度航空公司和受此次空难影响的人们表示哀悼的同时，表达了对波音787梦想飞机的信心。【原文：The head of Air France-KLM voiced confidence in the Boeing 787 Dreamliner as he expressed condolences to Air India and those affected by the deadly crash of a London-bound passenger jet in Ahmedabad on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-france-klm-ceo-voices-confidence-boeing-787-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDAEVKTWKJOFLJ2NNCRY2Z2KXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：以色列罢工打击原油市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融与市场》无任所编辑 Mike Dolan 为您解读当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：A look at what matters in U.S. and global markets today from Mike Dolan, Editor-At-Large, Finance and Markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDJTQMGZ55PFFJNFTFKCKIPO3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:49:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Meliuz 公司发行股票融资 3240 万美元，用于购买比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西金融科技公司Meliuz在周五提交的一份证券文件中称，该公司在一次后续股票发行中筹集了1.808亿雷亚尔（约合3239万美元），旨在获得购买比特币的资金。【原文：Brazilian fintech Meliuz raised 180.08 million reais ($32.39 million) in a follow-on share offering aimed at obtaining funds to purchase bitcoin, it said in a securities filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-meliuz-raises-324-million-share-offering-buy-bitcoin-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W547MR6AMBPGVPD65UX4I6FMOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:43:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于担心疾病预防控制中心新成立的疫苗顾问小组会影响 RSV 疫苗的前景，Moderna 下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五收盘前，Moderna 的股价下跌了 2.5%，原因是人们担心新成立的疾病预防控制中心顾问小组是否会支持在更广泛的年龄组中使用该公司的呼吸道合胞病毒疫苗。【原文：Moderna's shares fell 2.5% before the bell on Friday, on concerns whether a new CDC advisory panel would back the use of the company's respiratory syncytial virus vaccine in a broader age group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/moderna-falls-fears-new-cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-could-cloud-rsv-shot-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTOLTKZ53NKEZPNYFJKKVVJFFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:42:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国称不再需要谷歌的在线广告承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国反垄断监管机构称，在谷歌公司4月份决定不对第三方cookie进行独立提示后，该机构于2022年从谷歌公司获得的有关在线广告的承诺已不再需要。【原文：Britain's antitrust regulator said commitments it secured from Google in 2022 related to online advertising were no longer needed after the tech company decided against a standalone prompt for third-party cookies in April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/britain-says-googles-online-ad-commitments-no-longer-needed-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2P6PR2NVFMUDOOOZEYPYGKFKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构简化自动驾驶汽车豁免审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周五表示，它正在简化对汽车制造商提出的申请的审查，这些汽车制造商希望在没有方向盘、刹车踏板或后视镜等必要的人为控制装置的情况下部署自动驾驶汽车。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on Friday said it was streamlining reviews of requests filed by automakers seeking to deploy self-driving vehicles without required human controls like steering wheels, brake pedals or mirrors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-agency-streamlining-self-driving-car-exemption-reviews-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2FAFZWTZCFICNGJVU3ADSPPEAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:17:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家称中国太阳能产业将应对产能过剩挑战，但转机尚远]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的太阳能制造企业负责人正在努力应对亏损和对美出口关税问题，他们呼吁结束价格战，并解决该行业产能过剩的问题，但业内人士预测形势将缓慢好转。【原文：Solar manufacturing company heads in China, grappling with losses and tariffs on exports to the U.S., called for an end to a price war and a solution to overcapacity in the sector, but industry participants predict a slow turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/china-solar-industry-address-overcapacity-challenge-turnaround-far-off-experts-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULE5MIFAAVMY3CCMP3SDSBZFII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀压力降温，贸易协议前景乐观，美国股票基金流出缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至6月11日的一周内，美国股票基金创下四周来最小的单周净抛售量，原因是5月份消费者物价涨幅低于预期，以及美国与中国达成的贸易协议缓解了投资者的担忧。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed the smallest weekly net disposal in four weeks in the week through June 11 as a smaller than expected rise in consumer prices in May, and a U.S. trade deal with China, eased investor worries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-fund-outflows-ease-cooling-inflation-pressure-trade-deal-optimism-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFGJKX6JZBJGPF7MK65VRCZ32A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:43:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mediobanca 的纳格尔（Nagel）寄希望于最后的改造行动来抵御意大利竞争对手]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mediobanca 首席执行官阿尔贝托-纳格尔（Alberto Nagel）三十年前开始对该公司进行全面改革，将一家为意大利战后重建提供资金而诞生的银行转变为意大利第二大财富管理公司，该公司股东将于周一就这一改革的最后行动进行投票表决。【原文：Mediobanca shareholders will vote on Monday on the final act of an overhaul its CEO Alberto Nagel began three decades ago to turn a bank born to fund Italy Inc's postwar reconstruction, into its No. 2 wealth manager.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mediobancas-nagel-bets-final-makeover-act-fend-off-italian-rival-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKXSCVRUNJM2PBM66ESDBQNURM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:41:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管征收关税，欧盟 4 月份对美贸易顺差仍有增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的数据显示，即使在美国加征关税之后，欧盟4月份对美国的货物贸易顺差仍有所扩大，而欧盟对中国的出口则连续第九个月下降。【原文：The European Union's goods trade surplus with the United States expanded in April even after U.S. tariffs, data released on Friday showed, while the bloc's exports to China dropped for a ninth consecutive month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-trade-surplus-with-us-grows-april-despite-tariffs-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYPMJZCLC5OPPD5GG7LRCJCOCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:21:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金因偏冷的 CPI 报告和中美协议而吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至6月11日的一周里，全球股票基金四周来首次吸引到资金净流入，这主要是受到美国通胀报告向好和中美贸易协议进展的推动，尽管中东紧张局势一触即发缓和了投资者的兴趣。【原文：Global equity funds attracted net inflows for the first time in four weeks in the week through June 11, driven by a benign U.S. inflation report and developments on a U.S.-China trade deal, though simmering Middle East tension tempered investor interest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUYJMQNNVNI47G3W3TQGPITNC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD 向人工智能初创企业寻求芯片和软件设计灵感]]></title><description><![CDATA[先进微设备公司（Advanced Micro Devices）与一批人工智能初创企业建立了密切的联系，这也是该公司加强软件和打造卓越芯片设计的努力的一部分。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices has forged close ties to a batch of artificial intelligence startups as part of the company's effort to bolster its software and forge superior chip designs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/amd-turns-ai-startups-inform-chip-software-design-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKO5RVGNWNJTLGPHGM3UWE3GAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:36:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由 J.C. Flowers 支持的 Jefferson Capital 希望在美国 IPO 中获得 11 亿美元估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权投资支持的杰斐逊资本（Jefferson Capital）周五表示，该公司在美国首次公开募股的目标估值高达 11 亿美元，因为收购公司希望利用不断改善的新上市市场。【原文：Private equity-backed Jefferson Capital said on Friday it was targeting a valuation of up to $1.1 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, as buyout firms look to take advantage of an improving new listings market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/jc-flowers-backed-jefferson-capital-targets-11-billion-valuation-us-ipo-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZ4WJ7PJ6BMF5PFYJQPBWIFOV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西牛肉大亨在华尔街上市标志着从流亡中回归]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西肉类加工企业 JBS 周五开始在纽约证券交易所交易，这是约埃斯利-巴蒂斯塔和韦斯利-巴蒂斯塔兄弟在创纪录的腐败丑闻中锒铛入狱、被迫退出其全球食品帝国后不到十年时间里的一次惊人复出。【原文：Brazilian meatpacker JBS begins trading on the New York Stock Exchange on Friday, capping a stunning comeback by brothers Joesley and Wesley Batista less than a decade after they were jailed in a record-breaking corruption scandal and forced into the backseat of their global food empire.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-beef-barons-wall-street-listing-caps-return-exile-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NU5ZTQJRAROLFFRQIJASIK55DU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美联储会议成焦点，投资者寻求利率路径暗示]]></title><description><![CDATA[未来一周，投资者在权衡美国股市反弹的风险时，将重点关注美联储在对劳动力市场疲软和通胀仍高于目标的担忧之间的平衡。【原文：The Federal Reserve's balancing act between concerns about a weakening labor market and still above-target inflation will take center stage for investors in the coming week as they weigh risks to the rally in the U.S. stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-fed-meeting-focus-investors-seek-rate-path-hints-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7CIGZ2TMZJHHEGF4IAKPDAACI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税风险大于通胀数据，美联储有望维持利率稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[人们普遍预计美联储下周将维持利率稳定，投资者将重点关注央行的新预测，这些预测将显示决策者对近期疲软数据的重视程度，以及他们对尚未解决的贸易和预算问题的风险程度。【原文：The Federal Reserve is widely expected to hold interest rates steady next week, with investors focused on new central bank projections that will show how much weight policymakers are putting on recent soft data and how much risk they attach to unresolved trade and budget issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-expected-keep-rates-steady-tariff-risks-outweigh-inflation-data-2025-06-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVZAATP35ZNUBP22WR54UM6QPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>