<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:36:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:36:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[大众将从 2027 年起在阿根廷为南美市场制造 Amarok]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司周四表示，将从 2027 年起针对南美市场推出新版 Amarok 中型皮卡，这是汽车行业企业实现本地化生产的最新例证。【原文：Volkswagen is launching a new version of its Amarok mid-size pick-up truck targeted at the South American market from 2027, the carmaker said on Thursday, in the latest example of auto industry players localising production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-build-amarok-south-american-market-argentina-2027-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A2PCR7JHOZIKZKCDKJ3X4EFJOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储已掌握关税细节，现在必须权衡通胀风险与经济增长所受打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会官员曾表示，在估计唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易计划对经济的影响之前，他们需要更多的细节，而周三特朗普公布的全面关税可能会大幅重塑美国的经济前景。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve officials who've said they needed more details before estimating the economic impact of President Donald Trump's trade plans got perhaps more than they bargained for on Wednesday when he unveiled sweeping tariffs analysts say could dramatically reshuffle the country's economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/with-tariff-details-hand-fed-now-has-weigh-inflation-risks-against-blow-growth-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6S2OL53VRMEDHTS3R7QBAALME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税方案迷惑世界，惩罚穷人]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普因对主要由企鹅居住的冰冻岛屿征收贸易关税而受到讥讽，但他的征税计算公式也有严重的一面：它也对世界上一些最贫穷的国家造成了最严重的打击。【原文：Ridiculed for imposing trade tariffs on frozen islands largely inhabited by penguins, Donald Trump's formula for calculating those levies has a serious side: it is also hitting some of the world's poorest nations hardest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trumps-tariff-formula-confounds-world-punishes-poor-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKODLO7OFRKIJLHN7JTWYEYYDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:15:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税给交易和贷款需求蒙上阴影，美国银行股下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税计划引发了对资本市场疲软和消费者支出放缓的担忧，美国银行股价周四跌至数月低点。【原文：Shares of U.S. banks tumbled to multi-month lows on Thursday, after President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs plan sparked fears of weaker capital markets and a slowdown in consumer spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-stocks-sink-trumps-tariffs-cloud-dealmaking-loan-demand-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H26NFQIGDJKJJBFCYG6IO7XA44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:11:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空客领导的机构呼吁应对关税，航空航天走钢丝]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士说，法国航空航天业已致函欧盟委员会，呼吁在美国关税对这一关键出口行业造成重大损害时，采取 "适度和果断 "的反制措施。【原文：France's aerospace industry has written to the European Commission calling for "proportionate and assertive" countermeasures if U.S. tariffs cause significant damage to the key export sector, a person familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aerospace-walks-tightrope-airbus-led-body-calls-tariff-response-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QRCWGGMZRJL7CZMA6GHAYF6PE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛、百思买、耐克在亚洲的主要供应中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对美国进口产品全面征收关税的举动，可能会迫使大型零售商提高从服装、鞋类到电子产品等产品的价格，因为越南、柬埔寨和孟加拉国等供应中心正面临新的征税。【原文：President Donald Trump's move to impose sweeping tariffs on U.S. imports could force major retailers to raise prices on products ranging from apparel and footwear to electronics as supply hubs Vietnam, Cambodia and Bangladesh reel from fresh levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-best-buy-nikes-major-supply-hubs-asia-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XTEFSD7AJLKDL5CQM7FAYVCJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新兴经济体为特朗普关税 "转折点 "做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税，使美国进口商品的征税达到了百年来的最高水平，全球新兴经济体正在为货币下滑和主权信用可能恶化做准备。【原文：Emerging economies worldwide are bracing for sliding currencies and a possible deterioration of their sovereign credit after U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs brought levies on U.S. imports to their highest levels in 100 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging-economies-brace-trump-tariff-turning-point-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D44IQPUMT5JALMIRC4LWQEHLJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币高管要求国会允许稳定币支付利息，法案即将推进]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些有影响力的加密货币高管正在向国会做最后的游说，希望允许为与美元挂钩的代币支付利息，作为建立稳定币监管框架的流行立法的一部分。【原文：Some influential cryptocurrency executives are making a last-minute pitch to Congress to allow interest to be paid on U.S. dollar-pegged tokens as part of popular legislation establishing a regulatory framework for stablecoins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-execs-ask-congress-let-stablecoins-pay-interest-bill-set-advance-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXMYOVZVPBJKBB775FKRBBYYWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彪马聘请阿迪达斯销售主管为新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国运动服装集团彪马（Puma）在经历了一段时间的销售困境后，周四更换了首席执行官，阿迪达斯全球销售主管阿瑟-霍埃尔德（Arthur Hoeld）接替了阿尔内-弗罗因特（Arne Freundt）的职位，原因是该公司称其 "在战略执行方面意见不一"。【原文：German sportswear group Puma replaced its CEO on Thursday after a period of struggling sales, with Adidas global sales chief Arthur Hoeld taking over from Arne Freundt due to what the company called "differing views on strategy execution".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/puma-replaces-ceo-over-differing-views-strategy-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75WBNXV2PFLIVCTUCIXC4LW64I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农场和食品集团对特朗普关税大体持批评态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国农民和食品加工商的团体对唐纳德-特朗普总统周三宣布对进口商品全面征收关税大多持批评态度。【原文：Groups representing U.S. farmers and food processors were mostly critical of President Donald Trump's announcement on Wednesday of sweeping tariffs on imports, which have sparked threats of retaliation and which analysts say will hike prices for consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-farm-food-groups-largely-critical-trump-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFXOEKWNTZMEFDKM44646BUNYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:41:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受到特朗普关税威胁的美非贸易计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）已着手对进口到美国的大部分商品全面征收关税，其中包括受益于美国针对非洲大陆的旗舰贸易计划的非洲国家的商品。【原文：President Donald Trump has moved to impose sweeping tariffs on most goods imported to the United States, including from African countries that benefit from a U.S. flagship trade programme for the continent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/us-africa-trade-programme-under-threat-trump-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3FLBKHWGNNCNBMTFCPSFNVGDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:31:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能视频制造商 Runway 在 General Atlantic 领投的新一轮融资中获得 3.08 亿美元投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能视频初创公司Runway周四表示，它已在新一轮融资中筹集到3.08亿美元，由私募股权公司General Atlantic领投，用于扩展其新媒体生态系统。【原文：AI video startup Runway said on Thursday it had raised $308 million in a new funding round, led by private equity firm General Atlantic, to expand its new media ecosystem.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-video-maker-runway-raises-308-million-general-atlantic-led-funding-round-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQXZENSG6NOWNEKWJKG2KTPYEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司首席执行官誓言在美国生产更多汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在美国对全球汽车征收 25% 关税生效之际，沃尔沃汽车公司（Volvo Cars）新任高层周四表示，该公司将在美国生产更多汽车，同时加大区域化力度。【原文：Volvo Cars' new top executive said on Thursday the company would produce more cars in the United States while ramping up its regionalisation efforts, just as a 25% U.S. tariff on global autos takes effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-ceo-vows-produce-more-cars-us-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNSI5G5LNFLINBVT6WD3TT7Y5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西咖啡关税引发担忧，Lavazza 计划在美国扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利咖啡制造商拉瓦扎公司（Lavazza）周四表示，该公司计划继续扩大在美国市场的业务，并补充说，该公司将评估对巴西咖啡豆征收关税的潜在影响，然后再决定是否提高当地产量。【原文：Italian coffee maker Lavazza plans to press ahead with expansion in the U.S. market, it said on Thursday, adding it would assess the potential impact of tariffs on its Brazilian beans before making a decision on boosting local production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lavazza-plans-us-expansion-amid-brazil-coffee-tariff-concerns-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSRO55VR2BNW5FCYSYPMARPJWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲银行监管局称美国银行在欧洲衍生品市场 "占主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲银行管理局（European Banking Authority）周四表示，随着人们对欧洲金融业战略自主性的担忧与日俱增，非欧盟银行已经在欧洲的一些关键金融市场占据了 "主导 "地位，其中包括美国银行占主导地位的金融衍生品市场。【原文：Non-EU banks have carved out "dominant" roles in some of Europe's key financial markets, including derivatives where U.S. banks prevail, the European Banking Authority said on Thursday as concerns about the strategic autonomy of the European financial sector grow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-banks-are-dominant-european-derivatives-eba-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56GIFKZGZBOTBI2WIDQWLVAD64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联想与爱立信就国际专利纠纷达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[联想集团周四表示，它与爱立信已就全球专利交叉许可达成协议，并解决了所有未决诉讼，从而结束了一场全球范围的法律战。【原文：Lenovo said on Thursday it and Ericsson had reached an agreement on a global patent cross-licence and to settle all pending litigation, ending a worldwide legal battle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/lenovo-ericsson-settle-international-patent-dispute-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGTJKVJ3GRJJZE7GWG5UP3VASE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥宣布新关税后继续与美国对话]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普公布了不包括墨西哥在内的全面新关税之后，墨西哥与美国之间的对话与合作仍在继续。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Thursday that dialogue and cooperation remain ongoing with the United States, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled sweeping new tariffs that did not include Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-continues-dialogue-with-us-after-new-tariffs-announcement-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYW4TZQ6UFIQHE3G4RK4W4NIL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治紧张局势下汇丰银行上调金价预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行以地缘政治风险为由，将 2025 年和 2026 年的平均金价预测分别上调至每盎司 3015 美元和 2915 美元。【原文：HSBC raised its average 2025 and 2026 gold price forecast to $3,015 and $2,915 per ounce respectively, citing geopolitical risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/hsbc-raises-gold-price-forecasts-amid-geopolitical-tensions-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SE243DNEOBJZ7HJSIDCEL6WRAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢特尼克说，各国需要允许更多美国产品进入，以降低关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周四表示，特朗普政府正在与全球所有主要贸易伙伴商讨如何降低唐纳德-特朗普总统的新关税，并补充说，这些伙伴将不得不改变其规则，以允许更多美国产品进口。【原文：The Trump administration is talking to all major trading partners throughout the world about ways to bring down President Donald Trump's new tariffs, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said on Thursday, adding that they will have to change their rules to allow more imports of U.S. products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/countries-need-allow-more-us-products-bring-down-tariffs-lutnick-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LS7GA6ODWRIAZA7E5QJG6I24XQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月服务业增长几近刹车]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份，美国服务业增速放缓，创 9 个月新低、【原文：The U.S. services sector slowed to a nine-month low in March,】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-service-sector-growth-nearly-brakes-march-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSRQY43TIFNN7HIPNTO2ZBIJ5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉因贸易紧张局势下的债务风险下调中国信用评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构惠誉周四下调了中国的主权信用评级，理由是预计中国的公共财政将继续疲软，债务将迅速增加。【原文：Global ratings agency Fitch on Thursday downgraded China's sovereign credit rating, citing expectations of a continued weakening of public finances and rapidly rising debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/fitch-cuts-china-credit-rating-debt-risks-amid-trade-tensions-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CKPBLDTNFPHRPV6WHO2YIFLUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:50:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发需求担忧，咖啡和可可价格下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界可可和咖啡价格周三下跌，因为投资者担心唐纳德-特朗普总统对美国进口产品征收惩罚性关税的举动将损害世界第一大巧克力和咖啡消费国的巧克力和咖啡需求。【原文：World cocoa and coffee prices fell on Wednesday as investors fretted that President Donald Trump's move to slap punishing tariffs on U.S. imports would damage chocolate and coffee demand in the world's top consumer of the products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/coffee-cocoa-slide-trump-tariffs-spark-demand-worries-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQDSAGPLPVKXFDRPHJMXKZSCHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:49:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月贸易逆差收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 2 月份的贸易赤字有所收窄，但进口水平仍然较高，因为企业为避免关税导致价格上涨而提前采购商品，这使得贸易有望拖累第一季度的经济增长。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit narrowed in February, but the level of imports remained elevated after businesses front-loaded goods to avoid higher prices from tariffs, keeping trade on track to be a drag on economic growth in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-trade-deficit-narrows-february-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOF3EGIT3VJI5IWWR4MJZC45CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 表示将在关税宣布后临时裁员 900 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布加征关税后，公羊卡车和吉普车制造商 Stellantis NV 周四表示，将在美国五家工厂临时裁员 900 人，并暂时停止在墨西哥和加拿大一家装配厂的生产。【原文：Stellantis NV, maker of Ram trucks and Jeeps, said on Thursday it was temporarily laying off 900 workers at five U.S. facilities after President Donald Trump's tariffs were announced, and temporarily pausing production at an assembly plant in Mexico and in Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-says-will-temporarily-lay-off-900-us-workers-following-tariff-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBU3GFQA4BLYBCFOIC6ZJKSKN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:42:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国干邑行业组织呼吁缓和美国与欧盟的贸易争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[干邑行业游说团体干邑国家跨行业办公室（BNIC）主席弗洛伦特-莫里隆（Florent Morillon）说，欧盟和美国需要缓和贸易争端，而葡萄酒和烈酒则不应受到双方的影响。【原文：The European Union and the United States need to de-escalate their trade dispute and wine and spirits should be left untouched by both sides, said Florent Morillon, the president of the National Interprofessional Office of Cognac (BNIC), the cognac industry's lobby group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/french-cognac-industry-group-calls-de-escalation-us-eu-trade-dispute-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FX5MDDDCNMZRKRIURQJFCMFAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国钢铁制造商阿佩拉姆公司将寻求美国关税的潜在豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国钢铁生产商阿佩拉姆公司（Aperam）周四表示，它将与美国客户一起探索美国宣布的关税豁免可能。【原文：French steel producer Aperam said on Thursday it would explore potential exemptions from announced U.S. tariffs, along with its U.S. customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/french-steelmaker-aperam-seek-potential-exemptions-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOMXXMKS3ZLPTNVTPEDZBJTYQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对非洲小国莱索托征收最高关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[南部非洲小国莱索托被美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收 50%的互惠贸易关税，这是他一长串目标经济体名单中征税最高的一个国家。【原文：The tiny southern African kingdom of Lesotho has been hit with a 50% reciprocal trade tariff by U.S. President Donald Trump, the highest levy of any single state on his long list of target economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/trump-slaps-tiny-african-kingdom-lesotho-with-highest-tariff-all-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZFANTEUBJOTNNWZ3XH25T3APY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利预计美联储今年不会降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利周四表示，预计美国联邦储备委员会今年不会降息，原因是特朗普最新关税政策可能导致通胀水平上升。【原文：Morgan Stanley said on Thursday it expects the U.S Federal Reserve will not cut rates this year due to potential elevated inflation levels on the back of Trump's latest tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/morgan-stanley-expects-no-rate-cuts-fed-this-year-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFWQH64WEVLMBODQDPVKM2GKOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:53:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉下调中国评级至 "A]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构惠誉周四将中国的长期外币评级从 "A+"下调至 "A"，理由是预计公共财政将继续疲软，债务将迅速增加。【原文：Global ratings agency Fitch on Thursday downgraded China's long-term foreign currency rating to 'A' from 'A+', citing expectations of a continued weakening of public finances and rapidly rising debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/fitch-downgrades-chinas-rating-a-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3RDFHEDXNOZRGHMG5KB7WFT44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:51:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降，劳动力市场暂时保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数有所下降，表明在进口关税带来潜在波动之前，劳动力市场将继续保持稳定。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell last week, pointing to continued labor market stability ahead of potential volatility from import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-labor-market-stays-stable-now-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZS2CVJ5MZNNNG2MBX2MUUFX6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>