<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:04:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:04:54 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道：Alphabet 旗下谷歌裁减部分云计算部门员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司裁减了云计算部门的员工。【原文：Alphabet's Google cut employees in its cloud division, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alphabets-google-cuts-some-cloud-division-staff-bloomberg-reports-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6QON2V2V5M2LJTRPFKO572EJM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 19:23:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷油籽工会威胁在主要大豆加工厂举行罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷主要油籽工会 SOEA 的一位领导人周三表示，由于出口企业集团 Vicentin 的工资纠纷，该工会威胁要在大豆加工厂举行全国性罢工。【原文：Argentina's main oilseed union SOEA has threatened a national strike in soybean processing plants over a salary dispute at exports conglomerate Vicentin, a union leader said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentine-oilseed-union-threatens-strike-key-soy-processing-plants-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQRSQQI4XFISRDF6RMN5N24D4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 19:15:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司创始人从葡萄牙被引渡至美国，面临欺诈指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家加密货币金融服务公司的创始人已被从葡萄牙引渡到美国，他被指控参与了一个大范围的计划，代表客户公司操纵数字代币市场。【原文：The founder of a cryptocurrency financial services firm has been extradited from Portugal to face U.S. charges that he participated in a wide-ranging scheme to manipulate the market for digital tokens on behalf of client companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cryptocurrency-firm-founder-extradited-portugal-face-us-fraud-charges-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAGB44GCRVPOZAAGAASLJBDNGI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 19:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行预测第四季度铜关税将达到 25]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗银行周三在一份报告中称，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发布行政命令启动对美国进口铜的调查后，花旗预计到2025年第四季度将最终实施25%的铜关税。【原文：Citi anticipates an eventual implementation of a 25% copper-specific tariff by the fourth quarter of 2025, following U.S. President Donald Trump's executive order initiating an investigation into U.S. copper imports, the bank said in a note on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/citi-predicts-25-copper-specific-tariff-by-fourth-quarter-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ES3IWKBXBVPXJEQBPFSJGKLYSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 19:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度法院命令亚马逊在比佛利山马球俱乐部案中支付 3,900 万美元赔偿金]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度一家法院周三发布的一项命令显示，亚马逊的一个部门因侵犯 "比佛利山马球俱乐部 "商标而被勒令支付 3900 万美元的赔偿金，因为亚马逊的印度网站上销售了带有相同品牌的服装。【原文：An Indian court has ordered an Amazon unit to pay $39 million in damages for infringing the "Beverly Hills Polo Club" trademark after garments with identical branding were sold on Amazon's India website, a court order showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/india-court-orders-amazon-pay-39-million-damages-beverly-hills-polo-club-case-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKQI24N7TBOSBBXI2FQ4D2OTV4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 18:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，美国证券交易委员会通知工会员工四月中旬返回办公室]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，美国证券交易委员会已告知工会成员员工，除非他们有某些豁免，否则他们必须在四月中旬返回办公室。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has told employees who are union members they will have to return to the office in mid-April, unless they have certain exemptions, according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-tells-unionized-employees-return-office-mid-april-memo-shows-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZJQSM7CEFPY7JWEFY7R2SPK7A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 18:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[农用设备制造商迪尔的投资者拒绝接受反经济增长决议]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪尔投资者周三以压倒性多数票反对一项针对其多元化、公平和包容努力的决议，延续了股东厌恶反多元化、公平和包容措施的模式，尽管共和党对高管们施加了政治压力。【原文：Deere investors voted overwhelmingly against a resolution aimed at its diversity, equity and inclusion efforts on Wednesday, continuing a pattern of shareholder distaste for anti-DEI measures despite Republican political pressure on executives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-farm-equipment-maker-deere-reject-anti-dei-resolution-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3TVMPFXH5KGNJ5P33CROQVTXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 18:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美乌矿产协议草案的主要条款]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是乌克兰与美国之间的矿产框架协议草案的一些关键细节，路透社已对该草案 2 月 25 日的副本进行了审查。【原文：Following are some key details of a draft framework minerals agreement between Ukraine and the United States, a copy of which - dated Feb. 25 - has been reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/key-provisions-us-ukrainian-draft-minerals-deal-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2IUVKX3YLJPCLAAN4SY7A6IKIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:47:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯特兰蒂斯汽车公司董事长敦促特朗普保持墨西哥和加拿大 "免关税 "政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯特兰蒂斯面临着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺征收关税的不确定性，这可能会大幅减少其利润，而吉普车制造商已经在努力从其所谓的 "艰难 "的2024年中恢复过来。【原文：Stellantis faces uncertainty around tariffs promised by U.S. President Donald Trump that could significantly reduce its profits, while the Jeep-maker is already struggling to recover from what it called a "rough" 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chairman-automaker-stellantis-urges-trump-keep-mexico-canada-tariff-free-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DB3OC5XGZNLWVDICMFW4K36J7A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:42:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利铜业巨头 Codelco 评估大规模停电造成的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的铜生产商智利国营矿业公司 Codelco (COBRE.UL) 周三表示，该公司正在评估全国性停电对其生产的影响，恢复生产将是其主要关注点。【原文：Chile's state miner Codelco (COBRE.UL), the world's largest copper producer, said on Wednesday it was evaluating the impacts of a nationwide powercut on its production, and that recovery would be its main focus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chiles-copper-giant-codelco-evaluating-impacts-massive-power-outage-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BL62LM6UVLKLJ3K2BZFEVFRW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:41:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[倍耐力考虑在美国投资以抑制关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[轮胎制造商倍耐力（Pirelli）周三表示，将设法限制可能的关税影响，包括扩大美国的产量，同时预计2025年调整后的息税前利润率（EBIT）将达到16%左右，高于去年。【原文：Tyremaker Pirelli will seek to limit the impact of possible tariffs, including by expanding U.S. output, it said on Wednesday, while forecasting an adjusted earnings before interest and tax (EBIT) margin of around 16% for 2025, higher than last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/pirelli-works-counter-possible-tariffs-expects-16-ebit-margin-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZV2CKIHWZN7JE5PHNUIMT45OI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国审查英国对苹果公司的加密要求是否违反数据条约]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，英国要求苹果公司为其加密云存储系统建立一个后门，美国官员正在审查英国是否违反了两国之间的协议。【原文：U.S. officials are examining whether the U.K. broke agreements between the two nations with a reported demand that Apple build a backdoor into its encrypted cloud storage systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-examining-whether-uks-encryption-demand-apple-broke-data-treaty-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYQXA35KT5LHBABAR3DZUZHE3E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》舆论主管离职，版面重心转移]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》社论版编辑戴维-希普利（David Shipley）周三在给员工的一份备忘录中写道，随着《华盛顿邮报》舆论版将重点转向支持和捍卫个人自由和自由市场的主题，《华盛顿邮报》社论版编辑戴维-希普利（David Shipley）将离开该报。【原文：Washington Post editorial page editor David Shipley is leaving the paper as its opinion section shifts its focus to supporting and defending the topics of personal liberties and free markets, owner and Amazon founder Jeff Bezos wrote in a memo to staff on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/washington-post-opinion-head-leaves-paper-section-shifts-focus-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PM3B2Q6NNI6JEDU4LRMHCFTCA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[申银万国加强供应商审计，2024 年报告两起童工案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[快时尚零售商希恩（Shein）在一封信中告诉英国立法者，在对其主要位于中国的第三方制造商进行更多审计后，该公司去年在其供应商处发现了两起童工案件，与 2023 年的数字相同。【原文：Fast-fashion retailer Shein found two cases of child labour at its suppliers last year, the same number as in 2023, following more audits of its mostly China-based third-party manufacturers, the company told British lawmakers in a letter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shein-reports-two-child-labour-cases-2024-it-increased-supplier-audits-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EY2TVQOS4ZK2XDJLDWAG5RC3RE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:55:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[初创公司 PsiQuantum 称正在制造数百万量子计算芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsiQuantum 公司周三表示，它已经破解了量子计算领域的一个关键难题：即如何制造出商业上可行的机器所需的量子芯片。【原文：PsiQuantum said on Wednesday it had cracked one of the crucial challenges in quantum computing: a method to manufacture quantum chips at the volumes needed to build commercially viable machines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/startup-psiquantum-says-it-is-making-millions-quantum-computing-chips-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZPDI4DE5NO5FLSYPKA4COM5DQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:45:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债务上限担忧颠覆美联储量化紧缩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周对 1 月份政策会议的解读显示，央行行长们担心削减债券的努力可能会与围绕联邦债务上限的动态发生冲突。【原文：Expectations for the future path of the Federal Reserve's balance sheet drawdown process have been scrambled in the wake of last week's readout of January's policy meeting, which showed central bankers concerned about how the effort to shed bonds might collide with dynamics around the federal debt ceiling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-quantitative-tightening-expectations-upended-by-debt-ceiling-worries-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BK2JJRQWVKG5D3CQT4VMEPRAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟 Discovery 的 Max 将为高级用户和标准用户免费提供体育和新闻内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司（Warner Bros Discovery）周三表示，计划在其流媒体平台 Max 上向美国的标准和高级用户免费提供体育和新闻内容。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery said on Wednesday that it plans to offer sports and news content at no additional cost on its streaming platform, Max, to standard and premium subscribers in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-discoverys-max-offer-sports-news-content-no-extra-cost-premium-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MACLE2P4A5OP5CFA3GLDCHSKQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:31:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊 Prime 将独家播放纽约洋基队本赛季比赛，推动体育直播发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周三表示，在即将到来的 2025 赛季，它将在 Prime Video 服务中独家播放 21 场纽约洋基队的常规比赛，因为流媒体公司在直播体育赛事方面面临着越来越激烈的竞争。【原文：Amazon said on Wednesday it will exclusively stream 21 New York Yankees regular games on its Prime Video service for the upcoming 2025 season, as streaming companies face increasing competition to broadcast live sporting events.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/amazons-prime-exclusively-stream-new-york-yankees-season-games-amid-live-sports-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VW5OEMM2BJJEZO3SAOLLFHYRLE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛认为特朗普政策将促进美国能源和金属生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）周三在一份报告中称，美国能源和金属生产在短期内可能会因美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易和外交政策计划而受到有限的提振，但从长期来看可能会受到更大的提振。【原文：U.S. energy and metals production could see a limited boost in the short run as a result of U.S. President Donald Trump's trade and foreign policy plans, but a potentially bigger boost over the longer run, Goldman Sachs said in a note on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/goldman-sachs-sees-boost-us-energy-metal-production-trumps-policies-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDJTLER6SBMODD6HRBTBHDUKJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:50:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard 称基金董事会受托人轻松当选]]></title><description><![CDATA[顶级共同基金管理公司先锋（Vanguard）周三表示，其提名的 13 名基金托管人在股东大会上轻松当选。【原文：Top mutual fund manager Vanguard said on Wednesday that its 13 fund trustee nominees were easily elected at a shareholder meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/vanguard-says-fund-board-trustees-easily-elected-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2D2AKTCFBI2XCBTZZITQ3MY4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税阴影笼罩下，制药商在会上大肆宣扬人工智能成果]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周于印度举行的一次会议上，制药业对人工智能的采用日益增多成为讨论的主要内容，而高管们大多倾向于等待美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税威胁得到更多澄清。【原文：The rising adoption of artificial intelligence in the pharmaceutical industry dominated discussions at a conference in India this week, while executives largely preferred to wait for more clarity on U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/conference-drugmakers-tout-ai-efforts-us-tariffs-cast-shadow-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4HFXZZSANNOVNAXIWO6AIAYCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:35:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息称欧洲央行准备批准联合信贷银行对德国商业银行的投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，欧洲中央银行准备为意大利联合信贷银行增持德国商业银行股份开绿灯，此举可能为欧洲自全球金融危机以来最大的跨境银行交易铺平道路。【原文：The European Central Bank is poised to give Italy's UniCredit the green light to build up its stake in German rival Commerzbank , a person familiar with the matter told Reuters, a move that could pave the way for Europe's biggest cross-border banking deal since the global financial crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecb-poised-approve-unicredits-investment-commerzbank-source-says-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMHZR22QTZIITJHJY4WPH37UFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:16:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟批准诺基亚以 23 亿美元收购英飞朗]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周三表示，已无条件批准诺基亚以 23 亿美元收购美国光半导体和网络设备制造商英飞朗。【原文：The EU Commission on Wednesday said it had unconditionally approved the $2.3 billion acquisition of U.S. optical semiconductors and networking equipment maker Infinera by Nokia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/eu-approves-23-billion-takeover-infinera-by-nokia-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XC5EGXULYNMDXGKNT2SLMU25HA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月新屋销售大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于抵押贷款利率居高不下，潜在购房者望而却步，1 月份美国新建独户住宅的销量降幅超出预期，这是第一季度初房地产市场活动疲软的最新迹象。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell more than expected in January as persistently high mortgage rates sidelined potential buyers, the latest indication that housing market activity softened early in the first quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-sharply-january-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSTO6AGURVKUPMCARQ46SYAXSQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列监管机构称银行应帮助减轻战争受害者的经济负担]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列银行业监管机构周三要求商业银行在 2026 年前拨出多达 30 亿谢克尔（约合 8.41 亿美元）的资金，用于救济零售客户，并改善向受 16 个月战争伤害的客户提供的利息条件。【原文：Israel's banking regulator on Wednesday asked commercial banks to allocate up to 3 billion shekels ($841 million) through 2026 to fund relief for retail customers and to improve interest terms offered to clients hurt by the 16-month old war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-regulator-says-banks-should-help-ease-financial-burden-those-harmed-by-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTSRB3G5WFLW7NQX3OOSWCLPE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国可能对铜征收关税，国内产业损失惨重]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析人士称，美国可能对铜征收关税，美国工业部门将损失最大，因为在恢复国内铜矿开采和提炼的漫长过程中，成本将大幅上升。【原文：The U.S. industrial sector will have the most to lose from potential U.S. tariffs on copper, analysts say, with costs seen rising significantly during what would be a lengthy process of reviving domestic mining and refining of the metal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/potential-us-copper-tariffs-seen-costing-domestic-industry-dearly-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KFYRBQQWJP7PLM4FLIKCWLQ5Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:53:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国百威啤酒和米其林啤酒价格暂时不受关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[Anheuser-Busch InBev 首席执行官 Michel Doukeris 周三表示，铝关税在 2025 年不会对百威和 Michelob Ultra 等啤酒的美国价格产生重大影响，但可能会在晚些时候产生影响。【原文：Tariffs on aluminium should not have a major impact on the U.S. prices of beers like Budweiser and Michelob Ultra in 2025, but could at a later date, Anheuser-Busch InBev CEO Michel Doukeris said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-budweiser-michelob-prices-safe-tariff-impact-now-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJRYH3XK2FJ3ZO2MLXNJHP45NM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:41:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国电信首席执行官呼吁即将上任的德国政府和欧洲投资人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国电信（Deutsche Telekom）首席执行官周三呼吁德国即将上任的政府和欧洲在人工智能（AI）和数据中心的发展方面发挥更大的领导作用，以便与美国和亚洲竞争。【原文：The chief executive of Deutsche Telekom on Wednesday called on Germany's incoming government and Europe to take on more leadership in the development of artificial intelligence (AI) and data centres to compete with the U.S. and Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/deutsche-telekom-ceo-calls-incoming-german-government-europe-invest-ai-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55D2I5CMGNNRDJIPFLYVTL55DE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:39:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收药品关税，礼来计划投资270亿美元在美国新建工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来制药公司（Eli Lilly）周三在华盛顿举行的新闻发布会上表示，该公司计划斥资至少270亿美元在美国新建四家生产厂，以应对特朗普政府征收药品进口关税的威胁。【原文：Eli Lilly plans to spend at least $27 billion to build four new manufacturing plants in the U.S., the drugmaker said at a Washington press conference on Wednesday, as it grapples with the threat of drug import duties from the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-plans-invest-27-billion-new-us-plants-trump-threatens-pharmaceutical-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAAPVX47KNNSRG26AUACBHXVWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:38:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟促进清洁技术发展、降低能源费用的计划有哪些内容？]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周三提议提供 1,000 亿欧元（1,049.7 亿美元）用于支持欧盟制造的清洁制造业，同时采取措施降低电费。【原文：The European Commission proposed on Wednesday to make 100 billion euros ($104.97 billion) available to support EU-made clean manufacturing along with measures to lower power bills.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/whats-eus-plan-boost-clean-tech-lower-energy-bills-2025-02-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4UKCAJTRROTXBBUKNCQYT5A74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>