<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:45:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:45:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[由于石油和天然气价格下跌，道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）季度收入下降 23]]></title><description><![CDATA[道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）周四公布的第二季度盈利下降了 23%，这是这家法国石油巨头四年来的最差表现，原因是上游产量的增加未能抵消石油、天然气和精炼燃料盈利的下降。【原文：TotalEnergies reported a 23% fall in second-quarter earnings on Thursday, the French oil major's worst performance in four years, as higher upstream production failed to offset lower earnings from oil, gas, and refined fuels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/totalenergies-posts-23-drop-quarterly-income-oil-gas-prices-sag-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FP6HBBRYSFPR5NSQV4TMPLIZWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国计划建立网络出售剩余计算能力，以解决数据中心过剩问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国涌现出数千个由地方政府支持的数据中心，造成容量过剩并威胁到其生存能力之后，中国正在采取措施建立一个网络来出售计算能力，并遏制数据中心的过快增长。【原文：China is taking steps to build a network to sell computing power and curb the unwieldy growth of data centres after thousands of local government-backed centres that sprouted in the country caused a capacity glut and threatened their viability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/china-plans-network-sell-surplus-computing-power-crackdown-data-centre-glut-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTFYYHN4FZJSRKPDPCLVVLV62Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英美资源集团上半年铜和钻石产量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球矿业公司英美资源集团（Anglo American）周四报告称，由于需求持续低迷，今年上半年铜产量下降了13%，降至34.22万吨，毛坯钻石产量下降了26%。【原文：Global miner Anglo American on Thursday reported a 13% fall in copper production in the first half of the year to 342,200 metric tons, and a 26% fall in rough diamonds, as demand remains sluggish.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/anglo-americans-copper-diamond-production-falls-first-half-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BP5BTXRFXRJGDNOAJ4AH3EIHI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:14:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉业绩公布后股价下跌近 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉股价周四在欧洲早盘交易中下跌近 6%，此前埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的电动汽车制造商公布了十多年来最严重的季度销售下滑。【原文：Tesla shares fell nearly 6% in early trading in Europe on Thursday, after Elon Musk's electric vehicle maker posted its worst quarterly decline in sales in over a decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-shares-drop-almost-6-after-results-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLZSHCJXVZMYNMOAWQEIZUPRRQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：俄罗斯卢布表现优异的原因及其意义]]></title><description><![CDATA[自今年年初以来，俄罗斯卢布兑美元汇率上涨了 45%，成为全球表现最好的货币之一，但事实证明，大幅升值对受到严厉制裁的俄罗斯经济来说是一把双刃剑。【原文：The Russian rouble's 45% rise against the U.S. dollar since the start of the year has made it one of the world's best performing currencies - but the sharp appreciation is proving to be a double-edged sword for the heavily sanctioned Russian economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/why-russian-rouble-is-outperforming-what-it-means-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMMCIQ4TKNOKNIGI65JXSJUUEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:09:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[资本支出计划提振谷歌母公司 Alphabet 股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在谷歌母公司上调资本支出计划后，Alphabet 股价在周四的欧洲早盘交易中上涨了 2.5%，此前该公司的季度营收和利润均大幅超出华尔街预期。【原文：Alphabet shares rose 2.5% in early European trading on Thursday after the Google parent company raised its capital spending plans, following a strong beat of Wall Street estimates for quarterly revenue and profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/shares-google-parent-alphabet-rise-after-capex-plans-boost-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKGZKMAELNLU3BAUDGHX2QABFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：关税战期间，玩具制造商放弃电池和其他材料以节约成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[这个假期，美国的父母们可能不得不多跑一趟--不是去买玩具，而是去买给玩具供电的电池，因为在关税上涨的情况下，制造商们会减少装饰和包装，以降低成本。【原文：This holiday season, U.S. parents may have to make an extra pit stop - not for toys, but for the batteries that power them, as manufacturers pare down on frills and packaging to cut costs amid rising tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/toy-makers-nix-batteries-other-materials-save-costs-during-tariff-war-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U7UE7LS7FKTTNLITVYDO65EBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普华永道：人工智能广告将推动全球娱乐和媒体行业增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[普华永道（PwC）的数据显示，人工智能在广告中的应用日益广泛，预计到 2029 年，全球娱乐和媒体行业的收入将增至 3.5 万亿美元。【原文：Growing use of artificial intelligence in advertising is expected to boost the global entertainment and media industry's revenue to $3.5 trillion by 2029, according to PwC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ai-powered-ads-drive-growth-global-entertainment-media-industry-pwc-says-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBZ3USELERM5XCA5QUW3JDZC7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:01:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 6 月汽车销量下滑，汽车制造商困境加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲汽车制造商协会（ACEA）周四表示，6月份欧洲新车销量下降了5%以上，这反映出汽车制造商面临的全球性挑战。【原文：New car sales in Europe fell more than 5% in June, the European Automobile Manufacturers Association (ACEA) said on Thursday, in a reflection of the global challenges faced by automakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-car-sales-slump-june-automakers-woes-deepen-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4UCGPHEQZOIXJ63MC4HAMTYPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税不确定性挥之不去，企业盈利出现亮点]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括美国搜索巨头 Alphabet、韩国芯片制造商 SK Hynix 和印度 IT 服务提供商 Infosys 在内的一些世界顶级科技公司在其最新财报中提供了乐观的指导，摆脱了不确定的美国贸易政策。【原文：Some of the world's top tech firms, including U.S. search giant Alphabet, South Korean chipmaker SK Hynix and Indian IT services provider Infosys, have provided upbeat guidance in their latest earnings reports, shrugging off an uncertain U.S. trade policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bright-spots-emerge-corporate-earnings-tariff-uncertainty-lingers-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQQVHAUCR5OOZB7M3JVI562KKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:28:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商意法半导体报告第二季度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的芯片制造商之一意法半导体公司（STMicroelectronics）周四公布了第二季度亏损报告，业绩低于市场预期。【原文：STMicroelectronics , one of Europe's largest chipmakers, reported a second-quarter loss on Thursday, a performance that was worse than market expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmaker-stmicro-reports-second-quarter-loss-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6GHP4U455NBHLOTJAS2ZXJNYA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大泰克资源公司季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大矿业公司泰克资源公司（Teck Resources）周四公布的第二季度利润超出预期，这主要得益于其特雷尔运营公司（Trail Operations）盈利能力的提高。【原文：Canadian miner Teck Resources beat second-quarter profit estimates on Thursday, helped by improved profitability at its Trail Operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-teck-resources-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTCXQV67C5MQRBLB2NEIX3YPHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:20:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税影响，现代汽车第二季度利润下降 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国开始对汽车和零部件征收关税，现代汽车公司周四公布第二季度营业利润下降，同比下降 16%。【原文：Hyundai Motor posted a decline in second-quarter operating profit on Thursday, down 16% from a year earlier, as U.S. tariffs on vehicles and parts started to weigh on its bottom line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-q2-profit-falls-16-us-tariffs-weigh-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FM5RQUIS5JMC7EXWBNVH77IESU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢上半年销售增长好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司周四公布的上半年有机销售额增长好于预期，原因是这家全球最大的包装食品公司提高了价格，以应对咖啡和可可相关品类的投入成本上涨。【原文：Nestle posted better-than-expected first-half organic sales growth on Thursday as the world's biggest packaged food company raised prices to address input cost inflation in coffee and cocoa-related categories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nestle-posts-better-than-expected-h1-sales-growth-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAYCQBDMAZPDRPTO44N2VY3ZEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:13:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第二季度业绩不佳，诺基亚下半年业绩将更强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺基亚首席执行官贾斯汀-霍塔德（Justin Hotard）周四表示，诺基亚预计 2025 年下半年的业绩将强于上半年，两天前，这家网络设备制造商因美元走弱和关税问题发布了盈利预警。【原文：Nokia's expects the second half of 2025 to be stronger than the first, CEO Justin Hotard said on Thursday, two days after the network equipment maker issued a profit warning due to a weaker U.S. dollar and tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nokia-sees-stronger-second-half-after-second-quarter-miss-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXZP55GMOJJRHJJAWE236UUIQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软件公司达索系统第二季度收入增长，但不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国软件制造商达索系统公司（Dassault Systemes）周四公布，其第二季度总收入增长了 6%，略低于市场预期。【原文：French software maker Dassault Systemes reported a 6% rise in its second-quarter total revenue on Thursday, slightly below market estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/software-firm-dassault-systemes-q2-revenue-rises-misses-estimates-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AI6EYX2YIRKEBF5RIWLKCKXC6Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国寻求在关税谈判中利用特朗普对造船业的关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国政府和业界消息人士称，韩国和美国一直在讨论造船合作事宜，其中可能包括投资美国造船厂的现代化改造，以及为美国海军舰队的维修提供更多帮助，因为首尔正在寻求更好的关税条件。【原文：South Korea and the United States have been discussing a shipbuilding tie-up that could include investments to modernise U.S. shipyards and more help to repair the U.S. naval fleet as Seoul seeks better tariff terms, government and industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/south-korea-seeks-leverage-trumps-focus-shipbuilding-tariff-talks-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5TW27SI4FKL5DDKLGGCAT2AUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行第二季度利润好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管德意志银行全球投资银行部门的业绩喜忧参半，欧元升值也对其造成了冲击，但该行第二季度的利润仍好于一年前的预期。【原文：Deutsche Bank returned to a better-than-expected profit in the second quarter from a year ago despite mixed results at its global investment banking division and a hit from the jump in the euro's value.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-posts-better-than-expected-q2-profit-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNESCHMT25JRHJBAR5HLOF7JIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场震荡，中国选股者引领全球对冲基金收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[受港股反弹以及押注人工智能和 "新消费 "企业的推动，专注于中国股票的对冲基金在今年上半年取得了两位数的回报，表现优于全球同行。【原文：Hedge funds focused on Chinese equities posted double-digit returns in the first half of the year, outperforming global peers, fuelled by a rebound in Hong Kong stocks and bets on artificial intelligence and "new consumption" firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-stock-pickers-lead-global-hedge-fund-gains-markets-swing-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTDL3323EVMABOQM3NWBSC6T4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国支持 MP 材料公司后，林纳斯公司认为稀土价格将上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[稀土顶级生产商林纳斯稀土公司（Lynas Rare Earths）首席执行官表示，鉴于对西方材料的需求不断增长，稀土价格可能会进一步反弹。【原文：Prices of rare earths could rally further given growing demand for Western material, reflected in a recent deal by the United States that has shown its resolve to rebuild the sector outside China, the CEO of top producer Lynas Rare Earths said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/lynas-sees-higher-rare-earths-prices-after-us-backs-mp-materials-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5RU6ZYYCGBMG7OOFILSUPQLYSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 贸易协议再次带来欢乐时光]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWPROBDM7NKKFO72WU2IA7P5N4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：随着前景改善，高盛将放弃第二轮裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，在投行业务复苏好于预期之后，高盛决定今年不再进行第二轮基于业绩的大范围裁员。【原文：Goldman Sachs has decided not to go ahead with a second round of broad performance-based job cuts this year after a better than expected recovery in investment banking, Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-forgo-second-round-job-cuts-outlook-improves-ft-reports-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H32FSVK42VNTHNH3ABX6GOEA5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:12:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软称部分 SharePoint 黑客正在使用勒索软件]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软表示，一些参与针对美国科技巨头 SharePoint 服务器的网络间谍活动的黑客现在正在使用勒索软件，这可能是大范围间谍活动的升级。【原文：Microsoft said some of the hackers involved in the cyberespionage sweep aimed at the U.S. tech giant's SharePoint servers are now using ransomware, a potential escalation in the wide-ranging spy campaign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-says-some-sharepoint-hackers-now-using-ransomware-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4FSRDLHAZKL3NVX6YHWDZOIHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:29:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行行长：关税可能降低中期通胀风险，抑制支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰一位央行高官周四表示，虽然美国关税的全面影响仍不确定，但可能会缓解该国的中期通胀压力，尽管关税可能会抑制商业投资和家庭支出。【原文：A top New Zealand central banker said on Thursday that while the full impact of U.S. tariffs remains uncertain, they could ease medium-term inflation pressures in the country, although the tariffs might dampen business investment and household spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tariffs-may-lower-medium-term-inflation-risks-curb-spending-says-new-zealand-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQKTSLIYTFN3HG2CIV3SBLEO4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行未对失业率上升感到震惊，将逐步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚最高央行行长周四表示，由于劳动力市场只是略有缓解，因此采取有节制的渐进式宽松货币政策是合适的。【原文：Australia's top central banker said on Thursday a measured and gradual approach to monetary policy easing was appropriate as the labour market had only eased slightly, shrugging off concerns about a recent jump in the unemployment rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-not-shocked-by-jobless-rise-cut-rates-gradually-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDUANOPT2BMNRJUU7T3KSXBFJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:08:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府建议对人工智能芯片进行位置验证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周三建议实施出口管制，以核实先进人工智能芯片的位置，此举受到美国国会参众两院两党议员的称赞。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration on Wednesday recommended implementing export controls that would verify the location of advanced artificial intelligence chips, a move that was applauded by U.S. lawmakers from both parties in both houses of Congress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-administration-recommends-location-verification-ai-chips-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6D32AEO6VOVVJNJ36RZPN56ZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:23:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市和澳元因贸易和盈利乐观情绪攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对盈利和贸易的乐观情绪支撑了对高收益资产的需求，周四亚洲股市上涨，澳元创下八个月新高。【原文：Shares in Asia rallied and the Australian dollar hit an eight-month high on Thursday as optimism over earnings and trade supported demand for higher yielding assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWAILKHJT5IF3PZFCLDLSIYPDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易乐观，原油库存下降，油价攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国贸易谈判将缓解全球经济压力的乐观情绪以及美国原油库存降幅超过预期的影响，油价周四上涨。【原文：Oil prices rose on Thursday, buoyed by optimism over U.S. trade negotiations that would ease pressure on the global economy and a sharper-than-expected decline in U.S. crude inventories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-climb-us-trade-optimism-drop-crude-stockpiles-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ245XAGKBK3FNM5LDODYSJJKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德克萨斯州陪审团称 Verizon 在专利侵权案中欠款 1.75 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州马歇尔市一家联邦法院周三表示，美国电信公司威瑞森无线（Verizon Wireless）必须支付 1.75 亿美元的赔偿金，因为该公司侵犯了一位发明家与无线通信技术有关的专利权。【原文：A federal court in Marshall, Texas, said on Wednesday that U.S. telecom company Verizon Wireless must pay $175 million in damages for violating an inventor's patent rights related to wireless communications technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/verizon-owes-175-million-patent-infringement-case-texas-jury-says-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FREDVALKHJM6PKZSPQ7BO5BTOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国贸易部称美韩贸易谈判因贝森特日程安排而取消]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部周四表示，由于美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）的日程安排冲突，韩美两国高官就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）关税问题进行谈判的会谈已被取消。【原文：Talks between top South Korean and U.S. officials to negotiate over U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs have been cancelled due to a scheduling conflict for U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent, South Korea's finance ministry said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-south-korea-trade-talks-cancelled-due-bessent-schedule-ministry-says-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWR5G6VXMVI6VFCLW653SWKZXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>