<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:08:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:08:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度塔塔工厂起火后，苹果可能需要转向中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位行业观察家和一位消息人士称，塔塔集团位于印度南部的苹果 iPhone 部件工厂发生火灾，造成大面积损坏，可能会在节日销售旺季到来之前阻碍生产，迫使这家美国公司的供应商从中国或其他地方安排关键部件。【原文：Extensive damage from a fire at Tata Group's Apple iPhone component plant in southern India could hamper production ahead of a festive season sales surge, an industry watcher and a source said, forcing the U.S. firm's suppliers to arrange critical parts from China or elsewhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-may-need-turn-china-after-indian-tata-plant-fire-sources-say-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUHJ7TKWORMSPOP4XMQRCJSLAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:36:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰跻身全球十大避税天堂排行榜]]></title><description><![CDATA[税收正义网络（Tax Justice Network）是一个致力于提高税收透明度的压力组织，根据该组织的一项排名，爱尔兰已超过巴哈马，成为全球第九大避税天堂。【原文：Ireland has leapfrogged the Bahamas to become the world's ninth most significant tax haven, according to a ranking by pressure group the Tax Justice Network, which campaigns for tax transparency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ireland-edges-into-top-10-global-tax-haven-ranking-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOWAJEAQZRJTPIIFL2RERV6PAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:27:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着需求复苏，香料制造商麦考密克上调了年度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[辣酱生产商麦考密克周二发布了好于预期的第三季度财报，并上调了全年盈利预期。【原文：Hot sauce maker McCormick raised its annual earnings forecast on Tuesday after posting better-than-expected third-quarter results, banking on consumers choosing to make meals at home to curb discretionary spending amid sticky inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spice-maker-mccormick-lifts-annual-forecast-demand-recovers-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIGB64X7U5IEXC6XN3UTL2W43U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：布伦特石油交易商利用鲜为人知的规则改变美国货运路线]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为布伦特基准基础的石油货物贸易，大型能源商利用一个隐晦的条款，将美国的货物从欧洲改道，这种做法让人怀疑原油价格标记的改革是否成功。【原文：Big energy merchants trading oil cargoes that form the basis of the Brent benchmark have used an obscure clause to reroute U.S. shipments from Europe, in a practice that raises doubts over whether reforms to the crude price marker have succeeded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/brent-oil-traders-use-little-known-rule-reroute-us-cargoes-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVVEMLBHUZMGBA7II7PU3YJ6KE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员要求墨西哥当选总统解决中国汽车问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国国会约 20 名民主党议员敦促墨西哥当选总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）解决中国汽车制造商在墨西哥生产的联网汽车所带来的国家安全问题。【原文：About 20 Democrats in the U.S. Congress on Tuesday urged Mexican President-elect Claudia Sheinbaum to address national security concerns posed by internet-connected vehicles produced by Chinese automakers in Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-lawmakers-ask-mexican-president-elect-address-chinese-vehicle-concerns-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETREVO2IZNNDFJ2PHS5DKVYL5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷贫困地区出现粮食危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[在阿根廷的贫困街区，随着贫困率的上升，食品紧急状况正在形成，营养不良现象日益严重，医护人员正在治疗儿童的眼疾，甚至与缺乏维生素的饮食有关的坏血病。【原文：In Argentina's poor barrios a food emergency is taking hold as poverty rises, with malnutrition on the increase and medics treating children for eye diseases and even scurvy linked to a vitamin-deficient diet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentinas-poverty-hit-barrios-food-emergency-takes-hold-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JGAMPAYCFMB3I2OR6JLMOW5OU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车卡车部门Traton计划到2029年提高盈利能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车卡车部门Traton在本周二的资本市场日上提出了五年目标，希望从电气化转型中获益，并计划提高电池电动汽车在其销售中的份额。【原文：Volkswagen's truck unit Traton set out five-year targets during its Capital Markets Day on Tuesday, as it expects to benefit from the shift towards electrification and plans to raise the share of battery electric vehicles in its sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagens-truck-unit-traton-plans-increase-profitability-by-2029-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDFGB2TZZBKL7NK7VLATBXF3VY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉不顾罢工提高瑞典市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，北欧国家的汽车销售数据显示，尽管特斯拉在近一年的时间里一直受到劳资冲突的影响，但该公司2024年在瑞典的市场份额仍有所增长。【原文：Tesla has increased its market share in Sweden in 2024 despite a labour conflict targeting the company for almost a year, car sales data from the Nordic country showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-raises-sweden-market-share-despite-labour-strike-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VB7U7L5QAJKLLFQ2Z22YXYSZ3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:31:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CVC 支持的 Moove Lubricants 在美国 IPO 的目标估值高达 19 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由欧洲私募股权公司CVC Capital Partners支持的巴西Moove润滑油公司周二为其在美国的首次公开募股设定了高达19.4亿美元的估值目标。【原文：Brazil's Moove Lubricants, backed by European private equity firm CVC Capital Partners , set a target of up to $1.94 billion valuation on Tuesday for its U.S. initial public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/cvc-backed-moove-lubricants-targets-up-19-bln-valuation-us-ipo-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNLTOJSJHNPV5JGJEWXORK4XEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[劳动力数据公布前期指下跌；鲍威尔发出温和降息信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）回击了市场对大幅降息的预期后一天，投资者在等待劳动力市场数据之际，美国股指期货周二持平或小幅下跌。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were flat to slightly lower on Tuesday as investors awaited labor market data, a day after Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell pushed back against market expectations for outsized interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-dip-ahead-labor-data-powell-signals-modest-rate-cuts-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBYQJRSNUBLA3HDBJ67POMFGIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，波音考虑出售股票筹集至少 100 亿美元资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引熟悉相关讨论的人士的话报道称，波音公司正在考虑通过出售新股筹集至少 100 亿美元的资金。【原文：Boeing is considering raising at least $10 billion by selling new stock, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-weighs-raising-least-10-bln-selling-stock-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KR32IVXXSRIM5FNHSOWODZDUIU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:28:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子能源就燃气轮机合同案与美国达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子能源公司（Siemens Energy）同意支付 1.04 亿美元，以了结美国当局的调查。【原文：Siemens Energy has agreed to pay $104 million to settle an investigation with U.S. authorities, it said, after it used stolen trade secrets to inflate bids for contracts five years ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/siemens-energy-agrees-settlement-with-us-case-over-gas-turbine-contracts-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FE2GQ7FJRLHJBBUQN22WCINVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥央行行长表示墨西哥央行可能考虑更大幅度降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥银行行长维多利亚-罗德里格斯（Victoria Rodriguez）周一晚些时候在接受路透社采访时表示，随着拉美第二大经济体通胀降温，墨西哥银行管理委员会可能会考虑在未来更大幅度地下调基准利率。【原文：The Bank of Mexico's governing board may consider larger cuts to its benchmark interest rate going forward as inflation in Latin America's second largest economy cools, bank governor Victoria Rodriguez told Reuters in an interview late on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-mexico-may-consider-larger-rate-cuts-says-bank-governor-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOSAZAZNJ5LZPAMXWHVE73TLNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻第四季度股市创新高，欧元通胀低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N36SFGM5DBKV5IWQT3PE7WAYGE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在热情好客的内华达州，小费不是问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[克丽丝蒂-斯特雷奇（Kristie Strejc）在内华达州里诺市做了二十年的工会调酒师，她的工作稳定，可以选择最好的班次，而且与许多酒店业从业者不同的是，她的收入足以让她从两位美国总统候选人提出的免征小费联邦所得税的计划中获益。【原文：Two decades into her work as a unionized bartender in Reno, Nevada, Kristie Strejc has the comfort of job stability, her pick of the best shifts, and, unlike many in the hospitality industry, enough income that she'd actually benefit from plans floated by both U.S. presidential candidates to exempt tips from federal income tax.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/nevada-where-hospitality-rules-tipping-is-not-issue-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24PYDND2RBKAJPYRSB7XZ54QWU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Serve Robotics 与 Alphabet 旗下无人机部门合作，在得克萨斯州开展无人机送货试点]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用人行道机器人为 Uber Eats 送餐的 Serve Robotics 公司表示，它将与 Alphabet 旗下的 Wing Aviation 合作使用无人机，将作业范围扩大到 6 英里以上。【原文：Serve Robotics , which delivers food for Uber Eats using sidewalk robots, said it would partner with Alphabet-owned Wing Aviation to use drones, extending the operational range to more than six miles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/serve-robotics-ties-up-with-alphabets-unit-drone-deliveries-launching-pilot-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQZB2AEGF5NCZHWI64SDYQTYMU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度新车销量增速放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[据业内专家预测，由于通胀压力继续促使消费者不再考虑购买新车，第三季度美国汽车销量的增长速度将低于去年同期。【原文：U.S. auto sales are projected to grow at a weaker pace in the third quarter from a year earlier, according to industry experts, as inflationary headwinds continue to push consumers away from considering new vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-new-vehicle-sales-q3-seen-be-growing-weaker-pace-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVH2Z4DOM5IAXDB64CW7DSJICI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于需求不佳，Stellantis 将延长菲亚特 500 电动车的停产时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 汽车制造商周二表示，由于需求不佳，该公司将把菲亚特 500 城市电动车的停产期延长至 11 月 1 日。【原文：Stellantis will extend the suspension of production of its electric Fiat 500 city car until Nov. 1 due to poor demand, the automaker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-halt-production-electric-fiat-500-longer-due-poor-demand-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H44542OR35LIPGASSDA6JKFHXU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:58:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康称来自英伟达、谷歌和宝马的高管将在其年度论坛上发言]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约电子制造商富士康周二表示，包括英伟达（Nvidia）、谷歌（Google）和宝马（BMW）在内的公司高管将在下周举行的年度科技日论坛上发表演讲。【原文：Foxconn, the world's largest contract electronics maker, said on Tuesday that executives from companies including Nvidia , Google and BMW will speak at its annual tech day forum next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-says-execs-nvidia-google-bmw-will-speak-its-annual-forum-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRNGI4Q3RBM75GPCI4BKLBPIRA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席执行官的目标是到 2026 年重振 "问题儿童 "航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席执行官表示，作为欧洲顶级航空公司之一，汉莎比其地区性竞争对手更需要努力应对成本上升和波音飞机交货长期拖延的问题，因此汉莎航空的目标是在 2026 年之前重振其核心航空公司。【原文：Lufthansa is aiming to revive its core airline by 2026 as one of Europe's top carriers struggles more than its regional rivals with higher costs and prolonged delays in Boeing plane deliveries, its chief executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lufthansa-ceo-aims-revive-problem-child-airline-by-2026-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCUBANVI7JMBZLO52MTT6RDWIU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[采购经理人指数显示欧元区 9 月份工厂活动转差]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项调查显示，由于需求急剧下降，尽管工厂下调了价格，欧元区9月份的制造业活动仍以今年以来最快的速度下滑。【原文：Manufacturing activity across the euro zone declined at its fastest pace this year in September as demand waned sharply despite factories cutting their prices, a survey showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-september-factory-activity-took-turn-worse-pmi-shows-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JOIBVVZZ3JK5LJKH42SCS43ZHY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚飞行员工会拒绝澳航的工资提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚飞行员工会周二表示，该工会拒绝了澳航（Qantas Airways）为其短途飞行员提出的工资提案，几天前，该公司的工程师们举行了罢工，要求获得更好的薪酬待遇。【原文：The Australian pilots union said on Tuesday that it has rejected a wage proposal from Qantas Airways for its short haul pilots, days after the company's engineers went on a strike to demand a better pay deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australian-pilots-union-rejects-qantas-airways-wage-proposal-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5CWPYQEQZJ4VJJEVKDODD2QCI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:38:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞斥资 33 亿美元出售感舒雅生产商 Haleon 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家账簿管理人周二表示，辉瑞以每股 380 便士的价格出售了价值约 32.6 亿美元的海伦股份，将其在全球最大的独立消费者保健公司的持股比例降至 15%。【原文：Pfizer offloaded shares worth roughly $3.26 billion in Haleon at 380 pence apiece, cutting its stake to 15% in the world's largest standalone consumer healthcare firm, a bookrunner said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/pfizer-offloads-33-bln-stake-sensodyne-maker-haleon-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2SRGKMHVNP3XGOF2BKEDSWAOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 06:13:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公司已计划美国东海岸港口罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月 1 日，约 45,000 名工会工人在美国东海岸和海湾地区的海港罢工，在美国总统大选前几周切断了重要的贸易通道。【原文：Some 45,000 union workers walked off the job at seaports on the U.S. East and Gulf Coasts on Oct. 1, cutting off vital trade arteries just weeks ahead of the nation's presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/companies-have-planned-us-east-coast-ports-strike-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CTNPIW4EJMWRLBTBXD3PA76AY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:21:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[浏览器安全初创公司 Menlo 年经常性收入达 1 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Menlo Security 公司首席执行官 Amir Ben-Efraim 在接受采访时说，该公司的年度经常性收入 (ARR) 已超过 1 亿美元，比上一年增长了约 30%，预计到 2025 年将实现现金流正增长。【原文：Menlo Security's annual recurring revenue (ARR) has exceeded $100 million, rising by about 30% from the prior year, CEO Amir Ben-Efraim said in an interview, and expects to be cash flow positive by 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/browser-security-startup-menlo-annual-recurring-revenue-reaches-100-million-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NGQOXXK3RIULDL33AFDLZGISI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:01:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：通胀放缓为降息埋下伏笔]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2L33VBEONMLPDMFMYPZEUVG7M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 04:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国东海岸码头工人在协议最后期限过后举行罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸的码头工人预计将于周二上午举行罢工，因为午夜最后期限已过，但没有迹象表明他们与港口业主达成了新的合同协议。预计罢工将导致全国约一半的远洋运输停顿。【原文：Dockworkers on the U.S. East Coast and Gulf Coast were expected to strike on Tuesday morning after a midnight deadline passed with no sign of a new contract deal with port owners. The strike is forecast to halt about half the nation's ocean shipping.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-east-coast-dockworkers-head-toward-strike-after-deal-deadline-passes-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4OMEFUWQFOLJGTBCW5CCKX7XM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 04:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果中国摆脱对真菌的担忧，澳大利亚将成为油菜籽贸易赢家]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果中国对加拿大进口的油菜籽征收关税，澳大利亚很可能成为全球油菜籽贸易流向变化的赢家，但中国政府需要克服对真菌的担忧。【原文：Australia would be the likely winner from a shift in global canola trade flows should China impose tariffs on Canadian imports of the oilseed, but Beijing will need to overcome their worries about a fungus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australia-could-be-canola-trade-winner-if-china-gets-over-fungus-worries-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIZ2IEXZ75IJTDPQCYVLOJ5UDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 02:44:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士透露，澳大利亚央行禁止加拿大投资银行参加私人简报会]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士周二表示，澳大利亚央行已禁止加拿大全球投资银行参加机密简报会，因为该银行的一位客户泄露了一次闭门简报会的细节。【原文：Australia's central bank has barred Canada's global investment bank from confidential briefings after one of its clients leaked details from a closed door briefing, two sources aware of the decision said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-central-bank-bars-canadian-investment-bank-private-briefings-after-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PH2CWIJTUVINXOPPDAPCCTVMHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 02:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球不确定性打击亚洲工厂活动，中国刺激政策受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[民间调查显示，由于中国需求疲软和全球经济不确定性导致前景充满挑战，亚洲工厂活动在9月份有所减弱，使政策制定者面临支撑其脆弱经济的压力。【原文：Asia's factory activity weakened in September as soft Chinese demand and global economic uncertainty pointed to a challenging outlook, private surveys showed, keeping policymakers under pressure to shore up their fragile economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-economy-asias-factory-activity-hit-by-global-uncertainty-focus-china-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BA5F2M4JJFJEPA6SJYCWJ5HHDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 02:15:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>