<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:37:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:37:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，本田公司将因制动踏板问题召回超过25.9万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，本田汽车公司（Honda Motor）将在美国召回259,033辆汽车，原因是这些汽车的制动踏板存在故障，可能会偏离位置并妨碍制动，从而增加撞车或受伤的风险。【原文：Honda Motor is recalling 259,033 vehicles in the U.S. due to a faulty brake pedal that can shift out of position and hinder braking, raising the risk of crashes or injury, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-recall-over-259000-us-vehicles-over-brake-pedal-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4MCI5BI7RNQRJAEIZWVINPDD4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:19:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[能源巨头锁定东南亚，争夺更多天然气以满足人工智能电力需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源巨头正在马来西亚和印度尼西亚投入天然气勘探和生产，以满足该地区人口增长和数据中心激增带来的电力需求。【原文：Energy majors are pouring money into gas exploration and production in Malaysia and Indonesia to meet rising power demand from growing populations and a proliferation of data centres in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/energy-majors-lock-onto-southeast-asia-race-more-gas-ai-power-demand-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSM5QVAOZNI37HNKMFHIFA2BOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:14:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国央行行长称不反对基于韩元的稳定币，但有外汇方面的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国央行行长周三表示，他不反对发行韩元计价的稳定币，但对管理资本流动感到担忧。【原文：South Korea's central bank governor said on Wednesday he was not against issuing won-denominated stablecoins but had concerns about managing capital flows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bok-chief-says-he-is-not-against-won-based-stablecoins-has-forex-concerns-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5DA3745BZPJ5LT5FDQXYJ245I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 PBB 公司在结束美国业务时撤回指导意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国最大的房地产金融机构之一--德国储蓄银行（Deutsche Pfandbriefbank）周三表示，由于终止在美国的业务产生了特殊支出，该行将撤回全年业绩指引。【原文：Deutsche Pfandbriefbank , one of Germany's top property financiers, said on Wednesday that it was withdrawing its full year guidance amid extraordinary expenses from discontinuing its business in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/germanys-pbb-withdraws-guidance-it-winds-down-us-business-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPFPLMCPFFLXDMSOEMANSVMIQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国媒称中国将稳定发放剩余消费品补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[据国营媒体《证券时报》周三报道，中国将有序发放剩余的消费品以旧换新资金，目前中央政府正在指导地方政府稳妥使用这笔资金。【原文：China will issue the rest of its consumer goods trade-in funds in an orderly manner and the central government is now guiding local governments to use the funds at a stable pace, state media Securities Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/china-will-issue-remaining-consumer-goods-subsidies-stable-rate-state-media-says-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GX5RX6HK7JK2LJSK6S6WMZU4OE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:33:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[资金耗尽，中国部分城市暂停购车补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社对政府公告的审查，6 月份中国至少有六个城市和直辖市暂停了对购车者的以旧换新补贴，这可能会减缓世界第二大经济体的新车销售。【原文：At least six cities and municipalities across China have suspended trade-in subsidies for car buyers in June, according to Reuters’ review of government announcements, which could slow new car sales in the world's second-biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/some-chinese-cities-pause-car-buying-subsidies-funds-run-out-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXUX4MLFWRKAHI4D7ZP6Z5KD2U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债券投资者青睐亚洲，马来西亚创下资金流动纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[逃离美国的债券投资者正在稳定且利润丰厚的亚洲债务市场上寻找避风港，其中马来西亚是外国资金的首选目的地。【原文：Bond investors fleeing the United States are finding a haven in stable and lucrative Asian debt markets, with Malaysia leading the pack as the destination for foreign money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/malaysia-scores-record-flows-bond-investors-favour-asia-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSW2YGTKTBLINLLTZ2UAIVETPE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行的通胀警告为今年再次加息留有余地]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行在再次加息之前可能会停顿很长时间，但今年仍有采取行动的余地，因为它对可能播下过高通胀种子的不断扩大的价格压力持谨慎态度。【原文：The Bank of Japan may take a long pause before raising interest rates again, but it has still left scope for action this year by signaling caution over broadening price pressures that could sow the seeds of too-high inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bojs-inflation-warning-leaves-room-another-rate-hike-this-year-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J753P6G7F5L7LI7HASELEA7SKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石破茂离开 G7，美国贸易协议和政治前途成疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，日本首相石破茂希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）放宽危及其国家经济和政治前途的关税的努力落空，这凸显了盟国之间的鸿沟，因为更多的关税即将开始征收。【原文：Japanese premier Shigeru Ishiba's bid to get U.S. President Donald Trump to relax tariffs imperiling his country's economy and his political future fell flat this week, underlining the gulf between the allies as more levies are set to kick in.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japans-ishiba-departs-g7-with-us-trade-deal-political-future-doubt-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6AV6HDU3JK6RJWYZNA7HDZSVY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西欧人不去美国旅行，跨大西洋机票价格下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[从欧洲到美国的机票价格已降至自大流行病发生前从未有过的水平，因为西欧游客引领了赴美旅游的回潮，预计这种情况至少会持续到 7 月份。【原文：Airfares from Europe to the United States have dropped to rates not seen since before the pandemic, as travelers from Western Europe lead a pullback in travel to the U.S. that is expected to continue through at least July.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/transatlantic-airfares-slump-western-europeans-skip-us-travel-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3KR6A4M2ZMT7J2XT6LDVL7KII</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国央行称美国关税可能带来价格下行压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国央行周三表示，美国加征关税可能会对国内价格造成下行压力，因为由于华盛顿的征税，更多的中国商品可能会被运往邻国而不是美国。【原文：South Korea's central bank said on Wednesday that U.S. tariffs were likely to exert downward price pressure domestically as more Chinese goods might be sent to neighbouring countries rather than the U.S. because of Washington's levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/skorea-central-bank-says-us-tariffs-may-exert-downward-price-pressure-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTN446HLJZLJPMUUDURQG7TWVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国比特币挖矿机主导制造商在美国建立生产基地以抵御关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税战重塑了加密货币供应链，全球最畅销的三家比特币挖矿机制造商--全部来自中国--正在美国建立生产基地。【原文：The world's three best-selling makers of bitcoin mining machines - all of Chinese origin - are setting up manufacturing footholds in the United States as President Donald Trump's tariff war reshapes the cryptocurrency supply chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dominant-chinese-makers-bitcoin-mining-machines-set-up-us-production-beat-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YHICYARNNIDRKHFNOY76H66UE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 04:33:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美联储会议结果出炉前阴霾弥漫]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CQNWYH5R5LZVIBOIVZTKUPGQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 04:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司将提高派息范围，并确认指导原则]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司（Airbus）周三表示，将把股息支付率上限从目前的 30%-40% 扩大到 30%-50%。【原文：Airbus said on Wednesday that it will extend its upper range of its dividend payout to 30%-50% from the current payout ratio of 30%-40%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-raise-dividend-payout-range-confirms-guidance-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSCH4RPXEJMAVOBZYQED5PDCMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 04:23:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡金管局调查显示经济学家下调国内生产总值和通胀预期，并认为将进一步放宽政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡金融管理局（Monetary Authority of Singapore）周三对预测者进行的一项调查显示，经济学家下调了对新加坡今年经济增长和通货膨胀的预测，并预计下个月将进一步放宽货币政策。【原文：Economists have lowered their forecasts for Singapore's growth and inflation this year and are expecting a further easing of monetary policy next month, a survey of forecasters by the Monetary Authority of Singapore showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-mas-survey-shows-economists-cut-gdp-inflation-forecasts-see-more-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">65E3RS5EWBJUFNHNVT2A5R6THM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 04:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在推动多极货币体系建设中谈论数字人民币]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行行长承诺扩大数字人民币在国际上的使用，并呼吁发展多极化全球货币体系，让几种货币主导世界经济。【原文：The head of China's central bank pledged to expand the international use of the digital yuan and called for the development of a multi-polar global currency system, where several currencies dominate the world economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/chinas-central-bank-says-promote-digital-yuan-multi-polar-currency-system-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFCV4OXMHZKK5BMPTPXV7T7JSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 03:46:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地区顶级银行家称，高盛利用改革提升亚洲投资银行份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街高盛新任命的地区投资银行主管告诉路透社，高盛将在亚洲进行重大改革，以占据更大的投资银行市场份额，并抓住 "强劲的发展机遇"。【原文：Goldman Sachs will leverage a major revamp in Asia to capture a larger share of the investment banking market and capitalize on "strong tailwinds", the Wall Street bank's newly appointed regional investment banking chief told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-leveraging-revamp-boost-asia-investment-banking-share-says-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZZ47CJBKNMTVHS5DAKZKNYLBA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 03:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者在美联储会议前关注以色列与伊朗冲突，美元持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三早些时候，美元兑主要货币保持涨势，受安全需求提振，因为在美联储当天晚些时候做出利率决定之前，以色列和伊朗之间的冲突令投资者惶惶不安。【原文：The U.S. dollar held on to gains against major currencies early on Wednesday, buoyed by demand for safety as conflict between Israel and Iran kept investors on edge ahead of a Federal Reserve decision on interest rates later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-steady-investors-monitor-israel-iran-conflict-ahead-fed-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NN3IH2ZNEVPZPEIRCXZOFXKHB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 02:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东冲突愈演愈烈，市场翘首以待美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，对中东敌对行动升级的担忧仍是市场关注的焦点，导致油价上涨，投资者急于购买安全的美国国债和美元，同时抛售股票。【原文：Concerns over escalating hostilities in the Middle East stayed front and centre in markets on Wednesday, sending oil prices higher and investors rushing for the safety of U.S. Treasuries and the dollar while dumping stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYLMDUBX2NKTDB54WDE2TDWPY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[山姆-奥特曼称 Meta 为 OpenAI 员工提供了 1 亿美元奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 首席执行官山姆-阿尔特曼（Sam Altman）说，Meta 为其员工提供了 1 亿美元的奖金来招募他们，因为这家科技巨头正努力加强其人工智能战略。【原文：OpenAI CEO Sam Altman said that Meta has offered his employees bonuses of $100 million to recruit them, as the tech giant seeks to ramp up its artificial intelligence strategy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sam-altman-says-meta-offered-100-million-bonuses-openai-employees-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTCTQIIZNBM6FCS75CHP2ATLAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊朗-以色列冲突进入第六天，油价继续上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三早盘，由于担心伊朗和以色列的冲突可能会扰乱石油供应，油价在上一交易日结束时上涨了4%以上。【原文：Oil prices ticked up in early trading on Wednesday after ending the previous session up more than 4% on worries that the Iran-Israel conflict could disrupt supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-extend-rise-iran-israel-conflict-enters-sixth-day-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKMZ2XPJDRP7NISM6XWQU5X7NY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:59:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车工人联合会（UAW）主席法因（Fain）被发现在费用纠纷中对高级官员进行报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责监督美国汽车工人工会的联邦监察员发现，该工会主席肖恩-费恩（Shawn Fain）在与工会秘书兼财务主管就支出问题产生分歧后对其进行了报复。【原文：The federal monitor overseeing the United Auto Workers union has found that its president, Shawn Fain, retaliated against the union's secretary-treasurer after disagreements over spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/auto-workers-union-president-retaliated-against-top-officer-monitor-says-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWRDJ7NUKJMUJFCI7TAABRDYVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:48:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国小米将于 6 月底发布 YU7 电动 SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国科技公司小米首席执行官雷军周三在其微博上表示，小米计划于 6 月底开始接受新款 YU7 电动运动型多用途车的订单。【原文：Chinese technology company Xiaomi plans to start taking orders for its new YU7 electric sports utility vehicle at the end of June, its CEO Lei Jun said on Wednesday on his Weibo account.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/chinas-xiaomi-release-yu7-electric-suv-end-june-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLPQ2NC46BKDJI57ILBSGRLWLQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对汽车征收关税，日本出口出现 8 个月来首次下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的数据显示，日本5月份的出口额出现了八个月来的首次下降，这表明美国的全面关税正在威胁日本脆弱的经济复苏。【原文：Japan's exports fell for the first time in eight months in May, data showed on Wednesday, indicating that sweeping U.S. tariffs were threatening the country's fragile economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-exports-post-first-drop-8-months-us-tariffs-hit-autos-2025-06-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANHC74SGBRLNHGCS3PFPUO2AYE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:12:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：中国制药项目因中美紧张局势而中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士称，包括药明康德和药明生物在内的中国药物研发公司正在改变项目计划、囤积供应品并讨论在当地进行测试，以寻求缓解中美贸易紧张局势的影响。【原文：Drug research and development firms in China including WuXi AppTec and WuXi Biologics are changing project plans, stockpiling supplies and discussing testing locally, said sources with knowledge of the matter, as they seek to mitigate the impact of U.S.-China trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/china-pharma-projects-disrupted-by-sino-us-tensions-2025-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VD5SUXGY6JO35JT66DMZA2ICDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:10:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税和中国困境影响，6 月日本制造商信心下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社 Tankan 民意调查显示，6 月份日本制造商对经营状况的信心有所下降，并对未来三个月的前景表示谨慎，理由是美国关税不确定性和中国需求疲软。【原文：Japanese manufacturers grew less confident about business conditions in June and expressed caution about the outlook for the next three months, citing U.S. tariff uncertainties and weak Chinese demand, a Reuters Tankan poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japan-manufacturers-confidence-dips-june-tariffs-china-woes-2025-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33FKNCQJJZP25MBNGGIUVWJ46U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:06:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Viasat 被确认为中国 "盐台风 "网络间谍活动的受害者]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，Viasat 公司已被确认为去年总统竞选期间与中国有关的 Salt Typhoon 网络间谍行动的受害者。【原文：Viasat Inc has been identified as a victim of the Chinese-linked Salt Typhoon cyberespionage operation during last year's presidential campaign, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/viasat-identified-victim-chinese-salt-typhoon-cyberespionage-bloomberg-news-2025-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7BD4TFBVNJWVH3HXEDU7FUWWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 TC 能源公司在特拉华州关于哥伦比亚公司收购案的上诉中抹去了 1.99 亿美元的赔偿损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[特拉华州最高法院周二驳回了法官要求加拿大输油管运营商 TC Energy 支付 1.992 亿美元赔偿金的命令，该赔偿金源于其 2016 年斥资 130 亿美元收购哥伦比亚输油管集团（Columbia Pipeline Group）。【原文：Delaware's highest court on Tuesday threw out a judge's order requiring Canadian pipeline operator TC Energy to pay $199.2 million of damages stemming from its $13 billion purchase of Columbia Pipeline Group in 2016.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/canadas-tc-energy-erases-199-million-damages-loss-delaware-appeal-over-columbia-2025-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRDTJFHE5NM5PH5M5WCZWGY53A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 22:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用磨坊将从其所有美国谷物和食品中去除人工色素]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用磨坊（General Mills）周二表示，它将在 2027 年底之前从其全部美国零售产品组合中去除人工色素。【原文：General Mills said on Tuesday it would remove artificial colors from its full U.S. retail portfolio by the end of 2027.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/general-mills-remove-artificial-colors-all-its-us-cereals-foods-2025-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWG3E4FABFKV3K7DYGAYS24TVM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 22:41:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，特朗普将第三次延长 TikTok 出售期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将把中国字节跳动公司（ByteDance）剥离短视频应用 TikTok 美国资产的 6 月 19 日最后期限延长 90 天，尽管法律规定如果没有重大进展，就必须出售或关闭 TikTok。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will extend a June 19 deadline for China-based ByteDance to divest the U.S. assets of short video app TikTok by 90 days despite a law that had mandated a sale or a shutdown absent significant progress, the White House said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-will-extend-tiktok-sale-deadline-third-time-white-house-says-2025-06-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZPCA6HTMJIBZAQOHGR73S444Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 22:26:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>