<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:46:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:46:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司在指令结束罢工后恢复航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大劳资关系委员会（CIRB）根据加拿大就业部长帕蒂-哈伊杜（Patty Hajdu）的指示结束了导致 700 多个航班停飞的罢工，加拿大航空公司表示计划于周日恢复航班。【原文：Air Canada said it planned to resume flights on Sunday after the Canadian Industrial Relations Board (CIRB) acted on a directive from Canada's Jobs Minister Patty Hajdu to end the strike resulting in the suspension of more than 700 flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-canada-resume-flights-after-directive-ending-strike-2025-08-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6RD4GGDHVM6FK63WDYSJFL5HA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 08:59:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：欧盟推动保护数字规则阻碍了与美国的贸易声明]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周日报道，欧盟正试图阻止美国将目标对准该集团的数字规则，因为双方正在讨论一份延迟声明的最终细节，以正式确定上个月达成的贸易协议。【原文：The European Union is trying to prevent the United States from targeting the bloc's digital rules as both sides work through the final details of a delayed statement to formalise a trade deal reached last month, the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-push-protect-digital-rules-holds-up-trade-statement-with-us-ft-reports-2025-08-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SFR5B27MLZM7DMVUD7BW7NYSSY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与普京阿拉斯加会晤后石油市场看跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和俄罗斯领导人弗拉基米尔-普京在阿拉斯加举行了会晤，特朗普在会晤中表示，乌克兰的目标是达成全面和平协议，而不是停火。【原文：Oil markets are set for a muted price reaction when they open on Sunday after U.S. President Donald Trump's and Russian leader Vladimir Putin's meeting in Alaska, at which Trump said a fully-fledged peace deal was the aim for Ukraine rather than a ceasefire.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-markets-seen-bearish-after-trump-putin-alaska-meeting-2025-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LT3BIATLZBIQRHMJTD7WXW5JNA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:46:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加航机舱员工罢工，数百航班停飞]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与加拿大最大航空公司的合同谈判陷入僵局后，加拿大航空公司的工会空乘人员于周六清晨离开了工作岗位，此举可能会打乱十多万乘客的旅行计划。【原文：Air Canada's unionized flight attendants walked off the job early on Saturday morning after contract talks with the country's largest carrier stalled, in a move that could disrupt travel plans for more than 100,000 passengers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-canada-cabin-staff-go-strike-grounding-hundreds-flights-2025-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWJN4V6XTJIH5KU76AC4UNBH2E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示没有惩罚中国购买俄罗斯石油的迫切计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他不需要立即考虑对中国等购买俄罗斯石油的国家征收报复性关税，但 "两三周后 "可能不得不这样做。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he did not immediately need to consider retaliatory tariffs on countries such as China for buying Russian oil but might have to "in two or three weeks."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-says-no-imminent-plans-penalize-china-buying-russian-oil-2025-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZHS6XTNGROZZBUKFAGSWVK3TE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 02:24:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大劳工部长敦促加航与工会加紧谈判解决争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大劳工部长帕蒂-哈伊杜（Patty Hajdu）周五表示，她与加拿大航空公司和加拿大公共雇员工会（CUPE）举行了联合会议，敦促双方更加努力地工作，继续留在谈判桌上，以达成协议，避免可能发生的罢工。【原文：Canadian Labor Minister Patty Hajdu said on Friday that she met jointly with Air Canada and the Canadian Union of Public Employees (CUPE), urging both sides to work harder and remain at the negotiating table to reach a deal and avert a potential strike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/canada-labor-minister-presses-air-canada-union-intensify-talks-resolve-dispute-2025-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5EKXKBFRBKTPOU6Q2ONLGX7YA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:32:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对美俄峰会未达成协议的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他和俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔-普京在阿拉斯加举行了近三个小时的峰会，但没有就解决莫斯科的乌克兰战争达成协议，不过他认为这次会议 "非常有成效"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday that he and Russian President Vladimir Putin did not reach an agreement to resolve Moscow's war in Ukraine after a nearly three-hour summit in Alaska, though he characterized the meeting as "very productive."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/investors-react-us-russia-summit-reaching-no-deal-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGSLUSVDOBM3LHYHXCUXUEV62Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:52:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部扩大征收钢铝关税的产品范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周五扩大了对进口钢铁和铝征收 50%关税的范围，将数百种衍生产品列入征税商品清单。【原文：The Trump administration on Friday widened the reach of its 50% tariffs on steel and aluminum imports by adding hundreds of derivative products to the list of goods subject to the levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-commerce-dept-widens-products-subject-steel-aluminum-tariffs-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMEPVJ2MYFNZXMJNIQ2GB3BFZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:41:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利：今年或多或少宜降息两次]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）在经济报告显示上月零售销售强于预期、批发价格意外跳涨之后接受采访时表示，她仍然支持最快在下个月开始放宽政策。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly, in an interview following economic reports showing stronger-than-expected retail sales and an unexpected jump in wholesale prices last month, signaled that she is still on board for beginning to ease policy as soon as next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-two-rate-cuts-more-or-less-appropriate-this-year-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIGHFBZTY5JW7NLVDAULALHGJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，Meta 计划在六个月内对人工智能工作进行第四次重组]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周五援引三位知情人士的话报道，Meta 公司正计划在六个月内对人工智能工作进行第四次全面改革。【原文：Meta is planning its fourth overhaul of artificial intelligence efforts in six months, The Information reported on Friday, citing three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-plans-fourth-restructuring-ai-efforts-six-months-information-reports-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3HX5GAIP5N75LHPWZFQW2LJLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 22:34:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢拉在中国工厂开业典礼上表示，巴西对企业敞开大门]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦周五在中国汽车制造商广汽传祺位于圣保罗州的工厂开业典礼上表示，欢迎外国公司来巴西开展业务。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Friday that foreign companies that want to do business in Brazil are welcome, speaking at the opening ceremony for a factory for Chinese automaker GWM in the state of Sao Paulo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/brazil-is-open-business-lula-says-chinese-factory-opening-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WGJTMIBW5PGBBOCREDSSYXV6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 22:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉将美国精神航空的评级进一步下调至垃圾级]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉评级公司周五将精神航空的长期信用评级从 "CCC+"下调至 "CCC-"，理由是近期违约的可能性很高。【原文：Fitch Ratings on Friday downgraded Spirit Airlines long-term credit rating to 'CCC-' from 'CCC+', citing a high likelihood of near-term default.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fitch-cuts-spirit-airlines-rating-further-into-junk-territory-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNAQGLFGTJJH5II2AQECGSSV7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:59:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司克莱顿工厂因煤气阀门故障发生致命爆炸]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司周五称，其位于匹兹堡附近的克莱顿焦化厂在计划检修前冲洗煤气阀门时发生致命爆炸，造成两人死亡，10 人受伤。【原文：United States Steel said on Friday a fatal blast that killed two and injured 10 others at its Clairton Coke Works plant near Pittsburgh happened when flushing a gas valve, ahead of scheduled maintenance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-steels-deadly-clairton-plant-blast-caused-by-gas-valve-failure-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WKM5LG7F5OK5G5DCCBYBEDT5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:53:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，OpenAI 员工将向软银和其他投资者出售 60 亿美元股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，OpenAI 的现任和前任员工正寻求向由软银集团（SoftBank Group）等组成的投资集团出售价值近 60 亿美元的 ChatGPT 制造商股票，估值达 5000 亿美元。【原文：Present and former OpenAI employees are looking to sell nearly $6 billion worth of the ChatGPT maker's shares to an investor group comprising SoftBank Group , among others, valuing it at $500 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/openai-staffers-sell-6-billion-stock-softbank-other-investors-bloomberg-news-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZPU424FRVOLRGE6UBYVABWYM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6 月份外国持有的美国国债攀升至创纪录的 9.13 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五公布的数据显示，6月份外国持有的美国国债增至创纪录水平，连续第四个月超过9万亿美元。【原文：Foreign holdings of U.S. Treasuries rose to record levels in June, topping $9 trillion for a fourth straight month, data from the Treasury Department showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/foreign-holdings-us-treasuries-climb-record-913-trillion-june-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3Z6ZVRTONMTNBYP6TUQUJKEGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:21:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币交易所双子座公开美国首次公开募股申请文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[由亿万富翁双胞胎泰勒-温克莱沃斯（Tyler Winklevoss）和卡梅隆-温克莱沃斯（Cameron Winklevoss）创办的加密货币交易所双子星（Gemini）周五公布了其在美国首次公开募股的文件，加入了数字资产公司寻求进入公开市场的浪潮。【原文：Cryptocurrency exchange Gemini, founded by billionaire twins Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, on Friday made public its paperwork for a U.S. initial public offering, joining a wave of digital asset companies seeking to tap public markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/crypto-exchange-gemini-makes-us-ipo-filing-public-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBOO6JM2SNKP7HBEOHVDXM6QFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院批准阿根廷搁置 YPF 股份交易的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周五批准了阿根廷的请求，暂时搁置了法官要求阿根廷交出其在油气公司 YPF 51% 的股份以部分履行两名投资者赢得的 161 亿美元判决的命令。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Friday granted Argentina's request to put on temporary hold a judge's order that it turn over its 51% stake in oil and gas company YPF to partially satisfy a $16.1 billion judgment won by two investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-appeals-court-grants-argentina-request-put-ypf-share-turnover-hold-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDH4RSERPRNGNDKGKY4WFI4EIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 20:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国委员会敦促拉美实现市场多元化以应对特朗普的关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国拉丁美洲委员会主席何塞-曼努埃尔-萨拉萨尔（Jose Manuel Salazar）敦促该地区各国实现进出口市场多样化，并实现经济一体化，以应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税。【原文：The head of the U.N. commission on Latin America, Jose Manuel Salazar, urged the region's countries to diversify their export and import markets and to integrate their economies in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/un-commission-urges-latin-america-diversify-markets-confront-trumps-tariffs-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PX3MBNM2BZPKHH24QBBK3ECHQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 20:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯法令为埃克森重返萨哈林 1 号项目打开大门]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔-普京（Vladimir Putin）周五签署了一项法令，允许包括美国顶级石油巨头埃克森美孚（Exxon Mobil）在内的外国投资者重新获得萨哈林-1 号油气项目的股份。【原文：Russian President Vladimir Putin on Friday signed a decree that could allow foreign investors, including top U.S. oil major Exxon Mobil , to regain shares in the Sakhalin-1 oil and gas project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russia-decree-opens-door-exxon-return-sakhalin-1-project-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXA5BBI7PVIGPAVWVOGG5EFR2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 20:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府公布更严格的风能和太阳能项目补贴规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五公布了关于太阳能和风能项目如何获得联邦税收补贴的更严格规定，唐纳德-特朗普总统的新税收和支出法将在未来两年内逐步取消联邦税收补贴。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department on Friday unveiled stricter rules for how solar and wind projects can qualify for federal tax subsidies that President Donald Trump's new tax and spending law is phasing out over the next two years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trump-administration-unveils-stricter-subsidy-rules-wind-solar-projects-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKL3EB4D3BK4NISIBLOP2XVODM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:22:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比：希望在通胀方面得到更多保证，以便在 9 月或秋季降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，如果新的数据令人欣慰，他将支持在9月份降息，但最近的报告显示服务业通胀上升，这让他在关税带来的 "滞胀 "冲动面前有些犹豫。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve Bank President Austan Goolsbee on Friday left the door open to supporting an interest-rate cut in September should fresh data prove reassuring, but said recent reports showing a rise in services inflation give him some pause amid what he calls the "stagflationary" impulse from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-want-more-assurance-inflation-cut-sept-or-autumn-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TB3XDI3DARIJXGVQXLMYTW5TDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:15:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家新闻美国酝酿在峰会前使用俄罗斯破冰船开发天然气--消息人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，美国已就使用俄罗斯核动力破冰船支持阿拉斯加天然气和液化天然气项目的开发进行了内部讨论，并将此作为唐纳德-特朗普总统周五会见弗拉基米尔-普京时可能达成的交易目标之一。【原文：The United States has had internal discussions on using Russian nuclear-powered icebreaker vessels to support the development of gas and LNG projects in Alaska as one of the possible deals to aim for when President Donald Trump meets Vladimir Putin on Friday, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-mulled-use-russia-icebreakers-gas-development-ahead-summit-sources-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUDTUQLF7BP2LGPA75Q6PN36L4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员霍利对 Meta 公司的人工智能政策展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员乔希-霍利（Josh Hawley）周五对 Facebook 母公司 Meta Platforms 的人工智能政策发起调查，要求提供有关允许其人工智能聊天机器人 "与儿童进行浪漫或感性对话 "的规则的文件。【原文：U.S. Senator Josh Hawley launched a probe into Facebook parent Meta Platforms' artificial intelligence policies on Friday, demanding documents on rules that had allowed its artificial intelligence chatbots to “engage a child in conversations that are romantic or sensual.”】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senator-hawley-launches-probe-into-meta-ai-policies-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVGJ335YABLB7D67OUEGDPH52M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:47:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称加拿大总理卡尼计划 9 月访问墨西哥]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士周五表示，加拿大总理马克-卡尼计划于9月18日访问墨西哥，与墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢恩鲍姆会面，讨论在美国加征关税的情况下加强两国关系的问题。【原文：Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney is planning to visit Mexico on September 18 to meet with President Claudia Sheinbaum and discuss closer ties amid U.S. tariffs, a person familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadian-pm-carney-planning-visit-mexico-september-says-source-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7GT5F7AUBKT5P64Q7W4X4N27A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:38:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[民主党人谴责五角大楼暂停已接近完成的 8 亿美元软件项目的举动]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三报道称，海军和空军准备取消价值超过 8 亿美元、几乎已经完成的软件项目，民主党人将矛头指向特朗普政府。【原文：Democrats took aim at the Trump administration after Reuters reported on Wednesday that the Navy and Air Force were poised to cancel nearly completed software projects worth over $800 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democrats-decry-move-by-pentagon-pause-800-million-nearly-done-software-projects-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DONK6Q3WFK2TM7HUJLCPEYBGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰战争爆发后俄罗斯能源出口中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将于周五会见俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔-普京（Vladimir Putin），他鼓励普京在乌克兰停火问题上取得进展的筹码之一将是放松美国对俄罗斯能源产业和出口的制裁。【原文：When U.S. President Donald Trump meets Russian President Vladimir Putin on Friday, one of his bargaining chips to encourage Putin to make progress toward a ceasefire in Ukraine will be to ease U.S. sanctions on Russia's energy industry and exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russian-energy-export-disruptions-since-start-ukraine-war-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKAEEOXALZIDDGEQ7AKSRKLRQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:30:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工程服务公司 Legence 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[工程与维护服务供应商 Legence 周五表示，该公司已申请在美国进行首次公开募股。【原文：Engineering and maintenance service provider Legence said on Friday it had filed for an initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/engineering-service-firm-legence-files-us-ipo-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXB2V573FJMJNGJ3HQSRVSF4UI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 17:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管降息概率降低，但预计 9 月美国企业债券市场仍将繁忙]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家和策略师们表示，尽管国债收益率波动加大，但由于近期数据显示通胀依然疲软，美联储大幅降息的希望变得渺茫，因此公司发行的美元债券可能会使 9 月份成为今年投资级债券供应量最大的月份之一。【原文：Companies' U.S. dollar bond issuance will likely carry September to one of the heaviest months for investment-grade supply this year, despite more volatility in Treasury yields as hopes for a bigger Federal Reserve interest rate cut were dimmed by recent data that pointed to still-sticky inflation, said bankers and strategists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/busy-september-us-corporate-bond-market-expected-despite-lower-rate-cut-odds-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RQKF272XGVJFRJ7RS2NZQYCCCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 17:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据中心业主敦促美国财政部保留可再生能源补贴规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表包括谷歌、亚马逊和微软在内的数据中心所有者的数据中心联盟呼吁美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）维护现有的风能和太阳能补贴规则，称这些规则使风能和太阳能产业得以快速发展，并在来自中国的竞争中保持领先。【原文：The Data Center Coalition, which represents data center owners including Google, Amazon and Microsoft , called on U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent to uphold existing rules for wind and solar energy subsidies, saying they have enabled the industry to grow quickly and stay ahead of competition from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/data-center-owners-urge-us-treasury-keep-renewable-energy-subsidy-rules-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GHNYBUMOW5IMPG7WZ2WHNX46VE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 17:39:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界经济论坛任命贝莱德的拉里-芬克和罗氏的安德烈-霍夫曼为临时联合主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界经济论坛周五表示，已任命贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）和罗氏控股公司副董事长安德烈-霍夫曼（André Hoffmann）为论坛董事会临时联席主席。【原文：The World Economic Forum said on Friday it has appointed BlackRock CEO Larry Fink and Roche Holding's Vice-Chair André Hoffmann as interim co-chairs of its board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-economic-forum-names-blackrocks-larry-fink-roches-andre-hoffmann-interim-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBL2ST3WQBKLDPNKEUIKKDVOZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 17:16:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>