<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:35:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:35:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[AEP 和 Transource 将投资 17 亿美元进行电网升级，以满足不断增长的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电力公司（AEP）周四表示，美国电力公司及其输电关联公司 Transource Energy LLC 将投资约 17 亿美元用于输电系统升级，以提高可靠性和输送更多电力，满足日益增长的需求。【原文：American Electric Power and its transmission affiliate Transource Energy LLC will invest approximately $1.7 billion in transmission system upgrades to improve reliability and deliver more power to meet growing demand, AEP said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/aep-transource-invest-17-billion-power-grid-upgrades-meet-rising-demand-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SJCDYBT6RM4LPDF5VNKSDX2IE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:19:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈克表示支持维持政策利率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联邦储备银行行长帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）周四表示，支持继续将美国短期借贷成本维持在目前的4.25%-4.50%之间，他认为这一水平将有助于通胀率回落至美联储2%的目标，但不会损害就业市场或更广泛的经济。【原文：Philadelphia Federal Reserve Bank President Patrick Harker on Thursday expressed support for continuing to hold short-term U.S. borrowing costs in their current range of 4.25%-4.50%, a level he believes will help get inflation back down to the Fed's 2% target but isn't hurting the job market or the economy more generally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-harker-expresses-support-keeping-policy-rate-hold-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVITLI4PJFLNFF64FC4BLWHIIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 AAA 信用评级不受美国关税影响；各省面临的风险更大]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和经济学家表示，加拿大享有两家顶级评级机构的 AAA 主权评级，其财政可以承受美国的关税浪潮，但如果贸易战持续，加拿大的一些省份可能会受到评级打击。【原文：Canada enjoys AAA sovereign ratings from two top rating agencies and its finances could withstand a wave of U.S. tariffs, but some of its provinces could take a ratings hit if a trade war persists, analysts and economists said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-aaa-credit-ratings-are-safe-us-tariffs-provinces-more-risk-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GAYAUDNNVK7LNJGXL7MNMEEJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:50:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数字权利活动人士在欧洲就 Meta 的定向广告提出投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Eko 集团周四表示，网络权利活动人士已就美国软件公司 Meta 的定向广告行为向多个欧洲国家的数据保护机构提出投诉。【原文：Online rights activists have filed complaints with data protection authorities in several European countries about U.S. software firm Meta's targeted advertising practices, the Eko group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/digital-rights-activists-file-complaints-europe-over-metas-targeted-ads-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PONYQRK3CFKG7L6YR36PXEDTBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥官员分析采取更多措施打击低成本货运]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥一位官员周四表示，在对主要来自中国的所谓 "微量 "采购征收关税后，墨西哥正在权衡进一步的贸易措施，以打击低成本货物进入该国。【原文：Mexico is weighing further trade measures to crack down on low-cost shipments into the country, an official said on Thursday, after slapping tariffs on so-called "de minimis" purchases largely coming from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mexico-analyzing-more-measures-crack-down-low-cost-shipments-official-says-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMP4FEC32JJO3A5WLP3Z3D7SNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道T.Rowe和Columbia Threadneedle反击一些高收益债务保荐人]]></title><description><![CDATA[资产管理公司T. Rowe Price和Columbia Threadneedle正在对私募股权公司进行反击，这些公司在过去两年中积极举债，损害了高收益债投资者的利益。【原文：Asset managers T. Rowe Price and Columbia Threadneedle are pushing back against private equity firms that pursued aggressive debt raises in a practice that hurt high-yield debt investors over the past two years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/t-rowe-columbia-threadneedle-push-back-against-some-high-yield-debt-sponsors-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3XMUXV64RKUPI6GUAB372VAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:26:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[何塞-库尔沃龙舌兰酒制造商警告特朗普可能征收关税，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥何塞-库尔沃龙舌兰酒制造商贝克公司周四警告说，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下月威胁对墨西哥产品加征关税，该公司今年可能面临8000万美元的损失。【原文：Mexico's Becle , the maker of Jose Cuervo tequila, warned on Thursday that it could face an $80 million impact this year if U.S. President Donald Trump goes through with his threat of imposing tariffs next month on Mexican products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/jose-cuervo-tequila-maker-warns-potential-trump-tariffs-hit-shares-fall-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O75A5H257FLCLLGX36L55SNJNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:18:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥沃尔玛准备推出借记卡服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛墨西哥和中美洲分部的一位高管周四表示，沃尔玛正准备推出借记卡服务。【原文：Walmart's Mexico and Central America unit is preparing to launch its debit card service, an executive said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/walmart-mexico-readies-launch-debit-card-service-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXQRFVULNJNP5F63IXHPPQPUHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院驳回海康威视要求解除 FCC 设备审批禁令的申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周四驳回了海康威视提出的解除联邦通信委员会 2022 年对中国制造商生产的新视频监控和电信设备审批禁令的请求。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Thursday rejected a bid by Hikvision to lift a 2022 bar by the Federal Communications Commission on approvals of new video surveillance and telecommunications equipment produced by the Chinese manufacturer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-court-rejects-hikvision-bid-lift-fcc-ban-equipment-approvals-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I54XQ5Y2BVPVZHMGDGE7YENGMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:13:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Meta 正在洽谈由 Apollo 领投的 350 亿美元数据中心融资项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，阿波罗全球管理公司（Apollo Global Management）正在洽谈牵头为 Meta Platforms 公司提供约 350 亿美元的一揽子融资计划，以帮助该公司在美国开发数据中心。【原文：Apollo Global Management is in talks to lead a roughly $35 billion financing package for Meta Platforms to help develop data centers in the U.S., Bloomberg News reported on Thursday citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-talks-raise-35-billion-data-center-financing-led-by-apollo-bloomberg-news-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUH2TH6UXFKERG2737RC745UY4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:23:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席哈马克称利率可能会维持一段时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周四表示，她预计美国央行将暂时搁置利率政策，以寻找通胀压力正在缓解并回到2%目标的证据。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack said on Thursday she expects U.S. central bank interest rate policy is on hold for the time being amid a hunt for evidence that inflation pressures are easing back to the 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-hammack-says-rates-likely-hold-some-time-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHRRMMBCVBPMTISRP5XLUGM25I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特斯拉正在寻求批准在加州提供叫车服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，特斯拉正在寻求批准在加利福尼亚州提供叫车服务，这是埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的公司在其传统汽车销售业务摇摇欲坠时开始承载付费客户的关键一步。【原文：Tesla is seeking approval to offer ride-hailing services in California, a key step by Elon Musk's company to begin carrying paying customers while its traditional car-selling business falters, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-seeking-approval-offer-ride-hailing-services-california-bloomberg-news-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YB6QH6F32FLX7D7V2H7OZIFXKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，制裁和关税令欧佩克+对四月石油涨价犹豫不决]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+组织的八位消息人士称，由于美国对委内瑞拉、伊朗和俄罗斯实施了新的制裁，欧佩克+组织的成员国正在努力解读全球供应形势，因此欧佩克+组织正在争论是按计划提高四月份的石油产量，还是冻结产量。【原文：OPEC+ is debating whether to raise oil output in April as planned or freeze it as its members struggle to read the global supply picture because of fresh U.S. sanctions on Venezuela, Iran and Russia, eight OPEC+ sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/sanctions-tariffs-make-opec-hesitant-april-oil-hike-sources-say-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6XESFF3INOKPEWXTOTUW7SPYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:47:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦储蓄委员会驳回针对伯克希尔公司高风险住房贷款的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）驳回了指控沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下的范德比尔特抵押贷款与金融公司（Vanderbilt Mortgage and Finance）向借款人发放他们无力负担的贷款，以购买伯克希尔旗下克莱顿住宅公司（Clayton Homes）的房屋的诉讼。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau dismissed its lawsuit accusing Vanderbilt Mortgage and Finance, a unit of Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway , of driving borrowers into loans they could not afford to buy homes from Berkshire's Clayton Homes unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-cfpb-dismisses-lawsuit-against-berkshire-unit-over-risky-home-loans-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCWUY2W5C5KAXDZEEARLPE6JQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普取消石油开采许可证可能加剧委内瑞拉通货膨胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）取消了外国石油公司在受制裁的委内瑞拉的经营许可，这将减少该国外汇市场上的美元供应，从而刺激当地玻利瓦尔货币贬值和物价上涨。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's cancellation of licenses for foreign oil companies to operate in sanctioned Venezuela will reduce the dollars on offer in the country's exchange market, stoking depreciation of the local bolivar currency and prices, analysts said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-cancellation-oil-licenses-likely-stoke-venezuela-inflation-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3BRX2RJYBLJBDVLQX3H6E7WUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:37:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前商务部官员表示，将对违反出口规定的公司处以巨额罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据上月离职的一位美国商务部高级官员称，美国商务部可能在未来几个月内对一些大公司处以巨额罚款，这些公司的违法行为包括非法向中国客户运送技术。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department is likely to impose hefty fines on some large companies in the coming months for offenses such as illegally shipping technology to customers in China, according to a top department official who left last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/big-fines-coming-companies-with-export-violations-says-ex-commerce-official-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGCMNNZ74FJETCUVNFLADLS7QY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉巴纳品牌所有者 Puig 成为上市公司的第一年，利润就增长了 14]]></title><description><![CDATA[香水品牌拉巴纳（Rabanne）、卡罗琳娜-赫雷拉（Carolina Herrera）和让-保罗-高缇耶（Jean Paul Gaultier）背后的西班牙美容公司普伊格（Puig）周四公布，2024 年净利润增长 14%，略低于分析师对其作为上市公司第一年业绩的预期。【原文：Puig , the Spanish beauty company behind perfume brands Rabanne, Carolina Herrera and Jean Paul Gaultier, reported a 14% rise in 2024 net profit on Thursday, slightly missing analyst expectations in its first year as a listed company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/rabanne-owner-puigs-profit-rises-14-first-year-listed-company-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DX46VMHAEFPSLP6KONY2FE2KDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:07:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[格鲁吉亚在街头抗议镇压中购买以色列数据提取技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[采购文件显示，格鲁吉亚已着手与以色列技术公司 Cellebrite DI 有限公司续签合同，购买用于从移动设备中提取数据的软件，因为该国正在努力应对持续不断的反政府街头抗议活动。【原文：Georgia has moved to renew contracts with Israeli technology firm Cellebrite DI Ltd for software used to extract data from mobile devices, procurement documents show, as the country grapples with ongoing anti-government street protests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/georgia-purchase-israeli-data-extraction-tech-amid-street-protest-crackdown-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGFQD3MWYBNOBJA5IK5N5CHXDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:06:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Teleperformance 经过一年的整合后，收入增长加速]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国 Teleperformance 呼叫中心和办公服务集团周四表示，得益于两次收购和人工智能合作伙伴关系的整合，该公司预计今年的销售额将加速增长，此前该公司 2024 年的收入超过了市场预期。【原文：France's Teleperformance expects faster sales growth this year thanks to the consolidation of two acquisitions and AI partnerships, the call centre and office services group said on Thursday, after beating market expectations for 2024 revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/teleperformance-sees-revenue-growth-acceleration-after-year-consolidation-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJSVQZRWZFPZFBQWXVVCJOYGPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:55:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部提名人称台积电为华为制造芯片的报道 "令人严重关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提名的负责监督中国出口政策的职位人选周四称，有关台湾半导体制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co）为华为生产数十万颗芯片的报道 "非常令人担忧"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's nominee to a post overseeing export policy for China on Thursday called a report about Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co producing hundreds of thousands of chips for Huawei "a huge concern."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/report-tsmc-chips-made-huawei-huge-concern-us-commerce-nominee-says-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSYZIQZPPJPDPBSO7YRESXFOYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:53:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[缪西娅-普拉达称 "所有人 "都有意收购范思哲]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品集团普拉达（Prada）的所有者缪西娅-普拉达（Miuccia Prada）周四表示，许多时装公司都可能有意收购范思哲。【原文：Numerous fashion companies are potentially interested in buying Versace, Miuccia Prada, owner of the Italian luxury group Prada , said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/miuccia-prada-says-everybody-interested-buying-versace-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFXVN2P7WNKZDKOP4XFIPR7MDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:49:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士因摩根士丹利 2010 年洗钱案罚款 100 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士总检察长办公室周四表示，已对摩根士丹利在瑞士的业务处以 100 万美元的罚款，原因是摩根士丹利未能采取足够措施防止其一名客户顾问在 2010 年实施合格的洗钱行为。【原文：The Swiss attorney general's office said on Thursday it had imposed a $1 million fine on Morgan Stanley's Swiss operations for failing to do enough to prevent one of its client advisors committing qualified money laundering in 2010.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/switzerland-fines-morgan-stanley-1-million-over-2010-money-laundering-case-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUMYN72ZSZJ7XIJJM3UNXSDAKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福克斯公司任命 Pete Distad 为新订阅流媒体平台负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[福克斯公司周四任命前 Apple TV+ 高管 Pete Distad 担任其即将推出的订阅流媒体平台的首席执行官，该平台将与 Netflix 和 Disney+ 等公司竞争。【原文：Fox Corp on Thursday named former Apple TV+ executive Pete Distad as the CEO of its upcoming subscription streaming platform, which will take on the likes of Netflix and Disney+.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fox-corp-names-pete-distad-head-its-new-subscription-streaming-platform-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6P74G6IIFO63K2AHOGGLUCTPU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道富确认推出 SPDR 阿波罗私人信贷 ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[州立街全球顾问公司（State Street Global Advisors）表示，其与另类投资公司阿波罗全球管理公司（Apollo Global Management）联合开发的备受瞩目的私人信贷交易所交易基金已于周四上午开始交易。【原文：State Street Global Advisors said its much-anticipated private credit exchange-traded fund, developed in conjunction with alternatives investment firm Apollo Global Management, began trading on Thursday morning.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/state-street-confirms-launch-spdr-apollo-private-credit-etf-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y5CURRJV5LWRDB6FRXRGCVOOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行行长警告美国关税带来强烈的全球不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田一夫周四警告说，全球经济前景存在 "非常强烈 "的不确定性，需要在制定货币政策时保持警惕。【原文：Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda on Thursday warned of "very strong" uncertainty on the global economic outlook that required vigilance in setting monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-chief-warns-strong-global-uncertainty-us-tariffs-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCSF7D24JRLLRD3RZSUC2J5XFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 CFPB 撤销对 Capital One 的执法行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）周四撤销了对第一资本公司（Capital One）的法律诉讼，该机构上个月曾指控该公司在储蓄账户上骗取了消费者超过 20 亿美元的利息。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau on Thursday dropped a legal action against Capital One , which the agency had accused last month of cheating consumers out of more than $2 billion in interest payments on savings accounts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-cfpb-drops-enforcement-action-against-capital-one-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYGQRG7BHNIRPJBRZEM5IY2UAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会推进无线频谱拍卖以资助中国设备搬迁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会周四投票决定推进无线频谱拍卖，为美国电信公司提供近 31 亿美元，用于从美国无线网络中移除中国电信公司华为和中兴生产的设备，以应对安全风险。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission voted on Thursday to advance a wireless spectrum auction to provide nearly $3.1 billion for U.S. telecom companies to remove equipment made by Chinese telecoms firms Huawei and ZTE from American wireless networks to address security risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fcc-advances-auction-wireless-spectrum-fund-chinese-equipment-removal-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SX7Q75K7VPUXJHN7N3GW25QQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:05:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行将于 3 月 6 日再次降息，重点转向经济增长：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查的所有 82 位经济学家均预计，欧洲央行将在下周再次下调存款利率至 2.50%，并将在今年年中之前再下调两次。【原文：The European Central Bank will trim its deposit rate again next week to 2.50%, according to all 82 economists polled by Reuters who expected two further cuts by the middle of this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ecb-cut-rates-again-march-6-focus-turns-growth-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XI5FBKCBKJNHJJLGXFL2PHHR2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 15:38:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，利安德将在即将关闭的休斯顿炼油厂裁员 86]]></title><description><![CDATA[利安德巴塞尔工业公司（Lyondell Basell Industries）向德克萨斯州劳动力委员会（Texas Workforce Commission）提交的一份文件显示，该公司将于 4 月 17 日在其关闭的休斯顿炼油厂裁员 345 人。【原文：Lyondell Basell Industries' will lay off 345 workers at its shuttered Houston refinery on April 17, according to a filing with the Texas Workforce Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/lyondell-lay-off-86-workforce-houston-refinery-soon-close-filing-shows-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMNTVW73QFOR5E4OISACXP34EI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 15:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利总理梅洛尼会见梅塔公司总裁讨论投资事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利总理乔治亚-梅洛尼（Giorgia Meloni）办公室周四表示，意大利总理会见了美国科技巨头 Meta 公司的首席全球事务官乔尔-卡普兰（Joel Kaplan），讨论在意大利进行新投资的可能性。【原文：Italian Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni met Joel Kaplan, the chief global affairs officer of U.S. tech giant Meta , to discuss possible new investments in Italy, Meloni's office said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italys-pm-meloni-meets-meta-exec-discuss-investments-2025-02-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34F5MXB35VLNJHGAL7ST7V2V6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 15:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>