<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:09:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称涡轮机为 "垃圾 "后，欧洲风能股遭受重创]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他将努力确保在他的任期内 "不建造风车"，并在距离他就职不到两周的时间里批评风电行业，此后欧洲风电股周三下跌。【原文：European wind power stocks fell on Wednesday after U.S. President-elect Donald Trump said he would try to ensure that "no windmills" are built on his watch, criticising the sector less than two weeks before he is due to take office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/european-wind-stocks-take-beating-after-trump-calls-turbines-garbage-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4NH5Z72FNOYDMCMEJ4D4TBC64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在妹妹提起诉讼后，OpenAI 老板否认性侵妹妹]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI首席执行官萨姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）否认在其妹妹小时候对她实施过性虐待，此前她在美国提起诉讼，指控奥特曼在 1997 年至 2006 年间经常对她实施性虐待。【原文：OpenAI Chief Executive Sam Altman has denied sexually abusing his sister when she was a child, after she filed a lawsuit in the United States accusing him of regularly sexually abusing her between 1997 and 2006.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/openai-boss-denies-sexually-assaulting-his-sister-after-she-files-lawsuit-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKOR6SR5CVPVHNXCFKN6UKGMM4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:05:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席沃勒：可能会有更多削减，但时机取决于通胀进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯托弗-沃勒（Christopher Waller）周三表示，通胀率在2025年应继续下降，并允许美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）进一步降低利率，但降息的步伐并不确定。【原文：Inflation should continue falling in 2025 and allow the U.S. Federal Reserve to further reduce interest rates, though at an uncertain pace, Federal Reserve governor Christopher Waller said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-waller-more-cuts-likely-though-timing-depends-inflation-progress-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMR2MDRQHRN6JCYVLCB536VSVM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达首席执行官预言前路漫漫，量子计算股票受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）表示，量子计算技术的实际应用可能还需要二十年的时间，量子计算股票周三下挫，暂停了长达一年的涨势。【原文：Quantum computing stocks sank on Wednesday, pausing a year-long rally, after Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang said the technology's practical use was likely two decades away.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-take-hit-nvidia-ceo-predicts-long-road-ahead-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LYG4CH6LVO7LMO2GHWOUHSU6E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年末，欧元区经济在贸易担忧中走向低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，几项关键指标显示，欧元区经济在衰退中徘徊了一年多之后，在2024年年底出现了疲软，这表明人们期盼已久的复苏前景依然遥远。【原文：The euro zone economy, skirting recession for more than a year, ended 2024 on a weak note, several key indicators showed on Wednesday, suggesting that a long hoped for recovery remains a distant prospect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-economy-ended-2024-downbeat-note-amid-trade-fears-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QOYYY3G3VMCBKEXGJRJGRHEFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普交易摇摆不定，跌跌不休的欧洲股市吸引投资者回归]]></title><description><![CDATA[在 2024 年创下相对于华尔街表现不佳的记录之后，由于担心美国新任总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的经济冲击会增强国际市场的吸引力，被打压的欧洲股市正在吸引投资者回归。【原文：Beaten-down European stocks are luring investors back after a record underperformance versus Wall Street in 2024, as fears about U.S. economic shocks under incoming President Donald Trump boost the appeal of international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/beaten-down-european-stocks-lure-investors-back-trump-trades-wobble-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3TVHQ46CJICRMKP6SUT2UB45M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:48:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Albertsons 季度销售额不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，Albertsons 第三季度销售额未达预期，原因是沃尔玛和克罗格（Kroger）等大型零售商提供大量折扣和促销活动的激烈竞争损害了需求。【原文：Albertsons missed third-quarter sales expectations on Wednesday, as intense competition from bigger retailers such as Walmart and Kroger offering heavy discounts and promotions hurt demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/albertsons-misses-quarterly-sales-estimates-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DH72ZHS7QJKIPH4J34YHWAIQ3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:36:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管经济不景气，中国预计新年旅游人数仍将增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国预计参加即将到来的农历新年旅游高峰的人数将会增加，尽管经济不景气，但当局预计在为期 40 天的节日期间，国内旅游人数将达到创纪录的 90 亿人次。【原文：China expects an increase in the number of people joining the coming Lunar New Year travel rush, with authorities estimating a record 9 billion domestic trips will be made during the 40-day period of festivities, despite the stuttering economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-expects-increase-new-year-travel-numbers-despite-economic-doldrums-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">334MPEB2QRK23EJCQCWGOZL6DM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[测试在 Facebook Marketplace 上显示 eBay 列表的 Meta]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 公司周三表示，它将在德国、法国和美国启动一项测试，使买家能够在 Facebook Marketplace 上浏览 eBay 上的列表，然后在 eBay 上完成交易。【原文：Meta said on Wednesday it would launch a test in Germany, France and the United States that will enable buyers to browse listings from eBay on Facebook Marketplace and then complete their transactions on eBay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-test-showing-ebay-listings-facebook-marketplace-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6HFDEFOFBFOPPEFYUQF3EIGLXM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:07:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）报道：特朗普酝酿宣布国家经济紧急状态，以便实施新的关税计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）周三援引熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道称，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普正在考虑宣布国家经济紧急状态，以便为对盟友和对手征收一系列普遍关税提供法律依据。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump is considering declaring a national economic emergency to provide legal justification for a series of universal tariffs on allies and adversaries, CNN reported on Wednesday, citing sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-mulls-national-economic-emergency-declaration-allow-new-tariff-program-cnn-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZCXBUCHJRPFPMXNMVIRPLHQIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:48:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称汉莎航空将于下周收购意大利 ITA 航空公司股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉情况的消息人士周三告诉路透社，汉莎航空将于1月13日收购意大利国有航空公司ITA的股份，从而结束多年的谈判。【原文：Lufthansa is set to acquire a stake in Italian state-owned airline ITA on Jan. 13, a source familiar with the situation told Reuters on Wednesday, bringing to a close years of talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/lufthansa-acquire-stake-italys-ita-next-week-german-news-agency-reports-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YPVU5A7JVJORMSQTHWH4NKXEM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:29:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街大跌后期指上扬；经济数据值得期待]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周三走高，投资者正在等待一系列就业数据和美联储最近一次会议的纪要，此前一天，对持续物价压力的担忧引发了华尔街的谨慎情绪。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Wednesday, with investors awaiting a set of employment figures and minutes from the Federal Reserve's latest meeting, a day after worries of persistent price pressures sparked caution on Wall Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-up-after-wall-st-selloff-economic-data-awaited-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2R765GPQWJLE7GOSSJ25BNR55I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:17:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构称可能接受 350 亿美元 Synopsys-Ansys 交易中的补救措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构周三表示，可能会接受芯片设计软件制造商 Synopsys 以 350 亿美元收购 Ansys 公司的交易双方提出的补救措施。【原文：The UK's competition regulator said on Wednesday that it might accept remedies offered by the parties in chip design software maker Synopsys' $35 billion acquisition of Ansys .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/uk-watchdog-says-it-may-accept-remedies-35-bln-synopsys-ansys-deal-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AO3SZOETTJNEDAMILRVP5DHZKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:17:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：债券闪红，"期限溢价 "创 10 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFLSTKFWHRKFFB7S2D5HDKOSVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储会议纪要可能开始显示进一步降息的障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储官员一直表示，鉴于通胀进展放缓和美国经济依然强劲，进一步降息暂时搁置，但该央行 12 月份会议的纪要可能会显示，面对特朗普政府上台后新出现的不确定经济环境，决策者们对这一观点的认同程度有多深。【原文：Federal Reserve officials have been signaling that further interest rate cuts are on hold for now given slowed progress on inflation and a still-strong U.S. economy, but minutes from the central bank's December meeting may show just how deeply that sentiment is shared among policymakers facing a newly uncertain economic environment under the incoming Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-minutes-may-begin-show-hurdle-further-rate-cuts-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TU5QXM5GVBLPPGJV5GQA5AGDB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圭亚那石油出口猛增，2024 年将获得欧洲市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据贸易商和金融公司 LSEG 的航运数据，圭亚那的石油出口量去年增长了 54%，达到约 58.2 万桶/日，这主要得益于欧洲炼油商对易于加工的甜原油的需求，以取代部分中东原油。【原文：Guyana's oil exports rose 54% last year to some 582,000 barrels per day (bpd), fueled by European refiners' demand for easy-to-process sweet crudes to replace some Middle Eastern grades, according to traders and shipping data from financial firm LSEG.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/guyana-oil-exports-jump-gain-europe-market-share-2024-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKFF2KOSURNI5IKSUXAQWF6JJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院即将采取行动，TikTok 的命运令特朗普和共和党同僚产生分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）要求最高法院阻止美国即将对 TikTok 实施的禁令，这一重大案件将于本周五进行辩论。【原文：While President-elect Donald Trump has asked the Supreme Court to block a looming U.S. ban on TikTok in a major case being argued on Friday that pits free speech rights against national security concerns over the Chinese-owned short-video app, many of his Republican allies have urged the opposite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tiktoks-fate-divides-trump-fellow-republicans-supreme-court-action-looms-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FT35W3GSBLUXIYA7RAYI4RD7Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济大臣称日本的 Seven & i 交易与国家安全有关]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本经济大臣赤泽亮世周三表示，他认为外资可能收购零售巨头 Seven &amp; i 是一个与国家安全 "密切相关 "的问题。【原文：Japanese economy minister Ryosei Akazawa said on Wednesday he believed a potential foreign acquisition of retail giant Seven &amp; i was a matter "heavily related" to national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japans-seven-i-deal-related-national-security-economy-minister-says-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34KWB7S3OBKV3IZKRJVDBQITRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 09:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行：欧元区家庭可能继续储蓄以重建财富]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行认为，欧元区家庭可以继续将大部分收入储蓄起来，以重建因高通胀而损失的财富。【原文：Euro zone households could keep saving a large portion of their income to rebuild wealth lost to high inflation, the European Central Bank argued, suggesting lacklustre consumption will continue to weigh on growth in the near term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-households-likely-keep-saving-rebuild-wealth-ecb-says-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBO53HJOTRJV5OBQCRSMU34RBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 09:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本消费者情绪恶化，加息时机存疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府的一项调查周三显示，日本 12 月份的消费者情绪有所恶化，这使人们对日本央行关于稳健的家庭支出将支撑经济并成为加息理由的观点产生了怀疑。【原文：Japan's consumer sentiment deteriorated in December, a government survey showed on Wednesday, casting doubt on the central bank's view that solid household spending will underpin the economy and justify a rise in interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-consumer-mood-worsens-casting-doubt-rate-hike-timing-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B53EMWT6N5LQDCBLJ76ZBLY4CI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 08:56:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲股市寸步难行，医疗保健和金融股上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，欧洲股市在权重医疗保健股和金融股的带动下小幅上扬，而新年全球货币政策走势仍是市场关注的焦点。【原文：European shares advanced slightly on Wednesday, led by heavyweight healthcare and financial stocks, while focus remained on the global monetary policy trend in the New Year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-shares-inch-higher-healthcare-financials-rise-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCTJKPDQIZNDXEKPU2MHFHSPTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据当地报纸报道，大众汽车公司经理将合计减薪 3 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车人力资源董事会成员贡纳尔-基利安（Gunnar Kilian）周三向当地报纸《不伦瑞克日报》（Braunschweiger Zeitung）发表评论称，到 2030 年，大众汽车管理层的减薪总额将超过 3 亿欧元（约合 3.1008 亿美元）。【原文：Volkswagen's management will take pay cuts adding up to over 300 million euros ($310.08 million) by 2030, according to comments by VW human resources board member Gunnar Kilian to local paper Braunschweiger Zeitung published on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-managers-take-combined-300-mln-euro-pay-cut-reports-local-newspaper-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWI46MGZDZMUBMUVWMGZJ2JX7I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 08:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[壳牌下调第四季度液化天然气产量预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[壳牌周三下调了第四季度液化天然气产量预期，并表示其化学品和石油产品部门的贸易业绩预计将大大低于第三季度。【原文：Shell on Wednesday trimmed its LNG production outlook for the fourth quarter and said trading results for its chemicals and oil products division are expected to be significantly lower than in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-trims-q4-lng-production-outlook-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3DZXF45DZMP7P5JLHRALY3JTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 07:21:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗氏将以 15 亿美元完成对美国生物制药公司 Poseida 的收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗氏公司周三表示，计划完成对美国生物制药公司 Poseida Therapeutics 的收购，该公司是治疗多种类型血癌的复杂免疫细胞疗法专家。【原文：Roche on Wednesday said it planned to complete its purchase of U.S. biopharmaceutical company Poseida Therapeutics , a specialist in complex immune cell therapies to treat several types of blood cancer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/roche-complete-acquisition-us-biopharma-company-poseida-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DR4N2II6JRIFTPZQJ7ZWRGTNBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 06:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得益于客户维系和新合同的签订，Pluxee 第一季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国凭手机验证码领取彩金和福利公司 Pluxee 周三公布的第一季度营业收入有机增长 12.1%，超出市场预期，主要得益于良好的净保留率和持续的新客户收购。【原文：French voucher and benefits company Pluxee reported 12.1% organic growth in its first-quarter operating revenue on Wednesday, beating market expectations, supported by a sound net retention rate and continued new client acquisitions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pluxee-tops-q1-revenue-expectations-thanks-client-retention-new-contracts-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMAYQAXS75PHTDJD2AG5Q3NIDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 06:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[竞争加剧，印尼电子商务公司 Bukalapak 将停止销售实物商品]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚电子商务公司 Bukalapak 周二表示，在东南亚最大经济体 TikTok 的 Tokopedia 和 Sea 的 Shopee 的激烈竞争中，该公司将很快停止在其市场上销售实物商品。【原文：Indonesian e-commerce firm Bukalapak said on Tuesday that it would stop selling physical items on its marketplace soon, amid tough competition from TikTok's Tokopedia and Sea's Shopee in Southeast Asia's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/indonesia-e-commerce-firm-bukalapak-stop-selling-physical-goods-competition-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WV7VYZNKRNNN7CRBGGGL4FSXZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 06:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车因霍顿变速器问题在澳大利亚面临集体诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚律师事务所莫里斯-布莱克本（Maurice Blackburn）表示，它已对美国汽车制造商通用汽车公司（General Motors）的本地部门提起集体诉讼，指控其现已解散的通用汽车霍顿（Holden）品牌某些车型的变速箱系统存在缺陷。【原文：Australian law firm Maurice Blackburn said it had filed a class action lawsuit against U.S. carmaker General Motors' local unit, alleging the transmission systems of certain models of its now-defunct GM Holden brand were defective.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-faces-class-action-australia-over-holden-transmission-issues-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2FC6WBVTAVPZPLQNN5LIYVKBJU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 05:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南盾疲软促进出口，美国对越南贸易逆差飙升至 1100 亿美元以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最新数据显示，2024 年前 11 个月，美国对越南的贸易逆差超过 1100 亿美元，因为在越南货币兑美元汇率创纪录下跌的情况下，这个东南亚工业中心的出口增长了。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit with Vietnam exceeded $110 billion in the first 11 months of 2024, latest U.S. figures show, as exports from the Southeast Asian industrial hub grew amid a record fall of its currency against the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-trade-deficit-with-vietnam-soars-beyond-110-billion-weak-dong-boosts-exports-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7H75RKQ475N3VB2MYEB2LR22HM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 05:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美元走强、收益率上升成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7T3X3SGARLV3EKQ33E3EN7ONY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 05:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场最容易受到特朗普关税风险的影响特朗普关税风险对市场的冲击最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[从中国到欧洲，从加拿大到墨西哥，世界市场已经因唐纳德-特朗普承诺在不到两周后就任美国总统时提高关税而受到影响。【原文：From China to Europe, Canada to Mexico, world markets are already reeling from Donald Trump's promise to jack up tariffs when he becomes U.S. president in less than two weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trump-tariffs-graphic-2025-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAI25YZMBNOJLNBPMKA6XTPTHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 05:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>