<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 12:45:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 12:45:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会调查欧盟稳定币持有者安全网的深度]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会正在调查欧盟关于加密资产的规则在多大程度上保护了该集团投资者对相同电子货币代币（EMT）的赎回权，这些代币的价值与单一官方货币的价值挂钩。【原文：The European Commission is investigating the extent to which EU rules on crypto assets protect the redemption rights of the bloc's investors in identical e-money tokens (EMTs), the value of which is pegged to that of a single official currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-commission-investigates-depth-eu-safety-net-stablecoin-holders-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3NJYGS5OJNKRMF5LY6UP3ZW2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 12:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司因战略失误，预计 2025 年利润下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司（American Airlines）周四预测 2025 年利润低于华尔街预期，原因是喷气机燃油价格上涨，以及努力纠正销售策略失误导致企业旅客流失。【原文：American Airlines forecast 2025 profit below Wall Street expectations on Thursday, hurt by an uptick in jet fuel prices and efforts to fix a sales-strategy misstep that drove away corporate travelers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-forecasts-2025-profit-below-expectations-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZD75DFUXFK7FJ763GBLJPVZ2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 12:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通削减巴拿马对特朗普威胁 "收回 "运河的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普本周加大威胁要收回巴拿马运河之后，美国投资银行摩根大通下调了对巴拿马债券的建议评级。【原文：U.S. investment bank JPMorgan has downgraded its recommendation on Panama's bonds after U.S. President Donald Trump ramped up his threat this week to take back the Panama canal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/jpmorgan-cuts-panama-view-trumps-threat-take-back-canal-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USR74V3DJVOGHNTLS2VGC26SVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《经理人》杂志报道，宝马首席执行官不会将合同延长至 2026 年夏季之后]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国《经理人》杂志周四援引一位熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道称，宝马公司首席执行官奥利弗-齐普斯（Oliver Zipse）在明年夏天合同到期后将不再续约。【原文：BMW Chief Executive Oliver Zipse will not extend his contract beyond the summer of next year, when it expires, Germany's manager magazin reported on Thursday, citing a source familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-ceo-wont-extend-contract-beyond-summer-2026-reports-manager-magazin-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BL7UML6KFBMCFGNSO2IF35OHZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世贸组织负责人称贸易战将对全球经济增长造成 "灾难性 "影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织总裁周四在讨论美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税威胁时表示，任何针锋相对的贸易战都将给全球经济增长带来灾难性后果。【原文：The World Trade Organization chief said on Thursday that any tit-for-tat trade wars would have catastrophic consequences for global growth in a debate where U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats were discussed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trade-wars-would-be-catastrophic-global-growth-wto-chief-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHDNAKVU7BIQNBQMBSO7V77ZZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[General Atlantic 首席执行官表示对 TikTok 在美国的交易持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司 General Atlantic 的首席执行官、TikTok 母公司的董事会成员周四表示，他对达成让短视频应用继续在美国运营的协议感到乐观。【原文：The CEO of investment firm General Atlantic, a board member of TikTok's parent company, said on Thursday that he was optimistic that a deal to keep the short-video app operating in the United States would be agreed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/general-atlantic-ceo-says-he-is-optimistic-tiktok-deal-us-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LRFCYXTI5RMURIJEEXZUXEFPK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:33:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用电气航空航天集团（GE Aerospace）预计 2025 年利润将高于预期，原因是售后市场需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用电气航空航天公司（GE Aerospace）周四预计今年的利润将高于预期，原因是新飞机的持续短缺迫使航空公司改飞老式喷气式飞机，从而对其高利润率的零部件和服务产生了强劲需求。【原文：GE Aerospace on Thursday forecast profit for the current year above estimates, as persistent shortage of new aircraft forces airlines to fly older jets, creating strong demand for its high-margin parts and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ge-aerospace-forecasts-2025-profit-above-estimates-robust-aftermarket-demand-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTXXUWFZKNKY5DVAZVFDYEGVLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：股市徘徊在新纪录附近，石油退潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHUPSRU3CZK3FAHK243CZV5ESQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:18:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解释：特朗普称企业多元化努力是非法的--但真的是这样吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统发布了一项行政命令，旨在消除联邦政府和私营部门的劳动力多样性、公平和包容（DEI）举措。特朗普表示，如果一些公司的计划被认为具有歧视性，它们将面临调查和法律诉讼。【原文：President Donald Trump has issued an executive order designed to eradicate workforce diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) initiatives in the federal government and the private sector. Trump suggested that some companies will face investigations and legal action if their programs are deemed to be discriminatory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-corporate-diversity-efforts-are-illegal-are-they-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66OXLL5ITJLDJMR6LBBRBMLNOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利率敏感性困扰本已高企的巴西公共债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者已经对巴西在资深左派总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）领导下不断膨胀的公共债务负担感到担忧，现在又不得不考虑另一个风险：政府债务状况对高利率的敏感性越来越高。【原文：Investors already concerned about Brazil's ballooning public debt load under veteran leftist President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva are being forced to reckon with an additional risk: a government debt profile with growing sensitivity to high interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rate-sensitivity-haunts-already-elevated-brazil-public-debt-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRTM35ATPBOUFNKPRBHVDAQBPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:05:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道与特朗普的联系--为何有人购买世界自由金融代币]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日，就在唐纳德-特朗普就职典礼之前，加密货币投资者迈克-杜达斯（Mike Dudas）从世界自由金融公司（World Liberty Financial）购买了价值超过 14.5 万美元的代币。【原文：On Sunday, just before Donald Trump's inauguration, crypto investor Mike Dudas bought more than $145,000 worth of tokens from World Liberty Financial, a fledgling crypto company partly owned by the U.S. president.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-connection-why-some-bought-world-liberty-financial-tokens-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYKE6KELHRJ53ENZJGRMUXLKOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，福特将因电池问题召回超过 27 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周四表示，福特汽车公司因电池故障问题召回272817辆美国汽车。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Thursday Ford Motor is recalling 272,817 U.S. vehicles over battery failure concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-over-270000-us-vehicles-over-battery-concern-nhtsa-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJMKD76WZZPAZPJ34A53RE36NA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前一交易日跳涨后期货价格低迷；数据和财报即将公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国股指期货表现低迷，因为投资者在华尔街上一交易日的强劲表现后暂停交易，等待经济数据、更多企业财报和美国总统唐纳德-特朗普稍后的讲话。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were subdued on Thursday, as investors paused after Wall Street's strong performance in the previous session and awaited economic data, more corporate earnings and remarks from President Donald Trump later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-subdued-after-previous-sessions-jump-data-earnings-tap-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7U6CENOJ3JIGBDZXDM3GPZTLXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:56:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国金融科技公司 Broadridge 高层表示将在 3 年内将印度员工人数增加 26]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国金融科技公司 Broadridge Financial 的一位高管告诉路透社，该公司将在三年内把印度的技术人员增加 26%，达到 6800 人，以便在这个世界上人口最多的国家销售其产品。【原文：U.S. fintech firm Broadridge Financial will expand its India tech staff by 26% to 6,800 people over three years as it gears up to sell its products in the world's most populous nation, a top executive told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-fintech-firm-broadridge-boost-india-headcount-by-26-3-years-top-exec-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QC7ONQRH4ZOWZOKTPZPJUWDLII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:45:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威财富基金首席执行官在达沃斯：美国通胀压力是2025年市场面临的风险之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威1.8万亿美元的主权财富基金是世界上最大的投资者之一，该基金的首席执行官周四表示，美国的通胀压力对今年的金融市场构成了风险。【原文：The chief executive of Norway's $1.8 trillion sovereign wealth fund, one of the world's largest investors, said on Thursday that inflationary pressure in the United States posed a risk to financial markets this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/norway-wealth-fund-ceo-davos-us-inflationary-pressure-risk-markets-2025-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BT5PC5WEVVMUNL5IDOKDRAP4VI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官表示，如果征收关税，Essity 可能会将更多生产转移到美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典卫生用品和生活用纸生产商 Essity 首席执行官 Magnus Groth 周四表示，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税，该公司可能会将更多生产从墨西哥和加拿大转移到美国，但不会考虑关闭工厂。【原文：Swedish hygiene product and tissue maker Essity could move more of its production into the U.S. from Mexico and Canada if tariffs are introduced by President Donald Trump, but is not considering plant closures, CEO Magnus Groth said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/essity-could-move-more-production-into-us-if-tariffs-are-introduced-ceo-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBQO3HGINBN6VC5BQOBPOOZFWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，日产汽车将从 SK On 采购电动汽车电池，供应美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经新闻》周四称，日产汽车计划从2028年左右开始向韩国SK On公司采购在美国销售的电动汽车电池。【原文：Nissan Motor plans to procure batteries for electric vehicles sold in the U.S. from South Korea's SK On from around 2028 onwards, the Nikkei newspaper said on Thursday, as the troubled Japanese automaker looks to ramp up its EV business as part of a planned turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-procure-ev-batteries-sk-us-market-nikkei-reports-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLQWIGMWXNJ3BCINUR6K7KH4LI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行称，2025 年亚洲科技基金募集规模将扩大 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街花旗银行周四表示，受人工智能发展以及印度和台湾地区强劲活动的推动，花旗预计到2025年亚洲科技公司的筹资势头将有所增强。【原文：Citi expects increased momentum in Asian fundraising for tech companies into 2025, driven by developments in artificial intelligence and robust activity in India and Taiwan, the Wall Street bank said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/asian-tech-fundraising-expand-10-2025-says-citi-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IN5QJBYQNKGJPOWPIJESJBDRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称中国万科正洽谈向新加坡政府投资公司出售物流公司股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士透露，负债累累的房地产开发商中国万科有限公司正在就向新加坡主权财富基金 GIC 出售 VX Logistics 的控股权进行深入谈判。【原文：Indebted property developer China Vanke Co Ltd is in advanced talks to sell a controlling stake in VX Logistics to Singaporean sovereign wealth fund GIC, a person with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-vanke-talks-sell-logistics-firm-stake-gic-source-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SDE6GNPXVL7ZMO3BA6NQIKESU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港新世界发展称业务运营 "一切如常]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于香港的房地产开发商新世界发展（New World Development）周四表示，在 "媒体谣传 "其运营和财务责任后，该公司将继续照常营业。【原文：Hong Kong-based property developer New World Development said on Thursday that it continues to carry on business as usual, following "media rumours" about its operations and financial obligations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hong-kongs-new-world-development-says-business-operations-are-as-usual-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3DKTUXYX5L6LON2PEDXREMLNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能热潮减退，股市有所松动；美元在没有关税冲击的情况下萎靡不振]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，全球股市回落，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在人工智能基础设施方面的巨额支出计划引发的反弹止步，因为部分兴奋情绪逐渐消退，不过中国股市在中国政府的支持下表现较好。【原文：Global stocks eased on Thursday, halting a rally sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump's mammoth spending plans for artificial intelligence infrastructure as some of that excitement fizzled out, though Chinese shares fared better on Beijing's support.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-6-pix-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UMFYKM5DRKGNMFG7IB55UG6HY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政策成为焦点，日本对经济持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周四对经济前景保持谨慎，部分原因是决策者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政策及其对全球经济增长的潜在影响保持警惕。【原文：Japan's government on Thursday maintained a cautious outlook for the economy in part as policymakers kept a wary eye on U.S. President Donald Trump's policies and their potential impact on global growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-cautious-economy-trumps-policies-take-centre-stage-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RNSQMFG6FK3ZP2SOZ3TEWC544</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:34:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游说团体称，德国电子商务销售额自 2021 年以来首次增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家行业机构周四表示，德国在线零售商去年的收入自2021年以来首次略有增长，原因是储蓄率提高使德国人更有信心消费。【原文：German online retailers last year eked out slight revenue gains for the first time since 2021, an industry body said on Thursday, citing higher savings that are giving Germans more confidence to spend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/german-e-commerce-sales-rise-first-time-since-2021-says-lobby-group-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y4PV6SZHJPMLGQTXH5FJNGGN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席执行官称盈利能力 "尚未达到目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席执行官延斯-里特尔（Jens Ritter）周三晚间对记者说，汉莎航空的目标是重新盈利，但尽管重组计划取得了初步成功，但仍有一段路要走。【原文：Lufthansa Airlines aims to be profitable again but still has a ways to go despite the initial success of its restructuring plan, CEO Jens Ritter told journalists on Wednesday evening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lufthansa-airlines-not-there-yet-profitability-says-ceo-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZT36EPAYTJNK3JZTVJON6ZIP6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，汇丰关闭支付应用将危及约 400 个工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟知内情的消息人士称，汇丰银行已决定关闭其国际支付应用 Zing，这可能会导致约 400 人失业，因为该行首席执行官乔治-埃尔德里（Georges Elhedery）正在加大欧洲最大银行的成本削减力度。【原文：HSBC has decided to shutter its international payments app Zing, potentially triggering around 400 job losses, a source familiar with the matter said, as CEO Georges Elhedery steps up cost-cutting efforts at Europe's largest bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbcs-payments-app-closure-puts-around-400-jobs-risk-source-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHTZN2O3BZMI3PUCBPPNVQ3KEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 08:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，字节跳动计划 2025 年资本支出 200 亿美元，主要用于人工智能领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，TikTok 的中国所有者字节跳动公司今年的资本支出已超过 1,500 亿元人民币（约合 206.4 亿美元），其中大部分将集中在人工智能领域。【原文：ByteDance, the Chinese owner of TikTok, has earmarked over 150 billion yuan ($20.64 billion) in capital expenditure for this year, much of which will be centred on artificial intelligence, two people briefed on the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bytedance-plans-20-billion-capex-2025-mostly-ai-sources-say-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BTZWEV7GFNKLDYW7KWN5C2DXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 08:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本以安全为由堵塞外国投资报告规则漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务省计划堵塞《外汇和外贸法》中外国投资者报告要求的漏洞，以防止情报泄露给外国政府。【原文：Japan's finance ministry plans to plug a loophole in reporting requirements for foreign investors under the Foreign Exchange and Foreign Trade Act, in an effort to prevent intelligence from leaking to foreign governments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/citing-security-japan-plug-loophole-reporting-rules-foreign-investment-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VE6NIOLRPVMC7LPSB3PLFWQ2XY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 08:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全年利润下降，彪马股价下跌 11]]></title><description><![CDATA[彪马股价在周四的盘前交易中下跌了11%，这家德国运动服制造商在周三晚些时候表示，对去年盈利下降感到不满，同时还宣布了一项成本削减计划。
该公司表示，今年的净利润为 2.82 亿欧元（2.93 亿美元），而 2023 年为 3.05 亿欧元，但其首席执行官 Arne Freundt 表示，他预计 2025 年的销售增长将强于去年。【原文：Shares in Puma dropped 11% in pre-market trading on Thursday after the German sportswear maker late on Wednesday said it was dissatisfied with a decline in earnings last year, also announcing a cost-cutting programme.
The firm said net profit came in at 282 million euros ($293 million) for the year, compared to 305 million euros in 2023, but its CEO Arne Freundt said he expects stronger sales growth in 2025 than last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/puma-shares-indicated-11-lower-after-drop-full-year-profit-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2S7HSRGIBJIW3JJEDTLEV4PW5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 07:35:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税计划的开端不那么激进，亚洲外汇市场熊市退却--路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的就职政策暗示他将通过谈判而不是立即对贸易伙伴征收高额关税之后，投资者缩减了对大多数亚洲货币的看跌押注。【原文：Investors scaled back bearish bets on most Asian currencies after U.S. President Donald Trump's inaugural policies suggested he would negotiate rather than immediately impose hefty tariffs on trading partners, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia-fx-bears-retreat-after-less-aggressive-start-trumps-tariff-plans-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRDK2GPOENM53CEUEFU5D56VCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 07:27:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚澳航常客计划改革后飙升至历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，澳航股价创下历史新高，此前一天，这家澳大利亚航空公司公布了对其常旅客计划的调整，以吸引有成本意识的旅客，并在一连串争议之后恢复其信誉。【原文：Shares of Qantas rose to a record high on Thursday, a day after the Australian carrier unveiled changes to its frequent fliers programme to attract cost-conscious travellers and restore its credibility following a string of controversies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australias-qantas-soars-record-highs-after-frequent-flyer-programme-revamp-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPUFZ3IARRKFZLR45QFICEMAAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:28:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>