<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:38:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:38:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普会见美国企业界人士，经济担忧打压股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计总统将与约 100 位首席执行官发表讲话。【原文：The president is expected to speak with around 100 CEOs.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-meets-corporate-america-economic-fears-nip-stocks-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KMTLLA3KRO45FH73UHOVY3CB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:06:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税给威斯康星州的工厂车间带来了 "狂野的西部"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里恩斯公司（AriensCo）是一家生产鲜艳橙色吹雪机的公司，自 11 月份以来，该公司一直在为关税寒流做准备。【原文：AriensCo - a manufacturer of bright orange snowblowers - has braced for the cold blast of tariffs since November.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-tariffs-create-wild-west-wisconsins-factory-floors-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34BORXCWXRISZH4ONOWDG6IUFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院在民主党反对声中就政府拨款问题进行激烈投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[控制美国国会的共和党人将于周二试图推动立法，以避免政府在周末关门，而对唐纳德-特朗普总统大幅裁员感到震惊的民主党人预计将反对立法。【原文：Republicans who control the U.S. Congress will try on Tuesday to advance legislation that would avert a weekend government shutdown, while Democrats alarmed by President Donald Trump's dramatic downsizing effort were expected to oppose it.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-tees-up-close-vote-government-funding-face-democratic-opposition-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHFKKGRM4FJSFPXXWCEJU2XJX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:03:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莫斯科无人机袭击最新消息：乌克兰袭击俄罗斯首都]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰官员稍后将在沙特阿拉伯与美国团队会面，讨论可能的和平谈判。【原文：Ukrainian officials are due to meet a U.S. team in Saudi Arabia later to discuss possible peace talks.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/europe/moscow-drone-attack-latest-russian-capital-targeted-by-ukraine-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZEJBTIQM5DN5FHLQLMWKNDR3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将购买 "新特斯拉 "以示对马斯克的支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，他将购买一辆新的特斯拉汽车，以示对这家电动汽车制造商的掌门人及其盟友埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的支持。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday said he will buy a new Tesla car to show support for the electric carmaker's chief and his ally Elon Musk amid recent "Tesla Takedown" protests and the slump in the company's stock price.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-buy-new-tesla-show-support-musk-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25P5CHB4BNO45P3U6YLXKXQ3EY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 05:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国私募基金要求美国证券交易委员会重新考虑詹斯勒时代的规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募基金行业组织管理基金协会（Managed Funds Association）敦促美国证券交易委员会（SEC）改革或撤销过去四年来出台的法规。【原文：The Managed Funds Association, a private fund industry group, has urged the U.S. Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) to reform or withdraw regulations introduced over the past four years.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/us-private-funds-ask-sec-rethink-gensler-era-rules-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWBYHNNPCNPAZFODPUQTGBBRBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 04:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[权益组织称，以色列-加沙战争是美国反穆斯林事件创新高的幕后推手]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个穆斯林权益组织周二表示，由于美国盟友以色列在加沙发动的战争以及由此引发的大学校园抗议活动导致伊斯兰恐惧症加剧，2024 年针对美国穆斯林和阿拉伯人的歧视和攻击上升了 7.4%。【原文：Discrimination and attacks against American Muslims and Arabs rose by 7.4% in 2024 due to heightened Islamophobia caused by U.S. ally Israel's war in Gaza and the resulting college campus protests, a Muslim advocacy group said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/israel-gaza-war-behind-record-high-us-anti-muslim-incidents-advocacy-group-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIO6UHSDXNPOHAPQSMCW7ELDIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 04:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官命令特朗普政府恢复教师备课补助金]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一名联邦法官命令美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府暂时恢复八个州的教师培训补助金。【原文：A federal judge on Monday ordered U.S. President Donald Trump's administration to temporarily restore grants for teacher preparation in eight states that it nixed as part of its efforts to eradicate diversity, equity and inclusion initiatives.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-orders-trump-administration-restore-teacher-preparation-grants-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3LHYIO4DNIQ5DFDEOSO75Z3DY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:14:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部削减超过 10 亿美元的学校和当地食品采购资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一个学校组织称，美国农业部削减了两项联邦计划，这两项计划每年花费超过10亿美元帮助学校和食品银行从当地农场和牧场购买食品。【原文：The U.S. Agriculture Department has cut two federal programs that spent over $1 billion annually to help schools and food banks buy food from local farms and ranches, according to a school group and a Politico report on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-cuts-over-1-billion-funding-schools-local-food-purchases-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDQTTCESL5IBBDBSIKYQRZILAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:36:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官称马斯克的 DOGE 必须公布 "秘密 "运营的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周一下令，由美国总统唐纳德-特朗普创建、亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）带头的政府缩编团队必须公开有关其运作的记录，他说该团队的运作一直处于 "非同寻常的保密状态"。【原文：A federal judge on Monday ordered the government-downsizing team created by U.S. President Donald Trump and spearheaded by billionaire Elon Musk to make public records concerning its operations, which he said had been run in "unusual secrecy."】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-says-musks-doge-must-release-records-operations-run-secrecy-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2PU6Z6N6JK5TFBKYKRP5U2HCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:12:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官不会命令特朗普政府恢复被取消的对外援助合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周一拒绝命令唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府恢复自总统上任以来取消的数千份对外援助合同和赠款，但他认为政府必须加快支付已完成工作的近 20 亿美元。【原文：A federal judge on Monday declined to order President Donald Trump's administration to restore thousands of foreign aid contracts and grants that have been canceled since the president took office, though he found that the administration must speed up payments of close to $2 billion for already completed work.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/judge-will-not-order-trump-administration-restore-canceled-foreign-aid-contracts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNMQO5IWQRJZTFRXK6KPDE5VNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 01:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工人拆除华盛顿特区黑人生命事件广场壁画以避免资金削减]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，建筑工人开始拆除华盛顿特区黑人生命事务广场的壁画，此前市长穆里尔-鲍泽（Muriel Bowser）承诺将重新设计该广场，以应对共和党威胁削减该市交通资金，除非该广场重新命名。【原文：Construction workers began removing Washington, D.C.'s Black Lives Matter Plaza mural on Monday, after Mayor Muriel Bowser pledged to redesign the plaza in response to Republican threats to cut the city's transportation funding unless it was renamed.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/workers-remove-dc-black-lives-matter-plaza-mural-avoid-funding-cuts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3FALWUFRFOXVF7VC7LZJGKKTA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:20:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国交通部长将与波音公司就安全工作举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）计划于周四参观位于华盛顿州的波音工厂，以确保美国飞机制造商保持最高的安全水平。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy plans to visit a Boeing factory on Thursday in Washington State to ensure the U.S. planemaker is maintaining the highest level of safety.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transportation-chief-meet-with-boeing-safety-efforts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JBTKOWVFRJK3O7TD3LHQCYYHE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国交通部长将与波音公司就安全工作举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）计划于周四参观位于华盛顿州的波音工厂，以确保美国飞机制造商保持最高的安全水平。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy plans to visit a Boeing factory on Thursday in Washington State to ensure the U.S. planemaker is maintaining the highest level of safety.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transportation-chief-meet-with-boeing-safety-efforts-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JBTKOWVFRJK3O7TD3LHQCYYHE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，特朗普寻求在五角大楼基地提炼矿物以提高美国产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名高级政府官员告诉路透社记者，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的目标是在五角大楼军事基地上建造金属精炼设施，作为他促进国内关键矿产生产和抵消中国对该行业控制的计划的一部分。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump aims to build metals refining facilities on Pentagon military bases as part of his plan to boost domestic production of critical minerals and offset China's control of the sector, two senior administration officials told Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-seeks-minerals-refining-pentagon-bases-boost-us-output-sources-say-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACASFGTJCZJZJEMFNBABRLYF3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 23:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员指责特朗普削弱乌克兰国防，驳斥马斯克 "叛徒 "的侮辱性言论]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位刚刚访问过乌克兰的美国民主党参议员周一表示，特朗普政府暂停情报共享的做法削弱了基辅对俄罗斯的防御能力，并驳斥特朗普顾问埃隆-马斯克称他为 "叛徒"。【原文：A Democratic U.S. senator who just visited Ukraine said on Monday the Trump administration's suspension of intelligence-sharing had lessened Kyiv's defenses against Russia, and dismissed Trump advisor Elon Musk calling him a "traitor."】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senator-accuses-trump-weakening-ukraines-defense-dismisses-musk-traitor-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3DD6HA3ZNPPDGS32X4KSCA42M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府计划限制奥巴马医保的注册期]]></title><description><![CDATA[负责监督奥巴马医改计划的机构在一份新闻稿中说，特朗普政府的目标是在 12 月 15 日结束奥巴马医改健康保险计划的注册期，比目前的截止日期提前一个月。【原文：The Trump administration aims to close the enrollment period for Obamacare health insurance plans on December 15, one month earlier than the current deadline, the agency that oversees the program said in a press release.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-plans-restrict-obamacare-enrollment-period-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICSYOO6425NWLIR5OGNY47IYWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 气候活动人士在全球顶级能源会议上抗议]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，抗议者聚集在全球最大的能源主管年度会议外，美国能源部长克里斯-赖特在会上表示，气候变化是建设现代世界的副作用。【原文：Protesters gathered on Monday outside the world's largest annual meeting of energy executives, where the U.S. Energy Secretary Chris Wright said that climate change was a side effect of building the modern world.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/ceraweek-climate-activists-protest-top-global-energy-gathering-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ABWRMJE6JPOROL5PAGFGJD5GI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共和党人寻求在预算法案中保护绿色税收抵免]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周一散发的一封信称，一群共和党议员敦促众议院起草唐纳德-特朗普总统在即将出台的预算协调法案中提出的减税建议的委员会保留拜登政府时期颁布的关键清洁能源税收抵免政策，以保护私营部门在其选区的投资。【原文：A group of Republican lawmakers urged the House committee drafting President Donald Trump's proposed tax cuts in the upcoming budget reconciliation bill to preserve key clean energy tax credits enacted under the Biden administration to protect private sector investments in their districts, according to a letter circulated on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/republicans-seek-protect-green-tax-credits-budget-bill-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW4IOWOLLBM3BNEWZ6PQ2VC6PY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国环保局局长称取消总额 17 亿美元的 DEI 拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护署署长李-泽尔丁（Lee Zeldin）周一表示，他取消了 400 项环境正义和多元化、公平与包容补助金，总金额达 17 亿美元，这是特朗普政府对 DEI 行动的最新打击。【原文：U.S. Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Lee Zeldin said on Monday he canceled 400 environmental justice and diversity, equity and inclusion grants totaling $1.7 billion in the Trump administration's latest crackdown on DEI initiatives.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-epa-administrator-says-he-canceled-dei-grants-totaling-17-billion-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Q5V7C7OPZKXPMOQTGIBVFG6NA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国军方取消被五角大楼负责人称为 "垃圾 "的气候变化研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国军方正在取消 90 多项研究，其中包括一些被美国国防部长皮特-黑格塞斯（Pete Hegseth）斥为气候变化 "垃圾 "的研究。【原文：The U.S. military is canceling more than 90 studies, including some that U.S. Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth dismissed as climate change "crap."】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-military-cancels-climate-change-studies-that-pentagon-chief-calls-crap-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I64PUMTQVRJ7FL6CFTXNFSAXKE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:51:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼迪要求 FDA 修订食品配料安全规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：U.S. Secretary of Health and Human Services Robert F. Kennedy Jr. on Monday directed the Food and Drug Administration to revise its food safety guidance to increase its oversight of food ingredients considered to be safe.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kennedy-asks-fda-revise-rules-food-ingredient-safety-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RI6QXYDXF5MLHMMVAMCXQ2DE4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚广播公司敦促联邦通信委员会驳回有关《60 分钟》采访哈里斯的投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚广播公司（CBS）周一敦促联邦通信委员会驳回对时任美国副总统卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）接受《60 分钟》采访一事的投诉，称该机构在监督广播新闻编辑决定方面没有合法作用。【原文：CBS on Monday urged the Federal Communications Commission to reject a complaint over a "60 Minutes" interview with then-Vice President Kamala Harris, saying the agency has no lawful role in policing broadcast news editorial decisions.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/cbs-urges-fcc-reject-complaint-over-60-minutes-harris-interview-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3X4GNXQIWRNGVEVYCNDI7GTCFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局终止首席科学家职务，关闭政策办公室]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）周一表示，将取消首席科学家职位，并关闭一个研究空间和技术政策事务的办公室，此轮裁员将影响到 23 名员工。【原文：NASA is eliminating its chief scientist role and closing down an office that studies policy matters on space and technology, in a round of layoffs affecting 23 employees, the agency said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/nasa-terminates-chief-scientist-role-closes-policy-office-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ5PEQRJFJJ3TOMYNR66OJ2WZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:24:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将于周一签署救灾行政令]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员说，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普计划于周一签署一项行政命令，旨在授权州和地方政府及公民处理备灾和救灾工作。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump plans to sign an executive order on Monday designed to empower state and local governments and citizens to handle disaster preparations and relief, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-sign-executive-order-disaster-relief-monday-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQX7LH3A7ZIYFKKTAMDHRZWKHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛杉矶检察官称梅南德兹兄弟必须完全承认谎言才能获释]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶县地方检察官内森-霍赫曼（Nathan Hochman）周一表示，莱尔-梅嫩德斯（Lyle Menendez）和埃里克-梅嫩德斯（Erik Menendez）必须完全承认他们在 35 年前用猎枪杀害父母的事件中撒了谎，他才会支持他们出狱。【原文：Los Angeles County District Attorney Nathan Hochman on Monday said Lyle and Erik Menendez must fully acknowledge lies they told about the shotgun murder of their parents 35 years ago before he would support their release from prison.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/la-prosecutor-says-menendez-brothers-must-fully-admit-lies-be-freed-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUOWDXX3EZN3PEGF6NE2RJFXMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 暂缓对减肥药复制品采取行动，等待法院裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周一表示，在联邦法院就针对该机构的诉讼作出裁决之前，不会对仿制诺和诺德减肥药Wegovy的复合药房采取行动。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Monday it will not take action against compounding pharmacies making copies of Novo Nordisk's weight-loss drug Wegovy until a federal court delivers its ruling in a lawsuit against the agency.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-hold-off-action-weight-loss-drug-copies-pending-court-ruling-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LOJHHJEWVL5NHOYJZJFIKAJAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:57:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加巴德称特朗普下令撤销拜登时代官员的安全许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家情报总监图尔西-加巴德（Tulsi Gabbard）周一表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统已下令撤销前总统乔-拜登政府一些官员的安全许可，并禁止他们接触机密信息。【原文：U.S. National Intelligence Director Tulsi Gabbard said on Monday President Donald Trump has ordered that the security clearances be revoked and access to classified information be barred for some officials from the administration of former President Joe Biden.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/gabbard-says-trump-ordered-revoking-security-clearances-biden-era-officials-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQLUMSEC5VNOXM6VBIRW32R6VE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:36:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官驳回前俄罗斯石油公司总裁对被扣押游艇的索赔要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官周一裁定，俄罗斯国家石油和天然气公司（Rosneft）的一名前负责人对美国当局于 2022 年扣押的一艘价值 3 亿美元的超级游艇的所有权没有合理的主张，美国司法部在这一裁决中获胜。【原文：A U.S. judge on Monday ruled that a former chief of Russian state oil and gas company Rosneft does not have a plausible claim to own a $300 million superyacht that U.S. authorities seized in 2022, in a win for the U.S. Department of Justice.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-denies-ex-rosneft-chiefs-claim-seized-yacht-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJSYESUQQVJPJDNIBUQ5EJDHJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢比奥称美国人质特使与哈马斯的直接会面是 "一次性的]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务卿马可-卢比奥（Marco Rubio）周一表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的人质问题特使亚当-博勒（Adam Boehler）与巴勒斯坦激进组织哈马斯（Hamas）就释放加沙人质问题进行的直接会谈是 "一次性的"，到目前为止 "尚未取得成果"。【原文：President Donald Trump's hostage envoy Adam Boehler's direct meetings with Palestinian militant group Hamas on the release of hostages in Gaza was a "one-off situation" and as of now "hasn't borne fruit," U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio said on Monday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/rubio-says-us-hostage-envoys-direct-meeting-with-hamas-was-one-off-2025-03-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGR2ZXUL65LG5AK3FPTITCFE7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>