<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:38:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:38:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德计划明年开始肥胖症药物淀粉样蛋白的后期试验]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）周四表示，该公司计划在2026年第一季度开始对超重或肥胖的成年人进行实验性减肥药淀粉样蛋白（amycretin）的注射和口服后期试验。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Thursday it plans to start late-stage trials of its experimental weight-loss drug amycretin in injection and oral forms during the first quarter of 2026 for adults who are overweight or obese.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-plans-start-late-stage-trials-experimental-obesity-drug-amycretin-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RXFSUFST5I3TATXU6YJWTOYEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:22:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称可能很快提高汽车关税以增加美国产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四警告说，他可能很快会提高汽车关税，认为这可能会促使汽车制造商加快在美国的投资。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday warned he may soon hike auto tariffs, arguing that could prod automakers to speed U.S. investments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-he-may-soon-hike-auto-tariffs-get-more-us-production-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">656X4BVTEZOJLALWB67YE42MBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:17:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，美国联邦贸易委员会可能会对 Omnicom 和 Interpublic 合并后的广告限制进行限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周四报道，联邦贸易委员会正在审查广告巨头宏盟集团（Omnicom）和英特公共集团（Interpublic）的合并提案，可能会提出一个条件，阻止合并后的公司因政治内容而抵制平台。【原文：The Federal Trade Commission, reviewing ad giants Omnicom and Interpublic's proposed merger, may impose a condition that will stop the combined company from boycotting platforms because of political content, the New York Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ftc-may-restrict-omnicom-interpublic-over-ad-restrictions-after-their-merger-nyt-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPAQRRVNNZORLGHIHG6PTVS44Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:11:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州和其他 10 个州提起诉讼，要求阻止特朗普取消 2035 年电动汽车规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[以加利福尼亚州为首的 11 个州周四提起诉讼，对国会废除该州 2035 年电动汽车规定和重型卡车要求提出质疑。【原文：A group of 11 states led by California on Thursday filed suit challenging a repeal by Congress of the state's 2035 electric vehicle rules and heavy duty truck requirements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/california-10-other-states-sue-block-trump-killing-2035-ev-rules-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CQRADWB7FOBRIQWLJ5Z7PY7SI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度航空灾难沉重打击 "世界级航空公司 "雄心]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度航空公司周四发生空难，造成 200 多名乘客遇难，使该航空公司陷入了迄今为止最严重的危机，并将对其重振声誉和机队的努力造成沉重打击。【原文：The Air India plane crash in which more than 200 passengers were killed on Thursday has plunged the airline into its deepest crisis yet and will deal a heavy blow to its efforts to revamp its reputation and fleet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/air-india-disaster-deals-heavy-blow-world-class-airline-ambition-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4WYYNBHPNNMHCKLMQO2LVCLSI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国在美国钢铁业占有 "黄金份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，美国在美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）中拥有 "黄金股份"，这是新日本制铁公司（Nippon Steel）收购这家美国标志性企业的交易的一部分。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday said the United States has a "golden share" in U.S. Steel , as part of a deal for Nippon Steel to buy the iconic American company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-us-has-golden-share-us-steel-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPIVEWIDIRLGNFZZC7SSLM57TA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织称七月预测将考虑贸易协议和不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周四表示，其将于7月份发布的下一次全球经济增长预测将同时考虑积极和消极的贸易发展态势，但拒绝预测类似于世界银行本周发布的由关税驱动的国内生产总值降级。【原文：The International Monetary Fund said on Thursday that its next global growth forecast in July will take into account both positive and negative trade developments but declined to predict a tariff-driven GDP downgrade similar to that released by the World Bank this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/imf-says-july-forecasts-take-into-account-trade-deals-uncertainty-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTXC4RDPWVKIBEGVV2UYRAXRSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:44:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克不会很快离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克周四表示，他不打算很快离开这家资产管理公司。【原文：BlackRock CEO Larry Fink said on Thursday he was not planning to leave the asset manager anytime soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-not-leaving-anytime-soon-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCGCYLHWKJMN3MNN6AKYWG4UEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:38:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易部长称英国已准备好执行美国关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国贸易大臣乔纳森-雷诺兹（Jonathan Reynolds）周四表示，英国已准备好执行其与美国达成的关税协议，并希望美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）能在未来几天内宣布协议生效。【原文：Britain is ready to implement its side of a tariff deal with the United States and is hopeful for a proclamation from U.S. President Donald Trump to put the agreement into effect in the coming days, trade minister Jonathan Reynolds said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/britain-ready-implement-us-tariff-deal-trade-minister-says-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZE2HY775BMRDOVNEEUIBKKT5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的减税法案可能会阻碍美国关键矿产项目的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[该法案取消了为促进镍、稀土和其他用于先进电子产品和武器的材料的国内生产而提供的税收抵免。【原文：The bill eliminates a tax credit for boosting domestic production of nickel, rare earths and other materials used in advanced electronics and weaponry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-tax-cut-bill-could-hold-back-us-critical-minerals-projects-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TB6JHXXLZNIJVPYTB43GIKVOIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一季度美国家庭财富下降，关税担忧打击股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周四公布的数据显示，受股市暴跌拖累，美国家庭财富在第一季度末出现下降，但这一趋势后来有所扭转。【原文：U.S. household wealth fell at the end of the first quarter, Federal Reserve data showed on Thursday, dragged down by a stock market rout that has since reversed course.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-household-wealth-dropped-in-first-quarter-tariff-concerns-hit-stocks-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOBNZ3GBJJNIZIHOFYVAJ7SBL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:14:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称不会解雇美联储主席鲍威尔，但 "可能不得不在利率问题上采取强制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，他不会解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell），并补充说他 "可能不得不采取一些措施"，作为他不断推动央行降低利率的一部分。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday said he would not fire Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, adding that he "may have to force something" as part of his ongoing push for the central bank to lower rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-wont-fire-feds-powell-may-have-force-something-rates-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3LTWLB2LBLY7KWEJMKRJHMTA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:56:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织欢迎阿根廷在 6 月底访问前采取改革措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周四表示，欢迎阿根廷中央银行和财政部在基金组织 6 月晚些时候访问该国之前采取的最新措施。【原文：The International Monetary Fund said on Thursday that it welcomed recent measures taken by Argentina's central bank and finance ministry ahead of a visit by the Fund to the country later in June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/imf-welcomes-argentina-reform-steps-ahead-end-june-visit-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQWWEBASLZO5JFB26WJFFIWDKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[淡马锡与微软、贝莱德和 MGX 携手开发人工智能基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据贝莱德（BlackRock）周四的投资者日演示幻灯片显示，淡马锡已加入一个由微软、贝莱德和科技投资公司MGX支持的财团，投资并扩大人工智能基础设施。【原文：Temasek has joined a consortium backed by Microsoft , BlackRock and tech investment company MGX to invest and expand artificial intelligence infrastructure, according to BlackRock's investor day presentation slides on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/temasek-joins-microsoft-blackrock-mgx-develop-ai-infrastructure-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGHI55ACQBPUVN3CENZDWW5Z3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芭比娃娃制造商美泰与 OpenAI 合作，计划今年推出首款人工智能产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[芭比娃娃制造商美泰公司周四表示，美泰已与 OpenAI 合作开发人工智能玩具和游戏，预计今年晚些时候将推出首款人工智能产品。【原文：Mattel has teamed up with OpenAI to develop toys and games with artificial intelligence, and expects to launch its first AI-powered product later this year, the Barbie-maker said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/barbie-maker-mattel-teams-up-with-openai-eyes-first-ai-powered-product-this-year-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIQK5JTAMNM4LNEQ5D4EG3B7B4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:50:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯雷与花旗联手投资金融科技贷款机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司凯雷集团（Carlyle Group）与美国银行业巨头花旗集团（Citigroup）周四表示，双方将合作为金融科技贷款机构提供资产支持融资。【原文：Investment firm Carlyle Group has partnered with U.S. banking giant Citigroup to provide asset-backed financing to fintech lenders, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyle-teams-up-with-citi-invest-fintech-lenders-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FVS52LUCXBO6TNGB5VUOTACXGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[捷克政府因比特币丑闻面临不信任投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷克主要反对党周四要求对政府进行不信任投票，指责政府因接受一名前罪犯向国家支付的价值 4500 万美元的比特币而腐败。【原文：The main Czech opposition party on Thursday called a no-confidence vote in the government, accusing it of corruption over the acceptance of a payment to the state by an ex-convict worth $45 million in bitcoin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/czech-government-faces-no-confidence-vote-over-bitcoin-scandal-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6TB5KGPUZIZXLDDUGJ3JXVBXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦巴第大区的意大利企业制定应对美国关税的战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利银行（Bank of Italy）周四表示，在意大利工业中心地带向美国出口的企业中，半数以上正在研究关税对策，包括在大西洋彼岸建立更大的业务。【原文：More than half of the companies from Italy's industrial heartland which export to the U.S. are studying countermeasures to tariffs, including establishing a bigger presence across the Atlantic, the Bank of Italy said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italian-firms-lombardy-strategize-against-us-tariffs-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JOTATBUL3NPG3KINVXNJMYPUH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛将美国经济衰退概率降至 30]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于特朗普关税政策的不确定性有所缓解，高盛周四将美国经济衰退的可能性从35%下调至30%。【原文：Goldman Sachs on Thursday trimmed its U.S. recession probability to 30% from 35% on easing uncertainty around Trump's tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-sachs-trims-us-recession-probability-30-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2LIYXNTO5KUXCXAQNYQ6PEW7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国对美出口因特朗普关税而遭受创纪录打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的官方数据显示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收新关税后，英国4月份对美国的商品出口创下了历史新低，这使英国的商品贸易逆差达到了三年多来的最大值。【原文：British goods exports to the United States suffered a record fall in April after U.S. President Donald Trump imposed new tariffs, official figures showed on Thursday, pushing Britain's goods trade deficit to its widest in more than three years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/british-exports-us-suffer-record-hit-trump-tariffs-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PEDVNIN4VIJTCNRTJLTCPUJIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:42:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元王冠正在迅速滑落]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国贸易政策的迅速变化令市场不安，以及对美联储降息的预期升温，美元汇率跌至三年来的最低点，从而加剧了全球最大经济体的资金外流。【原文：The dollar has sunk to its lowest in three years as rapidly changing U.S. trade policy unsettles markets and expectations build for Federal Reserve rate cuts, fuelling outflows from the world's biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/dollars-crown-is-slipping-fast-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7AZGV7ZZNKUTO36IFRSAUXS5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:39:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多数七国集团成员准备在没有美国的情况下降低俄罗斯石油价格上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的消息人士称，即使美国总统唐纳德-特朗普决定退出，七国集团中的大多数国家也准备单独行动，降低七国集团对俄罗斯石油的价格上限。【原文：Most countries in the Group of Seven nations are prepared to go it alone and lower the G7 price cap on Russian oil even if U.S. President Donald Trump decides to opt out, four sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/most-g7-members-ready-lower-russian-oil-price-cap-without-us-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXL7RQ7WVNIEPLEEYDUMCUDWSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Telus 提议完全拥有数字设备，以便更好地控制人工智能功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大电信公司 Telus 周四表示，它打算收购其上市的数字服务子公司目前未持有的股份，以寻求对该公司人工智能能力的更大控制。【原文：Telus said on Thursday it intends to acquire the shares in its listed digital services subsidiary it does not currently own, as the Canadian telecom firm seeks greater control of the unit's artificial intelligence capabilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/telus-offers-fully-own-digital-unit-greater-control-ai-capabilities-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KY4D7FKQ3RMKJC7PCACPUX2U54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国公用事业公司 RWE 与科技巨头亚马逊宣布合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国公用事业公司 RWE 和科技巨头亚马逊周四宣布了一项战略框架协议，公用事业公司将提供清洁电力输送，并以此换取云服务。【原文：German utility RWE and tech giant Amazon announced a strategic framework agreement on Thursday, where the utility will provide clean power delivery and in exchange receive cloud services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/german-utility-rwe-tech-giant-amazon-announce-partnership-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UBI6ZFSPFNDPGGRLCXCVSGGXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:21:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PPI和申请失业救济人数数据公布后，交易员提高了对美联储降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周四政府数据显示美国每周申请失业救济人数稳定在较高水平后，与美联储政策利率挂钩的期货价格反映出市场对美国央行将从9月开始连续两次降息的押注不断升温。【原文：Futures that settle to the Federal Reserve's policy rate reflected rising bets that the U.S. central bank will deliver a pair of back-to-back interest rate cuts starting in September, after government data on Thursday showed US weekly jobless claims were steady at elevated levels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/traders-boost-bets-fed-rate-cuts-after-ppi-jobless-claims-data-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPL5JPWN2NOXHLDIX6EWLPQZXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:11:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月生产者价格反弹幅度低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受机票等服务成本下降的抑制，5 月份美国生产者价格的增幅低于预期。【原文：U.S. producer prices increased less than expected in May, restrained by lower costs for services like air fares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-producer-prices-rebound-less-than-expected-may-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACUQZIK6RBJUXLKNCSACFIGFLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管中国中化集团反对，倍耐力投资者仍支持 2024 年盈利报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[倍耐力公司周四表示，尽管最大股东、中国国有控股集团中化集团（Sinochem）反对，但投资者还是批准了这家意大利轮胎制造商去年的财报。【原文：Pirelli investors on Thursday approved the Italian tyremaker's earnings report for last year despite the opposition of its largest shareholder, the Chinese state-controlled group Sinochem , the company said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/pirelli-investors-back-2024-earnings-report-despite-opposition-chinas-sinochem-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOJUNHQFGZLVHNPRYA3EJ4FXJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报道称龙星集团将向法国 BPCE 出售葡萄牙 Novo Banco 银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[葡萄牙经济新闻媒体 ECO 周四称，美国私募股权基金 Lone Star 已决定将其持有的葡萄牙新银行（Novo Banco）75% 的股份出售给法国银行集团 BPCE，该交易对葡萄牙第四大银行的估值约为 70 亿欧元（81.4 亿美元）。【原文：U.S. private equity fund Lone Star has decided to sell its 75% stake in Novo Banco to French banking group BPCE in a deal that would value Portugal's fourth-largest lender at around 7 billion euros ($8.14 billion), Portuguese economic news outlet ECO said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/lone-star-sell-portugals-novo-banco-french-bpce-report-says-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPTBCDUKHRNSDAWWUT5SJC5WMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通维持 2025 年油价在 60 美元中低水平的预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周四淡化了对地缘政治的担忧，并维持其对油价的基本预测，即到2025年油价将保持在60美元上下，2026年将保持在60美元，但摩根大通表示，某些最坏的情况可能会使油价飙升至上述水平的两倍。【原文：JP Morgan downplayed geopolitical concerns on Thursday and maintained its base case forecast for oil prices to stay in the low-to-mid $60s through 2025 and $60 in 2026, but said certain worst-case scenarios could send prices surging to double those levels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/jp-morgan-maintains-2025-forecast-oil-prices-low-to-mid-60s-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJWYYUXADRI5BJXZ7DDXJBPI7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:51:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数稳定在较高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于劳动力市场状况继续稳步缓解，上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数保持在较高水平。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits was unchanged at higher levels last week as labor market conditions continued to steadily ease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-steady-higher-levels-2025-06-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYCNKSF4LBPFTMBTXZZJKUK7E4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>