<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 04:07:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 04:07:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，GIP 接近达成以约 400 亿美元收购 Aligned 数据中心的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，黑石集团旗下的全球基础设施合伙公司（Global Infrastructure Partners）正在就收购麦格理支持的 Aligned Data Centers 进行深入谈判，Aligned 的估值将达到 400 亿美元。【原文：BlackRock-owned Global Infrastructure Partners is in advanced talks to acquire Macquarie-backed Aligned Data Centers in a deal valuing Aligned at $40 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/gip-nears-deal-buy-aligned-data-centers-about-40-billion-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OBBYCFGJRMGLP7L47KSOJVMCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 02:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普政府施压后，苹果移除 ICE 跟踪应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四表示，在与唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府部门联系后，它已从应用商店中删除了最流行的 ICE 跟踪应用程序 ICEBlock 和其他类似应用程序。【原文：Apple said on Thursday that it had removed ICEBlock, the most popular ICE-tracking app, and other similar apps from its App Store after it was contacted by President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/apple-removes-ice-tracking-apps-after-pressure-by-trump-administration-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXIG33JM2NPEDE3QVYFP62RVMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 01:56:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者权衡日本央行和大选影响，日元缩减周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于交易商考虑到日本央行可能加息以及本周末领导层选举的影响，日元周五走低，缩减了四个多月来的最大单周涨幅。【原文：The yen edged lower on Friday, trimming its sharpest weekly gain in more than four months, as traders considered the impact of potential rate increases by the Bank of Japan and a leadership election this weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/yen-trims-weekly-advance-investors-weigh-boj-election-impacts-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6FNHNVBTNMYFEWOIMHXOANIXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 01:54:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文称黑客试图敲诈其客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[甲骨文公司周四表示，其电子商务套件产品的客户 "收到了勒索邮件"，这证实了 Alphabet 旗下谷歌公司周三首次发出的警告。【原文：Oracle said on Thursday that customers of its E-Business Suite of products "have received extortion emails," confirming a warning first issued on Wednesday by Alphabet's Google.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/oracle-says-hackers-are-trying-extort-its-customers-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDNCWXCNRJLW7FA4RDYII3GXQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 01:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚电信公司因在网速方面误导客户被罚款 1200 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚竞争监督机构周五表示，澳大利亚第一大电信公司 Telstra 因未通知约 9000 名用户而降低其网速计划，被联邦法院处以 1800 万澳元（约合 1187 万美元）的罚款。【原文：Telstra , Australia's no.1 telecom firm, has been fined A$18 million ($11.87 million) by the Federal Court for lowering internet speed plan for about 9,000 customers without informing them, the country's competition watchdog said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australia-fines-telstra-12-million-misleading-customers-internet-speed-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7E27YBR7M5OFNDYX5LWHPZ6F2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 01:49:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行上田警告全球不确定性将影响工资前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田一夫周五表示，央行将仔细研究美国关税和海外经济长期不确定性的影响是否会阻碍企业提高工资。【原文：Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda said on Friday the central bank will scrutinise whether the impact from U.S. tariffs and prolonged overseas economic uncertainty could discourage companies from raising wages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bojs-ueda-warns-global-uncertainty-impact-wage-outlook-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHTS4AWSRZJWPN57NR5GQW24T4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 01:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市因降息赌注和人工智能热潮而录得周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市有望实现稳健的周涨幅，因为美联储在短期内降息的可能性上升，有助于缓解因美国政府停摆而产生的不安情绪，这种情绪已将黄金推至纪录高位并拖累美元。【原文：Asian stocks were poised for solid weekly gains on Friday as rising odds of the Federal Reserve cutting rates in the near-term helped cushion jitters around a U.S. government shutdown that have pushed gold to record highs and weighed on the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLOVYW4QV5PB7B27CBCVERHKK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 01:22:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：特朗普推迟阿联酋芯片交易令英伟达黄仁勋和官员们感到沮丧]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，英伟达公司（Nvidia）向阿拉伯联合酋长国提供人工智能芯片的数十亿美元交易在签署近五个月后仍处于中立状态，这令公司首席执行官黄仁勋和一些高级政府官员感到沮丧。【原文：A multibillion-dollar deal to send Nvidia's artificial-intelligence chips to the United Arab Emirates is stuck in neutral nearly five months after it was signed, frustrating CEO Jensen Huang and some senior administration officials, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/delays-trumps-uae-chips-deal-frustrate-nvidias-jensen-huang-officials-wsj-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDSMW3ESLZJBDCRTHV7MEGU454</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油有望创下 3 个半月来最大单周跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在连续四个交易日下跌后周五小幅上涨，但由于市场预期欧佩克+组织可能不顾供应过剩的担忧进一步提高产量，油价有望创下6月底以来的最大单周跌幅。【原文：Oil prices rose slightly on Friday after four straight sessions of declines but were on track for their steepest weekly decline since late June due to market expectations that the OPEC+ group could hike output further despite oversupply concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-track-steepest-weekly-plunge-3-12-months-2025-10-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S46DZ6DNAFJGPEZS3AA2VEMRBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:19:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司第三季度交付 62 架喷气机，同比增长 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周四表示，2025年第三季度交付了62架飞机，比去年同期的59架高出约5%。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer said on Thursday it delivered 62 aircraft in the third quarter of 2025, about 5% higher than the 59 deliveries in the same period last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/planemaker-embraer-delivers-62-jets-q3-up-5-year-earlier-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWCLWF7KBVPWDB27YWXT2HNAZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 要求法院驳回马斯克 xAI 的商业机密诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI周四请求联邦法官驳回一项指控其引诱员工离开埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的人工智能初创公司xAI以窃取其商业机密的诉讼，并称此案是马斯克对该公司 "持续骚扰 "的一部分。【原文：OpenAI asked a federal judge on Thursday to dismiss a lawsuit alleging it lured employees away from Elon Musk's artificial intelligence startup xAI to steal its trade secrets, calling the case part of Musk's "ongoing harassment" of the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/openai-asks-court-dismiss-trade-secret-lawsuit-musks-xai-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANNO4JN5JRM5RPTFOULUFQVKRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片出口受限，应用材料公司 2026 年收入将减少 6 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片设备制造商应用材料公司（Applied Materials）预计，在美国扩大其限制出口名单，对半导体、飞机和医疗设备等行业造成打击后，2026 财年的收入将受到 6 亿美元的冲击。【原文：Chip equipment maker Applied Materials forecast a $600 million hit to fiscal 2026 revenue after the U.S. expanded its restricted export list in a blow to sectors such as semiconductors, aircraft and medical equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/applied-materials-flags-600-mln-revenue-hit-2026-broader-chip-export-curbs-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXBD7COT4VK6JLCNHUT76SK2SY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用动力公司获得 12.5 亿美元 IT 合同，为美军在欧洲和非洲的行动提供支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[国防巨头通用动力公司（General Dynamics）的信息和技术部门在宣布另一份价值 15 亿美元的美国国防合同一周后，于本周四表示已获得一份价值 12.5 亿美元的任务订单，以支持美国陆军在欧洲和非洲的行动。【原文：Defense giant General Dynamics' information and technology unit had secured a $1.25 billion task order to support the U.S. Army in Europe and Africa, it said on Thursday, a week after announcing another $1.5 billion U.S. defense contract.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/general-dynamics-gets-125-billion-it-contract-support-us-army-europe-africa-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQ3IXK6EPRPUXK2SHGV5AFKCZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:26:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的 1 万亿美元薪酬计划面临投资者和州政府官员的反对]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份监管文件显示，包括 SOC 投资集团和几位州政府官员在内的一批特斯拉股东敦促投资者在公司 11 月份的会议上投票反对埃隆-马斯克 1 万亿美元的薪酬方案。【原文：A group of Tesla shareholders including SOC Investment Group and several state officials urged investors to vote against Elon Musk's $1 trillion pay package at the company's November meeting, a regulatory filing showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/elon-musks-1-trillion-pay-plan-faces-pushback-investors-state-officials-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BYXOH7SJJZJSDGSKLGXFNL3VVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 人工智能、美联储押注一扫停摆焦虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FDQ7333RYNKJXD6JMEFQAQB6RI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，波音 777X 将推迟到 2027 年面世]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，波音公司的 777X 喷气式飞机将于 2027 年初而不是明年开始商业飞行。【原文：Boeing's 777X jet is slated to start flying commercially in early 2027 instead of next year, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-777x-be-delayed-2027-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIUAVTLFBVIGDG6GJSHR7ALRSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:14:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院将重新审议航空公司收费决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家联邦上诉法院周四表示，将重新考虑其最近的裁定，即美国运输部有权制定航空公司费用披露规则。【原文：A federal appeals court on Thursday said it will reconsider its recent holding that the U.S. Department of Transportation has authority to write rules governing disclosures of airline fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-appeals-court-reconsider-airline-fees-decision-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UREXMJAANVKYZKQHBLN6MRZDPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会（NTSB）和美国联邦航空局（FAA）将调查亚马逊两架无人机坠毁事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国两家机构周四表示，他们将亚利桑那州托勒森市两架亚马逊 Prime Air 无人机撞上起重机的事件。【原文：Two U.S. agencies said Thursday they will the collision of two Amazon Prime Air delivery drones into a crane in Tolleson, Arizona.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ntsb-faa-probe-crashes-two-amazon-delivery-drones-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L65EBSXM6FIEJEKEQXC3K76WYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与 NBC 环球达成协议防止 YouTube 内容停播]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌和康卡斯特旗下的 NBC 环球公司表示，他们已达成一项长期协议，将在 YouTube TV 上保留 NBC 的节目，包括 "周日橄榄球之夜 "和 "美国达人秀"。【原文：Alphabet's Google and Comcast-owned NBCUniversal said they had reached a long-term agreement to retain availability of NBC shows, including "Sunday Night Football" and "America's Got Talent", on YouTube TV.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/google-reaches-agreement-with-nbcuniversal-prevent-youtube-content-blackout-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYFY6XH6RBNAXEVA353GILE7SY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:47:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JBS 投资 7000 万美元重返巴拉圭，包括购买工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西肉类包装商 JBS 周四发表声明，宣布未来两年在巴拉圭投资 7000 万美元，其中包括收购一家鸡肉加工厂。【原文：Brazilian meatpacker JBS on Thursday announced investments of $70 million in Paraguay over the next two years, including the acquisition of a chicken processing plant, according to a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/jbs-returns-paraguay-with-70-million-investment-including-plant-purchase-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CR4UBXI2QZJLXIIC2ABYDJ2YDU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员呼吁波音公司结束长达八周的圣路易斯罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员伯尼-桑德斯（Bernie Sanders）在周三发出的一封信中敦促波音公司结束在圣路易斯地区长达八周的罢工。【原文：U.S. Senator Bernie Sanders urged Boeing in a letter sent on Wednesday to end the eight-week-long strike in the St. Louis area, where it produces fighters, munitions and other military aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/senators-call-boeing-end-eight-week-long-st-louis-strike-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR2APOJ7QROPDPC2O4VQHCTORA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称巴西有望凭借扩张潜力领跑全球罗布斯塔咖啡种植业]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰拉博银行（Rabobank）周四发布的一份报告显示，受罗布斯塔咖啡对气候的适应能力和全球需求增长的推动，巴西正准备超越越南，成为世界上最大的罗布斯塔咖啡生产国。【原文：Brazil is positioning itself to overtake Vietnam as the world's largest robusta coffee producer, driven by the crop's climate resilience and growing global demand, according to a report by Dutch bank Rabobank released on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-poised-lead-global-robusta-coffee-farming-expansion-potential-report-says-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCIPWRT4GFK7NDKSNCVQCYDTQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡斯卡迪亚资本设立硅谷新中心，瞄准科技并购领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[精品投资银行卡斯卡迪亚资本（Cascadia Capital）的高管告诉路透社，该公司正在向科技并购领域扩张，因为它聘请了一位资深科技银行家，并准备在硅谷开设办事处。【原文：Boutique investment bank Cascadia Capital is expanding into technology M&amp;A as it hires a veteran technology banker and prepares to open a Silicon Valley office, the firm’s executives told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cascadia-capital-targets-tech-ma-with-new-silicon-valley-hub-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOOB3E6ZLVLOBFUG35BFNMRKCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）认为在关税提高的情况下全球通胀形势喜忧参半]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）发言人朱莉-科扎克（Julie Kozack）周四表示，IMF认为全球通胀形势喜忧参半，因为美国和其他提高关税国家的企业迄今已消化了大部分较高的关税，而中国等主要出口国的需求仍受到抑制。【原文：The International Monetary Fund sees a mixed inflation picture globally as companies in the U.S. and other tariff-raising countries have so far absorbed much of the higher duties, while demand remains suppressed in major exporting countries like China, IMF spokesperson Julie Kozack said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imf-sees-mixed-global-inflation-picture-face-higher-tariffs-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3T7ZNYR2FFOKDH5MHXD4JNPHTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷债券摇摆不定，关注美国贝森特的支持承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）表示，即将在华盛顿举行的当面讨论将 "有意义地推进 "美国对阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱（Javier Milei）政府的财政支持承诺，但随后他在接受采访时又表示，美国 "不会向阿根廷投入资金"，此后阿根廷的国际美元债券在周四呈现震荡走势。【原文：Argentina's international dollar bonds zigzagged on Thursday after U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said upcoming in-person discussions in Washington would "meaningfully advance" the country's pledge of financial support for President Javier Milei's government, but later said in an interview that the U.S. is "not putting money into Argentina".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/argentinas-bonds-wobble-with-eyes-us-bessents-support-pledge-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFV5CWNP75NCTH3PABTHG57YUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026 年，Humana 将有 20% 的会员加入高评级医疗保险计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[Humana 周四表示，根据初步数据，该公司目前约有 20% 或 120 万会员参加了 2026 年被评为 4 星级及以上的医疗保险优势计划。【原文：Humana said on Thursday it has about 20%, or 1.2 million, of its members currently enrolled in Medicare Advantage plans rated 4 stars and above for 2026, based on preliminary data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/humana-sees-20-its-members-high-rated-medicare-plans-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U3KSYKLQFMUJEYYWK6NKVSUXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:48:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果美联储降息削弱美国加元，加元将反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于美联储降息预期对美元构成压力，加元兑美元汇率将在未来一年走强，但美国-墨西哥-加拿大贸易协定的不确定前景可能使这一预测面临风险。【原文：The Canadian dollar is set to strengthen over the coming year against its U.S. counterpart as expected Federal Reserve interest rate cuts weigh on the greenback, but uncertain prospects for the United States-Mexico-Canada trade agreement could put that forecast at risk, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadian-dollar-set-rebound-if-fed-rate-cuts-weaken-us-counterpart-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6N3EWJOMRLSNCF7VDZMIDWQAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长维勒鲁瓦表示，扩大与受美国关税影响国家的联系可增强欧元的全球作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国央行行长表示，欧洲必须迅速采取行动，加强欧元的全球作用，因为这样做的机会之窗可能很快就会关闭，欧洲集团应寻求与受美国关税影响最大的国家加强联系，以帮助其实现这一目标。【原文：Europe must act fast to bolster the global role of the euro as the window of opportunity to do so may soon close, and the bloc should seek greater ties with nations most affected by U.S. tariffs to help it achieve that, the French central bank chief said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/expanded-ties-with-countries-hurt-by-us-tariffs-could-bolster-euros-global-role-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EEN6E53JFLJNJEQMFOBR3OT2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定埃隆-马斯克不能将美国证券交易委员会对 Twitter 的诉讼移出华盛顿特区]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）未能说服华盛顿特区的一名联邦法官将美国证券交易委员会（Securities and Exchange Commission）对他迟迟未披露其在推特（Twitter）持股增加一事的诉讼移至德克萨斯州，此前他曾表示自己太忙，无法在美国首都为自己辩护。【原文：Elon Musk failed to persuade a Washington, D.C. federal judge to move a Securities and Exchange Commission lawsuit over his late disclosure of his growing Twitter stake to Texas, after saying he was too busy to defend himself in the nation's capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/elon-musk-cannot-move-secs-twitter-lawsuit-out-washington-dc-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFUSEHKRTFPGVLCF35OLN3K6G4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根称美国央行在降息问题上必须 "非常谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周四表示，美国央行上个月的降息行动适当地为劳动力市场的急剧恶化购买了一些保险，但需要对任何进一步的降息行动保持 "谨慎"，因为通胀率正在高于目标值，而且还在不断上升。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan on Thursday said the U.S. central bank appropriately took out some insurance against any sharp deterioration in the labor market with its interest-rate cut last month, but needs to be "cautious" with any further rate cuts because inflation is running above target and is heading upward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-says-us-central-bank-must-be-very-cautious-rate-cuts-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMKPYGHPJ5ONPII36OZYPEFMYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>