<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:04:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:04:30 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[密歇根大学数据显示，美国消费者近期通胀预期为2020年以来最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者认为明年的通胀将继续放缓，周五公布的8月份物价增长预期指数为2020年底以来的最低水平。【原文：U.S. consumers see inflation continuing to moderate in the next year, with a gauge of price growth expectations published on Friday at the lowest level in August since late 2020.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumers-near-term-inflation-expectation-lowest-since-2020-umich-data-shows-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IW43PHQU3FPP5LRNFNHTGDQNRI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺福克南方公司与另外五个工会达成临时协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铁路运营商诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern）周五表示，该公司已与五个工会达成了为期五年的临时劳资协议。【原文：Norfolk Southern has reached tentative, five-year labor agreements with five unions, the U.S. railroad operator said on Friday, at a time when thousands of employees in the industry are negotiating for better pay and working conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/norfolk-southern-reaches-tentative-agreements-with-five-more-labor-unions-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7W7DX4XORPVLDZRG6URYWFKSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度法庭批准迪士尼与 Reliance 媒体资产合并案]]></title><description><![CDATA[信实公司周五表示，印度公司法庭已批准信实工业公司和迪斯尼公司以 85 亿美元合并印度媒体资产。【原文：An Indian company tribunal has approved the $8.5 billion merger of Reliance Industries and Disney's Indian media assets, Reliance said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/indian-tribunal-approves-disney-reliance-media-assets-merger-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJZHG4Y6URPO3PENYOC3WXL6DM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:10:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国务院称 RTX 将因出口错误支付 2 亿美元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院周四的记录显示，RTX 公司将支付 2 亿美元的罚款，以了结其违反出口法，与包括中国在内的违禁国家交换数据和产品的指控。【原文：RTX Corp will pay a $200 million fine to settle allegations it violated export laws by exchanging data and products with prohibited countries including China, State Department records dated Thursday said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtx-pay-200-million-fine-export-mistakes-state-department-says-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPDXS5L56RNZFJPHODSPJINNBY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受房地产行业拖累，中国顶级银行第二季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[在经济放缓和房地产行业陷入困境的背景下，中国政府为刺激疲软的贷款需求而降低贷款利率，中国五大贷款机构中有四家本周公布第二季度利润下降。【原文：Four of China's five largest lenders reported a lower second-quarter profit this week after responding to a government nudge to lower lending rates in order to stimulate weak loan demand amid a slowing economy and struggling property sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-top-banks-post-lower-second-quarter-profit-property-sector-weighs-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXHVAFYQCFIQ7GJQQLQHUGPDA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[押注降息，美国债券基金资金大幅流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至8月28日的一周内，由于政府债券基金的强劲购买，美国债券基金获得了稳健的资金流入，这主要得益于对美联储9月份降息的押注以及投资者对中东地缘政治紧张局势的谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. bond funds racked up solid inflows in the week to Aug. 28 thanks to a robust purchase in government bond funds, driven by bets of a Federal Reserve interest rate cut in September and investor caution over geopolitical tensions in the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-bond-funds-see-sharp-inflows-amid-bets-rate-cut-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIR2R6PBS5PZXFAXAKCYZEGJ5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室称将在未来几天内宣布对中国进口商品征收 301 条款关税的决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室周五表示，正在继续就对中国进口商品征收301条款关税的问题制定最终决定，并将在未来几天内公布决定。【原文：The U.S. Trade Representative's office said on Friday it was continuing to develop final determination on Section 301 tariffs on Chinese imports and will make a decision public in the coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/ustr-says-decision-section-301-tariffs-chinese-imports-be-announced-coming-days-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTY5Y357RVNYDICW7N434R4UVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大铁路工会向法院提出复工令挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表加拿大两大铁路公司工人的工会周五表示，该工会已向法院提出四项异议，反对加拿大工业劳工委员会迫使工人复工的裁决。【原文：The union representing workers at Canada's two main rail companies said on Friday it had filed four court challenges against a ruling by the country's industrial labor board that forced them back to work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-rail-union-launches-court-challenge-back-to-work-order-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DH7HXXW7G5LKJP4A5S4N72HFC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称 "欧佩克+"可能从 10 月起按计划增产]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+组织的六位消息人士告诉路透社，欧佩克+组织将按计划从10月份开始提高石油产量，因为利比亚停产和一些成员国承诺减产以弥补产量过剩，从而抵消了需求低迷的影响。【原文：OPEC+ is set to proceed with a planned oil output hike from October, as Libyan outages and pledged cuts by some members to compensate for overproduction counter the impact of sluggish demand, six sources from the producer group told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-likely-proceed-with-planned-output-hike-october-sources-say-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NRLAKANMVOKNL37GHD4D63GZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:03:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国PCE通胀无意外改变美联储宽松路径]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五表示，个人消费支出（PCE）价格指数继6月份未经修正的0.1%涨幅之后，上个月又上涨了0.2%，符合经济学家的预测。【原文：The personal consumption expenditures (PCE) price index rose 0.2% last month after an unrevised 0.1% gain in June, the Commerce Department said on Friday, matching economists' forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-no-surprises-us-pce-inflation-alter-fed-easing-path-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOBRE6SDNNJKZO5PV62B3KHZ2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员认为美联储将在 9 月降息 25 个基点，年底前降息 100 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国中央银行首选的7月份通胀指标显示通胀上升符合经济学家的预期，甚至消费者支出稳健增长之后，交易员们增加了对美联储将在下个月开始降息的押注，将政策利率下调四分之一个百分点，而不是更大幅度的下调半个百分点。
交易员们继续认为美联储将在下半年降息。【原文：Traders added to bets that the Federal Reserve will start U.S. interest-rate cuts next month with a quarter-point reduction in the policy rate, rather than a bigger half-point cut, after the U.S. central bank's preferred gauge of inflation for July showed inflation rose in line with economist expectations even as consumer spending increased solidly.
Traders continued to see the Fed cutting rates b】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-see-fed-delivering-25-bps-cut-sept-100-bps-by-year-end-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HVP67DN2JJDTIIJIHJAFTKWQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:48:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者支出回升；7 月通胀温和上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者支出在 7 月份稳健增长，表明经济在第三季度初仍处于较为坚实的基础上，这也为美联储下月降息半个百分点提供了论据。【原文：U.S. consumer spending increased solidly in July, suggesting the economy remained on firmer ground early in the third quarter and arguing against a half-percentage-point interest rate cut from the Federal Reserve next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-spending-picks-up-inflation-rises-moderately-july-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2DOIMSNTNJBZE3EWQ5DKEEMRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:43:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车推迟向 Thacker Pass 追加 3.3 亿美元投资，Lithium Americas 表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[美洲锂业公司周五表示，汽车制造商通用汽车公司已将对该矿商价值 3.3 亿美元的第二批投资推迟到今年年底。【原文：Lithium Americas said on Friday automaker General Motors has delayed the second tranche of investment, worth $330 million, in the miner until the end of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-delays-additional-330-mln-investment-thacker-pass-lithium-americas-says-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7L7DRST4ZPATNLEOHTSZECV3U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:24:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢拉称马斯克必须尊重巴西最高法院，X 公司正准备停产]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周五表示，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）必须尊重巴西最高法院的裁决。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Friday that billionaire Elon Musk must respect the rulings of the country's Supreme Court, amid an ongoing feud that left social media giant X on the brink of being taken down in Brazil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/lula-says-musk-must-respect-brazils-top-court-x-braces-shutdown-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJWTQX54I5LL5HCUYXUQLIORKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:22:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息预期和中东紧张局势令全球债券基金获得稳健资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至8月28日的七天里，全球债券基金吸引了六周以来最大的单周资金流入，这主要是受美联储9月降息预期和中东持续紧张局势推动下政府债券购买增加的影响。【原文：Global bond funds attracted the biggest weekly inflow in six weeks in the seven days to Aug. 28, buoyed by heightened purchases of government bonds amid anticipation of a September Fed rate cut and ongoing Middle East tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDP3KUIIT5KPXMCEOE54I2EXI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:18:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔上涨，因有报道称芯片制造商正在探索各种选择，激发了投资者的热情]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五收盘前，英特尔的股价上涨了 3% 以上，因为有报道称这家陷入困境的芯片制造商正在探索包括合并或分拆在内的各种选择，这在该股经历了数十年来最严重的一次暴跌之后，激发了一些投资者的热情。【原文：Intel's shares rose more than 3% before the bell on Friday, as a report of the struggling chipmaker exploring options that could include a merger or a split induced some investor enthusiasm after one of the stock's worst slumps in decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-rises-report-chipmaker-exploring-options-stokes-investor-enthusiasm-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALM7TCYVGRIKZMZTSHNHLRWPNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:16:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴尔股价大涨，因人工智能服务器需求提振业绩和预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[戴尔科技公司（Dell Technologies）股价在周五的盘前交易中上涨了 6%，此前对其人工智能服务器的强劲需求推动该公司上调了全年盈利和营收预期。【原文：Shares of Dell Technologies rose 6% in premarket trading on Friday, after robust demand for its artificial intelligence-powered servers propelled the company to raise its full-year earnings and revenue forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/dell-shares-jump-ai-server-demand-boosts-results-forecasts-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6F6KU4EPURODLCNYE7CBYM25IU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:30:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价面临中国需求放缓和库存增加的压力 - 路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于主要进口国中国的燃料需求疲软，以及沙特阿拉伯和欧佩克+盟国准备从10月份开始放松部分减产措施导致库存水平上升，分析师们下调了2024年的油价展望。【原文：Analysts have lowered their 2024 oil price outlook due to weak fuel demand from leading importer China and rising inventory levels as Saudi Arabia and OPEC+ allies prepare to ease some output cuts from October, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-face-pressure-slow-china-demand-inventory-rise-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7W5MSTUQOVJG3HVYKHFBJ2NODE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息，预计美国房价将小幅上涨--路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查的住房分析师称，尽管供应紧张和美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）降息的预期，今明两年美国房价仍将相对温和地上涨。【原文：U.S. home prices will rise relatively modestly this year and next despite tight supply and expected U.S. Federal Reserve interest rate cuts, according to housing analysts polled by Reuters who said purchasing affordability will improve but would remain strained.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-home-prices-forecast-rise-modestly-fed-cuts-rates-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPULFVAVGVN6NP4H6S54PCUORI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[碧桂园进一步推迟 2023 年年度业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最大的房地产开发商碧桂园进一步推迟公布其 2023 年财务业绩，称在持续的债务重组中需要更多时间。【原文：China's largest property developer Country Garden further delayed the publication of its 2023 financial results saying it needed more time amid an ongoing debt restructuring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/country-garden-further-delays-2023-annual-results-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZ3XIZWHDNPVFE36V5XN4Y5LN4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储 9 月会议临近，期货上涨，通胀数据成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货走高，投资者关注一份至关重要的通胀报告，该报告可能会影响对美联储今年降息幅度的预期。【原文：U.S. stock index futures traded higher on Friday as investors focused on a crucial inflation report that could influence expectations about the extent of the Federal Reserve's interest-rate cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-rise-inflation-data-spotlight-feds-september-meeting-nears-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNKGPJIJJVNN3KZ3K6QNV2YUBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:32:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：屡创新高，除了老地方]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SG5BZLJJ5RIF7IKD2KXYA7D66I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:06:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国监管机构发现银行在气候风险方面还有很多工作要做]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士表示，美国银行业最高监管机构发现，主要贷款机构在评估和管理气候变化给其业务带来的风险方面还处于早期阶段，在某些领域还需要做大量工作。【原文：A top U.S. banking regulator has found that major lenders are in the early stages of assessing and managing the risks climate change poses to their businesses, and that significant work is needed in some areas, three people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-regulator-finds-banks-have-work-do-climate-risk-sources-say-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G57N4BBY7NM4FN67S4CESGXW6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:04:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼和 DirecTV 力争在 NFL 赛季前续约]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔特-迪斯尼公司和卫星电视供应商 DirecTV 正在争分夺秒地争取在当前协议于周日到期之前续签发行协议。【原文：Walt Disney and satellite TV provider DirecTV are racing to renew their distribution agreement before the current pact expires on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-directv-aim-renew-deal-ahead-nfl-season-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44ENVMGCUBMLNBSDBZRIDWPVLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门称电子商务巨头阿里巴巴已完成三年 "整改期"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家市场监督管理总局周五发表声明称，阿里巴巴集团在 2021 年因垄断行为被罚款后已完成三年 "整改"。【原文：China's State Administration of Market Regulation issued a statement on Friday saying Alibaba Group had completed three years "rectification" following a fine levied in 2021 for monopolistic behaviour.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinas-market-regulator-says-e-commerce-giant-alibaba-has-completed-three-year-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UACACND2OVM4HGBCZTB2QFCFOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:59:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒂森克虏伯工会称钢铁领导层危机使出售面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国企业集团蒂森克虏伯公司的劳资协议会负责人周五表示，蒂森克虏伯计划出售其钢铁业务，但由于该部门领导层出现危机，出售计划面临不确定性风险。【原文：Thyssenkrupp's planned sale of its steel business is at risk over uncertainy following a leadership crisis at the unit, the German conglomerate's works council head said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/thyssenkrupp-works-council-says-steel-leadership-crisis-puts-sale-risk-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7R3IMHMQRKTBHPN63M2JMLRWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:42:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，SIX 集团正在探索金融信息部门的备选方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位知情人士透露，瑞士证券市场运营商 SIX 集团正在权衡其金融信息部门的各种选择，包括可能与另一家公司合并。【原文：Swiss stock market operator SIX Group is weighing options for its financial information unit, including potentially merging it with another player, according to three people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/six-group-explores-options-financial-information-unit-sources-say-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76SOVVO3DRLRPIPKDMVLDVIM6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PDD 与中国其他大型电子商务公司相比有何优势？]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周早些时候，中国最大的电子商务公司--阿里巴巴、JD.com 和 PDD Holdings--的股票遭到抛售，原因是担心低价供应商 PDD 承诺为提供折扣投入更多资金后，这些公司的利润率会受到压力。【原文：Shares of China's biggest e-commerce companies - Alibaba , JD.com and PDD Holdings - were dumped earlier this week on worries about pressure on their margins after low-price vendor PDD pledged to invest more for offering discounts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/how-does-pdd-stack-up-against-other-big-china-e-ecommerce-firms-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQNWNGE2SZPIZGNNPPIRT6EV2U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:17:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[问克劳德？亚马逊求助于 Anthropic 的人工智能来改造 Alexa]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位熟知内情的人士告诉路透社，亚马逊将于 10 月份美国假日季前发布的改版 Alexa 将主要由 Anthropic 的 Claude 人工智能模型提供支持，而不是由亚马逊自己的人工智能提供支持。【原文：Amazon's revamped Alexa due for release in October ahead of the U.S. holiday season will be powered primarily by Anthropic's Claude artificial intelligence models, rather than its own AI, five people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/amazon-turns-anthropics-claude-alexa-ai-revamp-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTBRUVYHQBMKBCDJYE7ECA32MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国监管机构称特斯拉北京将召回 870 辆进口 Model X 电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周五表示，特斯拉汽车公司（Tesla Motors Beijing）将从10月8日起召回870辆进口Model X汽车，原因是需要检查用于固定车顶的粘合剂，该粘合剂可能存在安全隐患。【原文：China's market regulator said on Friday that Tesla Motors Beijing will recall 870 imported Model X vehicles from Oct. 8 due to a need to check the adhesive used to attach the roof of the vehicles which may pose a safety hazard.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-beijing-recall-870-imported-model-x-evs-china-regulator-says-2024-08-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LW3HAN6I3VIMPAFM3GNR6UCYNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 07:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>