<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:14:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:14:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[由于 B2C 增长缓慢，Expedia 下调全年收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线旅行社 Expedia 周四下调了 2024 年收入增长预期，原因是企业对消费者业务表现不佳，影响了总预订量。【原文：Online travel agency Expedia cut its 2024 revenue growth forecast on Thursday, as gross bookings were hit by poor performance in its business-to-consumer segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/expedia-lowers-full-year-revenue-forecast-slow-b2c-growth-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEOYY5IKPZPBTFUL7D6QW5UIHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果销售额降幅低于预期，首席执行官认为将恢复增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四公布的季度营收降幅小于预期，公司首席执行官蒂姆-库克（Tim Cook）告诉路透社记者，随着未来几个月对人工智能功能的投入，公司预计本季度销售额将恢复增长。【原文：Apple on Thursday reported a smaller than expected decline in quarterly revenue, and Chief Executive Tim Cook told Reuters the company expects a return to sales growth in the current quarter as it invests in AI features to be unveiled in the coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-sales-fall-less-than-expected-ceo-sees-return-growth-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUXZJXZVHRM7TNNU6W2Z3MO3YM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受国际旅游需求影响，Booking 季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Booking Holdings 周四公布第一季度利润增长，原因是强劲的国际旅游需求抵消了美国休闲旅游需求的放缓。【原文：Booking Holdings reported higher first-quarter profit on Thursday, as strong demand for international travel offset moderating leisure travel demand in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/booking-reports-higher-quarterly-profit-international-travel-demand-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLWD5EH4CFIJTE7FPGHUHGI43I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:29:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MP 材料公司第一季度亏损额超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[稀土矿商 MP Materials 周四公布的第一季度财报显示，受精矿销售下降和战略材料价格疲软的影响，该公司的亏损幅度超出预期。
 MP 公司将从加利福尼亚州山口矿开采的岩石加工成稀土精矿。该公司是继澳大利亚林纳斯稀土公司（Lynas Rare Earths）之后，中国以外的第二大稀土生产商，其稀土产量约占全球总产量的 15%。【原文：Rare earths miner MP Materials reported wider-than-expected loss in first quarter on Thursday, hurt by lower concentrate sales and weak prices of the strategic materials.
 MP processes rock it extracts from its Mountain Pass mine in California into rare earths concentrate. It is the second-biggest producer of rare earths outside China after Australia's Lynas Rare Earths and produces about 15% of t】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/mp-materials-report-wider-than-expected-q1-loss-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V25P7HC6ENOETMEAGSSIS3S3YM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:23:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油产量增加，EOG 资源公司第一季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于石油和天然气公司受益于石油产量的增加，EOG Resources 周四公布的第一季度利润超出预期。【原文：EOG Resources beat first-quarter profit estimates on Thursday as the oil and gas firm benefited from higher oil production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/eog-resources-beats-first-quarter-profit-estimates-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQIPHQAW3BMXHI4E6VGHMQSYSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费支出回暖，百佳超市第一季度利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰克-多西（Jack Dorsey）领导的布洛克公司（Block）周四公布第一季度利润大幅增长，原因是这家支付公司受益于消费者支出的恢复性增长和自身的成本削减。【原文：Jack Dorsey-led Block posted a jump in first-quarter profit on Thursday as the payments firm benefited from resilient consumer spending and its own cost cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blocks-first-quarter-profit-jumps-resilient-consumer-spending-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLCX66CBX5I5DFIEWQLCNCFZIE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:19:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币价格暴涨，Coinbase 利润飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase Global 第一季度利润大幅增长，这主要得益于 1 月份推出首批美国现货比特币交易所交易基金后加密货币交易量的上升。【原文：Coinbase Global posted a sizable jump in profit in the first-quarter, helped by an uptick in cryptocurrency trading following the launch of the first U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/coinbase-posts-soaring-profit-jump-crypto-prices-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7OGVXDEY5N75ED3HDSHZ3WGAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:17:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受巴西和墨西哥市场推动，MercadoLibre 净利润激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉丁美洲电子商务巨头 MercadoLibre 周四表示，由于巴西和墨西哥的业绩抵消了阿根廷的一些负面影响，其第一季度净利润同比激增 71%，超过了分析师的预期。【原文：Latin America e-commerce giant MercadoLibre said on Thursday its first-quarter net profit surged 71% from a year earlier, beating analysts' estimates as its performance in Brazil and Mexico offset some negative effects in Argentina.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mercadolibre-net-profit-surges-driven-by-brazil-mexico-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4V5HJB2PBJQ5MIF6HXADGJMVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安进公司第一季度利润下降 1%，收入增长 22]]></title><description><![CDATA[安进公司周四公布的第一季度利润略有下降，原因是最近收购罕见病制药商 Horizon Therapeutics 导致运营和利息支出增加，而两位数的收入增长部分抵消了这一影响。【原文：Amgen reported a slightly lower first-quarter profit on Thursday, citing higher operating and interest expense from its recent acquisition of rare disease drugmaker Horizon Therapeutics, partially offset by double-digit revenue growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/amgen-first-quarter-profit-dips-1-revenue-rises-22-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZZWCZFL65IMZH5RW7AP7H4Q74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，收购公司 Sycamore 有意将 Nordstrom 私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，Sycamore Partners 是表示有意将美国百货公司 Nordstrom 私有化的收购股权公司之一。【原文：Sycamore Partners is one of the buyout equity firms that have expressed interest in taking U.S. department store Nordstrom private, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/buyout-firm-sycamore-vies-take-nordstrom-private-sources-say-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIUUPDCGZNJFXABHLCWESVQEXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 19:49:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管困境加剧，美国高收益率利差依然紧缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国高收益债券的利差（即公司相对于美国国债的溢价）仍然很窄，尽管该资产类别中的困境有所加剧，因为投资者认为大多数发行人都将经受更高更长期利率的考验。【原文：Spreads on U.S. high yield bonds, or the premium companies pay over U.S. Treasuries, remain tight despite a pick-up in distress within the asset class, as investors see the majority of issuers weathering higher-for-longer interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-high-yield-spreads-still-tight-despite-pick-up-distress-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VRCXW66J65LQ7BUGV253G7EOKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 19:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，嘉能可正在研究英美资源集团的收购方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，大宗商品集团嘉能可正在研究收购英美资源集团（Anglo American），这一进展可能引发对这家拥有107年历史的矿业公司的竞购战。【原文：Commodities group Glencore is studying an approach for Anglo American , two sources said, a development that could spark a bidding war for the 107-year old mining company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/glencore-studying-an-approach-anglo-american-sources-say-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GINZKRFKJNOTTKQOSEE2BWM5ZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 19:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian 公司获得 8.27 亿美元的一揽子激励措施，以扩建伊利诺伊州的工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian Automotive 周四表示，该公司已从伊利诺伊州获得 8.27 亿美元的奖励，用于扩大其在伊利诺伊州正常工厂的运营。【原文：Rivian Automotive said on Thursday it has received $827 million in incentives from the State of Illinois to expand operations at its Normal facility in the state.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-receives-827-mln-incentive-package-expand-illinois-facility-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RW6EFNF4YZPVTKGSQ2YNEVZIHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FCC 称许多美国电信公司需要更多资金更换华为和中兴设备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（FCC）周四表示，近 40% 的美国电信公司需要政府提供额外资金，以便从美国无线网络中移除中国电信企业华为和中兴通讯生产的设备，以应对安全风险。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) said on Thursday nearly 40% of U.S. telecom companies need additional government funding to remove equipment made by Chinese telecoms firms Huawei and ZTE from American wireless networks to address security risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/many-us-telecom-firms-need-more-funding-replace-huawei-zte-equipment-fcc-says-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMUAKY4GBFKCVOBJUVWUF2K4OA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴基斯坦推迟就收购国家航空公司提交意向书的截止日期]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴基斯坦私有化部长周四表示，巴基斯坦将把企业表达收购国家航空公司巴基斯坦国际航空公司意向的截止日期推迟到 5 月 18 日。【原文：Pakistan will push back the deadline for companies to express interest in buying national carrier Pakistan International Airlines to May 18, the country's privatisation minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/pakistan-pushes-back-deadline-expressions-interest-buy-national-airline-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZSKRCTISQZP7TNBORCI5HHDS6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:42:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国生产率疲软可能威胁美联储的 "软着陆 "希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国第一季度生产率增幅疲软，这可能会对美联储在失业率不出现令人痛苦的上升的情况下完成通胀斗争的努力构成挑战，如果经济进一步放缓，物价方面的进展可能会停滞不前。【原文：Weaker U.S. productivity gains in the first quarter may challenge the Federal Reserve's efforts to finish its inflation fight without a painful rise in unemployment, potentially stalling progress on prices absent a further economic slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/weak-us-productivity-could-threaten-feds-soft-landing-hopes-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSIZURNC4NOWBKUGPFKB7HZGXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:59:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[环球音乐集团第一季度核心盈利超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）周四公布的第一季度调整后核心利润超出预期，这得益于旗下明星泰勒-斯威夫特（Taylor Swift）的成功。【原文：Universal Music Group on Thursday posted first-quarter adjusted core profit that beat expectations, helped by the success of its star Taylor Swift.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/universal-music-group-first-quarter-core-earnings-beat-forecast-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCVLVPDESZLVVB5J4TFAJ5CUYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音供应商精神航空系统公司起诉阻止得克萨斯州安全调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空零部件制造商 Spirit AeroSystems 要求美国法官阻止得克萨斯州总检察长肯-帕克斯顿（Ken Paxton）的调查，称该州要求提供内部文件和其他信息是不合理和不合法的。【原文：Airline parts manufacturer Spirit AeroSystems has asked a U.S. judge to block a probe by Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, calling the state's demand for internal documents and other information unreasonable and unlawful.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/boeing-supplier-spirit-aerosystems-sues-block-texas-safety-probe-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWRSF44PWFMFHG4GO7U4EYYPUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:58:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[商用飞机和汽车拉动美国工厂订单增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[受商用飞机和汽车需求的拉动，3 月份美国制成品的新订单稳健增长，但其他方面的增幅不大。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods increased solidly in March, boosted by demand for commercial aircraft and motor vehicles, but gains elsewhere were moderate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/commercial-aircraft-motor-vehicles-lift-us-factory-orders-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y73HSX7JIBJUTAKGAIPVJLWJCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，高盛取消了欧盟规定的英国顶级银行家奖金上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，在英国取消了从欧盟继承下来的这一政策数月之后，高盛（Goldman Sachs）已经取消了其在英国的顶级银行家的奖金上限。【原文：Goldman Sachs has removed the cap on bonuses for its top bankers in the UK, according to a source familiar with the matter, months after the country axed the policy it had inherited from the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-scraps-eu-era-bonus-cap-top-bankers-uk-source-says-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XX7YQAIARFLYRFJG5WUI5B2AHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国律师事务所 Mayer Brown 将与香港合伙企业分道扬镳]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国律师事务所 Mayer Brown 周四表示，随着许多国际律师事务所重新考虑或减少在中国的业务，该公司计划脱离目前在香港的业务。【原文：U.S. law firm Mayer Brown said on Thursday that it plans to separate from its current Hong Kong operations, as many international law firms rethink or reduce their presence in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-law-firm-mayer-brown-split-hong-kong-partnership-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPVCPWAASRO5BMIBQE4UYIQBJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，TOMS Capital 投资管理公司已入股 Kellanova 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士周四透露，投资公司 TOMS Capital Investment Management 已在美国跨国食品制造公司 Kellanova 持有 "大量 "头寸，并正在与该公司接触。【原文：Investment firm TOMS Capital Investment Management has taken a "significant" position in U.S. multinational food manufacturing company Kellanova and is engaging with the company, two sources familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/toms-capital-investment-management-has-taken-stake-kellanova-sources-say-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TONR6P35MJIRJKK6K6OATDCI7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:14:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国官员称俄罗斯向朝鲜运送石油的数量高于联合国规定水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位美国官员周四表示，俄罗斯一直在悄悄地向朝鲜运送精炼石油，其数量似乎违反了联合国安理会的授权，并补充说美国正计划对此实施新的制裁。【原文：Russia has been quietly shipping refined petroleum to North Korea at levels that appear to violate the mandates of the United Nations Security Council, a U.S. official said on Thursday, adding the U.S. is planning new sanctions in response.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russia-is-shipping-oil-north-korea-above-un-mandated-levels-us-official-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWXM3LHSSFIG3LBBDZXA2NJMSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[壳牌首席执行官称目前不考虑在纽约重新上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[壳牌公司首席执行官 Wael Sawan 周四表示，壳牌目前并不积极考虑在纽约重新上市，而是专注于股票回购。【原文：Shell is not actively looking at relisting in New York at the moment, and is focused on share repurchases, CEO Wael Sawan said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-not-looking-new-york-relisting-moment-ceo-says-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D76XOP6LSNORFEVXC5ETNRZREY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:04:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pinnacle West Capital 因客户增长和新费率而实现第一季度盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pinnacle West Capital Corp 周四公布，由于客户增长、销售额增加和新费率的提高，该公司一季度实现盈利，而去年同期则出现亏损。【原文：Pinnacle West Capital Corp posted a quarterly profit from year-ago loss on Thursday, on the back of customer growth, increased sales and new rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pinnacle-west-capital-posts-q1-profit-customer-growth-new-rates-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6LEFOII6BJNZBEW7UN5WPPQLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:54:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行称美加利率差异有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大央行行长蒂夫-马克莱姆（Tiff Macklem）周四在下议院金融委员会上表示，美国和加拿大的利率差异是有限度的，但 "我们肯定还没有接近这个限度"。【原文：There is a limit to how far U.S. and Canadian interest rates can diverge but "certainly we're not close to that limit", Bank of Canada Governor Tiff Macklem told the House of Commons finance committee on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/boc-says-theres-limit-how-far-us-canada-rates-can-diverge-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5JPJTATKRICVHZLFVZDHYQDGE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:51:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国三月份贸易逆差略有收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 3 月份的贸易赤字略有收窄，原因是出口的大幅下滑在一定程度上缓解了进口的下降。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit narrowed slightly in March as a decline in imports was tempered somewhat by a plunge in exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-trade-deficit-narrows-slightly-march-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAVGOJYTXZNJXAG4XE3VP2VE6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第一季度生产率大幅放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[第一季度，美国工人生产率的增长大幅放缓，导致劳动力成本飙升，但生产率的趋势依然稳健。【原文：U.S. worker productivity growth slowed sharply in the first quarter, resulting in a surge in labor costs, but the trend in productivity remained solid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-productivity-slows-sharply-first-quarter-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6TV3KLG75NP7ED6FXBWKB77OQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:07:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯拉诺瓦第一季度业绩喜人，需求保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[受谷物早餐和即食零食价格上涨和需求坚挺的推动，Pop-Tarts 生产商凯兰诺瓦公司周四公布的第一季度销售额和利润超出华尔街预期。【原文：Pop-Tarts maker Kellanova beat Wall Street estimates for first-quarter sales and profit on Thursday, boosted by higher prices and firm demand for its breakfast cereals and ready-to-eat snacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kellanova-posts-upbeat-q1-results-demand-held-steady-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MS3IZFZYM5NITPBHH3VDBGKGJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会下令禁止埃克森美孚与先锋自然资源公司的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周四表示，在解决埃克森美孚收购这家顶级页岩油生产商的反垄断问题时，该委员会阻止先锋自然资源公司前首席执行官斯科特-谢菲尔德（Scott Sheffield）进入埃克森美孚董事会。【原文：The Federal Trade Commission said on Thursday it prevented former Pioneer Natural Resources CEO Scott Sheffield from serving on Exxon Mobil's board of directors as it resolves antitrust concerns about Exxon's bid to buy the top shale oil producer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-ftc-order-bans-exxon-mobil-pioneer-natural-resources-deal-2024-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ICGKBHDVEBLIBGZ4DCVKWYG6CY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>