<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:15:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:15:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[马自达与长安汽车合资组建欧盟碳排放联营企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟的一份文件显示，日本汽车制造商马自达已与其与中国长安汽车的合资企业合作，以汇集碳信用额度，帮助避免碳排放罚款。【原文：Japanese automaker Mazda has teamed up with its joint venture with China's Changan to pool carbon credits and help avoid carbon emissions fines, an EU document showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/mazda-forms-eu-carbon-emissions-pool-with-changan-joint-venture-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJDIMPMMP5MP7AIZJVRCYFHZRI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价贸易和通胀缓解，股市大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VBRRNY5JZLZXGPDL7NFJXCFBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Albemarle 将在 6.6 亿美元交易中剥离 Ketjen 控制权和 Eurecat 股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[Albemarle 公司周一表示，将向私募股权公司 KPS Capital Partners 出售其炼油催化剂解决方案业务 Ketjen 51% 的股份，并将其在 Eurecat 合资企业中 50% 的股权剥离给法国 Axens SA 公司，交易价值约为 6.6 亿美元。【原文：Albemarle said on Monday it will sell a 51% stake in its refining catalyst solutions business, Ketjen, to private equity firm KPS Capital Partners, and divest its 50% interest in the Eurecat joint venture to France's Axens SA, in deals worth about $660 million.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/albemarle-divest-ketjen-control-eurecat-stake-660-mln-deal-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7ISKHSVPZPMHG5N4MTR5RLFFY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:38:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能推动美国资本支出创新高，回购退居次席]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者越来越青睐那些将资金用于人工智能创新的美国公司，而不是那些提供股息和回购等传统股东酬劳的公司，尽管有关估值飙升和人工智能泡沫的争论仍在继续。【原文：Investors are increasingly favoring U.S. companies that channel capital toward AI innovation over those offering traditional shareholder payouts such as dividends and buybacks, even as the debate over soaring valuations and an AI bubble rages on.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/buybacks-take-backseat-ai-drives-record-us-capex-spending-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYUCCA3JOBNFXEPKMICLCV7HYI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026 年年度金价预测首次突破 4000 美元/盎司]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于经济和地缘政治动荡使黄金的避险吸引力保持不变，分析师预测黄金的年度平均价格将首次超过每盎司4000美元。【原文：Gold's winning streak is seen extending into next year, with analysts forecasting an annual average price above $4,000 per ounce for the first time as economic and geopolitical turmoil keep the metal's safe-haven allure intact, a Reuters poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/annual-2026-gold-price-forecast-tops-4000oz-first-time-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZWYVQVHLFIMRE7KKAAR7JVCSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师在 2025 年铂金和钯金价格上涨后上调了 2026 年的价格预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师们以矿山供应紧张、关税不确定性以及黄金投资需求的轮动为由，大幅上调了对2026年铂金和钯金价格的预测，铂金接近其最佳年度表现，钯金则创下2017年以来的最佳年度表现。【原文：Analysts have sharply raised their price forecasts for platinum and palladium in 2026, citing tight mine supply, tariff uncertainty and rotation from investment demand for gold, as platinum nears its best yearly performance and palladium marks its best year since 2017.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/analysts-raise-2026-price-forecasts-platinum-palladium-after-2025-rally-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7SMSTJV4BIITAAA5T2NN4HX3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[饮料需求强劲，Keurig Dr Pepper 上调年度销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper 周一上调了年销售额预期，这主要得益于包括美国在内的市场对其能量饮料和碳酸软饮料的强劲需求。【原文：Keurig Dr Pepper raised its forecast for annual sales on Monday, banking on resilient demand for its energy drinks and carbonated soft beverages in markets including the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/keurig-dr-pepper-raises-annual-sales-forecast-strong-beverage-demand-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AGL6MBEZJMHHCPL3IX27NHRAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通选择 Perpetua Resources 作为 1.5 万亿美元安全基金的首笔投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[锑和金矿开采商 Perpetua Resources 是摩根大通 1.5 万亿美元美国国家安全投资基金的第一笔投资，此举凸显了该公司在生产一种被中国禁止出口、用于制造子弹和其他武器的金属方面的关键作用。【原文：Antimony and gold miner Perpetua Resources is the first investment from JPMorgan Chase's $1.5 trillion investment fund for U.S. national security, a move underscoring the company's key role in producing a metal whose exports China has blocked and which is used to make bullets and other weaponry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-picks-perpetua-resources-15-trillion-security-funds-first-investment-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XR5BUC2X2JNNZLHFUHL4GJ5RAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美达成暂停关税和出口限制的休战协议后稀土矿商下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一收盘前，在美国上市的稀土矿商股价下跌多达8%，此前华盛顿和中国政府达成了一项贸易协议框架，可能暂停美国计划对关键矿产征收的关税和中国的出口管制，从而缓解了市场对供应中断的担忧，而供应中断曾在今年提振了稀土行业。【原文：Shares of U.S.-listed rare earth miners fell as much as 8% before the bell on Monday after Washington and Beijing reached a framework for a trade deal that could pause planned U.S. tariffs and Chinese export controls on critical minerals, easing fears of supply disruptions that had boosted the sector this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/rare-earth-miners-fall-after-us-china-truce-pause-tariffs-export-curbs-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LZK73QX4JJPLIE65P44JGZBMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:40:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特会见日本财政大臣片山，庆祝日经指数里程碑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周一在东京与日本财务大臣片山聪树（Satsuki Katayama）举行会谈，庆祝日本日经平均股价首次突破 50,000 点。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent celebrated Japan's Nikkei share average closing above the 50,000 level for the first time on Monday, in a meeting with Japanese finance minister Satsuki Katayama in Tokyo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bessent-celebrates-nikkei-milestone-meeting-with-japan-finmin-katayama-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JXY266245JIRPLYZ35KOFVNUQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:35:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华股价下滑，Avidity 在 120 亿美元生物技术交易后大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺华公司计划以约 120 亿美元的价格收购美国生物技术公司 Avidity Biosciences，这是该瑞士制药公司在首席执行官 Vas Narasimhan 的领导下进行的最大一笔收购，随后该公司股价周一下跌了 1%。【原文：Shares of Novartis fell 1% on Monday following news of the company's plans to acquire U.S. biotech Avidity Biosciences for about $12 billion, marking the Swiss drugmaker's largest acquisition under CEO Vas Narasimhan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-shares-slip-avidity-soars-after-12-billion-biotech-deal-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQ5L57AHKNL47GQOI5P43PABG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:29:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局将扩大对 28.6 万辆通用汽车发动机故障问题的调查范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周一表示，尽管已经召回了几起投诉，但该安全监管机构正在扩大对美国通用汽车公司 28.6 万辆汽车发动机故障问题的调查。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration is expanding its probe into 286,000 General Motors vehicles in the U.S. over a possible engine failure issue, the safety regulator said on Monday, following several complaints, despite a recall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-open-probe-into-286000-gm-vehicles-over-possible-engine-failure-issue-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUCR7SODPBKHRIH2RZLC5KWDKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:23:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济放缓，加拿大央行准备将利率降至 2.25]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家预计，由于经济放缓和失业率居高不下，加拿大央行本周将连续第二次下调政策利率。【原文：Economists expect the Bank of Canada to make a second consecutive policy rate cut this week due to a slowing economy and high joblessness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-poised-cut-rates-225-amid-economic-slowdown-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCKKSBYWJRMCLNDXGBPKJP5GBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税焦虑促使美国进口商提前下达春季订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业正试图在特朗普摇摆不定的征税政策面前抢占先机。【原文：Businesses are trying to get in front of Trump's vacillating levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tariffs-anxiety-prompts-us-importers-place-spring-orders-early-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OU4SOQVLJVJYPA2HMYNVTSCKKI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:11:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 投资者将扭亏希望寄托在新任首席执行官身上]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）的一些长期投资者相信，一位拥有良好业绩记录的首席执行官和一个新的管理团队的回归，能够为历来高增长的 Optum 医疗服务业务带来转机，并将艰难的一年甩在身后。【原文：Some long-term UnitedHealth Group investors are putting their faith in the return of a CEO with a proven track record and a new management team they believe can deliver a turnaround for the historically high-growth Optum health services business and put a tough year behind it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-investors-pin-turnaround-hopes-new-ceo-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IAK75CKONPI3AMEQ4TXJSNJEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多伦多证券交易所（TSX）期货持平，中美贸易希望抑制大宗商品跌势]]></title><description><![CDATA[与加拿大资源重地主要股指挂钩的期货周一持平，大宗商品价格下滑抵消了中美贸易关系改善可能带来的收益。【原文：Futures linked to Canada's resource-heavy main stock index were flat on Monday with sliding commodity prices offsetting potential gains from improving U.S.-China trade relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsx-futures-flat-us-china-trade-hopes-blunt-commodity-slump-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQPJLCJEW5PY5NAHPSKW44NZR4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大科技公司将在人工智能泡沫阴影下公布财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国科技巨头纷纷公布财报，其中一个问题迫在眉睫：人工智能的蓬勃发展是否会导致估值膨胀，从而引发下一个大泡沫？【原文：As America's tech titans report earnings this week, one question looms large: is the artificial intelligence boom that has inflated valuations headed for the next big bubble?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/big-tech-report-earnings-under-specter-ai-bubble-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SFB7GHCWNIOVFJKBOKGCOXFHU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储减息倒计时：债券投资者减少购买较长期限的国债]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美联储准备在周三再次降息四分之一个百分点，债券投资者正在重新审视其持有的较长期限国债，一些投资者减少了头寸，另一些投资者甚至做空基准国债。【原文：Bond investors are re-examining their holdings of longer-dated Treasuries, with some reducing positions and others even going short relative to their benchmark, as the Federal Reserve prepares to cut interest rates by another quarter percentage point on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/countdown-fed-cut-bond-investors-scale-back-longer-dated-treasuries-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCHJSN5ICZN6NNAC4WJ6A5ONGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储本周准备降息，并可能推出更多宽松政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[人们普遍预计，美联储决策者本周将把美国短期借贷成本降低四分之一个百分点，这是他们今年第二次降低借贷成本，因为他们希望防止劳动力市场进一步放缓。【原文：Federal Reserve policymakers are widely expected to reduce U.S. short-term borrowing costs this week by a quarter of a percentage point for the second time this year as they look to prevent further slowing in the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-poised-cut-rates-this-week-with-more-easing-likely-tap-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDJRKDHTXZNSPBV33RNLHYL2F4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 LTIMindtree 公司首席执行官表示将大力发展新的人工智能部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[在印度 2830 亿美元的 IT 行业面临客户广泛削减非必要支出之际，LTIMindtree 公司的最高负责人表示，公司将加倍努力发展人工智能，投资于一个新推出的平台，帮助企业采用这项技术。【原文：LTIMindtree is doubling down on AI with investments in a newly-launched platform that helps companies adopt the technology, its top boss said, as India's $283-billion IT industry faces broader cuts in non-essential spending by clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-ltimindtree-betting-big-new-ai-unit-ceo-says-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4BE75UH3NKGPBGQ3GUYUYUYCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空首席执行官称美国政府关门影响 "不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司
 达美航空公司首席执行官周一表示，美国政府停摆造成的影响 "很小"，每天的损失不到 100 万美元，而机场安检人员的短缺才是更令人担忧的问题。【原文：Delta Air Lines 
 is seeing a "small" impact from the U.S. government shutdown, costing it less than $1 million a day, and the shortage of airport security staff is of greater concern, the carrier's CEO said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/delta-air-lines-seeing-small-impact-us-government-shutdown-ceo-says-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTXOW2PZUFNUDKX6DLIW5KFALY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:47:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美关系乐观，华尔街期货创历史新高；科技业绩受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国股指期货跃升至历史新高，原因是对中美达成贸易协议的预期在本周大科技公司财报和美联储可能降息的背景下刺激了风险偏好。【原文：U.S. stock index futures jumped to record highs on Monday as expectations of a trade deal between China and the United States fanned risk appetite in a week packed with Big Tech earnings and a potential interest-rate cut from the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/wall-st-futures-hit-record-highs-us-china-optimism-tech-results-focus-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NO7VAGZCVPYJBJZPDJOY6VXQ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊称尽管美国征收关税，但印度电子商务出口额仍突破 200 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周一表示，它已帮助印度卖家的出口总额突破 200 亿美元，其中包括今年的近 70 亿美元，因为小型经营者正在努力抵消 8 月份美国新征收的进口关税的影响。【原文：Amazon on Monday said it has helped Indian sellers surpass $20 billion in total exports, including nearly $7 billion this year, as small operators work to offset the impact of new U.S. import tariffs that were imposed in August.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-says-indias-e-commerce-exports-top-20-billion-despite-us-tariffs-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VIMTSH4ISJPQZAGPX7TK7MWVCU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴林主权基金与 SandboxAQ 签署协议，利用人工智能加速药物发现]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国人工智能和量子技术公司 SandboxAQ 周一与巴林主权财富基金签署了一项协议，旨在加快药物开发并创造价值 10 亿美元的生物技术资产。【原文：SandboxAQ, a U.S.-based artificial intelligence and quantum technology firm, signed an agreement with Bahrain's sovereign wealth fund on Monday aimed at speeding up the development of drugs and creating biotech assets worth $1 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bahrains-sovereign-fund-sandboxaq-sign-deal-speed-up-drug-discovery-with-ai-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETWDWF4U3JPZFNS66TPCQ34VQE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特人工智能公司 Humain 公布 6 千兆瓦数据中心计划和新的人工智能操作系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特人工智能公司 Humain 首席执行官塔里克-阿明（Tareq Amin）周一在利雅得举行的《财富》会议上表示，该公司计划建设约 6 千兆瓦容量的数据中心，并将推出 Humain 1。【原文：Saudi AI firm Humain is planning to construct approximately 6 gigawatts of data centre capacity and is launching Humain 1, its CEO Tareq Amin said on Monday at the Fortune conference in Riyadh.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-ai-firm-humain-unveils-6-gigawatt-data-centre-plan-new-ai-operating-system-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CM5VERGPFBI4NNQJ2AKDEBAWM4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 07:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称年底或将决定美联储新主席人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，可能会在今年年底前决定下一任美联储主席的人选。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said a decision on the next Federal Reserve chair might be made by the end of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-new-fed-chair-decision-might-be-made-by-year-end-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVGKBRJDBRIMPALBHCT3ZVYQ5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中美将达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，美国和中国将 "达成 "一项贸易协议，预计本周晚些时候他将在亚洲之行中与中国国家主席习近平在韩国会面。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said the U.S. and China are set to "come away with" a trade deal, as he is expected to meet Chinese President Xi Jinping later this week in South Korea during his Asia tour.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-says-he-might-sign-final-tiktok-deal-thursday-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSMITGHREFMPRFGNM6Y3RLDT3I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 FD 报道，亚马逊将向荷兰业务投资 16 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰金融日报《FD》周一援引亚马逊比利时和荷兰负责人的话报道，亚马逊计划未来三年在荷兰投资 14 亿欧元（16.3 亿美元）。【原文：Amazon plans to invest 1.4 billion euros ($1.63 billion) in the Netherlands in the next three years, Dutch financial daily FD reported on Monday, citing the company's head for Belgium and the Netherlands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-invest-16-billion-dutch-operations-fd-reports-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJ3KSJVWLJK4DJEODLIPHBLBMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[荷兰在线银行 Bunq 获得美国经纪商牌照]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰在线银行 Bunq 周一表示，该公司已获得在美国作为经纪交易商运营的许可，这也是该公司向欧洲以外地区扩张的举措之一。【原文：Dutch online bank Bunq said on Monday that it had received a licence to operate as a broker-dealer in the United States, part of a drive to expand outside of Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dutch-online-bank-bunq-gets-us-broker-dealer-licence-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DGWKJ2O3BLWXNH7HHZAQ4BABA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 06:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奢侈品牌在中国展现魅力]]></title><description><![CDATA[路威酩轩和爱马仕等公司越来越多地提供私密晚宴和大型表演，以及设有私人购物区和专用电梯的商店，他们打赌这些贵宾将有助于结束大流行后的销售低迷。【原文：Firms like LVMH and Hermes increasingly offer intimate dinners and large-scale shows, as well as stores with private shopping areas and exclusive elevator access for the VIPs they bet will help end a post-pandemic sales slump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/luxury-brands-turn-charm-china-kindle-nascent-spending-recovery-2025-10-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KS47HVOGRBPPJBA6X4VH4I6ABY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 05:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>