<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:08:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:08:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道大众西雅特老板警告：如果不降低中国制造的电动汽车关税，西班牙的就业岗位将面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司首席执行官告诉路透社，如果欧盟不在3月底之前降低对该品牌中国产电动汽车的关税，这家欧洲最大汽车制造商的西班牙子公司将被迫减产并裁员约1500人。【原文：Volkswagen's SEAT, the Spanish subsidiary of Europe's largest carmaker, will be forced to cut output and lay off around 1,500 workers if the EU does not lower its tariff on the brand's China-made electric car by the end of March, its CEO told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vws-seat-boss-warns-spanish-jobs-risk-if-china-made-ev-tariff-is-not-lowered-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3CYE3PNY5ICNN7MDHHT7OOY4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:29:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[抛开美联储，顶级央行仍有宽松空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[政策制定者和分析师认为，全球央行有足够的空间继续降息，随着美国联邦储备局暂停自己的宽松政策，与美国联邦储备局的有限 "脱钩 "可能会继续下去。【原文：Central banks around the globe have plenty of room to keep cutting interest rates, and a limited "decoupling" from the U.S. Federal Reserve could continue as it pauses its own policy easing, according to policymakers and analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/leaving-fed-behind-top-central-banks-have-room-ease-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNKWCLGCUZPTTFMF4FPGS7JJPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:25:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Northpointe Bancshares 在美国 IPO 的目标估值高达 5.95 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由私募股权投资支持的社区银行 Northpointe Bancshares 周五表示，其在美国首次公开募股的目标估值高达 5.95 亿美元。【原文：Northpointe Bancshares is targeting a valuation of up to $595 million in its initial public offering in the United States, the private equity-backed community bank said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/northpointe-bancshares-targets-up-595-mln-valuation-us-ipo-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYNUJ53SHZIXJLEINXFFOJX7RM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普继承了一个充分就业的劳动力市场。他能保持这个状态吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国的就业市场已经达到了美国央行官员所称的稳定充分就业的时刻，工资和就业增长平衡，失业率较低，这打破了人们对大流行病导致大萧条的担忧，也与美联储的加息背道而驰。【原文：Defying fears of a pandemic-driven Great Depression and bucking Federal Reserve interest rate hikes as well, the U.S. job market has hit what U.S. central bank officials are characterizing as a moment of stable full employment, with balanced wage and job growth and a low unemployment rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-inherits-labor-market-full-employment-can-he-keep-it-there-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAFI7T6IGNLXRI4ZGTMAHM74X4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:13:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 通胀数据考验市场，关税言论风起云涌]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者担心唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税计划会危及华尔街对今年降息的希望，因此对通胀速度的重新审视将在下周对美国股市构成考验。【原文：A fresh look at the pace of inflation will test the U.S. stock market in the coming week, as investors worry that President Donald Trump's tariff plans are endangering Wall Street's hopes for interest rate cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/wall-st-week-ahead-inflation-data-test-market-tariff-talk-swirls-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVVF5HJS7FLEJCWW3RHVH46O2E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税威胁令市场动荡不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）能够迅速对主要贸易伙伴征收关税，然后又推迟征收，这让世界市场摇摆不定。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's ability to swiftly impose, and then delay, tariffs on top trading partners has left world markets swinging one way and then another.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trump-tariffs-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQMIZYDGBBOOBJJTYM4EEECTI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[竞技报》称，Netflix 考虑竞购一级方程式赛车的美国电视转播权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《The Athletic》周五报道，Netflix 正在考虑竞购一级方程式赛车的美国电视转播权。【原文：Netflix is considering a bid for Formula One's U.S. TV rights, according to a report from The Athletic on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-considers-bid-formula-ones-us-tv-rights-athletic-says-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ESXAJQDC6VLX3PYADUYLN4OIUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:01:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 多云的亚马逊、薪资和更平坦的曲线]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQV6OLNRFBNZNKR7RCI6DOT3H4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 10:55:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《彭博新闻》报道，特朗普委派副总统万斯和安全顾问华尔兹监督潜在的 TikTok 交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Punchbowl News 周五报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普已责成副总统 JD Vance 和国家安全顾问 Michael Waltz 监督 TikTok 的潜在出售事宜。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has tasked Vice President JD Vance and national security adviser Michael Waltz with overseeing a potential sale of TikTok, Punchbowl News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-tasked-vp-vance-security-adviser-waltz-oversee-potential-tiktok-deal-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AQ3GCOLMNNENBYP77UUNOYSDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 10:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[截至 2 月 5 日的一周，美国股票基金资金大幅流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国征收新贸易关税所带来的地缘政治风险加剧，以及投资者对主要科技公司盈利逊于预期感到担忧的影响，截至2月5日的一周内，美国股票基金出现了五周以来的第四次单周资金外流。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed their fourth weekly outflow in five weeks in the week to Feb. 5, driven by heightened geopolitical risks from President Donald Trump's new trade tariffs on China and investor wariness over weaker-than-expected earnings from key technology companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-sharp-outflows-week-feb-5-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVDGPEIK7ZN4PCCAMOPSSJMWGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 10:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[月度薪资测试前期货持稳；亚马逊下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，与华尔街主要股指挂钩的期货市场表现低迷，原因是投资者在至关重要的 1 月份就业报告公布前避免了大量押注，而亚马逊公司的股价则因预测偏低和云计算部门的疲软而承压。【原文：Futures linked to Wall Street's main indexes were subdued on Friday as investors avoided large bets prior to the crucial January jobs report, while Amazon.com's shares were pressured by low forecasts and weakness in its cloud computing unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-steady-ahead-monthly-payrolls-test-amazon-slips-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAVQ4467ZBKL3FRTBJZ6QIPX3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 10:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税威胁加剧谨慎情绪，全球股票基金面临资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收高额关税后，投资者变得更加谨慎，截至2月5日，全球股票基金出现了七周以来的第二次单周资金外流。【原文：Global equity funds saw their second weekly outflow in seven weeks by February 5, as investors became more cautious following U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of steep tariffs on Mexico, Canada, and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRCJTF4L4BJCJNISLMXLN5L4UI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:41:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税效应提振台湾一月份出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[得益于人工智能需求和企业在唐纳德-特朗普就任美国总统并开始征收贸易关税之前获得订单，台湾 1 月份的出口增幅超过预期。【原文：Taiwan's exports rose more than expected in January thanks both to artificial intelligence demand and companies getting in orders before Donald Trump assumed office as U.S. president and began levying trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/trump-tariff-effect-boosts-taiwans-january-exports-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEGB7B4Y6BP2FDC3GNZUQB5SXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾顶级芯片设计商联发科针对美国可能征收关税进行模拟测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾顶级芯片设计公司联发科技（MediaTek）首席执行官周五表示，公司一直在模拟美国可能对台湾岛内征收关税的情况，但认为今年的情况 "可控"。【原文：The chief executive of Taiwan's top chip design company MediaTek said on Friday that the company has been running simulations for possible U.S. tariffs on the island, but thinks for this year it would be "manageable".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/top-taiwan-chip-designer-mediatek-running-simulations-possible-us-tariffs-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X24NG2U5OZLAFB5U67HJODDFUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:31:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 1 月中国产电动汽车销量同比下降 11.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国乘用车联席会周五公布的数据显示，1月份美国汽车制造商特斯拉在中国生产的电动汽车销量同比下降11.5%，至63,238辆。【原文：U.S. automaker Tesla's sales of China-made electric vehicles fell 11.5% to 63,238 units in January from a year earlier, data from the China Passenger Car Association showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-china-made-ev-sales-fall-115-yy-january-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RZPIXNYFJLAJM27WDC4JTFBEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅入股中国和北美诊所，了解医疗美容市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅首席执行官尼古拉斯-希罗尼穆斯在周五的财报电话会议上表示，欧莱雅已参股中国和北美的诊所，以观察和了解医疗美容市场。【原文：L'Oreal has taken stakes in clinics in China and North America in order to observe and understand the medical aesthetics market, L'Oreal CEO Nicolas Hieronimus said in an earnings call on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loreal-takes-stakes-chinese-namerican-clinics-understand-medical-aesthetics-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D7W47YA5CJOIVFBTMSHEEBYGQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:23:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国检方将对三星总裁案的裁决提出上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国检方表示，在上诉法院裁定三星电子董事长李在镕无罪后，韩国检方将向最高法院提起上诉。【原文：South Korean prosecutors will appeal to the Supreme Court after an appeals court found Samsung Electronics Chairman Jay Y. Lee not guilty on all charges stemming from a 2015 merger, prosecutors said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/south-korean-prosecutors-appeal-ruling-samsung-chiefs-case-yonhap-says-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7DD4NIACJPSRHC7F2LLVYC32A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pop Sondrio 称 BPER 竞购尚未达成一致，意大利并购狂潮促使 Unipol 加快合作步伐]]></title><description><![CDATA[BPER 对 Banca Popolare di Sondrio 的竞购此前并未达成一致，一位与该意大利银行关系密切的人士周五表示，在此之前，该银行已成为震惊业界的一系列竞购中的最新收购目标。【原文：BPER's bid for Banca Popolare di Sondrio was not previously agreed, a person close to the Italian bank said on Friday, after it became the latest takeover target in a series of bids rocking the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/pop-sondrio-says-bper-bid-not-agreed-italy-ma-frenzy-prompts-unipol-hasten-tie-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5HRDSHQPZP6VKIRKIQ4IZAX6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场拖累欧莱雅季度销售额，欧莱雅股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五早盘，法国化妆品巨头欧莱雅股价下跌超过 4%，受中国需求疲软拖累，该公司公布了自大流行病高峰期以来最低迷的季度销售业绩。【原文：Shares in French cosmetics giant L'Oreal fell by more than 4% in early trade on Friday after the company posted its slowest quarterly sales since the height of the pandemic, dragged down by weak Chinese demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loreal-shares-drop-after-china-drags-down-quarterly-sales-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZKCYF3B3RKX5I24IKQ6VAB6TA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，申银万国准备在伦敦上市时将估值降至 500 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士表示，在线快时尚零售商Shein将把其潜在伦敦上市的估值下调至500亿美元左右，这比该公司2023年的筹资价值低了近四分之一，因为该公司面临的不利因素越来越多。【原文：Online fast-fashion retailer Shein is set to cut its valuation in a potential London listing to around $50 billion, said three people with knowledge of the matter, nearly a quarter less than the company's 2023 fundraising value amid growing headwinds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shein-poised-slash-valuation-50-billion-london-ipo-sources-say-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPKTMOOGFBMFVOZM5YPAFTYNJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 08:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷警告新车型成本将影响 2025 年利润率，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[保时捷汽车公司周五股价下跌 7%，是欧洲公司中跌幅最大的一天，也是该公司自上市以来跌幅最大的一天，此前该公司警告称，新车型的成本和电池相关费用将影响其 2025 年的利润。【原文：Porsche AG's shares fell 7% on Friday, the biggest drop among European firms and its worst day since listing on the stock market, after the carmaker warned that the cost of new models and battery-related expenses would dent its 2025 profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/luxury-carmaker-porsches-grim-2025-outlook-sends-shares-down-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXOT2NTQQBIDJOTNURGD2WJXCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 08:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港将就美国关税决定向世贸组织投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将矛头指向中国进口商品，美国决定对来自亚洲金融中心的商品征收10%的关税，香港周五表示将就这一决定向世界贸易组织（WTO）提出申诉。【原文：Hong Kong said on Friday it would file a complaint with the World Trade Organisation (WTO) on a U.S. decision to impose 10% tariffs on goods from the Asian financial hub as U.S. President Donald Trump targets Chinese imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/hong-kong-complain-wto-us-tariff-decision-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNEVQVDHUFNRTLENEM6SRWPZNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 08:27:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商 Stellantis 与 Mistral AI 扩大其人工智能战略合作伙伴关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球第四大汽车制造商 Stellantis 与法国技术和人工智能（AI）公司 Mistral 决定扩大战略合作伙伴关系，Stellantis 表示此举将加速其行业数据分析。【原文：Stellantis , the world's fourth-largest carmaker, and French technology and artificial intelligence (AI) firm Mistral have decided to expand their strategic partnership in a move which Stellantis said will speed up its industry-data analysis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/carmaker-stellantis-mistral-ai-expand-their-ai-strategic-partnership-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFTTIW3MTZKEZEKHGVJXJPSNC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 08:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》报道：英国命令苹果公司允许其访问用户的加密账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，英国安全官员已下令苹果公司创建一个所谓的 "后门"，允许他们检索全球任何苹果用户上传到云端的所有内容。【原文：Britain's security officials have ordered that Apple create a so-called 'back door' allowing them to retrieve all the content any Apple user worldwide has uploaded to the cloud, The Washington Post reported on Friday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-asks-apple-let-it-spy-users-encrypted-accounts-washington-post-reports-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JRTQNNMPXVPSHH2TMTZIYKPZNU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡银行第四季度利润增长，但特朗普关税可能影响2025年增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，新加坡银行第四季度的利润将有所增长，但由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易关税和其他政策有可能破坏全球经济，今年的经济增长可能会受到打击。【原文：Singaporean banks are set to report stronger profits for the fourth quarter, but growth could take a hit this year as U.S. President Donald Trump's trade tariffs and other policies threaten to undermine the global economy, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/singapore-banks-post-higher-q4-profit-trump-tariffs-could-hurt-2025-growth-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GILUN4P3BBJGHGG4DURNZ4A5XE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉高出售北美零售商品牌业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国消费品制造商汉高（Henkel）周五表示，将把其在北美的零售商品牌业务出售给 First Quality Enterprises, LLC 的一家附属公司。【原文：German consumer goods maker Henkel said on Friday it would sell its retailer brands business in North America to an affiliate of First Quality Enterprises, LLC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/henkel-sell-retailer-brands-business-north-america-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4AXJPTY6FL2VNGZDKEQN7BFHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:27:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国保险公司 L&G 将以 23 亿美元出售美国保障业务部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国人寿保险公司 Legal &amp; General 周五表示，将以 23 亿美元现金向日本明治安田出售其美国保障业务。【原文：British life insurer Legal &amp; General said on Friday it would sell its U.S. protection business to Japan's Meiji Yasuda for $2.3 billion in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/british-insurer-lg-sell-us-protection-unit-23-billion-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CH4SSEZQ3BLB7NKYJKTDLUJSPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三菱化学将以 33.6 亿美元向贝恩出售药物部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本三菱化学公司周五表示，将向美国私募股权公司贝恩资本（Bain Capital）出售制药部门田边三菱制药公司（Tanabe Mitsubishi Pharma），交易价值为 5100 亿日元（33.6 亿美元），以寻求精简其投资组合。【原文：Japan's Mitsubishi Chemical said on Friday it will sell pharmaceutical unit Tanabe Mitsubishi Pharma to U.S. private equity firm Bain Capital in a deal worth 510 billion yen ($3.36 billion) as it seeks to streamline its portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/mitsubishi-chemical-sells-pharmaceuticals-subsidiary-bain-336-billion-deal-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEKZ236RNFLMTPHCCRH4WCBFZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[云计算部门报告增长逊于预期，亚马逊股价下跌 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周五在法兰克福的股价下跌了 4%，此前该零售商的财报显示其云计算部门表现疲软，并预测第一季度的收入和利润将低于预期。【原文：Amazon shares fell 4% in Frankfurt on Friday a day after the retailer's results showed weakness in its cloud computing unit and it forecast and lower-than-expected first-quarter revenue and profit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-shares-fall-4-after-cloud-unit-reports-weaker-than-expected-growth-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZ2LSHDNJRMJXMBUAT2PRJXJQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:12:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港 Gaw Capital 以超过 10 亿美元的价格收购东京标志性购物中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gaw 的日本负责人周五表示，房地产私募股权公司 Gaw Capital 和新加坡投资者 Patience Capital Group 已完成对东京市中心黄金购物中心 Tokyu Plaza Ginza 的收购，交易价值超过 10 亿美元。【原文：Real estate private equity firm Gaw Capital and Singapore-based investor Patience Capital Group have completed the acquisition of Tokyu Plaza Ginza, a prime mall in central Tokyo, in a deal worth more than $1 billion, Gaw's Japan head said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/hong-kongs-gaw-capital-buys-iconic-tokyo-mall-over-1-billion-2025-02-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DRTFNK57FKJRDRXKNDI5PZB54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>