<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:34:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:34:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利任命首席执行官 Ted Pick 为主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利周四表示，首席执行官泰德-皮克（Ted Pick）将接替詹姆斯-戈尔曼（James Gorman）担任下一任董事长。【原文：Morgan Stanley said on Thursday CEO Ted Pick would be its next chair succeeding James Gorman, who has been tapped to head the board at Walt Disney after he steps down as executive chair of the Wall Street titan at the end of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-names-ceo-ted-pick-its-chair-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXCRMTVABFKJNCPW6FF25PUYLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:22:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院阻止 Tapestry 85 亿美元收购竞争对手 Capri]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，一名美国法官阻止了美国手提包及配饰制造商 Tapestry 和 Capri 的 85 亿美元并购案，这是美国联邦贸易委员会在并购挑战罕见的行业中取得的一次胜利。【原文：A U.S. judge blocked the pending $8.5 billion merger of U.S. handbag and accessories maker Tapestry and Capri on Thursday, a victory for the U.S. Federal Trade Commission in an industry where merger challenges are rare.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-court-blocks-tapestrys-85-billion-acquisition-rival-capri-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">65HJZMXYVVMKXEIOWCTX723GM4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银首席执行官表示，瑞信客户迁移将耗时 18 个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥-埃尔莫蒂（Sergio Ermotti）周四表示，瑞信客户向瑞银迁移的初期工作应该还需要 18 个月左右的时间，因为瑞银正在加紧整合其前竞争对手。【原文：The incipient migration of clients from Credit Suisse to UBS should take about another 18 months, UBS CEO Sergio Ermotti said on Thursday, as his bank presses on with the integration of its former rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-migration-credit-suisse-clients-take-18-months-ceo-says-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VL34VJN35OYBIL5NH74WHQK6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Avangrid 以 1.6 亿美元向 Dominion Energy 出售海上风电租约]]></title><description><![CDATA[伊贝尔德罗拉集团（Iberdrola Group）旗下的 Avangrid 公司周四表示，已完成将其 Kitty Hawk North 海上风电租约以 1.6 亿美元的价格出售给 Dominion Energy 公司。【原文：Avangrid , part of the Iberdrola Group, has completed the sale of its Kitty Hawk North offshore wind lease to Dominion Energy at $160 million, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/avangrid-sells-offshore-wind-lease-dominion-energy-160-million-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADQDOW3KWZL4ZNWEY2VKCY33RM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:26:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行行长称将尽快解决部分财政问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行行长罗伯托-坎波斯-内托（Roberto Campos Neto）周四表示，巴西政府将很快发布公告，部分解决金融市场对财政问题的担忧，这些问题正在影响该国的风险溢价。【原文：Brazil's government will make announcements soon that will partly address financial markets' fiscal concerns that are affecting the country's risk premium, central bank chief Roberto Campos Neto said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-partly-address-fiscal-concerns-soon-central-bank-chief-says-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXXBPZ7JMZOXLA762B6FHFNJMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:10:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本敦促二十国集团警惕外汇过度波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣加藤胜信（Katsunobu Kato）周四表示，日本向二十国集团（G20）的同行们表示，当局必须对货币市场的过度波动和各成员国宏观经济政策的溢出效应保持警惕。【原文：Japan told its Group of 20 (G20) counterparts that authorities must be vigilant to excessive currency market volatility and spillovers from each member's macroeconomic policy, its finance minister Katsunobu Kato said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/japan-urges-g20-be-vigilant-excessive-fx-volatility-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYXUEQFDS5OPXJ7O36QADH3ESE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:56:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科罗拉多州爆发大肠杆菌疫情，麦当劳遭起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[科罗拉多州一名男子对麦当劳提起诉讼，这似乎是麦当劳因 Quarter Pounder 汉堡引发大肠杆菌疫情而遭到的第一起诉讼。【原文：A Colorado man has filed what appears to be the first lawsuit against McDonald’s over an E. coli outbreak linked to Quarter Pounder burgers that has killed one person and sickened nearly 50 others.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/mcdonalds-hit-with-lawsuit-after-colorado-man-sickened-e-coli-outbreak-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5PXEYA4FNN2JBSCPNVLCGFSLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:54:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行首席执行官称，其 CRE 办公楼贷款组合可能损失 20-30 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）首席执行官查理-沙尔夫（Charlie Scharf）周四表示，该美国贷款机构的商业地产办公楼贷款组合可能会损失 20 亿至 30 亿美元。【原文：Wells Fargo Chief Executive Officer Charlie Scharf said on Thursday that the U.S. lender may lose $2 billion to $3 billion on its commercial real estate office loan portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-may-lose-2-3-billion-its-cre-office-loan-portfolio-ceo-says-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAGNAWWBVRJETMRRYG3IXHOMFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:49:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Perplexity 表示将在道琼斯和《纽约邮报》的诉讼中为自己辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[Perplexity 周四表示，道琼斯和《纽约邮报》在诉讼中提出的版权侵权指控具有误导性，并誓言为自己辩护。【原文：Perplexity said on Thursday the allegations of copyright infringement in a lawsuit filed by Dow Jones and the New York Post were misleading, and vowed to defend itself.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/perplexity-says-will-defend-itself-dow-jones-new-york-post-lawsuit-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIONI4K3LBKQFLJNYHMZBK7CA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森美孚与卡塔尔的德克萨斯州液化天然气工厂建设项目延期三年]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份监管文件显示，联邦监管机构周四批准埃克森美孚和卡塔尔能源液化天然气合资企业延期三年，以完成金色通道液化天然气工厂的建设。【原文：Federal regulators on Thursday gave an Exxon Mobil and Qatar Energy LNG joint venture a 3-year extension to finish building their Golden Pass LNG plant, a regulatory document showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-mobil-qatar-get-3-year-extension-build-texas-lng-plant-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTE72HYGRRNORH2VRRI2QCXZUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳洋葱在美国爆发大肠杆菌疫情后受到审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部周三晚些时候表示，新鲜洋葱可能是麦当劳餐厅爆发大肠杆菌疫情的源头，该疫情已导致 49 人患病，1 人死亡。【原文：Fresh onions are the likely source of an E. coli outbreak at McDonald's restaurants that has sickened 49 people and killed one, the U.S. Department of Agriculture said late on Wednesday, alarming some McDonald's customers and other fast-food chains using onions as an ingredient.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mcdonalds-onions-under-scrutiny-after-us-e-coli-outbreak-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4KNL2WCEZOHTIPR7FWEHWNHZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于供应链持续中断，霍尼韦尔销售预期出现下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔周四预计全年销售额低于华尔街预期，季度营收也不及预期，这家工业巨头正努力应对持续的供应链中断和工业自动化业务的疲软。【原文：Honeywell projected annual sales below Wall Street expectations and missed quarterly revenue estimates on Thursday as the industrial giant struggles with persistent supply-chain disruptions and weakness in its industrial automation business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/honeywell-sales-projections-fall-short-due-ongoing-supply-chain-disruptions-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5OFQ3ATOBJD7I23NUN7WIJSP4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:30:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登政府对航空旅行竞争市场展开广泛调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部反垄断司和交通部周四表示，他们将对航空旅行的竞争状况展开广泛的公开调查。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department's Antitrust Division and the Transportation Department said on Thursday they are launching a broad public inquiry into the state of competition in air travel.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/biden-administration-launches-broad-inquiry-into-air-travel-competition-market-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPJOCGARXVI6XBLOD6GEJJB4CY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国空中出租车制造商 Lilium 旗下公司申请破产，股价大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国空中出租车开发商 Lilium 周四表示，在与州政府和联邦政府谈判解决现金危机未果后，该公司在德国的两家子公司已决定申请破产。【原文：German air-taxi developer Lilium said on Thursday two of its subsidiaries in the country have decided to file for insolvency following unsuccessful talks with state and federal governments to solve its cash crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/german-air-taxi-maker-liliums-units-file-insolvency-shares-plunge-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GK7RGDVDNBKVVPM23DSVWHSAOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁称世界经济面临低增长萎靡和不满加剧的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周四警告说，世界正面临着陷入低增长、高债务道路的危险，这将使各国政府失去更多的资源来改善本国人民的机会并应对气候变化和其他挑战。【原文：International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva warned on Thursday that the world is in danger of becoming mired in a low-growth, high-debt path that will leave governments with fewer resources to improve opportunities for their people and tackle climate change and other challenges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/imf-chief-says-world-economy-risk-low-growth-malaise-rising-dissatisfaction-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJUTWIJVSBOTNMHPHNKAR55VAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳爆发大肠杆菌疫情后，百胜餐饮集团从餐点中剔除洋葱]]></title><description><![CDATA[在麦当劳 Quarter Pounder 汉堡包引发大肠杆菌疫情后，百胜集团周四表示，出于 "谨慎起见"，将从某些塔可钟、必胜客和肯德基餐厅的餐点中去除新鲜洋葱。【原文：Yum Brands said on Thursday it would be removing fresh onions from its meals at certain Taco Bell, Pizza Hut and KFC restaurants out of an "abundance of caution", following an E.coli outbreak tied to McDonald's Quarter Pounder hamburgers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/yum-brands-takes-out-onions-meals-after-ecoli-outbreak-mcdonalds-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6OTWQN7YRPB7AK3ALV7QHNYVQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:35:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[D.E. Shaw 在空气产品公司董事会之争中支持曼特尔里奇公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士周四透露，对冲基金 D.E. Shaw 改变了其在工业气体公司空气化工产品公司（Air Products and Chemicals）的改革运动路线，目前正在支持竞争对手激进分子的努力，而不是继续挑战自己的董事会。【原文：Hedge fund D.E. Shaw shifted course in its campaign for change at industrial gases company Air Products and Chemicals and is now supporting a rival activist's efforts instead of pressing ahead with its own board challenge, sources familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/de-shaw-throws-support-mantle-ridge-air-products-board-fight-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LI56WVWOTRINROCQB5CA3TMO5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主席表示，桑坦德银行将于 2025 年底前在美国建立一家提供全面服务的数字化银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙桑坦德银行（Santander）执行主席安娜-博廷（Ana Botin）周四表示，到 2025 年，该银行将在美国拥有一家提供全面服务的数字银行。【原文：Spanish lender Santander will have a full service digital bank in the United States by 2025, its executive chairman Ana Botin said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/santander-will-have-full-service-digital-bank-us-by-2025-end-chair-says-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YLQ6HSXENKC5O7F7DW7DLYGIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:10:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国卫生部称，UnitedHealth 技术部门遭黑客攻击，1 亿人受到影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生部门网站显示，今年 2 月发生在 UnitedHealth 技术部门 Change 的黑客攻击事件影响了 1 亿人的个人信息，使其成为美国最大的医疗数据泄露事件。【原文：The February hack at UnitedHealth's tech unit Change affected the personal information of 100 million people, the U.S. health department's website showed, making it the largest healthcare data breach in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/hack-unitedhealths-tech-unit-impacted-100-mln-people-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MBOP3TWK5L6REXARIXOMSENMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，JBS 和 Sigma 正在争夺卡夫亨氏价值 30 亿美元的热狗业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟知内情的人士透露，巴西肉类包装商 JBS 和墨西哥 Sigma Alimentos 是竞相收购包装食品巨头卡夫亨氏（Kraft Heinz）旗下热狗和冷盘业务 Oscar Mayer 的两家公司之一。【原文：Brazilian meatpacker JBS and Mexico's Sigma Alimentos are among those competing to acquire Oscar Mayer, the hot dogs and cold cuts business of packaged food giant Kraft Heinz , according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/jbs-sigma-vie-kraft-heinzs-3-billion-hot-dog-business-sources-say-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVLORREKKZPMVHQZETPDZV2NUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:54:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期固定利率抵押贷款升至 6.54]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国抵押贷款利率连续第四周上升，这表明即使美联储降息，房地产市场在一段时间内仍将处于低迷状态。【原文：U.S. mortgage rates increased for a fourth straight week this week, suggesting the housing market could remain on the back foot for some time even as the Federal Reserve cuts interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-fixed-rate-mortgage-rises-654-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBE3ZPRDYNL2PGKRKQG7UXL7LU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英迈估值 60 亿美元，纽交所首日股价大涨 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[英迈（Ingram Micro）的股票在周四首次上市时大涨 15%，使这家全球最大的技术分销商的估值达到 60 亿美元。【原文：Ingram Micro's shares jumped 15% in their market debut on Thursday, giving one of the world's largest technology distributors a valuation of $6 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ingram-micro-valued-6-billion-shares-jump-15-nyse-debut-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTHX7NBWU5ITVJDEMFAKRCQD34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，美国食品和药物管理局正在调查麦当劳供应商泰勒农场是否是大肠杆菌爆发的源头]]></title><description><![CDATA[据CNBC周四报道，美国食品和药物管理局正在调查麦当劳的供应商泰勒农场（Taylor Farms）是否可能是与Quarter Pounder汉堡包有关的大肠杆菌疫情的源头。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration was investigating whether Taylor Farms, a supplier for McDonald's , was the possible source of the E. coli outbreak linked to Quarter Pounder hamburgers, which has killed at least one person and sickened nearly 50 others, CNBC reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/fda-probing-mcdonalds-supplier-taylor-farms-source-e-coli-outbreak-cnbc-reports-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I2D3KLN4BNN7DJDJ5A2FCLPGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国主权信用违约掉期因大选和债务上限问题而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府债务的投保成本已攀升至近一年以来的最高点，这表明投资者对美国总统大选的结果感到紧张，因为这可能会降低政府偿还债务的能力。【原文：The cost of insuring exposure to U.S. government debt has climbed to its highest in nearly one year, suggesting investors are getting nervous about a U.S. presidential election outcome that could make the government less able to repay debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-sovereign-credit-default-swaps-rise-election-debt-ceiling-jitters-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ2UZU4R6JMQLOIG5CNGDVK3PY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 15:33:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟领导人将为集团提高竞争力设定最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 11 月峰会的结论草案，欧盟领导人将为深化单一市场、增加投资资本和统一能源市场设定多个最后期限，峰会的重点是推动欧盟提高竞争力。【原文：European Union leaders will set multiple deadlines for a deeper single market, more capital for investments and a unified energy market, according to draft conclusions for a summit in November focused on the bloc's push to boost its competitiveness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-leaders-set-deadlines-blocs-competitiveness-push-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5T6LPOJPJPJ3DKDKO7ZFP2JPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 15:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者需求疲软，运营商下调年度收入预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于消费者在供暖、通风和空调系统等非必需品方面的支出疲软，开利全球周四下调了年度收入预期，导致其股价下跌超过 7%。【原文：Carrier Global cut its annual revenue forecast on Thursday due to weak consumer spending on non-essential items such as heating, ventilation and air conditioning systems, sending its shares down more than 7%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/carrier-cuts-annual-revenue-forecast-weak-consumer-demand-shares-fall-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X642WQEXBVM5HJ3RGR6XR4F65I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 15:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业产品公司联席首席执行官表示不考虑新建二叠纪石油管道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源管道运营商企业产品公司（Enterprise Products）联席首席执行官吉姆-蒂格（Jim Teague）周四表示，公司不考虑在德克萨斯州西部二叠纪页岩油田增设一条新的原油管道。【原文：U.S. energy pipeline operator Enterprise Products is not considering adding a new crude oil line out of the Permian shale field in West Texas, co-CEO Jim Teague said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/enterprise-products-not-considering-new-permian-oil-pipeline-says-co-ceo-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRWIUYIJQVPUXP3ISJXFJEEAXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 14:58:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，安联正在权衡 AllianzGI 部门的各种选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位知情人士告诉路透社，安联正在权衡其安联全球投资者部门的各种选择，包括可能合并或部分出售该部门，此举将扩大该业务的规模。【原文：Allianz is weighing options for its Allianz Global Investors unit, including a possible merger or partial sale of the division, four people with knowledge of the matter told Reuters, in a move that would give the business greater scale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/allianz-weighs-options-allianzgi-unit-sources-say-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHDTPBK66BO6VAR2NYQ5UAPSUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 14:56:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月新屋销售创近 1 年半最高纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于购房者急于利用抵押贷款利率的下降，9 月份美国新建独栋住宅的销量增至近 1 年半以来的最高水平。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes increased to the highest level in nearly 1-1/2 years in September as buyers rushed in to take advantage of a decline in mortgage rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-new-home-sales-highest-nearly-1-12-years-september-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISLCTUNTWVN7XM3W4MW6H36YI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 14:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[盎格鲁集团的铜矿业务支点能否帮助其挫败新的收购要约？]]></title><description><![CDATA[英美资源集团转变为以铜矿为主的矿业公司的速度很可能决定其最终命运--是作为独立运营商生存下去，还是被必和必拓集团（BHP Group）等更大的竞争对手吞并，必和必拓集团今年早些时候未能收购英美资源集团。【原文：The speed at which Anglo American shifts to becoming a copper-focused miner may well dictate its ultimate fate - survival as an independent operator, or absorption by a bigger rival such as BHP Group, which earlier this year failed to buy the group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/can-anglos-copper-pivot-help-thwart-renewed-takeover-bid-2024-10-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GXAWSFTGNOO7IEWHCRTQWUMZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 14:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>