<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:28:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:28:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月独户住宅开工量和许可量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[在抵押贷款利率回升的影响下，美国 4 月份的独栋住宅建设和许可证数量均有所下降，但待售房屋的严重短缺仍为新建筑提供了支撑。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding and permits fell in April amid a resurgence in mortgage rates, but new construction remains supported by an acute shortage of houses for sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-single-family-housing-starts-permits-fall-april-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZG2VVL5R5I5NNUNCT4GXKCZ6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月份进口价格创两年来最大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于能源产品和其他商品的成本上升，4 月份美国进口价格创下两年来的最大涨幅，这表明国内通胀可能在一段时间内持续走高。【原文：U.S. import prices rose by the most in two years in April amid rising costs for energy products and other goods, suggesting that domestic inflation could remain elevated for a while.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-import-prices-increase-by-most-two-years-april-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M37KNN22CJKSNG3AJDHUH3KV4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国因维吾尔族强迫劳动禁止从 26 家棉花贸易商和仓库进口棉花]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周四在网上发布公告称，美国正在阻止从26家棉花贸易商或仓库设施进口棉花，美国称这些棉花贸易商或仓库设施与强迫维吾尔人劳动有关。【原文：The United States is blocking imports from 26 cotton traders or warehouse facilities that it says are linked to forced Uyghur labor, a U.S. government notice posted online on Thursday said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-bars-imports-26-cotton-traders-warehouses-over-uyghur-forced-labor-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNWUO2WP4JIWZBA7DLCDXTKIHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雨果-博斯与大卫-贝克汉姆合作推出设计系列]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国时尚品牌雨果-博斯（Hugo Boss）周四表示，该公司已与前曼联中场大卫-贝克汉姆（David Beckham）建立了多年的设计合作伙伴关系，以提高对其 Boss 品牌的需求。【原文：Hugo Boss has struck up a multi-year design partnership with Former Manchester United midfielder David Beckham, the German fashion house said on Thursday, as it seeks to boost demand for its Boss brand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hugo-boss-david-beckham-partner-up-design-collection-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGSNEHA53FJUTG62SJSS3SILKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:43:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降；劳动力市场逐步缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量有所下降，表明劳动力市场基本强劲。【原文：The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits fell last week, pointing to underlying strength in the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-labor-market-gradually-easing-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HW4PJAUG3NN3BIL45A2DULJVSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀数据疲软，主要券商维持美国降息观点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在通胀数据低于预期提振了经济软着陆的希望之后，全球顶级券商维持了对美国联邦储备委员会今年降息时间的预期。【原文：Top global brokerages have retained their expectations for when the U.S. Federal Reserve will lower interest rates this year, after softer-than-expected inflation data boosted hopes of a soft landing for the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/major-brokerages-retain-us-rate-cut-view-after-soft-inflation-data-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBZAHWBUCJOYLI5DBOZWE3ALDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:16:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络设备需求回升，思科公司股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四收盘前，思科系统公司股价上涨约 4%，因为其乐观的第四季度预测表明，网络设备需求进一步趋稳，而且该公司以 280 亿美元收购网络安全公司 Splunk 的交易也带来了收益。【原文：Cisco Systems shares rose about 4% before the bell on Thursday after an upbeat fourth-quarter forecast signaled further stabilization in networking equipment demand and benefits from its $28 billion deal for cybersecurity firm Splunk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cisco-rises-networking-equipment-demand-rebound-takes-root-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PCHPTBQMFJ63LDZHGMET22Z3E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:59:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司将以 8.5 亿美元收购 Proteologix 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司（Johnson &amp; Johnson）周四表示，将以 8.5 亿美元现金收购私人控股的 Proteologix 公司，并有可能获得额外的里程碑付款。【原文：Johnson &amp; Johnson on Thursday said it would acquire privately held Proteologix for $850 million in cash, with potential for an additional milestone payment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/johnson-johnson-acquire-proteologix-850-million-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQL7DTAYHRIUJP3XOSZARSNGHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:40:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Under Armour 预测全年销售额和利润均将下滑，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[服装生产商 Under Armour 周四预测其年度收入和利润低于分析师预期，这表明美国消费者在通胀压力下削减了可自由支配的开支，从而导致对其运动服装的需求疲软。【原文：Apparel maker Under Armour forecast its annual revenue and profit below analysts' expectations on Thursday, a sign of soft demand for its sportswear in the U.S. as consumers cut back on discretionary spending in the face of sticky inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/under-armour-forecasts-annual-sales-below-estimates-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMNZ6YDRRVIILODES7OW4WMCSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:39:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，汉莎航空为达成 ITA 协议提供了短途航线折中方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接了解此事的人士周四表示，汉莎航空已提出保留一些竞争性的 ITA 短途航线，以争取欧盟反垄断机构批准其竞购意大利航空公司的股份。【原文：Lufthansa has offered to keep some competing ITA short-haul routes in an effort to secure EU antitrust approval for its bid for a stake in the Italian airline, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/lufthansa-offers-short-haul-compromise-ita-deal-sources-say-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6MFCNYKGBMAFLITS4JZXDFDUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛上调全年销售和利润预期，股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国零售业巨头沃尔玛周四上调了 2025 财年的销售和利润预期，预计通胀缓解将进一步刺激生活必需品的需求，并带来电子产品等可自由支配产品销售的反弹。【原文：U.S. retail giant Walmart raised its fiscal 2025 sales and profit forecast on Thursday, betting on easing inflation to further boost demand for essentials and bring a rebound in sales of discretionary products like electronics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-lifts-full-year-sales-profit-forecast-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FWAWWWH6VI4RMDRD6DGQVJXXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:13:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 和 AMC 业绩滑坡，主题股涨势乏力]]></title><description><![CDATA[零售业宠儿 GameStop 和 AMC 周四在盘前交易中继续下滑，因为作为 2021 年 meme 股涨势核心人物的 "咆哮的凯蒂猫 "回归的兴奋情绪逐渐消退。【原文：Retail darlings GameStop and AMC continued their slide into premarket trading on Thursday, as the euphoria over the return of "Roaring Kitty", who was the central figure in 2021 meme stock rally, fizzles out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestop-amc-slide-meme-stocks-rally-loses-steam-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C46YKUZKEVPFTGZDTJQO5ZIB7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球监管机构称银行业数字化带来新风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球银行业监管机构周四在一份报告中称，数字化和大科技进入金融业会带来新的漏洞，并扩大银行系统中现有的风险，可能需要新的规则来缓解这些风险。【原文：The digitalisation and entry of Big Tech into finance create new vulnerabilities and amplify existing risks in the banking system that may need new rules to mitigate, global banking regulators said in a report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/digitalisation-banking-creates-new-risks-says-global-watchdog-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ST5WR33R7JLB3EQD7YT7EBA2II</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:13:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[作物价格下跌挤压需求，迪尔下调 2024 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于农作物价格下跌，农民购买拖拉机和联合收割机的数量减少，迪尔公司周四第二次下调了年度利润预期。【原文：Deere trimmed its annual profit forecast for the second time on Thursday, as farmers buy fewer tractors and combine harvesters due to falling crop prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/deere-cuts-2024-profit-forecast-demand-slowdown-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7REQFLP7BNKXABBL5GSBAUZKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:09:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国零售商京东商城第一季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国在线零售商京东周四公布的第一季度营收超过了市场预期，原因是大幅降价帮助提振了因顾客谨慎情绪而遭受重创的销售额。【原文：Chinese online retailer JD.com on Thursday reported first-quarter revenue that beat market estimates, as deep price cuts helped boost sales that had been hit hard by cautious customer sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinese-retailer-jdcom-reports-q1-revenue-that-beats-estimates-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NYB6Q57EJKRXGUADR46EBESJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小企业如何成为高盛盟友，对抗华盛顿法规]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰夫-里格斯（Jeff Riggs）是蒙大拿州的一名商人，拥有一个小型数据中心，他于 11 月飞往华盛顿特区与美国参议员史蒂夫-戴恩斯（Steve Daines）会面。【原文：Jeff Riggs, a Montana businessman who owns a small data center, flew to Washington D.C. in November to meet with his U.S. Senator Steve Daines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/basel-battle-goldmans-unlikely-foot-soldiers-fight-against-bank-capital-hikes-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5YMN2F735O6FDKEBCIPQFUHSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美达公司因儿童安全隐患面临欧盟调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟监管机构周四表示，Meta Platforms 的社交媒体网站 Facebook 和 Instagram 将因可能违反欧盟有关儿童安全的在线内容规定而接受调查，此举可能导致巨额罚款。【原文：Meta Platforms' social media sites Facebook and Instagram will be investigated for potential breaches of EU online content rules relating to child safety, EU regulators said on Thursday, a move that could lead to hefty fines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-faces-eu-investigation-over-child-safety-risks-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOZ4WXICTFMVNOCI5QJF7WHSHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储威廉姆斯访谈实录]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯周三接受了路透社的采访。为清晰起见，以下文字实录经过编辑：【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams was interviewed by Reuters on Wednesday. The following transcript has been edited for clarity:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/transcript-interview-with-new-york-feds-williams-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7STSUX2ABJJS7G2ZZ6SYARL5IA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通货紧缩重现，美国经济降温，美国股市维持新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZKVTDJNKFJZLFZGPCSGNXUZOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储威廉姆斯欢迎通胀数据，但不准备寻求降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）对消费者通胀数据走软表示欢迎，但他对路透社记者说，这一利好消息还不足以要求美国央行很快降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams welcomed the arrival of softer consumer inflation data, he told Reuters, but said that positive news is not enough to call for the U.S. central bank to cut interest rates sometime soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-williams-welcomes-inflation-data-not-ready-seek-rate-cuts-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AEN4VED2GJMDTE76EDKWPV3YQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:01:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：雪佛龙准备在 55 年后退出北海]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司（Chevron）准备出售其剩余的英国北海石油和天然气资产，此举标志着这家美国能源巨头在 55 年多后将退出这个老化的盆地。【原文：Chevron is set to launch the sale of its remaining UK North Sea oil and gas assets, in a move that would mark the U.S. energy giant's exit from the ageing basin after more than 55 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chevron-prepares-north-sea-exit-after-more-than-55-years-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDEAOZPG55JMTLRTCT5CLKJBVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典法院驳回特斯拉车牌案上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典一家上诉法院周四支持驳回特斯拉因车牌冲突对瑞典交通局提起的诉讼，这是该美国公司与北欧国家工会之间更广泛争议的一部分。【原文：A Swedish appeals court upheld on Thursday a dismissal of Tesla's lawsuit against Sweden's Transport Agency in a conflict over licence plates, part of a wider dispute between the U.S. company and labour unions in the Nordic country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/swedish-court-rejects-tesla-appeal-licence-plate-case-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHAN4B33XNKZ3NOHC2MQOQSI5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AIG 将以 38 亿美元出售 Corebridge 20% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国际集团（American International Group）周四表示，将以 38 亿美元的价格出售其寿险和养老金部门 Corebridge Financial 20% 的股份。【原文：American International Group said on Thursday it would sell a 20% stake in its life insurance and retirement unit Corebridge Financial for $3.8 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/aig-sell-20-stake-corebridge-38-bln-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CENVZUVUFLI3K5OMJK7UUL35Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:42:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀报告疲软，降息希望升温，期权走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于不温不火的通胀报告增强了降息的希望，周四美国股指期货走高，使华尔街有望延续上一交易日创下的历史高点的涨势。【原文：U.S. stock index futures inched higher on Thursday, putting Wall Street on track to extend gains from the all-time highs hit in the previous session as a tepid inflation report bolstered hopes of interest-rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-higher-softer-inflation-report-lifts-rate-cut-hopes-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQROXBLPKJNTDINRG5OIZZCCUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行因邮政银行问题遭投资者抨击]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行的大投资者周四对这家德国第一大银行表达了不满，称其邮政银行业务出现的问题是一种破坏信任的尴尬。【原文：Big investors in Deutsche Bank vented their frustration at Germany's top lender on Thursday, describing problems at its Postbank business as a trust-damaging embarrassment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-under-fire-investors-over-postbank-problems-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEBF6YQF4VPY3MO4AP7Z57BZLQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:32:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[S 对德国 "去工业化 "的担忧可能被夸大了--目前是这样]]></title><description><![CDATA[高昂的能源成本、疲软的全球需求、向净零排放经济体的颠覆性转变以及来自中国的日益激烈的竞争，都对德国的经济模式提出了生存问题。【原文：High energy costs, weak global demand, a disruptive shift towards net-zero economies, and growing competition from China are raising existential questions for Germany's economic model.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/s-fears-german-de-industrialisation-may-be-overblown-now-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D47YDPRNYZIMFK6PUQBZETZCTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:29:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[连抛三周后外国投资者抢购日本长期债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[外国投资者结束了连续三周抛售日本债券的趋势，转而购买长期证券，但分析人士认为，在市场不确定性持续存在的情况下，反弹可能稍纵即逝。【原文：Foreign investors ended a three-week trend of selling Japanese bonds by purchasing long-term securities, although analysts suggest the rebound could be fleeting amid ongoing market uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/foreign-investors-snap-up-long-term-japan-bonds-after-three-week-selling-streak-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQU5DL7PBZPWXD364FMAU5SF5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:19:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫采取行动保护美国太阳能制造商免受中国竞争之害]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周四表示，将取消对进口双面板的关税豁免，使项目更容易因使用美国制造的产品而申请补贴，从而保护国内太阳能工厂免受中国竞争的影响。【原文：The White House on Thursday said it would protect domestic solar factories from Chinese competition by scrapping a tariff exemption for imported double-sided panels and making it easier for projects to claim a subsidy for using American-made products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/white-house-moves-protect-us-solar-manufacturers-chinese-competition-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGK7P2UXNVLS5HDHDNBBMKM4QY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以旧换新：中国最新房地产市场计划开局不利]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国政府发起的一项鼓励人们将旧公寓换成新公寓的活动正引起人们的兴趣，但却面临着一个重大障碍：该计划的参与者正竭力出售他们目前的住房。【原文：A campaign by Chinese authorities to encourage people to replace their old apartments with new ones is attracting interest, but faces one major hurdle: the participants in the scheme are struggling to sell their current homes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/swap-old-new-chinas-latest-property-market-plan-off-poor-start-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIGO7EVXLBK77AXZ223XQ7CR7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:53:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田在泰国量产前测试新型电动皮卡车]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车一位高管周四表示，丰田汽车正在测试新型电池电动 Hilux 皮卡，以评估其在不同条件下的性能，该汽车制造商准备在 2025 年底前在泰国生产这种汽车。【原文：Toyota Motor is testing the new battery-electric Hilux pickup truck to assess its performance in different conditions as the car maker prepares to manufacture the vehicle in Thailand by the end of 2025, an executive said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-tests-new-ev-pickup-truck-ahead-mass-production-thailand-2024-05-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTDADFFY2ZLWRMMVVYNSCKRKKA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>