<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:39:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:39:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[本田将停产由通用汽车在美国组装的讴歌电动车]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本汽车制造商本田将停止在美国生产由通用汽车公司组装的讴歌 ZDX 电动跨界车。【原文：Japanese automaker Honda is ceasing production in the U.S. of its Acura ZDX electric crossovers assembled by General Motors .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-discontinue-acura-ev-assembled-by-gm-us-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUSGFNJN4BOH7OY2IMIWLKIK5E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:37:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国支持提振阿根廷股票、债券和比索]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对哈维尔-米莱（Javier Milei）总统领导下的南美政府推动改革的支持有了更多细节，阿根廷陷入困境的债券、股票和比索货币在周三连续第三天上涨。【原文：Argentina's embattled bonds, stocks and peso currency gained for a third day on Wednesday after more details were shared on U.S. support for the reform push by the South American government under President Javier Milei.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/view-us-support-boosts-argentina-stocks-bonds-peso-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OV52S6MGW5LTRNUUFGC4L25744</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司将F/A-18服役期改装工作迁出圣路易斯]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周三表示，将把F/A-18战斗机的服役期改装工作迁出圣路易斯地区，以支持其未来项目的扩展计划。【原文：Boeing said on Wednesday it would relocate F/A-18 fighter jet's service life modification work out of the St. Louis region to support its expansion plans for future programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-relocate-fa-18-service-life-modification-work-out-st-louis-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNF763D7RNN7VN52LMSSWTU75E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司 Modular 融资 2.5 亿美元，欲挑战英伟达的主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Modular周三表示，它在一轮融资中筹集了2.5亿美元，估值达16亿美元，旨在挑战英伟达（Nvidia）在人工智能计算市场的软件垄断地位。【原文：AI startup Modular said on Wednesday it raised $250 million in a funding round valuing it at $1.6 billion, as it aims to challenge Nvidia's software stranglehold on the AI computing market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-startup-modular-raises-250-million-seeks-challenge-nvidia-dominance-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3R3HIKBVVRIOPFNQU6DA364RGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将人类学人工智能模型引入 365 Copilot，实现 OpenAI 以外的多元化发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周三表示，将把 Anthropic 公司的人工智能模型整合到其 Copilot 助手中，这表明这家软件巨头正在努力减少对其与 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 的高调合作关系的依赖。【原文：Microsoft said on Wednesday it will integrate artificial intelligence models from Anthropic into its Copilot assistant, signaling the software giant's push to reduce dependence on its high-profile partnership with ChatGPT maker OpenAI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-brings-anthropic-ai-models-365-copilot-diversifies-beyond-openai-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2SZ47J65VLADHSH4AKLT2L37I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国确认从 8 月 1 日起对欧盟汽车和汽车零部件征收 15%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周三发布正式通知，实施美国与欧盟的贸易协定，确认从8月1日起对汽车和汽车进口征收15%的关税，并列出了对某些药物化合物、飞机零部件和其他进口产品的豁免。【原文：The Trump administration issued a formal notice on Wednesday implementing the U.S. trade agreement with the European Union, confirming that autos and auto imports will be subject to a 15% duty from Aug. 1, and listing exemptions for certain pharmaceutical compounds and aircraft parts, and other imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/us-confirms-eu-autos-auto-parts-15-tariffs-started-aug-1-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBWALUCOLVM5BGQRPXW65EZAMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 首席执行官扎克伯格称 Instagram 月活跃用户已增至 30 亿]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 公司首席执行官马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）周三表示，Instagram 的月活跃用户已增至 30 亿，这是全球最受欢迎的社交媒体应用之一的又一个里程碑。【原文：Meta Platforms' Instagram has grown to 3 billion Monthly Active Users, CEO Mark Zuckerberg said on Wednesday, marking another milestone for one of the most popular social media apps in the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-ceo-zuckerberg-says-instagram-has-grown-3-billion-monthly-active-users-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBZZNKUFMZOYPESWLWTGN6SIJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:57:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waymo 推出企业机器人出租车账户，以满足商务出行需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的 Waymo 周三推出了 "Waymo for Business "企业计划，该计划允许企业设立账户，这样员工就可以在洛杉矶、凤凰城、旧金山、奥斯汀和亚特兰大呼唤其机器人出租车。【原文：Alphabet-owned Waymo on Wednesday rolled out "Waymo for Business," a corporate program that lets companies set up accounts so employees can hail its robotaxis in Los Angeles, Phoenix, San Francisco, Austin and Atlanta.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/waymo-launches-corporate-robotaxi-accounts-court-business-travel-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">674DQQVHRBLTVNG76KSLGPKDT4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会任命乔恩-克罗珀（Jon Kroeper）为交易与市场部副主任]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周三发表声明称，任命乔恩-克罗珀（Jon Kroeper）为该机构交易与市场部副主任，自 9 月 29 日起生效。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Wednesday that Jon Kroeper has been appointed deputy director of the agency's division of trading and markets effective Sept. 29, the SEC said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/jon-kroeper-named-sec-deputy-director-trading-markets-division-agency-says-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVELHZJNSRPRXEZCOFNP6EQACI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:22:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉米-基梅尔的独白在社交媒体上获得了超过 1,500 万次点击量]]></title><description><![CDATA[在华特-迪士尼（Walt Disney）解除对吉米-基梅尔（Jimmy Kimmel）的禁赛后，他周二重返美国深夜电视节目的独白在谷歌的 YouTube 和 Meta 的 Instagram 上被观看了 1400 多万次。【原文：Jimmy Kimmel's monologue on his return to U.S. late-night television on Tuesday after Walt Disney lifted his suspension has been seen more than 14 million times on Google's YouTube and Meta's Instagram.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/jimmy-kimmel-monologue-racks-up-more-than-14-million-views-social-media-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6TPOPIXARI4NFBQDTOLRJJJBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国贸易机构称关税和冲突导致航运业大幅波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国贸易和发展会议（United Nations Trade and Development agency）周三发布的一份报告显示，由于地缘政治紧张局势加剧以及新关税浪潮造成的干扰，航运业正在经历重大波动。【原文：The shipping industry is experiencing major volatility amid rising geopolitical tensions and disruptions caused by a wave of new tariffs, according to a report published on Wednesday by the U.N. Trade and Development agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/tariffs-conflict-causing-major-volatility-shipping-industry-says-un-trade-agency-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">II5RS64N3FOQ3A7EVUZYKHVPGQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特详述美国的大力支持，阿根廷资产反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特详细阐述了对阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱伊的右翼政府和该国市场的大规模支持后，阿根廷的金融资产周三连续第三天反弹。【原文：Argentina's financial assets rallied for a third day on Wednesday after U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent detailed a massive support for Argentine President Javier Milei's right-wing government and the country's markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentine-assets-rally-bessent-details-strong-us-support-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSZA3SO3HBON5K2QSGPQVN3WRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:01:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，本-卡森将加入美国农业部担任营养顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，前住房部长、退休神经外科医生本-卡森（Ben Carson）将暂时担任美国农业部高级营养和住房顾问。【原文：Former housing secretary and retired neurosurgeon Ben Carson will take charge as senior nutrition and housing adviser at the U.S. Department of Agriculture temporarily, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-name-ben-carson-nutrition-adviser-usda-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y32A4SIXPJN27JYALODQG2VNUU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达拉斯联储调查显示，2025 年第三季度石油和天然气产量下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[据达拉斯联储周三称，2025 年第三季度，德克萨斯、路易斯安那和新墨西哥等主要产油州的石油和天然气生产及活动略有下降。【原文：Oil and gas production and activity in the key producing states of Texas, Louisiana and New Mexico declined slightly in the third quarter of 2025, according to the Dallas Fed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-gas-activity-texas-louisiana-new-mexico-slipped-q3-2025-dallas-fed-survey-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GU3UTY4CABOYDKYSGLXKGPU3VI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田巴西工厂因暴风雨受损而停产]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本汽车制造商丰田公司周三在一份声明中说，由于大雨和狂风严重损坏了其费利茨港工厂，该公司周二被迫停止了巴西两家工厂的生产。【原文：Japanese carmaker Toyota was forced to halt production at two plants in Brazil on Tuesday after heavy rain and winds severely damaged its Porto Feliz factory, the company said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-halts-production-brazil-plants-after-storm-damage-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUT547W3WFNKLHH6PTCZC2W7RE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:18:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月新屋销售激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份，美国新建独栋住宅的销售量激增，但抵押贷款利率下降带来的提振作用可能会受到劳动力市场疲软的限制。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes surged in August, but the boost from declining mortgage rates could be limited by a weakening labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-surge-august-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73GEMT5LMVLNBMPUYGCSJWXDZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:14:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比利时法院驳回阿尔斯通对 SNCB 选择 17 亿欧元列车交易的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[比利时最高行政法院周三驳回了阿尔斯通关于暂停国家铁路运营商 SNCB 指定 CAF 为 AM30 列车合同首选供应商的决定的请求。【原文：Belgium's top administrative court on Wednesday rejected Alstom's request to suspend national rail operator SNCB's decision to name CAF as the preferred supplier for its AM30 train contract.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/belgian-court-overrules-alstoms-appeal-sncbs-pick-17-billion-euro-trains-deal-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7R7X5ONEVO6JGEURSSTP5PRFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员称 FAA 拟对波音公司罚款 310 万美元不够]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党参议员理查德-布卢门撒尔（Richard Blumenthal）表示，联邦航空管理局拟对波音公司一系列违反安全规定的行为处以 310 万美元的罚款是不够的，并希望该机构解释是如何计算处罚的。【原文：Democratic Senator Richard Blumenthal said the Federal Aviation Administration's proposed $3.1 million fine against Boeing for a series of safety violations is inadequate and wants the agency to explain how it calculated the penalty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/faas-proposed-31-million-fine-boeing-inadequate-senator-says-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRO5YNO2IVKUFCT5IAJQIH7VRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[里克-佩里的数据中心房地产投资信托公司费米在美国首次公开募股中的目标估值为 130 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由美国前能源部长里克-佩里（Rick Perry）共同创办的数据中心制造商费米公司（Fermi）周三表示，其在美国首次公开募股的目标估值为 131.6 亿美元。【原文：Fermi, a data center builder co-founded by former U.S. Energy Secretary Rick Perry, said on Wednesday it was targeting a $13.16 billion valuation in its initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rick-perrys-data-center-reit-fermi-targets-13-billion-valuation-us-ipo-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4VXDWAA55I73C4AKBQF5Z5VUM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:29:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利将为 BPM 银行与法国农业信贷银行的任何交易设定条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济部长吉安卡洛-乔盖蒂（Giancarlo Giorgetti）周三表示，罗马政府将为 BPM 银行和法国农业信贷银行意大利分行之间可能的合作设定条件。【原文：The Rome government will set conditions on a possible tie-up between Banco BPM and the Italian unit of France's Credit Agricole , Economy Minister Giancarlo Giorgetti said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/italy-set-conditions-any-banco-bpm-credit-agricole-deal-finmin-says-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4P6DLOQ2EZNADOLKPLKDW7W2ZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，甲骨文希望通过出售债券融资 150 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道，甲骨文公司正寻求通过公司债券销售融资150亿美元，因为该公司希望投入巨资建设云基础设施，以满足蓬勃发展的人工智能需求。【原文：Oracle is looking to raise $15 billion in corporate bond sales, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter, as the company looks to invest heavily in building out cloud infrastructure to cater to burgeoning AI demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/oracle-looks-raise-15-billion-bond-sales-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CS5MNRLTMBI3BKRSBTMT42FX2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥 9 月初通胀加速]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥的总体通胀率在 9 月上半月加速上升，与市场预期基本一致，接近央行目标的上限。【原文：Mexico's headline inflation sped up in the first half of September, broadly in line with market expectations, heading closer to the upper limit of the central bank's target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-inflation-speeds-up-early-september-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PST2FQGZHBIUFBIUXHXFC5V7NQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特股市因外资持股规定放宽的报道而创下 5 年来最大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，沙特阿拉伯股市创下 2020 年以来的最大单日涨幅，此前有报道称市场监管机构可能会放宽对外资持有上市公司股份的限制。【原文：Saudi Arabia's stocks posted their biggest daily rise since 2020 on Wednesday, following a report that the markets regulator may ease rules capping foreign ownership of listed companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-shares-jump-by-most-5-years-report-easing-foreign-ownership-rules-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYZLUG2G4VNGHJRMX7GU6I3EMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:51:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称飞机发动机和化学品可能成为中美谈判的筹码]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，美国的飞机发动机和零部件以及某些化学品可以为美国与中国的谈判提供筹码。【原文：U.S. aircraft engines and parts, along with certain chemicals, could give the United States leverage in its talks with China, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/bessent-says-aircraft-engines-chemicals-could-be-leverage-us-china-talks-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PYW5SEVNJLVHD47QKIAVPNTKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Freeport-McMoRan 预计第三季度铜、金综合销售额下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[Freeport-McMoRan 公司周三表示，预计第三季度铜和黄金的综合销售额将分别比此前预测下降约 4% 和近 6%，这使得该矿业公司的股价在盘前交易中下跌了 9%。【原文：Freeport-McMoRan said on Wednesday it was expecting consolidated sales to be lower by about 4% for copper and nearly 6% for gold in the third quarter, compared with its prior forecast, sending the miner's shares down 9% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/freeport-mcmoran-expects-lower-consolidated-sales-copper-gold-third-quarter-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPGWZ247NZOINNCSZIT5NUIB44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，美国准备以 200 亿美元的互换额度支持阿根廷]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三在 X 上发表文章称，美国目前正在与阿根廷央行就 200 亿美元的互换额度进行谈判，并随时准备采取必要行动支持这个南美国家。【原文：The U.S. is currently in negotiations for a $20 billion swap line with Argentina's central bank and stands ready to do what is needed to support the South American country, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-ready-support-argentina-needed-bessent-says-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YK6MNQJPJJOMDBWP7ERTANWPQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:30:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部贝森特表示，他正在寻找一位思想开放的人担任美联储主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，他将在下周对许多候选人进行面试，以接替杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）担任美联储主席，并计划在10月的第一周完成第一轮面试。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Wednesday said he would interview a lot of candidates next week to replace Jerome Powell as chair of the Federal Reserve, with an eye to completing the first round of interviews by the first week of October.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/treasurys-bessent-says-hes-looking-someone-with-an-open-mind-fed-chair-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIWBEY2XORPNJJ47BNNGZ3H2XU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:24:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私募股权公司 Novacap 将以 19 亿美元收购 Integral Ad Science]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司 Novacap 将收购 Integral Ad Science，该交易对这家数字广告验证公司的估值约为 19 亿美元，目标公司的股价在盘前交易中上涨了约 20%。【原文：Private equity firm Novacap will acquire Integral Ad Science in a deal that values the digital ad verification firm at around $1.9 billion, sending the target's shares up about 20% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/private-equity-firm-novacap-buy-integral-ad-science-19-billion-deal-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHQCSMT6NZOTDEV2WAL4CO4AJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[两位美国参议员敦促 Tinder 母公司采取行动，打击其应用程序中的约会诈骗行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名美国参议员周三致信 Tinder 母公司 Match，要求该公司采取行动打击其平台上的约会诈骗行为，并询问该公司在侦查欺诈行为和保护用户方面所做的努力。【原文：Two U.S. senators sent a letter to Tinder parent Match on Wednesday, pushing for action against dating scams on the company's platforms and asking for information about its efforts to detect frauds and protect its users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/two-us-senators-urge-tinder-parent-act-against-dating-scams-its-apps-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN4C4VGZDROXXDITKEIFJ7LVMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:13:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟询问苹果、谷歌和微软如何应对金融诈骗]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司、谷歌公司和微软公司被欧盟技术监管机构问及采取了哪些措施防止其平台被用于金融诈骗，这凸显了欧洲对网络欺诈成本的担忧。【原文：Apple , Google and Microsoft have been asked by EU tech regulators about the measures they are taking to prevent their platforms being used for financial scams, underscoring Europe's concern about the cost of online fraud.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/eu-asks-apple-google-microsoft-what-they-are-doing-tackle-finance-scams-2025-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLO2HZINVJM3LHP3LBXHHBSX3Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>