<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:35:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:35:53 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯谢韦尔钢铁公司警告：该地区禁止外来劳工，建筑业面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯钢铁制造商谢韦尔钢铁公司（Severstal）周五抨击了一位州长禁止农民工从事建筑业的决定，并称此举可能对工业项目造成严重损害。【原文：Russian steelmaker Severstal on Friday slammed a decision by a regional governor to ban migrant workers in the construction industry and said the move could cause serious harm to industrial projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russias-severstal-warns-construction-risks-region-bans-migrant-labour-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A65LOB4MNNI73AFJAEW2FDP4FY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚 Capital A 公司因外汇损失转为年度亏损，预计 2025 年实现盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚廉价航空公司亚航（AirAsia）的所有者 Capital A Berhad 公司周五出现年度亏损，主要原因是外汇损失，但该公司表示今年将恢复盈利。【原文：Malaysia's Capital A Berhad , owner of budget airline AirAsia, swung to an annual loss on Friday due mainly to foreign exchange losses, but the company said it would return to profitability this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/malaysias-capital-swings-annual-loss-forex-losses-expects-profitability-2025-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKHH5KUA6RK2ZF2GYRTIYVCQPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管存在关税担忧，美国股票基金仍获得大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至2月26日的一周内，投资者增持了美国股票基金，原因是他们对经济的韧性充满信心，并预期美联储将在今年晚些时候降息以刺激经济增长。【原文：Investors increased their holdings in U.S. equity funds over the week to February 26, buoyed by confidence in the economy's resilience and expectations of a Federal Reserve rate cut later this year to stimulate growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-gain-sharp-inflows-despite-tariff-concerns-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TMCFULJJZLPPONVBHJJ3HSONA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 获得 4.5 亿美元贷款，推迟发布季度财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 周五表示，该公司已获得一笔为期 12 个月的贷款，金额高达 4.5 亿美元，并将把第四季度业绩推迟到四月份，同时提交 2024 财年的年度文件。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Polestar has secured a 12-month loan facility of up to $450 million, it said on Friday, and would delay its fourth-quarter results to April along with its annual filing for fiscal 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestar-secures-450-million-loan-facility-delays-quarterly-results-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADZQKJPLPVMKXO5AHOOWNFR2ME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利法院解除对 LVMH 旗下迪奥意大利分公司涉嫌劳工行为的管制]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，意大利一家法院宣布提前结束对法国奢侈品巨头路威酩轩集团（LVMH）旗下一家意大利子公司的特别管理制度，该子公司被指控在生产迪奥（Dior）品牌手袋的过程中存在剥削劳工的行为。【原文：An Italian court on Friday announced the early end of a special administration regime placed on an Italian subsidiary of French luxury giant LVMH over allegations of labour exploitation in the manufacturing of Dior-branded handbags.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/italy-court-lifts-controls-lvmhs-dior-italian-unit-over-alleged-labour-practices-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWXL4VMOHBK67AHNDYGEV4ACSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:53:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[今年美国住房的可负担性将有所提高，但主要原因是利率降低：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对房地产市场专家进行的调查显示，未来一年美国房地产市场的可负担性将略有改善，这主要是基于对再次降息的预期，而非可购买房屋数量的增加。【原文：Affordability in the U.S. housing market will improve modestly in the coming year, according to property market experts polled by Reuters, based on expectations for a few more interest rate cuts, not an increase in homes available to purchase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-housing-get-bit-more-affordable-this-year-mainly-due-lower-rates-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFFSTEBQ3NJ3NKXGRJ4EQBZCGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:42:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战担忧加剧，美国标普500指数2025年收红]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7N6UMDM22RJI3KVI5ZXLDJOXBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大牧场主因担心特朗普征收关税而缩减牛群，牛肉价格可能上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普当选后，加拿大农民乔恩-瓦格斯（Jon Vaags）于 11 月放弃购买肉牛，因为对加拿大出口产品征收关税似乎是一个严重的风险。【原文：Canadian farmer Jon Vaags quit buying beef cattle in November after the election of U.S. President Donald Trump made tariffs on Canadian exports seem like a serious risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/beef-prices-may-rise-canadian-ranchers-shrink-cattle-herds-fearing-trump-tariffs-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3WH3NSDFBIXFJ5UMFKLIDFSTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联想在英国与爱立信关于临时专利许可的上诉中胜诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[联想集团周五在英国的上诉中胜诉，试图获得使用爱立信专利的临时许可证，这是两家公司就5G无线技术的全球许可纠纷做出的最新裁决。【原文：Lenovo on Friday won an appeal in Britain in its attempt to get an interim licence to use Ericsson's patents, in the latest ruling in the companies' global licensing dispute over 5G wireless technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/lenovo-wins-appeal-uk-fight-with-ericsson-over-interim-patent-licence-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA3QBWPF4RJATJO7PO5H3AWUNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:20:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点转向关键通胀数据，期指稳步上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五小幅上扬，在本周早些时候大幅下跌后企稳，原因是投资者将注意力转移到一个可能影响美联储货币政策预期的关键通胀数据上。【原文：U.S. stock index futures inched up on Friday, steadying after sharp declines earlier this week, as investors shifted their focus to a key inflation figure that could influence expectations regarding the Federal Reserve's monetary policy trajectory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-inch-up-focus-shifts-key-inflation-data-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFYAJKQVYJMCRKGD5YBT7V6NMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:12:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克陷入困境，阿迪达斯瞄准更大的美国市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者和分析师表示，阿迪达斯能否从市场领导者耐克手中赢得更多美国购物者的青睐，将是其今年能否继续取得成功的关键，因为这个德国品牌正在桑巴（Samba）和瞪羚（Gazelle）运动鞋之外寻找新的增长点。【原文：Whether Adidas can win more American shoppers from market leader Nike will be key to its continued success this year, investors and analysts said, as the German brand looks for new sources of growth beyond its Samba and Gazelle sneakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-targets-larger-us-market-share-nike-struggles-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP5QSSAYWRLPNE2YRE6XVVBVDA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:09:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 投资者对经济的担忧加剧，美国就业数据将是考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的美国月度就业报告事关重大，因为投资者要判断一连串令人担忧的数据是否预示着对经济的重大担忧。【原文：The stakes are high for the monthly U.S. jobs report in the coming week, as investors gauge whether a string of worrisome data is signaling significant concern about the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-rising-investor-angst-about-economy-be-tested-by-us-jobs-data-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMHN33GT7NJU3LPBY4YLFVF374</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：特朗普瞄准电动汽车补贴，通用汽车的电动汽车收益面临严峻考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[几十年来，通用汽车斥资数十亿美元试图开辟一条电动汽车发展之路，推出了许多电动汽车和混合动力汽车的先驱，但最终都未能在市场上实现大规模销售，最终被废弃。这一次可能会有所不同。【原文：General Motors has spent billions over decades trying to blaze an electric trail, releasing pioneering EVs and hybrids that ultimately failed to achieve mass-market sales before being scrapped. This time might be different.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gms-electric-gains-face-critical-test-trump-targets-ev-subsidies-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CXHAGJZ75I4BF5KNKCZ4CEKQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金因关税问题吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 2 月 26 日的一周内，受今年晚些时候降息预期持续升温的刺激，全球股票基金资金大幅流入，而本周报告的疲软经济数据又为这一预期提供了支撑。【原文：Global equity funds witnessed sharp inflows in the week through February 26, spurred by sustained expectations of rate cuts later this year, which were bolstered by weaker economic data reported during the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEQWMJLUZRKPHG7D36NH36ZDPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国规定自动驾驶软件升级须经监管部门批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国工业部周五表示，与自动驾驶相关的空中软件升级必须获得监管部门的批准，这是旨在防止汽车制造商利用软件升级隐瞒缺陷或逃避责任的新规定的一部分。【原文：Autonomous driving-related over-the-air software upgrades will be subject to regulatory approvals, China's industry ministry said on Friday, part of new regulations aimed at preventing automakers using them to conceal defects or avoid liability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-mandates-regulatory-approvals-autonomous-driving-software-upgrades-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CDMUM4JSBORTA4K4N3MFCWMEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新华社：中国空间站将在未来几年迎来首位外国宇航员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据新华社报道，中国和巴基斯坦周五签署了关于航天员选拔和培训的合作协议。【原文：China and Pakistan signed a cooperation agreement on the selection and training of astronauts on Friday, Xinhua reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/chinas-space-station-welcome-first-foreign-astronaut-next-few-years-xinhua-says-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYBY7A5ARBKWZCM72H2UU6UJK4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:22:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀疲软、增长乏力支持欧洲央行降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的最新数据显示，欧元区的通胀前景有所改善，但经济增长依然乏力，这为欧洲央行进一步降息以刺激已停滞近两年的经济提供了更充分的理由。【原文：Euro zone inflation prospects improved while growth remained anaemic, fresh data showed on Friday, solidifying the case for further ECB rate cuts to stimulate an economy that has been stagnant for nearly two years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/softer-inflation-weak-growth-bolster-case-ecb-rate-cuts-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTBAGNIXMRLCHNLPVHTNQMI2NU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 10:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行数万亿美元的支付崩溃令欧洲震动]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，欧洲中央银行支持数万亿欧元资金流动的机器发生了前所未有的长达一天的故障，银行在处理付款方面举步维艰。【原文：Banks struggled to process payments on Friday after an unprecedented day-long breakdown in the European Central Bank's machine underpinning trillions of euros of money movements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/deutsche-boerses-clearstream-deals-with-residual-impact-ecb-outage-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QTDU7JYD5N3NNHDFREFUH57XI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:49:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two dozen arrested for distributing AI-generated child abuse images]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two dozen people were arrested this week for their role in a criminal group that distributed images generated by artificial intelligence of children being sexually abused, Europol said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/two-dozen-arrested-distributing-ai-generated-child-abuse-images-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JN5RZSMODVNQXBGFQ4VFFOZ7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New World Development reports $852 million first-half net loss]]></title><description><![CDATA[New World Development , one of the biggest property developers in Hong Kong, reported an interim net loss of HK$6.63 billion ($852.45 million) on Friday, following a prolonged property downturn and high interest costs.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/new-world-development-reports-852-million-first-half-net-loss-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PP7VGSMWKBL33FCCEDAG2SIBEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK chip parts supplier Morgan Advanced flags revenue hit as trade tariff woes hit demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Semiconductor parts supplier Morgan Advanced Materials on Friday forecast a drop in organic revenue this year due to uncertain demand, sparked, in part, by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff threats.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-chip-parts-supplier-morgan-advanced-flags-revenue-hit-trade-tariff-woes-hit-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TCXYJMUIVKEBC5PCM4KZ44QNU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Euro zone consumers lower near-term inflation expectations, ECB survey shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Euro zone consumers lowered their near-term inflation expectations last month but continued to see economic contraction ahead, indicating that households remain relatively downbeat on the bloc's prospects, an ECB survey showed on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/euro-zone-consumers-lower-near-term-inflation-expectations-ecb-survey-shows-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTIGZMP37RM55N3X64FRYFR47U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chinese mainland investors drive surge in Hong Kong stocks]]></title><description><![CDATA[China's mainland investors have played an unprecedented role in a rally on Hong Kong's equity market that has pushed the benchmark index to its highest level since 2022.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-mainland-investors-drive-surge-hong-kong-stocks-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FHJ7F2VVVRKHDKOJG5TWH5PMU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citi raises first-quarter average tin price forecast, sees easing in second quarter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citi Research raised its average tin price forecast for the first quarter of 2025 to $32,000 per metric ton from $29,000 on Friday but noted that prices will start easing from the second quarter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-raises-first-quarter-average-tin-price-forecast-sees-easing-second-quarter-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLXKOWOLUJMRHLWDY5SCV2FYH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citigroup mistakenly credits customer account with $81 trillion in "near miss", FT reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citigroup erroneously credited $81 trillion, instead of $280, to a customer's account and took hours to reverse the transaction, a "near miss" that shows up the bank's operational issues it has sought to fix, the Financial Times reported on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-mistakenly-credits-customer-account-with-81-trillion-near-miss-ft-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZQR55CGGJLVNLXK42ZJRGJXAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:52:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[British Airways owner IAG profit beats estimates, plans share buyback]]></title><description><![CDATA[British Airways owner IAG reported a 27% jump in annual operating profit on Friday, beating market expectations as it curbed costs and growth in its lucrative transatlantic routes took off.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/british-airways-owner-iags-annual-earnings-beat-expectations-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5ZV3SAGQRL2LOYK75CDJRDQBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡指控三人诈骗，媒体称与英伟达芯片有关]]></title><description><![CDATA[Singapore charged three men with fraud in a case domestic media have linked to the movement of Nvidia's advanced chips from the city state to Chinese artificial intelligence firm DeepSeek.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/singapore-charges-three-with-fraud-that-media-link-nvidia-chips-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LISWVWPYMRLXJNDYZUEJNQWBXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:57:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Car parts supplier Forvia forecasts 2025 sales at around last year level]]></title><description><![CDATA[French car parts supplier Forvia said on Friday it sees sales in 2025 at around last year's level, reflecting a downturn in European and North American automotive demand dragging into the new year.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/car-parts-supplier-forvia-forecasts-2025-sales-around-previous-year-level-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6RC753U2JKANPYCPV3SBQOBUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Chinese banks heed PBOC call to cut dollar deposit rates, say sources]]></title><description><![CDATA[China's banks are cutting the interest rates offered on U.S. dollar deposits after being asked to do so by the central bank, possibly to curtail dollar hoarding and also prop up a weakening yuan, sources said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-banks-heed-pboc-call-cut-dollar-deposit-rates-say-sources-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6NGMEO2OJPZRNXPLGP322KY6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bytedance's TikTok to invest $8.8 bln in Thailand data centres, official says]]></title><description><![CDATA[ByteDance's TikTok will invest $8.8 billion in data centres in Thailand over five years, Helena Lersch, TikTok's Vice President of Public Policy, said on Friday at an event in Bangkok.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bytedances-tiktok-invest-88-bln-thailand-data-centres-official-says-2025-02-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F5OVD43XJO6LPYHQTSJFGE4CI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 06:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>