<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:35:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:35:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官称，Tether 计划推出新的美国稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大稳定币的创造者Tether公司首席执行官保罗-阿多诺（Paolo Ardoino）周五表示，该公司计划推出一款专为美国居民设计的美国稳定币，名为USAT。【原文：Tether, the creator of the world's largest stablecoin, plans to launch a U.S.-based stablecoin designed for U.S. residents, called USAT, the company's CEO Paolo Ardoino said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/tether-plans-launch-new-us-stablecoin-ceo-says-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WHP2MJTXJMNHH5EC65BELYQLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大象象牙、别墅和沃霍尔肖像在阿玛尼的遗嘱中共享]]></title><description><![CDATA[已故意大利时装设计师乔治-阿玛尼（Giorgio Armani）在其遗嘱中遗赠了两根大象象牙、日本折叠屏风、一只青铜熊和一幅美国艺术家安迪-沃霍尔（Andy Warhol）的肖像画。【原文：Two elephant tusks, Japanese folding screens, a bronze bear and a portrait by American artist Andy Warhol are some of the more singular possessions bequeathed by late Italian fashion designer Giorgio Armani in his will.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/elephant-tusks-villas-warhol-portrait-shared-out-armanis-will-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRTO764Y2JPPRIQP6O7HBITVW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:48:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[主办中国贸易谈判，西班牙看到修复与美国关系的机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[几天前，华盛顿称西班牙阻碍向以色列出售武器的计划是 "为恐怖分子壮胆"，而西班牙则将在未来几天主办美国和中国之间的会谈视为修复与唐纳德-特朗普政府关系的机会。【原文：Spain sees hosting talks between the United States and China in the coming days as a chance to repair ties with Donald Trump's government, days after Washington described its plan to impede arms sales to Israel as "emboldening terrorists".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/spain-sees-chance-repair-ties-with-us-it-hosts-china-trade-talks-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUM66XK5NRKCVLPPIGJPCGP3HU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:46:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥官员将于下周就关税问题与中国会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-谢因鲍姆周五表示，墨西哥官员将于下周与中国代表就墨西哥计划对来自亚洲国家的商品加征关税一事进行会谈，并称加征关税并非胁迫措施。【原文：Mexican officials are set to speak with representatives from China next week about Mexico's planned tariffs on goods from the Asian country, President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Friday, saying the tariffs were not intended as a coercion measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexican-officials-speak-with-china-tariffs-next-week-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RM6T3LJXVRNJRFVOMIA5AJQYGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国敦促美国通过对话解决 TikTok 问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周五发表声明称，中方将依法依规审查围绕 TikTok 的问题，并敦促美方在相互尊重、平等协商的基础上，通过对话解决有关关切。【原文：China will review issues around TikTok in accordance with laws and regulations and urges the U.S. to resolve concerns through dialogue based on mutual respect and equal consultation, a Chinese commerce ministry statement said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-urges-us-address-tiktok-issue-through-dialogue-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3SAMW5VDBN7VK36EX2V3EM4SI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:17:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[密歇根大学调查显示：9 月美国消费者信心再次下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于消费者认为商业环境、劳动力市场和通货膨胀的风险上升，9月份美国消费者情绪连续第二个月下降。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment fell for a second straight month in September as consumers saw rising risks to business conditions, the labor market and inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-slips-again-september-university-michigan-survey-says-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4SBWSP6WJPYXF6EIHWWHLJCZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道：美国联邦贸易委员会就搜索广告行为调查谷歌和亚马逊]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，美国联邦贸易委员会正在调查亚马逊公司和 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司是否误导了在其网站上投放广告的广告商。【原文：The US Federal Trade Commission is investigating whether Amazon.com and Alphabet's Google misled advertisers that place ads on their websites, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-ftc-probes-google-amazon-over-search-advertising-practices-bloomberg-reports-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">253TGYAIZBNRBLIGM7MCUYOS2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:56:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国启动试点计划加速空中出租车部署]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府将于周五宣布一项新的试点计划，以加快飞行出租车的部署，因为各公司正在努力应对先进空中交通的监管障碍。【原文：The Trump administration is announcing a new pilot program on Friday to speed the deployment of flying air taxis as companies work to meet regulatory hurdles for advanced air mobility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-launching-pilot-program-speed-air-taxi-deployment-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPAVUZQHVJIEZEYBWECY6BCRAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:47:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融科技公司 Lendbuzz 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车贷款平台 Lendbuzz 周五提交了在美国首次公开募股的申请，这是最新一家准备在新股市场上市的金融科技公司。【原文：Auto loans platform Lendbuzz on Friday filed for an initial public offering in the U.S., the latest financial technology firm set to hit the new listings market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fintech-lendbuzz-files-us-ipo-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTUFQHCOHFJ4ZIUVB5Q2QUV6IE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:45:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金创下五周来最大单周流出记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 9 月 10 日的一周内，美国投资者抛售股票基金，在创纪录高位获利了结，并因对高估值以及中东和乌克兰地缘政治紧张局势的谨慎态度而削减了风险敞口。【原文：U.S. investors dumped equity funds in the week to September 10, booking profits at record highs and cutting exposure on caution over lofty valuations and geopolitical tensions in the Middle east and Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-record-biggest-weekly-outflow-five-weeks-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETY467VFIVJO3A7OEQW23UBJFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:41:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部呼吁七国集团和欧盟对中国和印度购买俄罗斯石油征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五呼吁七国集团和欧盟盟国对来自中国和印度的商品征收 "有意义的关税"，以停止购买俄罗斯石油，并召开七国集团财政会议，讨论加大对莫斯科施压以结束乌克兰战争的努力。【原文：The U.S. Treasury on Friday called on Group of Seven and European Union allies to impose "meaningful tariffs" on goods from China and India to halt their purchases of Russian oil and convened a G7 finance meeting to discuss efforts to step up pressure on Moscow to end its war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-treasury-calls-g7-eu-impose-tariffs-china-india-over-russian-oil-purchases-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGN2NQHW3JNXDFUAP7XGME6BMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:28:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行将于 9 月 17 日维持利率在 15%不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，在通胀压力居高不下的情况下，巴西央行将在 9 月 17 日的会议上维持 15%的关键利率不变。【原文：Brazil's central bank is set to keep its key rate unchanged at 15% in a meeting on September 17 amid persistently high inflation pressures, a Reuters poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/brazils-central-bank-keep-rates-unchanged-15-september-17-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3PIA7UATVIV3OAFCJS77RQDTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度瓦迪拉尔工业公司美国分公司将在当地生产冰淇淋以减少进口]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度瓦迪拉尔工业公司（Vadilal Industries）的一位高管周五表示，该公司在美国的子公司将于年底前开始在当地工厂生产冰淇淋，以减少对进口的依赖并促进销售。【原文：The U.S. subsidiary of India’s Vadilal Industries will start manufacturing ice cream at its local facility by the year-end to reduce dependence on imports and boost sales, an executive of the unit said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/indias-vadilal-industries-us-unit-make-ice-creams-locally-cut-imports-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NU4P6LWSEJM7PFGEPI4TB7TLWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金创下五周来首次单周资金外流记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 9 月 10 日，由于投资者锁定利润并减少风险敞口，全球股票基金出现了五周以来的首次单周资金外流。【原文：Global equity funds registered their first weekly outflow in five weeks through September 10 as investors locked in profits and trimmed their risk exposure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CPNFDYQRNJ3BOYONNBGSG43T4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乔治-阿玛尼基金会提出新任首席执行官人选，保留 30% 股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿玛尼执行委员会周五表示，2016 年成立的乔治-阿玛尼基金会（Giorgio Armani Foundation）将提出集团新任首席执行官的人选，该基金会是这位意大利设计师接班人的重要支柱。【原文：The Giorgio Armani foundation, set up in 2016 and the key pillar of the Italian designer's succession, will propose the name of the group's new CEO, Armani's executive committee said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/giorgio-armani-foundation-propose-new-ceo-keep-30-stake-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OR7SFL7AZP4DC4SRNLEKYZQLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:22:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼公司首席执行官与美国代表团会面以加强能源关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃尼公司首席执行官克劳迪奥-德斯卡尔齐（Claudio Descalzi）周五会见了美国能源部长和内政部长，华盛顿正努力达成能源供应协议，希望借此加强其在该地区的影响力，同时削弱俄罗斯的影响力。【原文：Eni's Chief Executive Claudio Descalzi met the U.S. energy and interior secretaries on Friday as Washington pushes to seal energy supply deals that it hopes will strengthen its influence in the region while weakening Russia's.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eni-ceo-us-delegation-meet-bolster-energy-ties-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6W2VFDBXNNI5RFO4EB4ENY57XM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行将于 9 月 17 日降息，今年至少再降息一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，由于劳动力市场恶化和经济活动疲软，大多数经济学家预计加拿大央行将于9月17日将隔夜利率下调四分之一个百分点。【原文：The Bank of Canada will cut its overnight rate by a quarter point on September 17 as the labour market deteriorates and economic activity weakens, according to most economists in a Reuters poll, who also expect at least one more cut next quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-cut-rates-september-17-least-one-more-follow-this-year-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JK7XGGFPRVK5XDGGOWUXQBWNEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：乔治-阿玛尼之后的阿玛尼：其遗嘱的关键细节]]></title><description><![CDATA[乔治-阿玛尼（Giorgio Armani）上周去世，享年 91 岁，他指示继承人逐步出售他在长达 50 年的职业生涯中建立起来的帝国，令时尚界大吃一惊。【原文：Giorgio Armani, who died last week aged 91, surprised the fashion world by instructing his heirs to gradually sell the empire he had set up in his 50-year long career.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/armani-after-giorgio-armani-key-details-his-will-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B22UYC2ALVLXNKTHP7CNF2NLQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:01:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：贡渥集团将贵金属业务扩展至实物交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球大宗商品贸易公司贡渥集团（GGL.UL）告诉路透社，该公司正在将其贵金属业务从衍生品交易扩展到实物金属交易，并已在伦敦和新加坡交易中心聘请了专家。【原文：Global commodity trading house Gunvor (GGL.UL) is expanding its precious metals business from trading derivatives into physical metal and has hired specialists in the London and Singapore trading hubs, the company told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gunvor-expands-precious-metals-business-into-physical-trading-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBEL24DPVBNN3DTEKA7UWBQ22E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于美国合作伙伴克罗格重新考虑仓库战略，Ocado 股价暴跌 13]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国合作伙伴克罗格公司（Kroger）表示可能放弃对自动化仓库的投资后，在线超市和技术集团 Ocado 的股价周五大幅下跌。【原文：Shares in Ocado , the online supermarket and technology group, fell sharply on Friday after U.S. partner Kroger signalled a potential retreat from investment in automated warehouses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ocado-shares-plunge-13-us-partner-kroger-rethinks-warehouse-strategy-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNNYXNOODRPCLBE4SQY3MP4Z3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:59:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国能源部长称欧盟可能在一年内退出俄罗斯天然气市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）周五告诉路透社记者，欧盟可能在六到十二个月内逐步淘汰俄罗斯天然气，代之以美国液化天然气，美国本周已向欧盟官员传达了这一立场。【原文：The European Union could phase out Russian gas within six to 12 months by replacing it with U.S. liquefied natural gas, and the United States communicated this position to EU officials this week, U.S. energy secretary Chris Wright told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/eu-could-quit-russian-gas-within-year-us-energy-chief-says-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6ZS2KWHJJMIVMIK66KGCGZHKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利预计美联储将在 2025 年的三次会议上全部降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）周五表示，预计美国联邦储备委员会将在今年的三次会议上全部降息，此前的数据显示，8月份美国消费者物价增幅为七个月来最大。【原文：Morgan Stanley said on Friday it expects the U.S. Federal Reserve to cut interest rates in all three of its meetings this year, after data showed U.S. consumer prices increased by the most in seven months in August.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/morgan-stanley-expects-fed-cut-rates-all-three-meetings-2025-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6SXB6NQGRIJZLJR7FU5PK2B2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:59:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 降息在即，投资者寻求美联储对不稳定劳动力市场的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者将期待美联储在下周的会议上传达其对美国劳动力市场疲软的担忧，他们预计该央行将在九个月来首次降息，以支撑就业。【原文：Investors will look for the Federal Reserve to communicate how worried it is about the flagging U.S. labor market at its meeting next week and they expect the central bank to cut interest rates for the first time in nine months to shore up employment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-seek-feds-view-shaky-labor-market-rate-cut-looms-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWI5ADJHNVNTHC2VCCBXBK3RBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:10:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国央行将加强对银行间跨境人民币融资的监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行周五表示，计划加强对银行间跨境人民币融资的监管，并促进人民币的离岸使用。【原文：China's central bank said on Friday it plans to better regulate cross-border yuan financing between banks, and promote offshore use of the Chinese currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/china-central-bank-better-regulate-cross-border-yuan-financing-between-banks-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDH5Z3NQTVL4JHTXNVOUCHPJ2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯沃琪出售手表，嘲讽特朗普对瑞士征收 39% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士钟表制造商斯沃琪公司开始销售一款表面数字3和9颠倒的特别版手表，这是对唐纳德-特朗普总统上个月对美国从瑞士进口商品征收39%关税的一种戏弄。【原文：Swiss watchmaker Swatch has begun selling a special edition watch with the numbers three and nine reversed on its face in a play on the 39% tariffs President Donald Trump imposed on U.S. imports from Switzerland last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swatch-sells-watch-lampooning-trumps-39-tariffs-switzerland-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYDH7XNHPZKK7KTST7GXW4LQUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:07:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货小幅回落，指数将实现周线上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国三大股指在上一交易日创下历史新高后，华尔街期货周五表现低迷，一周来的经济数据并未缓和美联储降息的预期。【原文：Wall Street futures were subdued on Friday after the three main U.S. indexes hit record highs in the previous session, packing up a week of economic data that did not temper expectations of interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-ease-slightly-indexes-set-weekly-gains-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XY3QVCZ2BBP53BNKCTEDG53BVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街为货币市场季度末流动性压力做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[近几个月来，美国国债发行量激增，减少了金融业的流动性，加剧了投资者对资金市场可能在 9 月份面临挤压的担忧。【原文：A surge in U.S. Treasury bill issuance in recent months has reduced liquidity in the financial sector, stoking investor concerns that funding markets could face a September squeeze.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-braces-quarter-end-liquidity-stress-money-markets-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SC2P7OQAE5MK3P2KZFIZIJRSPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Kenvue公司首席执行官游说小肯尼迪不要将泰诺列为自闭症病因]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引一位熟悉此事的人士的话称，Kenvue 公司临时首席执行官柯克-佩里（Kirk Perry）与小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：Kenvue's interim CEO Kirk Perry met Robert F. Kennedy Jr. to try and dissuade him from listing Tylenol as a potential cause of autism in an upcoming report, the Wall Street Journal said on Friday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kenvue-ceo-lobbied-rfk-jr-not-cite-tylenol-autism-cause-wsj-reports-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMVADS5FDRPLPLMULJHWJVZQAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的恐惧指数可能指向停滞而非滞胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储官员已预计将于下周降息，在最近的数据显示雇佣长期疲软和通胀担忧缓解之后，他们也可能更接近于解决长达数月之久的关于滞胀风险的争论。【原文：Federal Reserve officials, already expected to cut interest rates next week, may also be closer to settling a months-long debate over the risks of stagflation after recent data showed longstanding weakness in hiring and easing inflation concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-fear-meter-may-be-pointing-stagnation-rather-than-stagflation-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7JFXTKNIJIHPB3I6FGURQ4PNU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因转向助力装置可能失灵，中国新鹏将召回 47490 辆 P7+ 电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周五发表声明称，由于转向助力装置可能失灵，中国电动汽车制造商新鹏将从9月15日起召回47490辆P7+电动轿车。【原文：Chinese electric carmaker Xpeng will recall 47,490 P7+ electric sedans from Sept. 15 due to a potential steering assist failure, the Chinese market regulator said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-xpeng-recall-47490-p7-electric-cars-over-potential-steering-assist-2025-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NDVNDYPWNIMROIM4NAZ5BQC2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:40:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>