<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 18:05:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 18:05:37 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院驳回对 FCC 批准 SpaceX 卫星的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周五维持了联邦通信委员会的决定，批准 SpaceX 部署数千颗 Starlink 卫星以提供天基宽带互联网服务的计划。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Friday upheld the decision of the Federal Communications Commission to approve a SpaceX plan to deploy thousands of Starlink satellites to provide space-based broadband internet service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-court-rejects-challenges-fcc-approval-spacex-satellites-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3PIV4DZBVPUJOGPITCISGYZXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:55:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，Arbor Realty 因贷款行为受到美国司法部调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，Arbor Realty Trust 正在接受纽约联邦检察官和联邦调查局的调查，几个月前做空者曾对该贷款公司的做法和信息披露进行过攻击。【原文：Arbor Realty Trust is being probed by Federal prosecutors and the Federal Bureau of Investigation in New York months after short sellers attacked the lender's practices and disclosures, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/arbor-realty-being-probed-by-us-doj-over-loan-practices-bloomberg-reports-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGPYFKUL7FPMFI355WEERB35M4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:40:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行业高管权衡宏观经济风险和美联储加息路径]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国顶级银行的高管们在报告喜忧参半的第二季度业绩时，对美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）未来的降息路径仍存在分歧，并指出消费者健康状况恶化。【原文：Executives from top U.S. banks remained divided over the U.S. Federal Reserve's future path on interest rate cuts and flagged deterioration in consumer health when they reported mixed second-quarter results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-banking-execs-weigh-macroeconomic-risks-feds-interest-rate-path-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDOPMQ33TZJVJOHETCVRSMHGEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利部长称欧洲央行逼迫裕信银行退出俄罗斯太过分了]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利外交部长安东尼奥-塔亚尼（Antonio Tajani）周五表示，欧洲中央银行在推动意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）退出俄罗斯市场方面做得太过分了。【原文：The European Central Bank has overreached in pushing Italian bank UniCredit to get out of Russia, Italy's Foreign Minister Antonio Tajani said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecb-has-gone-too-far-pushing-unicredit-quit-russia-italy-minister-says-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJBXQQ5ETNJW7J47HBRWY72NNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织称新兴市场资本流入量恢复至 2018 年水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周五表示，去年流入除中国以外的新兴市场的资本总额增至1100亿美元，占其经济产出的0.6%，为2018年以来的最高水平。【原文：The International Monetary Fund on Friday said gross capital inflows into emerging markets excluding China last year rose to $110 billion or 0.6% of their economic output, the highest level since 2018.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-says-emerging-market-capital-inflows-recover-2018-levels-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FV4IECG5ZRO5XHOZQC3RIPWS3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街银行投资银行业务有所改善，但仍需谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街银行周五公布的季度财报显示，交易渠道更加畅通，投资银行业务活动跃升，但同时也提到了一些不利因素和谨慎行事的理由。【原文：Wall Street banks reported a healthier pipeline for deals and a jump in investment banking activity in quarterly earnings on Friday, but also cited some headwinds and reasons for caution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-banks-see-investment-banking-improvement-with-some-caution-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQWOG7PAUJOCJFWH66M7P3EYIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，Bunge和Viterra提出出售在两个欧盟国家的资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据直接知情人士周五透露，美国谷物商邦吉（Bunge）和嘉能可（Glencore）支持的维特拉公司（Viterra）已提出出售在两个欧盟国家的资产，以争取获得欧盟反垄断机构对其340亿美元合并案的批准。【原文：U.S. grains merchant Bunge and Glencore-backed Viterra have offered to sell assets in two European Union countries in a bid to secure EU antitrust clearance for their $34 billion merger, people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bunge-viterra-offer-sell-assets-2-eu-countries-sources-say-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNDMYXC4BBM5NBG4KRQGL37GPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团寻求结束因 ATM 收费引发的种族偏见诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团要求美国法官驳回一项种族歧视诉讼，该诉讼称花旗银行免除少数族裔银行客户的 ATM 费用违反了联邦民权法。【原文：Citigroup asked a U.S. judge to dismiss a racial-discrimination lawsuit that claims the bank violated federal civil rights law by waiving ATM fees for customers of minority-owned banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/citigroup-seeks-end-racial-bias-lawsuit-over-atm-fees-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKVZJSWC6VMDRLCFGQB7T2LYGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 15:44:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[道指在大盘反弹中创下历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[道琼斯工业平均指数（Dow Jones Industrial Average）周五盘中创下历史新高，在近期广泛的市场涨势中追赶其他两个美国主要指数。【原文：The Dow Jones Industrial Average scaled an intraday record high on Friday, playing catch-up with two other main U.S. indexes in recent broad-based market gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/dow-hits-all-time-high-broader-market-rally-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYHK6Q6GJJNPRLKABWLSUV3SJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 15:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，德国将在欧盟对中国电动汽车征收关税的投票中投弃权票]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士周五告诉路透社，德国将在周一欧盟成员国对中国电动汽车征收临时关税的投票中投弃权票。【原文：Germany is set to abstain in Monday's vote by European Union member states on imposing provisional tariffs on Chinese electric vehicles, sources told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/germany-set-abstain-vote-eu-tariffs-chinese-evs-sources-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WM5V7ZCBXNJZZIS35BIJC5TBYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 15:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月消费者信心下滑；通胀预期改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，7月份美国消费者情绪回落，但对未来一年及以后的通胀预期有所改善。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment ebbed in July, but inflation expectations over the next year and beyond improved, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-ebbs-july-inflation-expectations-improve-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEIKMCE7GRIKPIWKVHFL4KHK3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定亚马逊必须服从美国机构的怀孕偏见调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦法官已下令亚马逊公司遵守美国民权机构的传票，该机构正在调查关于该在线零售商歧视怀孕仓库工人的指控。【原文：A New York federal judge has ordered Amazon.com to comply with a subpoena from a U.S. civil rights agency investigating claims that the online retailer discriminated against pregnant warehouse workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/amazon-must-comply-with-us-agencys-pregnancy-bias-probe-judge-rules-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OY4F5W4LQRKCJPG2FNMRFR45J4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奖杯资产：欧洲杯和美洲杯夺冠提振股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日英格兰对阵西班牙的 2024 年欧洲杯决赛以及阿根廷对阵哥伦比亚的美洲杯对决看起来都很激烈，但历史表明，有一样东西通常会胜出，那就是获胜方的股票市场。【原文：Sunday's Euro 2024 final between England and Spain and the Copa America showdown between Argentina and Colombia both look like being tight affairs - but history shows there is one thing that usually comes out on top - the winning side's stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trophy-assets-euros-copa-wins-lift-stock-markets-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GSRUG3UPRKSLEWA5GLFD3LARY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:33:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金在财报公布前因谨慎而出现资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 7 月 10 日的七天内，美国股票基金面临三周以来的首次单周资金外流，原因是在新一轮财报季到来之前，谨慎情绪和获利回吐占据上风。【原文：U.S. equity funds faced their first weekly outflow in three weeks in the seven days to July 10 as caution and profit-taking took hold ahead of the new earnings season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-outflows-caution-ahead-earnings-reports-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XS55OXBCD5K3JLCLCGZCVHPLRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：空客在产量困境后启动新一轮成本削减行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内消息人士援引一份给员工的备忘录称，在最近削减飞机生产目标之后，空中客车公司已经启动了一项绩效改进计划，包括削减成本和冻结其飞机制造业务的整体员工人数。【原文：Airbus has launched a performance improvement plan including cost cuts and a freeze on overall headcount in its planemaking business, after recent cuts in targets for aircraft production, industry sources said, citing a memo to staff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-launches-new-cost-cutting-drive-after-output-woes-sources-say-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TY6J7FMJGZIZHFMTOXIDDIJ2KU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:54:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月生产者价格温和上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国生产者价格在 6 月份温和上涨，进一步证实通胀已恢复下降趋势，并加强了 9 月份降息的理由。【原文：U.S. producer prices increased moderately in June, further confirmation that inflation had resumed its downward trend and strengthening the case for a September interest rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-producer-prices-rise-moderately-june-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THMPSCR4AJPQ3O3AF5K54ZIUWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:46:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资银行业务激增，服务业表现强劲，花旗利润攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团第二季度利润增长，主要得益于投资银行业务收入跃升 60% 以及服务部门的收益，这使得该银行股价在收盘前上涨了 2%。【原文：Citigroup's profit rose in the second quarter, boosted by a 60% jump in investment banking revenue and gains in its services division, sending the bank's shares up 2% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-profit-climbs-investment-banking-surge-services-strength-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7FAPMLIHFIIDLJ26AORVVL6OU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称施普林格和 KKR 考虑分拆德国媒体巨头]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国媒体巨头阿克塞尔-施普林格（Axel Springer）旗下拥有德国著名的《图片报》（Bild）和政治新闻公司 Politico，该公司正考虑与私募股权投资集团 KKR 共同拆分公司，两位熟悉此事的消息人士周五告诉路透社。【原文：German media giant Axel Springer, which owns Germany's popular Bild tabloid and political news company Politico, is considering a split of the company together with private equity group KKR , two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/springer-kkr-considering-split-german-media-giant-sources-say-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBVEUACLZBMUJLZLW4UP2RZFZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:47:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合利华将裁减欧洲三分之一的办公室职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华计划在 2025 年底之前削减欧洲三分之一的办公室职位，作为首席执行官推动这家陷入困境的消费品巨头恢复增长的一部分。【原文：Unilever plans to cut a third of all office roles in Europe by the end of 2025 as a part of a push by the CEO to revive growth at the struggling consumer goods giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-cut-third-office-jobs-europe-ft-reports-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JO5RHQ6SXVMVPOPUXT5P6S3JC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电话电报公司称约 1.09 亿个美国用户账户的数据被非法下载]]></title><description><![CDATA[AT&amp;T 周五表示，大约 1.09 亿个客户账户中包含 2022 年通话和短信记录的数据在 4 月份被非法下载。【原文：AT&amp;T said Friday that data from about 109 million customer accounts containing records of calls and texts from 2022 was illegally downloaded in April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/att-says-data-around-109-mln-us-customer-accounts-illegally-downloaded-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZMIKHZAVZLWRO6SASRFYEQ5QI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷通胀降至个位数，居民仍持怀疑态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷人表示，他们尚未感受到通胀降温带来的好处，分析师预测，6 月份的官方数据将于周五公布，届时连续五个月的通胀降温可能会结束。【原文：Argentines say they are yet to feel the benefits of cooling inflation and analysts predict the five-month streak could end when official figures for June are released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/argentine-inflation-cools-single-digits-residents-are-still-skeptical-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWXQ7CAHMRPU7O6RQUPK7BOWX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康菲石油公司和马拉松石油公司就 225 亿美元交易第二次收到美国联邦贸易委员会的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的独立石油生产商康菲石油公司（ConocoPhillips）周五表示，该公司收到了美国联邦贸易委员会的第二份请求，要求其提供有关拟收购竞争对手马拉松石油公司（Marathon Oil）的信息。【原文：Top U.S. independent oil producer ConocoPhillips said on Friday it received a second request from the U.S. Federal Trade Commission for information on its proposed acquisition of rival Marathon Oil .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/conocophillips-marathon-oil-get-second-us-ftc-request-over-225-bln-deal-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5V2SIIISFMN5E6XCENPDDIK7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:04:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行利润因存款成本而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）周五表示，该公司第二季度利润下降，原因是在争夺客户资金的激烈竞争中，该银行为留住存款付出了更多成本。【原文：Wells Fargo's second-quarter profit declined as the lender shelled out more to hold on to deposits amid intense competition for customers' money, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-profit-falls-deposit-costs-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYMZXN2F5VJZZIFRAOIAJWOXNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通因投资银行业务费用增加和会计收益而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通第二季度利润增长，主要得益于投资银行业务费用的增加，以及与 Visa 的换股交易带来的 80 亿美元会计收益。【原文：JPMorgan Chase's profit rose in the second quarter, buoyed by rising investment banking fees and an $8 billion accounting gain from a share exchange deal with Visa.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-profit-jumps-higher-investment-banking-fees-accounting-gain-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSA5L3VPAJK67NSJ7L7YPRWSWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:52:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球债券基金因预期降息而大量流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至7月10日的七天里，全球债务基金连续第29周吸引资金流入，原因是在劳动力市场状况疲软、通胀水平放缓的情况下，市场预期美联储将降息。【原文：Global debt funds attracted inflows for a 29th straight week in the seven days to July 10 on expectations of a Federal Reserve rate cut amid weakening labour market conditions and easing inflation levels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAZVREWQBVMT7N47ITIK2SR6HU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资服务费增加，纽约银行季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，纽约银行公布第二季度净利润增长 10%，原因是投资服务费的增长足以抵消这家全球最大托管银行较低的利息收入。【原文：BNY posted a 10% rise in second-quarter net profit on Friday, as higher investment service fees more than offset the world's largest custodian bank's lower interest income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-quarterly-profit-rises-investment-service-fee-boost-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXKLXFIIGFIMBOOIOSVCBO26JM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:43:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空下调 2024 年利润目标，因收益率低而削减开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汉莎航空公司（Deutsche Lufthansa）周五下调了今年的盈利预期，并表示将实施一项影响深远的增效计划，理由是亚洲的低收益率和国内的运营问题。【原文：German airline group Deutsche Lufthansa on Friday slashed its earnings guidance for the year and said it would have a far-reaching efficiency programme, citing low yields in Asia and problems in operations at home.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lufthansa-cuts-2024-earnings-target-low-yields-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QGU2PLVX5O63KRDGI55P6LSVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克里姆林宫称，一些北约成员国允许基辅用武器打击俄罗斯的举动是危险的升级]]></title><description><![CDATA[克里姆林宫周五表示，它注意到一些西方国家在本周的北约峰会上发表声明，允许基辅使用它们提供的武器打击俄罗斯领土，克里姆林宫称此举是危险的升级。【原文：The Kremlin said on Friday that it had noted some Western countries' statements at this week's NATO summit permitting Kyiv to use arms they had supplied to strike Russian territory in a move it called a dangerous escalation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/move-by-some-nato-members-let-kyiv-strike-russia-with-their-arms-is-dangerous-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XB2FAKQOCRI7NGYTWRRJIPAL2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因欧佩克+、制裁和需求担忧，石油自2022年以来窄幅震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[自 2022 年末以来，布伦特原油一直在每桶 75 美元至 90 美元的狭窄区间内交易，原因是欧佩克+的减产措施维持了油价的底线，而可观的剩余产能、需求的不确定性和制裁政策阻碍了市场的突破性上涨。【原文：Brent crude oil has been trading in a tight range of $75-$90 a barrel since late 2022 as OPEC+ cuts keep a floor under prices while sizeable spare capacity, demand uncertainty and sanctions policy prevent the market breaking higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-trades-narrow-range-since-2022-opec-sanctions-demand-worries-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNDOOWFLI5MCREVT4SNFYQTZOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:26:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邦吉（Bunge）和维泰拉（Viterra）在寻求欧盟批准 340 亿美元交易时作出让步]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会网站周五发布的最新消息显示，美国谷物商邦吉（Bunge）和嘉能可（Glencore）支持的维特拉公司（Viterra）已做出让步，试图为其价值340亿美元的合并案赢得欧盟反垄断批准。【原文：U.S. grains merchant Bunge and Glencore-backed Viterra have offered concessions in an attempt to win EU antitrust approval for their $34 billion merger, an update on the European Commission website showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bunge-viterra-offer-concessions-they-seek-eu-okay-34-bln-deal-2024-07-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">473QDQJ6BBLNNIL5TAXWDH5I6Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:20:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>