<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:34:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:34:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行行长宣布圣诞节前再减息两次，2025 年再减息两次]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰央行行长阿德里安-奥尔（Adrian Orr）周五提出了在年底前再降息50个基点的明确前景，并表示 "我很乐意实现这一目标"，他的明确评论为果断的宽松政策指明了方向。【原文：New Zealand’s central bank governor Adrian Orr on Friday raised the distinct prospect of cutting rates another 50 basis points by year-end, saying "I would love to be delivering that" in explicit comments setting the course for decisive policy easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/nz-central-bank-chief-flags-two-mores-cuts-by-christmas-more-2025-2024-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FU4YPWDFLFJEXNFA4FQSWAKZ7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 03:53:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 在法庭上诉中质疑美国对华关系的说法]]></title><description><![CDATA[TikTok 周四向联邦上诉法院表示，美国司法部错误陈述了该社交媒体应用与中国的关系，敦促法院推翻要求中国字节跳动公司出售 TikTok 美国资产或面临禁令的法律。【原文：TikTok told a federal appeals court on Thursday that the U.S. Department of Justice has misstated the social media app's ties to China, urging the court to overturn a law requiring China-based ByteDance to sell TikTok's U.S. assets or face a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tiktok-disputes-us-claims-china-ties-court-appeal-2024-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQBHMBOXYNNF3F4CYHFO5VSD6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济增长担忧消退，日本股市迎来四年来最佳一周]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于华尔街蔓延出乐观的风险情绪，亚洲股市迎来周线上涨，日本基准日经指数有望创下四年多来最好的一周，而美元和美国国债收益率则基本持稳。【原文：Asia shares were headed for a weekly gain on Friday and Japan's benchmark Nikkei was poised for its best week in over four years as upbeat risk sentiment spilled over from Wall Street, while the dollar and U.S. Treasury yields held broadly steady.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1pix-2024-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFCW2Z2JIVIGBCVMDMCXDKBCYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:38:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[盈利超预期后，JD.com 股价将上涨 6.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电子商务集团京东在香港上市，周五其股价将大涨 6.5%，此前该公司公布了超预期的季度利润报告，降价吸引了对成本敏感的消费者进入其平台。【原文：The Hong Kong-listed shares of Chinese e-commerce group JD.com were set to jump 6.5% on Friday after it reported forecast-beating quarterly profits, helped by price cuts that lured cost-conscious consumers to its platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/jdcom-shares-set-rise-65-after-earnings-beat-forecasts-2024-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HF2XOMEQQNMPDLIX2IUSRUHJHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:26:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经济重燃热情，油价将实现周度上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚市早盘，油价走低，但在乐观的美国经济数据缓解了投资者对头号石油消费国潜在衰退的担忧之后，市场基准油价将连续第二周上涨。【原文：Oil prices edged lower in early Asian trading on Friday, but the market's benchmarks were set for a second consecutive weekly gain after upbeat U.S. economic data eased investor worries about a potential recession in the top oil consuming nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-set-weekly-gains-renewed-enthusiasm-around-us-economy-2024-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZ4HI7PCJJKCXMKODRWJWEOQIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国数据平息经济衰退担忧后美元坚挺]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国经济数据强劲，几乎消除了人们对经济衰退的担忧，美元兑日元汇率在创下四周来最大单日涨幅后徘徊在两周高点附近。【原文：The dollar hovered near a two-week high to the yen after its biggest one-day gain against major peers in four weeks as firm U.S. economic data all but eliminated fears about a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-firm-after-us-data-quells-recession-fears-2024-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JU7BCE2M2ZIEVD2XB7LH636UCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡 7 月出口同比增长 15.7%，增幅高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，新加坡7月份非石油国内出口同比增长15.7%，其中电子产品和非电子产品出口均有增长。【原文：Singapore's non-oil domestic exports rose 15.7% in July from a year earlier, data on Friday showed, with both electronics and non-electronics exports growing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/singapores-july-exports-rise-157-yy-stronger-than-forecast-2024-08-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5I54KCQXGJKETOW7RWQZF5ROHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:33:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政治不确定性可能促使日本央行暂停而非结束加息路径]]></title><description><![CDATA[首相岸田文雄的下台决定所带来的政治不确定性很可能会导致日本央行从接近零的水平稳步提高利率的计划暂停，而不是完全停止。【原文：The political uncertainty left by Prime Minister Fumio Kishida's decision to step down will likely lead to a pause, rather than a full stop, to the Bank of Japan's plan to raise interest rates steadily from near-zero levels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/political-uncertainty-may-prod-boj-pause-not-end-rate-hike-path-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SL3BK4V43RNPBLMQJIEV2ZBRNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:26:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行第三季度现金收益下降近 8]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行周五报告称，受住房贷款市场竞争加剧和运营费用增加的影响，该行第三季度现金收益下降了8%。【原文：National Australia Bank reported as much as 8% drop in its cash earnings for the third-quarter on Friday, hurt by rising competition in the housing loan market and higher operational expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/national-australia-bank-third-quarter-cash-earnings-drop-nearly-8-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJ4Y62WVMVI3TKAJJQMOBUC23A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:22:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州旨在通过要求储备汽油来解决油泵油价暴涨问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州州长加文-纽森（Gavin Newsom）周四提出一项计划，要求炼油厂保持最低限度的汽油储备，以防止价格飙升。【原文：California Governor Gavin Newsom proposed a plan on Thursday requiring oil refiners to maintain minimum reserves of gasoline in an effort to prevent price spikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/california-aims-tackle-pump-spikes-by-requiring-gas-reserves-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5SYUBM66JKT7EX7ZLE5UFBLZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格计划在 Albertsons 合并结束后降价 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[连锁超市克罗格（Kroger）公司发言人周四表示，该公司计划在与规模较小的竞争对手阿尔伯森（Albertsons）完成拟议的 250 亿美元合并后，将杂货价格降低 10 亿美元。【原文：Supermarket chain Kroger plans to lower grocery prices by $1 billion after the completion of its proposed $25 billion merger with smaller rival Albertsons , a company spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kroger-plans-lower-prices-by-1-bln-after-albertsons-merger-closes-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3D7SOXYIW5NEPB34N74DVZDVA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[收益令人失望，Stellantis 股东在美国起诉汽车制造商]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis在美国遭到股东起诉，称这家欧美汽车制造商在公布令人失望的收益导致股价下跌之前，隐瞒了库存增加和其他弱点，欺骗了他们。【原文：Stellantis has been sued by shareholders in the United States who said the European-American automaker defrauded them by concealing rising inventories and other weakness, before posting disappointing earnings that caused its stock price to fall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/stellantis-shareholders-sue-automaker-us-after-disappointing-earnings-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCJTH5WA2FNLZLPVQJLXTJQV34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:43:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，巴西央行联合提名人中有卢拉看中的加里波洛]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）正考虑一次性提交他即将提名的央行董事会所有四名成员人选，其中包括加布里埃尔-加里波洛（Gabriel Galipolo）的央行总裁职位。【原文：Brazil's President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva is looking at submitting all four of his upcoming nominations for the board of the central bank at once, including Gabriel Galipolo for the bank's presidency, people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/lula-eyes-galipolo-among-joint-nominations-brazil-central-bank-sources-say-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVHGA2BO5FIQRIP52FHNJ2NWWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:56:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席鲍威尔将主持下周杰克逊霍尔会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔定于下周五就经济前景发表讲话，这是堪萨斯城联储在怀俄明州杰克逊霍尔举行的年度经济研讨会的第一个全天。
全球央行行长的年度聚会让鲍威尔有机会对美国经济轨迹和货币政策前景做出最新评估，这也是美联储和堪萨斯城联储之间的一次重要会议。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell is scheduled to deliver remarks on the economic outlook next Friday, the first full day of the Kansas City Fed's annual economic symposium in Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
The annual gathering of global central bankers offers Powell a chance to give an updated assessment of the U.S. economic trajectory and the outlook for monetary policy, midway between the central ban】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-chair-powell-give-economic-outlook-aug-23-jackson-hole-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6QOXAMQ2FOFRCZCEXEIH6TOSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:41:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，巴西总统卢拉将在两周内提名加里波洛为新任央行行长]]></title><description><![CDATA[据巴西当地电视台 Globo News 周四报道，巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦将在两周内提名现任央行行长加布里埃尔-加里波洛（Gabriel Galipolo）担任巴西货币管理局的新局长。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva will nominate current central bank director Gabriel Galipolo to be the monetary authority's new chief in two weeks, local TV station Globo News reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/brazils-lula-nominate-galipolo-new-cenbank-chief-two-weeks-local-media-reports-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXFIUAI6FBNL5FI235GM63HG4U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[应用材料公司预计季度收入高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[应用材料公司（Applied Materials）周四预测第四季度营收将高于华尔街预期，预计人工智能将推动对其芯片制造设备的需求激增。【原文：Applied Materials forecast fourth-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, anticipating a surge in AI-fueled demand for its chip-making equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/applied-materials-forecasts-fourth-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NK6YVVOF25LVTBSLVJ3JLPLMJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联航首席执行官在会见新老板奥特伯格后表示对波音公司充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）首席执行官斯科特-柯比（Scott Kirby）周四在与波音公司新任最高负责人凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）会面后，预测波音公司的复苏将 "快于大多数人的预期"。【原文：United Airlines CEO Scott Kirby on Thursday predicted Boeing's recovery to be "faster than most expect" after meeting with the planemaker's new top boss, Kelly Ortberg.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-ceo-expresses-confidence-boeing-after-meeting-new-boss-ortberg-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4QDFW7XRVN3JBIG6C5TWJRWQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 19:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济数据向好，美国企业债券利差回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在近期强劲的经济数据增加了人们对降息的希望并平息了对经济衰退的担忧之后，美国公司债券利差（公司为债务支付的相对于国债的溢价）开始收复一些失地。【原文：U.S. corporate bond spreads, the premium over Treasuries that companies pay for debt, are starting to recoup some lost ground after recent strong economic data increased hopes for interest rate cuts and calmed recession fears.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-corporate-bond-spreads-recover-promising-economic-data-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXZ2E65A6RMSHFLJQIVWX6BWIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜耳公司在美国反 "驱集 "致癌诉讼案中获胜]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜耳公司（Bayer）在争取限制其 "Roundup 除草剂 "致癌责任的斗争中取得了法律上的胜利，美国一家上诉法院周四表示，联邦法律保护这家德国公司免受宾夕法尼亚州一名园艺师的起诉。【原文：Bayer won a legal victory in its fight to limit liability from claims that its Roundup weed killer causes cancer, as a U.S. appeals court on Thursday said federal law shields the German company from a lawsuit by a Pennsylvania landscaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/bayer-wins-victory-us-legal-battle-against-roundup-cancer-claims-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJCLTL3V2JI23NXAUUSBVTL56U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大驳回 CN Rail 就劳资纠纷提出的具有约束力的仲裁请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大劳工部长发言人周四表示，加拿大劳工部长史蒂文-麦金农（Steven MacKinnon）拒绝了 CN Rail 就与卡车司机工会的劳资纠纷提起具有约束力的仲裁的请求。【原文：Canadian Labour Minister Steven MacKinnon has rejected a request by CN Rail to initiate binding arbitration in a labor dispute with the Teamsters union, a spokesman for the minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/canada-rejects-cn-rails-request-binding-arbitration-labor-dispute-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFKA5VZPAJNWDNPHTQP57CA2TM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[基于摇头丸的创伤后应激障碍药物在 FDA 遭到挫折后，Lykos 将裁员 75]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lykos Therapeutics 公司在美国食品药品管理局拒绝批准其基于亚甲二氧基甲基安非他明（MDMA）的创伤后应激障碍治疗方案几天后，于本周四表示将裁员 75%，并启动一些高管变动。【原文：Lykos Therapeutics said on Thursday it would reduce its workforce by 75% and initiate some executive changes, days after the U.S. Food and Drug Administration declined approval for its MDMA-based treatment for post-traumatic stress disorder.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lykos-cuts-workforce-by-75-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57EZYA2665O55OEVVEGPW26FT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德公司将斥资 4.5 亿美元收购卫星产品制造商 Terran 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司（Lockheed Martin）周四同意以 4.5 亿美元的价格收购卫星产品制造商 Terran Orbital 公司。【原文：Lockheed Martin on Thursday agreed to acquire satellite products maker Terran Orbital in a $450 million deal, months after the defense contractor withdrew it previous bid to take it private.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/lockheed-buy-satellite-products-maker-terran-450-mln-deal-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJBPLBKGIFIBNGZHI7QME2VNMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 因非法向中国实体运输零部件与美国达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球电子公司 TE Connectivity 已同意支付 580 万美元，与美国商务部达成和解，原因是该公司非法向与中国高超音速、无人机和军事电子项目有关的各方运送物品。【原文：Global electronics company TE Connectivity has agreed to pay $5.8 million to settle with the U.S. Department of Commerce for illegally shipping items to parties tied to Chinese hypersonics, drone and military electronics programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/te-connectivity-settles-with-us-illegally-shipping-components-chinese-entities-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VLB5M2HWZP3ZA3ASVFDQFDSZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，埃德加-布朗夫曼准备竞购派拉蒙母公司 National Amusements]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，前华纳音乐董事长小埃德加-布朗夫曼正准备竞购派拉蒙全球公司的家族企业 National Amusements。【原文：Former Warner Music Chairman Edgar Bronfman Jr. is preparing a bid for National Amusements, the family company that controls Paramount Global , the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/edgar-bronfman-prepares-bid-paramount-parent-national-amusements-wsj-reports-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSHSNXFSCZPKNEMVU4LE32IIPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:46:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 EIA 称中国 6 月柴油需求创三年来最大降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署周四称，6月份中国柴油需求量同比下降11%，至每天390万桶，是2021年7月以来的最大降幅。【原文：China's diesel demand fell by 11% year over year to 3.9 million barrels per day in June, the biggest percentage drop since July 2021, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-diesel-demand-fell-june-by-most-three-years-us-eia-says-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5JAJUZCLBO2TMQRHHTQ7OXC5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓在智利的罢工进入第三天，推动全球铜价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[矿业巨头必和必拓（BHP）位于智利的埃斯孔迪达（Escondida）大型矿山的罢工周四进入第三天，推动了全球铜价的上涨，因为该公司与工人之间的持续对峙开始蔓延对红色金属供应的担忧。【原文：A strike at mining giant BHP's huge Escondida mine in Chile entered its third day on Thursday, bolstering global copper prices as an ongoing standoff between the company and workers starts to spread worries about supply of the red metal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/bhp-strike-chile-enters-third-day-buoying-global-copper-price-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YU4D7FOVBOMBBLE2N7L25Y5UE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:05:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官称可就佳得乐蛋白棒的健康声明起诉百事公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官裁定，百事可乐公司可以被起诉推销其佳得乐蛋白棒，称其对人体有益，尽管这些蛋白棒的含糖量超过了蛋白质，比一般的糖果棒含糖量还高。【原文：PepsiCo can be sued for marketing its Gatorade protein bars as good for you though they have more sugar than protein and more sugar than typical candy bars, a federal judge ruled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pepsico-can-be-sued-over-health-claims-gatorade-protein-bars-judge-says-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPBJI2GAUBM6JDNPJT4VAGOR34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月商业库存小幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于零售商库存的激增被批发商库存的温和增长所抵消，6 月份美国商业库存温和增长。【原文：U.S. business inventories increased moderately in June as a surge in stocks at retailers was offset by mild gains at wholesalers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-inventories-rise-marginally-june-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I3TDJL3XRPAFJL57GILOCWJWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车和飓风贝雷尔影响美国 7 月制造业产出]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于机动车产量下降和飓风贝里尔的影响，7 月份美国工厂的产量有所下降。【原文：Production at U.S. factories fell in July amid a decline in motor vehicle output and disruptions from Hurricane Beryl.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/autos-hurricane-beryl-weigh-us-manufacturing-output-july-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNABMB6PKVLDPNNB3X2LR5Z7OU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克股价大涨，阿克曼回归燃起扭亏希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克股价周四上涨近 4%，因为投资者希望亿万富翁威廉-阿克曼（William Ackman）重新成为耐克的股东后，这家一直在与战略失误和激烈竞争作斗争的运动服装巨头能迎来转机。【原文：Nike shares gained nearly 4% on Thursday as investors hoped the return of billionaire William Ackman as a stakeholder could spark a turnaround at the sportswear giant that has been battling with strategy missteps and tough competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-shares-jump-ackmans-return-sparks-turnaround-hopes-2024-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCGM4D4ZTZI77COACYSLVZIG2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>