<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:11:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:10:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 大行情，重大周前夕]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球股市周一攀升至新高，黄金价格突破每盎司5000美元大关，而美元跌势加速，因投资者正为本周即将到来的美国企业财报洪流及美联储政策决议做准备。【原文：World stocks climbed to new highs and gold smashed through the $5,000-an-ounce barrier on Monday, while the dollar's slide gathered pace as investors braced for a deluge of U.S. earnings and a Federal Reserve policy decision this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CBDZH5XZZLKLCJJJBPFUPQOUA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[W. R. 伯克利季度营业收入因承保业务强劲及投资收益增长而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[商业保险公司W. R. Berkley周一报告称，得益于稳健的承保业绩和投资组合收益，其第四季度营业利润实现增长。【原文：Commercial insurer W. R. Berkley reported a rise in fourth-quarter operating profit on Monday, helped by steady underwriting performance ​and gains from its investment portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/w-r-berkley-quarterly-operating-income-rises-strong-underwriting-investment-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DA57HK45YVIILMP66S56DHMWUQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国国民议会支持禁止15岁以下青少年使用社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国国民议会周一批准了一项立法，禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体，此举源于人们对网络欺凌和心理健康风险日益增长的担忧。【原文：France's National Assembly on Monday approved legislation banning children under 15-years old from social media over growing concerns about online bullying and mental health risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/frances-lower-house-backs-social-media-ban-those-under-15-years-old-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SNQTWFZAJOJTJN4M2DPN6237A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:41:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得州州长禁止州政府雇员使用阿里巴巴、Temu旗下产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[得克萨斯州州长周一发表声明称，该州将禁止其雇员使用阿里巴巴、Temu和TP-Link的软硬件产品，并表示此举旨在保护"得州居民隐私"免受中国政府侵害。【原文：Texas will bar its employees from using Alibaba, Temu and TP-Link hardware and software, the governor said in a statement on Monday, saying his state made the decision to protect the "privacy of Texans" from the Chinese government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/texas-governor-bars-state-employees-using-alibaba-temu-products-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCYBFT6QE5L6XCOEQGIRHP7T3A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《华尔街日报》报道，美国政府提议明年保持医保保险公司支付费率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周一报道，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普政府提议明年对保险公司支付的联邦医疗保险费用平均仅提高0.09%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has proposed an average rate increase of just 0.09% in Medicare payments to insurers next year, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-proposes-keeping-steady-medicare-rates-paid-insurers-wsj-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLFFXHGRVVOY7DA4JMFEGDLLSE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:20:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据CNBC报道，耐克将在美国分销中心裁员775人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国财经媒体CNBC周一报道，耐克公司正计划裁员775人，以提升利润并加速自动化进程。该报道援引知情人士消息称。【原文：Nike is laying off 775 employees in a bid to boost profits and accelerate its use of automation, CNBC reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-cut-775-jobs-us-distribution-centers-cnbc-reports-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDIKHQI3YZK4TJW7OZ7KV7F364</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士及文件显示，贸易公司将开始出口委内瑞拉液化石油气]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周一获得的两份消息来源及一份航运文件显示，贸易公司已开始为装运和出口委内瑞拉液化石油气（LPG）做准备，此举是加拉加斯与华盛顿之间达成5000万桶石油供应协议的一部分。【原文：Trading houses have begun making preparations to load and export Venezuelan liquefied petroleum gas (LPG) as part of a 50-million-barrel oil supply deal between Caracas and Washington, according to two sources and a shipping document seen by Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trading-houses-begin-exporting-venezuelan-lpg-sources-document-say-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MILAMC4LBRPYJGW3ELN5XYGVQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国设备租赁与融资协会称，12月美国企业设备贷款增长逾5%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国设备租赁与金融协会周一表示，去年12月美国企业为购买设备融资的借款额较上年同期增长5.9%，达到历史第二高水平。【原文：U.S. companies borrowed 5.9% more to finance equipment purchases in December than a year earlier, reaching the second-highest level ever, the Equipment Leasing and Finance Association said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-business-borrowing-equipment-rises-over-5-december-elfa-says-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5EINSGMV5NQRIA6MVGNBKU3Q4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:10:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔吉特新任首席执行官称明尼苏达州暴力事件"令人痛心不已"]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯市塔吉特公司即将上任的首席执行官周一告诉员工，"暴力事件和生命逝去令人痛彻心扉"。此前联邦特工于周末在明尼阿波利斯市枪杀了一名抗议者。【原文：The incoming CEO of Minneapolis-based Target told employees on Monday that "the violence and loss of life is incredibly painful" after federal agents shot and killed another protestor in Minneapolis over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/targets-incoming-ceo-calls-minnesota-violence-incredibly-painful-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5MYJ3ZXP5O7JBRRZL3E64SVUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达推出AI模型，实现更快、更经济的天气预报]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达周一发布了三款开源人工智能模型，旨在帮助更快地创建更精准的天气预报。【原文：Nvidia on Monday released three open-source artificial intelligence models aimed at helping create better weather forecasts, faster.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/nvidia-unveils-ai-models-faster-cheaper-weather-forecasts-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA2JDTJYTVOPPIIMAQICEPWK7A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:44:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源行业因冬季风暴导致日均200万桶原油产量中断而陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和交易员估计，上周末美国石油生产商每日减产高达200万桶，约占全国产量的15%。这场席卷全美的冬季风暴使能源基础设施和电网承受巨大压力。【原文：U.S. oil producers lost up to 2 million barrels per day or roughly 15% of national production over the weekend, analysts and traders estimated, as a winter storm swept across the country, straining energy infrastructure and power grids.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-energy-sector-reels-after-winter-storm-knocks-out-2-million-bpd-crude-output-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MON26QNP2RKPBGVSJMN5C6PQ4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府迈出在加州提供新近海石油钻探租约的第一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周一邀请石油和天然气行业提名加州南部和中部海域的潜在油气租赁区块，相关拍卖最早将于明年举行。【原文：The Trump administration on Monday invited the oil and gas industry to nominate areas for a potential sale of offshore oil and gas leases in Southern and Central California to be held as soon as next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-takes-first-step-toward-offering-new-offshore-oil-drilling-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RORSIPBDD5JADO6B6L3ZOP7LQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VinFast携手Autobrains开发低成本自动驾驶技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南汽车制造商VinFast周一宣布，已与人工智能公司Autobrains达成合作，共同开发包括低成本"机器人汽车"系统在内的先进自动驾驶技术，此举有望推动这家越南电动汽车制造商的自动驾驶技术发展。【原文：VinFast has partnered with AI firm Autobrains to develop advanced autonomous driving technology, including a low-cost "Robo-car" system, the companies said on Monday, potentially boosting the Vietnamese EV maker's self-driving tech push.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vinfast-teams-up-with-autobrains-develop-low-cost-self-driving-tech-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZ7MSGCMQFLRXOOEIYQH2SWVRE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[First Brands在破产危机中寻求买家，将逐步关闭核心业务部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[First Brands周一表示，已开始逐步缩减其北美部分业务，包括Brake Parts、Cardone和Autolite等业务单元，同时保留其余业务的运营，该公司正寻求为这些资产寻找买家。【原文：First Brands said on Monday it has begun winding down parts of its North American operations, including its Brake Parts, ​Cardone and Autolite units, while keeping its remaining businesses ‌running as the company seeks buyers for the assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/first-brands-wind-down-key-units-it-seeks-buyers-amid-bankruptcy-crisis-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2V6VCBOHZPHDNLGM4HBSGASWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:56:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯在委内瑞拉看到显著的收入机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[油田服务公司贝克休斯周一表示，委内瑞拉蕴藏着巨大的营收机遇，在该国开展业务的主要考量因素包括员工安全与工作条件，以及法律法规框架的明确性。【原文：Oilfield services company Baker Hughes said on Monday that there is significant revenue opportunity in Venezuela, with the main considerations for operating there being safety and conditions for employees, and clarity on legal and regulatory frameworks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/baker-hughes-sees-significant-revenue-opportunity-venezuela-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIXTA37VHRPYFL4QWQSSDJN3FU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tether称其在第四季度购入27吨黄金]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大稳定币发行方Tether周一表示，2025年第四季度其基金黄金配置增加了约27吨，与分析师预估的第三季度26吨购金量基本持平。【原文：Tether, issuer of the world's largest stablecoin, added about 27 metric tons of gold to its fund exposure in the fourth quarter of 2025, it said on Monday, broadly unchanged from its third-quarter purchases estimated by analysts at 26 tons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tether-says-it-bought-27-tons-gold-fourth-quarter-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSIHWESIPFJU3BEGQSR32I4M2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:50:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储加息暂停在即，推动债券投资者重返风险资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[债券投资者正为美联储降息周期的延长停顿做准备，同时他们正转向风险稍高的交易。这种转变源于经济韧性强劲以及美国新的财政刺激计划——这些计划很可能在今年提振消费者支出。【原文：Bond investors are bracing for an extended pause in the Federal Reserve's rate-cutting cycle as they edge into slightly riskier trades, driven by a resilient economy and fresh U.S. fiscal stimulus plans that are likely to boost consumer spending this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/looming-fed-rate-pause-nudges-bond-investors-back-into-risk-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HS737GI3H5PIZKQOV6PAOQ27GA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟议员就重启美欧贸易协定谈判存在分歧，此前因格陵兰岛问题引发危机]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲议会已将关于是否重启欧盟与美国贸易协定谈判的决定推迟至下周。此前议会曾暂停该谈判，以抗议美国总统特朗普要求收购格陵兰岛及威胁加征关税的行为。【原文：The European Parliament has put off until next week a decision on whether to resume work on the EU's trade deal with the United States, which it had suspended in protest at President Donald Trump's demands to acquire Greenland and threats of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-lawmakers-divided-over-resuming-work-us-trade-deal-after-greenland-crisis-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YDVB66LC5PTZJERAJLNI23JFA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:46:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国国民议会辩论禁止15岁以下青少年使用社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国国民议会周一就一项立法展开辩论，拟禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体。此举源于人们对网络欺凌及心理健康风险日益增长的担忧。【原文：France's National Assembly debated legislation to ban children under 15 years old from social media on Monday, amid growing concerns about online bullying and mental health risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/frances-national-assembly-debates-banning-under-15s-social-media-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBRKY6C65FIF3E6NS2PFT7FITQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前美国财政部长姆努钦加入狮门娱乐董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[狮门影业周一宣布，已任命美国前财政部长史蒂文·姆努钦为公司董事会董事，该任命即刻生效。【原文：Lionsgate Studios has appointed former U.S. Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin as a director on the company's board effective immediately, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/former-treasury-secretary-mnuchin-joins-lionsgates-board-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XIQ7HQV62JKQRJAZKDA6JKELKM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:31:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克表示正在调查可能的数据泄露事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司表示正在调查一起潜在的数据泄露事件，此前一个以网络攻击闻名的组织据称宣称泄露了大量与该公司业务运营相关的数据。【原文：Nike says it is investigating a potential data breach, after a group known for cyber attacks reportedly claimed to have leaked a trove of data related to its business operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nike-says-it-is-investigating-possible-data-breach-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G76M3BITUFPJJIEPAN4E245TRM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子游戏巨头Valve因定价及佣金问题面临英国诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[视频游戏开发商兼发行商Valve公司将在英国面临6.56亿英镑（约合8.977亿美元）的诉讼。该诉讼指控其在Steam在线商店向出版商收取过高佣金。此前法庭于周一裁定此案可继续审理。【原文：Video game developer and distributor Valve must face a 656 million-pound ($897.7 million) lawsuit in Britain, which alleges it charged publishers excessive commissions for its Steam online store, after a tribunal ruled on Monday the case could continue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/video-game-giant-valve-facing-uk-lawsuit-over-pricing-commissions-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RG65FJNG55IG3OWJTYIJNYYN4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元再度承压，投资者重新评估特朗普政策及地缘政治风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[2026年开局几周动荡不安，美元再度遭受冲击。随着包括华盛顿希望美元走弱在内的一系列因素不断发酵，投资者对美元将保持稳定的乐观预期正面临重新审视。【原文：The dollar is coming under fire again in the first few turbulent weeks of 2026 as a growing range of factors -- including Washington's desire for a weaker dollar -- ​prompts a rethink of investors' optimistic assumptions for a period of stability for the currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-under-fire-again-investors-reassess-trump-policies-geopolitical-risk-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHK65NGXAVITDDI6DQOL6GDLOY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[桥水首席信息官称，人工智能投资热潮或将重塑经济格局]]></title><description><![CDATA[桥水基金联合首席投资官周一在致客户的报告中表示，大型企业对人工智能的投入将持续呈指数级增长，并重塑经济格局。【原文：Spending on artificial intelligence by large corporations will continue to grow exponentially and reshape the economy, Bridgewater Associates' co-chief investment officers said in a client note on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-spending-frenzy-could-reshape-economy-bridgewater-cios-say-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5VNYKJLGBI2TALLILXFRHJZ5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软推出新一代AI芯片，瞄准英伟达的软件业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周一发布了其自主研发的人工智能芯片第二代产品，同时推出的软件工具瞄准了英伟达在开发者群体中最具竞争力的优势之一。【原文：Microsoft on Monday unveiled the second generation of its in-house artificial intelligence chip, along with software tools that take aim at one of Nvidia's biggest competitive advantages with developers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-rolls-out-next-generation-its-ai-chips-takes-aim-nvidias-software-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YO62JQ4NCNINZKGJSSVRSPUB4Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大总理卡尼表示，对《美墨加协定》的审查将十分严格]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克·卡尼周一表示，将于今年晚些时候启动的美墨加自由贸易协定审查将十分严格，并称美国总统唐纳德·特朗普是位强硬的谈判者。【原文：A review ​of the U.S.-Mexico-Canada free trade deal that ‌is due to start later this year will be robust, Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney said on Monday, describing U.S. President Donald Trump as ‌a tough negotiator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/review-usmca-trade-deal-will-be-robust-says-canada-pm-carney-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2YVMDYATBOXNEM5ISJS6EQS5Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空客新任商用飞机首席执行官聚焦产量，支持扩大A220机队规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[空客喷气机制造部门新任首席执行官周一承诺将专注于提升包括A350宽体客机在内的生产能力，并支持推出区域客机A220的加长版机型。【原文：The new CEO of Airbus' jet-making division pledged on Monday to focus on increasing production including the A350 wide-body jet and backed calls for a larger version of the regional A220.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/new-airbus-commercial-ceo-focused-output-backs-bigger-a220-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SOT3HLDQBMGJJEV5N3UCJNMFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将要求WhatsApp在处理有害内容方面承担更多责任]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周一宣布，已根据《欧盟数字服务法》正式将Meta Platform旗下的WhatsApp列为超大型平台，要求其承担更多责任以打击非法和有害内容。【原文：The European Commission on Monday said it had formally designated Meta Platform's WhatsApp as a very large platform under the EU's Digital Services Act (DSA), making it more responsible for tackling illegal and harmful content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eu-make-whatsapp-more-responsible-tackling-harmful-content-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F6OOOG7VZZO5TNK6W3RG75J32M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:24:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部取消所有与博思艾伦汉密尔顿公司的合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周一宣布已取消与博思艾伦咨询公司所有合同，指控该公司未能保护敏感数据，包括美国国税局的敏感数据。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department said on Monday it had canceled all of its contracts with Booz Allen Hamilton, accusing the company of failing to protect sensitive data, including at the Internal Revenue Service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/treasury-cancels-all-booz-allen-hamilton-contracts-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZWWFHPRR5PPDNWX2DJJ2LNGUQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:12:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌以6800万美元和解谷歌助手隐私诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌同意支付6800万美元以和解一起诉讼，该诉讼指控其语音助手不当监视智能手机用户，侵犯了他们的隐私权。【原文：Google agreed to pay $68 million to settle a lawsuit claiming that its voice-activated assistant spied inappropriately on smartphone users, violating their privacy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-settles-google-assistant-privacy-lawsuit-68-million-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHQAI6ERLFPBXAE2KBGQVSEFTE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>