<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:33:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:33:41 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国华为技术公司寻求撤销美国刑事指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[华为技术公司（HWT.UL）要求美国法官驳回联邦起诉书中的大部分指控，该起诉书指控这家中国电信公司试图窃取美国竞争对手的技术机密，并在伊朗业务方面误导银行。【原文：Huawei Technologies (HWT.UL) asked a U.S. judge to dismiss much of a federal indictment accusing the Chinese telecommunications company of trying to steal technology secrets from U.S. rivals and misleading banks about its business in Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/default/chinas-huawei-technologies-seeks-dismissal-us-criminal-charges-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4T23JFNZ3RJCTLZRYQUJA5MUDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:59:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FTX 起诉 Binance 及其前首席执行官，索赔 18 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[倒闭的加密货币公司 FTX 正在起诉 Binance 及其前首席执行官赵长鹏，指控 FTX 管理层向 Binance 及其高管 "欺诈性转移 "了 18 亿美元。【原文：Collapsed cryptocurrency company FTX is suing Binance and its former CEO Changpeng Zhao, alleging that $1.8 billion was "fraudulently transferred" by FTX management to Binance and its executives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ftx-sues-binance-its-former-ceo-18-bln-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72TOVOUB4VMZRJT5ILLZS6JXWU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Moncler 未就收购巴宝莉进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利 Moncler 公司 MONC.MI 没有参与收购 Burberry 的谈判。
 周一，针对英国《星期日邮报》关于 Moncler 即将竞购巴宝莉的报道，四位接近此事的消息人士称，Moncler 并未就收购巴宝莉进行谈判。【原文：Italy's Moncler MONC.MI is not in talks to take over Burberry 
 , four sources close to the matter said on Monday in response to a report by Britain's Mail on Sunday that a bid by Moncler was imminent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/moncler-not-talks-take-over-burberry-sources-say-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWAHMENY3FJEFCJPYB3OVVHMGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:38:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府推迟宣布新财政措施，巴西货币走软]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）的政府推迟发布人们期待已久的控制支出措施，尽管此前有迹象表明该措施即将宣布，但巴西货币周一还是走软了。【原文：Brazil's currency weakened on Monday as President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva's administration postponed the release of long-awaited spending-containment measures, despite earlier signals of an imminent announcement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/brazils-currency-weakens-amid-government-delays-announcing-new-fiscal-measures-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RK24HG6RJIT3HUHQV3HSXM7RU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:23:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩进一步推迟富士软收购要约计划，等待公司批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与竞争对手巨头 KKR 的收购竞争中，私募股权公司贝恩资本周一宣布，由于仍在等待日本富士软公司的批准，该公司目前预计将于 11 月中下旬启动对该公司的要约收购。【原文：Bain Capital now expects to launch its tender offer for Japan's Fuji Soft in mid-to-late November as it continues to await company approval, the private equity firm announced on Monday, amid a buyout competition with rival giant KKR .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-further-delays-fuji-soft-tender-offer-plans-awaits-company-approval-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZRY4LRB3BKM3KNHRPNMI3EUMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着 C-390 销售回升，巴西航空工业公司计划在欧洲设立防务办事处]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）的防务部门正计划在欧洲开设一个办事处，因为其 C-390 千禧型军用货运飞机在该地区的销售步伐正在加快。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer's defense unit is planning to open an office in Europe, as sales of its C-390 Millennium military cargo aircraft gain pace in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/embraer-plans-defense-office-europe-c-390-sales-pick-up-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYOVNCVWWBJ6VCFJPNFISSXI7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利将向高盛出售暖通空调公司 Sila]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利的私募股权部门周一表示，将向高盛另类投资公司（Goldman Sachs Alternatives）出售其家庭服务公司 Sila Services。【原文：Morgan Stanley's private equity arm said on Monday it would sell its home services company, Sila Services, to Goldman Sachs Alternatives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/morgan-stanley-sell-hvac-firm-sila-goldman-sachs-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4IJ4KNYYVPMBHSK6YIHICSUMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普获胜后，比特币大涨引发加密货币空头交易商损失数十亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[自11月6日以来，加密货币和区块链相关股票的卖空者损失惨重，此前比特币飙升至历史新高，原因是人们乐观地认为美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普将实施更有利的监管框架。【原文：Short sellers of cryptocurrency and blockchain-related stocks have suffered heavy losses since Nov. 6, after bitcoin surged to record highs, on optimism U.S. President-elect Donald Trump would implement a more favorable regulatory framework.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-surge-triggers-billions-losses-crypto-short-traders-after-trump-win-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CQHBSKWMNPO5IXWGNT76QMJ54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利的 Intesa 与贝莱德合作在比荷卢开展私人银行业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利最大的银行意大利联合圣保罗银行（Intesa Sanpaolo）表示，将与全球最大的资产管理公司、意大利联合圣保罗银行的主要股东贝莱德（BlackRock）合作，为比利时和卢森堡的客户提供数字财富管理服务。【原文：Italy's largest bank Intesa Sanpaolo said it would partner with BlackRock , the world's biggest asset manager and a leading Intesa shareholder, to offer digital wealth management services to clients in Belgium and Luxembourg.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/italys-intesa-partners-with-blackrock-private-banking-benelux-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27KXXHRV6ZMX3K4DO6C4MQNFXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 13:29:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢旗下 KitKat 签订一级方程式赛车协议，首席执行官 Freixe 寻求更广泛的吸引力]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司的 KitKat 品牌与一级方程式赛车签订了一份全球赞助协议，新任首席执行官洛朗-弗莱克西（Laurent Freixe）试图改变这家全球最大食品公司营销其价值数十亿美元的核心品牌的方式。【原文：Nestle's KitKat brand has signed a global sponsorship deal with Formula 1 as new Chief Executive Laurent Freixe seeks to change the way the world's biggest food company markets its core, multi-billion-dollar brands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nestles-kitkat-signs-formula-1-deal-ceo-freixe-seeks-broader-appeal-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5R3NYECY65MGZPZ5VCDZWJGMPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 13:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cigna 表示不寻求与 Humana 合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[医疗保险公司 Cigna Group 周一表示，它不会寻求与同行 Humana 合并。【原文：Health insurer Cigna Group said on Monday it is not pursuing a combination with peer Humana .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/cigna-says-it-will-not-pursue-combination-with-humana-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNDIYRHJDBMENGVMUFISH6AAII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:37:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西总统卢拉敦促国会削减开支以帮助 "战胜 "金融市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统在周日晚些时候播出的采访中誓言要打击金融市场的 "投机贪婪"，并敦促国会在政府准备新的财政措施时通过削减开支来树立榜样。【原文：Brazil's president vowed to beat the "speculative greed" of financial markets in an interview broadcast late on Sunday and urged Congress to set an example by cutting spending as the government readies new fiscal measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-lula-urges-congress-cut-spending-help-beat-financial-markets-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6HPYYGJXVIQNO6BV5QWYYSCDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金涌入银行，美国大选后抛售绿色能源，高盛集团称]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）的一份报告显示，由于投资者对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在美国总统大选中获胜作出反应，对冲基金上周以三年来最快的速度抢购银行股，同时对可再生电力生产商下注。【原文：Hedge funds snapped up bank stocks at the quickest clip in three years while taking bets against renewable electricity producers last week, a Goldman Sachs note showed, as investors reacted to Donald Trump's win in the U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-pile-into-banks-dump-green-energy-post-us-election-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GX5TDQ2LMNO4VN6MSOWX4CVTLE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉股价延续涨势，马斯克与特朗普结盟助推涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉股价周一盘前跳涨逾 7%，延续了投资者对该汽车制造商将受益于首席执行官埃隆-马斯克支持美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的押注所推动的红火涨势。【原文：Tesla shares jumped more than 7% premarket on Monday, extending a red-hot rally fueled by investor bets that the automaker would benefit from CEO Elon Musk's backing of U.S. President-elect Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tesla-stock-extends-rally-musk-trump-alliance-fuels-gains-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUQNPFR3HROL3HUEPU7HRHD2GA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 12:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多伦多证券交易所开盘上涨，科技股和金融股走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大主要股指周一高开，受助于科技股和金融股，同时投资者等待本周的关键经济数据，以衡量美国联邦储备委员会的货币政策路径。【原文：Canada's main stock index opened higher on Monday, helped by technology and financial shares, while investors awaited this week's key economic data to gauge the U.S. Federal Reserve's monetary policy path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/tsx-futures-rise-ahead-data-heavy-week-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IORVCT4CUBP4BKHAWFE7RHAESY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 11:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价大选后美元升值，中国对抗通缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5YO4T2DPNL4BPEXOZ3ZIGG6HY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 11:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普推动期货市场反弹，特斯拉跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周一上涨，扩大了大选后的涨幅，而投资者则在期待下一批经济数据，这些数据可能决定股市涨势能否持续。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Monday, adding to post-election gains, while investors looked ahead to the next batch of economic data that could decide whether the equity rally can sustain itself.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-build-trump-fueled-rally-tesla-jumps-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36S6TANGW5JYRNKUEOI5CCQLXY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 11:13:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，亚马逊正在开发司机眼镜，以缩短送货时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位熟悉内情的人士透露，亚马逊正在为其送货司机开发智能眼镜，以引导他们前往、绕过建筑物并在建筑物内行驶，因为亚马逊正试图顺利完成将订单送至客户家中的最后一段旅程。【原文：Amazon is developing smart eyeglasses for its delivery drivers to guide them to, around and within buildings, as it tries to smooth the final stretch of an order's journey to a customer's home, five people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-developing-driver-eyeglasses-shave-seconds-off-deliveries-sources-say-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2GNBDJXWFOHRFHNVS2GPYJOPY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 11:10:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴上 "百叶窗"，但要做好准备：2016 年，美联储注意到特朗普的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）2016 年当选后的几周内，美国联邦储备委员会（美联储）的政策制定者们就开始酝酿预期的减税和关税对经济的影响，对即将发生的事情进行了粗略的估计，其中一些人认为可能需要提高利率来抑制通胀。【原文：Within weeks of Donald Trump's 2016 election, U.S. Federal Reserve policymakers began mulling the impact of expected tax cuts and tariffs on the economy, penciling in rough estimates of what was to come, with some among them concluding higher interest rates may be needed to keep inflation in check.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/blinders-on-be-prepared-2016-fed-took-note-trumps-plans-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LQE6HB6SRN7JGTGH3V62UHABI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 11:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国干旱卷土重来，推迟牛群重建，损害泰森食品公司利益]]></title><description><![CDATA[牧场主和分析师说，在美国牛群数量缩减到七十年来最小的水平之后，美国产牛区再次出现的干旱正在推迟牧场主扩大生产的计划。【原文：The return of drought in U.S. cattle-producing areas is delaying ranchers' plans to expand production after the nation's herd shrank to its smallest level in seven decades, farmers and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/return-us-drought-delays-cattle-herd-rebuilding-hurting-tyson-foods-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DD35A65BZOW3AMV4L3RYBBDVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 11:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Asterion 同意将数据中心运营商 Nabiax 出售给 Aermont]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙基础设施投资基金 Asterion Industrial Partners 和西班牙电信公司周一在一份联合声明中表示，双方同意将西班牙数据中心运营商 Nabiax 出售给欧洲资产管理公司 Aermont Capital。【原文：Spanish infrastructure investment fund Asterion Industrial Partners and Telefonica agreed to sell Spanish data centre operator Nabiax to European asset manager Aermont Capital, the companies said on Monday in a joint statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/asterion-agrees-sell-data-centre-operator-nabiax-aermont-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KRNPQCXCVMKPDFP6WPLO36ZO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于现有方法受到限制，OpenAI 和其他公司正在寻求实现更智能人工智能的新途径]]></title><description><![CDATA[像 OpenAI 这样的人工智能公司正在寻求通过开发训练技术，使用更像人类的方式让算法 "思考"，从而克服在追求越来越大的语言模型过程中出现的意外延误和挑战。【原文：Artificial intelligence companies like OpenAI are seeking to overcome unexpected delays and challenges in the pursuit of ever-biggerlarge language models by developing training techniques that use more human-like ways for algorithms to "think".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-rivals-seek-new-path-smarter-ai-current-methods-hit-limitations-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTHE3MBBCVNTHH4FW4MRHKX67U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究发现，美国少数民族退伍军人在获得 Ozempic 和 Wegovy 方面面临不平等待遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一（美国退伍军人节假期）发表的一份患者数据审查报告显示，美国退伍军人在获得诺和诺德糖尿病和减肥药物方面面临着种族和民族的不平等。【原文：U.S. military veterans face racial and ethnic inequities in access to Novo Nordisk's highly in-demand drugs for diabetes and weight loss, according to a review of patient data published on Monday, the U.S. Veterans Day holiday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-minority-veterans-face-unequal-access-ozempic-wegovy-study-finds-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JR5QUDLY2NJ75BUJDIM7Y2ULYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moncler 重申不会对有关 Burberry 的 "未经证实的传言 "发表评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利 Moncler 公司周一重申，当被问及《每日邮报》关于这家奢侈外衣制造商可能收购英国奢侈品牌 Burberry 的报道时，该公司不会对 "未经证实的传言 "发表评论。【原文：Italy's Moncler on Monday reiterated it would not comment "on unsubstantiated rumors", when asked about a Daily Mail report about a possible takeover by the luxury outerwear maker for British luxury brand Burberry .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/moncler-repeats-it-wont-comment-unsubstantiated-rumors-about-burberry-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X7MBQMEHA5NW5O6AYPI4M24ACA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 09:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚即将与澳新银行达成协议，阻止太平洋地区银行关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚国库部长吉姆-查莫斯（Jim Chalmers）周一表示，澳大利亚与澳新银行集团（ANZ Group）就保留该银行在太平洋地区分支机构的协议谈判已进入最后阶段。【原文：Australia is in the final stages of talks with ANZ Group over a deal to maintain the bank's branches across the Pacific, Treasurer Jim Chalmers said on Monday, a diplomatic win in a region contested with China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australia-nears-deal-with-anz-stop-bank-closures-pacific-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OT337356TROE3OVT7MS4UROE3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 09:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普胜选给新兴市场蒙上阴影，投资者看好印度的安全性]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普的经济政策，包括任何可能引发新兴市场波动的贸易保护主义政策的外溢效应，可能会使全球投资者在印度金融市场找到相对安全的投资环境。【原文：Global investors are likely to find relative safety in India's financial markets from the spillover of Donald Trump's economic policies, including from any protectionist trade policies that could spark emerging market volatility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/investors-see-safety-india-trump-win-casts-shadow-emerging-markets-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TM2WR7TESZMFTGACLJW2G5YUAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 08:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电订单助推自力更生，中国芯片指数逼近三年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国半导体指数周一跃升至接近三年高点，原因是美国下令停止台湾中芯国际集成电路制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：China's semiconductor index leapt close to a three-year high on Monday on bets a U.S. order halting Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co's shipments of advanced chips to Chinese customers could accelerate Beijing's self-reliance efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/china-chip-index-nears-3-year-high-tsmc-order-fuels-self-reliance-bets-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3LKUQHBKNLGTPK5RAZT6OXUTI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业情绪低迷、破产数量增加为日本央行的加息之路蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的数据显示，10月份日本服务业景气度恶化，破产案件增加，这让人对日本央行认为在强劲内需的推动下，日本有望实现2%的通胀目标产生怀疑。【原文：Japan's service-sector sentiment worsened and bankruptcy cases rose in October, data showed on Monday, casting doubt on the central bank's view the country was on track to meet its 2% inflation target driven by robust domestic demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/dampening-corporate-mood-rising-bankruptcies-cloud-bojs-rate-hike-path-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBNPAKQC2FLNDKPIVW3S64LEPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 07:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着监管审查的加强，印度将传唤亚马逊和 Flipkart 高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高级政府消息人士称，印度金融犯罪机构将传唤 Flipkart 和亚马逊的高管，因为该机构在突袭了这两家电子商务公司的一些卖家几天后，加紧了对涉嫌违反外国投资法的调查。【原文：India's financial crime agency will summon Flipkart and Amazon executives as it steps up an investigation into alleged foreign investment law violations, days after raiding some of the e-commerce firms' sellers, a senior government source said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/india-summon-amazon-flipkart-executives-regulatory-scrutiny-grows-source-says-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4WELMXKHZMS7EWOCXDUCUCHY4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 06:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大陆集团下调销售指引，第三季度利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车和工业供应商大陆集团（Continental）周一今年第二次下调了销售指导，原因是欧洲和北美需求疲软，尽管该公司公布的第三季度核心利润高于预期。【原文：German automotive and industrial supplier Continental on Monday cut its sales guidance for the second time this year, blaming weak demand in Europe and North America, even as it posted third-quarter core profit above expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/continental-cuts-sales-guidance-posts-q3-profit-beat-2024-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEI3FWAZ7VN3BDG4NJUAOUPLKE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 06:32:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>