<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:39:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:39:40 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[股价下滑，欧洲汽车制造商接受特朗普的现实检验]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲的汽车制造商已经在与来自亚洲的激烈竞争和代价高昂的电动汽车转型作斗争，周一又要面对另一个现实--美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税。【原文：Europe's carmakers, already battling stiff competition from Asia and a costly transition to electric cars, were dealing with another dose of reality on Monday - tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-carmakers-get-reality-check-trump-shares-slide-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVK54LD2FZODDCLNXRSGQFTQ4Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:30:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟和美国将组建金属联盟制衡中国产能过剩]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易委员马罗斯-塞夫科维奇（Maros Sefcovic）周一表示，作为贸易协议的一部分，欧盟和美国将建立金属联盟，以减轻中国补贴生产对全球市场的影响。【原文：The European Union and United States will develop a metals alliance to mitigate the impact of subsidised Chinese production on global markets as part of their trade deal, European Trade Commissioner Maros Sefcovic said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-us-form-metals-alliance-counterbalance-chinese-overcapacity-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6J77FVSRBRLTPIT3BBS5ZKHOO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西咖啡种植者对特朗普即将征收的关税保持警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西里约热内卢州瓦苏拉斯的咖啡种植者希望在巴西对美国出口征收 50%的关税之前，能在最后一刻获得缓和。【原文：Coffee growers in Vassouras, in Brazil's Rio de Janeiro state, are hoping for an eleventh-hour reprieve before the country is subject to tariffs of 50% on its exports to the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-coffee-growers-wary-incoming-trump-tariffs-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5A2NERHUFL7VGYQAO6QRNOVPI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金价将保持在 3000 美元/盎司以上，因为避险情绪仍在持续：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[对全球贸易和财政债务的担忧导致人们纷纷转向更安全的资产，使黄金作为避险天堂的优势更加突出，促使路透社民意调查的分析师大幅提高了他们的预测。【原文：Global trade and fiscal debt concerns are feeding into a flight to safer assets, sharpening gold's edge as a haven from risk, prompting analysts in a Reuters poll to sharply raise their forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gold-price-stay-above-3000oz-flight-safety-endures-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGGFCCSVNZJNPCC6BOXSIVL2OM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着赫姆斯利成为焦点，联合健康的投资者可能会寻求成本路线图]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康（UnitedHealth）新任首席执行官斯蒂芬-赫姆斯利（Stephen Hemsley）可能将面临投资者的审查，因为这家美国最大的健康保险和服务公司正在努力控制医疗成本的上升，而这正是其撤回年度预测的原因。【原文：UnitedHealth's newly returned CEO, Stephen Hemsley, will likely face investor scrutiny over the largest U.S. health insurance and services company's efforts to rein in the elevated medical costs behind the withdrawal of its annual forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/unitedhealth-investors-may-seek-roadmap-costs-hemsley-takes-center-stage-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P25IJDCSHJKJLGQ6Z5KYMLL3CY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创公司智璞发布开源模型 GLM-4.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创公司智璞周一发布了专为智能代理应用设计的开源模型GLM-4.5。【原文：Chinese AI startup Zhipu on Monday released open-source model GLM-4.5 designed for intelligent agent applications, a statement said, as it joins a wave of similar releases from local rivals in an increasingly competitive sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-ai-startup-zhipu-releases-open-source-model-glm-45-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAUASRDFSBMKXOZ5GYWE7VIEXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥本海默因贸易乐观情绪将标普 500 指数年末目标上调至华尔街最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥本海默资产管理公司（Oppenheimer Asset Management）周一将 S&amp;P 500 指数的年终目标上调至 7100 点，在华尔街主要券商中居首位，押注贸易紧张局势缓解和企业盈利强劲。【原文：Oppenheimer Asset Management on Monday raised its year-end target for the S&amp;P 500 index to 7,100, the highest among major Wall Street brokerages, betting on easing trade tensions and strong corporate earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/oppenheimer-lifts-sp-500-year-end-target-wall-street-high-trade-optimism-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3AMR4UVXFITLFWD2YVCBY6C5U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究人员称，卢布支持的加密货币交易额在七月激增后突破 400 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[区块链研究公司Elliptic周一表示，一种由卢布支持、可帮助俄罗斯规避西方支付限制的稳定币7月份交易量激增，通过该币转移的资金总额超过400亿美元。【原文：A rouble-backed stablecoin that could help Russia circumvent Western restrictions on payments has seen a jump in transaction volumes in July, with funds moved through the coin surging past $40 billion in total, blockchain research firm Elliptic said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/transfers-with-rouble-backed-crypto-coin-pass-40-billion-after-july-spike-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKTORRR2HJOSVPBH7JXTKNSGPM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:09:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡莱尔在重组后挑选内部人士担任新的联席总裁职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[另类资产管理公司凯雷（Carlyle）周一表示，该公司已对高级领导层进行了调整，并任命三名资深人士担任新设立的联席总裁一职。【原文：Alternative asset manager Carlyle said on Monday it has rejigged its senior leadership ranks and named three of its veterans for its newly created role of co-presidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/carlyle-picks-insiders-newly-minted-role-co-presidents-after-reshuffle-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WFLGONFIROYZMOLCOH74ETXDE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：巴西与 TPG 和布鲁克菲尔德公司就推动 40 亿美元气候融资进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西正在与包括 TPG 和布鲁克菲尔德（Brookfield）在内的全球投资者洽谈，为气候项目筹集近 40 亿美元的资金，在 11 月主办 COP30 气候峰会之前加大绿色金融的推进力度。【原文：Brazil is in talks with global investors including TPG and Brookfield to raise nearly $4 billion for climate-focused projects, as it ramps up a green finance push ahead of hosting the COP30 climate summit in November.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/brazil-talks-with-tpg-brookfield-over-4-billion-climate-finance-push-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRYN7AFEMVNGDKB7ICJNEH5J3Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:51:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，EQT 将以超过 30 亿美元的价格收购软件供应商 Neogov]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周一表示，投资公司 EQT 已同意从其私募股权所有者手中收购 Neogov，包括债务在内，这家人力资源软件供应商的估值超过 30 亿美元。【原文：Investment firm EQT has agreed to acquire Neogov from its private equity owners, valuing the human resources software provider at more than $3 billion including debt, people familiar with the matter said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/eqt-acquire-software-provider-neogov-more-than-3-billion-sources-say-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QIBK2P5ANI33CLSEIIHAJ3MTI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:49:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税将考验奢侈品牌的定价能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周日的欧盟-美国贸易协议中，奢侈品公司幸免于最糟糕的情况，但它们面临着微妙的平衡，因为已经疲软的消费需求考验着它们进一步提价的能力。【原文：Luxury goods companies were spared their worst case scenario in Sunday's EU-U.S. trade deal but they face a delicate balancing act as already weak consumer demand tests their ability to raise prices further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-tariffs-will-be-test-luxury-brands-pricing-power-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5DUJB34RNICDFLNHOF25Y4YSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:15:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国政策变化打击诊断需求，Revvity 下调 2025 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Revvity公司周一下调了全年调整后利润预期，因为该公司预计其主要市场中国对诊断产品的需求将因中国报销政策的变化而受到影响，这导致该公司股价下跌近10%。【原文：Revvity on Monday lowered its full-year adjusted profit forecast as it expects demand for diagnostics products in its key market China to be hurt by changes to the country's reimbursement policy, sending the company's shares down nearly 10%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/revvity-trims-2025-profit-forecast-china-policy-changes-hit-diagnostics-demand-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MMDI3SU4EJOMXAW4WYA5ADW7WQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗马尼亚预计美国新贸易协定将对经济增长造成小幅冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗马尼亚周一表示，美国对欧洲商品征收15%的进口关税将意味着中欧第二大经济体受到的打击不大，而依赖出口的斯洛伐克则称赞美国的贸易协议是一个 "好结果"。【原文：Romania said on Monday a 15% U.S. import tariff on European goods would mean a small hit to central Europe's second-largest economy, while export-reliant Slovakia hailed the U.S. trade deal as a "good result".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/romania-expects-small-growth-hit-new-us-trade-deal-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFVI4VE6NZOONIWPKG73BGD5NQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:07:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员希望马斯克阻止东南亚金融诈骗集团使用 "星链 "系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位民主党参议员周一敦促 SpaceX 公司首席执行官埃隆-马斯克阻止东南亚的跨国犯罪集团利用 Starlink 卫星互联网服务对美国人实施诈骗。【原文：A Democratic senator on Monday urged SpaceX CEO Elon Musk to block transnational criminal groups in Southeast Asia from using Starlink satellite internet service to commit fraud against Americans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-senator-wants-musk-block-use-starlink-by-financial-fraud-groups-southeast-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLV6MTMKNJKJBJ4MMIV47Z4L3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:35:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国太空竞赛白热化，Firefly Aerospace 首次公开募股寻求 55 亿美元估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[太空技术初创公司 Firefly Aerospace 在美国首次公开募股的目标估值约为 55 亿美元，因为投资者对高增长行业的偏好显示出持续反弹的迹象。【原文：Space technology startup Firefly Aerospace is targeting a valuation of about $5.5 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, as investor appetite for high-growth sectors shows signs of a sustained rebound.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/firefly-aerospace-seeks-55-billion-valuation-ipo-us-space-race-heats-up-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6LHOEQUGBO4LKTPQDONSAD67U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Auterion 称将向乌克兰提供 33,000 套人工智能无人机制导套件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国防务公司 Auterion 周一表示，该公司将为乌克兰无人机提供 33,000 套人工智能制导工具，五角大楼为此提供了 5,000 万美元的合同资金。【原文：U.S. defence company Auterion will provide 33,000 artificial intelligence guidance kits for Ukrainian drones, funded by a $50 million Pentagon contract, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/auterion-says-it-will-provide-ukraine-with-33000-ai-drone-guidance-kits-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QY7JQUFK7JL7LOZPBCPH3IZNEU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:26:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受欧盟制裁的印度炼油厂纳亚拉公司就断电问题将微软告上法庭]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯支持的印度炼油厂纳亚拉能源公司（Nayara Energy）周一表示，在总部位于美国的软件巨头突然单方面中止关键服务后，该公司已开始对微软提起法律诉讼。【原文：Russia-backed Indian refiner Nayara Energy Monday said it has started legal proceedings against Microsoft following the abrupt and unilateral suspension of critical services by the U.S.-headquartered software giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eu-sanctioned-indian-refiner-nayara-takes-microsoft-court-over-outage-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3COXY3YVCRJ3BK5ARDA7I54QKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:18:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大道明银行任命新行长领导监督工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[道明银行已任命独立董事约翰-麦金太尔（John MacIntyre）为新任董事会主席，这家加拿大贷款机构将启用新的后卫来加强监管并让投资者放心。【原文：TD Bank has named independent director John MacIntyre as the new chair of its board, as the Canadian lender turns to a new guard to bolster oversight and reassure investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/canadas-td-bank-names-new-chair-steer-oversight-push-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4I4VKTN5JRJHFICUZTHSPP5ADM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:17:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟称特木公司违反了防止销售非法产品的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周一称，中国在线市场特姆优在防止通过其平台销售非法产品方面做得不够，因而违反了欧盟规则。【原文：The European Commission on Monday said Chinese online marketplace Temu was breaking EU rules by not doing enough to prevent the sale of illegal products through its platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/eu-says-temu-breach-rules-prevent-sale-illegal-products-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAICRRQTO5IWHEGPR5HTLAISBY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:55:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BTG Pactual 将以 1.75 亿美元收购汇丰银行在乌拉圭的业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西银行 BTG Pactual 周一表示，将以 1.75 亿美元的价格收购汇丰银行在乌拉圭的业务，这是该银行首次进军这个西班牙语国家，并将扩大其在拉丁美洲的业务。【原文：Brazilian bank BTG Pactual on Monday said it will snap up HSBC's operations in Uruguay for $175 million, marking its first foray into the Spanish-speaking country and expanding its presence in Latin America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/btg-pactual-buy-hsbcs-uruguay-operation-175-million-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6E3K53BZYJI47MPMYSTNJOW25Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻美欧协议提振市场和美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">36HLJAJ4DNKMDLGGJLID5GTHRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯就俄航网络攻击立案调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯总检察长办公室周一称，俄罗斯检察官对未经授权访问俄航计算机系统的行为展开刑事调查，此前该航空公司将数十个航班被取消归咎于信息技术故障。【原文：Russian prosecutors on Monday opened a criminal investigation into unauthorised access to computer systems at Aeroflot , the Prosecutor General's office said, after the airline blamed an IT failure for the cancellation of dozens of flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-opens-criminal-case-over-aeroflot-cyberattack-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MPVJ5OIKVK4PAZLHBHSVZGL2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:28:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟同意每年购买 2,500 亿美元液化天然气，美国液化天然气生产商大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国液化天然气开发商的股票在周一盘前交易中大涨，此前欧盟承诺在未来三年内购买价值 7500 亿美元的超冷燃料，作为一项全面贸易协议的一部分。【原文：Shares of U.S. liquefied natural gas developers surged in premarket trading on Monday, after the European Union pledged to purchase $750 billion worth of the super-cooled fuel over the next three years as part of a sweeping trade pact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-lng-producers-soar-eu-agrees-250-billion-annual-purchases-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEVOYTY6OFORPKUN3AWM2QW7FM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interactive Brokers 考虑为客户推出新的稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国放宽对加密货币行业的监管，许多大型金融公司都在大力押注数字代币热潮，互动经纪集团（Interactive Brokers Group）正在考虑为客户推出稳定币。【原文：Interactive Brokers Group is considering launching a stablecoin for customers, joining a number of large financial firms that are betting big on the digital token boom as the U.S. eases regulations around the crypto industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/interactive-brokers-considers-launching-new-stablecoin-customers-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3JCS57X6VKGRBJ4TF6VV4DXQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[这家由贝索斯支持的电动汽车初创公司打赌，你会为你的小型皮卡中的立体声音响支付额外费用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年春天，当威尔-哈瑟尔廷在网上看到初创公司 Slate Auto 推出的小型箱式电动皮卡的图片时，他立刻就加入了候选名单。稀疏的内饰和曲柄车窗
 
 让他想起了他在田纳西州孟菲斯长大时身边的那些简朴的皮卡车
 
 - 但最让他着迷的还是低于 20,000 美元的价格。【原文：When Will Haseltine saw images online of a small, boxy electric pickup from startup Slate Auto this past spring, he got on the waitlist right away. The sparse interior and crank windows
 
 reminded him of the no-frills pickups he grew up around in Memphis, Tennessee
 
 – but he was most enamored with the sub-$20,000 price tag.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/this-bezos-backed-ev-startup-is-betting-youll-pay-extra-stereo-your-petite-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7WDWND6RBMMVAZQANRD6WCTGI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:21:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在行动密集的一周到来之前，华尔街期货受美欧贸易协议提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，华尔街期货攀升，原因是美国和欧盟之间达成的贸易协议在本周伊始提振了市场情绪，本周将迎来巨头财报、美联储会议和美国关税最后期限。【原文：Wall Street futures climbed on Monday as a trade agreement between the U.S. and the European Union boosted sentiment at the start of a week packed with megacap earnings, a Federal Reserve meeting and a U.S. tariff deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/wall-street-futures-boosted-by-us-eu-trade-deal-ahead-action-packed-week-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQNDRK3SDFNPJBDCFGSCRE4FMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行博客认为：美元稳定币威胁欧洲货币自主权]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行周一发表博文称，美元在稳定币中的早期主导地位给美国带来了优势，最终可能推高欧洲的借贷成本，削弱欧洲央行的自主性，并增加对美国的地缘政治依赖。【原文：The dollar's early dominance of stablecoins gives the U.S. an advantage that could ultimately push up borrowing costs for Europe, reduce the ECB's autonomy and increase geopolitical dependency on the U.S., an ECB blog post argued on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dollar-stablecoins-threaten-europes-monetary-autonomy-ecb-blog-argues-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6WNIDFUSVORTFEI32LOMHEAMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储在筛选喜忧参半的经济数据时预计将维持利率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[令唐纳德-特朗普总统懊恼不已的是，美国央行很可能在本周的政策会议上维持利率不变，但这并不是说不会有激烈的辩论，如果不是两位美联储理事，也可能会有一位理事罕见地提出异议，支持降低借贷成本。【原文：The U.S. central bank, to President Donald Trump's chagrin, will likely leave interest rates unchanged at a policy meeting this week, but that's not to say there won't be a vigorous debate, with one if not two Federal Reserve governors possibly casting a rare dissent in support of lower borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-expected-keep-rates-unchanged-it-sifts-through-mixed-economic-data-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6AM6A54EZIOXIOVW5RUITED2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲对美国贸易协议的反应既欣慰又担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲各国政府和企业都承认这是一项不平衡的协议，但它避免了更深层次的贸易战。【原文：European governments and companies acknowledged what was seen as an unbalanced deal but one that avoided a deeper trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/europe-reacts-with-mix-relief-concern-us-trade-deal-2025-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAHXXRMWZVMPHMRUAJDOR2BBNQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>