<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 05:08:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 05:08:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国需求强劲，丰田 10 月产量连续第五个月增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周四称，受美国对混合动力汽车的强劲需求抵消了日本和中国销售疲软的影响，10月份全球产量连续第五个月增长。【原文：Toyota Motor said on Thursday its global production rose for a fifth consecutive month in October, lifted by strong U.S. demand for hybrid vehicles that offset weaker sales in Japan and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-october-output-grows-fifth-straight-month-strong-us-demand-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QV4WIRAQNPTDOTEOF35B64HR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 04:30:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国监管机构发布智能手机行业竞争合规指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家媒体周四报道，中国市场监管部门周三在深圳发布了针对智能手机制造商和移动应用平台公司的反不正当竞争合规指导意见。【原文：China's market regulator issued an anti-unfair competition compliance guidance for smartphone makers and mobile application platform firms in Shenzhen on Wednesday, Chinese state media reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/china-regulator-issues-competition-compliance-guidance-smartphone-industry-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7T4URWIWRVMDFBFOCJEMXNN2DE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 04:07:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络攻击可能泄露了朝日集团 150 万客户的个人信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本朝日集团（Asahi Group）周四表示，9 月份的一次网络攻击可能导致 152 万客户的个人信息泄露。【原文：A cyberattack in September may have caused the leak of the personal details of 1.52 million customers of Japan's Asahi Group , it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/personal-details-15-million-asahi-group-customers-may-have-been-leaked-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BV43FGGRWRM57LX4JGASI5RTQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 02:25:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元回落，奇异果跃升，利率走向分化]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美元走势疲软，美国感恩节假期前交易清淡，投资者转而关注来年美国的一系列降息措施。【原文：The dollar was on the back foot on Thursday, with trade thinned ahead of the U.S. Thanksgiving holiday and investors turning to the coming year where a series of U.S. interest rate cuts are priced in.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-retreats-kiwi-leaps-rate-direction-diverges-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEGHMIS4CFNMDIJWTPG7XCZNYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 02:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达在给分析师的备忘录中反驳批评者的意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界上最有价值的公司英伟达（Nvidia）在华尔街和社交媒体上发起了一场信息攻势，以回击对其 4.5 万亿美元估值（低于历史上的 5 万亿美元）的质疑。【原文：Nvidia , the world's most valuable company, has gone on the defensive against skeptics of its $4.5 trillion valuation, down from a historic $5 trillion, by waging an information campaign on Wall Street and social media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nvidia-rebuts-critics-memo-analysts-amid-pushback-campaign-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBYUY26OMBIR3JGY4OZWV6HD6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 02:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰停火有望释放俄罗斯供应，油价因此下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四下跌，原因是人们预期乌克兰与俄罗斯将实现停火，这将为西方解除对俄罗斯供应的制裁铺平道路，但由于美国感恩节假期，油价交投仍将清淡。【原文：Oil prices fell on Thursday on expectations of a Ukraine‑Russia ceasefire which could pave the way for the unwinding of Western sanctions against Russian supply, though trading was set to remain thin due to the U.S. Thanksgiving holiday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-drop-expectations-ceasefire-ukraine-unlocking-russian-supply-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQRIGZQ4MJM3ZHXO4R5TMNV7P4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 01:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市因美国降息希望而上涨，日元仍处于干预区间]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲股市上涨，美元走软，原因是市场对美联储下月降息的预期不断增强，而日元仍是市场关注的焦点，交易商正在权衡年底前加息的前景。【原文：Asian stocks rose on Thursday and the dollar was soft on growing expectations of an interest rate cut from the Federal Reserve next month, while the yen stayed in the spotlight, with traders weighing the prospect of a rate hike before the end of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5RIWE4CEBZOJ7MUMQRATNXER2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 01:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示数以千计的美国用户无法使用 Netflix]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Downdetector.com 网站报道，流媒体平台 Netflix 周三在美国有数千名用户遭遇宕机。【原文：Streaming platform Netflix is down for thousands of users in the United States on Wednesday, according to Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-down-thousands-us-users-downdetector-shows-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSNORQJX3BKNZGBQY4LY66O5WE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 01:16:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰住房问题引发对可靠投资战略的怀疑，拖累经济发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰房地产市场剧烈的繁荣-萧条周期给许多新西兰人和投资者留下了伤痕，经济也在挣扎着起火，这让曾经值得信赖的创造财富的策略变成了一段不安的时期，未来的回报可能会更少。【原文：A dramatic boom-bust cycle in New Zealand's housing market has left many Kiwis and investors scarred and an economy struggling to fire, turning what was once a trusted strategy for creating wealth into a period of unease and potentially smaller future returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nzs-housing-funk-sows-doubts-reliable-investment-strategy-drags-economy-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETKKR7NUKJPNHKYXU5A3AN5HXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔否认台积电高管泄露商业机密的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔公司周四否认了台湾芯片制造商台积电关于该公司一名高管罗伟仁泄露商业机密的指控。【原文：Intel on Thursday denied allegations by Taiwanese chipmaker TSMC that one of the U.S. firm's executives, Wei-Jen Lo, had leaked trade secrets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/intel-denies-tsmc-allegations-that-executive-leaked-trade-secrets-2025-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FW55SFLX5NO6XG56COHC7SQVYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:16:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊赢得纽约劳动法禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周三向亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）发出初步禁令，阻止纽约州公共就业关系委员会执行一项新的州法律，该在线零售商认为该法律试图非法管理私营部门的劳资关系。【原文：A federal judge on Wednesday granted Amazon.com a preliminary injunction to block the New York State Public Employment Relations Board from enforcing a new state law that the online retailer considers an attempt to illegally regulate private-sector labor relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/amazon-wins-injunction-against-new-york-labor-law-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAWOCUBY6BOIFKV6YDJOM2V3F4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 22:23:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智能橱窗 "制造商 View 前首席财务官与美国证券交易委员会达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[View 公司前首席财务官就美国证券交易委员会的一项诉讼达成和解，该诉讼称他因疏忽而允许公司低报更换有缺陷的 "智能窗户 "的成本。【原文：The former chief financial officer of View settled a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission lawsuit claiming he negligently allowed the company to understate the cost of replacing defective "smart windows."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/ex-cfo-smart-window-maker-view-settles-with-us-sec-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6JOHPLOEBMB3GCUQALEZK2WQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 22:20:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 火鸡节前公牛当道]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYUOM4UPDRNERH52NFDRMCPIYU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flutter 称 2026 年英国博彩税将使息税折旧及摊销前利润减少 3.2 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[FanDuel 的所有者 Flutter Entertainment 周三表示，英国政府提高在线游戏税的计划将在 2026 财年对其调整后的息税折旧摊销前利润（EBITDA）造成约 3.2 亿美元的冲击，并在 2027 财年造成 5.4 亿美元的冲击，然后才能减轻影响。【原文：FanDuel-owner Flutter Entertainment said on Wednesday the UK government's plans to raise online gaming taxes will hit its adjusted EBITDA by about $320 million in fiscal 2026 and $540 million in 2027 before it can mitigate the impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/flutter-says-uk-gambling-duties-hit-ebitda-by-320-million-2026-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMBB6QNY65OSTNLJ7CULKERDBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 21:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉吉公司表示不打算关闭美国牛肉加工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[在肉类加工企业泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）宣布将关闭内布拉斯加州一家大型工厂几天之后，嘉吉公司周三表示，该公司目前没有关闭其美国牛肉加工厂的计划，因为肉类加工行业正在努力应对牛类供应紧张的问题。【原文：Cargill Inc has no immediate plans to close its U.S. beef processing plants, the company said on Wednesday, days after meatpacker Tyson Foods announced it would shutter a major Nebraska facility as the industry grapples with tight cattle supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cargill-says-it-does-not-plan-close-us-beef-processing-plants-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3A67B2KYXJOVXFV3DY2V2SSZTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 21:50:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司赢得价值 47 亿美元的 AH-64E 阿帕奇直升机外国军用合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周三表示，根据美国陆军授予的一份价值近 47 亿美元的对外军售合同，该公司将为国际客户生产 AH-64E 阿帕奇攻击直升机，其中包括为波兰武装部队生产 96 架。【原文：Boeing said on Wednesday it will produce AH-64E Apache attack helicopters for international customers, including 96 for the Polish Armed Forces, under a Foreign Military Sales contract worth nearly $4.7 billion awarded by the U.S. Army.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-wins-47-billion-foreign-military-contract-ah-64e-apache-helicopters-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUXHRKQOJJKXXM75O4DALTWMTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 21:45:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，UPS 飞机坠毁后，MD-11 机队的停飞不可能在 2026 年前结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周三告诉路透社记者，本月一架MD-11喷气式客机坠毁，导致大量飞机停飞，这种情况不太可能在2026年之前结束。【原文：The vast grounding of MD-11 jets after a fiery crash this month involving one of the planes, is unlikely to end before 2026, a source told Reuters on Wednesday, driving industry demand for alternatives as peak delivery season kicks off this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/md-11-fleet-grounding-after-ups-crash-unlikely-end-before-2026-source-says-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5L7ISZ5P5O5TITZJLC7EBVAVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者称，哈塞特执掌美联储可能给美元带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国债券市场对白宫经济顾问凯文-哈塞特（Kevin Hassett）成为下一任美联储主席的前景保持镇定的背后，隐藏着一种令人不安的担忧，即他对降息的偏好将削弱美元。【原文：Beneath the U.S. bond markets' composure around the prospect of White House economic adviser Kevin Hassett becoming the next Federal Reserve chair lies a niggling worry that his bias for interest rate cuts will undermine the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hassett-fed-helm-could-pressure-dollar-investors-say-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DOTCJIJBBOTZM3HANLCO6JRYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉堡王 Whopper 广告诉讼被美国法官驳回]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官对起诉汉堡王为其 Whopper 三明治做广告的顾客作出了让步，称他们的索赔要求过于悬殊，不足以证明有理由进行全国范围的集体诉讼。【原文：A federal judge dealt a setback to customers suing Burger King over advertising for its Whopper sandwiches, saying their claims were too disparate to justify certifying a nationwide class action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/lawsuit-over-burger-kings-whopper-ads-set-back-by-us-judge-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXK2MIT2XNJPTKHRVS5WUDQWVY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大推出更多措施保护受关税影响的钢铁和木材行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社渥太华11月26日电）加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周三表示，加拿大将提供更多支持，帮助钢铁和木材行业应对美国关税，并创造一个国内市场。【原文：OTTAWA, Nov 26 (Reuters) - Canada will offer more support to help the steel and lumber industries deal with U.S. tariffs and create a domestic market, Prime Minister Mark Carney said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/canada-unveils-more-measures-protect-tariff-hit-steel-lumber-sectors-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2P43J4IDBOQVGLRN5FULKHOSQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅恩交易受阻后，澳大利亚并购将面临更高的反向中断费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[律师表示，在梅恩制药公司（Mayne Pharma）4.34 亿美元的收购失败后，如果未获得监管部门的批准，澳大利亚公司的外国竞购者可能需要支付更高的反向收购费。【原文：Foreign bidders for Australian companies could be liable for higher reverse break fees if regulatory approval is not received, in the wake of the failed $434 million takeover of Mayne Pharma , lawyers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/after-blocked-mayne-deal-australia-mas-set-higher-reverse-break-fees-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYSCUVXBZVPDXESQ5OQMTZZVQ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥银行下调 2025 年经济增长预期，上调 2026 年初通胀预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥银行周三将墨西哥经济增长预期下调至接近于零，因为该银行董事会押注该国疲软的经济将有助于将粘稠的通货膨胀率降至目标值。【原文：The Bank of Mexico cut its growth forecast for Mexico's economy to close to zero on Wednesday, amid bets by the bank's board that the country's weak economy will help bring sticky inflation to target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-mexico-lowers-2025-growth-forecast-raises-inflation-estimates-early-2026-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFC42WJCABL4LKD3KV5GLEBDCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[米色报告》显示，美联储下次会议前美国经济活动变化不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国中央银行周三表示，最近几周美国经济活动变化不大，但美联储12个地区中约有一半地区就业疲软，消费者支出下降，这可能加剧了人们对劳动力市场疲软的担忧。【原文：U.S. economic activity was little changed in recent weeks, though employment was weaker in about half of the Federal Reserve's 12 districts and consumer spending declined, the U.S. central bank said on Wednesday, likely reinforcing concerns about labor market softening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-economic-activity-little-changed-ahead-next-fed-meeting-beige-book-report-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOLN4R43OBO4BN53WS2CAVEB2Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜耳为巴西农民推出新型大豆种子]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国企业集团拜耳公司周三表示，它将向世界上最大的油籽出口国和生产国巴西的农民销售一种名为 Intacta 5+ 的大豆新产品，以寻求在这个南美国家永久使用转基因种子。【原文：German conglomerate Bayer on Wednesday said it will sell a new soybean product called Intacta 5+ for farmers in Brazil, the world's largest exporter and producer of the oilseed, as it seeks to perpetuate the use of genetically engineered seeds in the South American country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bayer-unveils-new-soy-seed-brazils-farmers-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7DS64LXZBN3PIJSJE35A5U7EU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：五角大楼建议将阿里巴巴、百度和比亚迪列入援助中国军方名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，五角大楼认为阿里巴巴集团、百度公司和比亚迪公司应被列入援助中国军方的公司名单。【原文：The Pentagon has concluded that Alibaba Group Holding , Baidu Inc and BYD Co should be added to a list of companies that aid the Chinese military, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/pentagon-suggests-adding-alibaba-baidu-byd-list-aiding-china-military-bloomberg-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4H66IAH5QNIGFO2SAPUFFMY3TE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:11:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国钻井商四周来首次削减石油和天然气钻井平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周三在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周削减了石油和天然气钻井平台的数量，这是四周以来的首次。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut the number of oil and natural gas rigs operating for the first time in four weeks, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-drillers-cut-oil-gas-rigs-first-time-four-weeks-baker-hughes-says-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWTQVB6Q6RLRTDKF5TNZSPHKOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[证券交易委员会不得让加密公司 "绕过 "规则，证券交易所称]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些证券交易所在本周致美国监管机构的一封信中表示，美国证券交易委员会可能计划给予加密货币公司销售 "代币化 "股票的监管豁免，这有可能损害投资者的利益。【原文：The Securities and Exchange Commission's possible plan to grant crypto companies relief from regulation to sell "tokenised" stocks risks harming investors, a group of stock exchanges said in a letter to the U.S. regulator this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/sec-must-not-let-crypto-companies-bypass-rules-stock-exchanges-say-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXIMZ3RYUVJKXGKNESWRL76T4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 18:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲立法者寻求在欧盟范围内规定使用人工智能聊天机器人和社交媒体的最低年龄]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲议会周三批准了一项不具约束力的决议，呼吁将访问社交媒体和人工智能聊天机器人的默认最低年龄设定为 16 岁，以确保 "适龄的在线参与"。【原文：The European Parliament on Wednesday approved a non-binding resolution which calls for a default minimum age of 16 to access social media and AI chatbots to ensure "age-appropriate online engagement".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/european-lawmakers-seek-eu-wide-minimum-age-access-ai-chatbots-social-media-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4W4G62PTBNKBLDRNOINKOQVTA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 18:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会称黑客劫持美国无线电设备发送虚假警报和脏话]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（Federal Communications Commission）周三表示，黑客正在劫持美国的无线电传输设备，播放虚假的紧急信息和淫秽语言。【原文：Hackers are hijacking U.S. radio transmission equipment to broadcast bogus emergency messages and obscene language, the Federal Communications Commission said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fcc-says-hackers-hijack-us-radio-gear-send-fake-alerts-obscenities-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAODVRPPLBM73MGTQQS3X7U6TU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，苹果对印度反垄断处罚法提出异议，面临 380 亿美元罚款风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社在德里高等法院看到的一份法庭文件显示，苹果公司正在挑战印度新的反垄断处罚法，根据该法，这家美国公司可能面临高达 380 亿美元的罚款。【原文：Apple is challenging India's new antitrust penalty law under which the U.S. company could potentially face a fine of up to $38 billion, a court filing at the Delhi High Court, seen by Reuters, shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apple-contests-indias-antitrust-penalty-law-with-risk-38-billion-fine-filing-2025-11-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LE5PZB5Z4VNVRFM5CON3IG3RVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:45:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>