<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 08:36:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 08:36:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪承包商否认巴西当局 "类似奴役条件 "的说法]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车生产商比亚迪的承包商锦江集团周四表示，巴西当局将其员工描述为奴隶的说法与事实完全不符。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle producer BYD's contractor Jinjiang Group stated on Thursday that the Brazilian authorities' portrayal of their employees as enslaved is completely inconsistent with the facts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-contractor-denies-slavery-like-conditions-claims-by-brazilian-authorities-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSWJ3DDJWFPYDPTCTX3I626CCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 08:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国新世界集团将与阿里巴巴国际公司成立合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国零售商新世界集团（Shinsegae Group）的关联公司易买得（E-Mart）周四表示，该集团计划与阿里巴巴国际公司（Alibaba International）成立一家合资企业。【原文：South Korean retailer Shinsegae Group plans to set up a joint venture with Alibaba International, Shinsegae affiliate E-Mart said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/south-koreas-shinsegae-set-up-joint-venture-with-alibaba-international-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV5QMQX7ENONBJEJO2ABR6MJ7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将 2023 年 GDP 上调至 17.73 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家统计局局长康义周四在北京举行的新闻发布会上表示，中国将2023年的国内生产总值（GDP）上调了2.7%，达到129.4万亿元人民币（合17.73万亿美元）。【原文：China on Thursday revised up its 2023 gross domestic product (GDP) by 2.7% to 129.4 trillion yuan ($17.73 trillion), the head of the National Bureau of Statistics Kang Yi said at a press conference in Beijing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-revises-up-2023-gdp-1773-trillion-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GDMYAMN3ZNXHL75Q4E4DPVMPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:38:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本新日铁修改收购美国钢铁公司的截止日期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新日铁公司（Nippon Steel）周四表示，该公司修改了收购美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）的截止日期，并表示相信此次收购将保护和发展这家美国公司。【原文：Japan's Nippon Steel said on Thursday it revised the closing date for its purchase of U.S. Steel, expressing confidence that the acquisition will protect and grow the American company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japans-nippon-steel-revises-closing-date-us-steel-acquisition-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6FPGZK7BBI2FMVD3GECBLGVHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元保持坚挺，亚洲股市节日大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲股市在假日清淡的交易中小幅上涨，延续了本周早些时候的涨势，但没有什么消息或数据能改变其走势，而美元则在两年高点附近徘徊。【原文：Asia shares rose slightly in holiday-thinned trade on Thursday, extending gains from earlier in the week with little news or data in the way to alter their direction of travel, while the dollar was perched near a two-year high.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5TQBUFGX5N4HJRWX6WT6GQI7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因希望中国采取更多刺激措施而走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四在清淡的假日交易中走高，原因是全球最大的石油进口国中国希望采取更多财政刺激措施，同时美国原油库存预期下降也为油价提供了支撑。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Thursday in thin holiday trading, driven by hopes for additional fiscal stimulus in China, the world's biggest oil importer, while an anticipated decline in U.S. crude inventories also provided support.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-edge-higher-hopes-more-china-stimulus-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVKGSWBTURNCLIO5OFQGOZDR2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯财政部长称俄罗斯在对外贸易中使用比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯财政部长安东-西卢安诺夫（Anton Siluanov）周三表示，在允许使用比特币和其他数字货币以对抗西方制裁的立法改革之后，俄罗斯公司已开始在国际支付中使用比特币和其他数字货币。【原文：Russian companies have begun using bitcoin and other digital currencies in international payments following legislative changes that allowed such use in order to counter Western sanctions, Finance Minister Anton Siluanov said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/russia-is-using-bitcoin-foreign-trade-finance-minister-says-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QK47K5BTENIS5BRXMNQVJAPMJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 11:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将欧盟白兰地反倾销调查延长三个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周三表示，将把对原产于欧盟的白兰地的反倾销调查延长三个月，少于之前指导意见允许的全部延长时间。【原文：China's commerce ministry said on Wednesday it would extend its anti-dumping investigation into brandy originating from the European Union by three months, less than the full extension allowed under its previous guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-extends-eu-brandy-anti-dumping-investigation-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSARECUQOZPAFLJ4Y2JN3MUVUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 07:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，台湾阻止了优步斥资 9.5 亿美元收购 Foodpanda 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三援引台湾官方中央社（CNA）的报道称，出于反竞争考虑，台湾已阻止优步科技公司（Uber Technologies）以 9.5 亿美元收购外卖英雄（Delivery Hero）在台湾的 Foodpanda 业务。【原文：Taiwan has blocked Uber Technologies' $950 million purchase of Delivery Hero's Foodpanda business on the island because of anti-competition concerns, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing Taiwan's official Central News Agency (CNA).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/taiwan-blocks-ubers-950-mln-foodpanda-deal-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JV7PGUMKRLXFL3OE5MIV42YVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国骗子借鉴 "乌贼游戏 "向负债者下手]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国的 "鱿鱼游戏 "中，骗子们以奖金、债务重组和其他并不总是如约而至的计划为诱饵，欺骗经济不景气中的经济困难者。【原文：In China's take on Squid Game, fraudsters are preying on the financially distressed in a slumping economy with promises of prize money, debt restructuring and other schemes that are not always what is promised.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-tricksters-take-cue-squid-game-prey-indebted-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LENXHRT37FKCVGVLALIS37PNC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高管称新日铁收购美国钢铁公司的计划在炼钢领域获得支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新日铁公司总裁今井忠志（Tadashi Imai）周三告诉记者，日本新日铁公司收购美国钢铁公司的提议正在美国钢厂所在地区得到支持。【原文：Japan's Nippon Steel is seeing support for its proposal to acquire U.S. Steel in the regions of the United States where steel mills are located, Nippon Steel's President Tadashi Imai told reporters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steels-us-steel-takeover-plan-has-support-steelmaking-areas-executive-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2VHSEDEBRIN5C7HFPFXI4BGSU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 05:32:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管销量上升，丰田全球产量仍连续第 10 个月下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本汽车制造商丰田汽车公司周三表示，尽管由于美国和中国的强劲需求，其全球销量连续第二个月增长，但该公司 11 月份的全球产量已连续第 10 个月下降。【原文：Toyota Motor's global production decreased for a 10th straight month in November, the Japanese carmaker said on Wednesday, although its worldwide sales grew for the second consecutive month on solid demand in the United States and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-global-production-down-10th-month-despite-rising-sales-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYGDVKPVQ5IT7BWJMB6ATVV2UM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 04:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，KKR、贝恩对 Seven & i 资产的出价从 48 亿美元到 76 亿美元不等]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，包括 KKR 和贝恩资本在内的私募股权公司在对日本 Seven &amp; i 控股公司非核心资产的第一轮竞购中，出价从约 7,500 亿日元（48 亿美元）到约 1.2 万亿日元（76 亿美元）不等。【原文：Private equity firms including KKR and Bain Capital offered from around 750 billion yen ($4.8 billion) to around 1.2 trillion yen ($7.6 billion) in a first round of bidding for the non-core assets of Japan's Seven &amp; i Holdings , according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-bain-bids-ranged-48-bln-76-bln-seven-i-assets-sources-say-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHVZYLIFCZNZJM2UR6CB3WRCOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:46:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[计划草案显示，日本下一财年将编制创纪录的 7,340 亿美元预算]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社（Reuters）看到的一份计划草案显示，由于社会保障和偿债成本增加，日本政府将为从 4 月开始的财政年度编制创纪录的 7,340 亿美元预算，这将使日本成为世界上债务最沉重的工业国。【原文：Japan's government is set to compile a record $734 billion budget for the fiscal year from April due to larger social security and debt-servicing costs, adding to the industrial world's heaviest debt, a draft plan seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-government-plans-record-730-bln-budget-next-fiscal-year-jiji-reports-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUONPCYFVJIUNDYH22EPJECDCQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 02:50:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本喜剧演员变身投资家，与前高盛 "股票怪才 "共同发起基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[从表面上看，作为日本最新股票基金的幕后主脑，这两人似乎很难让人产生信心：一个曾是喜剧演员，另一个则是千篇一律的 "宅男 "怪才。【原文：On the face of it, the duo hardly seem fit to inspire confidence as the brains behind Japan's newest stock fund: one, a former comedian and the other, every bit the stereotypical "otaku" geek.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-comedian-turned-investor-launches-fund-with-ex-goldman-stock-geek-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMJZYJH4WVNYBGH6VFYEOYVR7U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 01:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚最低工资将增长 9.54%，2025 年达到每月 323 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚总统古斯塔沃-佩特罗（Gustavo Petro）周二表示，哥伦比亚的最低工资将在 2025 年提高 9.54%，在政府、商业协会和工会之间未能达成协议后，他通过法令宣布了这一涨幅。【原文：Colombia's minimum wage will increase by 9.54% in 2025, Colombia's President Gustavo Petro said on Tuesday, announcing the hike by decree after a deal was not reached between the government, business associations and workers unions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-minimum-wage-increase-954-323-per-month-2025-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NW5KNPYPMFLKTCNC4ARRCBSLQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 21:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道墨西哥央行副行长称 2 月可能考虑降息 25 或 50 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥央行副行长乔纳森-希思（Jonathan Heath）告诉路透社记者，墨西哥央行董事会可能会在 2 月份的下一次决策中讨论降息 25 个基点或 50 个基点的问题，尽管他警告说美国贸易的不确定性正在增加。【原文：Mexico's central bank board could discuss a rate cut of either 25 basis points or 50 basis points in its next decision in February, Deputy Governor Jonathan Heath told Reuters, even as he warned of growing uncertainty regarding U.S. trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/mexico-central-bank-could-weigh-rate-cut-25-or-50-bps-february-deputy-governor-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XP7BYDCC7ZKATJMTCH43646ZBE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 17:35:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田将为特朗普就职典礼捐款 100 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[在底特律的福特汽车公司和通用汽车公司表示将提供相同数额的捐款后一天，丰田汽车公司发言人周二表示，北美丰田汽车公司将为当选总统唐纳德-特朗普 1 月 20 日的就职典礼捐款 100 万美元。【原文：Toyota Motor of North America is donating $1 million to President-elect Donald Trump's Jan. 20 inauguration, a company spokesman said on Tuesday, a day after Detroit's Ford Motor and General Motors , said they would give the same amount.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/toyota-is-donating-1-million-trumps-inauguration-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33NR7EFHD5P2DHMQSNH7V5MHXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 15:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者称，塔吉特的假日广告推广只能到此为止]]></title><description><![CDATA[在多年来竞争最激烈的假日季，美国主要零售商塔吉特（Target）和沃尔玛（Walmart）正在加大广告投入，以便通过短视频应用 TikTok 和流媒体平台接触购物者。【原文：In the most competitive holiday season in years, major U.S. retailers Target and Walmart are spending more on ads to reach shoppers on short-video app TikTok and streaming platforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/targets-holiday-advertising-push-will-only-take-it-so-far-investors-say-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAVX5QMRVRMR5IBCOFWMYQOSLY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 15:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果寻求为谷歌在搜索案中支付的十亿美元辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司已要求参加谷歌即将在美国举行的在线搜索反垄断审判，并表示不能依靠谷歌来维护收入分成协议，因为谷歌将其 Safari 浏览器作为默认搜索引擎，每年会给这家 iPhone 制造商带来数十亿美元的收入。【原文：Apple has asked to participate in Google's upcoming U.S. antitrust trial over online search, saying it cannot rely on Google to defend revenue-sharing agreements that send the iPhone maker billions of dollars each year for making Google the default search engine on its Safari browser.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-seeks-defend-googles-billion-dollar-payments-search-case-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5HJNP7Y6RLQTMNFLOARUBYZNU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 15:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国营媒体称伊朗解除对 WhatsApp 和 Google Play 的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据伊朗国家媒体周二报道，伊朗当局已经解除了对 Meta 即时通讯平台 WhatsApp 和 Google Play 的禁令，作为减少互联网限制的第一步。【原文：Iranian authorities have lifted a ban on Meta's instant messaging platform WhatsApp and Google Play as a first step to scale back internet restrictions, Iranian state media reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/iran-lifts-ban-whatsapp-google-play-state-media-says-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3AQZBPQ4ZICZCOPPMLLZCYFAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:43:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[减肥药数据令人失望，散户投资者买入诺和（Novo）跌停股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Vanda Research 公司称，美国散户投资者流入诺和诺德公司的资金周五激增了 32 倍，原因是这家丹麦制药商的肥胖症药物数据弱于预期，提供了一个难得的逢低买入机会。【原文：U.S. retail investor fund flows into Novo Nordisk surged 32-fold on Friday, as the Danish drugmaker's weaker-than-expected obesity drug data offered a rare dip-buying opportunity, according to Vanda Research.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/retail-investors-buy-novo-dip-after-disappointing-weight-loss-drug-data-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHWUZMABJZPTHHWKCKUQ2MLZ4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:38:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国药明康德将在美国限制措施下出售先进疗法部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国药明康德（WuXi AppTec）周二表示，其子公司已与美国私募股权公司 Altaris LLC 签订协议，出售其细胞和基因治疗生产部门药明康德先进疗法公司（WuXi Advanced Therapies），出售金额未披露。【原文：China's WuXi AppTec said on Tuesday its subsidiaries have signed a deal with U.S.-based private equity firm Altaris LLC for the sale of its cell and gene therapy manufacturing unit, WuXi Advanced Therapies, for an undisclosed sum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-wuxi-sell-advanced-therapies-unit-us-private-equity-firm-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SVRQLNXK5P3NKY4GBBDN742XY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行和商业团体就压力测试框架起诉美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国银行和企业的团体周二表示，他们将起诉美联储，挑战他们所称的 "压力测试框架的不透明之处"。【原文：Groups representing U.S. banks and businesses said on Tuesday they were suing the Federal Reserve to challenge what they described as the "opaque aspects of the stress testing framework."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-bank-business-groups-sue-fed-over-stress-test-framework-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFA5UY4UVVJFNC66LRGKYW7QJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本田和日产的合作需要双方都腾不出的时间：时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[本田和日产希望从潜在的合并中获得巨大利益，以创建世界第三大汽车集团，但来自中国的激烈竞争让人怀疑它们能否及时实现合并。【原文：Honda and Nissan expect big benefits from their potential merger to create the world's third-largest auto group but intense competition from China raises questions about whether they can make it work in time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-nissan-tie-up-requires-something-neither-can-spare-time-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRV3SPR4ZNKIDBSOLGKIGCNY4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 13:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据CNBC报道，大型银行计划就年度压力测试起诉美国联邦储备委员会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周二援引一位熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道，各大银行正计划就美联储进行的年度压力测试起诉该监管机构。【原文：Major banks are planning to sue the U.S. Federal Reserve over the annual stress tests conducted by the regulator, CNBC reported on Tuesday, citing a source familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/big-banks-planning-sue-us-fed-over-annual-stress-tests-cnbc-reports-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRF4KJVYZBMLBDXGHJETXCNAVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 13:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司在繁忙的平安夜停飞所有美国航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国航空公司（American Airlines）周二称，由于一个不明的技术问题，该公司停飞了其在美国的所有航班。【原文：American Airlines on Tuesday grounded all its flights in the U.S. due to an unspecified technical issue, according to the company and a regulatory notice, disrupting the travel plans of thousands of passengers set to fly out for Christmas Eve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-says-experiencing-technical-issue-with-its-flights-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBOTKDA4KBPB3PMMPXYB3QQRYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 12:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圣诞节前夕交易缩短，期货价格低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周二缩短的交易时段之前，美国股指期货依然低迷，华尔街在结束连续第二年上涨之前进入了一个历史上强劲的时期。【原文：U.S. stock index futures remained subdued ahead of Tuesday's shortened trading session, with Wall Street entering a historically strong period before rounding off its second consecutive year of gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-muted-before-shortened-christmas-eve-trading-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVLSOJ5VORPLHGQ7LIMWAPFO6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 10:56:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称星巴克罢工将在平安夜扩大到 300 多家美国门店]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克工会表示，星巴克美国门店的罢工将于周二扩大到 300 多家门店，预计将有 5000 多名工人离职，为期五天的停工将于平安夜晚些时候结束。【原文：A strike at Starbucks' U.S. stores will expand to over 300 stores on Tuesday, with more than 5,000 workers expected to walk off the job, before the five-day work stoppage ends later on Christmas Eve, the workers' union said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-strike-expand-over-300-us-stores-christmas-eve-union-says-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6EJGCNHDZMHJHQVHB2PIAQ4YA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 06:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国计划明年发行 4110 亿美元特别国债]]></title><description><![CDATA[此举正值北京准备减轻唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）1 月份重返白宫时美国对中国进口商品加征关税的预期带来的打击之际。【原文：The move comes as Beijing prepares to soften the blow from an expected increase in US tariffs on Chinese imports when Donald Trump returns to the White House in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-plans-411-bln-special-treasury-bond-issuance-next-year-sources-say-2024-12-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVAYMC4KPRIKLEWJZUUV22VTAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>