<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:40:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:40:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Shopee 所有者 Sea 季度收入略低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，东南亚科技公司 Sea Ltd 第一季度营收略低于预期，原因是面对不确定的经济形势，消费者减少了在其电子商务平台上的消费。【原文：Southeast Asian technology firm Sea Ltd narrowly missed estimates for first-quarter revenue on Tuesday, as consumers dialed back spending on its e-commerce platform in the face of an uncertain economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/shopee-owner-sea-narrowly-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRASHDECEBPWNA65J7S2I24CLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:34:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽瓦克机场混乱，美国联合航空公司首当其冲]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽瓦克机场是美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）最大的枢纽机场之一，也是美国最繁忙的机场之一，由于该机场不断发生故障，航班延误和取消的情况不断增加，美国联合航空公司正面临着经济损失和潜在的长期声誉损害。【原文：United Airlines is facing a financial hit and potential long-term reputational harm as flight delays and cancellations pile up due to ongoing disruptions at Newark airport - one of its largest hubs and among the busiest in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-bears-brunt-newark-airport-chaos-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D53ECQHA2ZNCZLTPRAQO5YPABM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:31:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消防车价格高达 200 万美元，美国消防员要求进行反垄断调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的消防员工会要求反垄断机构调查生产消防车的公司，称行业整合导致成本飙升，等待时间长达数年，危及消防员和公众。【原文：The largest firefighters' labor union in the U.S. is demanding antitrust authorities investigate the companies that make fire trucks, saying industry consolidation has led to skyrocketing costs and years-long wait times, endangering fire fighters and the public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/fire-truck-prices-hit-2-million-us-firefighters-demand-an-antitrust-probe-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5X32MTOHTJJA7I7C4UIHK5CCEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:12:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4 月份美国小型企业景气度进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[4 月份，美国小企业信心连续第四个月下降，报告职位空缺的企业主比例降至四年多来的最低水平，这可能暗示着劳动力市场的显著放缓。【原文：U.S. small-business confidence fell for a fourth straight month in April, with the share of owners reporting job openings declining to the lowest level in more than four years, potentially hinting at a significant labor market slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-small-business-sentiment-declines-further-april-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTNYDWA2WVK6BE7SNJ7TWB6D6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农民称，尽管贸易休战，巴西在中国大豆市场仍有优势]]></title><description><![CDATA[生产商们说，如果没有额外的让步，北京和华盛顿之间令人惊讶的关税暂停将无助于美国农民在中国获得大豆销售，因为头号供应国巴西仍然具有价格竞争优势。【原文：A surprising tariff pause between Beijing and Washington will not help U.S. farmers gain soy sales in China without additional concessions, producers said, because top-supplier Brazil still has a competitive price advantage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-farmers-say-brazil-still-has-edge-chinas-soybean-market-despite-trade-truce-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DP6OVHJ2JRIVLIZSRE2WAW6L6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行业称美国放宽杠杆率规定可支持国债市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行业乐观地认为，美国监管机构很快就会采取行动，改变他们为典型的安全投资预留的资本额，尤其是在上个月国债市场动荡之后。【原文：The banking industry is optimistic that U.S. regulators will soon move to change how much capital they set aside against typically safe investments, particularly after the turmoil in Treasury markets last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/banking-sector-says-easing-us-leverage-rules-could-support-treasury-market-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2I6WMNZONNLXJTAEXIXNJ7FPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉对最畅销的 Model Y SUV 进行更新换代的道路坎坷不平]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉的投资者曾寄希望于该公司旗舰紧凑型 SUV 的更新换代来重振销量。但是，Model Y 最低的融资价格和它的便捷供应表明，这种期望是不现实的。【原文：Tesla investors had pinned their hopes on a refresh of the company's flagship compact SUV to reinvigorate sales. But rock-bottom financing deals for the Model Y and its easy availability suggest that this expectation is unrealistic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-refresh-best-selling-model-y-suv-starts-rocky-road-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKLBZ7EDQ5ICRETEH4UUOIEZU4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易休战涨势消退，通胀数据成为焦点，美股期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周二下跌，在中美贸易休战推动的大幅反弹后回落，投资者将焦点转向可能影响货币政策前景的美国关键通胀数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were down on Tuesday, pulling back after a sharp rally fueled by a U.S.-China trade truce, as investors turned their focus to a key U.S. inflation reading that could shape the outlook for monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-down-trade-truce-rally-fades-inflation-data-focus-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Q654RI2SBJIDGJ45GEXKHOGWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗杰-费德勒支持的安踏上调年度销售预期，促销和新品发布刺激需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[罗杰-费德勒（Roger Federer）支持的On Holding公司周二上调了年度销售预期，并表示将不得不采取选择性定价，以减轻美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税影响。【原文：Roger Federer-backed On Holding raised its annual sales forecast on Tuesday and said it would have to undertake selective pricing to mitigate impacts from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/roger-federer-backed-raises-annual-sales-forecast-promotions-new-launches-fuel-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQKW74QMXFNGHAPFITWVN3SYUE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税不确定性挥之不去，中国对美出口商步履谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[邓金玲是一家向美国出口保温瓶的中国公司的经理，当她听到华盛顿削减对中国的惩罚性关税至少90天的消息时，她和丈夫打开了一瓶香槟。【原文：When she heard the news that Washington had slashed punitive tariffs on China for at least 90 days, Deng Jinling, manager of a Chinese company that exports thermos flasks to the U.S., popped open a bottle of champagne with her husband.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-exporters-us-tread-warily-tariff-uncertainties-linger-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5F37MBQWZLEFE4CI7K2VOWIKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的 JD.com 季度收入超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，中国电子商务巨头京东商城（JD.com）的季度营收超过了市场预期，这表明，即使美国加征关税和经济长期疲软影响了消费者情绪，该公司仍有稳定的需求。【原文：China's JD.com topped market estimates for quarterly revenue on Tuesday, in a sign the e-commerce giant saw steady demand even as U.S. tariffs and prolonged economic weakness weighed on consumer sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-jdcom-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3QLYXKF55OEJHBZPIUHU54YVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[订阅用户增加，腾讯音乐季度收入大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[受在线音乐服务用户增长的推动，腾讯音乐娱乐周二公布的第一季度营收超出分析师预期。【原文：Tencent Music Entertainment exceeded analysts' expectations for first-quarter revenue on Tuesday, driven by growth in subscribers for its online music services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tencent-music-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BKVTLWZLVOL7ACCQPHIPJMON4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:06:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德的芬克认为数万亿美元闲置，波动性持续存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）表示，在贸易战忧虑和美国经济不确定性的背景下，数万亿美元的金融火力被闲置在现金中，美国的赤字开始令投资者感到恐慌。【原文：BlackRock CEO Larry Fink says tens of trillions of dollars of financial firepower is sitting idle in cash amid trade war worries and uncertainty over the United States economy, whose deficits are beginning to spook investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrocks-fink-sees-trillions-dollars-idle-volatility-persists-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PZF3D2PGFKL5OPC6YDYSBRYTI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外国投资者 5 月重返亚洲股市，扭转了长期资金外流的局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对贸易谈判取得进展的乐观情绪缓解了对美国加征关税加剧全球经济放缓的担忧，5 月份迄今为止亚洲股市正在吸引外资，与今年前四个月的外资流出情况相比出现了急剧逆转。【原文：Asian equities are attracting foreign investments so far in May, marking a sharp reversal from outflows in the first four months of the year, as optimism over progress in trade talks has eased fears of U.S. tariffs fuelling a global economic slowdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/foreign-investors-return-asian-equities-may-reversing-prolonged-outflows-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XCSS7KDEJKWXIX6YBSTIGIYWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:45:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，2025 年美国的国外旅游支出将下降 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[据世界旅行和旅游理事会（World Travel and Tourism Council）称，由于政治和强势美元促使外国游客选择其他目的地，预计 2025 年美国的国际旅游支出将下降约 7%，即 125 亿美元。【原文：International travel spending in the United States is expected to decline about 7%, or $12.5 billion, in 2025 as politics and a strong dollar prompt foreign visitors to opt for other destinations, according to the World Travel and Tourism Council.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/foreign-travel-spending-us-decline-7-2025-report-says-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZS7TRWAQVOYRA72V72Z5TPUTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产汽车宣布新的成本节约措施，暂不公布 2025 财年业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本汽车制造商日产汽车公司周二宣布了一系列新的成本节约措施，包括再裁员1.1万人，并暂缓发布本年度至2026年3月的财务盈利预期。【原文：Japanese automaker Nissan announced on Tuesday a slate of new cost-saving measures including 11,000 more job cuts and held off on releasing financial earnings estimates for the current year through March 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-announces-new-cost-savings-measures-withholds-fy2025-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIDGQIPYLRKZ5MPXMR2WVGZUQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:18:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税闪电战达成交易，但未能解决全球贸易问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易专家和分析人士说，唐纳德-特朗普的关税闪电战正在达成一些初步协议，包括美国和中国的天价关税暂停90天，以及与英国达成一项有限的贸易协定，但这位美国总统远未重新平衡全球贸易流动。【原文：Donald Trump's tariff blitz is yielding some initial deals, including a 90-day pause in sky-high U.S. and Chinese duties and a limited trade pact with Britain, but the U.S. president is far from rebalancing global commerce flows, trade experts and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trumps-tariff-blitz-yields-deals-misses-global-trade-fix-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJUG2QCTFJORNL35A235HYFRVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 M&S 称客户信息在网络攻击中被窃取]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国零售商玛莎百货公司周二表示，一些客户的个人信息在网络攻击中被窃取，这次攻击使其在线业务瘫痪了三个多星期。【原文：British retailer Marks and Spencer said on Tuesday some personal customer information was taken in the cyber attack that has crippled its online operation for more than three weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uks-ms-says-customer-information-was-taken-cyber-attack-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHZGMK3XGRMIPGFIJ4SCCI5CYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行称，基金经理自 2006 年以来最看淡美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行周二发布的全球基金经理调查（FMS）显示，由于唐纳德-特朗普总统混乱的贸易政策降低了投资者对美国资产的偏好，5月份全球资产经理持有19年来最大的美元减持仓位。【原文：Global asset managers held their biggest underweight position in the dollar in 19 years in May, as President Donald Trump's chaotic trade policy cut investor appetite for U.S. assets, Bank of America's global fund manager survey (FMS) showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fund-managers-most-underweight-us-dollar-since-2006-bofa-says-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJOAEMLFGBMZBCIHDQZUPXG3SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚太贸易特使讨论关税时代的多边合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚太地区的贸易特使们本周将齐聚韩国，就多边合作展开讨论，而会谈正值各国争相应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税之际。【原文：Asia-Pacific trade envoys will gather this week in South Korea for discussions on multilateral cooperation, with talks taking place at a time when countries are scrambling to respond to U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asia-pacific-trade-envoys-discuss-multilateral-cooperation-tariff-era-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7MWLEFRRNJDFO7E3A3GG4TXDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:03:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球首家商业规模的电子甲醇工厂在丹麦开业]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，全球首家商业规模的电子甲醇工厂在丹麦投入运营，航运巨头马士基公司将购买部分产品，作为其集装箱船队的低排放燃料。【原文：The world's first commercial-scale e-methanol plant began operations in Denmark on Tuesday, with shipping giant Maersk set to buy part of the production as a low-emission fuel for its fleet of container ships.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/worlds-first-commercial-scale-e-methanol-plant-opens-denmark-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFR3OCFZGJL45JXZRHGKRETIFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国暂停对中国征收关税给 "中国加一 "国家带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美达成新协议，暂停互相征收天价关税，这迫使越南和墨西哥等制造业中心与美国达成更好的协议，以继续从全球生产商的 "中国加一 "战略中获益。【原文：A new U.S.-China agreement to pause sky-high tariffs on each other is pressuring manufacturing hubs such as Vietnam and Mexico to make their own, better deals with the U.S. to continue benefiting from a "China-plus-one" strategy by global producers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-tariff-pause-beijing-puts-pressure-china-plus-one-countries-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EDLZ36JIJLIXEYTGYAQWVTRF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:51:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税影响，本田全年利润下降 59%，推迟加拿大电动车计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税带来的不确定性，日本本田汽车公司预测本财年利润将下降59%，并表示将搁置在加拿大建立电动汽车供应链的计划。【原文：Japan's Honda Motor forecast a 59% profit decrease in the current financial year and said it would put on hold a plan to build an EV supply chain in Canada, amid the uncertainty stemming from U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-sees-full-year-profit-declining-59-us-tariffs-bite-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F36QBHGFJNZNBTPYPXYAHPBZ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本软银集团第四季度盈利 35 亿美元，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本投资集团软银集团（SoftBank Group）1-3 月净利润达 5,170 亿日元（约合 34.9 亿美元），原因是其持有的电信资产表现良好。【原文：Japanese investment conglomerate SoftBank Group booked a net profit of 517 billion yen ($3.49 billion) for January-March as its telecommunications holdings performed well.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/japans-softbank-group-books-35-billion-q4-profit-beats-estimates-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57BYQ2VDVZLUPKLIHPYDLPYKM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因看好贸易休战，高盛将美国经济衰退概率从 45% 下调至 35]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛将美国经济衰退预期从 45% 下调至 35%，成为首家下调预期的大型券商，此前与中国达成的临时关税休战协议提振了全球贸易战有所缓和的希望。【原文：Goldman Sachs cut its recession forecast for the U.S. to 35% from 45%, the first major brokerage to do so, after a temporary tariff truce with China boosted hopes of some easing in the global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-cuts-us-recession-odds-35-45-trade-truce-optimism-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FYRILQGMRJ3PIQ6KM2276JH5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:31:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果供应商 IQE 的年收入在市场预期之内]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国半导体公司 IQE 周二表示，预计其 2025 财年的收入将与市场预期一致，并补充说该公司正在关注出售其台湾业务的可能性。【原文：British semiconductor company IQE expects its revenue for the fiscal year 2025 to align with market expectations, the company said on Tuesday, adding that it was focusing on the potential sale of its Taiwan operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-chip-supplier-iqe-sees-fy25-revenue-within-market-view-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7FJRKLN6FKFZEIR3QKXL7UHAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:26:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称，作为重组的一部分，日产将暂停部分国内工厂的运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周二报道，作为业务重组努力的一部分，日本日产汽车公司决定暂停部分国内工厂的运营。【原文：Japan's Nissan Motor has decided to suspend operations at some domestic factories as part of a business restructuring effort, the Nikkei business daily reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-suspend-operations-some-domestic-plants-part-restructuring-nikkei-says-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JAVAJSZPBNXHEULBJ6SIVZIQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年，CATL 将在全球最大规模的上市活动中为银行提供低廉的费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[处理今年迄今为止全球最大上市交易的投资银行将获得远低于行业标准的承销费，在上市交易长期低迷之后，顾问们愿意忍受微薄的利润来赢得业务。【原文：Investment banks handling the world's largest listing so far this year are set to earn underwriting fees well below the industry norm, with advisers willing to endure skinny margins to win business following a prolonged slump in listings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/catl-offers-banks-slim-fees-worlds-largest-listing-2025-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KEZPBC4KVJCDLWOCBOMKXRHVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:26:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：美国贸易休战后，中国取消了对波音公司的交货禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，在与美国达成贸易休战协议后，中国取消了对航空公司接收波音飞机的禁令。【原文：China has removed a ban on airlines taking delivery of Boeing planes following a trade truce with the United States, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/china-removes-ban-boeing-deliveries-after-us-trade-truce-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MQ72IUWWVN37BCXSSUO54WT74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：在美国关税谈判之际，越南加大打击进口假冒产品的力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的文件显示，在美国指责越南是假冒伪劣和数字盗版的主要集散地并威胁要征收严厉的关税之后，越南正在加大打击假冒伪劣和数字盗版的力度。【原文：Vietnam is stepping up its fight against counterfeits and digital piracy after the United States accused the country of being a major hub for these illegal activities and threatened crippling tariffs, documents reviewed by Reuters show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/vietnam-cranks-up-fight-imported-counterfeits-amid-us-tariff-talks-2025-05-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWM4O7AU4RNDJJHBPZTJ7PHYQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>