<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:34:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:34:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[有报道称三菱汽车可能加入日产-本田联盟，三菱汽车股价随之上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，日本汽车制造商三菱汽车正在商谈加入日产汽车和本田汽车之间的联盟，该公司股价周一上涨超过 6%。【原文：Shares of Japanese automaker Mitsubishi Motors rose more than 6% on Monday following local media reports the company is in talks to join an alliance between Nissan Motor and Honda Motor .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mitsubishi-motors-shares-rise-after-reports-it-might-join-nissan-honda-alliance-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KX6MSKLPSRNAFK4WVA5ARPXUH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:23:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法院称碧桂园清盘听证会延期至明年 1 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港一家法院周一将碧桂园清盘呈请的听证会延期至 2025 年 1 月 20 日，为这家正试图敲定离岸债务重组计划的陷入困境的中国开发商提供了喘息的机会。【原文：A Hong Kong court on Monday adjourned a hearing into a petition seeking liquidation of Country Garden until Jan. 20, 2025, giving a breather to the embattled Chinese developer which is trying to finalise an offshore debt revamp plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/country-garden-liquidation-hearing-adjourned-january-next-year-court-says-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI77VVOVKFP67F4QY665A5UZXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:16:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟否决阿尔茨海默氏症药物后，日本卫材股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，日本卫材股价暴跌 11%，有望创下三年来最大单日跌幅，此前欧盟监管机构拒绝了这家制药商生产的治疗早期阿尔茨海默病的 Leqembi 药物。【原文：Shares of Japan's Eisai tumbled 11% and were on track for their biggest one-day fall in three years on Monday, after the European Union's regulator rejected the drugmaker's Leqembi treatment for early Alzheimer's disease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/shares-japans-eisai-tumble-after-eu-rejects-alzheimers-drug-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AZLAN6GSFO5ZNGDFEWFB5GIDQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经指数跳涨，日元走软，央行会议迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于股市回升削弱了对日元的避险需求，日元兑美元汇率在一周内飙升至 12 周以来的最强水平，周一有所回落。【原文：The yen ticked lower on Monday after a week when it surged to its strongest in 12 weeks against the dollar, as a recovery in equity markets sapped demand for the currency as a safe haven.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yen-eases-nikkei-jumps-central-bank-meetings-loom-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHSS25W7WVKZZL36CS67OJP64Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市反弹，期待美联储鸽派指引]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市反弹，因为本周将有大量财报发布，同时还将举行三场央行会议，美国和英国可能会开启宽松政策大门，而日本则可能会提高借贷成本，向 "正常化 "迈出一步。【原文：Asian shares bounced on Monday ahead of a week packed with earnings and a trio of central bank meetings that could see the United States and UK open the door to easing, while Japan might lift borrowing costs in a step toward "normality".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6OBTJ5LHJIWLHPC3NSVC4RXNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:47:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国准备为受支付延迟影响的电子商务供应商提供支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部周一表示，韩国金融当局将向因最近电子商务平台延迟付款而陷入困境的小企业提供至少 5600 亿韩元（约合 4.0455 亿美元）的流动性支持。【原文：South Korea's financial authorities will provide at least 560 billion won ($404.55 million) of liquidity support to small businesses having trouble due to recent payment delays by e-commerce platforms, the finance ministry said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/south-korea-prepares-support-e-commerce-vendors-hit-by-payment-delays-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASTV7SZ6XZI47DK3OHYIQO4YO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:35:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戈兰高地遭火箭弹袭击后，人们担心中东冲突扩大，油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列和美国指责黎巴嫩武装组织真主党在以色列占领的戈兰高地发动火箭弹袭击，人们担心中东冲突会扩大，因此油价周一上涨，收窄了上周的跌幅。【原文：Oil prices rose on Monday, paring last week's loss, on fears of a widening conflict in the Middle East following a rocket strike in the Israeli-occupied Golan Heights, which Israel and the United States blamed on Lebanese armed group Hezbollah.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-rise-fears-wider-middle-east-conflict-after-rocket-strike-golan-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHX7VDISRRLG5EDCHPWLJG526Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:31:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚银行监管机构表示不会放宽住房贷款规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚银行业监管机构周一表示，考虑到利率和经济前景的不确定性，该机构将保留其严格的住房贷款规定，因为人们担心金融系统的整体风险水平仍然较高。【原文：Australia's banking regulator on Monday said it would retain its strict home loan lending rules amid concern that the level of overall risk to the financial system remained elevated, taking into account an uncertain interest rate and economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-banking-regulator-says-it-will-not-ease-home-lending-rules-2024-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NEL6UMQJL5LIHKPNE5OX4TXFBM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行战胜通缩为加息周期铺平道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士和分析师称，日本央行正在为稳步加息时代的到来做好准备，声称在与通货紧缩的长期斗争中取得了胜利，并对过去的政策进行了一次重要的回顾，指出了消费者行为的重大转变。【原文：The Bank of Japan is setting the stage for an era of steady interest rate hikes by claiming victory in its long battle with deflation, sources and analysts say, in a major review of past policy that nods to significant consumer behaviour shifts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/bojs-victory-lap-deflation-paves-way-rate-hike-cycle-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCK6Y5LA4JLGLP37Y55UQX7HAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报道称前罗克韦尔柯林斯首席执行官正被考虑出任波音公司首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《航空周刊》周日援引业内官员的话报道，前罗克韦尔柯林斯公司总裁凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）已加入波音公司正在认真考虑的下一任首席执行官外部竞争者名单。【原文：Former Rockwell Collins chief Kelly Ortberg has joined the list of outside contenders under serious consideration by Boeing as its next CEO, The Air Current reported on Sunday, citing industry officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/former-rockwell-collins-chief-being-considered-boeing-ceo-report-says-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZRO7AIJKNLJVFXPAR5NUAWNFU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价希望风平浪静，准备迎接更多波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJ6NFNEZ2VMZ3IOHZBNYSK2NRI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：苹果人工智能功能将推迟发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周日报道，苹果公司即将推出的人工智能功能将晚于预期，并将错过即将推出的 iPhone 和 iPad 软件大修的首发时间。【原文：Apple's upcoming artificial intelligence features will arrive later than anticipated and will miss the initial launch of upcoming iPhone and iPad software overhauls, Bloomberg News reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apples-artificial-intelligence-features-be-delayed-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOPCSNFSCFJ6HJADS5R4H7HR6Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，富达和野村正在排队竞购 Ola Electric 在印度的首次公开募股]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接知情的消息人士告诉路透社，软银支持的印度电动摩托车制造商Ola Electric的首次公开募股将吸引来自富达（Fidelity）、野村（Nomura）和挪威诺日银行（Norges Bank）以及几家印度共同基金的投资者竞购。【原文：SoftBank-backed Indian e-scooter maker Ola Electric's IPO is set to draw investor bids from Fidelity, Nomura and Norway's Norges Bank, as well as several Indian mutual funds, two sources with direct knowledge told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/fidelity-nomura-line-up-bids-ola-electrics-india-ipo-sources-say-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUMLGN53LJJ3VOWPT3HHKYLSJ4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:31:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[秘鲁总统称 2024 年国内生产总值增长率将超过 3.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[秘鲁总统迪娜-博卢阿尔特周日在南美国家独立日向国会发表讲话时说，秘鲁的经济增长率将超过此前预计的 3.1%。【原文：Peru's economic growth should surpass the 3.1% rate previously estimated, President Dina Boluarte said on Sunday in a speech to the South American nation's Congress on its independence day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/peru-2024-gdp-growth-should-surpass-31-president-says-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNKVB7TKXJIH3DSVXXPDL6MMHA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 16:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》：2023 年美国房屋保险公司将遭受本世纪最大损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周日报道，由于自然灾害、通货膨胀和高风险地区人口增长等因素的共同作用，美国房屋保险公司在 2023 年遭遇了本世纪最严重的承保损失，使这个重要的金融市场承受了巨大压力。【原文：U.S. home insurers suffered their worst underwriting loss this century in 2023, as a toxic mix of natural disasters, inflation and population growth in at-risk areas put a vital financial market under acute pressure, the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-home-insurers-suffer-biggest-loss-century-2023-ft-says-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNCG6A7XORPTBLK7WFHD4BWQPY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福耀玻璃称俄亥俄州分部不是国土安全局突袭调查的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车玻璃制造商福耀玻璃工业集团称，美国政府机构于 7 月 26 日在俄亥俄州搜查了其子公司，这是对一家第三方劳务公司正在进行的调查的一部分。【原文：Chinese automotive glass maker Fuyao Glass Industry Group said the United States government agencies searched its subsidiary on July 26 in Ohio as part of an ongoing investigation into a third-party labour services company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fuyao-glass-says-ohio-unit-not-target-investigation-after-homeland-security-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJCUB5DIUNMBLLTAZWOILJ5Z5A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 08:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，三菱汽车将加入本田-日产联盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》周日报道，日本三菱汽车公司（Mitsubishi Motors）将加入本田汽车公司（Honda Motor）和日产汽车公司（Nissan Motor）之间的联盟，创建一个汽车总销量超过 800 万辆的汽车集团。【原文：Japan's Mitsubishi Motors is set to join an alliance between Honda Motor and Nissan Motor , creating an auto group with combined sales of more than 8 million vehicles, the Nikkei business daily said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mitsubishi-motors-join-honda-nissan-alliance-nikkei-reports-2024-07-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNEYPKQNBFOOXFCIX4E3GJMTCY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 02:36:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普以中国竞争为由誓言建立比特币 "储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周六在比特币会议上表示，美国必须主导这一行业，否则中国就会这样做，这是他讨好加密货币拥护者的最新举动。【原文：Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump told a bitcoin conference on Saturday that the U.S. must dominate the sector or China would, his latest move to court advocates of cryptocurrency, which Beijing has restricted and which he once dismissed as a "scam."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-cites-china-competition-vowing-create-bitcoin-stockpile-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EPKZUE4I35NKRNLXBDK4SL7NAI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 23:45:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴黎奥运会开幕式吸引 2860 万美国观众，为 2012 年以来最多]]></title><description><![CDATA[据康卡斯特旗下的 NBC 环球公司周六提供的初步数据显示，巴黎奥运会开幕式吸引了 2860 万美国观众，该公司称这是自 2012 年伦敦奥运会以来，夏季奥运会开幕式收视率最高的一次。【原文：The opening ceremony for the Paris Olympics drew 28.6 million U.S. viewers, according to preliminary data from Comcast's NBCUniversal on Saturday, which the company said was the most-watched start to a summer Games since London in 2012.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/olympics/paris-olympics-opening-ceremony-draws-286-million-us-viewers-most-since-2012-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TD2BPUVN5BMIPM4WTENJVX34BU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普向加密货币听众发表讲话，比特币价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六，美国共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普对一群加密货币爱好者说，比特币将登上月球，他希望美国能引领比特币的发展，比特币价格因此有所回落。【原文：The price of bitcoin eased on Saturday as U.S. Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump told an audience of cryptocurrency enthusiasts that bitcoin was going to the moon and he wanted the U.S. to lead the way.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bitcoin-price-dips-trump-addresses-crypto-audience-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOWIXP34F5OLFAGTVWZRB6RCRI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 20:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称每年需要 3 万亿美元气候融资，远高于当前水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周六表示，全球向低碳经济转型需要在2050年前每年新增3万亿美元的资金，远远高于目前每年的融资额，但填补这一缺口是21世纪最大的经济机遇。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Saturday that the global transition to a low-carbon economy requires $3 trillion in new capital each year through 2050, far above current annual financing, but that filling the gap is the biggest economic opportunity of the 21st century.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/yellen-says-3-trillion-needed-annually-climate-financing-far-more-than-current-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A2WHFZLJRJJIPBGWDD7KFMSP3Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 19:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚签署 14 亿美元协议升级海军潜艇]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚周六表示，已与国有潜艇建造商 ASC 公司签署了一份价值 22 亿澳元（14 亿美元）的四年期合同，以升级澳大利亚海军的柯林斯级潜艇。【原文：Australia said on Saturday it had signed a A$2.2 billion ($1.4 billion) four-year contract with state-owned submarine builder ASC to upgrade the navy's Collins class submarines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australia-signs-14-bln-deal-upgrade-navy-submarines-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2OBPQ5GPRK4VKBDBLSGZROV64</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士央行行长乔丹："无趣 "是央行成功的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[即将离任的瑞士国家银行行长托马斯-乔丹（Thomas Jordan）上周六表示，中央银行业务并不枯燥，尽管准备好贴上这个标签也许是成功的关键。【原文：Central banking is not boring, although being prepared to carry the label is perhaps the key to success, departing Swiss National Bank Chairman Thomas Jordan said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/being-boring-key-central-bank-success-says-snbs-jordan-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDN75ATPDJJ6FMGLSBYLBRDAUM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部要求法院驳回 TikTok 对打击法的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五晚些时候要求美国上诉法院驳回对要求中国字节跳动公司（ByteDance）在 1 月 19 日前剥离 TikTok 美国资产，否则将面临禁令的法律挑战。【原文：The Department of Justice late on Friday asked a U.S. appeals court to reject legal challenges to a law requiring China-based ByteDance to divest TikTok's U.S. assets by Jan. 19 or face a ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/usdoj-tells-court-reject-tiktok-challenge-crackdown-law-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBL7SN4T7BPFVIAAB6EWEDXUWU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管经济不景气，中国 6 月工业利润仍实现较快增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周六的官方数据显示，中国 6 月份的工业利润增速加快，尽管在经济复苏不稳的情况下，企业仍在努力应对消费者情绪的下滑。【原文：China's industrial profits grew at a faster clip in June, official data showed on Saturday, even as businesses were grappling with a downshift in consumers' sentiment amid a shaky economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-industrial-profits-post-faster-gains-june-despite-faltering-economy-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIE63BWGGBLV3DNAY52Z3FTHMM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:11:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国工会与苹果公司达成临时劳资协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际机械师和航空航天工人协会（IAM）零售员工组织联盟（IAM CORE）周五与科技巨头苹果公司就改善工作与生活的平衡、加薪和工作保障等问题达成了临时协议。【原文：The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM) Coalition of Organized Retail Employees (IAM CORE) reached a tentative agreement with tech giant Apple on Friday over improvement in work-life balance, pay raises and job security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-union-apple-reach-tentative-labor-agreement-2024-07-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7DE3F7ENJJZZPZDPYFMOF5IWY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:49:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小肯尼迪质疑特朗普最近支持加密货币的论调，两人正在争夺选票]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国独立总统候选人小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr）周五质疑共和党提名人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最近支持加密货币的立场，两人正在比特币2024大会上争夺11月选举中加密货币持有者的选票。【原文：Independent U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr on Friday questioned Republican nominee Donald Trump's recent pro-cryptocurrency stance, as the two vie for votes in November's election from crypto-holders at the Bitcoin 2024 conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/rfk-jr-questions-trumps-recent-pro-crypto-tone-two-vie-votes-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNXAFPSJDVPCBB2UJNO75MWCBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:49:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》报道，耶伦称日本解释了 2022 年的外汇干预措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经商业日报》（Nikkei Business daily）周六报道，美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）表示，日本已就其在2022年干预货币市场做出了解释。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said Japan had explained its intervention into the currency market in 2022, the Nikkei Business daily reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/yellen-says-japan-explained-2022-fx-intervention-nikkei-reports-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEI6TK5K25K3PJYYIXEGGJGFXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金关于美国国债发行的研究引发争论]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金的一份研究报告称，美国财政部去年通过放缓长期债券销售有效地刺激了经济，该报告在债券市场引发了一场争论，美国财政部也否认了这一说法，称其目的并非如此。【原文：A hedge fund study that said the U.S. Treasury last year effectively provided economic stimulus by moderating long-dated bond sales has sparked a debate in the bond market and a denial from the U.S. Treasury that said it was not aiming for such an effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-fund-study-us-treasury-issuance-fuels-debate-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFUETR5EXJOD3OLDWQRRCS5MQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:35:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦：新兴市场共同关注中国工厂产能过剩问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周五表示，包括一些二十国集团（G20）国家在内的新兴市场与她一样对中国工业产能过剩感到担忧，并应敦促中国政府改变其经济模式。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Friday that emerging markets, including some G20 countries, share her concerns about China's excess industrial capacity and should press Beijing to change its economic model.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/yellen-emerging-markets-share-concerns-chinas-excess-factory-capacity-2024-07-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WT4OUV3KM5LKRHJ4NQDH46F3FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>