<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:33:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:33:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通聘请前汇丰银行交易员 Kamal Jabre 推动欧洲、中东和非洲地区的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份备忘录，摩根大通已任命汇丰银行前全球并购主管卡迈勒-贾布雷（Kamal Jabre）为其新任并购部副主席，负责推动在欧洲、中东和非洲（EMEA）的扩张。【原文：JPMorgan has named HSBC's former global head of mergers and acquisitions, Kamal Jabre, as its new M&amp;A Vice Chair to drive expansion across Europe, the Middle East and Africa (EMEA), according to a memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-hires-former-hsbc-dealmaker-kamal-jabre-drive-emea-growth-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGV2QQ7SABIONCHL5UV2NJMLDE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:19:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟调查后，Shein将加强产品安全检测]]></title><description><![CDATA[快速时尚零售商 Shein 周四表示，今年将加强对产品的检测，因为欧盟警告称，如果该公司不解决欧盟对其网站上销售的不安全和危险产品的担忧，将被处以罚款。【原文：Fast-fashion retailer Shein on Thursday said it would increase its testing of products this year, after the European Union warned of fines if it does not address the bloc's concerns about unsafe and dangerous products sold on its site.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/shein-increase-product-safety-testing-after-eu-probe-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">737KYNTMFNJY7LXBVMB6RINGPU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税影响，电子产品零售商百思买下调年度销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[百思买周四下调了年度可比销售额预期，原因是有迹象表明，消费者对家电、家庭影院和游戏机等大件商品的需求将受到美国关税的压力。【原文：Best Buy slashed its annual comparable sales forecast on Thursday, on signs that consumer demand for big-ticket items such as appliances, home theater and gaming consoles will be pressured by U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/electronics-retailer-best-buy-cuts-annual-sales-forecast-tariff-pain-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XR5STQBDSBKW3NB7GWAG5AVRHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[季度亏损低于预期，科尔百货坚持年度目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[科尔百货公司（Kohl's）周四公布了好于预期的第一季度业绩，维持了其年度预期，因为这家美国连锁百货公司在关税引发的需求波动的背景下，押注于其扭亏为盈的努力。【原文：Kohl's retained its annual forecasts after reporting better-than-expected results for the first quarter on Thursday, as the U.S. department store chain bets on its turnaround efforts against the background of tariff-induced choppy demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/department-store-chain-kohls-quarterly-loss-smaller-than-expected-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSSSF6OJ5ZOSZLMULFLJOI3AFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:10:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[捷蓝航空和美联航合作让乘客在两个网站上预订机票]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）和美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周四公布了一项消费者合作计划，允许旅客在两家航空公司的网站上预订航班，同时互换赚取和使用其飞行常客计划中的积分。【原文：JetBlue Airways and United Airlines unveiled on Thursday plans for a consumer collaboration that allows travelers to book flights on both carriers' websites, while interchangeably earning and using points in their frequent flyer programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/jetblue-united-tie-up-let-passengers-book-both-websites-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDVXSD6ABNKCDHDXZEAEEB7BFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊的 Zoox 在旧金山坠机后发布本月第二次软件召回公告]]></title><description><![CDATA[继本月早些时候在旧金山发生车祸后，亚马逊公司的自动驾驶部门 Zoox 在本月发布了第二次软件召回，以改进其车辆追踪附近行人的方式，并在有人靠近时防止车辆移动。【原文：Amazon.com's self-driving unit Zoox has issued a second software recall this month to improve how its vehicles track nearby pedestrians and prevent movement when someone is close, following a crash in San Francisco earlier this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/amazons-zoox-issues-second-software-recall-this-month-after-san-francisco-crash-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6W3WYHS4VOBLOVIPDNF3RTX2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 新任命的首席执行官选择欧洲作为公司巡展的第一站]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 新任命的首席执行官安东尼奥-菲罗萨（Antonio Filosa）周四在下月底正式履新之前，前往欧洲参观了这家汽车制造商的生产基地和办公场所。【原文：Stellantis' newly appointed CEO Antonio Filosa on Thursday picked Europe to kick off a tour of the automaker's production sites and offices before formally taking up his new job at the end of next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-newly-appointed-ceo-chooses-europe-first-leg-company-tour-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIVTSBZEDNOKXBAXOH2XOWZTCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:58:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标特朗普关税受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3Z4B3ZIPRNULDQ5BAAYFY2JIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:46:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国裁定特朗普关税不合法引发宽松与不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易法院的一项裁决阻止了唐纳德-特朗普总统的大部分关税措施，并认定他越权行事，这在周四引发了金融市场的一些松动，同时也增加了拖累全球经济的不确定性。【原文：A U.S. trade court ruling that blocked most of President Donald Trump's tariffs and found he had overstepped his authority triggered some relief on financial markets on Thursday, while adding to the uncertainties weighing on the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-ruling-that-trump-tariffs-are-unlawful-stirs-relief-uncertainty-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXSX7ATW3VPRTLDPUE6OROLVKE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Omada Health 在美国 IPO 的目标估值超过 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[虚拟慢性病护理服务提供商 Omada Health 在美国首次公开募股的目标估值约为 11 亿美元，这标志着资本市场在经历了几个月的上市放缓后又开始复苏。【原文：Virtual chronic care provider Omada Health is targeting a valuation of about $1.1 billion in its initial public offering in the United States, signaling a comeback for capital markets after several months of slowdown in listings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/omada-health-targets-valuation-over-1-billion-us-ipo-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6QOOOA4SRMTFMTXI4A3FOJJMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院做出裁决后，特朗普在全球关税问题上还能做些什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易法院周三作出一项全面裁决，认定唐纳德-特朗普总统越权对美国贸易伙伴的进口商品征收全面关税，从而阻止了特朗普总统的大部分关税措施。【原文：A U.S. trade court blocked most of President Donald Trump's tariffs in a sweeping ruling on Wednesday that found the president had overstepped his authority by imposing across-the-board duties on imports from U.S. trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/what-else-can-trump-do-global-tariffs-after-us-court-ruling-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCGWKBTCWFJIRHHGYJRXPIZ2CY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:13:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公司在关税动荡期间求助于私人信贷以获得贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[关税的不确定性和市场的不稳定性使一些公司开始寻求灵活、更确定的途径，从私人信贷公司获得资金，从而在某些情况下放弃了传统的贷款机构。【原文：Tariff uncertainty and market volatility have sent some companies looking for a flexible, more certain route to funding from private credit firms, resulting in the spurning of traditional lenders in some cases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/companies-turn-private-credit-during-tariff-turmoil-loans-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J24NILPNABLFTPJISNJESPE5PM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的税收和支出法案也将提高部分关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[众议院通过的大规模税收和支出法案还将进一步推进唐纳德-特朗普总统的另一个优先事项：提高关税。该法案将把特朗普在关税方面采取的行政措施的几个关键要素编纂成法律，使未来的政府更难解除这些措施。以下是该方案中与关税相关内容的细目，特朗普还必须在参议院通过该方案后才能将其签署为法律。【原文：The massive tax and spending bill that has passed the House of Representatives would also further another priority of President Donald Trump: higher tariffs. The bill would codify into law several key elements of the executive actions Trump has taken on tariffs, making it more difficult for a future administration to unwind them. Here is a breakdown of the tariff-related elements in the package, which also must pass the Senate before Trump can sign it into law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-tax-spending-bill-would-raise-some-tariffs-well-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SA5Z37LLWZOGPE56YDWA5QWFI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小米特斯拉 Y 的竞争对手 YU7 进入北京展厅]]></title><description><![CDATA[小米公司周四在北京推出了新款运动型多功能车，这家以智能手机和消费电子产品闻名的公司正准备在全球最大的汽车市场进一步挑战特斯拉。【原文：Xiaomi rolled out its new sports utility vehicle in Beijing on Thursday, as the firm best known for smartphones and consumer electronics gears up to further challenge Tesla in the world's largest auto market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/xiaomis-tesla-y-rival-yu7-hits-showrooms-beijing-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPJ3AEYVTNLSXCVPY3OOSBLBWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦法院裁定特朗普的关税措施无效，美国股指期货攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国贸易法院阻止了唐纳德-特朗普总统提出的大部分关税建议后，华尔街期货周四攀升，而人工智能芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）的股价在季度营收强于预期后上涨。【原文：Wall Street futures climbed on Thursday after a U.S. trade court blocked most of President Donald Trump's proposed tariffs, while shares of AI chipmaker Nvidia gained following stronger-than-expected quarterly revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-climb-federal-court-rules-against-trumps-tariffs-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNWC74CLSNJI7PWV3FWUM2Q6XY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲五月份出口至美国西海岸的航油将创一年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据船运跟踪数据和三个贸易消息来源，由于加利福尼亚州炼油厂的停工刺激了价格和进口需求，预计五月份亚洲出口到美国西海岸的航空燃油将至少创下一年来的新高。【原文：Asia's jet fuel exports to the U.S. West Coast are expected to hit at least a one-year high in May, according to shiptracking data and three trade sources, as refinery outages in California boosted prices and import demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/asia-jet-fuel-exports-us-west-coast-hit-1-year-high-may-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NELA52AFL5METKM42JBNSUFP3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲股市将在 2026 年再创新高，贸易紧张局势削弱了更高的希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，受货币宽松政策和财政支出增加的提振，欧洲股市有望在2025年年底前小幅上涨，然后在2026年再创新高，但关税和贸易的不确定性正在削弱人们对更大涨幅的希望。【原文：European shares are expected to rise slightly by the end of 2025 before scaling new heights in 2026, boosted by monetary easing and higher fiscal spending, but tariff and trade uncertainties are tempering hopes for bigger gains, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/european-stocks-scale-new-heights-2026-trade-tensions-temper-loftier-hopes-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THCZNOYKGVLJDPV4LAPMOEG4PY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前日本央行决策者称日本可能暂缓出售美国国债]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行（BOJ）前决策者白井小百合（Sayuri Shirai）周四表示，日本可能暂缓抛售其持有的巨额美国国债，因为鉴于美元的全球储备货币地位，日本没有其他投资选择。【原文：Japan likely held off selling from its huge U.S. Treasury holdings as there is no alternative investment given the dollar's status as a global reserve currency, former Bank of Japan (BOJ) policymaker Sayuri Shirai said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/japan-likely-held-off-us-treasury-sales-says-ex-boj-policymaker-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COU2QGZIVRKZZMZ7BGPVMSSPPU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼称分拆金融部门将确保筹资能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼公司首席执行官周四表示，分拆金融服务部门将确保该业务拥有自己的筹资能力。【原文：Sony's CEO said on Thursday the spin-off of the financial services arm will secure that business its own fundraising capabilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sony-says-financial-arm-spin-off-will-secure-fundraising-capabilities-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PD7BKAXKLZIEBHN565R3JVSMPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:51:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，2025 年全球政府发行的美元债务将大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲和欧洲各国政府以美元举债的情况比往常少得多，它们更倾向于在国内发行，以避免受到美国收益率上升、货币波动以及对美国政府财政的更广泛担忧的影响。【原文：Governments in Asia and Europe are raising far less debt in U.S. dollars than usual, preferring to issue at home as they avoid exposure to rising U.S. yields, currency volatility and broader concerns about U.S. government finances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/global-government-issuance-us-dollar-debt-tumbling-2025-data-shows-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCTOFBCUKRLGRFPUKEOEVXMN5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼尔森智库（NielsenIQ）称，尽管受到网络攻击，M&S食品销售仍表现出韧性]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国零售商玛莎百货公司（Marks & Spencer）周四公布的行业数据显示，尽管上个月的网络攻击影响了食品供应，但该公司的食品业务在截至5月17日的12周内销售额同比增长了10.8%。【原文：British retailer Marks & Spencer's food business saw food sales increase 10.8% over the 12 weeks to May 17 year-on-year despite the fallout from a cyberattack last month denting availability, industry data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ms-food-sales-show-resilience-despite-cyberattack-says-nielseniq-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4NVLSLS4BKTTD4DKVBINJASLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法院的关税裁决给市场带来短期刺激和长期忧虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全面关税政策在法律上遇到了障碍，这引起了市场的欢呼，但长期政策和经济瘫痪的风险给担心长远发展的投资者投下了更深的阴影。【原文：A legal roadblock on U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs drew early cheer from markets on Thursday, but the risks of extended policy and economic paralysis cast a deeper shadow for investors worried about the longer term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-courts-tariff-ruling-gives-markets-short-term-pop-long-term-angst-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAYWN6HVB5OHZGI3FGC4ND5S3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 06:52:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克：特斯拉将于 6 月交付首款自动驾驶汽车 Model Y]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周四表示，特斯拉将于 6 月交付首辆自动驾驶汽车 Model Y。【原文：Tesla will deliver its first self-driving Model Y car in June, CEO Elon Musk said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-deliver-first-self-driving-model-y-car-june-musk-says-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJZ4PK2FXBNKTEVUFY2N7XTDXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 06:27:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌开始在印度在线直销 Pixel 手机]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，谷歌开始在印度直接在线销售其流行的硬件设备，包括 Pixel 手机、手表和耳塞，在此之前，谷歌预计将在这个南亚国家开设首家实体店。【原文：Google on Thursday began direct online sales of its popular hardware devices in India, including Pixel phones, watches and earbuds, ahead of an anticipated launch of its first physical stores in the South Asian nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/google-begins-direct-online-sales-pixel-phones-india-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHCUPX5KVVM5HEKGFJZJJAHMWY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场询问新日铁多久能从美国钢铁公司 150 亿美元的竞购中获益]]></title><description><![CDATA[新日铁的投资者和分析师们都在问，新日铁斥资 150 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司的交易虽然得到了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的支持，但尚未获得其批准。【原文：Nippon Steel investors and analysts are asking if its $15-billion deal to buy U.S. Steel , backed but not yet approved by President Donald Trump, is positive for the near term, even if its hopes for strong U.S. demand materialise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/markets-ask-how-soon-nippon-steel-will-benefit-15-billion-bid-us-steel-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVK2523VO5PPRNUG4XK25UJSQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出口商称韩国对美国的贸易顺差将缩小]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国最大的出口商集团周四表示，随着企业继续投资美国市场，韩国对美贸易顺差将逐步收窄，创下历史新高。【原文：South Korea's record-high trade surpluses with the United States will gradually narrow as companies continue to invest in the U.S. market, the country's biggest exporter group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-koreas-trade-surplus-with-us-will-shrink-exporters-say-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXXL7DXD3RKXDKLFSPJP4IVZIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国银行认为汽车、钢铁和芯片出口将因关税影响而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国央行周四表示，随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税影响在今年晚些时候生效，韩国的汽车、钢铁和半导体出口预计将下降。【原文：South Korea's exports of automobiles, steel and semiconductors are expected to fall as the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs take effect later this year, the central bank said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bank-korea-sees-auto-steel-chip-exports-falling-when-tariffs-hit-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6FUVVLNCNN57BUXHFYE4O7WZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 市场希望特朗普关税保持 "非法 "状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4IATN7EGBPLHG3J6KIO4IJFIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田汽车 4 月份全球产销量连续第四个月增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田公司周四表示，由于混合动力汽车需求强劲以及美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收进口关税引发的美国抢购潮，该公司4月份的全球产销量连续第四个月增长。【原文：Toyota said on Thursday its worldwide output and sales rose for a fourth consecutive month in April on strong demand for hybrid vehicles and rush buying in the United States over U.S. President Donald Trump's import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-global-output-sales-rise-fourth-straight-month-april-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKU7BCD32ZPQ3HR74QV5UPCPA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美解冻、贸易协议震荡美元，亚洲货币看涨押注激增 - 路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，由于中美关税紧张局势的缓解、新贸易协议的达成以及对美国政策日益增长的不安促使投资者撤出美元资产，投资者对包括人民币在内的亚洲货币下了大量看涨赌注。【原文：Investors piled up bullish bets on Asian currencies, including the yuan, as easing U.S.-China tariff tensions, new trade deals and a growing unease with U.S. policies prompted them to pull out of dollar assets, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bullish-bets-surge-asian-currencies-us-china-thaw-trade-deals-rattle-dollar-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLDYSNT2JZNVHJWW3EQRZMFZ7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:31:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>