<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:04:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将其持有的公司股份转让给可撤销信托后，特朗普传媒股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普将其持有的社交媒体公司股份转移到可撤销信托之后，特朗普媒体与科技公司的股价周五下跌了约 6%。【原文：Trump Media &amp; Technology's shares fell about 6% on Friday after U.S. President-elect Donald Trump moved the stake he owns in the social media company to a revocable trust.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-media-shares-fall-after-trump-transfers-his-stake-company-revocable-trust-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAYRUEIKZVIAVP6YTAUDJXEZME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:55:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 与国际足联达成 2027 年和 2031 年女足世界杯转播协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界足球管理机构周五表示，国际足联和 Netflix 已签署协议，将在美国转播 2027 年和 2031 年两届女足世界杯。【原文：FIFA and Netflix have signed a deal to broadcast the 2027 and 2031 editions of the women's World Cup in the United States, world soccer's governing body said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-inks-broadcast-deal-with-fifa-2027-2031-womens-world-cups-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKWPOKWKTJIULCBH3QMLNFAHLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经理人》杂志称，未来几年大众汽车将裁员 1 万多人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《经理人》杂志报道，作为与工会就德国品牌未来达成的协议的一部分，大众汽车计划在未来几年内裁员 1 万多人，但未说明从何处获得这一信息。【原文：Volkswagen plans to cut more than 10,000 jobs in the next few years as part of an agreement with unions over the future of the German brand, manager magazin reported, not citing where it obtained the information.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/more-than-10000-jobs-be-cut-vw-next-years-says-manager-magazin-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2QX4Y3TRVKUXAA7KVGI4DXEIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CFPB 起诉美国顶级银行，称其纵容支付平台 Zelle 上的欺诈行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局周五表示，已对摩根大通、美国银行和富国银行提起诉讼，指控这些银行允许点对点支付平台 Zelle 上的 "欺诈行为恶化"。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau said on Friday it had filed a lawsuit against JPMorgan Chase , Bank of America , and Wells Fargo , accusing the banks of allowing "fraud to fester" on peer-to-peer payments platform Zelle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cfpb-sues-top-us-banks-says-they-allowed-fraud-payment-platform-zelle-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AWT2M4QSZP2FGBREINBWR3R2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邮轮运营商嘉年华因需求强劲而收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘉年华公司周五公布的第四季度营收超出预期，这主要得益于美国人渴望在夏季出游，对价格较高的航次需求旺盛，使其股价在盘前交易中上涨了约 4%。【原文：Carnival Corp beat fourth-quarter revenue estimates on Friday, helped by resilient demand for its pricier voyages from Americans eager to go on summer cruises, sending its shares up about 4% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/carnival-forecasts-annual-profit-below-estimates-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UORIYYIWMRLIZDZBGTK22PJX6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:26:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 11 月 PCE 通胀降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[11 月份个人消费支出（PCE）物价指数增长 0.1%，低于预期，与 10 月份未经修正的 0.2% 的增幅相比，通胀形势有所降温，加之消费者支出稳健但令人失望，支撑着因美联储本周 "鹰派 "降息而苦苦挣扎的市场。【原文：The personal consumption expenditures (PCE) price index rose a less-than-expected 0.1% in November, marking a cooler inflation picture than October's unrevised 0.2% gain, and, combined with solid but disappointing consumer spending, supported markets struggling with the Federal Reserve's "hawkish' rate cut this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-us-pce-inflation-cools-november-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJREJN2GHRL5JPLR63KQQ5X27A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈马克称经济强劲反对降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周五表示，她对央行本周早些时候的降息行动投了反对票，因为经济实力和通胀前景都不支持放松政策。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack said Friday she voted against the central bank’s rate cut earlier this week because economic strength and the inflation outlook argued against easing policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-hammack-says-economic-strength-argued-against-rate-cut-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUERXZKW5VJKLIIPQWTZV5KA7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯美联储仍在减息轨道上，但前景不明朗]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，他预计央行将实施更多的降息措施，但他指出，在政策仍在抑制经济发展势头的情况下，降息措施的实施将受到新数据的驱动。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams said Friday that he expects the central bank to deliver more interest rate cuts but noted what happens will be driven by incoming data, amid a policy that's still providing restraint on the economy's momentum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-williams-fed-remains-track-cuts-amid-uncertain-outlook-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KDA2I75ANOWNCTINTQB5RNFHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席戴利称本周降息 "千钧一发]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周五表示，美国央行周三再次降息四分之一个百分点的决定是一个 "千钧一发的决定"，并补充说她同意主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）的观点，即现在需要对进一步的政策调整保持谨慎。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly on Friday said the decision by the U.S. central bank to lower interest rates on Wednesday by another quarter percentage point was a "close call," adding she agreed with Chair Jerome Powell that caution is now warranted toward further policy adjustments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-daly-says-this-weeks-rate-cut-was-close-call-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNZLJRUJDFJXVHFBSJWF2QFSKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:41:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月消费者支出增长；月度通胀率减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者支出在 11 月份有所增加，凸显了经济的持久强劲，这促使美联储本周预计 2025 年的降息次数将少于三个月前。【原文：U.S. consumer spending increased in November, underscoring the economy's enduring strength, which prompted the Federal Reserve this week to project fewer interest rate cuts in 2025 than it had three months ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-spending-rises-november-monthly-inflation-subsides-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXTLJCLJUVIOPH6BOFKMZLRNFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《德国商报》报道，大众汽车与劳资协议会达成临时协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《德国商报》周五援引熟知内情的人士的话报道，大众汽车与其劳资协议会就削减成本措施达成了临时协议，但仍需双方进一步审查并达成一致。【原文：Volkswagen and its works council reached a provisional deal on cost-cutting measures that still requires further scrutiny and agreement from both sides, Handelsblatt reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the proceedings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vw-works-council-reach-provisional-deal-handelsblatt-reports-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6MPGNQUSVMCPF5G6JIK2SNC3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 将菲亚特 500 工厂的停工期延长至 1 月 20 日]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商 Stellantis 周五表示，菲亚特 500 城市电动车的停产时间将再延长几周，直至 1 月 20 日，这证实了工会的预期。【原文：Automaker Stellantis said on Friday a pause in production of its electric Fiat 500 city car will be extended by another couple of weeks until Jan. 20, confirming the expectations of trade unions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-extends-stoppage-fiat-500-plant-until-jan-20-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IGDJMR5IVP4TKDIAADMNFTS6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁拉托因腐败案被判处 4 年 9 个月监禁]]></title><description><![CDATA[马德里一家法院周五发表声明说，国际货币基金组织前总裁罗德里戈-拉托（Rodrigo Rato）因与腐败有关的各种罪行被判处四年九个月零一天的监禁。【原文：A Madrid court has sentenced former International Monetary Fund chief Rodrigo Rato to four years, nine months and a day in prison for various crimes related to corruption, the court said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ex-imf-chief-rato-sentenced-4-years-9-months-prison-over-corruption-case-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOFQQKXCAZNW5HVMRYLKYQHHWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 12:42:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金在美联储决议前面临巨额资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至12月18日的一周内，投资者以15年来最快的速度清算股票基金，原因是在近期市场反弹之后，投资者因预期美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）政策会议将出现鹰派结果而谨慎行事并获利了结。【原文：Investors liquidated equity funds at the fastest rate in 15 years in the week to Dec. 18, driven by caution and profit-taking in anticipation of a hawkish outcome from the U.S. Federal Reserve's policy meeting after a recent market rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BBXLFELFBOSVGDYIPGFE7EGHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 12:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储决议前美国股票基金出现 15 年来最大净流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据理柏集团（LSEG Lipper）的数据，在截至12月18日的一周内，投资者从美国股票基金中净撤资502亿美元，这是自2009年9月以来最大的净流出量，因为他们在美联储政策决定之前兑现了市场反弹带来的利润。【原文：Investors pulled a net $50.2 billion from U.S. equity funds in the week ending Dec. 18, according to LSEG Lipper data, the biggest net outflow since Sept. 2009, as they cashed in profits from a market rally ahead of the Fed policy decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-saw-biggest-net-outflows-15-years-ahead-fed-decision-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUMJZK7GYJI45BV7XBINSG447Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 12:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递货运分拆计划强化核心业务，促进行业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师周五表示，联邦快递分拆货运卡车业务部门的决定将加强该业务，同时使这家包裹递送巨头能够更好地应对其核心业务面临的挑战。【原文：FedEx's decision to spin off its freight truckload segment will strengthen the business while allowing the parcel delivery giant to better tackle challenges in its core operations, analysts said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fedexs-freight-spinoff-plan-fortify-core-business-boost-industry-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TTRR4ZVCZ5IM7DMPFHC2XSWIYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 12:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利因 OpenAI 违反隐私保护规定罚款 1500 万欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利隐私监管机构周五表示，在结束对生成式人工智能应用程序使用个人数据的调查后，对 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 罚款 1500 万欧元（合 1558 万美元）。【原文：Italy's privacy watchdog said on Friday it fined ChatGPT maker OpenAI 15 million euros ($15.58 million) after closing an investigation into use of personal data by the generative artificial intelligence application.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/italy-fines-openai-15-million-euros-over-privacy-rules-breach-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIXDOTTIH5LILJI2TITMDO5VOE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：特朗普瞄准拜登的《降低通货膨胀法案》：电动汽车、清洁能源和制造业]]></title><description><![CDATA[当选总统唐纳德-特朗普誓言要废除乔-拜登的标志性气候法案--《通货膨胀削减法案》，该法案最初旨在通过约 4000 亿美元的新支出、减税和信贷来加速美国向绿色能源经济的转型。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump has vowed to repeal Joe Biden's signature climate bill called the Inflation Reduction Act, which initially aimed at some $400 billion in new spending and tax cuts and credits at accelerating America's transition to a green energy economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-aims-bidens-inflation-reduction-act-evs-clean-energy-manufacturing-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LB4X5DPH6VJBVGI5UGYTQUGFOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市连年繁荣，投资者希望在 2025 年实现三连胜]]></title><description><![CDATA[受支撑企业利润的稳健经济、缓和的利率以及即将上任的总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的支持增长政策的推动，投资者预计 2025 年美国股市将取得更多涨幅。【原文：Investors are expecting more gains for the U.S. stock market in 2025 after two straight standout years, fueled by a solid economy supporting corporate profits, moderating interest rates and pro-growth policies from incoming president Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-hope-us-stock-market-trifecta-2025-after-back-to-back-boom-years-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSN4GHGGCZK3LFMBG5CZ4MKMRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国液化天然气出口工厂的天然气需求将出现 8 年来首次下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年，美国用于生产液化天然气（LNG）以供出口的天然气需求量将出现自八年前美国开始从低纬度 48 个州出口这种超冷燃料以来的首次下降。【原文：Demand for U.S. natural gas to produce liquefied natural gas (LNG) for export this year is headed for its first decline since the country started exporting the super-chilled fuel from the lower 48 states eight years ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/natural-gas-demand-us-lng-export-plants-heads-first-decline-8-years-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZX5CDXJYVKWZKZDSD6NNBU4XM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:13:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国做出投资决定之前，哥伦比亚埃克石油公司的动荡加剧了对利润的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚总统古斯塔沃-彼得罗（Gustavo Petro）涉嫌干预国有控股公司哥伦比亚石油公司（Ecopetrol），并清洗了数百名员工为亲政府的接替者让路，这加剧了人们对该能源公司未来利润和对经济贡献的担忧。【原文：Alleged interference by Colombian President Gustavo Petro in majority state-owned Ecopetrol and purges of hundreds of staff to make way for pro-government replacements are fueling fears about the energy company's future profits and contributions to the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/turmoil-colombias-ecopetrol-raises-profit-fears-ahead-us-investment-decision-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6L6M572GZKWJBNW6GJE23GCO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:10:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 投资者期待 "圣诞老人 "反弹，股市却失去动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[12 月迄今为止，美国股市在本该辉煌的一年中取得了 "守财奴 "般的回报，投资者希望 2024 年的尾声能带来一些节日的欢乐，但同时也对潜在的不利因素发出了警告。【原文：With December so far delivering Scrooge-like returns in an otherwise stellar year for U.S. stocks, investors hope the tail end of 2024 offers some holiday cheer, but warn of potential headwinds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-hope-santa-claus-rally-stocks-lose-steam-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRY4Y6Y2HVPY7JS3EPNMERDYXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：政府停摆和关税担忧扰乱年末市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNHNB556SRIALNEY677VG2OZMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[禽流感促使美国鸡蛋价格在圣诞节前创下历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着蛋鸡禽流感疫情的加速爆发，美国鸡蛋批发价格不断刷新纪录，供应量锐减，而购物者则购买更多鸡蛋来烘焙圣诞饼干和其他节日食品。【原文：U.S. wholesale egg prices are shattering records as an accelerating outbreak of bird flu in laying hens slashes supplies while shoppers buy more to bake Christmas cookies and other holiday treats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bird-flu-drives-us-egg-prices-all-time-highs-before-christmas-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GVQ626QE7VOSTHAWA4FVEEHNL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 2024 年的交付量增长可能取决于马斯克的非正统 Cybertruck]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，特斯拉的目标是在2024年通过对其电动汽车的慷慨激励，使交付量比去年略有增长，但这在很大程度上取决于新款Cybertruck皮卡的成功与否，而这款皮卡正显示出疲软的迹象。【原文：Tesla is aiming to post slight growth in 2024 deliveries over last year with generous incentives across its EVs - but a lot depends on the success of the new Cybertruck pickup, which is showing signs of weakness, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-2024-deliveries-growth-might-hinge-musks-unorthodox-cybertruck-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBAGABNZNFJ3XCCHCYZJEGY7VM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟准备加强与美国的关系，重点关注能源领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟发言人周五表示，欧盟已准备好与美国当选总统特朗普讨论进一步加强经济关系的问题，包括能源领域的共同利益。【原文：The EU is ready to discuss further strengthening economic ties with U.S. President-elect Trump, including common interests in the energy sector, an EU spokesperson said on Friday, adding the EU was also committed to phasing out energy imports from Russia and diversifying supply sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eu-ready-strengthen-ties-with-us-focus-energy-sector-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLULRYIHTNOWFNFQKIV4OA7TAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 10:58:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟批准英伟达收购 Run:ai]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周五表示，已无条件批准英伟达以 7 亿美元收购 Run:ai。【原文：The European Commission said on Friday it has approved unconditionally Nvidia's $700 million bid for Run:ai.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/eu-approves-nvidias-acquisition-runai-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QCSRGWFBJOVFCU47BOEYDEZLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 10:52:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德新一代肥胖症药物 CagriSema 的减重效果低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德公司周五表示，其试验性下一代肥胖症药物CagriSema在一项后期试验中帮助超重患者减轻了22.7%的体重，低于其预期的25%，这导致其股价大幅下跌。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Friday its experimental next-generation obesity drug CagriSema helped overweight patients cut their weight by 22.7% in a late-stage trial, below the 25% it had expected, sending its shares down sharply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisks-next-gen-obesity-drug-cagrisema-achieves-lower-weight-loss-than-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLX6ZCT7VVN7RJEKX6W26CYRTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 10:51:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀数据公布前，政府关门担忧打击期指]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货下跌，原因是投资者在一份关键的通胀报告公布之前，正努力应对政府关门的可能性和提高利率的路径。【原文：U.S. stock index futures dropped on Friday as investors grappled with the possibility of a government shutdown and a higher interest rate path ahead of a key inflation report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-hit-by-government-shutdown-fears-ahead-inflation-data-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAZJX4XRJ5KIPI247ES3XRCBZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 10:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉因胎压监测系统问题在美国召回近 70 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周五表示，因轮胎压力监控系统问题，将在美国召回694304辆汽车。【原文：Tesla said on Friday it was recalling 694,304 vehicles in the United States over an issue with the tire pressure monitoring system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-recalls-nearly-700000-vehicles-us-over-tire-pressure-monitoring-system-2024-12-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUFOLEKCC5KPBOA6L5BQOXRQVA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 10:42:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>