<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:38:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:38:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州起诉礼来公司，指控其贿赂医疗服务提供者以开具其药品处方]]></title><description><![CDATA[得克萨斯州总检察长肯-帕克斯顿（Ken Paxton）周二起诉美国制药商礼来公司，指控其 "贿赂 "医疗服务提供者开具其药品处方。【原文：Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton on Tuesday sued U.S. drugmaker Eli Lilly for allegedly "bribing" providers to prescribe its medications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/texas-sues-eli-lilly-allegedly-bribing-providers-prescribe-its-medications-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAJ756N2LRLAXBOL4EH5WROZ4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机票数据显示定价能力增强，美国航空公司股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国主要航空公司股价大涨，因为7月份乐观的机票价格数据表明，随着航空公司调整运力以适应疲软的需求环境，美国航空业的定价能力正在提高。【原文：Shares of major U.S. carriers jumped on Tuesday after upbeat airfare data for July signaled improving pricing power for the industry, as airlines bring capacity in check to align with a soft demand environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-airlines-shares-jump-airfare-data-signals-improving-pricing-power-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDLPPLHOEVK4LFNRSAG3YHFBYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普斥责高盛所罗门和该银行关于关税影响的经济学研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，消费者并未支付关税成本，并反驳了高盛（Goldman Sachs）研究部门最近的一项估计，即截至 6 月份，消费者已吸收了 22% 的关税成本。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday consumers are not paying the costs of tariffs, countering a recent Goldman Sachs' research division estimate that they had absorbed 22% of the costs through June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-rebukes-goldmans-solomon-banks-economics-research-tariff-impact-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNWIB43GVZORVFK4MKHV2ZXCRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[米兰称美联储的独立性 "至关重要"，但拒绝详述 - CNBC]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的美联储理事会成员周二表示，美国中央银行的独立性 "至关重要"，但他拒绝进一步阐述，理由是参议院即将对其进行审批。【原文：President Donald Trump's nominee to the Federal Reserve Board of Governors on Tuesday said the U.S. central bank's independence was 'of paramount importance' but declined to elaborate further, citing his coming approval process in the Senate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/miran-calls-fed-independence-paramount-declines-elaborate-cnbc-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A73WFGYCN5PDJH2BGE2VHRY7XI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司 Perplexity 大胆出价 345 亿美元收购谷歌 Chrome 浏览器]]></title><description><![CDATA[Perplexity AI 表示，它已主动向 Alphabet 的 Chrome 浏览器提出了 345 亿美元的全现金收购要约，出价低但很大胆，所需的融资远远高于这家初创公司自身的估值。【原文：Perplexity AI said it has made a $34.5 billion unsolicited all-cash offer for Alphabet's Chrome browser, a low but bold bid that would need financing well above the startup's own valuation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ai-startup-perplexity-makes-bold-345-billion-bid-googles-chrome-browser-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VNV25OFHUVNBLBI5UGLP6ATM7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Paytm 支付服务公司获央行批准作为在线支付聚合商运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度金融科技公司 Paytm 周二表示，其部门 Paytm 支付服务已获得印度中央银行的 "原则性 "批准，可以作为在线支付聚合商运营。【原文：Indian fintech firm Paytm on Tuesday said its unit Paytm Payments Services has got 'in-principle' approval from the country's central bank to operate as an online payment aggregator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-paytm-payments-services-gets-central-bank-nod-operate-online-payment-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYO7M3CBEFPVRCFCJNUCX7PFUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:25:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 7 月咖啡消费价格 18 个月来首次下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二公布的巴西全国消费价格总指数（IPCA）数据显示，7月份巴西咖啡消费价格下降了1.01%，为18个月来首次下降。【原文：Brazil's consumer coffee prices fell 1.01% in July, the first drop in 18 months, according to data from the country's Broad National Consumer Price Index (IPCA) published on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-consumer-coffee-prices-fall-july-first-time-18-months-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRW77T2HDRNTDPNKJT6THTSPHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[系统故障导致短暂停飞后，西捷航空恢复航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[西捷航空公司（WestJet Airlines）周二表示，该公司正在恢复正常运营，此前该公司曾因临时系统故障被迫短暂停止所有航班的起飞。【原文：WestJet Airlines said on Tuesday a return to normal operations was underway after a temporary system outage had forced the Canadian carrier to briefly halt all departures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/westjet-resumes-flights-after-system-outage-triggered-brief-ground-stop-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEPKFUV2TFKCJELSHVL262433I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:10:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立法者称智利当局已开始调查阿尔贝马锂电厂事故]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名当地立法者周二告诉路透社记者，继上周报道了一起事故后，智利当局已对 Albemarle 公司的 La Negra 锂加工厂展开调查。【原文：Chilean authorities have opened an investigation into Albemarle's La Negra lithium processing plant following an accident reported last week, a local lawmaker told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/chilean-authorities-have-opened-probe-into-accident-albemarle-lithium-plant-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XARTSHXXVJNJLC5SR4PARYFOGM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司七月份飞机交付量比六月份下降 20%，落后于空中客车公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国飞机制造商波音公司周二表示，该公司7月份交付了48架飞机，低于6月份的60架，但比去年同期增加了5架。这是该公司自2017年以来交付飞机最多的7月份，当时交付了58架飞机。【原文：U.S. planemaker Boeing said on Tuesday that it delivered 48 airplanes in July, down from 60 in June but five more than a year earlier. It was the most deliveries by the company in July since 2017, when it delivered 58 aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-july-aircraft-deliveries-tumble-20-june-trailing-airbus-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOFMI6H7UFOKDC5IBFXZXEWRLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜权将承认在 400 亿美元加密货币崩盘案中的美国共谋和欺诈指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名法官在美国法院的听证会上说，韩国加密货币企业家权斗（Do Kwon）计划于周二承认共谋诈骗和电信欺诈两项指控。【原文：Do Kwon, the South Korean cryptocurrency entrepreneur behind two digital currencies that lost an estimated $40 billion in 2022, is planning to plead guilty on Tuesday to two charges of conspiracy to defraud and wire fraud, a judge said at a U.S. court hearing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/do-kwon-plead-guilty-us-conspiracy-fraud-charges-40-billion-crypto-collapse-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5H2HVHPPBKV7NZHA44RZTF5Q4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[施密德：美联储政策利率应暂时按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储主席杰弗里-施密德（Jeffrey Schmid）周二表示，美国央行不应将关税迄今为止对通胀的微弱影响视为降息的契机，而应将其视为货币政策 "校准适当 "的标志，他的这番言论与他的一些同事日益鸽派的基调形成了鲜明对比。【原文：The U.S. central bank should not take tariffs' muted effect on inflation so far as an opportunity to cut interest rates, but rather as a sign that monetary policy is "appropriately calibrated," Kansas City Federal Reserve President Jeffrey Schmid said on Tuesday, in remarks that contrast with the increasingly dovish tone of some of his colleagues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-policy-rate-should-stay-hold-now-schmid-says-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOQNYGMOJBOYTNREWNXAZCPGEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴姆勒、沃尔沃和其他卡车制造商起诉加州，要求阻止排放规则的实施]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括戴姆勒和沃尔沃在内的四大卡车制造商起诉加利福尼亚州，要求阻止该州执行美国总统唐纳德-特朗普 6 月份宣布无效的严格排放标准。【原文：Four major truckmakers, including Daimler and Volvo, sued California to block the state from enforcing strict emissions standards that U.S. President Donald Trump declared void in June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/daimler-volvo-other-truckmakers-sue-california-block-emissions-rules-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENAIAQ3V3NNQTIC6DWBW6VFIEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:24:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称，2024 年美国一次能源产出的 30% 用于出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（EIA）周二称，去年美国出口的能源约占其国内初级能源产量的 30%，与近几十年相比有了大幅增长。【原文：The United States exported about 30% of its domestic primary energy production last year, a significant increase over recent decades, the Energy Information Administration (EIA) said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-exported-30-its-primary-energy-output-2024-says-eia-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I46MBK3W3RMTJOXJYFEWY3RTOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普援引针对美联储鲍威尔的 "重大诉讼"，再次敦促降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二再次呼吁美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）降低基准利率，并列举了针对美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）有关央行大楼装修的 "重大诉讼"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday reiterated his call for the U.S. Federal Reserve to lower benchmark rates, and cited "a major lawsuit" against Fed Chair Jerome Powell over renovations of the central bank's buildings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-cites-major-lawsuit-against-feds-powell-again-urges-rate-cut-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWQJLUAU2RIMDKJKQ5HZS5T7WM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:03:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[里士满联储主席巴金消费者将是未来通胀和就业结果的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席汤姆-巴尔金（Tom Barkin）周二表示，消费者的积极购物行为可能会削弱关税对通胀的影响，但也可能导致需求下降和失业率上升的循环。【原文：Aggressive shopping by consumers may mute the impact of tariffs on inflation but could also lead to a cycle of falling demand and rising unemployment, Richmond Fed president Tom Barkin said on Tuesday, while adding he is hopeful a sharp rise in the jobless rate will be avoided because household spending has held up well so far.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/richmond-feds-barkin-consumers-will-be-key-coming-inflation-jobs-results-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMNS3VNLGJOHTEBVF7KQC4S5ZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，在高利率环境下，美国公司持有的现金自2021年以来减少了一半]]></title><description><![CDATA[清水分析公司（Clearwater Analytics）周二的数据显示，由于利率升高促使企业转向收益更高的国库券，美国企业的现金分配自2021年以来减少了一半。【原文：Cash allocations by U.S. corporations have halved since 2021 as elevated interest rates prompt a shift to higher-yielding treasury bills, data from Clearwater Analytics showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cash-held-by-us-companies-halved-since-2021-amid-high-interest-rates-data-shows-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUVP3AU54FJSRPZWMVDOZNMSF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电将在两年内逐步淘汰 6 英寸晶圆生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾积体电路制造股份有限公司（TSMC）周二表示，将在未来两年内逐步淘汰6英寸晶圆制造业务，并继续整合8英寸晶圆产能，以提高效率。【原文：Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC) will phase out its 6-inch wafer manufacturing business over the next two years and continue consolidating its 8-inch wafer production capacity to improve efficiency, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tsmc-phase-out-6-inch-wafer-production-over-two-years-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VU6GIREBZMF5MWTISNDIDNYGA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:15:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰成功测试星链（Starlink）的直达蜂窝技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰最大的移动运营商 Kyivstar 周二表示，该公司已在东欧成功进行了埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 Starlink 直对蜂窝卫星技术的首次现场测试。【原文：Ukraine's largest mobile operator Kyivstar has successfully conducted the first field test of Elon Musk's Starlink direct-to-cell satellite technology in Eastern Europe, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ukraine-successfully-tests-starlinks-direct-to-cell-technology-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNYNCENTXVN45MTIAJKMTHHOXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[注重隐私的智能手机制造商 Unplugged 将开始在美国内华达州组装手机]]></title><description><![CDATA[智能手机初创公司Unplugged周二表示，将于今年秋天开始在内华达州组装其注重隐私的 "UP Phone "手机，这标志着在特朗普政府推动扩大国内制造业的背景下，该公司将战略重点转向陆上生产。【原文：Smartphone startup Unplugged said on Tuesday it will start assembling its privacy-focused "UP Phone" in Nevada this fall, marking a strategic pivot toward onshore production as the Trump administration pushes to expand domestic manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/privacy-focused-smartphone-maker-unplugged-start-us-assembly-nevada-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUWSXJZH2FL6NHFPNW6XRIVWYY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:04:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic 以 1 美元的价格向美国政府提供人工智能聊天机器人 Claude]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）支持的 Anthropic 公司周二表示，它将以 1 美元的价格向美国政府提供其 Claude 人工智能模型，加入了越来越多的人工智能初创公司的行列，这些公司为赢得联邦合同提出了利润丰厚的交易。【原文：Amazon.com-backed Anthropic said on Tuesday it will offer its Claude AI model to the U.S. government for $1, joining a growing list of artificial intelligence startups proposing lucrative deals to win federal contracts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/anthropic-offers-ai-chatbot-claude-us-government-1-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A25VFFAVG5NR7AOHCG7DEIH5DA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 7 月通胀率上升，符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份美国消费者价格温和上涨，基本符合预期，但由于进口关税导致商品成本上升，衡量基本通胀率的指标出现了六个月来的最大涨幅。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased moderately in July, largely in line with expectations, though rising costs for goods because of import tariffs led to a measure of underlying inflation posting its largest gain in six months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-us-inflation-rises-july-line-with-expectations-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPCIJ24EEBIJBL7YCTF6G4MVUQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲软件股因担心人工智能陷阱而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，欧洲软件类股大幅下跌，权重股思爱普（SAP）下滑超过6%，原因是人们担心人工智能可能给这部分技术行业带来风险。【原文：Software stocks in Europe fell sharply on Tuesday, with heavyweight SAP sliding more than 6% amid concerns over the risks that artificial intelligence could pose to this part of the technology sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/software-stocks-europe-fall-concerns-over-ai-pitfalls-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRU6D5UYKVNBBNSRGXNZQ47NOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:53:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月消费者物价温和增长；数据质量问题日益突出]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管进口关税导致商品成本上升，导致衡量基本通胀率的指标出现六个月来的最大涨幅，但 7 月份美国消费者物价温和上涨。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased moderately in July, though rising costs for goods because of import tariffs led to a measure of underlying inflation posting its largest gain in six months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-prices-increase-moderately-july-data-quality-concerns-rising-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7NBPXULE5PG5JE2VNKDNCDLEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:40:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电气元件制造商 Hubbell 将以 8.25 亿美元收购同行 DMC Power]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hubbell 周二表示，它将以 8.25 亿美元现金收购规模较小的同行 DMC Power，这家电气设备制造商将加强其关键元件组合，以满足预期的电力需求增长。【原文：Hubbell said on Tuesday it will acquire smaller peer DMC Power for $825 million in cash, as the electrical equipment maker bolsters its critical components portfolio to meet an expected boom in power demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/electrical-component-maker-hubbell-buy-peer-dmc-power-825-million-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QFVQHURGHBMRDBKXFJWX34H47I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟等待美国就贸易协议承诺采取后续行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟发言人周二表示，欧盟无法透露与美国的关税联合声明何时准备就绪，也无法透露白宫何时会就欧洲汽车进口关税发布行政命令。【原文：The European Union could not say when a joint statement on tariffs with the United States would be ready, nor when the White House would issue an executive order on European car import duties, a spokesperson said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-union-awaits-us-follow-up-trade-deal-promises-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNO5W62INJJUXMNS5HQPSB2U4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:10:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国大麻重新分类如何帮助大麻公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府正寻求将大麻重新归类为危险性较低的毒品，这一转变可能会减轻刑事处罚，并通过降低税收负担和使企业更容易获得资金来重塑大麻产业。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is looking to reclassify marijuana as a less dangerous drug, a shift that could ease criminal penalties and reshape the pot industry by lowering tax burdens and making it easier for firms to secure funding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/how-us-marijuana-reclassification-could-help-cannabis-companies-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ5TVVOTIFKJJOBT56CE4NJSR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:59:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易平台 eToro 盈利超预期，零售投资蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[股票和加密货币交易平台eToro周二公布的第二季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，原因是尽管新关税带来了更广泛的宏观经济不确定性，但散户投资者仍保持了坚定的风险偏好。【原文：Stock and crypto trading platform eToro beat Wall Street views for profit in the second quarter on Tuesday, as retail investors maintained a firm risk appetite despite broader macroeconomic uncertainty due to new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trading-platform-etoro-beats-profit-estimates-retail-investing-boom-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNQSTANUYNKB7HSEQANOP5FEH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲第二季度企业利润前景进一步改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，最新的盈利预测显示，欧洲企业的健康前景已大大改善，在中美关税休战和欧盟-美国贸易协议延期后，欧洲企业的盈利持续上升。【原文：The outlook for European corporate health has considerably improved, the latest earnings forecasts showed on Tuesday, showing a continued rise after the extension of the U.S.-China tariff truce and the EU-U.S. trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-q2-corporate-profit-outlook-improves-further-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5XEOO44265PQBFU7M27FBW5H3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:14:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[稳定币发行商 Circle 自首次公开募股（IPO）以来的首份业绩报告显示，公司收入大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，Circle 发布了自 6 月份上市以来的首份季度财报，收入和储备收入均有所增长，这主要得益于其 USDC 稳定币发行量的增加和订阅服务的加强。【原文：Circle posted higher revenue and reserve income on Tuesday in its maiden quarterly results since going public in June, driven by increased circulation of its USDC stablecoin and stronger subscription services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stablecoin-issuer-circles-revenue-jumps-first-results-since-blockbuster-ipo-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDT6HJLSDVPUBJANGCSC3K2RIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>