<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:35:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:35:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车第三季度销量因欧洲和电动汽车而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车集团周五公布的第三季度全球交付量增长了 1%，原因是新车型促进了西欧市场的销售。【原文：Volkswagen Group reported a 1% increase in third-quarter global deliveries on Friday as new models helped sales in Western Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagens-third-quarter-sales-lifted-by-europe-evs-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIDYS37YIBNG5HOO6S4JLGCLVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场分析师对日本执政联盟分裂的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本执政联盟周五解体，小伙伴公明党反叛自民党新任强硬派领导人高市真奈，此举使她的首相候选人资格受到质疑。【原文：Japan's ruling coalition broke up on Friday, with junior partner Komeito rebelling against the Liberal Democratic Party's new hardline leader Sanae Takaichi in a move that cast doubt over her premiership bid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/market-analysts-reaction-japans-ruling-coalition-split-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUAIMFYRQZIN5M6E6M2VCXVH4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:26:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国机器人制造商 AgiBot 计划明年在香港上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，中国仿人机器人制造商AgiBot计划明年在香港首次公开募股，目标估值为400亿至500亿港元（合51.4亿至64亿美元）。【原文：Chinese humanoid robot maker AgiBot plans to launch an initial public offering in Hong Kong next year, eyeing a valuation of HK$40 billion to HK$50 billion ($5.14 billion to $6.4 billion), sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-robot-maker-agibot-plans-hong-kong-ipo-next-year-sources-say-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCDSWTFMLRJNPKKLGQCQOSZQJQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:20:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国就高通公司涉嫌违反反垄断法展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场监管部门周五表示，中国已对美国半导体制造商高通公司展开调查。【原文：China has initiated an investigation into U.S. semiconductor manufacturer Qualcomm, the country's market regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-opens-probe-into-qualcomm-suspected-anti-trust-violation-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FF5QGALN7JLPXGQUFM247EHS54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国启动监管谷歌搜索的新权力]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国周五指定谷歌在网络搜索领域具有 "战略市场地位"，这是英国首次运用新的权力来应对大型科技公司的主导地位，并为其认为必要的干预措施铺平道路。【原文：Britain on Friday designated Google with "strategic market status" in online search, the first time it has deployed new powers to tackle the dominance of big tech and paving the way for interventions it deems necessary.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/uk-gains-new-powers-over-google-with-search-market-designation-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIND63GCSVPN3EUSKTGJPL6LDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，投资者将目光投向大名鼎鼎的公司之外，创纪录地向太空投资 35 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据专注于太空领域的投资公司 Seraphim Space 周五发布的一份报告显示，在更多初创企业和持续国防开支的推动下，第三季度全球太空投资达到创纪录的 35 亿美元。【原文：Global space investment hit a record $3.5 billion in the third quarter, driven by a wider range of startups and continued defense spending, according to a report released Friday by space-focused investment firm Seraphim Space.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/investors-pour-record-35-billion-into-space-investors-look-beyond-big-names-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7EEVMQXTNLTJDSEF2DXKXHYXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行研究发现美国关税拖累欧盟信心和就业]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行研究人员周五在一篇博文中写道，只有少数欧元区工人担心美国关税会危及他们的工作，但这仍可能给本已疲软的经济带来拖累。【原文：Only a small minority of euro zone workers fear that U.S. tariffs will jeopardise their jobs but that could still create a drag for an already sluggish economy, European Central Bank researchers wrote in a blog post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-tariffs-drag-eu-confidence-jobs-ecb-study-finds-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPKLJOUTGJKKRB2KFZ7XPTFG7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因关税相关成本影响预期，李维斯下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 的股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌了 7.7%，原因是与关税相关的成本超过了欧洲和美洲市场对宽腿牛仔裤的强劲需求，这家牛仔布生产商的年度利润预期未能达到投资者的预期。【原文：Levi Strauss's shares slipped 7.7% in premarket trading on Friday after the denim maker's annual profit forecast failed to meet investor expectations, as tariff-linked costs outweighed strong demand for wide-leg denims in Europe and the Americas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/levi-strauss-slips-tariff-related-costs-weigh-forecast-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6HFGDP4WDBMTNN2NEC35ZPJHHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Five：政治的危险]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国和日本的政治动荡笼罩着市场，美国银行拉开了最新财报季的序幕，而政府关门仍在继续，决策者们聚集在华盛顿参加国际货币基金组织（IMF）和世界银行的年会。【原文：Political turmoil in France and Japan looms large over markets as U.S. banks kick off the latest earnings season, while the government shutdown drags on and policymakers gather in Washington for the IMF and World Bank annual meetings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/take-five/global-markets-themes-graphic-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSSFRSJEQBM2ZGVUFU2JZBK5TU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国银行转向美国金融公司 BNY 进行国际汇款]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国的储蓄银行正在求助于一家领先的美国金融公司来帮助客户进行国际支付，此举旨在抵御后起的低成本竞争者，引起了人们对欧洲金融服务主权的担忧。【原文：Germany's savings banks are turning to a leading U.S. financial firm to help customers with international payments, a move aimed at fending off upstart low-cost competitors that has raised concerns over the sovereignty of Europe's financial services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/german-banks-turn-us-financial-firm-bny-international-money-transfers-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJA4R5FH5ZII3JWX2QHSOBG7RI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:36:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚称取消芯片关税豁免会损害竞争力和美国供应链]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一份政府报告称，马来西亚周五警告称，美国取消对其半导体出口的关税豁免可能会损害其竞争力，并使供应网络紧张。【原文：Malaysia warned on Friday that any removal of tariff exemptions on its semiconductor exports by the United States could hurt its competitiveness and strain supply networks, according to a government report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/malaysia-says-removing-chip-tariff-exemption-could-harm-competitiveness-us-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCDX3Y4YXZLGBNL6ILSXKRIVEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Papa John's 高层表示将印度列为优先考虑的素食地区]]></title><description><![CDATA[约翰爸爸国际公司（Papa John's International）的高管们表示，该公司将印度列为其全球优先市场之一，并根据当地人的口味推出了素食占多数的处女菜单，预计此举将促进公司的长期增长。【原文：Papa John's International is placing India among its priority markets globally and tailoring its offerings to local tastes with its maiden majority-vegetarian menu, executives said, in a move the U.S. pizza chain expects will fuel long-term growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/papa-johns-puts-india-priority-list-with-vegetarian-fare-executives-say-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U27JDDNSNJNANBAVYG6WUENYIE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长称希腊力争今年敲定雪佛龙天然气勘探合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊能源部长周五表示，希腊正在努力争取与美国石油巨头雪佛龙及其希腊合作伙伴 Helleniq Energy 在年底前敲定希腊近海能源勘探合同。【原文：Greece is working hard to finalise a contract with U.S. oil major Chevron and its Greek partner Helleniq Energy for energy exploration offshore Greece by the end of the year, the country's energy minister said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/greece-seeks-finalise-chevron-gas-exploration-contract-this-year-says-minister-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERRLXQ2Y55JLLG52PDAEB3VZZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球金融监管机构将加强对人工智能的监控]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着银行和金融业其他部门加大人工智能的使用，全球金融监管机构已经制定了更密切监控风险的计划。【原文：Global financial regulators have laid out plans for closer monitoring of the risks as banks and other parts of the financial industry ramp up the use of artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-financial-watchdogs-ramp-up-monitoring-ai-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWSU75JYPBKD3KSXKH6TF6HHRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将从 10 月 14 日起对美国船只征收额外港口费]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国交通部周五表示，自10月14日起，美国公司和个人拥有或运营的船舶，或在美国建造或悬挂美国国旗的船舶，将被征收额外的港口费。【原文：Vessels owned or operated by U.S. firms and individuals - or those built in the United States or that fly the U.S. flag - will be charged additional port fees per voyage starting on October 14, China's transport ministry said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-hit-us-ships-with-additional-port-fees-october-14-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQM4URMMWFLJFPPX6TTDGJ22EA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 第三季度出货量增长 13%，达到 130 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 汽车制造商周五表示，第三季度全球出货量同比增长 13%，估计达到 130 万辆。【原文：Stellantis' global shipments rose 13% year-on-year in the third quarter to an estimated 1.3 million units, the automaker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-third-quarter-shipments-rise-13-13-million-vehicles-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2D2NFRTFVMMPHMZ3CFFBZWHGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：比尔-盖茨与泛美卫生组织考虑为低收入国家提供减肥药物的方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[盖茨基金会和泛美卫生组织告诉路透社，这两个全球健康组织都在研究如何让低收入国家更容易获得减肥药物，如诺和诺德的Wegovy和礼来的Mounjaro。【原文：The Gates Foundation and the Pan American Health Organization are both working on ways to make weight-loss drugs like Novo Nordisk's Wegovy and Eli Lilly's Mounjaro more accessible in lower-income countries, the global health groups told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bill-gates-paho-consider-ways-bring-weight-loss-drugs-lower-income-countries-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5UP7XSW25I5DINGA4AUNS5VNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美紧张局势的最新症结是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）和中国国家主席习近平将于本月访问首尔，在中美举行会谈之前，中国政府正在积累谈判筹码，宣布新的出口管制措施，以加强对高科技制造业供应链的控制。【原文：Beijing is stacking up its bargaining chips ahead of expected U.S.-China talks when Presidents Donald Trump and Xi Jinping visit Seoul this month, announcing new export controls to tighten its grip over high-tech manufacturing supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/what-are-latest-sticking-points-us-china-tensions-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RACNVINLSRIF7NZOKANWOUPVKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[基金经理薪酬飙升让艾斯勒资本公司损失惨重]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者和业内人士表示，由于员工成本飙升侵蚀了交易利润，艾斯勒资本公司决定关闭其旗舰多策略对冲基金，这暴露出总部位于伦敦的基金在试图快速发展和复制规模更大、根基稳固的美国公司时所面临的困难。【原文：Eisler Capital's decision to close its flagship multi-strategy hedge fund as soaring staff costs eroded trading profit exposes the difficulty London-based funds face when trying to grow rapidly and replicate bigger, entrenched U.S. players, investors and industry insiders say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/soaring-fund-manager-pay-cost-eisler-capital-dear-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INUU2NKUYVJX3KPJDLHWJVMJGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，软银正在洽谈由 Arm 股票支持的 50 亿美元保证金贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，软银集团公司（SoftBank Group Corp）正在商谈以其芯片部门 Arm Holdings 的股票为抵押，向全球银行借入 50 亿美元保证金贷款。【原文：SoftBank Group Corp is in talks to borrow $5 billion from global banks for a margin loan secured by shares of its chip unit Arm Holdings , Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-talks-5-billion-margin-loan-backed-by-arm-stock-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2KVQ6A6LBIQ3GRZL2LRIOGBJM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:55:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国海关加大对英伟达人工智能芯片的打击力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周五报道，中国加大了对芯片进口限制的执行力度，旨在减少国内科技公司对美国产品的依赖，如英伟达（Nvidia）的人工智能处理器。【原文：China has ramped up enforcement of its chip import restrictions, aiming to reduce domestic technology companies' dependence on U.S. products such as Nvidia's artificial intelligence processors, the Financial Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-steps-up-customs-crackdown-nvidia-ai-chips-ft-reports-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNIXKTYQ2RJXTJNX4LEABWO7HQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利：劳动力市场正处于 "令人担忧 "的地步]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周四表示，劳动力市场疲软和通胀放缓是上个月做出降息决定的原因，并促使美联储发出了未来可能进一步降息的信号。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly said on Thursday that a softening labor market and easing inflation were reasons behind last month's decision to cut rates, and prompted the Fed to signal the possibility of further rate cuts ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-daly-labor-market-is-worrisome-point-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLBBHOWX2NPCHJ7ISJQ6Q2U5JE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大宗商品反弹后喘息，亚洲股市波澜不惊，日元成为关注焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于华尔街的跌势持续到早盘，亚洲股市在本周结束时摇摇欲坠，而大宗商品市场则在近期冲高后稍作喘息。【原文：Asian stocks limped towards the end of the week on a shaky footing on Friday as declines on Wall Street lingered into early trading, while commodity markets took a breather after their recent charge higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2H2MMHDXJMOXN3D24TVSCQXRM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:51:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加息预期减弱，日元创一年来最大单周跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元将创下一年来的最大单周跌幅，因为投资者担心今年再次加息的可能性迅速减小，而日本下任首相的言论也未能安抚市场的不安情绪。【原文：The yen was set for its steepest weekly drop in a year on Friday, as investors fretted about fast-receding chances of another rate hike this year while comments from Japan's likely next prime minister failed to soothe market jitters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-heads-sharpest-weekly-fall-year-rate-hike-wagers-recede-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYYDH6XDXFNQHLN24CCHW3MX7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加沙协议达成后风险溢价消退，石油价格变化不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五亚市早盘，油价在上一交易日下跌超过1%后变化不大，原因是以色列和哈马斯就结束加沙战争的第一阶段计划达成一致后，市场的战争风险溢价减弱。【原文：Oil prices were little changed in early Asian trade on Friday after falling more than 1% in the previous session, as the market's war risk premium faded after Israel and Hamas agreed to the first phase of a plan to end the war in Gaza.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-little-changed-amid-fading-risk-premium-after-gaza-deal-2025-10-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGOI62V2TFITFC2HUPVVMEHHPY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:19:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通估计美国每周申请失业救济人数再次增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）周四估计，上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量再次增加，暗示与美国政府停摆有关的一些提前裁员现象。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased again last week, JPMorgan estimated on Thursday, hinting at some early layoffs related to the U.S. government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increased-again-jpmorgan-estimates-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJIWWPFPDRNWLMDJLCQPREIK7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国停摆阻碍关键农作物数据，农民和贸易商 "盲目飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[在联邦政府停摆期间，对全球谷物和大豆交易至关重要的美国数据已经失效，导致大宗商品交易商和农民在秋收高峰期无法获得作物产量预估、出口销售数据和市场报告。【原文：U.S. data vital to global grain and soybean trading has gone dark during the federal government's shutdown, leaving commodity traders and farmers without crop production estimates, export sales data and market reports during the peak of the autumn harvest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/farmers-traders-flying-blind-us-shutdown-blocks-key-crop-data-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLNLOQWWY5NT5PL5BRRJY3RBSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称殖民地管道公司将裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，美国最大的燃料运输系统运营商 Colonial 管道公司本周通知员工，该公司正计划裁员。【原文：The Colonial Pipeline Company, operator of the largest U.S. fuel transportation system, informed employees this week that it is planning to cut some jobs, according to two sources familiar with the matter and a company statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/colonial-pipeline-cut-jobs-sources-say-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHAFCK2RMFP3PCK5LRG2K2JTH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:05:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，美国前美联储理事拉里-林赛撤回美联储主席候选人提名]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国有线电视新闻网（CNBC）周四报道，前美国联邦储备委员会理事拉里-林赛（Larry Lindsey）已退出美国央行主席一职的竞选。【原文：Former U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Larry Lindsey has withdrawn his name from consideration for the position of chair of the U.S. central bank, CNBC reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/former-us-fed-governor-larry-lindsey-withdraws-name-fed-chair-cnbc-reports-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5DENUBMSRLLPIETBKV6V5ZVOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街监管机构在政府停摆期间放宽 IPO 通道]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街最高监管机构周四在其网站上发布公告，放宽了公司在联邦政府关门期间进行首次公开募股的条件。【原文：Wall Street's top regulator on Thursday eased the way for companies to proceed with initial public offerings during the federal government's shutdown, according to an announcement on its website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/wall-street-regulator-eases-ipo-path-during-government-shutdown-2025-10-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMA3G7JJVRINLAU5DIO6SULXEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:52:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>