<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:37:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:37:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行调查显示，12月澳大利亚商业活动有所回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项衡量澳大利亚商业状况的指标显示，随着销售额和利润的改善，12月份该指标有所回升。但企业闲置产能有限，表明经济可能正接近其增长上限。【原文：A measure of Australian business conditions picked up in December as sales and profits improved, a survey showed on Tuesday, while limited spare capacity at firms suggested the economy could be bumping up against its speed limit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-business-activity-picks-up-december-nab-survey-shows-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5JTECKSXJLPXDQWI5AFAYGZ3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:33:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国安踏体育斥资18亿美元收购彪马29.1%股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国安踏体育周二宣布，已同意以15.1亿欧元（约合17.9亿美元）从皮诺家族旗下的Artémis控股公司手中收购德国运动服饰制造商彪马29.06%的股权。【原文：China's Anta Sports Products said on Tuesday it had agreed to buy a 29.06% stake in German sportswear maker Puma from the Pinault family's Artémis holding company for 1.51 billion euros ($1.79 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/anta-sports-acquire-291-puma-artmis-18-billion-deal-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABAFR7J4IVNE7EX2K7FZECWV4E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:21:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发文提议提高关税后，韩国汽车制造商股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车股价周二开盘下跌4%，此前美国总统特朗普在社交媒体发文称，将把包括汽车在内的韩国商品关税从15%提高至25%。【原文：Hyundai Motor ​shares fell 4% ‌at the opening on Tuesday, after ‌U.S. President Donald Trump ​said in a social ‍media post that he will raise ⁠tariffs ‍on South Korean goods ‌including ‌autos from 15% to 25%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shares-south-korean-automakers-slide-after-trump-post-raising-tariffs-2026-01-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5K6WAFORPZKSDFXWZ2BZBTP5RY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国重整联邦航空管理局，旨在加强安全监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周一宣布，将重组联邦航空管理局，并设立新的安全监督办公室，整合五个不同部门的职能。【原文：The Trump administration said on Monday it is restructuring the Federal Aviation Administration and will create a new safety oversight office to consolidate functions across five different units.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-revamps-faa-aiming-improve-safety-oversight-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGXDNX2X6ZMJVDJLZTO5QNGPVI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:50:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官权衡学区对社交媒体公司的成瘾指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms及其他社交媒体公司的律师周一请求加州联邦法官阻止多个学区将针对这些公司的诉讼提交审判，辩称联邦法律保护他们免于被指控蓄意诱使年轻用户上瘾。【原文：Attorneys for Meta Platforms and other social media companies asked a California federal judge on Monday to block several school districts from taking their lawsuits against the companies to trial, arguing that federal law protects them from claims they knowingly addicted young users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/us-judge-weighs-school-districts-addiction-claims-against-social-media-companies-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C43LYYERBBLUTOCZDXJ7ZOKIDI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:48:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团遭前高管起诉，指控其性骚扰处理不当]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周一被一名前董事总经理起诉，该员工称自己在遭到财富管理业务主管、银行高管之一安迪·西格性骚扰后被迫离职。【原文：Citigroup was sued on Monday by a former managing director who said she was forced out after being sexually harassed by Andy Sieg, who oversees the bank's wealth management unit and is one of the bank's top executives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/citigroup-sued-by-former-executive-who-says-it-mishandled-sexual-harassment-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZL5HRRQNFKD5AIQB225ROMT24</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管美国大豆进口量再度增加，中国上半年仍将优先进口巴西大豆]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计2026年上半年中国将加大巴西大豆进口力度。创纪录的产量和具有竞争力的价格将推动装运量增长，这将巩固南美在世界最大油籽进口国中的主导地位，即便美国供应恢复亦是如此。【原文：China is expected to boost imports of Brazilian soybeans in the first half of 2026, as record production and competitive prices propel shipments, reinforcing South America's dominance in the world's biggest oilseed importer, even as U.S. supplies return.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-favour-brazilian-soybean-imports-h1-despite-renewed-us-inflows-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RO7Q5UOTHFM3RNVDRFZOOYYUYE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布朗与布朗公司第四季度利润因手续费与佣金增长而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[布朗与布朗周一公布第四季度经调整利润上升，这家保险经纪公司受益于强劲需求推动的佣金和费用收入增长。【原文：Brown & Brown reported a rise in fourth-quarter adjusted profit on Monday, as the insurance broker benefited from higher income from commissions and fees on the back of strong demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/brown-browns-fourth-quarter-profit-rises-fee-commission-growth-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMPEVCRHVJNCJEEIOUJPI6X7N4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉石油改革吸引即时投资，但仍需深化改革，企业高管表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[委内瑞拉拟议的石油法改革足以鼓励在该国运营的企业扩大业务，并吸引部分新进入者开始投资。但外国和本地高管及律师表示，要吸引美国所称的1000亿美元资金以重振该国能源部门，则需要更深层次的改革。【原文：A proposed reform of Venezuela's oil law is enough to encourage companies working in the country to expand and for some new entrants to begin investing, but deeper reforms would be necessary to attract the $100 billion the U.S. says is required to revamp the nation's energy sector, foreign and local executives and lawyers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuela-oil-reform-encourages-immediate-investment-still-needs-go-deeper-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SELGGOKFDBODFOLPTZOU3DUUAE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽柯钢铁第四季度业绩未达预期，成本拖累利润率；股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁制造商纽柯公司周一公布的第四季度利润和营收未达华尔街预期，因成本上升对其钢铁生产部门的利润率构成压力，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌3.4%。【原文：U.S. steelmaker Nucor's fourth-quarter profit and revenue missed Wall Street expectations on ​Monday as rising costs pressured margins ‌in its steel-producing segments, sending its shares down 3.4% in aftermarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nucor-misses-fourth-quarter-estimates-costs-drag-margins-shares-fall-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYD6DL2GI5J3HMHUNQOMV4CAF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:49:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞穗银行聘请德意志银行资深人士理查德·罗宾逊担任高级工业银行家]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的一份内部备忘录显示，瑞穗金融集团已聘请投资银行家理查德·罗宾逊担任工业集团副主席兼董事总经理。【原文：Mizuho Financial Group has hired investment banker Richard Robinson as vice chairman and managing director in the Industrials Group, according to an internal memo reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/mizuho-hires-deutsche-bank-veteran-richard-robinson-senior-industrials-banker-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXZRAQ3Y5VNI7HVHOPUBWYVZXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:36:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[硅谷知名风投公司内部出现分歧，凸显科技界对ICE枪击事件的立场对立]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯移民官员周六枪杀美国公民事件引发的激烈政治言论蔓延至硅谷，一家知名风投公司的合伙人纷纷与为枪击行为辩护的同事划清界限。【原文：Heated political rhetoric over the fatal shooting of a U.S. citizen by immigration agents in Minneapolis on Saturday spilled into Silicon Valley as partners at an influential venture firm distanced themselves from a colleague who defended the killing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/rift-influential-silicon-valley-venture-firm-shows-techs-divide-over-ice-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXPXBCF2OZK3BBUCHJI53I5BXI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将提高对韩国进口商品的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周一宣布，将对韩国输美汽车、木材和药品等商品加征关税至25%，同时指责这个盟国的立法机构未能履行与华贸易协议。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Monday he was increasing tariffs on South Korean imports into the U.S. related to autos, lumber and pharmaceuticals to 25%, while accusing the ally's legislature of "not living up" to its trade deal with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-says-he-is-raising-tariffs-certain-south-korean-imports-25-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6J7FW4CXDBMTJMTQ2CBOD6HBBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:09:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 大行情，重大周前夕]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球股市周一攀升至新高，黄金价格突破每盎司5000美元大关，而美元跌势加速，因投资者正为本周即将到来的美国企业财报洪流及美联储政策决议做准备。【原文：World stocks climbed to new highs and gold smashed through the $5,000-an-ounce barrier on Monday, while the dollar's slide gathered pace as investors braced for a deluge of U.S. earnings and a Federal Reserve policy decision this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CBDZH5XZZLKLCJJJBPFUPQOUA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[W. R. 伯克利季度营业收入因承保业务强劲及投资收益增长而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[商业保险公司W. R. Berkley周一报告称，得益于稳健的承保业绩和投资组合收益，其第四季度营业利润实现增长。【原文：Commercial insurer W. R. Berkley reported a rise in fourth-quarter operating profit on Monday, helped by steady underwriting performance ​and gains from its investment portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/w-r-berkley-quarterly-operating-income-rises-strong-underwriting-investment-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DA57HK45YVIILMP66S56DHMWUQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国国民议会支持禁止15岁以下青少年使用社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国国民议会周一批准了一项立法，禁止15岁以下儿童使用社交媒体，此举源于人们对网络欺凌和心理健康风险日益增长的担忧。【原文：France's National Assembly on Monday approved legislation banning children under 15-years old from social media over growing concerns about online bullying and mental health risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/frances-lower-house-backs-social-media-ban-those-under-15-years-old-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SNQTWFZAJOJTJN4M2DPN6237A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:41:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得州州长禁止州政府雇员使用阿里巴巴、Temu旗下产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[得克萨斯州州长周一发表声明称，该州将禁止其雇员使用阿里巴巴、Temu和TP-Link的软硬件产品，并表示此举旨在保护"得州居民隐私"免受中国政府侵害。【原文：Texas will bar its employees from using Alibaba, Temu and TP-Link hardware and software, the governor said in a statement on Monday, saying his state made the decision to protect the "privacy of Texans" from the Chinese government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/texas-governor-bars-state-employees-using-alibaba-temu-products-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCYBFT6QE5L6XCOEQGIRHP7T3A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《华尔街日报》报道，美国政府提议明年保持医保保险公司支付费率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周一报道，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普政府提议明年对保险公司支付的联邦医疗保险费用平均仅提高0.09%。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has proposed an average rate increase of just 0.09% in Medicare payments to insurers next year, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-proposes-keeping-steady-medicare-rates-paid-insurers-wsj-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLFFXHGRVVOY7DA4JMFEGDLLSE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:20:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据CNBC报道，耐克将在美国分销中心裁员775人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国财经媒体CNBC周一报道，耐克公司正计划裁员775人，以提升利润并加速自动化进程。该报道援引知情人士消息称。【原文：Nike is laying off 775 employees in a bid to boost profits and accelerate its use of automation, CNBC reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-cut-775-jobs-us-distribution-centers-cnbc-reports-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDIKHQI3YZK4TJW7OZ7KV7F364</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士及文件显示，贸易公司将开始出口委内瑞拉液化石油气]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周一获得的两份消息来源及一份航运文件显示，贸易公司已开始为装运和出口委内瑞拉液化石油气（LPG）做准备，此举是加拉加斯与华盛顿之间达成5000万桶石油供应协议的一部分。【原文：Trading houses have begun making preparations to load and export Venezuelan liquefied petroleum gas (LPG) as part of a 50-million-barrel oil supply deal between Caracas and Washington, according to two sources and a shipping document seen by Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trading-houses-begin-exporting-venezuelan-lpg-sources-document-say-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MILAMC4LBRPYJGW3ELN5XYGVQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国设备租赁与融资协会称，12月美国企业设备贷款增长逾5%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国设备租赁与金融协会周一表示，去年12月美国企业为购买设备融资的借款额较上年同期增长5.9%，达到历史第二高水平。【原文：U.S. companies borrowed 5.9% more to finance equipment purchases in December than a year earlier, reaching the second-highest level ever, the Equipment Leasing and Finance Association said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-business-borrowing-equipment-rises-over-5-december-elfa-says-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5EINSGMV5NQRIA6MVGNBKU3Q4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:10:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔吉特新任首席执行官称明尼苏达州暴力事件"令人痛心不已"]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯市塔吉特公司即将上任的首席执行官周一告诉员工，"暴力事件和生命逝去令人痛彻心扉"。此前联邦特工于周末在明尼阿波利斯市枪杀了一名抗议者。【原文：The incoming CEO of Minneapolis-based Target told employees on Monday that "the violence and loss of life is incredibly painful" after federal agents shot and killed another protestor in Minneapolis over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/targets-incoming-ceo-calls-minnesota-violence-incredibly-painful-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5MYJ3ZXP5O7JBRRZL3E64SVUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达推出AI模型，实现更快、更经济的天气预报]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达周一发布了三款开源人工智能模型，旨在帮助更快地创建更精准的天气预报。【原文：Nvidia on Monday released three open-source artificial intelligence models aimed at helping create better weather forecasts, faster.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/nvidia-unveils-ai-models-faster-cheaper-weather-forecasts-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA2JDTJYTVOPPIIMAQICEPWK7A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:44:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源行业因冬季风暴导致日均200万桶原油产量中断而陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和交易员估计，上周末美国石油生产商每日减产高达200万桶，约占全国产量的15%。这场席卷全美的冬季风暴使能源基础设施和电网承受巨大压力。【原文：U.S. oil producers lost up to 2 million barrels per day or roughly 15% of national production over the weekend, analysts and traders estimated, as a winter storm swept across the country, straining energy infrastructure and power grids.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-energy-sector-reels-after-winter-storm-knocks-out-2-million-bpd-crude-output-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MON26QNP2RKPBGVSJMN5C6PQ4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府迈出在加州提供新近海石油钻探租约的第一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周一邀请石油和天然气行业提名加州南部和中部海域的潜在油气租赁区块，相关拍卖最早将于明年举行。【原文：The Trump administration on Monday invited the oil and gas industry to nominate areas for a potential sale of offshore oil and gas leases in Southern and Central California to be held as soon as next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-takes-first-step-toward-offering-new-offshore-oil-drilling-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RORSIPBDD5JADO6B6L3ZOP7LQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VinFast携手Autobrains开发低成本自动驾驶技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南汽车制造商VinFast周一宣布，已与人工智能公司Autobrains达成合作，共同开发包括低成本"机器人汽车"系统在内的先进自动驾驶技术，此举有望推动这家越南电动汽车制造商的自动驾驶技术发展。【原文：VinFast has partnered with AI firm Autobrains to develop advanced autonomous driving technology, including a low-cost "Robo-car" system, the companies said on Monday, potentially boosting the Vietnamese EV maker's self-driving tech push.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vinfast-teams-up-with-autobrains-develop-low-cost-self-driving-tech-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZ7MSGCMQFLRXOOEIYQH2SWVRE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[First Brands在破产危机中寻求买家，将逐步关闭核心业务部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[First Brands周一表示，已开始逐步缩减其北美部分业务，包括Brake Parts、Cardone和Autolite等业务单元，同时保留其余业务的运营，该公司正寻求为这些资产寻找买家。【原文：First Brands said on Monday it has begun winding down parts of its North American operations, including its Brake Parts, ​Cardone and Autolite units, while keeping its remaining businesses ‌running as the company seeks buyers for the assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/first-brands-wind-down-key-units-it-seeks-buyers-amid-bankruptcy-crisis-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2V6VCBOHZPHDNLGM4HBSGASWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:56:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯在委内瑞拉看到显著的收入机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[油田服务公司贝克休斯周一表示，委内瑞拉蕴藏着巨大的营收机遇，在该国开展业务的主要考量因素包括员工安全与工作条件，以及法律法规框架的明确性。【原文：Oilfield services company Baker Hughes said on Monday that there is significant revenue opportunity in Venezuela, with the main considerations for operating there being safety and conditions for employees, and clarity on legal and regulatory frameworks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/baker-hughes-sees-significant-revenue-opportunity-venezuela-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIXTA37VHRPYFL4QWQSSDJN3FU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tether称其在第四季度购入27吨黄金]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大稳定币发行方Tether周一表示，2025年第四季度其基金黄金配置增加了约27吨，与分析师预估的第三季度26吨购金量基本持平。【原文：Tether, issuer of the world's largest stablecoin, added about 27 metric tons of gold to its fund exposure in the fourth quarter of 2025, it said on Monday, broadly unchanged from its third-quarter purchases estimated by analysts at 26 tons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tether-says-it-bought-27-tons-gold-fourth-quarter-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSIHWESIPFJU3BEGQSR32I4M2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:50:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储加息暂停在即，推动债券投资者重返风险资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[债券投资者正为美联储降息周期的延长停顿做准备，同时他们正转向风险稍高的交易。这种转变源于经济韧性强劲以及美国新的财政刺激计划——这些计划很可能在今年提振消费者支出。【原文：Bond investors are bracing for an extended pause in the Federal Reserve's rate-cutting cycle as they edge into slightly riskier trades, driven by a resilient economy and fresh U.S. fiscal stimulus plans that are likely to boost consumer spending this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/looming-fed-rate-pause-nudges-bond-investors-back-into-risk-2026-01-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HS737GI3H5PIZKQOV6PAOQ27GA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>