<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 08:36:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 08:36:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，欧佩克+将在 2024 年和 2025 年延长减产计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+组织的两位消息人士在该组织周日召开会议前表示，欧佩克+组织可能会将自愿减产石油的期限延长至2024年第三季度，也可能延长至第四季度，并将部分减产期限延长至2025年。【原文：OPEC+ will likely prolong voluntary oil cuts into the third and possibly fourth quarters of 2024 and extend some cuts into 2025, two OPEC+ sources said ahead of the group's meeting on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-seen-prolonging-cuts-2024-into-2025-two-sources-say-2024-06-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLA3JGBIKRIHHJ4P36OF2JFJ7E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 07:33:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，波音公司高管不太可能因 737 MAX 坠毁事件受到指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部官员在一次会议上告诉受害者家属，波音公司高管不太可能因2018年和2019年造成346人死亡的致命空难受到刑事指控，因为诉讼时效很可能已经过去。【原文：Boeing executives are unlikely to be criminally charged over fatal crashes in 2018 and 2019 that killed 346 people as the statute of limitations has likely passed, U.S. Justice Department officials told victims' family members in a meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-executives-unlikely-be-charged-over-737-max-crashes-source-says-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJGVORVB3FJ33LV42IAMAG6MRQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:35:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司高管称波音公司的困境是整个行业的 "负担]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司的竞争对手空中客车公司（Airbus）的一位高层管理人员说，波音公司在今年早些时候发生门塞爆炸事故后暴露出的安全和质量问题有可能动摇旅客的飞行信心。【原文：Safety and quality problems exposed at Boeing following a door plug blowout earlier this year risk shaking travellers' confidence in flying, a top executive at rival Airbus said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-woes-burden-entire-sector-airbus-executive-says-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYC6NRZX2VLLHIRTAXDEF7IDNA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司承诺采用波音 MAX 10，但预计交付时间不会太短]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司首席执行官埃德-巴斯蒂安（Ed Bastian）上周六表示，尽管达美航空预计在一段时间内不会收到飞机，但该公司仍将继续订购波音 737 MAX 10 机型，并将于明年开始交付。【原文：Delta Air Lines is still committed to the Boeing 737 MAX 10 model that it has on order for deliveries beginning next year, even though it does not anticipate receiving the aircraft for some time, CEO Ed Bastian said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-air-lines-committed-boeing-max-10-doesnt-expect-delivery-soon-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F674E6RP4RMNBJ4FCWIXBVJUXM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 12:40:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国私募股权公司收购埃弗顿失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃弗顿俱乐部周六表示，埃弗顿与未来所有者 777 Partners 的收购协议已经到期，此前这家美国私募股权公司未能在周五截止日期前完成对 Farhad Moshiri 大部分股权的收购。【原文：Everton's takeover agreement with prospective owner 777 Partners has expired, the Premier League club said on Saturday, after the U.S. private equity firm failed to complete the acquisition of Farhad Moshiri's majority stake by the Friday deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/everton-takeover-by-us-private-equity-firm-falls-through-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IV2NDYBKSVK5VMZGABVNAZCOAA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 08:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯放宽卢布合同外汇销售要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据对政府法令的修改，如果出口商合同价值的一半以上是以卢布支付的，俄罗斯政府将放宽对出口商强制出售外汇的要求。【原文：The Russian government has softened requirements for mandatory sales of foreign currency for exporters if more than half of the value of their contracts is paid in roubles, according to changes to a government decree.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russia-eases-forex-sales-requirements-contracts-roubles-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSAI7JFJ6BPVNFHNQP2PXIIGII</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会谈判陷入僵局，美国航空公司面临罢工威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与美国航空集团公司的合同谈判未能达成协议后，代表该公司空乘人员的工会周五要求工人准备罢工行动。【原文：A union representing flight attendants for American Airlines Group Inc on Friday asked workers to prepare for strike action after contract negotiations with the carrier failed to produce an agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/american-airlines-faces-strike-threat-union-negotiations-stall-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZVAO2MCKVKODDG5LBCKJGEKXY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 05:40:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，5月份中国新房价格连续第9个月上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项民间调查显示，5月份中国新房价格连续第九个月小幅上涨。【原文：New home prices in China rose slightly for a ninth month in May, a private survey showed, driven higher by a slew of supportive steps to prop up the nation's crisis-hit property sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-new-home-prices-inch-up-9th-month-may-survey-shows-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EERE4CB4F5NUPKOLLW46AV4GVA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 02:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Live Nation 调查 Ticketmaster 黑客攻击事件，关注用户数据泄露问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[Live Nation Entertainment 周五表示，公司正在调查 5 月 20 日发现的 Ticketmaster 部门数据泄露事件，这是去年一连串备受瞩目的企业黑客攻击事件中的最新一起。【原文：Live Nation Entertainment said on Friday it was investigating a data breach at its Ticketmaster unit that it discovered on May 20, the latest in a string of high-profile corporate hacks in the past year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/live-nation-probing-ticketmaster-hack-amid-user-data-leak-concerns-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7KZHMX7ONLDDLIDE2LY5NQ43E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:57:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉股东起诉马斯克涉嫌 75 亿美元内幕交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名特斯拉股东周四提起诉讼，指控首席执行官埃隆-马斯克在2022年底出售这家电动汽车制造商超过75亿美元的股票时涉嫌内幕交易，称这位亿万富翁企业家在可能令人失望的生产和交付数据公布之前就出售了股票。【原文：A Tesla shareholder filed a lawsuit on Thursday accusing CEO Elon Musk of insider trading when he sold over $7.5 billion of shares of the electric car maker in late 2022, saying the billionaire entrepreneur sold the shares before potentially disappointing production and delivery numbers were made public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tesla-shareholder-sues-musk-alleged-75-billion-insider-trading-2024-06-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAHXSY73RBMZDCZOHX4YFXDK5Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:23:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大赛峰集团罢工工人提出新方案，工会称避免长期罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名工会官员周五告诉路透社记者，蒙特利尔地区生产空客和波音飞机起落架部件的赛峰集团工人已经提出了一个反建议，可能会避免更长时间的争端。【原文：Striking Montreal-area Safran workers who make components for landing gear used in Airbus and Boeing jets have made a counter offer that could avert a longer dispute, a union official told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/striking-canadian-safran-workers-make-new-offer-avert-lengthy-walkout-union-says-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJLOWLIHONMW3DOB5TMHK6YIOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 22:31:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在破产进程中，巴西戈尔航空公司更换财务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司周五宣布，董事会选举爱德华多-戈蒂利亚（Eduardo Gotilla）为新任首席财务官，同时还公布了 4 月份的初步业绩，其中包括 45 亿美元的净债务，这也是该航空公司正在进行的破产程序的一部分。【原文：Brazilian airline Gol announced on Friday that its board elected Eduardo Gotilla as its new chief financial officer, while also posting preliminary results for April including net debt of $4.5 billion as part of the carrier's ongoing bankruptcy proceedings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/amid-bankruptcy-process-brazil-airline-gol-swaps-finance-chief-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AOZABQYXHJLPPNCLMJKR6SLJ4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 22:26:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国运输部称美国主要航空公司不会承诺提高军人旅行福利]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部长皮特-巴蒂吉格（Pete Buttigieg）周五表示，美国各大航空公司拒绝承诺提高军人的旅行福利，这是拜登政府与航空公司之间的最新冲突。【原文：Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg on Friday said major U.S. airlines had declined to commit to boosting travel benefits for military personnel, the latest clash between the Biden administration and the air carriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/major-us-airlines-will-not-commit-boosting-military-travel-benefits-usdot-says-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKUDGIIFFBMM7P3S22SOEOKEGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 的 Facebook 表示，它吸引了三年来最多的年轻人]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 周五表示，其旗舰应用 Facebook 吸引的年轻人数量是三年来最高的，因为它正试图摆脱该平台作为老一代人聚集地的名声。【原文：Meta said on Friday its flagship app Facebook is attracting its highest number of young adults in three years, as it tries to shake the platform's reputation as a hangout for an older generation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/metas-facebook-says-it-is-attracting-most-young-adults-3-years-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Q32LWEO3ROEHP77ECMOO5WPZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员要求联邦调查局通报 GenScript 生物技术公司与中国的联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院中国问题委员会已要求联邦调查局和情报部门通报 GenScript 生物技术公司及其三家子公司的情况，以确定中国共产党是否对其运营施加了影响。【原文：The U.S. House of Representatives committee on China has asked the FBI and the intelligence community for a briefing on GenScript Biotechnology Co and three subsidiaries to determine if the Chinese Communist Party has influence over their operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-lawmakers-ask-fbi-briefing-genscript-biotechs-links-china-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HH67FTJ4VRIM5O65YQLR36QQMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉评级下调波音 2024 年飞机交付和现金流预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周五下调了对波音公司2024年飞机交付量和自由现金流的预期，因为这家飞机制造商正在努力应对调查和其最畅销喷气式飞机产量的下滑。【原文：Fitch Ratings lowered its 2024 forecasts for Boeing's aircraft delivery and free cash flow on Friday as the planemaker grapples with investigations and slumping production of its strongest-selling jet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-ratings-lowers-boeing-2024-aircraft-delivery-cash-flow-forecasts-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKVA3NPB4RMTRK463MNKGGG7OU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:37:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 道指运输股挣扎可能是经济预警信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年是美国主要股指大放异彩的一年，但市场中一个经济敏感的角落却让人感到痛苦。【原文：It's been a banner year for the major U.S. stock indexes, but one economically sensitive corner of the market sticks out as a sore spot.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-struggling-dow-transport-stocks-could-be-economic-warning-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3Y7IL76NDFJCVEYM2Z7GVYYRTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，派拉蒙特别委员会同意推荐 Skydance 交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，派拉蒙全球董事会的一个特别委员会同意建议与 Skydance Media 达成交易。【原文：A special committee of the Paramount Global's board agreed to recommend a deal with Skydance Media, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/paramounts-special-committee-agrees-recommend-skydance-deal-wsj-reports-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3IQB2C7VZPY3KTNO6NTINZZEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:42:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴牛仔帽的特斯拉主管金巴尔-马斯克是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉股东将于 6 月 13 日投票批准首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）560 亿美元的薪酬方案，该方案于今年 1 月被特拉华州法官宣布无效。此外，包括马斯克弟弟金巴尔在内的董事也将进行改选。【原文：Tesla shareholders will vote on June 13 to ratify CEO Elon Musk's $56 billion pay package that was voided by a Delaware judge in January. Also coming up is the re-election of directors, including Musk's younger brother, Kimbal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/who-is-kimbal-musk-tesla-director-cowboy-hat-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHWKOFLWRJKQ5ARVO4APDNUGMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:30:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，卡尔-伊坎持有凯撒娱乐公司大量股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引熟悉内情的消息人士的话报道，激进投资者卡尔-伊坎（Carl Icahn）在赌场运营商凯撒娱乐公司（Caesars Entertainment）持有相当大的仓位。【原文：Activist investor Carl Icahn has a sizable position in casino operator Caesars Entertainment , Bloomberg News reported on Friday citing sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/carl-icahn-has-sizable-stake-caesars-entertainment-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TUHLADSGNLCJBRC33OLMLOUGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司联席首席执行官将于周三主持市政厅会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一封电子邮件，派拉蒙全球公司的联席首席执行官将于 6 月 5 日为员工举办一次全体会议。【原文：Paramount Global's co-CEOs will host a town hall for its staff on June 5, according to an email seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-globals-co-ceos-host-town-hall-wednesday-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKVZULPPEBIQJDH3DX7RJ345S4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:35:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油厂提高燃油产量，超过 90% 的产能，以迎接夏季驾驶季节的到来]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社联系到的分析师表示，在完成计划中的检修后，美国原油炼制商的目标是在本季度剩余时间内将综合加工能力提高到 90% 以上。【原文：U.S. crude oil refiners aim to operate above 90% of their combined processing capacity for the remainder of the quarter after completing planned overhauls, said analysts contacted by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-refiners-boosting-fuel-output-past-90-capacity-summer-driving-season-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AULV3LST45OCXFKJU23TTNYQ5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达将超越苹果成为全球第二大最有价值公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[几乎所有的人工智能应用都依赖于 Nvidia 的芯片，这使得 Nvidia 的股价在过去一年中增长了近两倍，达到 2.72 万亿美元。【原文：The reliance of virtually all artificial intelligence applications on Nvidia's chips has helped the stock nearly triple in value over the past year to $2.72 trillion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-set-overtake-apple-worlds-second-most-valuable-company-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K57TJRWL2BKQVARTIAVCIVS3QM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[收益率上升和利率不确定性导致美国股票基金资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至5月29日的七天里，受债券收益率上升以及美联储降息时间和幅度的不确定性影响，美国股票基金在四周内首次出现资金外流。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw outflows for the first time four weeks in the seven days ended May 29, hit by rising bond yields and uncertainty over the timing and extent of Federal Reserve interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-hit-by-outflows-rising-yields-rates-uncertainty-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AIRIDYP5JVKF7FSGY3S2MYUJZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 14:25:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯诉讼放宽对联合信贷银行的限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，俄罗斯一家法院放宽了在天然气项目流产诉讼中对意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）施加的限制，允许这家意大利贷款机构以持有的俄罗斯主权债券作为抵押，而不是以其他资产和财产作为抵押。【原文：A Russian court has eased restrictions imposed on UniCredit in a lawsuit over an aborted gas project, on Friday permitting the Italian lender to offer Russian sovereign bond holdings as collateral instead of other assets and property.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/restrictions-unicredit-eased-russian-lawsuit-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W36NVKRGWZMRDLO644BGENTDWQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 14:21:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会主席称，加快美国证券结算速度的举措进展顺利]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会主席加里-根斯勒（Gary Gensler）周五表示，美国证券结算周期的全面改革本周进展顺利，所有交易均已结算。【原文：The overhaul of the settlement cycle for U.S. securities has gone smoothly this week, with all trades having settled, U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/move-faster-settlements-us-securities-has-gone-smoothly-sec-chair-says-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZN7TD43J5JPLBLR2FCNJLRMUJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PCE数据公布后，美联储更有可能在9月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易员们预计，在美国商务部的报告显示上个月通胀朝着美联储 2% 的目标取得了一些进展，且支出有所放缓之后，美联储更有可能在 9 月份进行期待已久的降息。【原文：The Federal Reserve is more likely to deliver a long-awaited rate cut in September after a U.S. Commerce Department report showed inflation made a bit of progress toward the Fed's 2% goal last month and spending softened, traders expect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-seen-more-likely-cut-rates-sept-after-pce-data-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5QBYJU6TFKW3HNXNUD4CO7FAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:33:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士信贷如何发展直至与瑞银合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士信贷集团是一家总部位于苏黎世的银行，去年被瑞士竞争对手瑞银集团以 30 亿瑞士法郎收购后，于上周五正式并入瑞士信贷集团，以下是瑞士信贷集团 168 年历史的时间轴。【原文：Following is a timeline outlining the 168-year history of Credit Suisse Group, the Zurich-based bank that was formally absorbed on Friday by Swiss rival UBS after a 3 billion franc takeover last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/how-credit-suisse-evolved-until-its-merger-with-ubs-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SO4D6HFUCBNANESKC7TIERLPQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构要求提供更多有关自动驾驶汽车 Zoox 车祸的详细信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，在对亚马逊公司的自动驾驶汽车 Zoox 因意外刹车导致两起追尾事故的调查中，该局正在寻求更多信息。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday it is seeking more information in its investigation into Amazon.com's self-driving Zoox vehicles due to unexpected braking leading to two rear-end collisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-agency-seeks-more-details-self-driving-zoox-crashes-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V2UL52YI4VIJDKN4YDLB5AVQFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4 月 PCE 物价指数横盘整理，显示通胀改善乏力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国通胀率在 4 月份横盘震荡，这对美国中央银行来说是一个令人担忧的迹象，表明物价上涨速度加快的情况可能会比预期持续更长时间，并使人怀疑中央银行何时能够降息。【原文：U.S. inflation tracked sideways in April, a worrying sign for the U.S. central bank that suggests the elevated pace of price increases could last longer than expected and casts doubt on how soon it will be able to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sideways-april-pce-price-index-shows-scant-inflation-improvement-2024-05-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCWPNHYO2JIXJISNOUTTSQUVHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>