<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:05:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:05:25 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国未发现汇率操纵者，但将爱尔兰和瑞士纳入监控范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四表示，在截至 12 月底的四个季度中，美国的主要贸易伙伴都没有操纵本国货币，但美国财政部已将其监控名单扩大到九个国家。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department said on Thursday that no major U.S. trading partners manipulated their currencies in the four quarters through to the end of December but it has expanded its monitoring list to nine countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-finds-no-currency-manipulators-adds-ireland-switzerland-monitoring-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LN5SETXWPJLSPED56PGAR4CGYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Circle 的大手笔 IPO 为其他加密货币上市铺平了道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[据专家和分析师称，稳定币发行商Circle周四首次公开募股10.5亿美元，这可能会刺激其他大型加密货币公司跟进，因为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对该行业的支持将使该行业受益。【原文：Stablecoin issuer Circle's $1.05 billion initial public offering on Thursday could spur other large crypto players to follow suit as the industry benefits from U.S. President Donald Trump's embrace of the sector, according to experts and analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/circles-blockbuster-ipo-paves-way-other-crypto-public-listings-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4EUGMNDDZI6LCIMO7GZRDMFQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：特朗普与马斯克的恩怨抨击股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6V6UUX4IVBI7DA25ZUVCV2SFVM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sunnova Energy 申请破产保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sunnova Energy 周四表示，该公司已在美国申请破产保护，因为这家住宅太阳能电池板安装商正努力应对巨额债务和需求低迷的问题。【原文：Sunnova Energy said on Thursday it has filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the United States, as the residential solar panel installer grapples with a massive debt pile and sluggish demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/sunnova-energy-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2322BXTRJNELNS5MZW5I5LV6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:59:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克称 SpaceX 将退役 "龙 "飞船，与特朗普的争执升级]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的火箭公司 SpaceX 将立即开始退役其 "龙 "飞船，这位亿万富翁周四回应美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于政府应取消马斯克联邦合同的声明时说。【原文：Elon Musk's rocket company SpaceX will begin decommissioning its Dragon spacecraft immediately, the billionaire said on Thursday in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's statement that the government should cancel Musk's federal contracts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spacex-will-decommission-dragon-spacecraft-musk-says-feud-with-trump-escalates-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">POUVFXIH5VOA5GBDUZ6IXFI6LY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:46:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银从纽约银行聘用科技银行家拉尔森和米克维奇]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份备忘录，瑞银在纽约从美国银行聘请了两名技术投资银行家。【原文：UBS hired two technology investment bankers in New York from Bank of America, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-hires-tech-bankers-larsen-michlovich-bofa-new-york-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EVFG5RPRROODFGRGH274R4MSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:44:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会驳回质疑股东提案规则收紧的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）规定，股东更难在公司年会上提交提案，包括就环境、社会和治理（ESG）问题进行改革。【原文：A federal judge on Thursday dismissed a lawsuit challenging U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission rule changes that made it harder for shareholders to file proposals at companies' annual meetings, including for reforms on environmental, social and governance (ESG) issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/sec-wins-dismissal-lawsuit-challenging-tighter-rules-shareholder-proposals-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTNUZ7BYABIMFOXFN3G2VNZJ5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:40:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）的目标是使非洲成为其在巴西以外的主要勘探地区]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）首席执行官周四表示，该公司的目标是将非洲作为其在巴西以外的主要发展地区，并补充说象牙海岸已为他们在其海岸附近的深海和超深海水域进行勘探铺上了 "红地毯"。【原文：Petrobras aims to make Africa its main region of development outside Brazil, the state-run oil firm's CEO said on Thursday, adding that Ivory Coast has extended the "red carpet" for them to explore in deep and ultra-deep waters off its coast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/petrobras-aims-make-africa-its-main-exploratory-region-outside-brazil-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EE2SQAGUFFJ2HAFHIML7KLKJJA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司证实五月份交付了 51 架喷气式飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲空中客车公司（Airbus）周四表示，该公司 5 月份交付了 51 架喷气式飞机，比去年同期下降了 4%。【原文：Europe's Airbus said on Thursday it had delivered 51 jets in May, down 4% from the same month last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-confirms-it-delivered-51-jets-may-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMJW43S2WBKG5CAQSNRNALHLFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:25:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博通公司预测季度收入高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[博通公司（Broadcom）周四预测第三季度营收将高于华尔街预期，押注于对其网络和定制人工智能计算芯片的强劲需求。【原文：Broadcom forecast third-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, betting on strong demand for its networking and custom AI computing chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/broadcom-forecasts-quarterly-revenue-above-estimates-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARWYQAZQ4FO2HLNY5AMG6FFLGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从 "令人作呕的憎恶 "到 "疯狂"：特朗普与马斯克在社交媒体上的争吵]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四威胁要切断政府与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）旗下公司的合同，因为这位世界上最有权势的人与世界上最富有的人之间曾经亲密无间的关系在他们对立的社交媒体平台上公开破裂了。【原文：President Donald Trump on Thursday threatened to cut off government contracts with Elon Musk's companies, as the once-close relationship between the world's most powerful man and its richest unraveled publicly on their rival social media platforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/disgusting-abomination-crazy-trump-musk-social-media-brawl-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HG3QHVCZNNLZHCB6Q5PF6Z5BVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求放缓、关税影响，Lululemon 下调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lululemon Athletica 周四下调了年度利润预期，原因是竞争加剧导致消费者需求减弱，以及特朗普政府贸易政策的不确定性引发经济逐步放缓。【原文：Lululemon Athletica cut annual profit forecast on Thursday, as consumer demand waned amid increased competition and a gradual economic slowdown triggered by uncertainty over the Trump administration's trade policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lululemon-cuts-annual-profit-forecast-demand-slows-tariffs-weigh-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPXG6WORR5JQ3GMOEJI5SK5DOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:12:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国认定 2024 年无汇率操纵，爱尔兰和瑞士被列入监控名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四在唐纳德-特朗普总统新政府的首份半年度货币报告中称，2024 年没有任何美国主要贸易伙伴操纵其货币，不过，随着爱尔兰和瑞士的加入，其值得密切关注的国家 "监测名单 "增至九个，并对中国发出了严厉警告。【原文：No major U.S. trading partner manipulated its currency in 2024, the Treasury Department said on Thursday in the first semi-annual currency report of President Donald Trump's new administration, although its "monitoring list" of countries warranting close attention grew to nine with the addition of Ireland and Switzerland and it issued a stern warning to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-finds-no-currency-manipulation-2024-ireland-switzerland-added-monitoring-list-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXW4ZLUJ6NOCXLOG5IDK4A5EQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克首席执行官称，尽管存在关税忧虑，IPO需求仍受提振，看好得克萨斯州的经济繁荣]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克（Nasdaq）首席执行官阿迪娜-弗里德曼（Adena Friedman）周四表示，交易所运营商纳斯达克正在与考虑首次登陆股市的公司进行积极洽谈，这凸显了美国经济的韧性，也预示着市场将重新焕发活力。【原文：Exchange operator Nasdaq is holding active talks with companies considering stock market debuts, CEO Adena Friedman said on Thursday, underscoring the U.S. economy's resilience and signaling renewed market vigor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nasdaq-ceo-says-ipo-demand-boosted-despite-tariff-worries-banks-texas-boom-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JNH7NKLFVPODLVW6IVPAGCHEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由关税推动的集装箱运价飙升有达到顶峰的迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[金融分析师和海运顾问表示，受中美暂时停止征收关税的影响，本周集装箱运价继续攀升，但有迹象表明，支撑运价飙升的需求正在放缓。【原文：Container shipping rates continued their climb this week, fueled by the temporary tariff pause between the U.S. and China, but there are signs that demand underpinning the surge is moderating, financial analysts and maritime consultants said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tariff-fueled-surge-container-shipping-rates-shows-signs-peaking-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAIMPPQCZ5OS3LBHQX7VRLAFSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德克萨斯证券交易所首席执行官称 35% 的美国上市公司不符合上市条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯证券交易所首席执行官詹姆斯-李（James Lee）在周四举行的派桑德勒全球证券交易会议上表示，目前在美国证券交易所公开交易的 4600 家公司中，多达 35% 的公司没有资格在拟议中的新德克萨斯证券交易所上市。【原文：As many as 35% of the 4,600 companies now publicly traded on a U.S. stock exchange would not qualify to list on the proposed new Texas Stock Exchange, James Lee, CEO of the TXSE, told the Piper Sandler Global Exchange & Trading conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/texas-stock-exchange-ceo-says-35-us-listed-public-companies-would-not-qualify-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLQSN5FDR5O3REIHXNE3TOFSAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）新任主席要求员工删除有关工作活动的子弹式电子邮件]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）主席周四告诉员工，他们不再需要每周发送电子邮件，详细说明上周的工作成绩。【原文：The chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission told staff Thursday they no longer need to send weekly emails detailing their work accomplishments from the previous week, according to two sources with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/new-sec-chief-tells-staff-nix-bulleted-emails-about-work-activities-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSLQSHU7QRKIVHLICCIWOXRTOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:08:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与马斯克因税收法案的争执升级；特斯拉、道琼斯工业平均指数股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周四抨击了埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk），称他对这位亿万富翁公开反对作为特朗普议程核心的全面减税和支出法案感到 "失望"。【原文：President Donald Trump lashed out on Thursday against Elon Musk, saying he was "disappointed" by the billionaire's public opposition to the sweeping tax-cut and spending bill that is at the heart of Trump's agenda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-musk-feud-escalates-over-tax-bill-tesla-djt-shares-tumble-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CBKC6ZVPFKQNNCEFQKAZMGAJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普建议终止马斯克的美国政府合同和补贴]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四暗示，他可能会终止美国政府给予埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）公司的合同和补贴，因为两人在税收和支出法案上的公开争执正在升级。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump suggested on Thursday that he may terminate U.S. government contracts and subsidies given to Elon Musk's companies, as the public feud between the two men escalates over a tax and spending bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-suggests-terminating-musks-us-government-contracts-subsidies-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDFYWM7OHVKG5AZRV5YMOPELKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:55:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[钻井商和工会敦促美国参议员保护氢气信贷]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，一个由近 250 家公司、商业和劳工团体组成的联盟敦促美国共和党高层参议员在讨论唐纳德-特朗普总统的税收和支出法案时，保留对新兴氢燃料产业的信贷。【原文：A coalition of nearly 250 companies and business and labor groups on Thursday urged top U.S. Republican senators to preserve a credit for the emerging hydrogen fuel industry as they hash out President Donald Trump's tax and spending bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/drillers-unions-urge-us-senators-preserve-hydrogen-credit-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QS3J2C2HD5JF5N3IHQYIHRTYS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:49:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的预算法案将扼杀使家用太阳能成为主流的补贴政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[据行业代表称，美国国会上月通过的共和党预算法案在最后一刻做出调整，将立即终止对太阳能租赁公司的补贴，而这些公司帮助房主买得起屋顶系统，这很可能导致安装速度大幅下降。【原文：A last-minute tweak to the Republican budget bill passed by Congress last month would immediately end subsidies for solar leasing companies that help make rooftop systems affordable to homeowners, likely leading to a massive drop in the pace of installations, according to industry representatives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-budget-bill-would-kill-subsidies-that-made-home-solar-mainstream-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLKQXW4ICRNRPJIXMCTTLS5RYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:22:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利商业巨头庞塞退出持有锂矿商 SQM 股份的公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利商业巨头胡里奥-庞塞（Julio Ponce）在周四的一份声明中表示，他将离开旗下的几家公司，同时这些公司宣布进行更广泛的重组，力求将各部门合并成更少的实体。【原文：Chilean business magnate Julio Ponce will leave several of his companies, he said in a statement on Thursday, while the firms announced a broader restructuring that seeks to merge units into fewer entities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/chilean-business-magnate-ponce-exits-firms-with-stakes-lithium-miner-sqm-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQENYJL5I5K3NOOQMDQZS6M6TM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塞尔维亚农民誓言反对力拓锂矿项目，即使欧盟已将其列为战略项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[塞尔维亚亚达尔地区的农民兹拉特科-科卡诺维奇（Zlatko Kokanovic）决心阻止力拓锂矿项目的开发，该项目本周被欧盟委员会确定为战略性项目，旨在减少矿产资源对中国的依赖。【原文：Zlatko Kokanovic, a farmer from Serbia's Jadar region, is determined to stop development of a Rio Tinto lithium project, identified this week as strategic by the European Commission as it aims to cut dependency on China for mineral resources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/serbian-farmers-vow-oppose-rio-tinto-lithium-project-even-after-eu-labels-it-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKOWTFHPUJPOXE44EVYNC6H3XQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:52:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood 高管吹捧散户投资者实力，称隔夜交易是未来趋势]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 公司高管史蒂夫-奎克（Steve Quirk）周四称，散户投资者帮助市场在 4 月份暴跌后反弹，并补充说，年轻的自主交易者越来越多地在传统时间以外进行交易。【原文：Robinhood executive Steve Quirk on Thursday credited retail investors with helping the market rebound after a sharp plunge in April, adding that young self-directed traders were increasingly making trades outside traditional hours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/robinhood-exec-touts-retail-investor-strength-says-overnight-trading-future-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GFJJ2DUKRK2JNSCNCVMMQTREE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈克表示，在不确定性中应谨慎对待货币政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联储主席帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）周四在作为央行行长的最后一次演讲中表示，目前经济前景尚未明朗，无法说明下一步货币政策的走向。【原文：In his final speech as a central banker, Philadelphia Federal Reserve President Patrick Harker said on Thursday the economic outlook is too unsettled right now to say what's next for monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-harker-says-its-time-caution-monetary-policy-amid-uncertainty-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNK5NYQ4NRLGNMDCICXL76ACOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:40:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德：对关税推动的价格上涨感到不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联邦储备银行行长杰夫-施密德（Jeff Schmid）周四表达了对关税可能重新引发通胀的担忧，称未来几个月物价上涨的压力可能会显现，但在更长的时间内还无法完全知晓。【原文：Kansas City Federal Reserve Bank President Jeff Schmid on Thursday expressed concern that tariffs could rekindle inflation, saying upward price pressure could be apparent in coming months but not fully known for much longer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-schmid-uncomfortable-with-looking-through-tariff-driven-price-push-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJPZWFDVIVOQDFOGU36LE4OYLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克有更多时间回应美国证券交易委员会就推特股份提起的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）又给了埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）六周的时间来回应其民事诉讼，指控这位世界首富在 2022 年披露其在 Twitter（他后来收购并更名为 X 的社交媒体公司）的巨额股份时等得太久。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has given Elon Musk six more weeks to respond to its civil lawsuit accusing the world's richest person of waiting too long in 2022 to reveal his large stake in Twitter, the social media company he later bought and renamed X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/elon-musk-gets-more-time-respond-us-sec-lawsuit-over-twitter-stake-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4H45MLXMRKYFJMHQE4F4LRPD4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空警告新关税可能迫使其停止购买外国制造的飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司警告说，对进口飞机和零部件征收新关税可能迫使该公司停止购买外国制造的飞机，从而影响数百万客户。【原文：Delta Air Lines warned new tariffs on imported airplanes and parts could force the airline to stop buying foreign-made planes impacting millions of customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-warns-new-tariffs-could-force-it-stop-buying-foreign-made-airplanes-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJBKQZU7UJKSVMFKDAZHEJXFTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:23:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安杜里尔在最新一次融资中获得 305 亿美元估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[国防技术初创企业安杜里尔工业公司（Anduril Industries）周四表示，该公司在最新一轮融资中获得了 305 亿美元的估值，融资额达 25 亿美元。【原文：Defense technology startup Anduril Industries has clinched a valuation of $30.5 billion in its latest funding round where it raised $2.5 billion, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/anduril-secures-305-billion-valuation-latest-fund-raise-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYWHYG3S2JPB5KMI4OCBOJOMRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西生物资源局坚信禽流感危机将很快结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西食品加工商巴西食品公司（BRF）相信，当地公司将能在几天内规避鸡肉贸易禁令，因为迄今为止，当地政府已经能够控制世界上最大的鸡肉出口国爆发的禽流感疫情。【原文：Brazilian food processor BRF is confident local companies will be able to circumvent chicken trade bans in a matter of days as local authorities have so far been able to control a bird flu outbreak in the world's largest chicken-exporting nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/brazils-brf-confident-bird-flu-crisis-will-be-over-soon-2025-06-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG25KNW3HJJGTFFGAS4LD5CAFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>