<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:22:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:22:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国中央电视台称英伟达首席执行官将出席中国供应链博览会]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国中央电视台周二称，英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋将于周三出席中国国际供应链博览会开幕式。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang will attend the opening ceremony of China's international supply chain expo on Wednesday, Chinese state broadcaster CCTV said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-ceo-attend-china-supply-chain-expo-chinas-cctv-says-2025-07-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKFDS44SDNKTDBG5YZUWTLHGBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:16:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管征收关税，但亚洲传统汽车制造商仍以美国为先]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车和现代汽车可能对美国的保护主义心存芥蒂，但它们与唐纳德-特朗普总统有一个共同点：在全球汽车市场上，亚洲的传统汽车制造商都是美国优先。【原文：Toyota and Hyundai Motor may have a beef with U.S. protectionism, but they have one thing in common with President Donald Trump: when it comes to global car markets, it's America first for Asia's legacy automakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/despite-tariffs-its-still-america-first-asias-legacy-automakers-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZC2I5OJMTVMJREZ2F53GYWYQ2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:58:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚希望取消大部分银行卡支付附加费]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚中央银行周二建议取消对消费者的大部分借记卡和信用卡支付附加费，同时降低企业支付的交换费，这些措施每年将为这两个群体节省约 24 亿澳元（15.7 亿美元）。【原文：Australia's central bank on Tuesday proposed to scrap surcharges on most debit and credit card payments for consumers while lowering interchange fees paid by businesses, steps that would save the two groups around A$2.4 billion ($1.57 billion) a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-looks-scrap-surcharges-most-card-payments-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMSB5EGUCNICDJPS6CTKY2MGOQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究公司称，尽管北美市场举步维艰，但 6 月份全球电动汽车销量仍猛增 24]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场研究公司 Rho Motion 周二表示，由于中国和欧洲向电动汽车转换的势头保持良好，6 月份全球电动汽车和插电式混合动力汽车的销量比去年同期猛增 24%。【原文：Global sales of electric and plug-in hybrid vehicles jumped 24% in June from a year ago, as a switch to electric vehicles maintained momentum in China and Europe, market research firm Rho Motion said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-ev-sales-jump-24-june-though-north-american-market-struggles-research-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KC2HHOYRBITXED2GAL6DYR5KE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:11:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税压力增大，中国第二季度经济增速将放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于贸易紧张局势和房地产长期低迷拖累了需求，中国经济在经历了年初的稳健增长后，很可能在第二季度出现降温，从而加大了政策制定者推出额外刺激措施以支撑经济增长的压力。【原文：China's economy is likely to have cooled in the second quarter after a solid start to the year, as trade tensions and a prolonged property downturn drag on demand, raising pressure on policymakers to roll out additional stimulus to underpin growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-economy-set-slow-q2-pressure-us-tariffs-mounts-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5FDSPDBJBIR7CF6LPTYEOSWFY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行称，新西兰老年人的行为将影响利率和资产价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰中央银行在周二发布的一份报告中说，随着人口老龄化，新西兰的储蓄、借贷和投资行为可能会发生变化，从而影响利率、资产价格和对金融产品的需求。【原文：New Zealand’s savings, borrowing and investment behaviour is likely to change as its population ages, affecting interest rates, asset prices and demand for financial products, New Zealand’s central bank said in a report released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/behaviour-aging-new-zealanders-impact-interest-rates-asset-prices-rbnz-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43HNS2ULZRLSLNO6YX2XAP5WII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，洛克希德-马丁公司交付 72 架面临升级延误的 F-35 喷气式战斗机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引五角大楼项目办公室的消息报道，洛克希德-马丁公司已经向美国政府交付了72架F-35喷气式战斗机，截至5月1日，由于软件改进不及时，交付时间推迟了几个月。【原文：Lockheed Martin has delivered 72 F-35 jets to the U.S. government as of May 1, after several months of delay due to late software improvements, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing the Pentagon's program office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-martin-delivers-72-f-35-jets-facing-upgrade-delays-bloomberg-news-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRMF67TQ5NMK7I2Q775VSFZOXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Politico 报道，美联储鲍威尔要求监督机构重新审视翻新项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Politico 周一援引鲍威尔写给立法者的一封信报道，美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）已要求美联储委员会的监察长重新审视旨在彻底改造美联储大楼的项目。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell has asked the Fed board's inspector general to take a fresh look at the project aimed at overhauling Fed buildings, Politico reported on Monday, citing a letter to lawmakers by Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-powell-asks-watchdog-take-fresh-look-renovation-project-politico-reports-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFJH4TULJVNLVDKGB25NXMQDJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 22:46:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对进口无人机和多晶硅展开国家安全调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，已对无人机和相关部件以及太阳能电池板和半导体的关键部件多晶硅的进口展开国家安全调查。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Monday it has opened national security investigations into the import of drones and related components as well as polysilicon, a key component in solar panels and semiconductors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-opens-national-security-probes-into-imported-drones-polysilicon-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJ2LR4Z5HJO6XDMP3LXVWAS6JQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 22:27:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精灵宝可梦 X 账户遭黑客攻击，发布反犹太主义和种族主义信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[儿童电视节目制作者周一表示，黑客侵入了《芝麻街》卡通人物精灵宝可梦的 X 账户，并发布了反犹太主义和种族主义信息。【原文：Hackers broke into the X account of Sesame Street character Elmo and posted antisemitic and racist messages, the makers of the children's TV show said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/elmos-x-account-gets-hacked-posts-antisemitic-racist-messages-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UM3CMV33OJMPFO7JU7ZDUOR7HQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 22:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[帝亚吉欧称龙舌兰酒纯度指控 "毫无根据"，美国诉讼仍在继续]]></title><description><![CDATA[帝亚吉欧公司（Diageo）周一对一起指控该烈酒巨头误导美国消费者的诉讼做出了初步回应，称其一些广受欢迎的龙舌兰酒品牌的纯度是 "毫无根据的"。【原文：Diageo on Monday filed an initial response to a lawsuit accusing the spirits giant of misleading U.S. consumers about the purity of some of its popular tequila brands, calling the claim "baseless".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/diageo-calls-tequila-purity-allegation-baseless-us-lawsuit-proceeds-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQKLPKHFXNP23NK36ZTB54P744</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:53:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[万豪财务总监 Leeny Oberg 将于明年退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[万豪国际酒店集团（Marriott International）周一表示，其首席财务官利尼-奥伯格（Leeny Oberg）将于明年退休，他在这家美国酒店运营商工作了二十多年。【原文：Marriott International said on Monday its chief financial officer, Leeny Oberg, would retire next year after spending more than two decades with the U.S. hotel operator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/marriott-finance-chief-leeny-oberg-retire-next-year-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG53ZSTOFJKN3P6GNJ63NRHLFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国退出与墨西哥的番茄协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，将退出2019年暂停对墨西哥新鲜番茄征收反倾销税调查的协议，并将对从美国邻国进口的大部分番茄征收17.09%的关税。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said on Monday it was withdrawing from a 2019 deal suspending an anti-dumping duty investigation on fresh tomatoes from Mexico, and that it will issue duties of 17.09% on most of those imports from the U.S. neighbor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-withdraws-tomatoes-agreement-with-mexico-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7G3HQ2RXZNNSDNPOE4TVCDX6AA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:32:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽蒙特首席财务官 Karyn Ovelmen 辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[黄金矿商纽蒙特公司（Newmont Corp）周一表示，其首席财务官 Karyn Ovelmen 已辞职，并任命内部人士 Peter Wexler 担任临时首席财务官，直到选出永久继任者为止。【原文：Gold miner Newmont Corp said on Monday its CFO Karyn Ovelmen has resigned and named insider Peter Wexler as interim CFO until a permanent successor is selected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/newmont-cfo-karyn-ovelmen-resigns-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKVRQARA2JMODPOVX24DBV7D5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰 6 月房价基本持平，买家期待更好的报价]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰房地产协会（REINZ）周二表示，6月份新西兰房价基本持平，因为在市场挂牌量增加的情况下，买家在等待更好的出价。【原文：New Zealand home prices were largely flat in June as buyers await better offers amid higher listings in the market, the Real Estate Institute of New Zealand (REINZ) said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealand-home-prices-largely-flat-june-buyers-eye-better-offers-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CB5BA2CBVN3FIW43NK3ZYIVVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：抵制关税紧张局势再起]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphics-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWWINOZMGFOGVHFTOCSMFWOE7E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 21:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cognition AI 收购 Windsurf，加倍努力发展人工智能驱动的编码技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司 Cognition AI 周一同意收购集成开发环境平台 Windsurf，从而加强了其在快速发展的企业软件市场中的地位。【原文：Artificial intelligence startup Cognition AI on Monday agreed to acquire Windsurf, an integrated development environment platform, strengthening its position in the rapidly evolving enterprise software market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/cognition-ai-buy-windsurf-doubling-down-ai-driven-coding-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5SAT67FAFNC5HHSZE2KJ37HUA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 19:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克首席执行官表示，星巴克将从三天工作制改为四天工作制]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克首席执行官布莱恩-尼科尔（Brian Niccol）表示，作为预计今年晚些时候开始实施的新政策的一部分，这家咖啡巨头将要求许多员工每周至少外出工作四天，而不是现在的三天。【原文：Starbucks CEO Brian Niccol said the coffee giant will require many of its employees to work out of office for a minimum four days a week, from the current three, as part of a new policy expected to kick in later this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/starbucks-shift-four-day-work-office-three-says-ceo-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRPJWTKJGVNYLBKTBDSEZOIMSI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 19:11:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行行长贝利表示金融稳定需要全球合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[英格兰银行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）周一在致二十国集团（G20）决策者的一封信中强调了国际合作对于实现金融稳定的重要性，并表示不确定性继续对全球增长预期构成压力。【原文：Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey stressed the importance of international cooperation to achieve finance stability, saying in a letter to G20 policymakers on Monday that uncertainty continued to weigh on global growth expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/boes-bailey-says-uncertainty-continues-weigh-growth-expectations-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSOKRLPOQFOVHJI6HAKB3IAZBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:35:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛将 2025 年下半年布伦特原油预测值上调至 66 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）周一上调了 2025 年下半年的油价预测，理由是供应中断风险、经济合作与发展组织国家石油库存减少以及俄罗斯的产量限制。【原文：Goldman Sachs raised its oil price forecasts for the second half of 2025 on Monday, citing the risk of supply disruption, lower oil inventories in Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development countries and Russia's production constraints.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/goldman-sachs-raises-brent-oil-forecast-second-half-2025-66-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAIZWDJUANPOFNFOBFTDLBJ7GM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总部设在中国的和赛就美国将公司与中国军方挂钩的裁决提出上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国激光雷达制造商合赛集团周一对一项裁决提出上诉，该裁决维持了美国政府将其列入涉嫌与中国军方合作的公司名单的决定。【原文：China-based lidar manufacturer Hesai Group appealed a ruling on Monday upholding a U.S. government decision to add it to a list of companies allegedly working with Beijing's military.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/china-based-hesai-appeals-ruling-over-us-linking-firm-chinese-military-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MMDNYI55NLKVOBJ4Q3U7TBVDQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:29:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利、高盛和富国银行达成与 Archegos 倒闭有关的和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）、高盛（Goldman Sachs）和富国银行（Wells Fargo）将支付总计 1.2 亿美元的赔偿金，以了结一项诉讼，该诉讼称他们在销售 ViacomCBS 股票时隐瞒了利益冲突，助长了 Bill Hwang 的 Archegos Capital Management 公司的倒闭。【原文：Morgan Stanley , Goldman Sachs and Wells Fargo will pay a total of $120 million to settle a lawsuit claiming they hid conflicts of interest while sales of ViacomCBS shares helped fuel the collapse of Bill Hwang's Archegos Capital Management.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/morgan-stanley-goldman-wells-fargo-reach-settlement-tied-archegos-collapse-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZN7Y3OL7ZOF3CD3UR6ZBYPOCM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国稀土定价体系有望挑战中国的主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国努力打破中国在稀土市场的主导地位，并推动对本国稀土产业的投资，在华盛顿的支持下，美国计划建立一个独立的、更高的定价体系。【原文：U.S. efforts to break China's dominance of the rare earths market and to drive investment in its own industry have moved up a gear with a Washington-backed plan to create a separate, higher pricing system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-rare-earth-pricing-system-is-poised-challenge-chinas-dominance-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQGJ5NBU4FLDFCOWPGSW7F4WEE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:48:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[到 2028 年，许多美国冰淇淋生产商将逐步淘汰人工食品染料]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际乳制品食品协会（International Dairy Foods Association）周一表示，数十家美国冰淇淋生产商计划在 2028 年之前从其产品中去除人工色素。【原文：Dozens of U.S. ice cream producers are planning to remove artificial colors from their products by 2028, the International Dairy Foods Association said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/many-us-ice-cream-producers-phase-out-artificial-food-dyes-by-2028-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KQGUT4BLVKV3JRRVA7P3EX7VE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IDC 认为尽管关税和宏观经济存在不确定性，全球智能手机市场仍将增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司IDC的初步数据显示，尽管存在关税问题和宏观经济的不确定性，第二季度全球智能手机出货量仍增长了1%，达到2.952亿部。【原文：Global smartphone shipments increased 1% to 295.2 million units in the second quarter, despite tariff concerns and macroeconomic uncertainty, according to preliminary data from research firm IDC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/idc-sees-growth-global-smartphone-market-despite-tariffs-macroeconomic-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUSUTJEYDBOCJOR5VINHLH5SWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:44:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普将公布 700 亿美元的人工智能和能源投资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引一位政府官员的话报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周二宣布在宾夕法尼亚州投资 700 亿美元用于人工智能和能源领域。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will announce $70 billion in artificial intelligence and energy investments in Pennsylvania on Tuesday, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing an administration official.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-unveil-70-billion-ai-energy-investments-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFWHBVAAQ5LI3L5OIHTEFVHQZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[旧金山联储称，特朗普关税将提升美国工厂就业岗位，但削减整体收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联储周一的最新研究显示，特朗普政府的关税措施可能会促进美国大多数州的制造业就业和实际收入，但会降低全国的就业率和经通胀调整后的收入。【原文：The Trump administration's tariffs are likely to boost U.S. manufacturing jobs and real income in a majority of states, but lower employment and income adjusted for inflation in the country as a whole, new research from the San Francisco Federal Reserve showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-would-lift-us-factory-jobs-cut-overall-income-san-francisco-fed-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZUOX5RW7UBLMZMFHMATLJEDYBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最繁忙港口称中国降低关税后 6 月进口反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最繁忙的海港洛杉矶港执行董事周一表示，6 月份该港的进口量强劲反弹，与去年同期相比增长了 10%，并使该月的总进口量创下历史新高。【原文：Imports to the busiest U.S. seaport in Los Angeles rebounded strongly in June, finishing up 10% versus a year ago and contributing to record total volume for the month, the port's executive director said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/busiest-us-port-says-june-imports-rebound-after-china-tariffs-reduced-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S45RHN33INMIJO4W4JFQKTCESQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，关税威胁使欧洲央行七月决策复杂化，但不会破坏降息暂停计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位欧洲央行决策者告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁对欧盟进口商品征收30%的关税，这使欧洲央行的决策变得更加复杂，但不太可能破坏下周暂停降息的计划。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's threatened 30% tariff on European Union imports is complicating the European Central Bank's decision-making but is unlikely to derail plans for a pause in rate cuts next week, five ECB policymakers told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/tariff-threat-complicates-ecbs-july-decision-wont-derail-pause-rate-cuts-sources-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCUQPOAFLZNXJO2G3TJJX3TK4A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:13:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国防部授予谷歌和 xAI 合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防部首席数字与人工智能办公室（Chief Digital and Artificial Intelligence Office）周一表示，OpenAI、Alphabet 旗下谷歌公司 Anthropic 和埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的人工智能公司 xAI 赢得了旨在扩大美国国防部采用先进人工智能能力的合同。【原文：OpenAI, Alphabet's Google , Anthropic and Elon Musk's AI firm xAI have won contracts aimed at scaling up adoption of advanced AI capabilities in the U.S. Department of Defense, the Chief Digital and Artificial Intelligence Office said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-department-defense-awards-contracts-google-xai-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TO5P76H3NOWVKHPO5L7IUZ2GY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>