<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 22:13:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 22:13:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：让耐克和乐高进入战时俄罗斯商店的荷兰人]]></title><description><![CDATA[两年多前，莫斯科全面入侵乌克兰后不久，耐克公司就停止向俄罗斯出售运动服装。但这并没有阻止俄罗斯泽尼特足球俱乐部旗下的在线体育零售商 footballstore.ru。【原文：Nike stopped selling its sportswear to Russia soon after Moscow launched its full-scale invasion of Ukraine over two years ago. But that hasn’t stopped footballstore.ru, an online sports retailer owned by Russia’s Zenit soccer club.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dutchman-who-gets-nike-lego-into-wartime-russias-stores-2024-06-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZX2KZNT5BLCFLSRLMC7RO7YMU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 09:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 首席执行官称公司可能成为福利公司 - The Information]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周五报道，OpenAI 首席执行官山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）告诉一些股东，公司正在考虑改变治理结构，将其转变为一家营利性企业，OpenAI 的非营利性董事会并不控制该企业。【原文：OpenAI CEO Sam Altman told some shareholders that the company is considering changing its governance structure to a for-profit business that OpenAI's nonprofit board doesn't control, The Information reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-ceo-says-company-could-become-benefit-corporation-information-2024-06-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLOV6WA4YJMFZJPHZGHTFCWXFI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德首席执行官将在美国参议院听证会上就 Ozempic 和 Wegovy 的高昂成本作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院健康、教育、劳工和养老金委员会周五表示，诺和诺德公司首席执行官拉尔斯-约根森（Lars Jorgensen）已同意在9月份举行的听证会上自愿作证，该听证会将重点讨论美国减肥药Ozempic和Wegovy的价格问题。【原文：The U.S Senate Committee on Health, Education, Labor, and Pensions said on Friday that Novo Nordisk CEO Lars Jorgensen has agreed to testify voluntarily in a September hearing focusing on U.S. prices for weight loss drugs Ozempic and Wegovy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/novo-nordisk-ceo-testify-us-senate-hearing-high-cost-ozempic-wegovy-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNSQRI2V5VPI7JNH3I3LC3K3EU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 21:41:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，凯雷探索出售电力生产商 Cogentrix]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》援引三位知情人士的话报道称，私募股权投资公司凯雷（Carlyle）已聘请顾问探讨出售 Cogentrix 的事宜，该公司总部位于北卡罗来纳州，对这家电力生产商的估值可能高达 30 亿至 40 亿美元。【原文：PE firm Carlyle has hired advisers to explore a sale of Cogentrix that could value the North Carolina-based power producer at as much as $3 billion to $4 billion, the Financial Times reported, citing three people briefed on the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/carlyle-explores-sale-electric-power-producer-cogentrix-ft-reports-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAD547EZDBNHHOKE6OOXR223BE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 21:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国工业团体寻求就拜登对华加征关税举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[一大批支持贸易的美国商业团体要求拜登政府再给他们一个月的时间，就对中国进口的电动汽车、电池、太阳能产品和其他商品征收更严厉关税的计划发表意见，这实际上推迟了许多关税于8月1日开始征收的日期。【原文：A wide swath of pro-trade American business groups has asked the Biden administration for another month to comment on plans to impose steeper tariffs on Chinese imports of electric vehicles, batteries, solar products and other goods, effectively delaying the Aug. 1 start date for many of the duties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-industry-groups-seek-hearing-more-bidens-china-tariff-hike-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKSRKQTIVNKA5LKE3FR3QJ3DRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 20:40:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储数据显示中性利率保持在较低水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周五公布的数据显示，今年前三个月，被视为对经济影响中性的基本利率水平稳定在较低水平。【原文：The underlying level of interest rates viewed as neutral in economic influence held steady at a low level over the first three months of this year, according to data released on Friday by the Federal Reserve Bank of New York.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ny-fed-data-shows-neutral-rate-holding-steady-low-level-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WIXMMBMOCZM57PB3XA6RE23W74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，波音告知供应商将把 737 产出目标放缓 3 个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位业内消息人士称，波音公司已告知供应商，将把其 737 喷气机系列的一个关键生产里程碑推迟三个月。【原文：Boeing has told suppliers it is delaying a key production milestone for its 737 jet family by three months, two industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-tells-suppliers-it-is-slowing-737-output-goal-by-3-months-sources-say-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGXSHLX5IZPCROMNO7HVMFQZYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:32:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 利率居高不下，零售股寻找方向]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国利率的升高给美国零售业带来了压力，许多公司的股价因数月来的紧缩货币政策而下跌，但也有少数公司的股价飙升。【原文：Elevated U.S. interest rates are pressuring the U.S. retail sector, where shares of many companies have been dented by months of tight monetary policy while a select few have soared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/wall-st-week-ahead-retail-stocks-search-direction-rates-stay-high-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APCN7D4MY5NJDHA7L7EYEQM7KQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储博斯蒂克指出财务信息披露存在更多问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）的财务披露表指出，在报告过去的交易和投资活动方面存在更多问题。【原文：A financial disclosure form for Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic notes more issues with reporting of past trading and investing activities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-bostic-flags-more-issues-with-financial-disclosures-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOSZUGBMGNM6HO6QLDV2AQLTQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比称最新消费者物价数据 "令人宽慰]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯汀-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，在本周的数据显示 5 月份消费者通胀率没有较上月上升后，他感到 "如释重负"。
古尔斯比在爱荷华州安肯尼举行的爱荷华州农业局经济峰会上说，如果有更多月份的数据与5月份的数据相同，"我们会感觉非常好"。他说，尽管如此，仍需取得更多进展，他表示将继续努力。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago President Austan Goolsbee on Friday said he felt "relief" after data this week showed consumer inflation in May did not rise from the month earlier.
"We would be feeling very good" if there were a lot more months like May's data, Goolsbee told the Iowa Farm Bureau Economic Summit in Ankeny, Iowa. Still, he said, there needs to be more progress, and he said he will b】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-says-latest-consumer-price-data-brought-relief-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMWTJ6SDJVOZ7IAJZD2GPZMUDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:18:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 NTSB 对西南航空波音 737 MAX 机上事件展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会（National Transportation Safety Board）周五表示，正在对西南航空公司（Southwest Airlines）运营的一架波音 737 MAX 于 5 月 25 日发生的飞行中振荡事件展开调查。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board said Friday it is opening an investigation into a May 25 in-flight oscillation event involving a Boeing 737 MAX operated by Southwest Airlines .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-ntsb-opens-probe-into-southwest-boeing-737-max-in-flight-event-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CXGZCIVALROYRJDTE6EEDCRDEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，根据具有里程碑意义的技术规则，苹果和 Meta 将面临欧盟指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位直接了解此事的人士周五表示，苹果公司和 Meta Platforms 将可能面临指控，因为它们未能遵守欧盟旨在在今年夏天之前约束其权力的具有里程碑意义的规定。【原文：Apple and Meta Platforms will likely face charges for failing to comply with landmark EU rules aimed at reining in their power before the summer, three people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-meta-set-face-eu-charges-under-landmark-tech-rules-sources-say-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROLH5BDD2VMMXE64RHGQ5DZJHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌在美国数字广告反垄断案中败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦法官周五裁定，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司必须就美国反垄断执法机构关于这家互联网搜索巨头非法主导在线广告技术市场的指控接受审判。【原文：Alphabet's Google must face trial on U.S. antitrust enforcers' claim that the internet search juggernaut illegally dominates the online advertising technology market, a federal judge ruled on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-loses-bid-end-us-antitrust-case-over-digital-advertising-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYM3BF2UPJMLFPSLTO3WM2SQWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:44:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚历克斯-琼斯的公司退出破产程序，其资产将被清算]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名破产法官周五下令在法院监督下清算阴谋论者亚历克斯-琼斯（Alex Jones）的个人资产，但他没有下令清算琼斯的公司 Free Speech Systems，而是驳回了该公司的破产申请。【原文：A U.S. bankruptcy judge on Friday ordered a court-supervised liquidation of conspiracy theorist Alex Jones' personal assets, but he dismissed the bankruptcy of Jones' company Free Speech Systems without ordering it to be liquidated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/alex-jones-bankruptcy-liquidation-approved-court-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJHUCNJSPZIHDI6PWN76XTMTUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共和党参议员格拉斯利对波音公司和美国联邦航空局展开新一轮调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党参议员查克-格拉斯利（Chuck Grassley）周五表示，在今年 1 月涉及一架 737 MAX 9 的空中紧急事件后，他将对联邦航空管理局和波音公司展开新一轮国会监督调查。【原文：Republican Senator Chuck Grassley said Friday he is launching a new congressional oversight inquiry into the Federal Aviation Administration and Boeing after a January mid-air emergency involving a 737 MAX 9.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/republican-senator-grassley-launches-new-probe-into-boeing-faa-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMSOATRQ2ZKDLEVSETH7BHODNQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报纸报道：可口可乐和星巴克申请延长在俄罗斯的商标期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[据俄罗斯国内商业报纸《Vedomosti》报道，可口可乐和星巴克在 2022 年因莫斯科入侵乌克兰而退出俄罗斯市场后，已申请在俄罗斯重新注册商标，以保护其知识产权。【原文：Coca-Cola and Starbucks have applied to re-register their trademarks in Russia to protect their intellectual property rights after exiting in response to Moscow's invasion of Ukraine in 2022, domestic business newspaper Vedomosti reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coca-cola-starbucks-file-extend-trademarks-russia-newspaper-reports-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVSGD37DTJLBTCMFZMTNJIA2PA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:22:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储因 Evolve 银行未能管理金融科技合作风险而对其进行处罚]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周五宣布，已下令 Evolve Bancorp Inc 围绕金融科技合作以及反洗钱法加强风险管理计划。【原文：The Federal Reserve announced Friday it had ordered Evolve Bancorp Inc to bolster its risk management programs around fintech partnerships as well as anti-money laundering laws.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-penalizes-evolve-bank-failing-manage-fintech-partnership-risk-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WG3BCBLXOJOBPJVWTW5G4J25GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债券交易员担心美国市场规模扩大后流动性会恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国债券市场参与者担心，随着美国财政部继续发行大量债务以支持赤字支出，而交易商又难以跟上市场规模的膨胀，市场流动性将继续恶化。【原文：U.S. bond market participants are worried market liquidity will keep deteriorating as the U.S. Treasury continues to issue large amounts of debt to back deficit spending while dealers struggle to keep up with the ballooning size of the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bond-traders-worry-liquidity-will-worsen-us-market-size-grows-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5REHNUBNAVIK5BZUITSOFMCV24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[上海允许特斯拉开展全自动驾驶试点]]></title><description><![CDATA[地方政府支持的《上海观察家报》周五称，上海将允许 10 辆特斯拉汽车进行该公司最先进的自动驾驶软件测试，为其在中国的推广铺平道路。【原文：Shanghai is allowing 10 Tesla vehicles to carry out tests of the company's most advanced autonomous driving software to pave way for its rollout in China, local-government-backed The Shanghai Observer said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shanghai-allows-tesla-carry-out-full-self-driving-pilot-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXNUHIVT2BJTFKTB6DPMZPW7B4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:54:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Redfin称，美国5月成屋销售因利率上升和房价创纪录而下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产经纪公司 Redfin 在一份报告中称，由于在高抵押贷款利率环境下需求和供应都持续低迷，美国 5 月份的房屋销售量降至过去十年来的最低水平。【原文：U.S. home sales in May fell to among the lowest levels in the past decade, real estate brokerage Redfin said in a report, as both demand and supply remained sluggish in a high-mortgage rate environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-home-sales-crumble-may-higher-rates-record-prices-says-redfin-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGAILEIOTVIDDGGZ3VTM47GESY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）称，波音 "星际客机 "将于 6 月 22 日脱离对接并返回地球]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）周五表示，波音公司的 "星际客机"（Starliner）航天器目前计划于6月22日从国际空间站脱钩，并与首批宇航员一起返回地球。【原文：The Boeing Starliner spacecraft is now scheduled to undock from the International Space Station and return to Earth on June 22 with its inaugural astronaut crew, NASA said on Friday, giving more time to finalize planning for the complicated process.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/boeing-starliner-undocking-return-earth-set-june-22-nasa-says-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A24C4GHBVVJZ5F2SXSNJLKSSPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，宝马电动迷你车将面临欧盟最高电动车关税的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士周五表示，根据欧盟的临时计划，宝马在中国生产的纯电动迷你车将被征收最高的电动车关税（38.1%），这对这款中档车的销售前景可能是一个致命打击。【原文：BMW's all-electric Mini made in China is set to be hit by the highest EV tariff of 38.1% under the EU's provisional plans, a source familiar with the matter said on Friday, a potential terminal blow for the mid-range car's sales prospects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-electric-mini-threatened-with-highest-ev-tariff-eu-source-says-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQO5I2Y7VZO3HPB4BDTBLG65S4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国5月进口价格意外下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于能源产品价格下降，5月份美国进口价格意外下降，再次推动了国内通胀前景。【原文：U.S. import prices import unexpectedly fell in May amid lower prices for energy products, providing another boost to the domestic inflation outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-import-prices-unexpectedly-fall-may-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHAMXZJ4B5NGVMXLFMKVQUBTJ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储决议公布前，美国股票基金创下 18 个月来最大单周流出量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 6 月 12 日的七天内，美国股票基金资金大量流出，原因是一些投资者在美联储做出政策决定前获利了结并保持谨慎。【原文：U.S. equity funds observed heavy outflows in the seven days through June 12 as some investors booked profits and exercised caution ahead of the Federal Reserve's policy decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-saw-largest-weekly-outflow-18-months-ahead-fed-decision-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWYTZTNHDRIYZFCM37PU4QGZCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将投资 71.6 亿美元在西班牙东北部新建数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软计划投资 66.9 亿欧元（71.6 亿美元）在西班牙东北部的阿拉贡地区开发新的数据中心，该地区正在成为欧洲主要的云计算中心。【原文：Microsoft plans to invest 6.69 billion euros ($7.16 billion) to develop new data centres in Spain's northeastern region of Aragon, which is becoming a major cloud computing hub within Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-invest-716-bln-new-data-centres-northeastern-spain-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXO356UHRJPV7BRVUK5MTNFVYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:30:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金在美联储会议前因谨慎而面临巨额资金流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至6月12日的七天内，全球股票基金资金大幅流出，因为在可能决定近期利率前景的关键性美国通胀报告和美联储政策决定出台之前，投资者谨慎地撤出了资金。【原文：Global equity funds suffered sharp outflows in the seven days to June 12 as investors cautiously took out money ahead of a key U.S. inflation report and Federal Reserve policy decision that could determine the near-term outlook for interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-market-data/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3T57GMTQ5OBNCLI2JNPOV6GRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，美国联邦航空局（FAA）正在调查部分波音和空客飞机上使用的假冒钛金属]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周五报道，美国联邦航空管理局正在调查伪造的文件，这些文件被用来验证最近生产的一些波音和空客喷气式飞机所使用的钛的真实性。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration is investigating falsified documents that were used to verify the authenticity of titanium used in some recently manufactured Boeing and Airbus jets, the New York Times reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-investigating-counterfeit-titanium-used-some-boeing-airbus-jets-nyt-reports-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K24XCNOP6FL7PBSMLGSGKON56A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道先锋集团的投票转换帮助特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克通过了 560 亿美元的薪酬方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉最大的外部投资者先锋集团（Vanguard）表示，该公司以公司业绩为由，对首席执行官埃隆-马斯克 560 亿美元的薪酬方案投了赞成票，从而促成了周四这一创纪录安排的通过。【原文：Tesla's largest outside investor Vanguard said it voted in favor of CEO Elon Musk's $56 billion pay package, citing the company's performance, contributing to the passage of the record-setting arrangement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vanguard-vote-switch-helped-pass-tesla-ceo-elon-musks-56-billion-pay-package-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35EQX77QD5OAHJUVWCBQO45XSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴基斯坦重税预算可能获得国际货币基金组织（IMF）救助，但会引发紧张局势]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴基斯坦一位前财政官员、专家和实业家表示，巴基斯坦计划在2024-25年预算中提高税收，增加国家收入，这将有助于巴基斯坦赢得国际货币基金组织的贷款批准，避免经济再次崩溃，但也可能激起民愤。【原文：Pakistan's plan to raise taxes in its 2024-25 budget and boost state revenues will help it win approval from the International Monetary Fund for a loan to stave off another economic meltdown, but could fuel public anger, a former finance official, experts and industrialists said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/pakistans-tax-heavy-budget-likely-land-imf-bailout-stoke-tensions-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YC2PYARCXBJF7BDYH6MHROLSSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:58:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，监管机构要求巴克莱审查私募股权风险敞口]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国审慎监管局（PRA）已要求巴克莱银行（Barclays）审查其在杠杆融资方面的风险敞口，一位熟悉此事的消息人士周五表示，这是针对贷款机构在私募股权行业风险敞口的全行业调查的一部分。【原文：Britain's Prudential Regulation Authority (PRA) has asked Barclays to review its exposure to leveraged finance, a source familiar with the matter said on Friday, part of an industry-wide probe into lenders' exposure to the private equity industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-asked-by-watchdog-review-private-equity-exposure-source-says-2024-06-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKGZF5DSABM6PGLIGZIMD7POAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:45:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>