<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 02:52:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 02:52:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚限制访问Grok AI，因性化图像引发的反响持续扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚周日暂时封禁了Grok的访问权限，成为继该生成式人工智能聊天机器人因允许用户创建并发布色情图像引发全球强烈反对后，采取行动的又一国家。【原文：Malaysia on Sunday temporarily blocked access to Grok, joining a growing list of countries taking action after the generative artificial intelligence chatbot sparked a global backlash by allowing users to create and publish sexualised images.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/malaysia-restricts-access-grok-ai-backlash-over-sexualised-images-widens-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7ZPERLACVOG3MVWWCHSQBIUTQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:58:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观察：特朗普与美联储矛盾升级，投资者反应激烈]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫与美国中央银行之间的紧张关系在周末急剧升级，美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔表示，政府曾威胁要以美联储总部翻修项目相关罪名对他提起刑事指控。【原文：Tension between the White House and the U.S. central bank sharply escalated over the weekend, with U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell saying the administration had threatened him with a criminal indictment related to the Fed headquarters renovation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-investors-react-trump-fed-feud-escalates-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATZC3BVQDZMATDBVDST75SB5PI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:38:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国奥维通在香港上市首日开盘小幅走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国半导体设计公司奥维通集成电路的股票在香港交易所首日上市时将小幅高开，此前该公司通过在香港二次上市筹集了48亿港元（6.1591亿美元）。【原文：Shares of Chinese semiconductor design company OmniVision Integrated Circuits are set to open slightly higher on their first day of trading on the Hong Kong bourse after having raised HK$4.8 billion ($615.91 million) from a second listing in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-omnivision-open-slightly-higher-hong-kong-trading-debut-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYLWH4PHJRPNZKUD2FA25NATVE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因美联储主席鲍威尔涉刑事调查而剧烈波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑欧元汇率周一早盘从一个月高位回落，因美国检方对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔启动刑事调查，加剧了与特朗普政府的紧张关系。【原文：The U.S. dollar retreated from its strongest in a month early on Monday, as U.S. prosecutors opened a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, adding to tensions with the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-reels-criminal-probe-into-fed-chair-powell-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDMGFCO5CVKFDCBNDQ7X3RCE7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:23:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示将与马斯克讨论恢复伊朗互联网服务事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周日表示，他计划与亿万富翁企业家埃隆·马斯克就恢复伊朗互联网服务进行沟通。此前伊朗当局在持续的反政府抗议活动中切断了该国互联网服务。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday that he plans to speak with billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk about restoring internet in Iran, where authorities blacked out service amid ongoing anti-government protests.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-talk-musk-about-restoring-internet-iran-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWEEIZQNLFOHHMSSU55DGGN7RA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:21:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔称特朗普政府曾威胁要对他提起刑事指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[杰罗姆·鲍威尔称此举是旨在向央行施加更多降息压力的"借口"。【原文：Jerome Powell called the action a "pretext" aimed at putting further pressure on the central bank to lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-powell-says-administration-has-threatened-criminal-indictment-over-his-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IIY5KCSZNMKVH7KRSNOJMFTOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:47:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称可能禁止埃克森美孚进入委内瑞拉，此前该公司首席执行官称该国"不值得投资"]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周日表示，他可能会阻止埃克森美孚在委内瑞拉投资。此前这家石油巨头首席执行官在上周白宫会议上称该国"不值得投资"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday that he might block Exxon Mobil from investing in Venezuela after the oil major's CEO called the country "uninvestable" during a White House meeting last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-says-he-might-keep-exxon-out-venezuela-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VD3GAG3F25KDFNZAJFSDA6YD4E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:46:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现货黄金上涨逾1%，触及4563.61美元的历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[现货黄金周一上涨逾1%，触及2026年首个历史高点4563.61美元/盎司。地缘政治风险推升避险需求，加之上周五疲软的就业数据增强市场对美联储降息的预期，共同推动金价走高。【原文：Spot gold rose over 1% to hit its first record high of 2026 on Monday, at $4,563.61/oz propelled by safe-haven demand amid geopolitical risks and a poor jobs print on Friday bolstering interest rate cut bets by the U.S. Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spot-gold-rises-more-than-1-hit-all-time-high-456361-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCUY7MJX6ZMWJKHICXS2NNM6UA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚关键矿产储备将优先储备锑、镓、稀土元素]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚周一宣布，将把锑、镓和稀土元素列为其12亿澳元（8.02亿美元）战略储备的优先储备品类。该国财政部长吉姆·查尔默斯正准备参加七国集团会议，讨论关键矿产问题。【原文：Australia will prioritise antimony, gallium and rare earth elements as part of its A$1.2 billion ($802 million) strategic reserve, it said on Monday, as its Treasurer Jim Chalmers prepares to join a G7 meeting to discuss critical minerals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/australia-critical-minerals-reserve-prioritise-antimony-gallium-rare-earths-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67YTY3IC7JPV3HCNQ7KJ3KAQRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价攀升，伊朗局势动荡加剧引发供应担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一油价延续涨势，因市场日益担忧伊朗抗议活动升级可能扰乱该欧佩克产油国的供应，不过委内瑞拉正努力迅速恢复石油出口，限制了油价涨幅。【原文：Oil prices extended gains on Monday on growing concerns that intensifying protests in Iran could disrupt supply from the OPEC producer although efforts to quickly resume oil exports from Venezuela are limiting price gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-climbs-intensifying-unrest-iran-spark-supply-concerns-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZP226XUWZPSPN7VCDZCYHJ7QQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本开启稀土资源搜寻之旅，中国正收紧供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[一艘日本采矿船周一启程前往偏远珊瑚环礁，探测富含稀土元素的泥浆。此举是东京为减少对中国关键矿物依赖所采取的举措之一，因北京方面正收紧供应。【原文：A Japanese mining ship departed on Monday for a remote coral atoll to probe mud rich in rare earths, part of Tokyo's drive to curb its reliance on China for critical minerals as Beijing tightens supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-sets-sail-rare-earth-hunt-china-tightens-supplies-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QP5BPTQYGFJ4REUFBUY2T55R2U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Allegiant航空将以15亿美元收购Sun Country航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[廉价航空公司Allegiant周日宣布，将以约15亿美元（含债务）收购Sun Country Airlines。【原文：Low-cost airline Allegiant will acquire Sun Country Airlines in a deal valued at about $1.5 billion, including debt, the companies said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/allegiant-acquire-sun-country-airlines-15-billion-2026-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPN6FSVJZZKHXCLQHJTFXO4QYE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列网络初创公司Torq以12亿美元估值完成1.4亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列网络初创公司Torq周日宣布完成1.4亿美元融资，公司估值达12亿美元。该公司计划加速推广其人工智能驱动的安全运营中心（SOC）平台，并拓展美国市场。【原文：Israeli cyber startup Torq said on Sunday it raised $140 million at a $1.2 billion valuation, as it looks to speed up adoption of its artificial intelligence-driven security operations center (SOC) platform and expand into the U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-cyber-startup-torq-raises-140-million-12-billion-valuation-2026-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EENVBIRX75OLZH2JVNMSNGYBK4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 19:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡塔尔和阿联酋将加入美国主导的加强技术供应链行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院经济事务副国务卿雅各布·赫尔伯格在接受路透社采访时表示，卡塔尔和阿拉伯联合酋长国即将加入美国主导的保障人工智能和半导体供应链安全的倡议。【原文：Qatar and the United Arab Emirates will soon join a U.S.-led initiative to secure AI and semiconductor supply chains, Undersecretary of State for Economic Affairs Jacob Helberg told Reuters in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/qatar-uae-join-us-led-effort-bolster-technology-supply-chain-2026-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZB4ESHSE5IDHOS3FS74UEEOEU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将推动加快行动以减少对中国的稀土依赖]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国高级官员表示，美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特将于周一主持七国集团及其他国家十余位高级财政官员的会议，届时他将敦促与会各方加大努力，减少对中国关键矿产的依赖。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent will urge Group of Seven nations and others to step up their efforts to reduce reliance on critical minerals from China when he hosts a dozen top finance officials on Monday, a senior U.S. official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-push-quicker-action-reducing-reliance-china-rare-earths-2026-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJZ7JLPUGNLL7MBSEDIIAAR4WE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:08:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达尔环球与特朗普集团启动100亿美元沙特开发项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特房地产开发商达尔环球公司首席执行官齐亚德·埃尔查尔周日表示，该公司将在利雅得和吉达推出两个特朗普品牌的豪华项目，总价值达100亿美元。【原文：Saudi real estate developer Dar Global will launch two Trump-branded luxury projects in Riyadh and Jeddah with a combined value of $10 billion, CEO Ziad El Chaar said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dar-global-trump-organization-launch-10-billion-saudi-developments-2026-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBV3O7CVBZJVBJPSI6P4AYY474</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度拟议的手机安全规则令科技公司忧心忡忡]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是印度政府拟向苹果、三星等智能手机制造商提出的关键安全要求，据路透社获得的四份消息来源及行业和政府文件显示，该举措已引发科技企业的反对。【原文：Below are key security requirements India is proposing for smartphone makers like Apple and Samsung, prompting opposition from tech companies, according to four sources, as well as industry and government documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/indias-proposed-phone-security-rules-that-are-worrying-tech-firms-2026-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPCGL4XWWNLYZHX264CAXAIZLA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:48:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：印度提议强制智能手机制造商在安全改革中提供源代码]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度提议要求智能手机制造商向政府共享源代码并进行多项软件修改，作为一系列安全措施的一部分，此举引发苹果和三星等巨头背后的反对。【原文：India proposes requiring smartphone makers to share source code with the government and make several software changes as part of a raft of security measures, prompting behind-the-scenes opposition from giants like Apple and Samsung.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/india-proposes-forcing-smartphone-makers-give-source-code-security-overhaul-2026-01-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZX22SBDUNOG7AHEGEWOK65TNM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:38:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：贝森特称美国下周可能解除更多委内瑞拉制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特向路透社表示，美国对委内瑞拉的额外制裁最早可能于下周解除，以促进石油销售。他同时透露，下周将与国际货币基金组织和世界银行的负责人会晤，商讨重启与委内瑞拉的合作事宜。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent has told Reuters that additional U.S. sanctions on Venezuela could be lifted as soon as next week to facilitate oil sales, and that he will also meet next week with the heads of the International Monetary Fund and World Bank on their re-engagement with Venezuela.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-may-lift-more-venezuela-sanctions-next-week-bessent-says-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YX3YXRNEJVNUFACVRQXYLOVGMQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的X平台将在七天内开源新算法]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克周六表示，社交媒体平台X将在七天内向公众开放其新算法，包括所有自然推荐和广告推荐的代码。【原文：Elon Musk said on Saturday that social media platform X will open its new algorithm, including all code for organic and advertising post recommendations, to the public in seven days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/musks-x-open-source-new-algorithm-seven-days-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VS5EMJ7EFJMIVF7OVZWJVQQ2L4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能研究人员称，尽管存在诸多限制，中国正在逐步缩小与美国的科技差距。]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国顶尖人工智能研究人员周六表示，尽管先进芯片制造工具的缺乏正制约着该行业的发展，但随着风险承担和创新能力的增强，中国有望缩小与美国的科技差距。【原文：China can narrow its technological gap with the U.S. driven by growing risk-taking and innovation, though the lack of advanced chipmaking tools is hobbling the sector, the country's leading artificial intelligence researchers said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-is-closing-us-technology-lead-despite-constraints-ai-researchers-say-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6FYB52LORL6LGBOEVLT3U2VGQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[焦点：力拓收购嘉能可计划给必和必拓带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓集团与嘉能可的收购谈判可能催生全球行业新领头羊，这将推动铜矿需求旺盛的采矿业加速整合，并给全球最大矿业公司必和必拓带来巨大压力，迫使其作出回应。【原文：Rio Tinto's , talks to buy Glencore and create a new global industry leader could spur consolidation efforts across the copper-hungry mining sector and heap pressure on BHP, currently the world's biggest miner, to respond.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/rio-tintos-bid-glencore-piles-pressure-bhp-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6WD4DODTZKRFB7GIEQJMZWRRM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度尼西亚因性化图像暂时封禁Grok访问权限]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚周六暂时封禁了埃隆·马斯克的Grok聊天机器人，原因是该人工智能工具存在生成色情内容的风险，成为首个禁止使用该人工智能工具的国家。【原文：Indonesia temporarily blocked Elon Musk's Grok chatbot on Saturday due to the risk of AI-generated pornographic content, becoming the first country to deny access to the AI tool.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/indonesia-temporarily-blocks-access-grok-over-sexualised-images-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUHDH2P55JMGFKXOL23ZWTJPQI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 07:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普呼吁将信用卡利率上限设定为10%，有效期为一年。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周五表示，他将呼吁从1月20日起对信用卡利率实施为期一年的10%上限，但他并未说明该计划如何落实，也未阐明如何确保企业遵守规定。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he was calling for a one-year cap on credit card interest rates at 10% starting January 20 but he did not provide details on how his plan will come to fruition or how he planned to make companies comply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-calls-one-year-cap-credit-card-interest-rates-10-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEA5KX7QM5MNZAQAWWP2I4DOPQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:47:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛将取代阿斯利康进入纳斯达克100指数]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克周五宣布，美国零售巨头沃尔玛将取代英国制药公司阿斯利康，于2026年1月20日起正式纳入纳斯达克100指数。【原文：Nasdaq on Friday said U.S. retailer Walmart will replace British drugmaker Astrazeneca in the Nasdaq-100 Index effective on January 20, 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/walmart-replace-astrazeneca-nasdaq-100-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MW3BWKA25RJM3ASPJ22A3SYNTI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示美国财政部可轻松承担任何关税退还款项]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五向路透社表示，若最高法院裁定特朗普总统的紧急关税措施无效，美国财政部拥有充足资金支付任何关税退还款项，但退款过程可能持续数周甚至长达一年。【原文：The U.S. Treasury has more than adequate funds to pay any tariff refunds ordered if the Supreme Court rules against President Donald Trump's emergency tariffs, but any repayments would be spread out over weeks or even a year, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/bessent-says-us-treasury-can-easily-cover-any-tariff-refunds-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPB3GC4MV5O3DHDMKOJEIYYB7E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称澳大利亚、印度获邀参加七国集团关键矿产会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特表示，澳大利亚及其他若干国家将参加他于周一在华盛顿主持的七国集团（G7）财长会议，共同商讨关键矿产问题。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said Australia and several other countries would join a meeting of finance ministers from the Group of Seven advanced economies that he is hosting in Washington on Monday to discuss critical minerals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-australia-india-invited-g7-meeting-critical-minerals-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3UEOOHM3ZIW5AP6XYK2OBJVZQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:28:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，如果人们能证明资金来源，海外汇款是可行的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五对路透社表示，美国财政部加强海外资金转移审查的计划，不应损害那些能证明资金并非来自社会福利金的人。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department's plan to increase scrutiny of overseas transfers of money should not harm people who can prove the funds did not come from social service payments, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bessent-says-overseas-money-transfers-are-fine-if-people-can-prove-origin-funds-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2JTFVLBFFJSPHARVAFQPUJ5WA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:24:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：MBS购买的目标是匹配美联储的资产缩减]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五表示，特朗普政府启动抵押贷款支持证券购买计划的目标，是使购买规模大致与这些债券从美联储资产负债表上滚出的速度相匹配。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Friday said the goal of the Trump administration's launch of mortgage-backed securities purchases is to roughly match the rate at which those bonds are rolling off the Federal Reserve's balance sheet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bessent-goal-mbs-buys-is-match-fed-run-off-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IBT6VZSDONMYHARXRVYXJMRSXA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国能源部长称雪佛龙公司已找到途径，可使委内瑞拉产量提升50%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长克里斯·赖特周五表示，雪佛龙公司已找到将委内瑞拉产量提升50%的途径。此前特朗普总统就该南美国家问题与多家石油公司举行了会晤。【原文：U.S. Energy Secretary Chris Wright said on Friday that Chevron saw a pathway to grow its Venezuela production by 50%, with his comments coming after a meeting that President Donald Trump had with oil companies on the South American nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-sees-pathway-grow-venezuela-production-by-50-us-energy-secretary-says-2026-01-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMS24L6S5NPYVFZMLYY3CVQQVE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>