<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 02:50:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市因特朗普关税放宽的前景而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周二上涨，追随华尔街的积极走势，一些投资者希望即将上任的美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普在上任后能采取比承诺更温和的关税立场。【原文：Asia shares rose on Tuesday, tracking Wall Street's positive lead and as some investors hoped incoming U.S. President-elect Donald Trump could adopt a less aggressive tariff stance than promised when he takes office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYAXCM6Q3RMO5NIGKERX7NZO24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 02:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场思考特朗普关税问题，美元汇率接近一周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美元兑主要货币汇率徘徊在一周低点附近，因为交易员们在考虑当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税措施是否会比承诺的力度小。【原文：The U.S. dollar hovered near a one-week low versus major peers on Tuesday as traders considered whether President-elect Donald Trump's tariffs would be less aggressive than promised.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-trades-near-one-week-low-market-ponders-trump-tariffs-2025-01-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7ROWLA3TRMHRK3AEP2XAOPQSA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:10:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CES 在股价创下历史新高后，英伟达首席执行官将在 CES 上发表演讲]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia 首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）将于周一晚些时候在 CES 上发表开幕主题演讲，届时可能会发布新的电子游戏芯片，并详细介绍该公司如何将人工智能领域的成功经验应用到数据中心以外的其他市场。【原文：Nvidia Chief Executive Jensen Huang is set to deliver the opening keynote speech at CES later on Monday and will likely unveil new videogame chips and detail efforts to parlay the company's success in artificial intelligence into other markets outside of the data center.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ces-nvidia-ceo-set-take-stage-ces-just-after-shares-hit-record-high-2025-01-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GJAVRUQXFPDNNU7LLZKPBV7JM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳取消总部的一些多元化做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦当劳在一封致员工和特许经营店主的公开信中称，美国的 "法律环境正在发生变化"，因此将放弃公司领导层多元化的目标，并放弃一些多元化做法。【原文：McDonald's is retiring its goal for diversity in corporate leadership and shifting away from some diversity practices, citing a "shifting legal landscape" in the United States in an open letter sent to employees and franchise owners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/mcdonalds-rolls-back-some-diversity-practices-head-office-2025-01-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEWBVEOOKNNN3L6PMNF2VXM3ZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁起诉拜登可为维持美国钢铁交易赢得时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[这些公司在周一宣布的一项诉讼中辩称，拜登通过虚假的国家安全审查阻止合并，剥夺了这些公司获得公平程序的权利，违反了宪法。【原文：The companies argued in a lawsuit announced on Monday that Biden violated the Constitution by blocking the merger via a sham national security review that deprived the companies of their right to a fair process.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/nippon-steel-lawsuit-against-biden-could-buy-time-keep-us-steel-deal-alive-2025-01-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNFYCESLM5LQHDF4OTMBLCZBIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[炼油商菲利普斯 66 计划以 22 亿美元收购 EPIC NGL]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国炼油商菲利普斯 66 周一表示，将以 22 亿美元的全现金交易收购 EPIC Y-Grade GP 和 EPIC Y-Grade。【原文：U.S. oil refiner Phillips 66 said on Monday it will acquire EPIC Y-Grade GP and EPIC Y-Grade in an all-cash deal for $2.2 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/oil-refiner-phillips-66-plans-acquire-epic-ngl-22-bln-deal-2025-01-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVMFNNE4Q5IKLF6COP2XQPOWOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即将卸任的美国运输主管称波音在 737 MAX 事件后还有更多工作要做]]></title><description><![CDATA[2024 年 1 月，阿拉斯加航空公司一架新的 737 MAX 9 飞机在飞行途中，一块缺少四个关键螺栓的门板脱落，即将离任的美国交通部长周一表示，波音公司还有更多工作要做，其改善企业文化的努力尚未完成。【原文：The outgoing U.S. transportation secretary said on Monday that Boeing has more to do and its efforts to improve its culture are unfinished after a door panel missing four key bolts flew off a new Alaska Airlines 737 MAX 9 in mid-air in January 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/outgoing-us-transport-chief-says-boeing-has-more-do-after-737-max-incident-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDGUYJ3BNBLUNKJV2AZJRXAHQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 23:40:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田自动驾驶部门投资北海道太空基础设施公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于日本的太空基础设施公司星际技术公司（Interstellar Technologies）周二表示，该公司已与丰田汽车公司（Toyota Motor Corp.【原文：Japan-based space infrastructure company Interstellar Technologies said on Tuesday that it has reached a strategic capital and business partnership with a Toyota Motor Corp unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyotas-autonomous-driving-unit-invest-hokkaido-based-space-infrastructure-firm-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYCVHODXIBNIVAZKGJJWQRUWBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 23:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 选举终极格斗锦标赛首席执行官白大拿和另外两人进入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周一表示，该公司已选出三名新董事加入董事会，其中包括终极格斗锦标赛（UFC）首席执行官、美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的密友达纳-怀特（Dana White）。【原文：Meta Platforms said on Monday it had elected three new directors to its board, including Dana White, CEO of Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) and close friend of President-elect Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-elects-ufc-ceo-dana-white-two-others-board-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ET6EYZHAJOJHEE4FZC5Q65NHY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 23:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星第四季度盈利预计将受英伟达人工智能芯片供应延迟影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球顶级存储芯片制造商三星电子预计将于本周三预测其第四季度利润增长继续放缓，原因是该公司难以跟上英伟达（Nvidia）对人工智能芯片的强劲需求。【原文：Samsung Electronics , the world's top memory chip maker, is expected to forecast on Wednesday its profit growth continued to slow in the fourth quarter as it struggled to keep up with Nvidia's strong demand for AI chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-q4-earnings-expected-be-hit-by-nvidia-ai-chip-supply-delay-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7JZE2DCNNKSXKHCDZZKQJD4EM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 22:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森美孚起诉加州总检察长和环保组织]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭记录显示，埃克森美孚周一对加州总检察长罗布-邦塔和几个环保组织提起诉讼。【原文：Exxon Mobil filed a lawsuit on Monday against California Attorney General Rob Bonta and several environmental groups, court records show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/exxon-mobil-sues-california-attorney-general-environmental-groups-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHNC5UPWWFPA7D3KTCRI5CMO3M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 22:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工机构称，谷歌应被迫与承包商工会谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司正面临美国劳工委员会的第二次投诉，该机构周一表示，谷歌是合同工的雇主，必须与他们的工会进行谈判。【原文：Alphabet's Google is facing a second complaint from a U.S. labor board claiming that it is the employer of contract workers and must bargain with their union, the agency said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-should-be-forced-bargain-with-contractors-union-us-labor-agency-says-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTL6QFQYRNJQLKYW2J2GKEQ4UY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：特朗普关税疑云重重，日本国债收益率岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AL4EMB5HTBJC5DGWBGSQDLADSQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾伯维因收购支出下调 2024 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯维周一下调了2024年调整后利润预期，原因是该制药商产生了16亿美元与里程碑付款相关的收购费用以及研发成本。【原文：AbbVie lowered its 2024 adjusted profit forecast on Monday as the drugmaker incurred $1.6 billion in acquisition expenses related to milestone payments as well as research-and-development costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/abbvie-cuts-2024-profit-forecast-acquisition-expenses-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLRQZV4F5BMSVJQOJA2NVJIDQ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 表示首席执行官戴夫-金贝尔将退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 周一表示，戴夫-金贝尔（Dave Kimbell）将卸任首席执行官一职，由总裁兼首席运营官凯西娅-斯蒂尔曼（Kecia Steelman）接任。【原文：Ulta Beauty said on Monday Dave Kimbell will retire as CEO and will be succeeded by President and Chief Operating Officer Kecia Steelman.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ulta-beauty-says-ceo-dave-kimbell-retire-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KG2EL4AEWBLXVJZ2IUHEYNG36Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:12:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着巴尔退出监管岗位，特朗普提前获得了重塑美联储的机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储监管副主席迈克尔-巴尔（Michael Barr）周一决定提前辞去监管职务，这是对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在其第二个总统任期内如何塑造美国中央银行的一个早期考验。【原文：Federal Reserve Vice Chair of Supervision Michael Barr's decision on Monday to resign early from his regulatory oversight role sets up an early test of how Donald Trump will try to shape the U.S. central bank during his second term as president.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/with-barrs-exit-regulatory-role-trump-gets-early-chance-reshape-fed-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAZB2RJJ7RJVRNF2UDA2PZKVXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ligado 在无线扩张停滞后申请破产]]></title><description><![CDATA[无线网络公司 Ligado Networks LLC 周日晚些时候在特拉华州申请破产，寻求削减 78 亿美元的债务，因为美国政府机构阻止了该公司向陆基 5G 无线服务扩张的计划。【原文：Wireless network company Ligado Networks LLC filed for bankruptcy in Delaware late on Sunday, seeking to cut $7.8 billion in debt after U.S. government agencies blocked its planned expansion into land-based 5G wireless services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ligado-files-bankruptcy-after-stalled-wireless-expansion-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4LFLI46YJORJARRQ3FKKOGUQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，BTG Pactual 将以 1.64 亿美元收购瑞士宝盛银行巴西分行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据巴西《环球报》（O Globo）周一报道，巴西投资银行 BTG Pactual 即将宣布收购瑞士私人银行瑞士宝盛（Julius Baer）在当地的分支机构，交易价值约为 10 亿雷亚尔（1.636 亿美元）。【原文：Brazilian investment bank BTG Pactual is set to announce the acquisition of Swiss private bank Julius Baer's local unit in a deal worth about 1 billion reais ($163.6 million), newspaper O Globo reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/btg-pactual-buy-julius-baers-brazil-unit-164-million-deal-local-media-reports-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDF6DMFDRNJALD27KLWV623HCM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司蜂拥进入债券市场筹资]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国公司纷纷涌入公司债券市场，因为在周五的就业数据公布后，通常在新年头几天进行的季节性筹资活动获得了额外的动力，以抢在国债收益率进一步上升（这将增加融资成本）之前。【原文：U.S. companies rushed to the corporate bond markets on Monday as what is usually a seasonal fund-raising spree over the first few days of a new year gained extra momentum to get ahead of any further rise in Treasury yields - which would increase funding costs - after jobs data on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-companies-rush-bond-market-fundraising-flurry-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXUULD2GZJI6DO7GCJ6BCYEJG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 19:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪尔利用新机器加大对自动驾驶拖拉机的投入]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪尔公司（Deere &amp; Co）周一在拉斯维加斯举行的 CES 展会上推出了新型拖拉机和工业设备，无需人在驾驶室内操作，从而加大了对自动机械的投入。【原文：Deere &amp; Co strengthened its bet on autonomous machinery by unveiling new tractors and industrial equipment, capable of operating without the need for a human being in the cab, at the CES trade show in Las Vegas on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/deere-boosts-bet-autonomous-tractors-with-new-machines-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4UUKNLZAJNFBCUC7DXEQC4D4A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 18:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国港口劳资谈判重启，自动化成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[涉及美国东海岸和墨西哥湾 45000 名码头工人的合同谈判将于周二重启，这场劳资纠纷将有助于确定从缅因州到德克萨斯州的港口自动化步伐。【原文：Contract talks covering 45,000 dockworkers on the U.S. East and Gulf Coasts are set to restart on Tuesday in a labor dispute that will help set the pace of automation at ports stretching from Maine to Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-port-labor-talks-resume-with-spotlight-automation-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5DNIGMJP5OSZNA3DR55GDFJMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:12:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，Gemini 同意因 CFTC 指控被处以 500 万美元罚款和禁制令]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一份法庭文件显示，双子座信托公司同意支付 500 万美元的民事罚款，以了结美国商品期货交易委员会对其 2017 年比特币期货合约相关声明的指控。【原文：Gemini Trust Company agreed to pay a civil penalty of $5 million to settle U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission charges in connection with statements it made in connection with its bitcoin futures contract in 2017, a court filing showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gemini-agrees-5-mln-fine-injunction-over-cftc-charges-filing-shows-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPIBY4L5WVLVJKW67VTJG62YY4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:58:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将腾讯、CATL列入涉嫌协助北京军方的中国公司名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防部周一表示，它已将包括游戏和社交媒体领军企业腾讯控股和电池制造商 CATL 在内的中国科技巨头列入它所说的与中国军方合作的企业名单。【原文：The U.S. Defense Department said Monday it had added Chinese tech giants including gaming and social media leader Tencent Holdings and battery maker CATL to a list of firms it says work with China's military.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-adds-tencent-catl-list-chinese-firms-allegedly-aiding-beijings-military-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSNWO4YRNJMIJPLHDROENGDINQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能需求强劲，芯片公司大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于微软计划在 2025 财年向人工智能数据中心投资 800 亿美元，刺激了对半导体需求将保持强劲的押注，芯片制造商的股票周一跳涨。【原文：Shares of chipmakers jumped on Monday as Microsoft's plan to invest $80 billion in AI-enabled data centers in fiscal 2025 spurred bets that semiconductor demand would remain strong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/chip-firms-surge-signs-strong-ai-led-demand-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSUCIIKIGVJQVHBMBFSVVJ3ZI4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:59:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：TikTok 禁令之后会发生什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院将于周五听取 TikTok 及其中国所有者字节跳动公司（ByteDance）的辩论，后者正寻求阻止乔-拜登（Joe Biden）总统签署的一项法律，出于国家安全考虑，该法律将从 1 月 19 日起禁止短视频应用，除非该应用从字节跳动剥离。TikTok 要求在法律程序期间暂停禁令，但最高法院没有批准。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court will hear arguments on Friday from TikTok and its China-based owner ByteDance, which is seeking to block a law signed by President Joe Biden that will ban the short-form video app beginning Jan. 19 unless it is divested from ByteDance, due to national security concerns. TikTok requested an injunction to pause the ban during the legal process, but the Supreme Court did not im】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/what-happens-after-tiktok-ban-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCJ42XCWLBIINEVDHAEQ3FAESI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:44:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月工厂订单下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周一公布的数据显示，11月份美国制成品新订单下降，而第四季度企业设备支出似乎有所放缓。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods fell in November while business spending on equipment appeared to have slowed in the fourth quarter, government data showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-factory-orders-fall-november-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5RJBNJCEZN2NJ7YMVD3QO55RE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[猪肉生产商史密斯菲尔德食品公司公开美国首次公开募股申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[猪肉生产商史密斯菲尔德食品公司（Smithfield Foods）周一公布了其在美国首次公开募股的文件。【原文：Pork producer Smithfield Foods on Monday made public its paperwork for an initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pork-producer-smithfield-foods-makes-us-ipo-filing-public-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQGBY7L3SNJ6VCA7SHV2F6JTCI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大服务业采购经理人指数显示年底经济活动萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P全球公司周一公布的加拿大服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）数据显示，由于邮政工人罢工影响了经济活动，加上未完成的工作数量下降，12月份加拿大服务业经济三个月来首次出现恶化。【原文：Canada's services economy deteriorated for the first time in three months in December as a postal workers' strike weighed on activity and work outstanding tumbled, S&amp;P Global's Canada services PMI data showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadas-services-pmi-shows-activity-shrinking-year-end-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VMV5IVQVBIS3AFF3ML6R6WUMU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:34:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称有关其关税政策变化的报道是错误的]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一驳斥了一份报纸的报道，该报道称他的助手们正在探讨只涵盖关键进口商品的关税计划。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump on Monday refuted a newspaper report that said his aides were exploring tariff plans that would only cover critical imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-reporting-changes-his-tariff-policy-is-wrong-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YRZFDHF3BK6THWMI5ZRUXAAI4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:31:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国出口禁令将锑价推向新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着贸易紧张局势日益加剧，中国最新的出口禁令改变了关键材料市场的态势，消费者开始寻求替代供应，锑的价格可能会创下历史新高。【原文：Antimony prices are likely to hit record levels as consumers seek alternative supplies following China's latest export ban with growing trade tensions changing the dynamics around markets for critical materials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-export-ban-push-antimony-prices-new-highs-2025-01-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAYIKA7EEZPQZATMZTYZY62UT4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>