<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:38:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:38:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官表示，如果征收关税，Essity 可能会将更多生产转移到美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典卫生用品和生活用纸生产商 Essity 首席执行官 Magnus Groth 周四表示，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税，该公司可能会将更多生产从墨西哥和加拿大转移到美国，但不会考虑关闭工厂。【原文：Swedish hygiene product and tissue maker Essity could move more of its production into the U.S. from Mexico and Canada if tariffs are introduced by President Donald Trump, but is not considering plant closures, CEO Magnus Groth said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/essity-could-move-more-production-into-us-if-tariffs-are-introduced-ceo-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBQO3HGINBN6VC5BQOBPOOZFWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，日产汽车将从 SK On 采购电动汽车电池，供应美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经新闻》周四称，日产汽车计划从2028年左右开始向韩国SK On公司采购在美国销售的电动汽车电池。【原文：Nissan Motor plans to procure batteries for electric vehicles sold in the U.S. from South Korea's SK On from around 2028 onwards, the Nikkei newspaper said on Thursday, as the troubled Japanese automaker looks to ramp up its EV business as part of a planned turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-procure-ev-batteries-sk-us-market-nikkei-reports-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLQWIGMWXNJ3BCINUR6K7KH4LI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行称，2025 年亚洲科技基金募集规模将扩大 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街花旗银行周四表示，受人工智能发展以及印度和台湾地区强劲活动的推动，花旗预计到2025年亚洲科技公司的筹资势头将有所增强。【原文：Citi expects increased momentum in Asian fundraising for tech companies into 2025, driven by developments in artificial intelligence and robust activity in India and Taiwan, the Wall Street bank said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/asian-tech-fundraising-expand-10-2025-says-citi-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IN5QJBYQNKGJPOWPIJESJBDRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称中国万科正洽谈向新加坡政府投资公司出售物流公司股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士透露，负债累累的房地产开发商中国万科有限公司正在就向新加坡主权财富基金 GIC 出售 VX Logistics 的控股权进行深入谈判。【原文：Indebted property developer China Vanke Co Ltd is in advanced talks to sell a controlling stake in VX Logistics to Singaporean sovereign wealth fund GIC, a person with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-vanke-talks-sell-logistics-firm-stake-gic-source-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SDE6GNPXVL7ZMO3BA6NQIKESU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港新世界发展称业务运营 "一切如常]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于香港的房地产开发商新世界发展（New World Development）周四表示，在 "媒体谣传 "其运营和财务责任后，该公司将继续照常营业。【原文：Hong Kong-based property developer New World Development said on Thursday that it continues to carry on business as usual, following "media rumours" about its operations and financial obligations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hong-kongs-new-world-development-says-business-operations-are-as-usual-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3DKTUXYX5L6LON2PEDXREMLNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能热潮减退，股市有所松动；美元在没有关税冲击的情况下萎靡不振]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，全球股市回落，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在人工智能基础设施方面的巨额支出计划引发的反弹止步，因为部分兴奋情绪逐渐消退，不过中国股市在中国政府的支持下表现较好。【原文：Global stocks eased on Thursday, halting a rally sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump's mammoth spending plans for artificial intelligence infrastructure as some of that excitement fizzled out, though Chinese shares fared better on Beijing's support.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-6-pix-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UMFYKM5DRKGNMFG7IB55UG6HY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政策成为焦点，日本对经济持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周四对经济前景保持谨慎，部分原因是决策者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政策及其对全球经济增长的潜在影响保持警惕。【原文：Japan's government on Thursday maintained a cautious outlook for the economy in part as policymakers kept a wary eye on U.S. President Donald Trump's policies and their potential impact on global growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-cautious-economy-trumps-policies-take-centre-stage-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RNSQMFG6FK3ZP2SOZ3TEWC544</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:34:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[游说团体称，德国电子商务销售额自 2021 年以来首次增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家行业机构周四表示，德国在线零售商去年的收入自2021年以来首次略有增长，原因是储蓄率提高使德国人更有信心消费。【原文：German online retailers last year eked out slight revenue gains for the first time since 2021, an industry body said on Thursday, citing higher savings that are giving Germans more confidence to spend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/german-e-commerce-sales-rise-first-time-since-2021-says-lobby-group-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y4PV6SZHJPMLGQTXH5FJNGGN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席执行官称盈利能力 "尚未达到目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席执行官延斯-里特尔（Jens Ritter）周三晚间对记者说，汉莎航空的目标是重新盈利，但尽管重组计划取得了初步成功，但仍有一段路要走。【原文：Lufthansa Airlines aims to be profitable again but still has a ways to go despite the initial success of its restructuring plan, CEO Jens Ritter told journalists on Wednesday evening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lufthansa-airlines-not-there-yet-profitability-says-ceo-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZT36EPAYTJNK3JZTVJON6ZIP6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，汇丰关闭支付应用将危及约 400 个工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟知内情的消息人士称，汇丰银行已决定关闭其国际支付应用 Zing，这可能会导致约 400 人失业，因为该行首席执行官乔治-埃尔德里（Georges Elhedery）正在加大欧洲最大银行的成本削减力度。【原文：HSBC has decided to shutter its international payments app Zing, potentially triggering around 400 job losses, a source familiar with the matter said, as CEO Georges Elhedery steps up cost-cutting efforts at Europe's largest bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbcs-payments-app-closure-puts-around-400-jobs-risk-source-says-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHTZN2O3BZMI3PUCBPPNVQ3KEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 08:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，字节跳动计划 2025 年资本支出 200 亿美元，主要用于人工智能领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，TikTok 的中国所有者字节跳动公司今年的资本支出已超过 1,500 亿元人民币（约合 206.4 亿美元），其中大部分将集中在人工智能领域。【原文：ByteDance, the Chinese owner of TikTok, has earmarked over 150 billion yuan ($20.64 billion) in capital expenditure for this year, much of which will be centred on artificial intelligence, two people briefed on the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bytedance-plans-20-billion-capex-2025-mostly-ai-sources-say-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BTZWEV7GFNKLDYW7KWN5C2DXM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 08:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本以安全为由堵塞外国投资报告规则漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务省计划堵塞《外汇和外贸法》中外国投资者报告要求的漏洞，以防止情报泄露给外国政府。【原文：Japan's finance ministry plans to plug a loophole in reporting requirements for foreign investors under the Foreign Exchange and Foreign Trade Act, in an effort to prevent intelligence from leaking to foreign governments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/citing-security-japan-plug-loophole-reporting-rules-foreign-investment-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VE6NIOLRPVMC7LPSB3PLFWQ2XY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 08:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全年利润下降，彪马股价下跌 11]]></title><description><![CDATA[彪马股价在周四的盘前交易中下跌了11%，这家德国运动服制造商在周三晚些时候表示，对去年盈利下降感到不满，同时还宣布了一项成本削减计划。
该公司表示，今年的净利润为 2.82 亿欧元（2.93 亿美元），而 2023 年为 3.05 亿欧元，但其首席执行官 Arne Freundt 表示，他预计 2025 年的销售增长将强于去年。【原文：Shares in Puma dropped 11% in pre-market trading on Thursday after the German sportswear maker late on Wednesday said it was dissatisfied with a decline in earnings last year, also announcing a cost-cutting programme.
The firm said net profit came in at 282 million euros ($293 million) for the year, compared to 305 million euros in 2023, but its CEO Arne Freundt said he expects stronger sales growth in 2025 than last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/puma-shares-indicated-11-lower-after-drop-full-year-profit-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2S7HSRGIBJIW3JJEDTLEV4PW5M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 07:35:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税计划的开端不那么激进，亚洲外汇市场熊市退却--路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的就职政策暗示他将通过谈判而不是立即对贸易伙伴征收高额关税之后，投资者缩减了对大多数亚洲货币的看跌押注。【原文：Investors scaled back bearish bets on most Asian currencies after U.S. President Donald Trump's inaugural policies suggested he would negotiate rather than immediately impose hefty tariffs on trading partners, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia-fx-bears-retreat-after-less-aggressive-start-trumps-tariff-plans-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRDK2GPOENM53CEUEFU5D56VCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 07:27:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚澳航常客计划改革后飙升至历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，澳航股价创下历史新高，此前一天，这家澳大利亚航空公司公布了对其常旅客计划的调整，以吸引有成本意识的旅客，并在一连串争议之后恢复其信誉。【原文：Shares of Qantas rose to a record high on Thursday, a day after the Australian carrier unveiled changes to its frequent fliers programme to attract cost-conscious travellers and restore its credibility following a string of controversies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australias-qantas-soars-record-highs-after-frequent-flyer-programme-revamp-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPUFZ3IARRKFZLR45QFICEMAAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:28:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微不足道"：随着中国紧张局势加剧，特朗普可能终止的贸易福利]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统正在考虑改变美国对其他国家的一项重要贸易优惠，即进口关税的 "微量 "豁免，因为他指责中国采取了不公平的贸易做法，并将致命毒品芬太尼的危机归咎于中国。【原文：President Donald Trump is considering changing a key U.S. trade benefit to other nations, the "de minimis" exemption on import tariffs, as he accuses China of unfair trade practices and blames it for a crisis over the deadly drug fentanyl.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/de-minimis-trade-perk-trump-may-end-china-tensions-rise-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AH5QE6TEIJPRXOHMEFW546QLLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于成本增加抵消了销量和价格增长，Essity 第四季度业绩不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典卫生用品生产商 Essity 周四公布的第四季度核心盈利低于市场预期，原因是其生活用纸业务的原材料成本高企和美元走强损害了利润率，尽管销量和价格组合发展良好。【原文：Swedish hygiene products maker Essity reported fourth-quarter core earnings below market expectations on Thursday, as high raw material costs in its consumer tissue business and strong U.S. dollar hurt margins despite positive volume and price mix development.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/essity-misses-q4-expectations-costs-offset-volume-price-growth-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4J2LXBKZ4ZIWTP642DXBUYU4ME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:13:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车与通用汽车旨在签署合作协议，包括联合采购零部件]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车公司（Hyundai Motor）周四表示，该公司的目标是与通用汽车公司（General Motors）签署具有约束力的协议，涉及包括联合采购汽车零部件在内的多个合作领域。【原文：Hyundai Motor said on Thursday that it aims to sign binding deals with General Motors involving various areas of cooperation including the joint purchase of vehicle parts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-gm-aim-sign-tie-up-deals-including-joint-parts-purchasing-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTCJGGRLWRJP7DQDHIFR4HRDZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:12:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将在达沃斯论坛上对商界和政界领袖发表远程讲话，主题尚不明确]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周三在瑞士达沃斯举行的世界经济论坛上发表远程演讲，这是他首次向全球商界和政界领袖发表重要讲话。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will speak remotely at the World Economic Forum on Wednesday in Davos, Switzerland, delivering his first major speech to global business and political leaders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-remotely-address-business-political-leaders-davos-forum-topics-unclear-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJQKRIT6MFMV3FAVRWSHAMK4WI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲航空公司整合升温，BA 所有者 IAG 被认为是出售 TAP 航空公司的领跑者]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家和分析师表示，英国航空公司的所有者 IAG 很可能成为收购葡萄牙航空公司 TAP 股份的领跑者，收购价值约为 10 亿美元，这标志着欧洲市场的下一阶段整合。【原文：British Airways-owner IAG is likely to be a frontrunner to buy a stake in Portuguese carrier TAP, valued at about $1 billion, bankers and analysts said, marking the next phase in consolidation of the European market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ba-owner-iag-tipped-frontrunner-tap-sale-europe-airline-consolidation-warms-up-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RGU4NA43BOFBOQFA6TWEKCY6I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:05:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标中国为市场注入一剂强心针]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCIOAHWWMBNKVMCEWXP6UPS6J4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 05:34:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南非储备银行将于 1 月 30 日降息 25 个基点至 7.50]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查预测，南非储备银行将在下周将回购利率下调四分之一个百分点至 7.50%，并在 3 月份再次下调，但会将本轮周期最后一次下调 25 个基点的时间推迟到第三季度。【原文：The South African Reserve Bank will trim its repo rate next week by a quarter of a percentage point to 7.50% and repeat that in March, but then delay its final 25 basis point cut of the cycle to the third quarter, a Reuters poll forecast on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/safricas-reserve-bank-cut-rates-by-25-bps-jan-30-750-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FD6YCAKX4RPEJMSEVQIDGKNBUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 05:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受折扣影响，现代汽车第四季度利润下降 17]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国现代汽车（Hyundai Motor）周四公布的第四季度营业利润下降了 17%，降幅超过了分析师的预期，原因是该公司在放缓的汽车市场上加大了促销力度。【原文：South Korea's Hyundai Motor reported on Thursday a 17% fall in fourth-quarter operating profit, declining more than analysts estimated, as it spent more on promotions in a slowing car market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-q4-profit-falls-17-discounts-weigh-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYUHEBXSMFJIDPGMBZRY3FZ2HM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 05:14:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[退出巴黎会议后，彭博慈善机构将承担美国的气候会费]]></title><description><![CDATA[前纽约市长迈克尔-布隆伯格（Michael Bloomberg）的慈善机构和其他美国资助者周四表示，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统呼吁美国第二次退出巴黎气候协定之后，他们将承担美国对联合国气候框架的财政义务。【原文：Former New York Mayor Michael Bloomberg's philanthropy and other U.S. funders said on Thursday they will cover U.S. financial obligations to the UN climate framework after President Donald Trump called for the U.S. to withdraw - for a second time - from the Paris climate agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/bloomberg-philanthropy-cover-us-climate-dues-after-paris-withdrawal-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCRNTH6GRFIKJEOQQYBR67LHMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 05:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者组织称，Meta 修订后的付费无广告服务可能违反欧盟隐私法]]></title><description><![CDATA[消费者组织称，Meta 平台修改后的付费无广告服务仍可能违反欧盟隐私和消费者法律【原文：META PLATFORMS REVISED PAID AD-FREE SERVICE MAY STILL BREACH EU PRIVACY, CONSUMER LAWS, CONSUMER GROUP SAYS】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/metas-revised-paid-ad-free-service-may-breach-eu-privacy-laws-consumer-group-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XS2XUAWHNNJJZPZNZFEEYCUNBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 05:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：印度监察机构质疑富士康招聘调查，下令重新调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[文件显示，印度强大的人权监督机构已对劳工官员提出警告，称其未能充分调查富士康（苹果 iPhone 生产商）存在就业歧视的证据，并要求他们重新调查此事。【原文：India's powerful human rights watchdog has admonished labor officials for failure to adequately investigate evidence of employment discrimination at Foxconn, which makes Apple iPhones, and told them to re-examine the matter, documents show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-watchdog-faults-probe-foxconn-hiring-orders-new-inquiry-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIMCVFALEZIOHF6WBDZBRFWNRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 04:51:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 VinFast 的亏损给母公司 Vingroup 带来压力，外国投资者纷纷抛售]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南企业集团 Vingroup 支持亏损电动汽车制造商 VinFast 的战略正面临新的审查，由于外国投资者抛售和借贷成本上升，其股价已接近多年低点。【原文：Vietnamese conglomerate Vingroup is facing renewed scrutiny on its strategy of backing loss-making electric vehicle maker VinFast , with its shares near multi-year lows as foreign investors sell and its borrowing costs rise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-vinfasts-losses-heap-pressure-parent-vingroup-foreign-investors-sell-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZCLUGY56BJYNG4CGBEEEY5N4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 04:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会调查波音公司将工作送到非工会地点的说法]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司的工程工会正在正式调查其成员关于该公司正在将工作转移到美国和海外非工会地点的说法。【原文：Boeing's engineering union is formally investigating claims from its members that the company is moving work to non-union locations in the United States and overseas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/union-investigates-claims-that-boeing-is-sending-work-non-union-locations-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDP77QUS4FJ6BBWQIM7WWC5YJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 04:19:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院委员会将于1月29日就特朗普提名的商务人选举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院商务委员会周三表示，将于1月29日就唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统提名的商务部领导人选举行听证会。【原文：The Senate Commerce Committee said on Wednesday it would hold a Jan. 29 hearing on President Donald Trump's nominee to lead the Commerce Department, the agency that has become a key U.S. tool in its efforts to constrain China's tech sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-committee-hold-jan-29-hearing-trump-commerce-nominee-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XAKQMMUB25K6TC2CGJAESAACVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 04:04:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网站显示特斯拉将从 2 月 1 日起提高加拿大所有汽车的价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据特斯拉加拿大网站上的通知，特斯拉将从2月1日起提高其在加拿大的所有汽车价格，其中Model 3的价格上涨高达9000加元（约合6254.78美元）。【原文：Tesla will raise prices of all its cars in Canada from Feb. 1, according to notices on its Canadian website, with Model 3 prices going up by as much as C$9,000 ($6,254.78).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-raise-prices-all-cars-canada-feb-1-website-shows-2025-01-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUCCKVPG7BKUFCZS3EG7NPUSBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 03:39:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>