<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 21:33:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 21:33:55 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中东紧张局势升级吓坏投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[中东紧张局势的升级打击了投资者的信心，并引发了对风险较高资产（包括估值很高的美国股市）在局势恶化时如何应对的担忧。【原文：Escalating tensions in the Middle East have dampened investor confidence and raised concerns about how riskier assets, including the highly valued U.S. stock market, might respond if the situation worsens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/escalating-middle-east-tensions-spook-investors-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SC5QEPMFZZIL7LS2UDXYVHHNKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 21:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司罢工工会在工人医疗保险被削减后向首席执行官发出呼吁]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司最大的工会周二敦促该公司新任首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）更多地参与解决美国西海岸约 33,000 名工人的罢工问题，因为他们的医疗福利被削减了。【原文：Boeing's largest union on Tuesday urged the planemaker's new CEO Kelly Ortberg to get more involved in resolving a strike by around 33,000 U.S. West Coast workers, after their healthcare benefits were cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/striking-boeing-union-appeals-ceo-after-workers-health-coverage-cut-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFVXDDQ7LNJJJHIPAF3GBQV3NU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:19:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国需求疲软，耐克季度销售额降幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司周二公布的第一季度营收降幅超过预期，这家运动服装巨头正在与主要市场中国的疲软需求作斗争，并面临来自全球新兴品牌的激烈竞争。【原文：Nike posted a bigger-than-expected drop in first-quarter revenue on Tuesday, as the sportswear giant battles weak demand in key market China and faces stiff competition from newer brands globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-posts-bigger-than-expected-quarterly-sales-drop-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q54OLUZZZFIPREGTD4A4J2LQX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:18:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通高管称美国反电子政务集团的反弹言过其实]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通的一位高管周二表示，美国对环境、社会和治理（ESG）相关问题的政治反弹影响被夸大了，而且对美国蓬勃发展的绿色经济影响甚微。【原文：The impact of a political backlash against environmental, social and governance-related (ESG) issues in the United States is overstated and having little bearing on the country's burgeoning green economy, a JPMorgan executive said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/anti-esg-backlash-us-is-overstated-jpmorgan-exec-says-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFTMQVPCU5JVVAHGRZRI3R5S4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社推出每周 1 美元的数字订阅服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社新闻周二宣布，将从本月起推出数字订阅服务，加入为在线内容收费的新闻机构的行列。【原文：Reuters News announced on Tuesday that it would roll out digital subscriptions starting this month, joining a crowded market of news organizations that charge for online content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/reuters-introduces-digital-subscriptions-1-week-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGHQSS346ZNY3KGQEQWFMI2BG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社报道：苹果准备明年初推出新款 iPhone SE 和升级版 iPad Air]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周二援引知情人士的话报道称，苹果公司即将生产更新版 iPhone SE，作为明年初的新入门级机型，同时还计划生产新款 iPad Air。【原文：Apple is nearing production of an updated iPhone SE that will serve as an new entry-level model for early next year and is also aiming to manufacture new iPad Air models, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-readies-new-iphone-se-upgraded-ipad-air-early-next-year-bloomberg-news-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YH6552HCNVPRZOXOCKHVPJRPQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:43:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储流动性工具需求在新一轮回购市场忧虑中有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储流动性工具的资金流入在新季度的第一天有所缓解，尽管市场上有些人现在担心，有迹象表明货币市场压力正在增加，可能导致央行重新考虑其资产负债表缩减计划。【原文：Inflows into Federal Reserve liquidity tools eased on the first day of the new quarter, although some in markets now worry there are signs of building money market pressures that could cause the central bank to rethink its balance sheet drawdown plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-liquidity-tools-see-demand-ease-amid-new-repo-market-anxieties-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEEWFXVPUROVFI6BLWN4NASVYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:26:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citgo 股票拍卖债权人反对埃利奥特附属公司的出价条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，寻求从 Citgo 石油公司母公司股份拍卖中获得收益以偿还委内瑞拉征用和拖欠债务的债权人广泛批评了美国法院第二轮竞标中选定的有条件出价的条款。【原文：Creditors seeking proceeds from an auction of shares in a parent of Citgo Petroleum to repay them for Venezuela's expropriations and debt defaults on Tuesday widely criticized terms of a conditional offer selected in the U.S. court's second bidding round.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/citgo-share-auction-creditors-oppose-terms-elliott-affiliates-bid-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FQQII4PFFNEVLVQGWHRBSUNZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:21:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[J&J 将投资 20 多亿美元新建生产设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司（Johnson &amp; Johnson）周二表示，它将投资 20 多亿美元在北卡罗来纳州威尔逊（Wilson）建立一个新的生产设施，以帮助生产新疗法。【原文：Johnson &amp; Johnson said on Tuesday it will invest more than $2 billion to build a new manufacturing facility at Wilson, North Carolina, aiding production of new therapies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/jj-invest-more-than-2-billion-new-manufacturing-facility-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSJHQOSE2NOBDMVRXWK7W3DCG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:08:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储终止 2013 年针对花旗集团的洗钱执法行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周二宣布，已经终止了 2013 年针对花旗集团的执法行动，原因是花旗集团的洗钱监管能力存在缺陷。【原文：The Federal Reserve announced on Tuesday that it had terminated a 2013 enforcement action it filed against Citigroup over shortcomings in its capacity to police money laundering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-terminates-2013-money-laundering-enforcement-action-against-citigroup-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25MYDUHXRNI5VAXPZAQOIPYFPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通计划招聘多达 20 名新员工，扩充加拿大资产管理团队]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）的一位高级管理人员周二表示，该行在加拿大不断扩大的资产管理业务将在未来 18 个月内增加多达 20 个工作岗位，同时该行还为注重收益的投资者推出了两只主动管理的交易所交易基金。【原文：JPMorgan's expanding asset management business in Canada will add up to 20 jobs over the next 18 months, a senior executive said on Tuesday, as the bank launched two actively managed exchange-traded funds for income-focused investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-plans-up-20-new-hires-expand-canadian-asset-management-team-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5ZITP7WBZLXJLGNDCD3T22SY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国港口罢工为美联储前景再添变数]]></title><description><![CDATA[COVID-19 大流行病对全球供应链造成的沉重打击也给美国联邦储备官员留下了伤痕，他们认为港口中断和集装箱货轮倒退造成的影响只会引发 "短暂的 "通货膨胀。【原文：The COVID-19 pandemic's crushing blow to global supply chains also scarred U.S. Federal Reserve officials who thought the fallout from disrupted ports and backed up container ships would cause only "transitory" inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-port-strike-adds-another-uncertainty-feds-outlook-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLWRK6VOGRP4NKYJTQ2EUK6KLQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，诺和诺德已制定缓解计划，以尽量减少港口罢工造成的干扰]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周二援引该公司发言人的话报道，丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司已制定了缓解计划，以尽量减少或防止因美国海港罢工而造成的生产中断。【原文：Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk has mitigation plans in place to minimize or prevent any disruption to its production due to sea port strikes in the United States, CNBC reported on Tuesday citing a company spokesperson.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-has-mitigation-plans-minimize-disruption-port-strikes-cnbc-reports-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIAKHGVJ4RPQBPFAANIFCMJGEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关键短期利率在月末动荡中飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国关键的隔夜融资利率跳升，表明月底和第三季度货币市场流动性趋紧。【原文：A key U.S. overnight funding interest rate jumped on Monday in a sign of tighter liquidity in money markets at the end of the month and the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/key-us-short-term-rate-surges-amid-month-end-turbulence-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWFSICREO5NYBAGZ567RQP2SVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国初步确定对从东南亚进口的太阳能产品征收新关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周二宣布对越南、柬埔寨、马来西亚和泰国公司进口的太阳能电池征收反补贴反补贴税。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department on Tuesday announced anti-subsidy countervailing duties on solar cells imported by companies from Vietnam, Cambodia, Malaysia and Thailand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-sets-preliminary-new-duties-solar-imports-southeast-asia-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VVX2N25XRPLRKUET3R6EH4GXU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部称，美国自 1 月 1 日起发放 20 亿美元电动汽车退税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周二表示，自1月1日以来，美国政府已提前发放了20亿美元的销售点消费者电动汽车（EV）税收抵免付款，涉及30多万辆汽车。【原文：The U.S. government has issued $2 billion in advance point-of-sale consumer electric vehicle (EV) tax credit payments since Jan. 1 covering more than 300,000 vehicles, the Treasury said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-issues-2-billion-ev-tax-rebates-since-jan-1-treasury-says-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZQ73F4KQZN6DIJGHWWY4UPZRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 为开发人员推出新工具，帮助他们快速构建人工智能模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，OpenAI 推出了一系列新工具，使开发人员能更容易地基于其人工智能技术建立模型。【原文：OpenAI unveiled a host of new tools on Tuesday that would make it easier for developers to build models based on its artificial intelligence technology, as the ChatGPT maker wrestles with tech giants to keep up in the generative AI race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-introduces-new-tools-developers-fast-track-building-ai-models-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXR7LLCAJ5PLVADWNJ5SCAHNQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:18:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton 击败股东对疫情后财务预测的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Peloton Interactive 赢得了一项诉讼的撤诉，该诉讼称 Peloton Interactive 通过隐瞒其家用健身器材的需求量在 COVID-19 大流行后激增，但随着疫苗的上市和健身房的重新开业，需求量却在下降，从而欺骗了股东。【原文：Peloton Interactive won dismissal of a lawsuit claiming it defrauded shareholders by concealing how demand for its home exercise equipment, which surged after the COVID-19 pandemic began, was declining as vaccines became available and gyms began reopening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/peloton-beats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-post-pandemic-financial-forecasts-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZWTKPFPCVN5FJEO6ZR27NDNB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:01:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CVS Health 为削减成本将裁员近 2,900 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[CVS Health 周二表示，该公司将裁员约 2900 人，占其员工总数的比例不到 1%，因为这家医疗保健企业集团的目标是削减成本。【原文：CVS Health said on Tuesday it would lay off about 2,900 employees, representing less than 1% of its workforce, as the healthcare conglomerate aims to cut costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-health-lay-off-nearly-2900-employees-cost-cutting-push-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOMUO4V2KRKDVPTCW3XRZ34PRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构称，吉普车主应将车停在室外，等待召回修复]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局表示，15.4 万辆吉普插电式混合动力电动 SUV 的车主应将车停在室外，远离建筑物或其他车辆，直到完成召回维修。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said owners of 154,000 Jeep plug-in hybrid electric SUVs should park outside and away from buildings or other vehicles until they get recall repairs completed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/jeep-owners-should-park-outside-pending-recall-fix-us-agency-says-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQ6CZRI2CNJU3CWT3HLMGBGGB4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:53:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田称因预计美国港口罢工而增加库存]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车北美分公司周二表示，在当天早些时候开始的美国港口罢工之前，该公司已经建立了额外的汽车和零部件库存。【原文：Toyota Motor North America said on Tuesday it had built extra inventory of vehicles and parts ahead of the U.S. port strikes, which began earlier in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-says-built-extra-stock-anticipation-us-port-strikes-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NS2DRKAXYJLLVN5X6EFZHGT7FU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监察机构向医疗债务催收者发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高消费者金融监督机构周二警告医疗债务催收者，如果他们非法试图催收不准确或法律上无效的医疗债务，他们将面临联邦监管机构的执法行动。【原文：The top U.S. consumer financial watchdog on Tuesday warned medical debt collectors they face enforcement action by federal regulators if they illegally attempt to collect on inaccurate or legally invalid medical debts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-watchdog-issues-warning-medical-debt-collectors-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KLI235U2BOEJOBWW7ABKQRBAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:41:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称欧洲汽车制造商受美国码头工人罢工影响最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，欧洲汽车制造商最有可能受到美国东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸港口码头工人罢工的影响，因为他们严重依赖这些港口，但如果供应商受到影响，时间更长的罢工可能会对汽车行业造成更广泛的冲击。【原文：European automakers are most likely affected by the dockworkers strike at U.S. East Coast and Gulf Coast ports because they rely heavily on those locations, but a longer walkout could hit the industry more broadly if suppliers suffer, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/european-automakers-most-risk-us-dockworkers-strike-analysts-say-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSGE6CMO4JP6FAO4PRUZEMXOYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美谈判有助于避免中国对加征关税的报复--财政部官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部最高经济外交官在周二接受采访时说，中国没有对美国提高中国进口商品关税进行报复，部分原因是世界上最大的两个经济体之间继续进行对话。【原文：China has not retaliated against U.S. tariff increases on Chinese imports partly because of continued dialogue between the world's two largest economies, the U.S. Treasury's top economic diplomat said in an interview aired on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-china-talks-helping-avoid-chinese-retaliation-against-tariff-hikes-treasury-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCT3EBHB7FOZJOCAC33A4FHKDY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车第三季度美国销量下降约 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，通用汽车公司（General Motors）发布报告称，其第三季度在美国的新车销量下降了 2.2%，这主要是受三个月内销售天数减少以及通货膨胀导致客户支出减少的影响。【原文：General Motors reported a 2.2% fall in third-quarter sales of its new vehicles in the United States on Tuesday, pressured by fewer sales days in the three-month period and lower customer spending due to inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gms-third-quarter-us-sales-fall-about-2-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRZFIKGNABNLHKRKJVNC626E6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）推出付费墙，对部分用户每月收费 3.99 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国有线电视新闻网（CNN）周二表示，该新闻网站已推出付费墙，并要求部分用户每月支付 3.99 美元来访问其内容，以寻求数字收入来源。【原文：CNN has rolled out a paywall and is asking some of its users to pay $3.99 a month for access to its content, the news website said on Tuesday, as it looks to generate a digital revenue stream.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cnn-launches-paywall-charge-399-month-some-users-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXVBIEQZR5PQNNZVD6XYFZJHLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金反弹削弱了主要市场的实物需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士和分析师表示，随着黄金价格持续上涨，主要市场对黄金的实物需求急剧下降，一些零售消费者选择出售所持黄金并将利润入账。【原文：Physical demand for gold across key markets has tumbled as prices continue to rise, with some retail consumers opting to sell their holdings and book the profit, industry players and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-rally-cripples-physical-demand-key-markets-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEYXCSPXLVKRRA2I52XYUQ3AN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司被美国劳工委员会指控实施非法工作场所规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会发出投诉，指控苹果公司通过维持一系列非法的工作场所规定，侵犯了员工组织和争取更好工作条件的权利。【原文：A U.S. labor board issued a complaint accusing Apple of violating employees' rights to organize and advocate for better working conditions by maintaining a series of unlawful workplace rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-accused-by-us-labor-board-imposing-illegal-workplace-rules-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7P27CBJ2UFLRVHN5PNMOMFWKKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:59:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月建筑支出因单户住宅建设而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于独户住宅项目支出大幅下降，8 月份美国建筑支出意外下降，但借贷成本的下降可能会刺激未来几个月的建筑活动。【原文：U.S. construction spending unexpectedly fell in August amid a sharp drop in outlays on single-family housing projects, but declining borrowing costs could stimulate activity in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-construction-spending-falls-august-single-family-homebuilding-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OT7PXSQJVRPJLJVQBZFFTIIKWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，凯雷支持的标准航空（StandardAero）将把首次公开募股定价定在区间之上]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周二表示，美国飞机维修服务提供商标准航空（StandardAero）在美国的首次公开募股定价将高于预期范围，这将使其成为今年股市首次公开募股规模最大的公司之一。【原文：StandardAero, a U.S. aircraft maintenance services provider, is set to price its U.S. initial public offering above its indicated range, setting it up for one of the biggest stock market debuts this year, people familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/carlyle-backed-standardaero-set-price-ipo-above-range-sources-say-2024-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2QQTHOIZFO3VAPNEBSUUUXMPY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>