<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:04:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:04:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国证交会指控 Foot Locker 前高级主管内幕交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周二指控一名前 Foot Locker 高管涉嫌内幕交易，称他在 2023 年两次公布财报前卖空了该零售商的股票。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charged a former Foot Locker executive on Tuesday with insider trading, saying he sold short the retailer's stock prior to two earnings announcements in 2023.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-sec-charges-former-foot-locker-senior-director-with-insider-trading-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PPV5PQQ72ZM7BJX7UDHDP5Q4MI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 16:28:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官支持挑战堕胎法规的天主教雇主]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官阻止了联邦机构执行乔-拜登总统政府制定的一项规定，该规定要求雇主为堕胎或接受某些生育治疗的员工提供便利，该规定针对的是一个全国性天主教商业协会的成员。【原文：A U.S. judge has blocked a federal agency from enforcing a rule crafted by President Joe Biden's administration requiring employers to accommodate employees who have abortions or undergo certain fertility treatments against members of a nationwide Catholic business association.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-backs-catholic-employers-who-challenged-abortion-regulation-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRYWPCJ4JROCBBGUDZ3CI2S6WA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 16:15:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克和 X 公司寻求驳回唐-莱蒙因取消合作而提起的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）和 X 公司要求联邦法官驳回 CNN 前主播唐-莱蒙（Don Lemon）的诉讼，唐-莱蒙声称他们在一次有争议的采访后取消了在社交媒体平台上的合作，从而欺骗了他。【原文：Elon Musk and X asked a federal judge to dismiss former CNN anchor Don Lemon's lawsuit claiming they defrauded him by canceling a partnership on the social media platform following a contentious interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/elon-musk-x-seek-dismissal-don-lemons-lawsuit-over-canceled-partnership-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXBAQPEW7ZO2DOZ4WIVUGNDWGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:53:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会就垃圾收费和成本问题与 Invitation Homes 达成 4800 万美元的和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周二表示，美国最大的独户住宅房东 Invitation Homes 将支付 4800 多万美元，作为在租赁费用方面欺骗租户和收取未披露垃圾费的和解令的一部分。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday said Invitation Homes , the largest landlord of single-family homes in the United States, would pay more than $48 million as part of a settlement order over deceiving renters about lease costs and charging undisclosed junk fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-ftc-reaches-48-million-settlement-with-invitation-homes-over-junk-fees-costs-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAWCX36BBBLCZAK6FBFPKVM73Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:50:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华平投资 4,500 万美元出售股份，退出印度 CarTrade Tech 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据印度证券交易所（NSE）的数据，美国私募股权公司华平投资集团（Warburg Pincus）旗下部门周二通过大宗交易出售了其持有的印度汽车门户网站 CarTrade Tech 的全部 8.6% 股份，价值 37.5 亿卢比（约合 4486 万美元）。【原文：U.S.-based private equity firm Warburg Pincus's unit sold its entire 8.6% stake in Indian automobile portal CarTrade Tech on Tuesday through a bulk deal worth 3.75 billion rupees ($44.86 million), according to NSE data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/warburg-pincus-exits-indias-cartrade-tech-45-mln-share-sale-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4AFE5YLGONNEPGQI7TR7ZBY3WA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[檀香山全球最大希尔顿酒店数千名员工罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[据希尔顿全球控股公司（Hilton Worldwide Holdings）旗下全球最大的酒店工会（Unite Here Union）称，由于合同谈判陷入僵局，本周二约有 2000 名酒店员工离职。【原文：Around 2,000 hotel workers walked off the job on Tuesday at Hilton Worldwide Holdings' largest hotel in the world as contract negotiations stalled, according to the Unite Here Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/thousands-hotel-workers-walk-off-job-worlds-largest-hilton-honolulu-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDNG3UNUHFP7FJAJLYDRKUYMQQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:47:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国政府推出新刺激措施，中国 ADR、矿商和赌场股大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在美国上市的中国公司股票以及以中国为重点的交易所交易基金、赌场公司和与大宗商品相关的股票纷纷上扬，原因是中国政府采取了自大流行病以来最大规模的刺激措施，使人们对恢复增长产生了希望。【原文：U.S.-listed shares of Chinese firms jumped on Tuesday, along with China-focused exchange-traded funds, casino companies and commodity-linked stocks, as Beijing's largest stimulus measures since the pandemic raised hopes of renewed growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/china-adrs-miners-casino-shares-leap-beijing-launches-fresh-stimulus-measures-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L7CHPQLBMJMOLK6MIU727V7LU4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国态度强硬，但阻止裕信银行向德国商业银行挺进的余地有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合信贷银行首席执行官安德里亚-奥塞尔（Andrea Orcel）成功地将德国政界人士团结起来，反对他入股德国第二大银行--德国商业银行（Commerzbank）。【原文：UniCredit Chief Executive Andrea Orcel has succeeded in uniting Germany's political establishment in opposition to his stakebuilding in Commerzbank , the country's second largest lender.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/germany-talks-tough-has-limited-room-halt-unicredits-advance-commerzbank-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXGX64QQBRP3JOIPMHF4IWOTJA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各国领导人在联合国会议期间重点讨论可再生能源问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，一个由全球最大的一些公司、金融机构和城市组成的联盟敦促各国政府采取相关政策，他们认为这些政策可以在2030年前释放出高达1万亿美元的清洁能源投资。【原文：A coalition of some of the world's biggest companies, finance houses and cities urged governments on Tuesday to adopt policies that they said could unleash up $1 trillion in clean energy investments by 2030.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/leaders-focus-renewables-un-sidelines-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APRHNJV6EZO7LAEPAAXCYSLDEI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦格理将以高达 17.3 亿美元的价格收购 D.E. Shaw 绿色能源部门的少数股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦格理集团（Macquarie Group）资产管理部门周二表示，该澳大利亚公司将以高达 17.3 亿美元的股权投资获得美国投资者 D.E. Shaw 旗下绿色能源部门的少数股权。【原文：Macquarie Group's asset management division is taking a minority stake in the green-energy arm of U.S. investor D.E. Shaw for an equity investment of as much as $1.73 billion, the Australian company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/macquarie-take-minority-stake-de-shaws-green-energy-arm-up-173-bln-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNBSSC4ICVL6FDU3HKGKJVJSIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多数银行预计黄金牛市将持续到 2025 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于交易所交易基金（ETF）的大量资金流入复苏，以及包括美国联邦储备委员会在内的全球主要央行将进一步降息的预期，各大银行预计黄金价格的破纪录涨势将延续到2025年。【原文：Major banks expect gold to extend its record-breaking price rally into 2025 because of a revival in large inflows to exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and expectations of additional interest rate cuts from prominent central banks around the world, including the U.S. Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/most-banks-expect-golds-bull-run-persist-into-2025-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNOKPXHJLVJ3PBPGZNDPBUMLO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:49:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司开始在美国进行第二阶段裁员，内部备忘录如是说]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份内部备忘录，随着媒体巨头努力提高盈利能力，派拉蒙全球公司已开始在美国实施第二阶段的裁员计划。【原文：Paramount Global has begun the second phase of its planned layoffs in the United States as the media giant pushes toward increasing profitability, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-global-begins-second-phase-layoffs-us-internal-memo-says-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAMVQU234JN5XCUJVKINBKN3NI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FAA 称波音安全文化改革可能需要数年时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局局长周二告诉美国众议院小组委员会，波音公司的安全文化改进工作可能需要三到五年才能完成。【原文：The head of the Federal Aviation Administration told a U.S. House subcommittee Tuesday that safety culture improvements at Boeing may take three to five years to complete.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-says-boeing-safety-culture-reforms-may-take-years-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAYAZXJFRFNGVMXSLYIUDXGT4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪称美国下届政府的财政状况将趋于恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[据评级机构穆迪（Moody's）称，由于政治两极分化，任何新总统政府都很难就减轻国债负担所需的措施进行谈判，美国的财政健康状况预计将进一步恶化。【原文：U.S. fiscal health is expected to deteriorate further as political polarization makes it hard for any new presidential administration to negotiate steps needed to reduce the national debt burden, according to ratings agency Moody's.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-fiscal-profile-set-weaken-under-next-administration-moodys-says-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BA2BGXOD4RIBZAIYSMRDVY763A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受劳动力市场担忧影响，美国 9 月消费者信心下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对劳动力市场健康状况的担忧日益加剧，9月份美国消费者信心意外下降。【原文：U.S. consumer confidence unexpectedly fell in September amid mounting worries over the health of the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-confidence-ebbs-september-labor-market-fears-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKKSTMLLKNJKJEAFS6GRQWXK7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:34:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brightmine 称，英国雇主的加薪幅度是 2022 年 6 月以来最低的]]></title><description><![CDATA[人力资源数据公司Brightmine周二公布的数据显示，在截至8月底的三个月里，英国雇主给员工的加薪幅度创下了自2022年6月以来的新低，加薪幅度中位数为4%。【原文：British employers gave staff the joint-lowest pay rises since June 2022 in the three months to the end of August, offering a median raise of 4%, figures from human resources data company Brightmine showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-employers-give-joint-lowest-pay-rises-since-june-2022-brightmine-says-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AODAM72QXBOPBMPWMW7ND64DCQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:09:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visa 因美国司法部指控借记卡垄断的诉讼报告而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[有报道称，美国司法部计划对这家全球最大的支付处理商提起诉讼，指控其非法垄断美国借记卡市场，Visa 公司股价周二下跌 3%。【原文：Visa shares fell 3% on Tuesday after a report said the U.S. Department of Justice plans to file a lawsuit against the world's largest payment processor, alleging it illegally monopolized the country's debit-card market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/visa-falls-report-us-doj-lawsuit-alleging-debit-card-monopoly-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZPH7MAP5KNNPTPS4PHLVPAWQY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，随着保留汇丰银行员工的承诺接近尾声，加拿大皇家银行的银行家们担心裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[据六位熟悉情况的消息人士透露，加拿大皇家银行的一些员工是在汇丰银行加拿大分行被收购后加入该行的，他们担心在本月为期六个月的担保期到期后会失去工作。【原文：Some Royal Bank of Canada employees who joined as part of an HSBC Canada acquisition are worried about losing their jobs when a six-month guarantee expires this month, according to six sources familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rbc-bankers-fear-layoffs-pledge-keep-hsbc-staff-nears-end-sources-say-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQWW5X6LKJNCHKQBKXNMXDXDTE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:48:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西方 ETF 投资者准备为黄金创纪录的涨势火上浇油]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，未来几个月黄金交易所交易基金的资金流入量，特别是来自西方投资者的资金流入量将增加，这将为已经创下历史新高的金银价格增添更多的利好刺激。【原文：Inflows into gold exchange-traded funds, particularly from Western investors, are set to rise in coming months, adding yet more positive stimulus for already record high bullion prices, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/western-etf-investors-poised-heap-fuel-golds-record-rally-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXV565XEP5L7ZGDUTEWAYEMNPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vista Outdoor 推迟股东大会，再次就南玻交易进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vista Outdoor 再次推迟召开特别股东大会，就捷克斯洛伐克集团（CSG）21.5 亿美元收购该公司弹药部门及其户外部门股份的报价进行投票。【原文：Vista Outdoor has again delayed a special shareholder meeting to vote on Czechoslovak Group's (CSG) $2.15 billion offer for the firm's ammunition unit and a stake in its outdoor division.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/vista-outdoor-delays-shareholder-meet-vote-csg-deal-again-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TERI7TYOGFPPFFWYYLG2LVT7FM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:44:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车之家因成本上升季度利润不及预期；股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车零部件零售商 AutoZone 周二公布的第四季度利润低于预期，受到通胀挑战的影响，其股价在早盘交易中下跌近 5%。【原文：Auto parts retailer AutoZone reported a lower-than-expected fourth-quarter profit on Tuesday, hurt by inflationary challenges, sending its shares down almost 5% in early trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/autozone-misses-quarterly-profit-estimates-rising-costs-shares-down-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U5QV6UIQVLQJN2EH3B2WVRWJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构将与谷歌合作解决有关 Chrome 浏览器 cookies 的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监督机构周二表示，将与 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司合作解决竞争问题，因为该机构发现，谷歌对 Chrome 浏览器上的第三方 cookie 所采取的修订方法仍会引发广告市场的担忧。【原文：UK's Competition watchdog said on Tuesday it would work with Alphabet-owned Google to address competition concerns after it found the company's revised approach towards third-party cookies on Chrome still raised concerns in the advertising market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uks-competition-watchdog-work-with-google-tackle-concerns-over-chrome-cookies-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRRYCB3LX5NHNGNDPURRUIDLXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:34:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会对 11 家违反记录保存规定的公司处以超过 880 万美元的罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周二宣布，11 家经纪自营商和投资顾问已同意支付超过 8800 万美元的罚款，以解决他们未能妥善保存电子通信记录的指控，这是美国监管机构在一系列此类执法行动中的最新一次。【原文：Eleven broker-dealers and investment advisers have agreed to pay fines of more than $88 million to resolve allegations they failed to keep proper records of electronic communications, U.S. regulators' latest in a series of such enforcement actions, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission announced Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sec-fines-11-companies-more-than-88-mln-over-record-keeping-violations-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWPVPVEQRVJDBPF2PIYBUKUBQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克说他的公司正寻求在阿根廷投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉和 SpaceX 公司首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周二在 X 上发帖说，他的公司正在寻找投资阿根廷和支持这个南美国家的途径。【原文：Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla and SpaceX, said in an X post on Tuesday that his companies are looking for ways to invest in Argentina and support the South American nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musk-says-his-companies-are-looking-invest-argentina-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGZHGF3VRFNRVNDV27ADT2MCQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:18:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vista、Blackstone 将以 84 亿美元收购 Smartsheet，这是今年最大的私有化交易之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[收购公司 Vista Equity Partners 和 Blackstone 周二表示，将以 84 亿美元收购协作软件制造商 Smartsheet，这是今年最大的私有化交易之一。【原文：Buyout firms Vista Equity Partners and Blackstone will purchase collaboration-software maker Smartsheet for $8.4 bln in one of the largest take-private deals this year, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/pe-firms-vista-blackstone-buy-software-maker-smartsheet-84-bln-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HGQKT7JARJFNJ2BSBUVEOZSEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飓风威胁促使美国海湾沿岸能源设施缩减运营规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[预计本周将有一场大飓风席卷近海产油区，在美国墨西哥湾沿岸运营的能源公司已开始缩减运营规模并撤离生产地点。【原文：Energy companies operating in the U.S. Gulf Coast have started to scale back operations and evacuate production locations in anticipation of the major hurricane this week, which is forecasted to sweep through offshore oil-producing areas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/hurricane-threat-prompts-us-gulf-coast-energy-facilities-scale-back-operations-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5GATIR4CRMUTG6QT7IZECKI3E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:10:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trafigura 任命 Richard Holtum 为新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[理查德-霍尔特姆（Richard Holtum）周二表示，他将从明年 1 月 1 日起接任全球贸易公司 Trafigura 的首席执行官一职。【原文：Richard Holtum will take over as Chief Executive of global trading house Trafigura from Jan. 1 next year, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trafigura-names-holtum-new-ceo-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K66HPZMSZ5JMNFF4VP3OEZ4NUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登的汽车技术禁令是打击中国电动汽车的有力新武器]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府提议禁止中国的车联网技术，这可能会成为其抵御中国廉价电动汽车冲击的最有力武器。【原文：The Biden administration's proposed ban on Chinese connected-car technology could prove its strongest weapon yet to fend off an onslaught of cheap Chinese electric vehicles that has upended the global auto industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bidens-car-tech-ban-is-powerful-new-weapon-against-chinese-evs-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3LJB3UI6FNGJIVMJ6CZKLQBK4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼通胀风险持续存在，应更谨慎地削减利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周二表示，衡量通胀的关键指标仍然 "令人不安地高于 "美联储2%的目标，因此在美联储继续降息时需要保持谨慎。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman said on Tuesday key measures of inflation remain "uncomfortably above" the Fed's 2% target, warranting caution as the Fed proceeds with cutting interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-bowman-lingering-inflation-risks-warrant-more-cautious-cuts-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6POFRWE5KNMNPOZHJHFYYATFKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月份月度房价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份，美国独户住宅价格略有上涨，但在供应量增加的情况下，整体趋势正在放缓。【原文：U.S. single-family home prices edged up in July, but the overall trend is slowing amid improving supply, which together with easing mortgage rates could make buying a house more affordable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-monthly-house-prices-edge-up-july-2024-09-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LNXSCCFFJKHRIYKTFOD74HQHI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>