<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:40:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:40:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，谷歌提议调整搜索结果以促进竞争对手，避免欧盟反垄断罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的文件显示，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司已提议对其搜索结果进行更多改动，以更好地展示竞争对手，从而避免可能被欧盟处以巨额反垄断罚款。【原文：Alphabet's Google has proposed more changes to its search results to better showcase rivals in a bid to stave off a possible hefty EU antitrust fine, according to documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/google-offers-tweak-search-results-promote-rivals-stave-off-eu-antitrust-fine-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7Y4IICEOZN2LDY37C453YPJSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:32:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储主席巴金不急于降息，不能忽视关税带来的通胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周五表示，鉴于新进口税可能引发通胀的风险仍未解决，而且美国就业市场和消费支出保持良好，因此不急于降息。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said on Friday there's no rush to cut interest rates given the still-unresolved risk that new import taxes might raise inflation, and with the U.S. job market and consumer spending holding up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-barkin-no-rush-cut-cant-dismiss-inflation-risks-tariffs-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOHEJ4EQSZIKFKKKX6UY5Z77BI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业科技资金荒仍在持续，乳业和太阳能行业成为亮点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业科技行业正处于充满挑战的投资环境中。然而，在资金不景气的情况下，一些公司正在寻找增长机会，尤其是在乳制品和太阳能领域。【原文：The U.S. AgTech sector is navigating a challenging investment climate. Yet, amid the funding downturn, some companies are carving out growth opportunities, particularly in the dairy and solar sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-agtech-capital-drought-continues-dairy-solar-sectors-offer-bright-spots-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVLLFKQM4NK73E4IEXPJQIYS2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AT&T 1.77 亿美元数据泄露和解协议获美国法院批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一名美国法官初步批准了一项价值 1.77 亿美元的和解协议，该协议解决了针对 AT&amp;T 公司的数据安全诉讼，该诉讼涉及该电信巨头数千万客户的个人信息泄露。【原文：A U.S. judge granted preliminary approval on Friday to a $177 million settlement that resolves data security lawsuits against AT&amp;T over breaches that exposed personal information belonging to tens of millions of the telecom giant’s customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/177-million-att-data-breach-settlement-wins-us-court-approval-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4W4SYQGEABIRVHSRNYJMRIFTEQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称花旗集团从摩根大通聘请德拉古-拉杰科维奇担任并购部门联席主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份备忘录，花旗集团从竞争对手摩根大通聘请德拉戈-拉杰科维奇（Drago Rajkovic）担任并购部门联席主管。【原文：Citigroup hired Drago Rajkovic as its co-head of mergers and acquisitions from rival JPMorgan Chase , according to a memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-hires-drago-rajkovic-co-head-ma-jpmorgan-memo-says-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7R3ETQIZHJI4ZAZMJVPAJF6YLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百胜中国推出人工智能工具以提高效率]]></title><description><![CDATA[百胜中国控股公司周五表示，已在部分肯德基门店推出新的人工智能免提助手工具，以提高效率。【原文：Yum China Holdings , said on Friday it has launched a new AI-enabled hands-free assistant tool at certain KFC stores in a bid to boost efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/yum-china-unveils-ai-tool-bid-boost-efficiency-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ2ZRUPFL5OVDAF4YHT42WFRCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:28:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国准备针对盟友在华芯片工厂采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，一名美国官员已通知全球领先的半导体公司，计划取消允许它们在中国使用美国技术的豁免。【原文：A U.S. official has informed leading global semiconductor companies of plans to cancel waivers allowing them to use American technology in China, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-prepares-action-targeting-allies-chip-plants-china-wsj-reports-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UG5U7ZQAZIPVLVQSTOAO4YOCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储报告称，评估关税对经济的影响为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周五向国会发布的最新货币政策报告称，美国通胀有所上升，劳动力市场状况稳健，但暗示唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税可能才刚刚开始显现，并重申了央行的观点，即在采取行动之前可以等待更多的明确信息。【原文：The Federal Reserve's latest Monetary Policy Report to Congress, released on Friday, said U.S. inflation is somewhat elevated and the labor market is in solid shape, but suggested that President Donald Trump's tariffs have likely only begun to be felt and repeated the central bank's view that it can wait for more clarity before taking action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/still-early-assess-tariff-impact-economy-fed-report-says-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7M4SYLRJCRI6BLMUDTHH6EUCQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，马斯克的 xAi 提高了 50 亿美元债务融资的收益率报价]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士周五透露，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 xAi 公司正在提高由摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）牵头的 50 亿美元债务融资的收益率。【原文：Elon Musk's xAi is increasing the yield it is offering on a $5 billion debt raise led by Morgan Stanley, a source with knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/musks-xai-increases-yield-offer-5-bln-debt-raise-source-says-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCTU325HT5MDVGKL3YK5ONQJLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[旅游科技公司纳凡秘密申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国企业差旅和费用公司 Navan 周五披露，该公司已秘密申请在美国首次公开募股，投资者对新股上市的乐观情绪正在增长。【原文：U.S. corporate travel and expense company Navan on Friday disclosed it had confidentially filed for a U.S. initial public offering, as investor optimism for new listings grow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/travel-tech-firm-navan-confidentially-files-go-public-us-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNMTUCUWLVKHHGDKXJ5XAC5KG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 与运动眼镜品牌奥克利合作推出人工智能眼镜]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 公司周五表示，它已与奥克利（Oakley）合作推出人工智能智能眼镜，这是继雷朋（Ray-Ban）Meta 眼镜取得成功后，该公司向可穿戴技术领域的进一步拓展。【原文：Meta said on Friday it has teamed up with Oakley to release AI-powered smart glasses, expanding its push into wearable tech after the success of Ray-Ban Meta glasses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-partners-with-sports-eyewear-brand-oakley-launch-ai-powered-glasses-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKAPUNIL6FONVGMJJWFINTN7GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:43:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，地铁公司最大股东对出售股份持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，哥伦比亚亿万富翁海梅-吉林斯基-巴卡尔（Jaime Gilinski Bacal）对出售其在英国贷款机构麦德龙银行（Metro Bank）的多数股份持开放态度，并已收到投资者的兴趣。【原文：Colombian billionaire Jaime Gilinski Bacal is open to selling his majority stake in British lender Metro Bank and has received interest from investors, two people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/metros-biggest-shareholder-open-selling-stake-sources-say-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVOVCI7MVNMKTBEUKS4AHECDKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔签署出售波斯尼亚钢厂和铁矿的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界第二大钢铁制造商安赛乐米塔尔公司在一份声明中说，该公司周五签署了一项协议，将其在波斯尼亚和黑塞哥维那的钢厂和铁矿出售给总部设在波斯尼亚的 Pavgord 集团。【原文：ArcelorMittal, the world's second-largest steelmaker, signed a deal on Friday to sell its steel mill and iron ore mine in Bosnia and Herzegovina to the Bosnia-based Pavgord Group, the company said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/arcelormittal-signs-deal-sell-its-steel-mill-iron-ore-mine-bosnia-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZKXUCO5TVID7D7J4D7667JSUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Haveli 投资公司将以约 15 亿美元收购人工智能数据库公司 Couchbase]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈维利投资公司（Haveli Investments）周五表示，将以约15亿美元的价格收购Couchbase，这家私募股权公司希望利用这家以人工智能为重点的数据库公司的平台。【原文：Haveli Investments will acquire Couchbase for about $1.5 billion, the companies said on Friday, as the private equity firm looks to capitalize on the artificial intelligence-focused database company's platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/haveli-investments-buy-ai-database-firm-couchbase-about-15-billion-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3N2FPPWEPFIBVOLGGJQFAVKDNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:57:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，阿波罗将为英国欣克利角核电项目提供 60 亿美元资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美国私募股权集团阿波罗全球将提供 45 亿英镑（60.8 亿美元）的债务融资，以支持英国欣克利角核电项目。【原文：U.S. private equity group Apollo Global will provide 4.5 billion pounds ($6.08 billion) in debt financing to support Britain's Hinkley Point nuclear project, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apollo-provide-6-billion-funding-uks-hinkley-point-nuclear-project-ft-reports-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7GMXAPMZRKSZK6TWEICGXVF7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒂森克虏伯首席执行官获得为期 5 年的新合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[蒂森克虏伯首席执行官米格尔-洛佩兹（Miguel Lopez）已获得一份为期五年的新合同，这家德国企业集团周五表示，还确定了夏季召开特别股东大会的日期，以便让股东批准其防务部门的上市计划。【原文：Thyssenkrupp CEO Miguel Lopez has received a new five-year contract, the German conglomerate said on Friday, also setting a summer date for an extraordinary general meeting to let shareholders approve the planned listing of its defence unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/thyssenkrupp-ceo-gets-new-5-year-contract-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AI5L6YBMJOSVOS7Q73LIIW4KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：竞购截止日期临近，土耳其航空探索收购欧洲航空股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，土耳其航空公司正在探讨竞购欧罗巴航空公司（Air Europa）的少数股份，这是对这家西班牙航空公司表示兴趣的最新一家航空公司。【原文：Turkish Airlines is exploring making a bid for a minority stake in Air Europa, the latest carrier to express interest in the Spanish airline, according to two sources with knowledge of the deal, with binding bids due in the coming weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/turkish-airlines-explores-air-europa-stake-bid-deadline-looms-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AG2T57KWCFK7PJ6L7MNRCYZZNU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称卡塔尔就以色列与伊朗冲突风险与能源公司举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位业内人士和该地区的一位外交官告诉路透社，在以色列袭击了伊朗与卡塔尔共享的巨大天然气田之后，卡塔尔本周与能源巨头举行了危机会谈。【原文：Qatar held crisis talks this week with energy majors after Israeli strikes on Iran's huge gas field, which it shares with Qatar, an industry source and a diplomat in the region told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/qatar-met-with-energy-majors-discuss-risks-israel-iran-war-sources-say-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4Z2DM2WUABORXENWXDPTOT52SA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席沃勒尔：鉴于通胀数据，美联储应在七月前考虑降息 - CNBC]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯-沃勒（Chris Waller）周五表示，鉴于近期通胀数据温和，且进口关税对价格的冲击将是短暂的，美联储应考虑在下次会议上降息。【原文：The Federal Reserve should consider cutting interest rates at its next meeting given recent tame inflation data and the fact that any price shock from import tariffs will be short lived, Fed governor Chris Waller said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-waller-rate-cuts-should-be-considered-by-july-given-inflation-data-cnbc-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7ISO4BQYRMJVCGZ6BT75NE7RU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博雅银行将 STOXX 600 指数年度目标上调至 530 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[博雅全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）周五将STOXX 600指数的年终目标从500点上调至530点，原因是中美贸易休战后全球经济增长具有韧性。【原文：BofA Global Research on Friday raised its year-end target for the STOXX 600 index to 530 from 500 on resilience in global growth following a U.S.-China trade truce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bofa-lifts-stoxx-600-annual-target-530-points-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMFLQVTY6JOHNBCC6ACTL4MJGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 12:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险公司 Aflac 披露网络安全事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[保险公司 Aflac 周五表示，它于 6 月 12 日在其美国网络上发现了可疑活动。【原文：Insurer Aflac said on Friday it identified suspicious activity on its network in the United States on June 12.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/insurer-aflac-discloses-cybersecurity-incident-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONY5WCF7NBPYTI5VZXVYM4RI4Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 12:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达顿餐饮公司上调销售预期，季度业绩超出预期，原因是休闲餐饮需求旺盛]]></title><description><![CDATA[达顿餐饮集团（Darden Restaurants）周五公布了强劲的季度业绩，预计全年同店销售额将高于预期，这主要得益于食品外卖的需求以及橄榄园（Olive Garden）等休闲餐饮连锁店的广告宣传。【原文：Darden Restaurants forecast annual same-store sales above estimates after strong quarterly results on Friday, banking on demand driven by food delivery and advertising efforts at its casual dining chains such as Olive Garden.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/darden-restaurants-lifts-sales-forecast-beats-quarterly-estimates-casual-dining-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNUY5OI4DRILRE7536JE35BCII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 12:16:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格上调年度销售目标，因杂货需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[克罗格（Kroger）周五上调了年度同店销售预期，押注强劲的食品杂货需求将抵消美国消费者因关税导致的经济不确定性而减少的自由支配支出。【原文：Kroger bumped up its annual same-store sales forecast on Friday, betting on strong grocery demand to offset reduced discretionary spending as American consumers grapple with tariff-driven economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kroger-lifts-annual-identical-sales-target-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXFZN3FMBNPWBNXMHHA7DYHRQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 12:07:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马克龙挑战欧洲在太空领域与美国和中国抗衡]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国总统埃马纽埃尔-马克龙支持欧洲卫星制造冠军计划，并呼吁加速部署 "星链"（Starlink）型卫星，同时宣布太空是世界力量竞争的新战场。【原文：President Emmanuel Macron threw France's backing behind plans for a European satellite manufacturing champion and called for accelerated deployment of Starlink-type satellites as he declared space the new theatre for world power competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/macron-calls-europe-ramp-up-investment-space-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3G36ZAFZYZJKHOZ3RAXBEW6U7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列与伊朗冲突导致美国股票基金资金大幅流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至6月18日的一周，美国股票基金创下三个月来最大单周流出量，原因是以色列与伊朗之间的紧张局势加剧，以及对美国提高关税对经济影响的持续担忧促使投资者减少风险敞口。【原文：U.S. equity funds logged the largest weekly outflow in three months in the week through June 18 as intensifying Israel-Iran tensions and persistent concerns over the economic impact of elevated U.S. tariffs drove investors to reduce risk exposure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-see-hefty-outflows-israel-iran-conflict-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQXF7WPO5NPSLKT32D2FBQEN7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标为期两周的中东窗口期令人欣慰]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QOMYLLFZ5LGPHXO6BB7ZQWPA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃森哲第三季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，埃森哲第三季度营收超出华尔街预期，原因是这家咨询巨头的企业客户对其人工智能驱动服务的需求不断增长。【原文：Accenture beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue on Friday, driven by growing demand for the consulting giant's AI-driven services from enterprise customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/accenture-beats-third-quarter-revenue-estimates-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GPOFKPHVVJSVCSL2IIUCFCA24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东紧张局势引发全球股票基金三个月来最大流出量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 6 月 18 日的一周，全球股票基金净流出 198.2 亿美元，为三个月来最大，原因是中东紧张局势升级和美国贸易政策的不确定性挥之不去，抑制了投资者情绪。【原文：Global equity funds recorded net outflows of $19.82 billion for the week ended June 18, the largest in three months, as escalating Middle East tensions and lingering uncertainty over U.S. trade policies dampened investor sentiment】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBGUMQJRRZJXRFUMJDFX7TWHRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[明镜》报道：奥迪可能在美国建厂以安抚特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《明镜》（Spiegel）新闻杂志周五报道，在关税冲突中，为了安抚唐纳德-特朗普总统，大众汽车旗下高端品牌奥迪可能考虑在美国的一个新地点建厂。【原文：Volkswagen's premium brand Audi could build a plant at a new location in the United States under scenarios being considered to placate President Donald Trump in the tariff conflict, the Spiegel news magazine reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/audi-could-build-plant-us-placate-trump-spiegel-reports-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRECGNXW5FMDVO44XI2EIAHP7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 投资者评估地缘政治和经济数据，股市稍作喘息]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者将关注以色列-伊朗冲突和下周公布的美国经济数据，以评估股市的近期前景，因为 S&amp;P 500 指数徘徊在略低于 2 月份高点的位置。【原文：Investors will focus on the Israel-Iran conflict and U.S. economic data releases next week to assess the near-term outlook for stocks, as the S&amp;P 500 hovers just below its February highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-stocks-take-breather-investors-assess-geopolitics-economic-2025-06-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEZXIIZI35MB3HIPXHQ4CFOSBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>