<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:05:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:05:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[智利 Codelco 公司 2 月份铜产量下降 6]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利铜业委员会（Cochilco）周四公布的数据显示，智利国营矿业公司 Codelco 2 月份的铜产量同比下降了 6%，降至 9.81 万吨。【原文：Copper production from Chilean state-run miner Codelco dipped 6% year-over-year in February, data from copper commission Cochilco showed on Thursday, slipping to 98,100 metric tons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/copper-output-chiles-codelco-slips-6-february-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WTH3DUJR5RLRZBTNPKMWOBNNTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:50:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[象牙海岸威胁提高可可价格以应对美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[西非国家象牙海岸农业部长周四表示，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提议的关税生效，世界最大的可可生产国象牙海岸可能会采取措施提高可可产品的价格。【原文：Ivory Coast, the world's biggest cocoa producer, could take measures to make the product more expensive if tariffs proposed by U.S. President Donald Trump go into effect, the West African country's agriculture minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/ivory-coast-threatens-more-expensive-cocoa-response-us-tariffs-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHAGSXWFBBIBLNUE7KPWNKI7RU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:28:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智能手机和大豆：卷入中美贸易战的主要产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美贸易战不断升级，导致可能影响多种产品的高额关税。【原文：An escalating trade war between the United States and China is leading to steep tariffs that could affect a wide range of products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/smartphones-soybeans-top-products-caught-up-us-china-trade-war-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANWMT37R4BMDZPVVSYOUTWXU4Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国卫生部长对 COVID 疫苗疗效表示担忧后，Novavax 股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[疫苗生产商 Novavax 的股价周四暴跌 22%，原因是美国卫生与公众服务部部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪在接受哥伦比亚广播公司新闻频道采访时对该公司生产的 COVID-19 疫苗表示担忧。【原文：Vaccine maker Novavax's shares plunged over 22% on Thursday after Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. raised concerns about the company's COVID-19 vaccine in an interview with CBS News.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novavax-shares-tumble-after-us-health-secretary-raises-concerns-over-covid-shots-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPHXCZL3PVONTJVWAE32Z4L4LI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税加剧风险，加拿大出口商寻求贸易保险]]></title><description><![CDATA[保险公司表示，一种鲜为人知的保险产品正在加拿大受到追捧，因为出口商们正在寻求防范美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税所造成的供应商和客户的损失和破产。【原文：A little-known insurance product is gaining traction in Canada as exporters seek to guard against losses and bankruptcies of their suppliers and customers due to U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, insurers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadian-exporters-inquire-trade-insurance-trumps-tariffs-heighten-risk-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3QGWHEQB5ZPODEX6RC6OR5X4CY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国工业部长表示支持意法半导体首席执行官奇瑞]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国工业部长马克-费拉齐（Marc Ferracci）周四表示，他支持意法半导体公司（STMicroelectronics）首席执行官让-马克-谢里（Jean-Marc Chery），因为该公司董事会两名成员被指控进行内幕交易。【原文：French Industry Minister Marc Ferracci said on Thursday he supported STMicroelectronics CEO Jean-Marc Chery amid allegations of insider trading by two members of its managing board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/french-industry-minister-says-he-supports-stmicroelectronics-ceo-chery-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INJ6QT7ODZN67D2HI5ZBCXM3TE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场动荡刺激资金寻觅，私人信贷二级市场销售额将上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[基金经理和高管们表示，随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战引发的市场波动加剧，迫使他们寻找新的方式来筹集现金，投资者正准备加紧出售其持有的私人信贷资产。【原文：Investors are preparing to step up sales of their private credit holdings, as heightened market volatility unleashed by U.S. President Donald Trump's trade wars forces them to find new ways to raise cash, fund managers and executives say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/private-credit-secondary-sales-set-rise-market-turmoil-spurs-hunt-cash-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STX64ZUCNVKQREDJWADTXIGHQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:25:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Janus Henderson 称，经济衰退迫在眉睫，投资者应减少股票投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[管理着 3,790 亿美元资产的 Janus Henderson 基金经理表示，由于关税可能导致全球经济增长放缓，该公司正建议投资者减持股票，购买更多投资级主权债券。【原文：Janus Henderson, which manages $379 billion in assets, is advising investors to cut stock holdings and buy more investment-grade sovereign bonds as tariffs threaten to slow global growth, a fund manager said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/janus-henderson-says-investors-should-cut-down-exposure-stocks-recession-looms-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFNQL44C4FIR7ABKAGBTWSY5HQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:25:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士称，美国将继续对道明银行和 Balfour Beatty 实施监控]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国司法部决定继续对军事住房公司贝尔福比蒂社区（Balfour Beatty Communities）和加拿大道明银行（TD Bank）进行企业监控，因为特朗普政府正在对这一做法进行审查。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department has decided to keep corporate monitors in place for military housing company Balfour Beatty Communities and Canadian lender TD Bank , amid the Trump administration's ongoing review of the practice, according to two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-keep-monitors-place-td-bank-balfour-beatty-people-familiar-say-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7W5S4SHX25NHROBWUEPHD6A3FE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:17:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比如果经济重回正轨，降息仍有可能]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行行长奥斯汀-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周四表示，降息仍有可能在某个时候出现，但与美国贸易政策的巨大变化有关的不确定性使得目前很难知道经济将如何发展以及美国央行的利率政策应如何调整。【原文：Interest rate cuts remain possible at some point, but uncertainty related to huge changes in U.S. trade policy make it hard to know how the economy will fare for now and how the U.S. central bank's rate policy should be adjusted, Austan Goolsbee, president of the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago, said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-goolsbee-rate-cuts-still-possible-if-economy-gets-back-track-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LO3OGOTZ2JPF5HVSKEM7Y6TB7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场动荡不安，中国茶叶品牌茶奇在美国上市，目标估值 51 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国茶叶连锁企业茶奇网周四表示，冒着波涛汹涌的市场环境，其美国首次公开募股的目标估值将高达 51 亿美元。【原文：Chinese tea chain Chagee said on Thursday it was targeting a valuation of up to $5.1 billion in its U.S. initial public offering, braving choppy market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinese-tea-chain-chagee-aims-raise-411-million-us-ipo-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CW5YB4LNM5O37LSVM4UF7GH5XY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:44:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示，中欧将研究制定电动汽车最低价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人周四表示，欧盟和中国已同意研究对中国制造的电动汽车设定最低价格，而不是欧盟去年征收的关税。【原文：The European Union and China have agreed to look into setting minimum prices on Chinese-made electric vehicles instead of tariffs imposed by the EU last year, a European Commission spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-china-start-talks-lifting-eu-tariffs-chinese-electric-vehicles-handelsblatt-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5TRBCIDO5JX7KC7BIODSB6LGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次威胁对药品征收关税，诺华计划投资 230 亿美元在美国建厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士制药商诺华公司（Novartis）周四表示，该公司计划斥资 230 亿美元在美国新建和扩建 10 家工厂，以应对特朗普政府再次威胁征收药品进口关税。【原文：Swiss drugmaker Novartis said on Thursday it plans to spend $23 billion to build and expand 10 facilities in the U.S., as it grapples with renewed threats of drug import duties from the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-plans-invest-23-billion-us-plants-trump-renews-drug-tariff-threats-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLEKCUM2ZRK47NLZOYJBI2MWQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:33:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡普里旨在通过降低价格和亚马逊电商销售重振 Michael Kors]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡普里控股公司在斥资 14 亿美元将范思哲出售给普拉达之后，可能不得不放弃其奢侈时尚品牌的形象，转而依靠中端定价以及与亚马逊网站的合作来打造其 Michael Kors 品牌。【原文：Capri Holdings may have to let go of its image as a luxury fashion house and bank on mid-tier pricing as well as a partnership with Amazon.com for its Michael Kors brand following its $1.4 billion sale of Versace to Prada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/capri-aims-revive-michael-kors-with-lower-prices-amazon-e-commerce-sales-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZ2ZXH2AZNN4LJWIKL7EDMAGZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Modelo 的所有者 Constellation 称，特朗普的移民政策打击了西语裔顾客]]></title><description><![CDATA[公司高管周四表示，由于特朗普打击移民，墨西哥和其他主要市场西班牙裔人口的需求放缓，Modelo Especial 所有者 Constellation Brands 的啤酒销售受到打击。【原文：Modelo Especial owner Constellation Brands' beer sales are taking a hit as demand from Hispanic populations in Mexico and other key markets slows down amid Trump's crackdown on immigration, company executives said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/modelo-owner-constellation-says-trump-immigration-crackdown-hitting-hispanic-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GV7JNVXLRFJZPEVHDPW2KEE6VU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:25:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新液化天然气工厂将提高 Venture Global 的利润，因为 Calcasieu 为长期客户提供服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Global 公司即将开始将路易斯安那州出口终端的液化天然气货物出售给长期客户，而不是全球出价最高的竞标者，但该公司计划在其正在新建的一个更大的终端采用这种有争议但利润丰厚的做法。【原文：Venture Global Inc is about to start selling liquefied natural gas cargoes from a Louisiana export terminal to long-term customers rather than to the highest global bidder, but it plans to employ the controversial but lucrative practice at a new and bigger terminal that it is starting up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-lng-plant-boost-venture-global-profits-calcasieu-serves-long-term-customers-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMDOO2M3XRMEBGQVUVJTU2SHAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，在特朗普发布行政命令后重启煤电厂没有经济意义]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源经济与金融分析研究所（IEEFA）周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普主张增加美国的煤炭产量，然而，为实现这一目标而恢复退役煤电厂 "没有经济意义"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is advocating for increased coal production in the United States, however, reviving decommissioned coal plants to meet this goal makes "no economic sense", the Institute for Energy Economics and Financial Analysis (IEEFA) said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/restarting-coal-plants-after-trumps-executive-orders-makes-no-economic-sense-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHUWDCOPKZMKPM5P3QV35OL5AA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗任命内部人士 Raymond Gatcliffe 为加拿大业务首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周四任命在该公司工作了三十年的资深人士雷蒙德-加特克利夫（Raymond Gatcliffe）担任其加拿大业务的首席执行官。【原文：Citigroup on Thursday named Raymond Gatcliffe, a three-decade company veteran, as the chief executive officer of its Canada operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-names-insider-raymond-gatcliffe-ceo-canada-operations-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KALHVDE3KZPNRGDJ3GLADPMNGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称，2025 年和 2026 年美国电力使用量将创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（U.S. Energy Information Administration）在本周四发布的《短期能源展望》（STEO）报告中称，美国的电力消耗量将在2025年和2026年创下历史新高。【原文：U.S. power consumption will hit new record highs in 2025 and 2026, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said in its Short Term Energy Outlook (STEO) on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-power-use-reach-record-highs-2025-2026-eia-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZP4RMK2QBP4DATM3EE6IPXSY4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶鲁大学研究人员称，特朗普暂停加征关税对降低总体关税率作用不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[耶鲁大学的研究人员周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普收回了他征收的部分高额关税，但这对降低平均进口税率并没有起到什么作用，而他的征税浪潮曾使平均进口税率升至较高水平。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's rollback of some of the steep tariffs he has imposed has done little to lower the average import duty rate from the elevated levels to which his wave of levies had driven them, researchers from Yale University said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-tariff-pause-does-little-lower-overall-tariff-rates-yale-researchers-say-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR6NUKWAKNPHXOMQMU4BKKQGXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[声明称，美国钢铁公司和新日铁公司与特朗普政府密切合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司和新日本制铁公司正在与特朗普政府密切合作，"以确保获得重大投资"，美国钢铁公司周四表示，在此之前，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的讲话使这两家公司长期寻求的合作获得绿灯的希望变得渺茫。【原文：U.S. Steel and Nippon Steel are working closely with the Trump administration "to secure a significant investment," U.S. Steel said on Thursday, after remarks from President Donald Trump dimmed hopes for a greenlight of the companies' long-sought tie-up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-nippon-steel-working-closely-with-trump-administration-statement-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7CTMI4NNFM6LNYU6L7YU7BCFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:54:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西贷款公司 BRB 首席执行官称，随着交易调整，Banco Master 的价格有望降低]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西商业银行总裁周四表示，巴西政府控制的银行巴西商业银行（BRB）收购 Banco Master 部分贷款机构资产的交易，可能会排除 "远超过 "230 亿雷亚尔（38.9 亿美元）的资产。【原文：The acquisition of some of lender Banco Master's assets by Brazil's government-controlled bank BRB is likely to exclude "much more" than 23 billion reais ($3.89 billion) in assets, BRB's president said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/brazilian-lender-brb-expects-lower-banco-master-price-with-deal-adjustment-ceo-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RVHPLY3DFODLP7UGIFZTXH6Y4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场关税混乱持续，华尔街转而大幅走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心高关税对全球经济的影响，华尔街主要股指周四再次重挫，与上一交易日美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）临时降低对一些国家征收关税时的历史性股价涨幅相比出现了逆转。【原文：Wall Street's main indexes fell hard again on Thursday on concerns over the impact of high tariffs on the global economy, marking a U-turn from the previous session's historic share gains when U.S. President Donald Trump moved to temporarily lower the levies on some countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-views-quotes-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZ6DIRVJGRPMXDM4OQPIJZ5IEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普暂停关税不会改变美联储看到未来风险的基本面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普暂停征收部分新的进口税，这可能减轻了金融市场目前所承受的压力，但同样的一系列情况仍在继续，这些情况重置了美国的经济前景，使衰退风险上升，通胀率可能上升。【原文：President Donald Trump's pause on some of his new import taxes may have lessened the stress that had been building in financial markets for now, but leaves in place the same set of circumstances that had reset the U.S. economic outlook with rising recession risks and potentially rising inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-tariff-pause-wont-change-fundamentals-fed-that-sees-risks-ahead-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHTUYLWP7VIVJIZCCZFMAUMYAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦称债券抛售引发不稳定威胁，影响特朗普关税转向]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周四表示，最近几天美国国债价格下跌引发的金融不稳定威胁很可能影响了唐纳德-特朗普总统扭转方向、部分暂停关税行动的决定。【原文：Former U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said on Thursday that the threat of financial instability prompted by falling prices for U.S. Treasury debt in recent days likely influenced President Donald Trump's decision to reverse course and partially pause his tariff campaign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/yellen-says-bond-sell-off-raised-instability-threat-influencing-trump-tariff-u-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SI5EQBVSKFPXVL4HMUVG7E7W7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈克表示，美联储应在金融科技领域发挥领导作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联储主席帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）周四在一个金融技术创新会议上发表演讲时，在准备好的发言稿中没有对经济前景或货币政策发表评论。【原文：Philadelphia Federal Reserve President Patrick Harker did not comment on the outlook for the economy or monetary policy in prepared remarks for a speech to a financial technology innovation conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fed-should-lead-financial-technology-space-harker-says-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZI6L2JC27RPHNO6UHO7DDEH4F4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约总检察长敦促国会加强加密货币监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长莱蒂西亚-詹姆斯（Letitia James）周四敦促立法者通过立法，为加密货币建立联邦监管框架，认为数字资产投资者迫切需要更有力的保护。【原文：New York Attorney General Letitia James urged lawmakers on Thursday to pass legislation to create a federal regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies, arguing that digital asset investors urgently need stronger protections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/new-york-attorney-general-urges-congress-bolster-crypto-regulations-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PSB5YIALJII5CKXLSPLH6CN2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌降低面向美国联邦机构的商业软件价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌将为美国联邦机构提供商业应用软件套餐的大幅折扣，该公司希望利用特朗普政府削减成本的推动力，削弱微软长期以来对政府软件市场的控制。【原文：Google will offer steep discounts to U.S. federal agencies for its business apps package as the company looks to capitalize on the Trump administration's cost-cutting push and chip away at Microsoft's longstanding grip on the government software market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-slashes-business-software-prices-us-federal-agencies-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7ZCDJ7B7ZOSBEYSZQRQEO425Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥银行美国关税可能对通胀两端造成压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥银行五位董事会成员中的大多数都认为，与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税相关的风险将对墨西哥通胀产生向上和向下的压力。【原文：Most of the Bank of Mexico's five governing board members agreed that the risks associated with U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs will exert both upward and downward pressures on Mexican inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-mexico-us-tariffs-may-exert-pressure-both-ends-inflation-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBNITINWAFNK3JC3JXSDDXZKLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:50:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司在印度寻找勘探机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）勘探与生产主管西尔维娅-多斯安若斯（Sylvia dos Anjos）周四表示，该公司正在权衡今年将在印度举行的石油区块拍卖所带来的机遇。【原文：Brazil's Petrobras is weighing opportunities from an oil block auction set to take place this year in India, said the state-run oil firm's head of exploration and production, Sylvia dos Anjos, on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazils-petrobras-eyes-exploration-opportunities-india-2025-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BL6OYPL34NJ5JKYM356UGCR4EM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>