<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:46:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:46:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月就业增长放缓；失业率稳定在 4.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[在关税不确定性的影响下，美国 5 月份的就业增长放缓，失业率稳定在 4.2%，这有可能使美联储推迟一段时间恢复降息。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed in May amid headwinds from tariff uncertainty, while the unemployment rate held steady at 4.2%, potentially giving the Federal Reserve cover to delay resuming interest rate cuts for a while.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-job-growth-slows-may-unemployment-rate-steady-42-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YI2I47LBWZMPRIDWQQ6J2RIW5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国法官警告：律师引用人工智能假案将面临制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦高等法院周五警告说，使用人工智能引用不存在的案例的律师可能会被认定为藐视法庭，甚至面临刑事指控，这是生成式人工智能将律师引入歧途的最新例证。【原文：Lawyers who use artificial intelligence to cite non-existent cases can be held in contempt of court or even face criminal charges, London's High Court warned on Friday, in the latest example of generative AI leading lawyers astray.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/lawyers-face-sanctions-citing-fake-cases-with-ai-warns-uk-judge-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TX6G73LVZKWRKEVDMHOMJBUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行决策者讨论通胀过低风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）的政策制定者们周五欢呼战胜了通胀失控的局面，尽管有些人警告说，现在的通胀率有可能过低，这让人再次回忆起 "大流行病 "爆发前十年的低迷物价增长势头。【原文：European Central Bank policymakers hailed victory over runaway inflation on Friday even as some warned that it was now at risk of going too low, rekindling memories of anaemic price growth in the pre-pandemic decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ecb-policymakers-debate-risk-inflation-going-too-low-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73U6XF42FNIGHPEBQOCW4SY2BY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:14:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，马斯克的 xAI 公司预计到 2029 年年收入将超过 130 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，根据这家人工智能初创公司的银行家摩根士丹利披露的数据，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的xAI公司预计到2029年的年收入将超过130亿美元。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk's xAI expects to generate more than $13 billion in annual earnings by 2029, according to numbers revealed by the artificial intelligence startup's banker Morgan Stanley , Bloomberg News reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-xai-expects-annual-earnings-over-13-billion-by-2029-bloomberg-reports-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJKPO5NIIFIIJKCPYOVSNPBIUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国将终止对散户投资者购买加密货币交易所交易票据的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融监管机构将取消对消费者购买加密货币交易所交易票据（ETNs）的禁令，放弃此前希望不让散户投资者购买的立场。【原文：Britain's financial regulator is to remove a ban on consumers buying crypto exchange-traded notes (ETNs), ditching its previous position of wanting to keep them out of the hands of retail investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/embargoed-uk-end-ban-retail-investors-buying-crypto-exchange-traded-notes-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXUTXBBWV5JXTE2XKLZ7XIC3XM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易政策担忧导致美国股票基金资金流出，欧洲央行降息前欧洲股票基金吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至6月4日，美国股票基金连续第三周出现资金外流，原因是对美国贸易政策不确定性的担忧挥之不去，而投资者在周五即将公布的关键就业报告前保持谨慎。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw outflows for a third straight week through June 4, as concerns lingered over uncertainty surrounding U.S. trade policies, while investors remained cautious ahead of a key jobs report due Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJBA5WOTXZIKJP65QG5DAXBVVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标特朗普与马斯克的争吵硝烟弥漫]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RR3GCIFWIZJ7JMYG7DFXJUSMFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:17:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲杯门票销售大增，曼联提高盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[曼联周五上调了年度核心利润预期，原因是俱乐部在欧洲杯上的强劲表现带动了门票销售和转播收入。【原文：Manchester United raised their annual core profit forecast on Friday as the club's strong performance in the Europa League drove ticket sales and broadcast revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/manchester-united-boost-profit-forecast-after-europa-league-run-lifts-ticket-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMZVMEUDFJPI5OOJVDJ5D4DB24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟对在贸易谈判中降低美国化肥关税持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟农业委员克里斯托夫-汉森（Christophe Hansen）告诉路透社，欧盟愿意在与特朗普政府的贸易谈判中降低美国进口化肥的关税，但不会为达成协议而削弱其食品安全标准。【原文：The European Union is open to lowering tariffs on U.S. fertiliser imports as an offer in trade talks with the Trump administration, but will not weaken its food safety standards in pursuit of a deal, EU agriculture commissioner Christophe Hansen told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-open-lowering-tariffs-us-fertilisers-trade-talks-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITLL3H7XGRMRHFGXSXQ2S22JLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 新任首席执行官 Filosa 年收入将高达 2300 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份文件显示，Stellantis 公司新任首席执行官安东尼奥-菲洛萨（Antonio Filosa）在执掌公司的头两年将获得至少 400 万美元的年薪，从 2028 年起，包括奖金在内的年薪将增至 2300 万美元，但他的薪酬将低于前任卡洛斯-塔瓦雷斯（Carlos Tavares）。【原文：Stellantis' new CEO Antonio Filosa will earn at least $4 million annually in his first two years at the helm, rising to up to $23 million a year from 2028, including bonuses, a document showed, although his remuneration will be lower than predecessor Carlos Tavares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/stellantis-new-ceo-filosa-set-earn-up-23-million-year-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIQH4DSSZZI7BHTFTF3SZKOB4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:44:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑜伽服公司警告关税将削弱利润，Lululemon 股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lululemon Athletica 的股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌了 21%，这家高端紧身裤制造商警告称，与关税相关的成本以及北美和中国等主要市场的不均衡需求将影响其今年的利润。【原文：Lululemon Athletica's shares fell 21% in premarket trading on Friday, as the maker of high-end leggings warned that tariff-related costs and uneven demand in key markets of North America and China will dent its profits this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lululemon-shares-tumble-yogawear-firm-warns-tariffs-will-crimp-profit-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UKV5ZX2TOBJPFPBUOPTFH7W32Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业数据公布前，华尔街期货走高；特斯拉反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在投资者等待月度就业数据之际，美国股指期货上扬，而特斯拉股价则因首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）之间的紧张关系出现降温迹象而反弹。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged up on Friday as investors awaited monthly payrolls data, while Tesla shares rebounded on signs of cooling tensions between CEO Elon Musk and U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/wall-street-futures-edge-up-ahead-jobs-data-tesla-rebounds-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOREDSM32ZP7JFIHENZL2LAHAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉亏损 3800 亿美元，创 2025 年顶级公司最大亏损纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于电动汽车需求下降、首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）与极右翼组织的关系引发政治争议，以及现在他与唐纳德-特朗普总统的公开不和，特斯拉成为今年表现最差的大盘股。【原文：Tesla is the worst-performing large-cap stock this year, thanks to declining electric vehicle demand, Chief Executive Elon Musk's political controversies over his ties to far-right groups, and now, his public feud with President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-markets-marketcap-pix-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIXMR2YB2FKY7AMHZKCABVTRII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Miniso 集团考虑分拆流行玩具业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miniso 集团周五表示，正在对其流行玩具业务 "TOP TOY "分拆上市的可能性进行初步评估。【原文：Miniso Group said on Friday it was making a preliminary assessment of a potential spin-off listing of its pop toy business operating under the brand, "TOP TOY".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/miniso-group-mulls-spin-off-its-pop-toy-business-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXB7ZC2RRNMV3FXHVV5HMZNIH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:11:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 通胀数据、政策进展成焦点，美股屡创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市的反弹已将主要股指推向创纪录水平的边缘，新的经济数据以及贸易和财政政策的发展将考验股市在短期内是否会再创新高。【原文：The U.S. stock rebound has driven key indexes to the cusp of record levels, with fresh economic data and trade and fiscal policy developments set to test whether equities will get an extra push higher in the near term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-us-stocks-edge-toward-records-with-inflation-data-policy-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCCDB32FZFMAHCGSTUU6BZXWNE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[稳定币迈向主流可能撼动部分美国国债市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着稳定币一步步成为主流，美国国债市场的某些部分，尤其是短期到期的证券，可能会因为与加密货币世界的联系更加紧密而容易受到波动的影响。【原文：As stablecoins take a step toward becoming mainstream, some segments of the U.S. Treasury market, notably securities with short-term maturities, could be vulnerable to volatility as they become more closely tied to the world of cryptocurrency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stablecoins-step-toward-mainstream-could-shake-up-parts-us-treasury-market-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2B4BBQDW7NKUVDEISV5YSIDFHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+增加产量，美国轻质甜原油需求下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+"供应量的增加和全球新石油流的上线，增加了欧洲和亚洲炼油厂的选择，并抑制了对美国轻质甜原油的出口需求，从而导致美国主要产油区的油价下跌。【原文：Rising OPEC+ supplies and new streams of oil coming online globally are increasing options for European and Asian refiners and weighing on export demand for light sweet U.S. crude, contributing to lower prices in the country's main oil-producing regions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/demand-us-light-sweet-crude-drops-opec-ramps-up-output-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4D672FKMCBMJRD5GMR52YLQZWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克与特朗普争吵后，特斯拉卖空者获利约 40 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）之间的公开争吵导致特斯拉股价创下有史以来最大单日跌幅后，交易商周四从特斯拉股票空头头寸中获利 40 亿美元。【原文：Traders raked in $4 billion in profit from their short positions in Tesla shares on Thursday after a public feud between President Donald Trump and CEO Elon Musk led to the stock's biggest single-day drop ever.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-short-sellers-pocket-about-4-billion-profits-after-musk-trump-spat-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5PRWVUJBBL7JBGK4U2LJ3ENTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国默茨公司希望在特朗普会谈后建立汽车关税抵消机制]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希-默茨（Friedrich Merz）周五表示，他将寻求达成一项协议，即美国汽车可以免税进口到欧洲，以换取同样数量的出口到美国的汽车的关税减免。【原文：German Chancellor Friedrich Merz said on Friday that he would pursue a deal under which U.S. cars could be imported into Europe duty free in exchange for tariff waivers on the same number of vehicles exported to the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/germanys-merz-eyes-car-tariff-offsetting-mechanism-after-trump-talks-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOZOID5IXRNYTPMJX3KGBZVQMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博通股价下跌，原因是营收预期不尽如人意]]></title><description><![CDATA[博通（Broadcom）股价在周五的盘前交易中下跌近 4%，此前该公司的第三季度营收预期未能打动在人工智能热潮中极度看好芯片股的投资者。【原文：Broadcom shares fell nearly 4% in premarket trading on Friday, after the company's third-quarter revenue forecast failed to impress investors who have been extremely bullish on chip stocks amid an artificial intelligence boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/broadcom-shares-drop-revenue-forecast-fails-impress-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5WMP2F7NJPPRPNUJPPG4I6RBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，马斯克的 "星链 "公司从印度电信部获得关键许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周五告诉路透社，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的Starlink公司已获得印度电信部颁发的关键许可证，为这家卫星供应商扫清了一大障碍，使其离在印度开展商业运营更近了一步。【原文：Elon Musk's Starlink has received a key licence from India's telecoms ministry, sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters on Friday, clearing a major hurdle for the satellite provider and taking it closer to launching commercial operations in India.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/musks-starlink-gets-key-india-licence-telecoms-ministry-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CDCX2SMGRKMPCLYIRLBQKSTZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士法郎走强为何可能导致其重回负利率水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士可能成为首个恢复负利率以应对货币飙升和物价下跌的大型经济体，这凸显出在全球贸易战持续发酵的背景下，央行可能很快就会耗尽常规政策工具。【原文：Switzerland could be the first big economy to return to negative interest rates to fight a surging currency and falling prices, highlighting how quickly central bankers may be running out of conventional policy tools as a global trade war rages on.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/why-switzerlands-strong-franc-could-lead-it-back-negative-interest-rates-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2E56BFSLBKZ7M2HYMUDOXVCYQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:28:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙对委内瑞拉石油的进口在美国制裁截止日期前枯竭]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府设定的关键制裁期限之前，西班牙在四月份没有从委内瑞拉进口原油。【原文：Spain didn't import crude oil from Venezuela in April, ahead of a key sanctions deadline set by U.S. President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/spains-imports-venezuelan-oil-dry-up-ahead-us-sanctions-deadline-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUACRVF43VNELN2RZA5KB7SN6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:20:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五月份世界粮食价格下降，谷物、糖和蔬菜价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国粮食及农业组织周五表示，受谷物、糖和植物油价格明显下跌的影响，5月份全球粮食商品价格有所下降。【原文：Global food commodity prices declined in May, driven by marked drops in cereal, sugar, and vegetable oil prices, the United Nations' Food and Agriculture Organization said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-food-prices-dip-may-cereal-sugar-vegoils-drop-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKEXRDVN5FMILIUZ4ECNFLZFGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国稀土武器改变贸易战战场轮廓]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周争夺稀土出口许可证的行为表明，中国已设计出一种更好、目标更明确的贸易战武器。【原文：The scramble in recent weeks to secure export licences for rare earths shows China has devised a better, more precisely targeted weapon for trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-rare-earth-weapon-changes-contours-trade-war-battlefield-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDPXHLODGNJQTOC3IC5HOSZIBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本前最高外汇外交官预计年底前日元将升至140附近]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本前最高货币外交官周五表示，美日利率差距的缩小，而不是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普削弱美元的任何努力，将有可能使日元兑美元汇率在年底前升至135-140左右。【原文：A narrowing U.S.-Japan interest rate gap, rather than any effort by President Donald Trump to weaken the dollar, will likely lift the yen to around 135-140 against the U.S. unit by year-end, Japan's former top currency diplomat said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-ex-top-fx-diplomat-expects-yen-rise-near-140-by-year-end-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3E72A3WT5J55DGGCTYK7J6C4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市迎来 15 个月来最大单月外资流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份，亚洲股市吸引了强劲的外资流入，因为市场对美国提高关税会对经济造成直接冲击的担忧有所缓解，这促使此前退出该地区大额集中头寸的投资者回流。【原文：Asian equities attracted strong foreign inflows in May as concerns over an immediate economic hit from higher U.S. tariffs eased, prompting a return by investors who had previously exited large and concentrated positions in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/asian-equities-see-largest-monthly-foreign-inflow-15-months-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57BEN2J3M5IWFNPMX4UX3YSNOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卫星公司 SES 聘用航空业资深人士担任新任财务总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲卫星公司 SES 周五表示，已任命 Elisabeth Pataki 为新任财务总监。【原文：SES has appointed Elisabeth Pataki as its new finance chief, the European satellite company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/satellite-firm-ses-taps-aerospace-veteran-new-finance-chief-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5L2UVTNNDBJMHIPRRSTDJ67VKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪将日产企业家族评级下调至 Ba2]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构穆迪（Moody's）周五将日产汽车公司的企业家族评级从Ba1下调至Ba2，这家陷入困境的日本汽车制造商正努力推动扭亏为盈。【原文：Global ratings agency Moody's on Friday cut Nissan Motor Co Ltd's corporate family rating to Ba2 from Ba1, as the embattled Japanese automaker seeks to push through a turnaround.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/moodys-cuts-nissan-corporate-family-rating-ba2-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLQMORM4J5OV7CAOYF5CN3QNUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:21:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政治报》报道马斯克与白宫将举行电话会议，特斯拉股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周五，在法兰克福上市的特斯拉股票上涨了 5.6%，此前 Politico 报道称，白宫助手已安排与首席执行官埃隆-马斯克通话，以便在与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普公开交恶后促成和平。【原文：Tesla shares listed in Frankfurt rose 5.6% on Friday after Politico reported White House aides have scheduled a call with CEO Elon Musk to broker peace after a public feud with U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-shares-rise-politico-reports-musk-white-house-hold-call-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN46NHYPEZNLLFBTYPKQSFKW4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>