<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:47:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:47:24 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[德国经济部长称欧洲准备就可能的贸易限制采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国经济部长罗伯特-哈贝克（Robert Habeck）周一在与行业游说团体和欧盟最高贸易代表就美国的关税威胁进行讨论后表示，欧洲已准备好采取行动应对可能出现的贸易限制。【原文：Europe is prepared to act in response to possible restrictions to trade, German Economy Minister Robert Habeck said on Monday, after holding discussions with industry lobbies and the EU's top trade representative about the threat of tariffs from the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-economy-minister-says-europe-prepared-act-possible-trade-restrictions-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGZRE6CLJVNMZPNFZSJ3NZP664</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯悦将以 26 亿美元收购普拉亚酒店集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯悦酒店集团（Hyatt Hotels）周一表示，将以约 26 亿美元（含债务）（扣除现金）的价格收购 Playa Hotels &amp; Resorts，以扩大其在墨西哥和加勒比海地区的业务。【原文：Hyatt Hotels will buy Playa Hotels &amp; Resorts for about $2.6 billion including debt, net of cash, the company said on Monday, seeking to expand its presence in Mexico and the Caribbean.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hyatt-acquire-playa-hotels-26-billion-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22HKDIS3EFPMXOJSSOEDFZT4HA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国比亚迪将销售 21 款搭载 "上帝之眼 "智能驾驶技术的车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪周一表示，计划开始销售 21 款配备 "天眼 "高级驾驶辅助系统（ADAS）的车型，这将加剧智能电动汽车市场的竞争。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle giant BYD plans to begin sales of 21 models equipped with its "God's Eye" advanced driver-assistance system (ADAS), it said on Monday, intensifying competition in the smart electric vehicle market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-byd-sell-21-models-with-its-gods-eye-smart-driving-tech-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XK5KTUFDVFIJNJ76H55DHYB4EQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:14:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊北卡罗来纳州仓库面临工会投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，北卡罗来纳州罗利郊区一家仓库的工人们将决定是否要与这家零售巨头进行集体谈判，亚马逊正面临几个月来的第二次工人工会投票。【原文：Amazon is facing its second workers’ union vote in as many months as laborers at a warehouse in suburban Raleigh, North Carolina, decide this week whether they wish to collectively bargain with the retail giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-faces-union-vote-north-carolina-warehouse-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CKGETYHXSVIEBHPXD3F732K7FA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普升级关税后，亚洲和欧盟钢铁制造商股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将在数小时内对所有进口钢铁和铝征收25%的关税后，欧洲和亚洲钢铁制造商的股票下跌。【原文：Shares in European and Asian steelmakers fell on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would introduce 25% tariffs on all steel and aluminium imports within hours in addition to existing metals duties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asian-eu-steelmakers-shares-fall-after-trump-escalates-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HBHUDJ3PJKLXO672LFJ2EGVDU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:08:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳美国销售额创近五年来最大跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦当劳周一公布的美国季度可比销售额降幅超过预期，原因是短暂的大肠杆菌疫情导致需求下降，而食客们仍在谨慎消费。【原文：McDonald's posted a steeper-than-expected drop in quarterly U.S. comparable sales on Monday, as demand took a hit from a brief E.coli outbreak while diners remained watchful of their spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mcdonalds-posts-biggest-us-sales-decline-nearly-five-years-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SHSJLLPMNMHRJX5S2DL4XL6IA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其 Europower Enerji 正在与潜在买家谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其能源设备制造商 Europower Enerji 公司董事长 Behic Harmanli 告诉路透社，该公司正在与来自美国、欧洲和亚洲的潜在买家讨论收购或合作事宜。【原文：Turkish energy equipment manufacturer Europower Enerji is in discussion with potential buyers from the United States, Europe and Asia over an acquisition or partnership, company Chairman Behic Harmanli told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/turkeys-europower-enerji-talks-with-potential-buyers-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZGKBPAHGFOCXJ43ZRZ7ZAJMNY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：加拿大的 Shopify 如何编织人工智能 "魔法 "吸引商家]]></title><description><![CDATA[希瑟-佩里（Heather Perry）在去年的假期高峰前下了一个大胆的赌注：将她的家族烘焙店Klatch Coffee的所有电子商务业务转到Shopify上。【原文：Heather Perry made a bold bet before last year's holiday rush: switch all e-commerce operations of her family-owned roastery, Klatch Coffee, to Shopify.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/how-canadas-shopify-is-weaving-ai-magic-pull-merchants-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLEDNGG7N5PCZIH4253PHTN23Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 11:23:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥银行行长称抗击通胀进入新阶段]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥银行行长告诉路透社记者，墨西哥的通胀环境预计将允许决策者继续下调基准利率，因为降低通胀的斗争已经进入了一个新阶段。【原文：Mexico's inflationary environment is expected to allow policymakers to keep cutting the benchmark interest rate, the head of the Bank of Mexico told Reuters, as the fight to bring down inflation has entered a new phase.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-mexicos-governor-says-inflation-fight-enters-new-phase-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54GFKY4WPBIALDGWG2UXXESGRE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 11:12:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官将审查特朗普向政府工作人员提出的买断方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普推进史无前例的解散政府机构和裁减联邦工作人员的努力之际，一名美国法官将于周一考虑唐纳德-特朗普总统向两百万联邦工作人员提出的买断方案的命运。【原文：A U.S. judge will consider on Monday the fate of President Donald Trump's buyout offer to two million federal workers as Trump presses ahead with an unprecedented effort to dismantle government agencies and downsize the federal workforce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/judge-review-trumps-buyout-offer-government-workers-cfpb-hq-shuttered-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4LI2YFR4JM3XPORBZJYOBAYII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 11:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉机器人轴将于六月问世？马斯克向德克萨斯州寻求放手监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）在 1 月底告诉投资者，特斯拉将于 6 月在德克萨斯州奥斯汀市推出 "自动驾驶打车赚钱 "服务，该州对特斯拉几乎没有任何监管，这不禁让人怀疑特斯拉在公共街道上部署未经验证的无人驾驶技术时，愿意承担多大的安全和法律风险。【原文：Elon Musk told investors in late January that Tesla would roll out “autonomous ride-hailing for money” by June in Austin, Texas — a state where the company faces almost no regulation, raising questions about how much safety and legal risk Tesla is willing to take on as it deploys unproven driverless technology on public streets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tesla-robotaxis-by-june-musk-turns-texas-hands-off-regulation-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH6WT5X2BFI4XPHHDB2BM3DWD4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 11:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Rivian 向所有车队开放商用车销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[这家电动汽车制造商周一表示，在结束与股东亚马逊（Amazon）的独家协议一年多之后，Rivian 将向美国各种规模的车队开放其送货货车的销售。【原文：Rivian is opening up sales of its delivery vans to fleets of all sizes in the United States, the electric vehicle maker said on Monday, more than a year after ending its exclusive deal with shareholder Amazon .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-rivian-opens-up-commercial-van-sales-all-fleet-sizes-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42BYYLDDD5OSRKZC46VR2PXTHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 11:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税迫在眉睫，一家美国制造商疯狂北上]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周一清晨，斯蒂芬-布洛克位于北卡罗来纳州的小工厂的电话响了，多伦多的经销商发来了一条紧急信息，美加贸易战似乎一触即发。【原文：Stephen Bullock’s phone rang early Monday morning last week at his small factory in North Carolina with an urgent message from his distributor up in Toronto who was rattled by what looked like an unfolding U.S.-Canada trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/looming-tariffs-turned-into-mad-dash-north-one-us-manufacturer-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WTO4USPEBNE7KVJUZCC6SPLQQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 11:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道OpenAI 将于今年完成首款定制芯片设计]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 正在推进其计划，通过开发第一代内部人工智能芯片，减少对英伟达（Nvidia）芯片供应的依赖。【原文：OpenAI is pushing ahead on its plan to reduce its reliance on Nvidia for its chip supply by developing its first generation of in-house artificial-intelligence silicon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-set-finalize-first-custom-chip-design-this-year-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKBHHHU3VNNDDCO6YBSABMUBJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 11:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税之痛？铜博士现在就来]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿曼达-库珀（Amanda Cooper）对美国和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by Amanda Cooper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYBU72UOORLTHDXLJVXXSBZTVI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 10:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度石油公司就购买美国液化天然气供应进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度石油部长潘卡杰-贾因（Pankaj Jain）周一表示，受特朗普政府取消新项目出口许可禁令的影响，印度石油公司正在寻求购买美国液化天然气（LNG）。【原文：Indian oil companies are looking to buy U.S. liquefied natural gas (LNG), buoyed by the Trump administration's lifting of a ban on export permits for new projects, Oil Secretary Pankaj Jain said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/indian-oil-companies-talks-buy-us-lng-supplies-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDIUFKEWVFJYLNQHBW3BAGHJHU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 10:53:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场摆脱特朗普的最新关税威胁，期货上涨；钢铁制造商跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将对进口钢铁和铝征收额外关税后，钢铁制造商领涨美国股指期货。【原文：U.S. stock index futures ticked up on Monday, recovering some losses after the last session, with steelmakers leading the gains after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would impose additional tariffs on steel and aluminum imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-rise-markets-shrug-off-trumps-latest-tariff-threat-steelmakers-jump-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JQNMBBHZ5J5FN5TU3H7THU5HU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 10:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：特朗普领导下的美国证券交易委员会开始转变工作重心，裁员威胁令员工感到恐慌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普政府向所有联邦雇员发出辞职信的第二天，美国证券交易委员会的代理主席马克-尤耶达（Mark Uyeda）在其华盛顿总部一个座无虚席的礼堂里向员工发表了讲话。【原文：A day after the Trump administration sent a missive to all federal employees inviting them to resign, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's acting boss, Mark Uyeda, addressed staff in a packed auditorium at its Washington headquarters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-sec-starts-shifting-agencys-focus-job-cut-threat-spooks-staff-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EO4D6PZFJKKVK73M5B3XEZUXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 10:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长德金多斯：特朗普关税引发经济不确定性，对通胀影响尚不明确]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行副行长路易斯-德金多斯（Luis de Guindos）周一表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布的贸易关税可能会引发经济不确定性，但对通胀的影响还不太明确。【原文：Trade tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump could trigger economic uncertainty but the impact on inflation is less clear, European Central Bank Vice President Luis de Guindos said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/trumps-tariffs-spur-economic-uncertainty-impact-inflation-less-clear-ecbs-de-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXXPZVFKRJJC5GS3ERISMHUUZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 09:39:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产如何失去与本田平起平坐的地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉日产汽车公司想法的人士透露，在与同城竞争对手本田汽车的合并谈判破裂后，日产汽车公司愿意与新的合作伙伴合作，甚至包括技术公司。【原文：Japan's Nissan Motor is open to working with new partners including even technology firms after merger talks with cross-town rival Honda Motor foundered, people familiar with the automaker's thinking have said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/how-nissan-lost-its-status-honda-equal-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37S7PWX4ENOWTMQ2I4NET2QANU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:59:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司表示在印度建立组装线之前需要更多订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周一表示，在考虑在印度建立民用飞机总装线之前，它需要更多来自印度的订单，这可能会给印度政府希望这家美国飞机制造商在该国组装商用喷气式飞机的愿望泼上一盆冷水。【原文：Boeing signalled on Monday it would need more orders from India before it considers setting up a final civil aircraft assembly line in the country, potentially throwing cold water on the government's hopes of the U.S. planemaker assembling commercial jets in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-signals-more-orders-needed-before-setting-up-assembly-line-india-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H746SH7ESFNRDHSUQVDIZCLE74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:56:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普终止出口许可禁令，印度天然气公司重启购买美国液化天然气计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度天然气公司（GAIL India Ltd）董事长桑迪普-库马尔-古普塔（Sandeep Kumar Gupta）表示，在特朗普政府取消新项目出口许可禁令后，该公司将寻求购买美国一家液化天然气工厂的股份，或确保美国液化天然气的长期供应。【原文：GAIL India Ltd will seek to buy a stake in a U.S. liquefied natural gas plant or secure long-term U.S. LNG supply after the Trump administration lifted a ban on export permits for new projects, chairman Sandeep Kumar Gupta said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/indias-gail-revives-plan-buy-us-lng-trump-ends-ban-export-permits-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPTTVRDTAJLX7FCVDR2PMIG2TA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃利奥特增持股份后，英国石油公司股价创八月以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社援引消息人士的话报道埃利奥特管理公司（Elliott Management）已增持英国石油公司股票后，英国石油公司股价在周一早盘交易中最多上涨了 7%，达到 8 月份以来的最高点。【原文：Shares in oil major BP rose as much as 7% to their highest since August in early trade on Monday after Reuters reported Elliott Management had built a stake in the company, citing a source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bp-shares-hit-highest-since-august-after-elliott-builds-stake-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R453VW77MVONVL4U5N5ANXH44I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:20:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收关税，德国钢铁制造商股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示将对所有进口钢铁和铝征收 25% 的新关税后，德国钢铁制造商蒂森克虏伯（Thyssenkrupp）和萨尔茨吉特（Salzgitter）的股票下跌。【原文：Shares in German steelmakers Thyssenkrupp and Salzgitter are down after U.S. President Donald Trump said he would slap new tariffs of 25% on all steel and aluminium imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-steelmakers-tumble-trump-threatens-tariffs-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCGKVRO2Z5PFLPCTHJPRZ6HF7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 08:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子投资者德卡将投票反对吉姆-哈格曼-斯纳布担任董事长]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子股东德卡投资公司（Deka Investment）周一表示，将投票反对吉姆-哈格曼-斯纳布（Jim Hagemann Snabe）连任这家德国工程集团的董事长。【原文：Siemens shareholder Deka Investment will vote against the reelection of Jim Hagemann Snabe as chairman at the German engineering group, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siemens-investor-deka-vote-against-jim-hagemann-snabe-chairman-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTUX4Q7GDJJJFLY7VRMEAJAPPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 07:53:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康 1 月份营收同比增长 3.16%，第一季度增长强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约电子制造商、苹果公司最大的 iPhone 组装商台湾富士康周一发布报告称，其 1 月份收入同比增长 3.16%。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker and Apple's biggest iPhone assembler, reported on Monday that its January revenue rose 3.16% on year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-january-revenue-up-316-yy-sees-strong-growth-q1-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSEIFUW4CNL4RFBSNF6K4NBW3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 07:51:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受 1 月地震影响，台积电第一季度营收接近预期下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的合约芯片制造商台积电周一表示，其第一季度营收将接近预期目标的下限，因为该公司预计 1 月份震撼该岛的地震将带来 1.61 亿美元的影响。【原文：TSMC , the world's biggest contract chipmaker, said on Monday its first-quarter revenue would be closer to the lower end of its guidance, as it expects a $161 million impact from an earthquake that rocked the island in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-sees-q1-revenue-near-lower-end-guidance-january-earthquake-impact-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RL3ZGZ46ZLFVLM4N7FVEAVCKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 07:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对钢铁和铝征收关税令金属生产商感到不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）计划对所有进口到美国的钢材和铝材征收 25% 的新关税，这可能会扰乱金属贸易流动，从而在周一对亚洲生产商的股价造成影响。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's plan to impose new 25% tariffs on all imports of steel and aluminium into the United States weighed on shares of producers in Asia on Monday as it threatened to disrupt trade flows in the metals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trumps-steel-aluminium-tariffs-rattle-makers-metals-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ND7KAGLEIJLYTK24MRBCSB755I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本资生堂称中国市场销售低迷导致年度利润骤降 73]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本化妆品巨头资生堂周一表示，由于中国市场销售低迷，其全年利润下降了 73%。【原文：Japanese cosmetics giant Shiseido said on Monday its full-year profit fell 73% amid sluggish sales in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/japans-shiseido-says-profit-plunges-73-amid-sluggish-sales-china-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7HK25R7MFMXLCMQKHFK4BF3VI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁拥有美国的债务？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府发行了近 36 万亿美元的债务，其债券是全球金融体系的基石。【原文：The U.S. government has nearly $36 trillion of debt on issue and its bonds are the bedrock of the global financial system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/who-owns-us-debt-2025-02-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LP3K5BMCTBJJBMFEBO5D23LGGY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>