<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:35:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:35:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[关税休战支撑市场情绪，亚洲股市多数走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[受全球最大的两个经济体延长关税休战期的影响，周二亚洲股市多数上涨，而日本股市在结束长周末假期后，受科技股推动创下历史新高。【原文：Most Asian stocks rose on Tuesday, buoyed by an extension of a tariff truce between the world's two largest economies, while Japanese shares hit an all-time peak, powered by tech shares after returning from a long weekend break.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4X6SVXNPXVNLDMNZCUVDIJ5G5A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:55:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元在通胀数据公布前保持涨势；澳元等待澳大利亚央行公布数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周二持稳，市场正在为当天晚些时候的一份关键消费者通胀报告做准备，该报告可能会影响美联储的降息预期。【原文：The U.S. dollar held steady on Tuesday, with markets braced for a key consumer inflation report later in the day that could shape expectations for Federal Reserve interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-holds-gains-ahead-inflation-data-aussie-awaits-rba-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5FNPZE5WFP4HLRSODC3P5OHII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚经济活动保持稳定，商业景气有所好转]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项调查显示，得益于服务业和建筑业的强劲表现，7 月份澳大利亚商业信心指数升至三年来的最高点，尽管成本上升也给零售价格带来了上涨压力。【原文：A measure of Australian business confidence rose to a three-year high in July thanks to strength in services and construction, a survey showed on Tuesday, though rising costs also put upward pressure on retail prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-business-mood-brightens-activity-holds-up-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VJZX642DNVOCVDNTA4NIT5MQBM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克指责苹果违反反垄断法，称 xAI 将采取法律行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周一表示，苹果公司涉嫌违反反垄断法，让除OpenAI之外的任何人工智能公司都无法在其应用商店排名中位居第一，称这是 "明确的反垄断违法行为"。【原文：Elon Musk said on Monday Apple is engaging in antitrust violations by allegedly making it impossible for any artificial intelligence company other than OpenAI to reach the No. 1 spot in its App Store rankings, calling it an "unequivocal antitrust violation."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/musk-accuses-apple-antitrust-violation-says-xai-will-take-legal-action-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVRFGJ4MHNJONOXD7OOKD6JOPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美关税暂停期延长提振贸易希望，石油上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周二上涨，原因是美国和中国延长了提高关税的暂停期，缓解了贸易战升级将扰乱两国经济并抑制全球两大石油消费国燃料需求的担忧。【原文：Oil prices rose on Tuesday as the United States and China extended a pause on higher tariffs, easing concerns an escalation of their trade war would disrupt their economies and crimp fuel demand in the world's two largest oil consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-gains-us-china-tariff-pause-extension-boosts-trade-hopes-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQ2V2KHIO5PW3IYHPHZK5CW3KM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[风险投资公司 Speciale Invest 将在 2029 年前出资 6900 万美元支持印度初创企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度 Speciale Invest 风险投资公司周二表示，该公司将在未来四年内投资 60 亿卢比（约合 6900 万美元）给处于早期阶段的初创企业，投资领域包括人工智能和空间技术。【原文：India's Speciale Invest will invest 6 billion rupees ($69 million) over the next four years in early-stage startups spanning across sectors including artificial intelligence and space technology, the venture capital company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/venture-capital-firm-speciale-invest-back-indian-startups-with-69-million-by-2025-08-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4SB4BYI3RO2NOUEYNI3K7YI4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《非洲金融报》报道，星空娱乐公司重启出售布里斯班度假村 50% 股份的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《澳大利亚金融评论报》（Australian Financial Review）周二报道，澳大利亚明星娱乐公司（Star Entertainment）已重启出售其在布里斯班度假村 36 亿澳元（23.5 亿美元）50% 权益的努力，并与香港投资者达成协议。【原文：Australia's Star Entertainment has restarted efforts to sell its 50% interest in the A$3.6 billion ($2.35 billion) Brisbane resort, striking an agreement with its Hong Kong-based investors, the Australian Financial Review reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/star-entertainment-revives-bid-sell-50-stake-brisbane-resort-afr-reports-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAJJOM6DWZLUBCZPVL52BBZ5SI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:39:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立法者和专家称，特朗普与英伟达的不寻常交易引发了新的企业和国家安全风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）与英伟达（Nvidia）达成协议，让美国政府从其销售额中提成，以换取英伟达恢复向中国出口被禁的人工智能芯片，这颠覆了美国数十年来的国家安全政策，创造了一种全新的企业风险。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump upended decades of U.S. national security policy, creating an entirely new category of corporate risk, when he made a deal with Nvidia to give the U.S. government a cut of its sales in exchange for resuming exports of banned AI chips to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trumps-unusual-nvidia-deal-raises-new-corporate-national-security-risks-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3I3FDOBK7NNXXEC3R5FJE576OE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:26:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普选择传统基金会的安东尼领导劳工统计局]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他将提名经济学家E.J. Antoni担任新一任美国劳工统计局局长。此前十天，美国劳工统计局前任局长因美国就业市场表现不佳而被解雇，特朗普在没有证据的情况下指责安东尼操纵数据。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said he was nominating economist E.J. Antoni as the new Bureau of Labor Statistics commissioner, ten days after firing the statistics agency's previous leader after a weak scorecard of the U.S. job market, accusing her without evidence of manipulating the figures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-selects-heritage-foundations-antoni-head-bureau-labor-statistics-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLTPG2NK3FJPTOATYME6YYL7WA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 22:53:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西化妆品制造商 Natura 第二季度扭亏为盈]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西化妆品制造商 Natura 周一公布，第二季度净利润为 1.95 亿雷亚尔（合 3580 万美元），扭转了去年同期净亏损 8.59 亿雷亚尔的局面。【原文：Brazilian cosmetic maker Natura posted on Monday a second-quarter net profit of 195 million reais ($35.8 million), reversing a 859 million real net loss from the same period last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-cosmetic-maker-natura-swings-profit-q2-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZTDE7FGG5M43G2D762HNSGVJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 22:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，花旗首席执行官在 Banamex 股权谈判期间访问墨西哥]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道，花旗集团首席执行官简-弗雷泽（Jane Fraser）正在墨西哥城与总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）举行会谈，内容包括该银行零售部门 Banamex 可能上市的事宜。【原文：Citigroup CEO Jane Fraser is in Mexico City for talks with President Claudia Sheinbaum that include the potential public listing of the bank's retail unit Banamex, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/citi-ceo-visits-mexico-during-banamex-stake-talks-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZNWCT3VYFNKHJODJRWO7IB73M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 22:47:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州商人因涉嫌贿赂墨西哥石油公司官员被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周一宣布，两名得克萨斯州商人因涉嫌用 15 万美元和奢侈品贿赂墨西哥国家能源公司 Pemex 的官员以获得合同而被起诉。【原文：Two Texas businessmen were indicted for allegedly bribing officials at Mexico's state energy company Pemex with $150,000 and luxury items to secure contracts, the U.S. Justice Department announced on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/texas-businessmen-indicted-allegedly-bribing-officials-mexicos-pemex-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SC74XVBHIZORDGPRFYCUOWVXYQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 22:46:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辛克莱启动广播部门战略审查，考虑分拆风险投资公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[辛克莱周一表示，公司董事会已授权对公司的广播业务进行战略审查，并正在考虑将其风险投资组合分离出去，这使得公司股价在延时交易中上涨了 15%。【原文：Sinclair said on Monday its board has authorized a strategic review of the company's broadcast business and it is considering a separation of its Ventures portfolio, sending its shares up 15% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/sinclair-launches-strategic-review-broadcast-unit-weighs-spinoff-ventures-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEA5LAIGYNKGPOEDQIE2YZ4UGY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 22:03:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[化学品生产商塞拉尼斯盈利预测黯淡，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[化学品生产商塞拉尼斯周一预测第三季度利润低于预期，预计下半年大部分主要市场的需求将减弱，导致其股价在延时交易中下跌 14.6%。【原文：Chemicals maker Celanese forecast third-quarter profit below estimates on Monday, anticipating waning demand across most of its key markets in the second half of the year, sending its shares down 14.6% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chemicals-maker-celaneses-dour-profit-forecast-sends-shares-tumbling-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2JZFVFTANNHZE2ZDNJKJFIBMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Albemarle 运营主管 Netha Johnson 将离开公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的充电电池锂生产商 Albemarle 周一表示，首席运营官 Netha Johnson 将离开公司。【原文：Albemarle , the world's largest producer of lithium for rechargeable batteries, said on Monday that Chief Operating Officer Netha Johnson will leave the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/albemarle-operating-chief-netha-johnson-leave-company-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIRFRIWZSBK3LPTF5K72EIF7BI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自由互惠保险公司达成特朗普冻结以来的首个美国贿赂和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部于今年 6 月恢复执行联邦反贿赂法，这是司法部首次公开执法行动，自由互惠保险公司（Liberty Mutual）将放弃 470 万美元的利润，以了结美国对一家印度子公司的刑事贿赂调查。【原文：Liberty Mutual will give up $4.7 million in profit to settle a U.S. criminal bribery probe into an Indian subsidiary, in the Department of Justice's first public enforcement action of a federal anti-bribery law it resumed enforcing in June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/liberty-mutual-first-us-bribery-settlement-since-trump-freeze-ended-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYUNM2KC4NKEDCQU7HT2MCKSLI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西商人 Nelson Tanure 可能放弃与 Braskem 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西商人纳尔逊-塔努雷（Nelson Tanure）可能会放弃收购拉丁美洲最大石化公司 Braskem BRKM3.SA 的控股权，因为他的独家谈判窗口即将关闭，但却没有就解决与该公司有关的环境事件索赔问题达成协议。【原文：Brazilian businessman Nelson Tanure may give up on his bid to acquire a controlling stake in Latin America's largest petrochemical firm Braskem BRKM3.SA as his exclusive negotiations window nears closing without an agreement to resolve claims from an environmental incident linked to the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazilian-businessman-nelson-tanure-may-give-up-braskem-deal-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6IYRFAD5JNU3OIKHISCJ4KXYI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与英特尔首席执行官及商务部长、财政部长会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他与英特尔首席执行官陈立武、商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克和财政部长斯科特-贝森特举行了会晤。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he met with Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan, along with Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick and Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-meets-with-intel-ceo-along-with-commerce-treasury-secretaries-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVTEU5CC2ZJCJCEJU5UHA2GKRE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[机舱乘务员抗议并威胁罢工，加航薪酬谈判加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，加拿大航空公司（AC.TO）与空乘人员就工资问题的谈判愈演愈烈，随时可能爆发罢工。【原文：Hundreds of cabin crew members took their fight to major Canadian airports on Monday, picketing against unpaid labor, as talks on wages intensify between Air Canada AC.TO and its flight attendants this week ahead of a possible strike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/air-canada-pay-talks-intensify-cabin-crew-protest-threaten-strike-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWWRIK5PVRLTHOUWVREZHCMH3Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:06:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 关税、CPI紧张情绪缓和]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4EVMRI72JKBXP6KHLZFBA6LJE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部支持撤销达美航空-墨西哥航空反垄断豁免权的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周一支持交通部关于撤销达美航空公司和墨西哥航空公司合资企业反垄断豁免权的建议，该合资企业允许两家航空公司在美国-墨西哥航班的调度、定价和运力决策方面进行协调。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice on Monday backed a Department of Transportation proposal to revoke antitrust immunity for the joint venture between Delta Air Lines and Grupo Aeroméxico, which allows the two carriers to coordinate on scheduling, pricing, and capacity decisions for U.S.–Mexico flights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-justice-department-backs-plan-revoke-delta-aeromexico-antitrust-immunity-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPNP7WW2KJIVVD2RXEN6UPPC7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉：第二季度美国企业私人债务违约上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[评级机构惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周一表示，今年第二季度美国企业发行人的私人债务违约率高于第一季度。【原文：U.S. corporate issuers defaulted on privately placed debt at a higher rate in the second quarter this year than in the first quarter, ratings agency Fitch Ratings said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-corporate-defaults-private-debt-rose-q2-fitch-says-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEPZ6TZWO5JZVOFF7EYWERGT3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币执行官 Do Kwon 被控欺诈，预计将认罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的法庭记录显示，韩国加密货币企业家权斗（Do Kwon）因两款数字货币在 2022 年损失了约 400 亿美元而面临美国欺诈指控，预计他将认罪。【原文：Do Kwon, the South Korean cryptocurrency entrepreneur facing U.S. fraud charges over two digital currencies that lost an estimated $40 billion in 2022, is expected to enter a guilty plea, court records showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/crypto-exec-do-kwon-charged-with-fraud-expected-plead-guilty-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIDGL6M4FNOWXEPSJRVDWAE7HE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:22:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CBO 估计，特朗普税收与支出法将导致 1,000 万美国人失去保险]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国国会预算办公室估计，由于唐纳德-特朗普总统的税收和支出法的修改，未来十年将有1000万美国人没有保险。【原文：Ten million more Americans will be uninsured in the next decade due to changes in President Donald Trump's tax and spend law, according to an estimate by the Congressional Budget Office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/10-million-americans-will-go-uninsured-due-trump-tax-spend-law-cbo-estimates-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYKFGG4QFZO3XOF2DNR62HAPEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:48:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利 Codelco 公司 6 月份铜产量增长 17]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利铜业委员会（Cochilco）周一提供的数据显示，智利国营矿业公司 Codelco 6 月份的铜产量同比增长了 17%，攀升至 12.02 万吨。【原文：Copper production from Chilean state-run miner Codelco ticked up 17% year-over-year in June, data from copper commission Cochilco showed on Monday, climbing to 120,200 metric tons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/copper-output-chiles-codelco-climbs-17-june-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HAXUA7B3A5IAPC44SKP7LCSAL4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税：哪些措施已经生效，哪些措施可能会出台？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发起了一场全球贸易战，针对个别产品和国家征收一系列关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has launched a global trade war with an array of tariffs that target individual products and countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/trumps-tariffs-whats-effect-what-could-be-store-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YP62T77MYVKPRD66T7K7433RKU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:27:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利科德尔科公司在致命事故后撤换埃尔泰尼恩特公司经理]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利国营铜矿公司 Codelco 周一表示，作为 "双方协议 "的一部分，该公司埃尔泰尼恩特矿总经理将离职。【原文：Chilean state copper miner Codelco said on Monday that the general manager of its El Teniente mine, where a recent collapse killed six workers, will leave his position as part of a "mutual agreement."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chiles-codelco-replaces-el-teniente-manager-after-deadly-accident-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QILWLDY7OZOOFDHYBKPWTNSYOA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:08:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称特朗普签署命令将对华关税期限延长90天]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普已签署行政命令，将美国对中国进口商品大幅提高关税的暂停期延长90天。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has signed an executive order extending a pause in sharply higher U.S. tariffs on Chinese imports for another 90 days, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-signs-order-extending-china-tariff-deadline-90-days-official-says-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NEMWMUHMVIAZIRAEHVOA6N6XY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉北美服务总监离开电动汽车制造商]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉北美市场服务总监皮耶罗-兰多菲（Piero Landolfi）在离开这家电动汽车制造商近九年后，加入了该公司因销量下滑而出现的高管离职潮。【原文：Piero Landolfi, Tesla's director of service for the North American market has left the EV maker after nearly nine years, joining an exodus of executives from the company grappling with a drop in sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-north-american-director-service-leaves-ev-maker-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNVD7N3OKZOBDIF5PRUMLWQF2Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:52:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CNBC 报道：特朗普签署行政令，将对华加征关税期限延长 90 天]]></title><description><![CDATA[据CNBC周一援引白宫官员的话报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普已签署行政命令，将对华加征关税的最后期限再延长90天。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has signed an executive order extending the China tariff deadline for another 90 days, CNBC reported on Monday, citing a White House official.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-signs-executive-order-extend-china-tariff-deadline-90-days-cnbc-reports-2025-08-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDLRCSKODJLANEUAWEETOAKSCY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>