<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 13:10:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 13:10:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息预期升温，全球股票基金每周资金流入强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至12月11日，全球股票基金连续第11周吸引资金流入，原因是有迹象表明，美国劳动力市场降温和消费者价格稳定可能有助于美联储本月连续第三次降息。【原文：Global equity funds attracted inflows for an 11th successive week through Dec. 11, supported by signs that a cooling U.S. labor market and stable consumer prices might facilitate a third consecutive rate cut by the Federal Reserve this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFG7N5OZGBOTPJN7IM6CMRTCLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 12:22:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国法院恢复马来西亚工人对戴森公司的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，英国上诉法院裁定，二十多名声称在一家马来西亚工厂为英国真空吸尘器制造商戴森制造零部件时遭到强迫劳动的移民工人可以在伦敦起诉戴森公司。【原文：Two dozen migrant workers who allege they were subjected to forced labour at a Malaysian factory while making parts for British vacuum cleaner manufacturer Dyson can sue the company in London, the Court of Appeal ruled on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/malaysian-workers-lawsuit-against-dyson-revived-by-uk-court-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAY2TN4VGBL6NK3E6SLYIOIM74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 12:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构对 Blackrock-Preqin 的 32.2 亿美元交易展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构周五表示，正在对资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock）以 25.5 亿英镑（32.2 亿美元）收购英国数据公司 Preqin 的交易展开调查。【原文：Britain's competition regulator said on Friday it was launching a probe into asset management firm BlackRock's 2.55 billion pounds ($3.22 billion) acquisition of UK data firm Preqin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/uk-competition-watchdog-launches-probe-into-322-bln-blackrock-preqin-deal-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YLQXIASGNOVLMRFDZXHZ6CI2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 12:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔瓦雷斯说，斯特兰蒂斯的 "友好 "退出是由于在战略上的分歧]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡洛斯-塔瓦雷斯（Carlos Tavares）于12月1日突然辞去汽车制造商Stellantis首席执行官一职，他在周四晚些时候发表的一篇访谈中表示，他 "友好 "离职的原因是与董事会在战略上存在分歧。【原文：Carlos Tavares, who abruptly resigned as CEO of carmaker Stellantis on Dec. 1, said his "amicable" departure was motivated by disagreements with the board over strategy, in an interview published late on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tavares-says-amicable-stellantis-exit-was-due-disagreements-strategy-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WULS7RRCORPL3CT45TJBQEGQVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 12:07:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博通因预测人工智能芯片需求激增而大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[博通公司（Broadcom）预测未来几年对其定制人工智能芯片的需求将持续上升，该公司股价周五飙升14%，市值接近1万亿美元。【原文：Shares of Broadcom soared 14% on Friday, with the chipmaker moving closer to $1 trillion in market value after it forecast that demand for its custom AI chips would keep rising in the coming years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/broadcom-rallies-forecast-booming-ai-chip-demand-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPAQUIKYFVPIZBBYVJZNUK7R7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:25:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒙古欺诈案后，特拉菲古拉净利润和股本减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球大宗商品贸易公司创辉集团（Trafigura）周五表示，由于在蒙古发现了价值数十亿美元的石油欺诈案，该公司2024年的盈利大幅下降，并下调了前几年的股本和利润。【原文：Global commodity trading house Trafigura saw a sharp drop in its earnings for 2024 and has revised down its equity and profits for previous years after it discovered a billion-dollar oil fraud in Mongolia, the company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trafigura-net-profit-equity-drops-after-mongolia-fraud-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JB23SADQBJJVDLFNVY2TB5XKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[T-Mobile 宣布 140 亿美元回购]]></title><description><![CDATA[电信巨头 T-Mobile 周五公布了 140 亿美元的股票回购计划。【原文：Telecom giant T-Mobile unveiled a $14 billion share buyback on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/t-mobile-announces-14-bln-buyback-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUTXDWSU6RKMFNK3ESEK3AMXHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社/益普索民调显示，如果关税引发通胀，美国人就会反感]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社/益普索（Reuters/Ipsos）的一项民意调查显示，如果进口关税导致价格上涨，美国人并不认为这是个好主意，而且他们对进口关税能否帮助美国工人也持怀疑态度，这凸显了当选总统唐纳德-特朗普对来自中国、墨西哥和其他国家的商品征收高额关税的计划所面临的政治风险。【原文：Americans don't think import tariffs are a good idea if they lead to higher prices and are skeptical they would help U.S. workers, a Reuters/Ipsos poll found, underscoring the political risks to President-elect Donald Trump's plan to impose heavy fees on goods from China, Mexico and other nations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/americans-are-sour-tariffs-if-they-spark-inflation-reutersipsos-poll-finds-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXDKLRPNSRMGHNCWPVDK7M6QTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:11:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普过渡政府建议取消特斯拉反对的汽车碰撞报告要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，特朗普过渡团队希望新政府放弃一项遭到埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的特斯拉公司（Tesla）反对的车祸报告要求。
 根据路透社看到的一份文件，此举可能削弱政府调查和监管自动驾驶系统车辆安全的能力。【原文：The Trump transition team wants the incoming administration to drop a car-crash reporting requirement opposed by Elon Musk’s Tesla 
 , according to a document seen by Reuters, a move that could cripple the government’s ability to investigate and regulate the safety of vehicles with automated-driving systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-transition-recommends-scrapping-car-crash-reporting-requirement-opposed-by-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNTJ5LCBQBLJZNNSVQHLCTBHHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：专家称，特朗普关税可能加剧美国卡车运输业的衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家表示，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁对主要贸易伙伴中国、墨西哥和加拿大征收关税，这将对价值 1.7 万亿美元的美国运输业造成打击，并加剧近三年来卡车运输业的衰退。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's threatened tariffs on top trade partners China, Mexico and Canada would deal a blow to the $1.7 trillion U.S. transportation industry and worsen a nearly three-year trucking recession, sector experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-tariffs-could-intensify-us-trucking-industry-slump-experts-say-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTZPAW7QNZO67NH6DDIPF5ZJ3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:08:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国数据显示美联储正大步迈向下周降息，并悄然迈向 2025 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者认为，美国联邦储备委员会将在 12 月 17 日至 18 日的会议上将利率下调四分之一个百分点几乎是板上钉钉的事，而更多的注意力则集中在决策者在做出决定的同时发布的新经济预测上。【原文：Investors view it as a near given that the U.S. Federal Reserve will cut interest rates by a quarter of a percentage point at its Dec. 17-18 meeting, with more attention focused on policymakers' new economic projections released alongside the decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-data-has-fed-striding-toward-rate-cut-next-week-tip-toeing-into-2025-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZGNDK7R45JJ5HXKULXYFHU2BI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：各国央行以降息结束 2024 年，华尔街接近历史记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[塞缪尔-因迪克对美国和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by Samuel Indyk】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4CR6JDRG5PJRLXMQP5YH62EPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博通发布乐观预测后，纳斯达克期货领涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货上涨，其中与科技重镇纳斯达克 100 指数挂钩的股指期货涨幅居前，原因是芯片制造商博通公司（Broadcom）的乐观预测使人们对人工智能的热情持续高涨。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Friday, with those linked to the tech-heavy Nasdaq 100 in the lead, after an upbeat forecast from chipmaker Broadcom kept alive the euphoria around artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-futures-lead-gains-after-broadcoms-upbeat-forecast-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4EHQXQJDVJNVHZ2ZDR4FANLBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Blackstone 和贝恩将竞购三菱制药部门，交易金额高达 35 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士称，全球私募股权投资公司 Blackstone 和贝恩资本是日本三菱化学集团旗下三菱田边制药公司的最终竞标者之一，该交易的估值可能在 30 亿至 35 亿美元之间。【原文：Global private equity firms Blackstone and Bain Capital are among final bidders for Mitsubishi Tanabe Pharma, a unit of Japan's Mitsubishi Chemical Group, in a deal that could value it at between $3 billion and $3.5 billion, three sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/blackstone-bain-bid-mitsubishi-pharma-unit-up-35-bln-deal-sources-say-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKICUNKRRBKQJAJZTGQBCA56OQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康集团首席执行官安德鲁-威蒂说医疗系统存在缺陷]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）首席执行官安德鲁-威蒂（Andrew Witty）周五在《纽约时报》的一篇评论文章中写道，医疗保健系统存在缺陷，是 "几十年来建立起来的拼凑"。【原文：UnitedHealth Group CEO Andrew Witty wrote in a New York Times opinion piece on Friday that the healthcare system was flawed and was a "patchwork built over decades."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-group-ceo-andrew-witty-says-healthcare-system-is-flawed-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBSL76A7RJLRJBJI5GJPUS6LEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与博世就 2.25 亿美元芯片资助达成初步协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五表示，已与德国汽车供应商博世达成初步协议，博世将获得高达 2.25 亿美元的补贴，用于在加利福尼亚州生产电动汽车所需的碳化硅功率半导体。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Friday it reached a preliminary deal with German auto supplier Bosch for up to $225 million in subsidies to build silicon carbide power semiconductors in California that are key for electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-reaches-preliminary-deal-with-bosch-225-million-chip-grants-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRLUNQRGM5KHNMOVZM7HPO7UY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[吉利和百度承诺解决电动车企业面临的薪酬问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国吉利（GEELY.UL）和百度周五表示，将帮助陷入困境的电动汽车合资企业吉利汽车管理层解决与员工的纠纷，包括社会福利和遣散费问题。【原文：China's Geely (GEELY.UL) and Baidu said on Friday they would help the management of their troubled electric vehicle venture Ji Yue Auto to solve disputes with employees including over social welfare and severance payments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/geely-baidu-pledge-solve-payroll-issues-facing-ev-venture-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNYKFG4QUJJU3EP6G3VVQZUHTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源机构称，页岩钻探技术可能导致地热激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际能源机构（IEA）周五表示，页岩钻探技术导致石油和天然气产量激增，同时也刺激了地热的发展，从理论上讲，地热可提供稳定的电力来源，相当于印度和美国需求的总和。【原文：The shale drilling techniques that led to a boom in oil and gas output have also spurred the development of geothermal, which in theory could provide a stable source of power equal to the demand of India and the United States combined, the IEA said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shale-drilling-techniques-could-lead-geothermal-surge-iea-says-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNRYKE32G5POLDCXRZNU3NBQIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 09:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收新关税，中国着眼于谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析人士称，随着唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）加大对中国的关税威胁，中国政府正在采取行动，以自己的限制措施击败下一任美国总统，并在全面爆发贸易战之前让华盛顿坐到谈判桌前。【原文：As Donald Trump steps up his tariff threats against China, Beijing is moving to beat the next U.S. president to the punch with its own restrictions and get Washington to the negotiating table ahead of a full-blown trade war, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-eyes-negotiations-trump-threatens-new-tariffs-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2QIJUEE2BMCRL4GAOAFPDLAHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:34:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：马来西亚棕榈油局（MPOB）称暴雨将在 12 月再次打击马来西亚棕榈油产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚棕榈油行业监管机构周五告诉路透社，由于强降雨影响了世界第二大热带油生产国的棕榈油收获，12月份马来西亚棕榈油产量将连续第四个月下降。【原文：Malaysia's palm oil production is set to fall for the fourth consecutive month in December as heavy rainfall hit harvesting in the world's second-largest producer of the tropical oil, the industry regulator told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/heavy-rains-hit-malaysian-palm-oil-output-again-december-says-mpob-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOO6P2RO6FOD7IS2STP5O6QE64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 CATL 为供应商提供资金支持以推动电池创新]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 CATL 向供应商表示，愿意为他们提供资金支持，以加快电池材料和设备的技术创新，这是在残酷的电动汽车价格战中缓解供应链压力的努力之一。【原文：China's CATL has told suppliers it is willing to provide them with financial support to speed up technology innovation in battery materials and equipment, part of efforts to relieve stress on its supply chain amid a brutal EV price war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-catl-offers-suppliers-financial-support-drive-battery-innovation-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEPZJ6OQNZKORESZYKNYRLU7KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:01:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在中国推出 "其实智能召唤 "功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车制造商特斯拉周五在中国推出了 "其实智能召唤 "功能。【原文：U.S. automaker Tesla on Friday launched the "Actually Smart Summon" feature in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-launches-actually-smart-summon-feature-china-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYVRWQNENBMYFIYZJZZB434ARQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰 CD Projekt 公司发布《巫师 4》游戏预告片]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰最大的视频游戏制造商 CD Projekt 周五发布了其计划中的奇幻大片《巫师》系列新游戏的预告片。【原文：Poland's biggest video game maker CD Projekt on Friday released a trailer for its planned new game in the blockbuster "Witcher" fantasy series.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/polands-cd-projekt-releases-trailer-witcher-iv-game-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRN6MBPCUJLNVMSHETGXQZXXYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 07:40:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚明星娱乐公司黄金海岸赌场主管离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[陷入困境的澳大利亚赌场运营商 Star Entertainment 周五表示，其旗下 Star Gold Coast 赌场的首席执行官在上任仅三个月后辞职，几天前该赌场的执照暂停期被延长至三月。【原文：Embattled Australian casino operator Star Entertainment on Friday said the CEO of its Star Gold Coast casino has resigned just three months into the job and days after the casino's license suspension was extended until March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australian-star-entertainments-gold-coast-casino-chief-exits-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5FKNREH6JZKCND6X6GJHUJT7S4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 07:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行维勒鲁瓦：未来将有更多降息举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（ECB）决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周五表示，欧洲中央银行明年可能会进一步放宽利率，并对市场对未来利率的预测表示放心。【原文：The European Central Bank is likely to further ease interest rates next year and is at ease with market projections for future rates, ECB policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecbs-villeroy-more-interest-rate-cuts-come-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6M2HRVHB7RMZDGHS5HB6DPBS7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 07:31:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国 10 月出口降幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国 10 月份出口降幅超过预期，这表明期待已久的外部需求复苏已被推迟。【原文：German exports fell more than expected in October, an indication that the long-awaited recovery in external demand has been delayed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-exports-fall-more-than-expected-october-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CB5JOG5XMZPV5GNL3C23F3PG3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 07:08:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国经济意外萎缩，蕾切尔-里夫斯再遭打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国经济在 10 月份意外萎缩了 0.1%，有迹象表明英国经济放缓幅度大于预期，这对财政大臣雷切尔-里夫斯（Rachel Reeves）来说是个坏消息，她认为周五的官方数据 "令人失望"。【原文：Britain's economy shrank unexpectedly by 0.1% in October, adding to signs of a bigger-than-expected slowdown in more bad news for finance minister Rachel Reeves, who described Friday's official data as "disappointing".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-economy-contracts-unexpectedly-by-01-october-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XN5T2CDJSNJCLECVZXH4NMRDEM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 07:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普政策担忧和美元升值影响，11月份外资流出打击亚洲债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于预期即将上台的特朗普政府将改变美国的贸易政策以及美元走强抑制了投资者的胃口，亚洲债务市场在 11 月份出现了七个月以来的首次外资流出。【原文：Asian debt markets witnessed foreign outflows in November for the first time in seven months as expectations of changes in U.S. trade policies under the forthcoming Trump administration and a strengthening dollar dampened investor appetite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/foreign-outflows-hit-asian-bonds-nov-trump-policy-concerns-dollars-rise-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2YAIGLURRKDFMW4WZRJGS2EZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 06:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国债券市场将面临更多经济阵痛]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国债券投资者押注 2025 年经济不会出现奇迹般的复苏，这使他们与押注消费复苏的股票市场背道而驰。【原文：Investors in Chinese bonds head for 2025 betting there will be no miraculous recovery in the economy, putting them at odds with an equities market that has wagered on a revival in consumption.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/chinas-bond-market-sees-more-economic-pain-ahead-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2WASUPPDNJ25KKN46BKE5TM5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 06:30:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 11 月通胀可能加速，出口因日元疲软而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，受大米价格居高不下和公用事业补贴逐步取消的影响，日本 11 月份的核心消费价格通胀可能加速。【原文：Japan's core consumer price inflation probably accelerated in November, driven by persistently high rice prices and the phasing out of utility subsidies, a Reuters poll showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-nov-inflation-likely-accelerated-exports-up-weak-yen-2024-12-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DTDE6SDNNLPZLOW6R7HW6NFUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 06:11:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>