<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:34:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:34:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期抵押贷款利率降至 6.13%，再融资跃升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国抵押贷款银行家协会（Mortgage Bankers Association）周三公布的数据显示，上周美国最受欢迎的住房贷款利率降至6.13%，创下约两年来的最低水平，再融资活动也大幅增加。【原文：The interest rate for the most popular U.S. home loan ticked down to 6.13% last week, the lowest in about two years, and refinancing activity jumped, data from the Mortgage Bankers Association showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-mortgage-rate-slips-613-refinancing-jumps-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EBIKH6OMTRMFJDQKWOUJO25FRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克公司的结直肠癌疗法晚期试验失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司（Merck）周三表示，该公司的疗法没有达到在一种结直肠癌患者中进行评估的后期试验的主要目标。【原文：Merck said on Wednesday its therapy did not meet the main goal of a late-stage trial evaluating it in patients with a type of colorectal cancer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/mercks-colorectal-cancer-therapy-fails-late-stage-trial-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTAOLECUVFKKDMTGWOPKNUMFAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，8月份中国外资智能手机销量下降12.7]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家政府下属研究公司周三公布的数据显示，包括苹果公司 iPhone 在内的外国品牌智能手机 8 月份在中国的销量同比下降了 12.7%。【原文：Sales of foreign-branded smartphones, including Apple Inc's iPhone, in China fell 12.7% in August year-on-year, according to data released on Wednesday from a government-affiliated research firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/foreign-smartphone-sales-china-drop-127-august-data-show-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQOMLOPNSNNM5EALGP3WO3OKOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔出售更多美国银行股票，自 7 月以来净赚 90 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）周二提交的最新文件显示，该公司抛售了更多的美国银行股票，自 7 月份以来共抛售了约 90 亿美元的股票。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway has offloaded more shares in Bank of America , its latest filing showed on Tuesday, raking in about $9 billion since July.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/berkshire-sells-more-bofa-shares-netting-9-bln-since-july-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WOIMU3PPVMLXPI3KJRM7GYHU4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:46:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司称南非正在洽谈购买 C-390 飞机事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周三表示，在第二次在非洲国家展示 C-390 千禧型军用货机之后，南非在可能购买该飞机的谈判中取得了进展。【原文：South Africa has advanced in talks for a potential purchase of Embraer's C-390 Millennium, the Brazilian planemaker said on Wednesday, after showcasing the military cargo aircraft in the African nation for the second time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/embraer-says-south-africa-talks-purchase-c-390-aircraft-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADHL7ABBNNI2HE5KJBKL5KVULA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待经济数据和美联储利率线索，期指下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周三下滑，投资者在等待有关经济健康状况和美联储一周前启动宽松政策周期后降息前景的更多线索时，避免了大举押注。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Wednesday, with investors avoiding big bets as they awaited more clues on the health of the economy and the outlook for interest rate cuts after the Federal Reserve kicked off its policy easing cycle a week ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-slip-investors-await-economic-data-fed-rate-clues-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EV4QITQ5ZJNZZMOP4SZK5GDBFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:32:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行首席财务官称美联储似乎正在赢得通胀之战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行首席财务官阿拉斯泰尔-博思威克（Alastair Borthwick）在周三的一次会议上表示，美联储似乎正在赢得美国的通胀之战。【原文：The Federal Reserve seems to be winning the inflation battle in the United States, Bank of America CFO Alastair Borthwick said at a conference on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bank-america-cfo-says-fed-seems-be-winning-inflation-battle-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBSYFQ73WFKKVPVGURLY3APA2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国信心动荡，中国受到鼓舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VNOWWG55NOHJMKJJB24OOE2J4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，Stellantis公司在美国召回15,000多辆菲亚特汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，由于软件错误可能导致前安全气囊在碰撞中过度展开，Stellantis公司将召回15,835辆菲亚特汽车。【原文：Stellantis is recalling 15,835 Fiat vehicles due to a software error that may cause the front airbags to deploy with excessive force in a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-recalls-over-15000-fiat-vehicles-us-nhtsa-says-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQNEL6ZIHRIWDPUZUETRXEPJTA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:10:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香蕉、汽车和服装：美国港口劳资纠纷威胁一系列产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月 1 日，美国东海岸和海湾地区的海港将有约 45,000 名工会工人失业，这将在美国总统大选前几周切断重要的贸易通道。【原文：Some 45,000 union workers could walk off the job at seaports on the U.S. East and Gulf Coasts on Oct 1, cutting off vital trade arteries just weeks ahead of the nation's presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bananas-cars-clothes-us-port-labor-dispute-threatens-range-products-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45BQBSRE6FIPJASLEFO5HQQ4KI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步与中国自动驾驶技术初创公司宣布合作在阿联酋推出机器人出租车]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步科技公司（Uber Technologies）和WeRide周三宣布建立合作关系，从阿联酋开始将中国自动驾驶技术公司的车辆引入优步的共享出行平台。【原文：Uber Technologies and WeRide announced a partnership on Wednesday to bring the Chinese self-driving technology firm's vehicles to the rideshare platform, starting in the United Arab Emirates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-chinese-self-driving-tech-startup-announce-partnership-launch-robotaxis-uae-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IO7MFLBIWZPYJAMMZQZYGY3RIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:08:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储大幅降息令美国债券市场重现 "通货再膨胀幽灵]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储积极启动宽松周期，重新点燃了美国债券市场对通胀的担忧，因为一些投资者担心宽松的金融条件可能会重新引发价格压力。【原文：The Federal Reserve's aggressive start of the easing cycle has rekindled inflation worries in the U.S. bond market, as some investors fear looser financial conditions could re-ignite price pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bumper-rate-cut-revives-reflation-specter-us-bond-market-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXCJSU5OQNODFP4P3GY2FCFD6E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：托运人在美国港口罢工威胁前争相寻求变通办法]]></title><description><![CDATA[依赖东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸海港的美国公司已经提前进口，将货物转移到西海岸，甚至将货物放在价格昂贵的航班上，以规避 10 月 1 日罢工的威胁，因为罢工可能会在美国总统大选前堵塞供应链并重燃通胀。【原文：U.S. companies that rely on East and Gulf Coast seaports have been importing early, shifting goods to the West Coast, and even putting cargo on pricey flights to hedge against a threatened Oct. 1 strike that could jam supply chains and reignite inflation ahead of the U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/shippers-scramble-workarounds-ahead-threatened-us-port-strike-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NV2XOY2W5ZPWDBDNA6S4Y6JO3Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 准备在 Connect 活动上展示 AR 眼镜]]></title><description><![CDATA[Facebook 的所有者 Meta 公司周三准备在其加利福尼亚总部召开年度 Connect 大会，预计将在会上预览其首款增强现实眼镜，并宣布对现有虚拟现实和人工智能产品进行更新。【原文：Facebook owner Meta prepared on Wednesday to kick off its annual Connect conference at its California headquarters, where it is expected to preview its first augmented reality glasses and announce updates to its existing virtual reality and artificial intelligence products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-readies-ar-glasses-reveal-connect-event-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBFUFO62M5KKVNSNHPS3CMJ2LE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:03:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空盈利乏力加剧业务模式改革压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师说，西南航空公司（Southwest Airlines）这家低成本航空公司的先驱正面临着一位激进投资者要求彻底改革其认为过时的商业模式的运动，这给首席执行官罗伯特-乔丹（Robert Jordan）带来了压力，并使该航空公司不得不努力实现现代化。【原文：Southwest Airlines , the pioneering low-cost carrier, is facing a campaign by an activist investor to overhaul a business model it says is outdated, putting pressure on CEO Robert Jordan and leaving the airline scrambling to modernize, analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-airs-lackluster-profit-fuels-pressure-revamp-business-model-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TC7PHELA3NIFXHSGRTHJ4X4RDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚明星娱乐公司获得债务生命线，将于周四公布业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[陷入困境的澳大利亚赌场运营商明星娱乐公司（Star Entertainment）周三表示，该公司已获得一笔高达 2 亿澳元（约合 1.3746 亿美元）的新债务融资，并将在一天后公布年度收益。【原文：Embattled Australian casino operator Star Entertainment said on Wednesday it has secured a new debt facility of up to A$200 million ($137.46 million) and that it will announce its annual earnings on a day later.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/australias-star-entertainment-gets-debt-life-line-announce-results-thursday-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJ5PFGNUP5P55OK6WX6DQOYNDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国顶级 Vape 公司研究尼古丁替代品]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的三家大型 Vape 公司正在研究类似尼古丁的化学物质，他们认为这种化学物质可以在 Vape 等产品中替代尼古丁，但对健康的影响可能还需要 "数年 "的调查。【原文：Three large Chinese vape companies are researching nicotine-like chemicals they think could serve as a substitute for nicotine in products like vapes, company officials said, but the health implications may still need "years" of investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/top-chinese-vape-firms-research-nicotine-alternatives-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VJJQ3XSJ5N4HGXLIMH6HNXQIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立法者称德国政府排除再次增持德国商业银行股份的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国议员迈克尔-施罗迪（Michael Schrodi）周三在议会金融委员会会议上表示，德国政府已排除在与意大利联合信贷银行（Unicredit）的收购纠纷中再次增持德国商业银行股份的可能性。【原文：The German government has ruled out increasing its stake in Commerzbank again in the takeover dispute with Italy's Unicredit during a meeting of the parliamentary finance committee, lawmaker Michael Schrodi said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/german-govt-rules-out-increasing-commerzbank-stake-again-says-lawmaker-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37YHVTK7PRMEZEVXBPF3J3NOMA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经合组织认为今年全球经济增长将稳定在 3.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[经合组织（OECD）周三表示，随着央行加息的拖累减弱以及通胀率下降提高了家庭收入，全球经济增长正在趋于稳定，并小幅上调了今年的经济展望。【原文：Global growth is in the process of stabilising as the drag from central bank rate hikes fades and falling inflation boosts households' incomes, the OECD said on Wednesday, marginally raising its outlook for this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/oecd-sees-global-growth-stabilising-32-this-year-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPU4UEY735MXBP5IRILHWIJK2Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国敦促美国停止在最新汽车争端中 "无理打压 "中国企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周三敦促美国停止对中国公司的 "无理打压"，以回应美国以国家安全为由禁止中国软件和硬件在其道路上行驶的提议。【原文：China urged the United States on Wednesday to stop "unreasonable suppression" of its companies, in response to U.S. proposals to ban Chinese software and hardware in vehicles on its roads due to national security concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-urges-us-stop-unreasonable-suppression-its-firms-latest-auto-row-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYXCK4CX25PEXJAXQQ36EHFDKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院委员会指责波音公司的安全做法和 FAA 的监督工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院一个调查波音公司安全文化的小组周三援引正在进行的调查中获得的文件，指责这家飞机制造商的质量做法和联邦航空管理局的监督。【原文：A U.S. Senate panel investigating Boeing's safety culture on Wednesday faulted the planemaker's quality practices and oversight by the Federal Aviation Administration citing documents obtained in an ongoing investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-senate-committee-faults-boeing-safety-practices-faa-oversight-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4OURATTZJNPZOP665IZGRW5UM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡马拉-哈里斯关于税收、儿童保育和住房的经济计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国副总统卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）宣布了一揽子经济提案，旨在通过税收优惠和其他税收转移措施，降低美国中下层民众的生活成本，促进整体经济发展。【原文：U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris has announced a basket of economic proposals aiming to lower living costs for middle and lower-class Americans and boost the economy overall by using tax incentives and other tax shifts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/kamala-harris-economic-plans-taxes-childcare-housing-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5S3BFNZIVNKNMYOFP7YMV2ZCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈里斯将推出新激励措施促进匹兹堡国内制造业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国副总统卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）周三计划提出新的激励措施，以促进国内制造业的发展，一天前她的共和党竞选对手唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，如果当选，他将寻求从其他国家 "夺走 "工厂的工作机会。【原文：U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris on Wednesday plans to propose new incentives to boost domestic manufacturing, a day after her Republican election rival Donald Trump said he would seek to "take" factory jobs from other countries if elected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/harris-push-new-incentives-boost-domestic-manufacturing-pittsburgh-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2G5PQS42VM3NASKFCXLWCNZ5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌、挪威财富基金支持英国实时债券带投标]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌云（Google Cloud）、挪威主权财富基金和瑞士银行瑞银（UBS）联手支持英国债券市场交易实时记录的竞标，主导该计划的固定收益技术公司告诉路透社。【原文：Google Cloud, Norway's sovereign wealth fund and Swiss bank UBS have joined forces to back a bid to run Britain's real-time record of transactions in bond markets, the fixed income technology firm leading the plan told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/google-norways-wealth-fund-back-uk-real-time-bond-tape-bid-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZADDFVFOBVP2REHNNELM5OE6UE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:40:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度尼西亚正式申请加入跨太平洋贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[据印尼国家通讯社安塔拉（Antara）报道，印尼首席经济部长周三表示，印尼已正式请求加入跨太平洋贸易协定，以拓宽其出口市场。【原文：Indonesia has formally requested to join the Trans-Pacific trade pact to widen its export markets, its chief economic minister said on Wednesday, according to a report by state news agency Antara.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-formally-requests-join-trans-pacific-trade-pact-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SKTT7D23JIXLHTYYKRCBLG5SI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 07:39:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国 Orange 退出纽约证券交易所]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电信运营商 Orange 周三宣布，以二次上市的财务成本为由，打算将其股票从纽约证券交易所（NYSE）退市。【原文：French telecom operator Orange announced on Wednesday its intention to delist its shares from the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), citing the financial cost of the secondary listing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/frances-orange-exit-new-york-stock-exchange-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DTRVDVS5BMOROUVUAL52Y6Z4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 06:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星展集团首席执行官表示，星展集团正着手将中国证券合资企业的持股比例提高至 91]]></title><description><![CDATA[星展集团首席执行官皮尤什-古普塔（Piyush Gupta）周三表示，该集团正在将其在中国合资证券公司的持股比例从51%增至91%。【原文：DBS Group Chief Executive Piyush Gupta said on Wednesday it is in the process of increasing ownership in its China securities joint venture to 91% from 51%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/dbs-moving-raise-china-securities-joint-venture-stake-91-ceo-says-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTNTGLWSFRONNJPBDH2XK366S4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 06:13:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国新经济刺激计划在全球市场引起轰动]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，中国政府宣布了自大流行病以来最大规模的经济刺激措施，希望将这个世界第二大经济体从通货紧缩的泥潭中拉出来。【原文：China-exposed assets jumped on Tuesday after Beijing announced its biggest stimulus since the pandemic in a bid to pull the world's second-largest economy out of the deflationary funk that has shaken global currency and equity markets this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/chinas-new-stimulus-plans-make-splash-global-markets-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDZH6SIZDZL7BAGE72ZGJ4CZHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 06:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国货币政策失误错过经济增长的关键威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行已转向更积极的宽松政策，但其政策武器并未将经济增长的关键敌人--持续疲软的消费需求--纳入视线。【原文：China's central bank has shifted to a more aggressive easing stance, but its policy weapons don't have the key enemy to economic growth in their line of sight: the persistently weak consumer demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-monetary-volleys-miss-key-threat-economic-growth-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SAE45ONPRVIFXJOJ5KP46TV4WQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 05:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[读卖新闻》报道：日本监管机构建议对野村经纪部门涉嫌操纵市场的行为进行处罚]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《读卖新闻》报道，日本证券监察机构预计将建议对野村控股公司经纪部门涉嫌操纵国债期货市场的行为处以数千万日元的罚款。【原文：Japan's securities watchdog is expected to recommend imposing tens of millions of yen in penalties on Nomura Holding's brokerage unit for alleged manipulation in the government bond futures market, the Yomiuri reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japan-watchdog-recommend-penalties-nomuras-brokerage-unit-alleged-market-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5N22SP25F5OTDI3K3EK7ASOMKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 05:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>