<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:36:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:36:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[法院禁令冻结 Raiffeisen 银行俄罗斯分支所有权]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯最大的西方银行 Raiffeisen Bank International 周四表示，俄罗斯法院冻结了该银行当地分支机构的股份，暂时排除了出售该业务的可能性。【原文：A Russian court froze the shares in Raiffeisen Bank International's local arm, the biggest Western bank in Russia said on Thursday, ruling out any sale of the business for now.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/raiffeisen-banks-russian-arm-ownership-frozen-ban-imposed-by-court-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CMSNK5FI5PCZDGGIYW52R5KZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储就紧急贷款行动征求反馈意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周四表示，它正在就如何运作 "贴现窗口 "征求反馈意见，该窗口的目的是在银行面临压力时向其提供紧急贷款。【原文：The Federal Reserve said on Thursday it was seeking feedback on how it operates its "discount window," which is intended to provide emergency lending to banks in times of stress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-seeks-feedback-emergency-lending-operations-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQHT5B4DQRMRLBW4YBCI5NP6ZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥银行监管机构批准股市改革细节]]></title><description><![CDATA[带头进行改革的墨西哥财政部副部长加布里埃尔-约里奥（Gabriel Yorio）说，墨西哥银行监管机构 CNBV 董事会周四批准了去年通过的股市改革条款。【原文：The board of Mexican bank regulator CNBV on Thursday approved the terms of a stock market reform passed last year, Deputy Finance Minister Gabriel Yorio, who spearheaded the reform, said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/mexico-bank-regulator-approves-details-stock-market-reform-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQB25WQTIJNVVE4A3HNV7MOHBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DOT 命令美国最大的航空公司回答关于飞行常客计划的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部周四表示，正在对美国四大航空运营商的奖励和飞行常客计划展开调查，以确保消费者不会遭遇不公平、欺骗性或反竞争行为。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department said on Thursday it is opening an inquiry into the four largest U.S. air carrier rewards and frequent flyer programs to ensure consumers do not face unfair, deceptive, or anticompetitive practices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/dot-orders-largest-us-airlines-answer-questions-frequent-flyer-programs-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33KKZYMPBRP4FHUUNZTET2IRVM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前英国交易员因奖金纠纷起诉德意志银行败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行的一名前交易员因近十年前未获得个人奖金而在伦敦对该银行提起诉讼，最终以 260 多万英镑（340 万美元）败诉。【原文：A former Deutsche Bank trader on Thursday lost her London lawsuit against the bank for just over 2.6 million pounds ($3.4 million) after she was not paid an individual bonus nearly a decade ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ex-uk-trader-loses-lawsuit-against-deutsche-bank-over-bonus-dispute-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIIP7RSIQFIMPADNM7TNWIKN4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 将向阿根廷工厂投资 3.85 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商 Stellantis 南美区负责人 Emanuele Cappellano 周四表示，该公司将在 2025 年至 2030 年期间向位于阿根廷科尔多瓦省的工厂投资 3.85 亿美元。【原文：Automaker Stellantis will invest $385 million in its plant in the province of Cordoba, Argentina, between 2025 and 2030, the firm's South America head Emanuele Cappellano said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-invest-385-mln-argentine-plant-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YP6JE224DJPZVIJVOP2ZLLREZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通任命中型企业并购部门新联席主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份内部备忘录，摩根大通已任命安德鲁-卡斯塔多（Andrew Castaldo）和安德鲁-马丁（Andrew Martin）为中型企业并购部门的联合负责人，该部门隶属于摩根大通的商业和投资银行。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has named Andrew Castaldo and Andrew Martin as co-heads of mid-cap mergers and acquisitions unit, housed within its commercial and investment bank, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-names-new-co-heads-mid-cap-ma-unit-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WSDBRKN65PN3A52RVA7CHCQB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，Vista 和 Blackstone 正在洽谈收购软件制造商 Smartsheet]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周四表示，包括 Vista Equity Partners 和 Blackstone 在内的私募股权投资财团正在洽谈收购 Smartsheet，这是一家市值约 70 亿美元的美国办公协作软件制造商。【原文：A private equity consortium including Vista Equity Partners and Blackstone is in talks to acquire Smartsheet , a U.S. maker of workplace collaboration software with a market value of about $7 billion, people familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/vista-blackstone-talks-acquire-software-maker-smartsheet-sources-say-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UT3KRRXQ4RPP3EPZZLMUAMVS5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:26:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，亿万富翁拉里-埃里森将在交易后控制派拉蒙公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引一份监管文件报道，在由软件亿万富翁拉里-埃里森（Larry Ellison）的儿子大卫-埃里森（David Ellison）领导的集团完成对雷德斯通（Redstone）家族在这家电影和电视公司的股权收购后，哥伦比亚广播公司的母公司派拉蒙全球公司（Paramount Global）将由软件亿万富翁拉里-埃里森（Larry Ellison）控制。【原文：CBS parent Paramount Global will be controlled by software billionaire Larry Ellison after a group led by his son David completes its purchase of the Redstone family's interest in the film and TV company, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing a regulatory filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/billionaire-larry-ellison-control-paramount-after-deal-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLGY2KVIRJPUZL5AT7BVGJ5AXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+同意将 10 月石油产量上调推迟两个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[在原油价格创下九个月来的最低点后，欧佩克+组织周四表示，已同意推迟10月和11月的石油增产计划，并补充说，如有必要，该组织可能会进一步暂停或扭转增产计划。【原文：OPEC+ has agreed to delay a planned oil output increase for October and November, the producers group said on Thursday after crude prices hit their lowest in nine months, adding that it could further pause or reverse the hikes if needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/opec-agrees-delay-october-oil-output-hike-two-months-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORDDMAULAJJVDEMCUXIKPZ56VA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递投资人工智能机器人公司 Nimble 以促进供应链业务发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递（FedEx）周四表示，已投资人工智能机器人和自主技术公司Nimble，以帮助该快递巨头扩大其履行部门的规模，该部门协助中小企业履行订单和管理库存。【原文：FedEx said on Thursday it has invested in AI robotics and autonomous technology company Nimble to help scale up the delivery giant's Fulfillment unit which aids small and medium-sized businesses in fulfilling orders and managing inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fedex-invests-ai-robotics-company-nimble-boost-its-supply-chain-business-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LA76UFF6J5JBPNCTEGIFQZ3IBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AT&T 向罢工的 CWA 工会提出最终报价]]></title><description><![CDATA[电信运营商 AT&amp;T 周四表示，已向美国通信工人工会的谈判委员会提交了最终报价，并补充说，该报价并未达到其预期。【原文：Telecom operator AT&amp;T has presented the Communications Workers of America's bargaining committee with its final offer, the union said on Thursday, adding that the proposal did not meet its expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/att-makes-final-offer-striking-cwa-union-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHUWKZU4KBJUTBVD53PXZ7OYZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长耶伦对美国钢铁公司与新日本的审查不予置评]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周四表示，美国欢迎外国直接投资，并严格审查交易中的国家安全问题，但她拒绝就乔-拜登总统的政府准备阻止美国钢铁公司与新日本钢铁公司合并的报道发表评论。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Thursday that the U.S. welcomes foreign direct investment and rigorously reviews deals for national security concerns, but declined to comment on reports that President Joe Biden's administration is poised to block the U.S. Steel-Nippon Steel merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-treasury-chief-yellen-has-no-comment-us-steel-nippon-review-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JNUBI43YZPLTKJX4JLJA5PUGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通称，尽管降息，但现金可能在数月内保持吸引力]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）的分析师说，迫在眉睫的降息可能不会立即刺激人们蜂拥抛出类似现金的工具，因为一些短期政府债券的收益率可能需要几个月的时间才能低于长期债务的收益率。【原文：Looming interest rate cuts may not immediately spur a rush out of cash-like instruments, as yields on some shorter-dated government bonds could take months to fall below those on longer-term debt, analysts at JPMorgan said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/cash-could-stay-attractive-months-despite-rate-cuts-jp-morgan-says-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QPXRLZN7ZNPRXK2IG5R4XKA3PU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:31:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[车队工会将于 9 月 16 日会见副总统哈里斯]]></title><description><![CDATA[民主党总统候选人卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）将于 9 月 16 日与国际卡车司机兄弟会（International Brotherhood of Teamsters）会面，该工会正在考虑是否为其总统竞选背书。【原文：Democratic presidential candidate Kamala Harris will meet with the International Brotherhood of Teamsters on Sept. 16 as the union considers a potential presidential endorsement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/teamsters-union-meet-with-vp-harris-sept-16-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPMEQ6FFMVLCXE6EGVD2FAPQK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息称法国埃利斯公司竞购美国制服供应商 Vestis]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟知内情的人士透露，法国工作场所用品供应商 Elis SA 已向 Vestis 提出收购要约，Vestis 是 Aramark 公司的前制服租赁业务。【原文：French workplace supplies provider Elis SA has approached Vestis , the former uniform rentals business of Aramark , with an acquisition offer, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/frances-elis-has-bid-us-uniform-supplier-vestis-sources-say-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECV6XTV7WBICFJQPQRU26HQ3TY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:10:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，CBOE 与英国公司合作推出美国私人股票交易平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，美国交易所运营商 CBOE 正在与一家总部位于伦敦的科技公司 Globacap 合作，创建一个美国紧密持股公司股票交易平台。【原文：U.S. exchange operator CBOE is partnering with a London-based tech firm, Globacap, to create a U.S. trading platform for shares of closely held companies, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/cboe-partners-with-uk-firm-launch-us-private-share-trading-platform-bloomberg-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPI27DMHLVKDDAQDUNV4RP5P34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[万豪称大中华区预订窗口期缩短至三天以内]]></title><description><![CDATA[酒店运营商万豪国际集团（Marriott International）周四表示，大中华区的一项关键预订指标目前已不足三天，在世界第二大经济体不确定性上升的背景下，旅游计划的谨慎性进一步增强。【原文：Hotel operator Marriott International said on Thursday a key bookings metric in Greater China is now under three days, amplifying caution around travel plans amid rising uncertainty in the world's second-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/marriott-says-booking-window-greater-china-down-under-three-days-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNM6SNPR5NPXRLSAPVYPCLCJPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦警告称终止美国清洁能源税收抵免将提高消费者成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周四警告说，任何试图削减拜登政府的清洁能源税收抵免政策的行为都将提高家庭的成本，并危及正在创造就业机会的美国制造业新投资。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Thursday warned that any attempts to roll back the Biden administration's clean energy tax credits would raise costs for families and jeopardize new investments in U.S. manufacturing that are creating jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/yellen-warns-that-ending-us-clean-energy-tax-credits-would-raise-consumer-costs-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3TGR6YTLVJEPAHLXBI4JDSHOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美洲开发银行在美国法院起诉前总裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[中美洲经济一体化银行（Central American Bank for Economic Integration）周四表示，已向美国地方法院提起诉讼，指控其前总裁违反一系列市场法规。【原文：The Central American Bank for Economic Integration has filed a lawsuit against its former president in a U.S. district court for allegedly violating a slew of market regulations, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/central-american-development-bank-sues-former-president-us-court-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X6L6AUUTDRK6XJBAXZJJ255PHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院小组将就俄罗斯武器问题质询美国半导体公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院常设调查小组委员会周四表示，将就俄罗斯在乌克兰战争中部署的武器中使用美国制造的半导体一事与四大半导体公司举行听证会。【原文：The U.S. Senate Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations said Thursday it will hold a hearing with four major semiconductor companies on the use American-manufactured semiconductors in Russian weapons deployed in the war in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senate-panel-question-us-semiconductor-firms-russian-weapons-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNV5CKZLNRNUVJY6QE5MV636V4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院做出裁决后，美国证券交易委员会放弃内部渎职诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会上个月要求撤销其内部法官正在审理的所有针对会计师的不当行为诉讼，法律专家认为，这是最高法院最近的一项裁决正在削弱该机构执法权力的一个新迹象。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission last month asked for the dismissal of all active misconduct proceedings against accountants sitting before its in-house judges, which legal experts said was a fresh sign that a recent Supreme Court ruling is curtailing the agency's enforcement powers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sec-abandons-in-house-malpractice-suits-after-supreme-court-ruling-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHB7AJWFU5LUTIOQFEQXSXCOUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:08:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snap 因未能保护儿童免受性剥削被新墨西哥州起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[新墨西哥州周四表示，它对 Snapchat 的所有者 Snap Inc 提起诉讼，指控该消息应用程序的政策和设计功能为分享儿童性剥削材料提供了便利。【原文：New Mexico said on Thursday it filed a lawsuit against Snapchat owner Snap Inc , alleging that the messaging app's policies and design features facilitate the sharing of child sexual exploitation material.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/snap-sued-by-new-mexico-over-failure-protect-children-sexual-exploitation-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZBNXZGPZUNMIDKRGYHS3MMPGWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西大法官要求最高法院合议庭审查对 X 禁令的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份文件显示，巴西大法官努内斯-马克斯（Nunes Marques）已决定要求最高法院全体成员审查政党新党（Partido Novo）提出的质疑社交媒体平台 X 在巴西被暂停服务的案件。【原文：Brazilian Justice Nunes Marques has decided to ask the full Supreme Court to review a case filed by political party Partido Novo challenging the suspension of social media platform X in the country, a document showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-justice-asks-full-supreme-court-review-challenge-x-ban-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LNNLPWF5BLXVPJVFNOXEIH3II</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:36:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者就服装工人权利问题对耐克施加压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威主权财富基金承诺支持一项决议，要求耐克公司考虑如何改善服装厂的工作条件。【原文：Investor pressure on Nike is building ahead of Tuesday's annual shareholder meeting, with Norway's sovereign wealth fund pledging to back a resolution demanding the company consider ways it can improve working conditions at garment factories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/investor-pressure-nike-builds-over-garment-workers-rights-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QULJY7FIEBPYZBWBDAMIBZYMSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:33:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，OpenAI 考虑为其人工智能聊天机器人提供更高的订阅价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周四报道，OpenAI 高层已经讨论了为即将推出的大型语言模型（如注重推理的 Strawberry 和被称为 Orion 的新旗舰 LLM）提供更高价订阅的问题。【原文：OpenAI executives have discussed higher-priced subscriptions for upcoming large language models, such as its reasoning-focused Strawberry and a new flagship LLM dubbed Orion, the Information reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-considers-pricier-subscriptions-its-chatbot-ai-information-reports-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHD6D2GWZ5KEND5JRWZZ42QS3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:19:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，欧佩克+同意将十月增产推迟两个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+组织的两位消息人士周四告诉路透社，在原油价格创下九个月来的最低点后，欧佩克+已同意推迟10月和11月的石油增产计划。【原文：OPEC+ has agreed to delay a planned October oil output increase for October and November after crude prices hit their lowest in nine months, two sources from the producers group told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-agrees-delay-october-output-hike-two-months-sources-say-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SWV7GEL4NOPDP2QR6IBJBFWYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行 2024 年第二季度利润猛增 11%，原因是支出减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦存款保险公司（Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation）周四发布报告称，2024 年第二季度美国银行业实现利润 715 亿美元，比上一季度增长 11.4%。【原文：The U.S. banking industry recorded profits of $71.5 billion in the second quarter of 2024, up 11.4% on the prior quarter, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation reported Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-profits-jump-11-q2-2024-expenses-shrink-fdic-says-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UF5OUVIGUFPW5AQI6N5NKOORUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国服务业 8 月份保持稳定；就业降温]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份，美国服务业活动保持稳定，但就业增长放缓，这与劳动力市场放缓的趋势一致。【原文：U.S. services sector activity was steady in August, but employment gains slowed, consistent with an easing labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-service-sector-steady-august-employment-cooling-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJ2JLVOFUROKPJ3QG2GC7QQZMU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[应用数字公司与包括英伟达在内的投资者达成融资协议，业绩大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[应用数字公司（Applied Digital）周四早盘股价飙升近 43%，此前该数据中心运营商表示将从包括芯片巨头英伟达（Nvidia）在内的一批投资者那里获得 1.6 亿美元融资。【原文：Applied Digital shares soared nearly 43% in early trading on Thursday, after the data center operator said it would receive $160 million in financing from a group of investors, including chip giant Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/applied-digital-surges-funding-deal-with-investors-including-nvidia-2024-09-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFGFHQRUINPRXMBN5PEU4IT2XE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>