<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:08:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:08:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业经济出现扩大裂痕，成本上升，就业岗位消失]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国农业带，如今的时局令人沮丧。农民们正面临又一个价格低迷、成本高昂的季节，他们不得不艰难抉择——究竟该如何经营，甚至是否该继续经营下去。就在种植户们急需资金周转之际，银行却切断了部分人的贷款渠道。随着肉类加工厂关闭和农机制造商缩减规模，成千上万的工人正面临失业。【原文：Across the U.S. farm belt, these have become depressing times. Farmers are facing another season of low prices, high costs and difficult decisions about how — or whether — to keep operating. Banks are cutting off some growers just as they urgently need cash. Thousands of workers are losing jobs as meatpacking plants close and farm ​equipment makers scale back.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-farm-economy-shows-widening-cracks-costs-rise-jobs-vanish-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JZC5PAOLFIZRIGY5HRSD2S7MU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国FDA因安全性和有效性问题，在新推出的优惠券计划中推迟两项药物审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局已推迟对两款药物的审查，这两款药物原被选入特朗普政府的新快速审批计划。路透社获得的内部文件显示，该机构科学家对这两款药物的安全性和有效性提出质疑，其中包括一名患者在服用其中一种药物期间死亡的情况。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has delayed reviews of two drugs chosen for the Trump administration's new fast-track program after agency scientists flagged safety and efficacy concerns, including the death of a patient while taking one of the medicines, internal documents seen by Reuters show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-fda-delays-two-drug-reviews-new-voucher-program-after-safety-efficacy-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EPIXLPM25LJFJ5DYVNO6CHGHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市领涨板块呈现扩大迹象，科技股之外领域开始发力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在多年见证科技股引领美国牛市之后，投资者正押注此轮涨势将扩展至工业、医疗保健及小盘股领域，这些板块有望迎头赶上并确立市场主导地位。【原文：After years of watching technology stocks drive the U.S. bull market, investors are betting the rally will broaden to industrial, healthcare and small-cap companies, with a chance they can catch up and assert market leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stocks-leadership-showing-signs-broadening-beyond-tech-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRYB7FDZMFPXLBRXGFPMATHW3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电带动半导体板块反弹，华尔街期货走高；金融企业财报即将发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四美国股指期货上涨，台积电亮眼财报推动半导体股走高，金融巨头财报发布前市场情绪升温。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Thursday after TSMC's blowout quarterly results fueled a rally in semiconductor shares ahead of earnings from financial heavyweights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-rise-tsmc-sparks-semiconductor-rally-financial-earnings-deck-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYNZ3XTXIJJVXMDLDCL7OHR5S4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国媒体监管机构称Snapchat加强了非法内容风险检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国通信管理局（Ofcom）周四表示，社交媒体平台Snapchat在去年该媒体监管机构提出担忧后，已显著改善其非法内容风险评估机制。【原文：Britain's Ofcom said on Thursday social media platform Snapchat has significantly improved its illegal content risk assessment following concerns raised by the media regulator last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-media-regulator-says-snapchat-improves-illegal-content-risk-checks-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOJEX4LLVVLG5DGYJYSMZYAZTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银集团首席执行官埃莫蒂强调希望由内部人士接任]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥·埃尔莫蒂希望继任者能从银行内部选拔，他在周四发表于瑞士《每日导报》的专访中如是表示。【原文：UBS CEO Sergio Ermotti hopes his successor will be a candidate from within the bank, he told Swiss newspaper Tages-Anzeiger in an interview published on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-ceo-ermotti-underlines-his-desire-internal-successor-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYYAR2UCFJOBBPYCDIDFR5YCLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:24:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基将恢复苏伊士运河航线以服务MECL航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦航运巨头马士基周四宣布，其连接中东、印度与美国东海岸的MECL航线将恢复经红海和苏伊士运河的航行。【原文：Shipping group Maersk will resume sailings via the Red Sea and the Suez Canal for its MECL service, connecting the Middle East and India with the U.S. east coast, the Danish company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/maersk-resume-suez-canal-sailings-mecl-service-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUNG454L4FI5FMSE3RYVXM3ZEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲律宾因儿童安全问题寻求封禁Grok应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲律宾信息通信技术部长周四表示，该国正着手阻止埃隆·马斯克的人工智能聊天机器人Grok进入市场，因其存在生成性化图像的风险，包括可能危及儿童安全的内容。【原文：The Philippines is moving to block Elon Musk's AI chatbot Grok amid concerns about its ability to generate sexualised images, including content that could pose child safety risks, the secretary of information and communications technology said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/philippines-seeks-block-access-grok-child-safety-concerns-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEUQNXYV5VOAJCZ6RND67OIIMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025年加拿大房屋销售因关税冲击下滑1.9%]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大房地产协会周四公布的数据显示，去年加拿大房屋销售量出现年度下滑，12月销售量和房价均出现下跌。【原文：Canadian home sales posted an annual decline last year as sales and prices fell in December, ​data from the Canadian Real Estate Association showed on ‌Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadian-home-sales-fall-19-2025-tariff-shock-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76CRI4Q4Y5NVXJBBS4EHFOF62I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASML市值突破5000亿美元，台积电财报点燃半导体板块涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[ASML股价周四飙升至历史新高，推动其市值突破5000亿美元大关，巩固了其作为欧洲市值最高企业的领先地位。【原文：Shares in ASML surged to a new all-time high on Thursday, pushing its market capitalisation past the $500 billion milestone and cementing its lead as Europe’s most valuable company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/asml-tops-500-billion-market-cap-tsmc-results-ignite-semis-rally-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4VOKN44MROBHECZ4PUAOAXIBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构表示将继续调查X平台深度伪造内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国媒体监管机构通信管理局（Ofcom）周四表示，尽管欢迎该公司近期政策调整，但仍将继续对埃隆·马斯克旗下X平台的Grok人工智能聊天机器人涉及性亲密深度伪造图像一事展开正式调查。【原文：British media regulator Ofcom said on Thursday its formal investigation into Elon Musk's X over its Grok AI chatbot's sexually intimate deepfake images would continue, even as it welcomed the company's recent policy change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/uk-regulator-says-its-x-deepfake-probe-will-continue-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUBEGNAEIFIABHKTRW7WIVPBHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[维基百科所有者与微软、Meta达成人工智能内容训练合作协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[维基百科周四宣布与微软、Meta和亚马逊等多家科技巨头建立合作伙伴关系，标志着这家非营利组织在将科技公司对内容的依赖转化为商业价值方面迈出了重要一步。【原文：Wikipedia on Thursday unveiled partnerships with several Big Tech companies including Microsoft , Meta and Amazon , marking a major step up in the non-profit's ability to monetize tech firms' reliance on its content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/wikipedia-owner-signs-microsoft-meta-ai-content-training-deals-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCIESMMCZJPSLKZT4LYBBOR56U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:34:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，和记黄埔寻求旗下零售业务以300亿美元估值进行第二季度首次公开募股。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，香港跨国企业和记黄埔有限公司正寻求为旗下零售业务屈臣氏集团筹备香港及伦敦上市事宜，估值约300亿美元，最早可能于第二季度启动。【原文：Hong Kong conglomerate CK Hutchison Holdings Ltd is seeking a valuation of around $30 billion for retail unit A.S. Watson Group's listings in Hong Kong and London as soon as the second quarter, two people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ck-hutchison-seeks-30-billion-valuation-retail-units-q2-ipo-sources-say-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAY4UY4DFBNAHDEQWG3I6AFT3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:16:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱立信将在瑞典裁员1600人]]></title><description><![CDATA[电信设备集团爱立信周四宣布，计划在瑞典裁员约1600人。【原文：Telecoms equipment group Ericsson plans to lay off some 1,600 employees in Sweden, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/ericsson-shed-1600-jobs-sweden-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBOUSCZKONJDLKXEVDW4J7OPOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国产业部长表示将持续关注美国芯片关税政策以最大限度降低影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国产业通商资源部部长金正宽周四表示，政府将持续关注美国对特定人工智能半导体芯片加征关税的进展，以最大限度减轻对本土产业的影响。该部声明称。【原文：South Korean Industry Minister Kim Jung-kwan said on Thursday that the government will keep monitoring developments on U.S. tariffs on certain AI semiconductor chips to minimise the impact on local industries, according to a ministry statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-keep-monitoring-us-chip-tariffs-minimise-impact-industry-minister-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXZMML6JUBN7RPDH5YEOHMFQYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:53:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[裕信银行否认有意收购蒙特帕斯基银行股份的传闻]]></title><description><![CDATA[裕信银行周四驳斥了有关其有意收购西恩纳蒙特帕斯基银行股权的传闻，称这些传闻"纯属猜测且毫无根据"。【原文：UniCredit on Thursday dismissed as "speculative in nature and unjustified" rumours of it being interested in buying a stake in Banca Monte dei Paschi di Siena .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-dismisses-rumours-about-mps-stake-says-it-studies-all-ma-options-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D62NFCYPDZMIVIBHEL6D7TVGCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:36:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper将于第二季度初完成对JDE Peet's的收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper与荷兰投资公司Kodiak BidCo于周四对咖啡茶饮集团JDE Peet's发起全现金收购要约，预计将于第二季度初完成交易。【原文：Keurig Dr Pepper and Dutch vehicle Kodiak BidCo launched on Thursday an all-cash takeover bid for coffee and tea group JDE Peet's , which they expect to complete early in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/keurig-dr-pepper-launches-all-cash-takeover-bid-jde-peets-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXIWK6C3NBPE3PKA47CHRCXZBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国称贝森特言论凸显外汇稳定对美韩合作的重要性]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国高级官员周四表示，美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特近期关于韩元汇率的言论，凸显了外汇稳定对首尔与华盛顿双边经济合作的重要性。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent's recent comments on the Korean won underscore the importance of foreign exchange stability for bilateral economic cooperation between Seoul and Washington, a senior South Korean official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bessents-comments-show-importance-fx-stability-us-south-korea-cooperation-seoul-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UEZVOKQWKVLOFL6GX4JBCV6RLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:21:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊推出基于欧洲的新云服务以解决用户担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊旗下AWS云服务周四推出全新云服务，该服务完全部署于欧洲。此举旨在解决用户对主要美国供应商数据安全性的担忧，为欧洲大陆提供独立的替代方案。【原文：Amazon's AWS launched a new cloud service located entirely in Europe on Thursday, addressing user concerns about the data security delivered by mainly U.S.-based providers by offering the continent's own independent alternative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-launches-new-europe-based-cloud-service-address-user-concerns-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2CPM2AU7VM5DEVL6KFLYV7OQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士竞争监管机构对微软许可费展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士竞争委员会周四表示，已对微软在该国的许可费问题启动初步调查。【原文：Switzerland's competition commission said on Thursday it launched a preliminary investigation into Microsoft's licensing fees in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swiss-competition-authority-opens-probe-into-microsoft-licensing-fees-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIBFWXCSIFMQZHZSQWQJBNLQUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨克斯全球公司获得美国法院批准4亿美元纾困融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名破产法官周三初步批准了萨克斯全球公司的破产融资方案，允许该公司提取4亿美元新资金，尽管其分道扬镳的商业伙伴亚马逊公司对此提出异议。【原文：A U.S. bankruptcy judge on Wednesday granted ​initial approval of Saks Global’s bankruptcy financing, allowing the company to draw on $400 million in new ‌cash despite an objection from Saks' estranged business partner Amazon.com 
 .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/saks-global-obtains-us-court-approval-400-million-rescue-financing-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEAQ6BA7HZOIVB5G6NHF3YJ6NE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普总统接受路透社采访的五大看点]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三在椭圆形办公室对美国总统唐纳德·特朗普进行了专访。以下是这场30分钟对话的若干要点：【原文：Reuters sat down with U.S. President Donald Trump for an interview in the Oval Office on Wednesday. Here are some takeaways from the 30-minute exchange:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/five-takeaways-reuters-interview-president-trump-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBQ4S7JW6VIXVMZMY6TC4WNY2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第四季度利润跃升35%创纪录，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大代工芯片制造商台积电周四公布，第四季度净利润飙升35%，不仅超出市场预期，更创下历史新高。这得益于人工智能应用领域对半导体需求的激增。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest contract chipmaker, posted a 35% jump in fourth-quarter net profit on Thursday, beating market forecasts and hitting a record as it benefited from surging demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsmc-q4-profit-jumps-35-record-beats-expectations-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWJYUNMIARNMVGS3BLXIIISJH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：大盘轮动持续进行]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文·巴克兰带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q35MC6ZJV5PVZOJFLVT4CEGLIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚力拓投资者对潜在嘉能可交易的合理性提出质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚历史最悠久、规模最大的投资机构之一，近日加入了国内日益高涨的质疑声浪，对力拓集团潜在收购嘉能可的交易提出质疑，质疑该拟议合并的合理性及时机。【原文：One of Australia's oldest and largest investors has added to the growing local chorus of concerns about Rio Tinto's , potential acquisition of Glencore , questioning the proposed tie-up's merits and timing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-rio-tinto-investor-raises-concerns-over-merits-potential-glencore-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJRPJHDMBZJAXOIJRU2OM7DH2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:12:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软创纪录收购土壤碳信用额，数据中心激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软已与Indigo Carbon达成协议，将购买创纪录的285万份与美国再生农业相关的土壤碳信用额。尽管人工智能相关的排放量激增，这家科技巨头仍致力于在2030年前实现"碳负排放"目标。【原文：Microsoft has agreed with Indigo Carbon to buy a record 2.85 million soil carbon credits linked to regenerative agriculture in the United States, as the tech giant aims to become "carbon negative" by 2030 despite surging emissions linked to AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/microsoft-record-deal-soil-carbon-credits-data-centres-surge-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JICVRS4IGRNXJBTJYKV2N3FKOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将在9月底前再次加息至1%或更高水平，可能提前至7月实施。]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家表示，日本央行很可能等到7月才会再次上调关键利率，其中超过75%的经济学家预计，该利率将从当前三十年来的低点0.75%升至9月的1%或更高水平。【原文：The Bank of Japan will likely wait until July before raising its key interest rate again, economists say, with more than 75% of them expecting it to climb to 1% or higher by September from the current three-decade high of just 0.75%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-raise-rates-again-1-or-higher-by-end-september-possibly-by-july-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6WOMW5X6ZPYVODQJYV7VN53GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经亚洲报道：中国拟制定英伟达H200芯片采购规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经亚洲》周四报道，中国正着手制定规则，限制国内先进人工智能芯片企业从英伟达等外国制造商处采购的数量。该报道援引了两位知情人士的消息。【原文：China is working to set rules on how many advanced artificial intelligence chip companies can buy from foreign makers such as Nvidia , Nikkei Asia reported on Thursday, citing two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-drafting-purchase-rules-nvidia-h200-chips-nikkei-asia-reports-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IL72LVLW5IJLP45P6XKHIV7CM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:21:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度法院就2018年沃尔玛交易税务案作出不利于Tiger Global的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度最高法院裁定，老虎环球基金2018年以16亿美元将印度电商企业Flipkart的股权出售给沃尔玛的交易需缴纳税收。这项具有里程碑意义的裁决支持了新德里政府对企业运用国际税收协定的立场。【原文：India's top court has ruled that Tiger Global's $1.6 billion stake sale in Indian e-commerce firm Flipkart to Walmart in 2018 is subject to taxes, handing a win to New Delhi in a landmark ruling on use of international tax treaties by companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/india-court-rule-tiger-globals-2018-deal-with-walmart-landmark-tax-case-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIIHWXNSU5KIHC7WCZXGTJK24Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR为第二只亚洲私募信贷基金筹集25亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球投资公司KKR周四宣布，其第二只信用基金已完成25亿美元的募资，该基金专注于亚太地区私营部门发起的优质信贷投资。【原文：Global investment firm KKR said on Thursday that it has completed a $2.5 billion fundraising for its second credit fund focused on privately originated performing credit investments in the Asia-Pacific region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kkr-secures-25-billion-second-asia-private-credit-fund-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MU4XT77VNP2TBHLRONLCCPPRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>