<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:05:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:05:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部命令国家安全律师审查肯尼迪事件文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封电子邮件称，美国司法部正在命令一些处理敏感国家安全事务的律师紧急审查将于周二公布的前总统约翰-肯尼迪遇刺案的记录。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department is ordering some of its lawyers who handle sensitive national-security matters to urgently review records from the assassination of former President John F. Kennedy that are due be released on Tuesday, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-justice-department-orders-national-security-lawyers-review-jfk-documents-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3GJOXGYJRM3PO4QW6FUASUX4U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:23:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府在法院下令后恢复 2.45 万名被解雇员工的工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府在法庭文件中首次承认解雇了近 2.5 万名新近雇用的工人，并表示在法官裁定解雇这些工人可能违法后，各机构正在努力让他们全部复职。【原文：The Trump administration in court filings has for the first time acknowledged that it fired nearly 25,000 recently hired workers, and said agencies were working to bring all of them back after a judge ruled that their terminations were likely illegal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trump-administration-reinstating-24500-fired-workers-after-court-order-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQOLMC4NZFIMTOYCRT2SLTZQCY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:46:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月份房屋开工强劲反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[2 月份，美国单户住宅建筑业大幅反弹，但关税和劳动力短缺导致的建筑成本上升威胁着经济复苏。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding rebounded sharply in February, but rising construction costs from tariffs and labor shortages threaten the recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-housing-starts-rebound-strongly-february-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFWZPKGVWRMEPO5M7ON3BTUOQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普普京的最新动态：美俄领导人将讨论乌克兰停火计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[双方领导人将讨论美国提议的 30 天休战。【原文：The leaders will discuss the U.S.-proposed 30-day truce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-putin-updates-us-russian-leaders-discuss-plans-ukraine-ceasefire-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFK6426ABNG77LDQF575ZME4HE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:23:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普面临向法院解释驱逐委内瑞拉人原因的最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府将在周二中午的最后期限前提供有关其驱逐委内瑞拉人的详细情况，尽管法官发布了临时驱逐禁令。【原文：The Trump administration faces a midday deadline on Tuesday to provide details about plane loads of Venezuelans it deported despite a judge issuing a temporary ban on removing them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trump-faces-court-deadline-explain-deportation-venezuelans-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUUQLAASCBO4HIAGHMDK367IVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:13:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将公布 8 万页肯尼迪遇刺案资料]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统计划于本周二公布约 8 万页与 1963 年约翰-肯尼迪总统遇刺事件有关的材料，以兑现他在竞选时做出的承诺，为这起发生在得克萨斯州的震惊事件提供更多的透明度。【原文：President Donald Trump plans to release about 80,000 pages of material related to the 1963 assassination of President John F. Kennedy on Tuesday, seeking to honor his campaign promise to provide more transparency about the shock event in Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-release-80000-pages-jfk-assassination-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LELWQQMR5IXXERT7FM7VAZPIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道盖茨警告白宫他无法弥补美国全球卫生资金的缺口]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，比尔-盖茨正亲自游说特朗普政府官员继续资助全球范围内的医疗卫生项目，从儿童疫苗接种到艾滋病治疗，并警告说他的基金会不能插手填补缺口。【原文：Bill Gates is personally lobbying Trump administration officials to keep funding health programs worldwide, from childhood vaccination to HIV treatment, and warning that his foundation cannot step in to fill gaps, two sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/gates-warns-white-house-he-cant-fill-shortfalls-us-global-health-funding-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VU6M4NLVUVIIDOXEJU4EIQVLKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家称，特朗普政府在打击移民活动中很可能越权行事]]></title><description><![CDATA[法律专家说，特朗普政府很可能越权援引了很少适用的法律来为其大肆打击移民的部分行动辩护。【原文：The Trump administration has likely exceeded its authority in invoking rarely applied laws to justify parts of its wide-ranging immigration crackdown, legal experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-likely-overstepped-authority-immigration-crackdown-experts-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JA2D4NMAYNMTHMZRADHWLIZ34I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司支线喷气机机翼撞上纽约机场跑道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局称，达美航空公司一架支线飞机周日晚些时候在纽约拉瓜迪亚机场执行绕场飞行时撞上了跑道。【原文：A Delta Air Lines regional jet struck the runway at New York LaGuardia Airport late on Sunday while executing a go-around, the Federal Aviation Administration said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/delta-regional-jet-wing-struck-runway-new-york-airport-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BV72M2MXD5I7DGN637AGYVVKO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:45:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州逮捕涉嫌非法堕胎的助产士]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州总检察长周一表示，该州逮捕了一名助产士，指控其在休斯顿地区提供非法堕胎服务并非法经营诊所网络。【原文：Texas arrested a midwife for allegedly providing illegal abortions and illegally operating a network of clinics in the Houston area, the state attorney general said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/texas-arrests-midwife-allegedly-providing-illegal-abortions-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5H6NMZSQFRKEVFEFJLEGSW57TM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WNBA-斯帕克斯队的布林克对要求男队员参加训练感到不满]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶火花队前锋卡梅隆-布林克（Cameron Brink）说，她在网上看到球队号召男队员参加练习队选拔的消息后感到非常反感。【原文：Los Angeles Sparks forward Cameron Brink said she was revolted by the response she had seen online to a call by the team for male players to try out for the practice squad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/basketball/wnba-sparks-brink-unhappy-with-call-male-practice-players-2025-03-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHZTXN7CXRMCVG4C5PA2HERX6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府旨在长期加快肉类加工速度]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周一表示，计划永久性地允许美国家禽和猪肉加工厂更快地运营，这引发了倡导团体对工人健康和食品安全的担忧。【原文：The Trump administration said on Monday it plans to permanently allow U.S. poultry and pork processing plants to operate more quickly, raising concerns among advocacy groups about worker health and food safety.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-aims-make-faster-meat-processing-permanent-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHUYHSWN6JIB3H7SNY6JZ6NRQQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普任命前顾问弗林为西点军校参观委员会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一任命迈克尔-弗林（Michael Flynn）为美国西点军校（U.S. Military Academy at West Point）访客委员会成员。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday named Michael Flynn, his former national security adviser who challenged the 2020 election results and pushed baseless conspiracy claims, to be on the board of visitors for the U.S. Military Academy at West Point.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-names-former-adviser-flynn-west-point-board-visitors-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZOTTD5C6RMQ5MSMF57D74ANHY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普撤销对拜登子女亨特和阿什利的特勤保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一撤销了对前总统乔-拜登的子女亨特-拜登和阿什利-拜登的特勤保护。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday revoked secret service protection for former president Joe Biden's children Hunter Biden and Ashley Biden.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-revokes-secret-service-protection-bidens-children-hunter-ashley-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIBGS3IIAZKLJBBICJ2U57ZODA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:26:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈佛为家庭收入在 20 万美元或以下的学生提供免学费待遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈佛大学周一表示，将对来自年收入低于 20 万美元家庭的本科生免收学费，还将为年收入低于 10 万美元的学生支付医疗保险、住房和其他费用。【原文：Harvard University said on Monday it would make tuition free for undergraduate students from families earning less than $200,000 a year and would also cover health insurance, housing and other expenses for those earning less than $100,000.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/harvard-offers-free-tuition-students-families-earning-200000-or-less-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HAPSB5DHNKYVK66IO4DX5W25I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 22:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名共和航空首席执行官布莱恩-贝德福德担任美国联邦航空局局长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一在社交媒体上表示，他提名共和航空公司首席执行官布莱恩-贝德福德（Bryan Bedford）担任美国联邦航空管理局局长。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump nominated Republic Airways CEO Bryan Bedford as the administrator of the Federal Aviation Administration, he said on social media on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-nominates-republic-airways-ceo-bryan-bedford-us-faa-head-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVC5WFCKTFOPXCTOELL4L4SRAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称美国航空局在法院下令后恢复被解雇员工的工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）的一个工会周一表示，在马里兰州的一名联邦法官下令让 132 名于 2 月 14 日被解雇的员工复职后，联邦航空管理局将恢复他们的工作。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration is reinstating 132 employees who were fired on February 14 after a federal judge in Maryland ordered their return, a union said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-aviation-agency-reinstating-fired-employees-after-court-order-says-union-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRGIVEZF3ZMZZBOGAGIATVYNTM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:17:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国民权机构就工作场所 DEI 政策向律师事务所发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国负责执行禁止工作场所歧视法律的机构负责人周一警告 20 家大型律师事务所，它们旨在促进多元化、公平和包容的就业政策可能是非法的。【原文：The head of the U.S. agency that enforces laws banning workplace discrimination on Monday warned 20 major law firms that their employment policies meant to boost diversity, equity and inclusion may be illegal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-civil-rights-agency-warns-law-firms-over-workplace-dei-policies-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4V7OOJ5ZLNL45LBWYTZILBFBAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:06:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名美联储理事鲍曼为负责监管的副主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在社交媒体上发文称，他提名美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）担任负责监管事务的副主席。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump nominated Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman to be vice chair for supervision, he said in a post on social media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-nominates-federal-reserve-governor-bowman-vice-chair-supervision-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTZESGQPMBMX7LHLCTE6XR546U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称周二将公布约 8 万页肯尼迪档案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他的政府将于周二公开约 8 万页与前总统约翰-肯尼迪有关的文件。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday his administration will make public around 80,000 pages of files related to former president John F. Kennedy on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/around-80000-pages-jfk-files-will-be-released-tuesday-trump-says-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FM2SWFZTABMLBJIV5TE5Q3TNXI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:44:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院委员会要求提供中国电信黑客攻击记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院一个委员会周一要求国土安全部交出有关联邦政府应对中国大规模黑客事件的文件。【原文：A U.S. House of Representatives committee on Monday asked the Homeland Security Department to turn over documents on the federal government's response to reported massive Chinese hacking incidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-committee-seeks-record-chinese-telecom-hacking-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYY5GFLMMBMPHPAA4XJCOO46GU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿特区最高检察官宣布调查选举舞弊，但权限不明]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封内部邮件，唐纳德-特朗普总统在华盛顿特区的最高联邦检察官周一宣布将推动调查选举舞弊案件的新工作，但尚不清楚他的办公室在这方面将有多大权力。【原文：President Donald Trump's top federal prosecutor in Washington, D.C., on Monday announced a new push to investigate election fraud cases, according to an internal email seen by Reuters, though it was not clear how much power his office will have to do so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/washington-dcs-top-prosecutor-announces-election-fraud-probe-though-authority-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KGJC2VZHRNQVGUVGCCZMQQ65Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国提供 5,700 万美元资金帮助密歇根反应堆重启]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部周一表示，已为霍尔泰克公司位于密歇根州的帕利塞德核电站提供了高达 15.2 亿美元贷款担保中的 5700 万美元。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy said on Monday it has disbursed $57 million of an up to $1.52 billion loan guarantee for Holtec's Palisades nuclear plant in Michigan, which the company hopes will be the first U.S. commercial reactor to restart after ceasing operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-releases-57-million-financing-help-reopen-michigan-reactor-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJSW6YI44FMHLCYC2BADLZWHHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称被驱逐至黎巴嫩的医生手机上有 "同情 "真主党的照片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当局周一表示，他们上周将一名罗德岛医生驱逐回黎巴嫩，因为在她的手机删除项目文件夹中发现了真主党前长期领导人和武装分子的 "同情照片和视频"。【原文：U.S. authorities on Monday said they deported a Rhode Island doctor to Lebanon last week after discovering "sympathetic photos and videos" of the former longtime leader of Hezbollah and militants in her cell phone's deleted items folder.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/doctor-deported-lebanon-had-photos-sympathetic-hezbollah-phone-us-says-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWGVLZW2CRLWRNZ7TFI6O5MXZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:35:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德雷克唱片公司称应驳回对拉马尔的《Not Like Us》提起的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[德雷克（Drake）的长期唱片公司环球音乐集团（Universal Music Group）周一要求驳回他因推广肯德里克-拉马尔（Kendrick Lamar）的格莱美获奖单曲《不像我们》（Not Like Us）而提起的诽谤诉讼。【原文：Drake's longtime label Universal Music Group on Monday sought a dismissal of his defamation lawsuit over its promotion of Kendrick Lamar's Grammy-winning single "Not Like Us," the biggest hit of a barrage of diss tracks between the two rappers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/drakes-label-says-lawsuit-over-lamars-not-like-us-should-be-dismissed-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CVOR7DT7BOTDJYE6DQTT3S2H4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:12:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[柯南-奥布莱恩将于 2026 年重返奥斯卡颁奖典礼担任主持人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电影艺术与科学学院（Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences）周一表示，喜剧演员、深夜电视节目主持人柯南-奥布莱恩（Conan O'Brien）将于 2026 年再次担任年度奥斯卡颁奖典礼的司仪。【原文：Comedian and late-night TV show host Conan O'Brien will return to emcee the annual Oscars ceremony for a second time in 2026, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/conan-obrien-return-oscars-host-2026-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Q347S7EUJNODOSWNLWEAQAO7E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:58:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国邮政局就零售租赁和伪造邮资问题寻求邮政总局团队的帮助]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国邮政总局局长路易斯-德乔伊（Louis DeJoy）周一表示，他已要求埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的邮政总局团队协助审查其零售中心续租事宜，并努力打击假冒邮资等问题。【原文：U.S. Postmaster General Louis DeJoy said Monday he had asked Elon Musk's DOGE team for assistance on a review of its retail center lease renewals and efforts to combat counterfeit postage among other issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-postal-service-seeks-doge-team-help-retail-leases-counterfeit-postage-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGBGQLTAAFNZNIYUD4NKRWBCMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA["布奇和苏尼 "宇航员准备在完成九个月的任务后于周二返航]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局（NASA）的两名宇航员布奇-威尔莫尔（Butch Wilmore）和苏尼-威廉姆斯（Suni Williams）已在国际空间站滞留了九个月，他们计划于周二清晨开始返回地球，踏上期待已久的回家之旅，为这次不同寻常的任务画上句号。【原文：Butch Wilmore and Suni Williams, two NASA astronauts who have been stuck on the International Space Station for nine months, are scheduled to begin their return to Earth early Tuesday morning on a long-awaited flight home to cap an unusual mission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/butch-suni-astronauts-prepare-tuesday-homecoming-after-nine-month-mission-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMBMHM5TVROZPNSQIFMQN62JMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国卫生机构认为缅因州关于变性运动员的政策属于歧视行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部周一表示，已认定缅因州教育当局允许变性女孩参加学校体育活动违反了禁止性别歧视的联邦法律。【原文：The U.S. Department of Health and Human Services said on Monday that is has determined Maine educational authorities are in violation of federal law prohibiting sex discrimination by allowing transgender girls to participate in school sports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-health-agency-finds-maines-policy-transgender-athletes-is-discrimination-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXC5VTC4ZJIQLMU2QOSFJXGFX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:33:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普最新消息：驱逐委内瑞拉人可能引发宪法冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[民权组织称，周末飞往萨尔瓦多的航班可能违反了法院命令。【原文：Civil rights groups said the weekend flights to El Salvador may have violated a court order.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-latest-deportation-venezuelans-sets-up-potential-constitutional-clash-2025-03-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7XD44XAMZA4LACNOA3RMDJPYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>