<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:46:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:46:40 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特称伯克希尔亏本出售派拉蒙股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）周六表示，伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）在亏损的情况下出售了其在派拉蒙公司的全部持股，他说这是他一个人的决定。【原文：Warren Buffett said on Saturday Berkshire Hathaway sold its entire holding in Paramount at a loss, a decision he said was his sole responsibility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-sold-entire-paramount-holdings-loss-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4GLJDUV4NJFNJ4T5OC5FFIONU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:59:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，中国平安投票反对续聘汇丰首席执行官为董事]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周六报道，汇丰控股公司最大的亚洲投资者--中国平安保险集团股份有限公司在该行股东大会上投票反对续聘离任首席执行官诺埃尔-奎恩（Noel Quinn）为董事。【原文：HSBC Holdings Plc's biggest Asian investor, China's Ping An Insurance Group Co, voted against the reappointment of departing chief executive Noel Quinn as a director at the bank's shareholder meeting, Bloomberg News reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ping-an-votes-against-reappointment-hsbc-ceo-director-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRJTRAEHONLQ5H5PDNDYLEQZJY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:48:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特称可能增加税收以抵消美国不断扩大的赤字]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）表示，他预计美国政府将增加税收以解决不断扩大的财政赤字问题，而不是减少支出。【原文：Warren Buffett said he expects the U.S. government to increase taxes to tackle widening fiscal deficits rather than reduce spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/warren-buffett-says-taxes-may-rise-offset-widening-us-deficits-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDXCOREXB5OSFOKVN72T5L4YZM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西航向其技术运营工会 AMFA 发出 72 小时停工通知]]></title><description><![CDATA[Onex Corp 旗下的 WestJet 航空公司周六表示，已向其技术操作工会‍飞机机械师兄弟会（AMFA）发出 72 小时停工通知。【原文：Onex Corp's WestJet on Saturday said that it has issued a 72-hour lockout notification to its technical operations union ‍Aircraft Mechanics Fraternal Association (AMFA).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/westjet-issues-72-hour-lockout-notification-its-tech-ops-union-amfa-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQQKN7GXBNK35ML7HROL54BFXQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:12:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴菲特在年会上谈接班人和伯克希尔的未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特周六在伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）的年度会议上发表讲话，向他的长期商业伙伴查理-芒格致敬，概述了被指定最终接替他的高管扩大后的角色，并讨论了伯克希尔公司的机遇。【原文：Warren Buffett took the stage at Berkshire Hathaway's annual meeting on Saturday, paying tribute to his longtime business partner Charlie Munger, outlining the expanded roles of the executives who are designated to eventually succeed him and discussing Berkshire's opportunities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/buffett-talks-succession-berkshires-future-annual-meeting-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFLXSWP3H5PNJHJG3KDC7Q4ZFY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔公司高管称针对公用事业公司的野火索赔 "毫无根据]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）领导的企业集团伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）的一位高管周六表示，该公司将抗击因野火而对其公用事业业务提起的所有诉讼，因为这些案件 "毫无根据"。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway , the conglomerate led by Warren Buffett, will fight all lawsuits brought against its utility business due to wildfires as the cases are "unfounded," a top executive said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-exec-calls-wildfire-claims-against-utility-unfounded-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EX4RJW3RJJNZZMOYPVBJLJHIDI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 16:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔利润创历史新高，现金增至 1,890 亿美元，但苹果股份减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway Inc）周六公布了创纪录的季度利润，这主要得益于其保险业务的强劲表现。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway Inc posted a record quarterly profit on Saturday, boosted by strength in its insurance operations, and appears to have sold a significant number of Apple shares as its cash stake swelled to $189 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-has-record-profit-cash-soars-189-bln-apple-stake-sinks-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHZ5SSONWFOHLAO3XHXQ6E4UTM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 12:51:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔营业利润创纪录，净利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway Inc）周六公布了创纪录的季度利润，这主要得益于保险承销收入的大幅增长。【原文：Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway Inc posted a record quarterly profit on Saturday, bolstered by a significant increase in income from insurance underwriting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-posts-record-operating-profit-net-declines-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIVBFZIUCJJDJP4SRPQLE4WZYI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 12:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔股东来到奥马哈，年会拉开帷幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）将在周六举行的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）年会上占据中心位置，股东们将前来观看这位著名的投资家及其预期的继任者。【原文：Warren Buffett will take center stage at Berkshire Hathaway's annual meeting on Saturday, as shareholders descend on to watch the famed investor as well as his expected successor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-shareholders-descend-omaha-annual-meeting-kicks-off-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LU4P47A6VJLNOX55PGFCOOUKM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 10:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯：通胀目标对实现物价稳定 "至关重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，他认为美国中央银行 2% 的通胀目标对其实现物价稳定的努力 "至关重要"。【原文：New York Federal Reserve Bank President John Williams on Friday said he believes the U.S. central bank's 2% target for inflation is "critical" to its efforts to achieve price stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-williams-inflation-target-critical-achieving-stable-prices-2024-05-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5V37LBMKZK5VOWZKZU6E6K62M</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:17:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比美国利率路径 "点阵图 "需要更多背景信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，美国联邦储备委员会应加强其对决策者利率路径看法的季度 "点阵图"，将每个人的经济预期纳入其中。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve should beef up its quarterly "dot plot" of policymakers' interest-rate-path views by including the individual economic expectations that inform each one, Austan Goolsbee, president of the Chicago Fed, said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-us-rate-path-dot-plot-needs-more-context-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSDLCS6OKVIP7IMHOUADQQ6L7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 23:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管文件显示，Reddit 首席执行官实益拥有 61.5% 的 A 类股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一份监管文件显示，Reddit 联合创始人兼首席执行官史蒂夫-赫夫曼（Steve Huffman）实际持有这家社交媒体公司 6240 万股 A 类股。【原文：Reddit co-founder and CEO Steve Huffman beneficially owns 62.4 million Class A shares of the social media company, a regulatory filing showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/reddit-ceo-beneficially-owns-615-class-shares-regulatory-filing-shows-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UTBRDDQHMFLDHAAB34I5XT23QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:18:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，派拉蒙将终止与 Skydance 的独家谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，派拉蒙全球周五将结束与 Skydance Media 的独家谈判，但未达成协议。【原文：Paramount Global Friday will end its exclusive negotiations with Skydance Media without reaching a deal, the New York Times reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-will-let-exclusive-talks-with-skydance-lapse-nyt-reports-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKA3R56PNJMIXLZZOJ5TQHIMGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 Zeekr 计划在美国首次公开募股中融资 3.68 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车品牌 Zeekr Intelligent Technology Holding 周五表示，该公司计划在美国首次公开募股中筹集高达 3.675 亿美元的资金。【原文：China-based electric vehicle brand Zeekr Intelligent Technology Holding said on Friday it was aiming to raise up to $367.5 million in its U.S. initial public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/chinas-zeekr-plans-raise-up-368-mln-us-ipo-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ILEPFQJPSNLCVPBUQNZWK7DFHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 21:21:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司收购先锋公司最长需要两年时间才能取得进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚公司以 600 亿美元收购了美国页岩油生产商先锋自然资源公司（Pioneer Natural Resources），该公司最高页岩油主管周五表示，埃克森美孚将需要 18 到 24 个月的时间来实现其预期的生产协同效应。【原文：Exxon Mobil will take 18 to 24 months to achieve its desired production synergies from its $60 billion purchase of U.S. shale oil producer Pioneer Natural Resources, the company's top shale executive said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-take-up-two-years-hit-stride-with-pioneer-purchase-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IR2O6MPDRINPLQI62Q5R6TRE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 4 月服务业采购经理人指数升至 10 个月高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P全球加拿大服务业采购经理人指数（PMI）周五公布的数据显示，4月份加拿大服务业萎缩速度放缓，原因是企业实现了一些意料之外的销售额并增加了员工人数，但工资增长导致通胀压力升温。【原文：Canada's services sector contracted at a slower pace in April as firms notched some unexpected sales and added workers, but increased wages led to inflation pressures heating up, S&amp;P Global Canada services PMI data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canada-services-pmi-climbs-10-month-high-april-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CO7R2Q4K7VNNNMEGSANVAB36CE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:38:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美国小型股步履维艰，高利率造成损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储与通胀作斗争的过程中，利率持续走高的前景进一步给美国小型公司的股票前景蒙上了阴影，这些公司的股票今年以来一直落后于大盘。【原文：The prospect of interest rates remaining elevated as the Federal Reserve battles inflation is further clouding the outlook for shares of smaller U.S. companies, which have lagged broader markets this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-us-small-caps-struggle-elevated-interest-rates-take-toll-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5RONH7JPNMU3GAFESJWBGAZOI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[根据法庭和解协议，Aetna 将承担 LGBTQ 人士的生育治疗费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周五提交的一份法庭文件，Aetna 将支付 200 万美元并更新其承保政策，以了结一起声称该医疗保险公司要求 LGBTQ 受益人自付比异性恋者更多的生育治疗费用的诉讼。【原文：Aetna will pay $2 million and update its coverage policies to settle a lawsuit claiming the health insurer required LGBTQ beneficiaries to pay more out of pocket for fertility treatments than heterosexual people, according to a Friday court filing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/aetna-will-cover-fertility-treatments-lgbtq-people-under-court-settlement-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMWZA7HQIFLFDFUS6BMSVK52ZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:22:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道西南航空飞行员因波音交付延迟面临工时和薪酬减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士称，西南航空公司计划减少飞行员的工作时间，实际上也就是减少月薪，因为波音公司推迟交付飞机导致成本上升和人员过剩。【原文：Southwest Airlines plans to offer its pilots reduced hours and, in effect, monthly pay, two people familiar with the matter said, as it grapples with higher costs and overstaffing due to delays in aircraft deliveries from Boeing .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-pilots-face-reduced-hours-pay-due-boeing-delivery-delays-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQKR7KQIP5MY5K5FRPFWHFR3OI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 受政治影响，科技平台争夺广告交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Snap 和 Meta 等平台希望利用 TikTok 在美国的政治不确定性，从竞争对手手中抢走广告费。【原文：Short-form video took center stage at tech and social media companies' annual presentations to advertisers, as platforms like Snap and Meta look to capitalize on TikTok's political uncertainty in the U.S. to take ad dollars from their rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tech-platforms-make-pitch-ad-deals-tiktok-is-roiled-by-politics-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RF2I5M572ZO57PMVMKGB5Q4UGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:43:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制药商 Amneal 同意在美国达成 2.7 亿美元的阿片类药物和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿姆纳尔制药公司（Amneal Pharmaceuticals）周五表示，该公司已达成一项价值超过 2.7 亿美元的协议，以解决其助长了美国致命的阿片类药物流行的指控，成为最新一家就各州和地方政府提起的成瘾危机诉讼达成和解的制药公司。【原文：Amneal Pharmaceuticals said on Friday it had reached a deal valued at more than $270 million to resolve claims it helped fuel the deadly U.S. opioid epidemic, becoming the latest drug company to settle lawsuits over the addiction crisis brought by states and local governments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drugmaker-amneal-agrees-270-million-us-opioid-settlement-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAABHAFGGZL3DCFOUI4PVYKXTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就业数据疲软令美联储稍感宽慰]]></title><description><![CDATA[近几个月来，美联储官员因担心经济可能再次过热而备受煎熬。周五，4 月份的就业数据显示，工资增长明显降温，招聘速度与 COVID-19 大流行之前的水平一致，这让他们松了一口气。【原文：Federal Reserve officials, buffeted in recent months by concerns the economy might again overheat, got relief on Friday when jobs data for April showed a marked cooling in wage growth and a pace of hiring in line with levels seen before the COVID-19 pandemic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/weaker-us-jobs-data-brings-some-relief-fed-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAB5QCZKXRO67ONJFJFG6OALDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 14:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车初创企业 Rivian 聘请沃尔沃老将瓦雷拉担任运营总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian Automotive 周五任命哈维尔-瓦雷拉（Javier Varela）为首席运营官，这位沃尔沃（Volvo）的资深员工为公司注入了新鲜血液，使这家电动汽车初创公司在努力应对需求放缓的同时扩大了生产设施。【原文：Rivian Automotive named Javier Varela its chief operating officer on Friday, bolstering its ranks with the Volvo veteran as the electric-vehicle startup expands its production facility even as it grapples with a slowdown in demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-startup-rivian-hires-volvo-veteran-varela-operations-chief-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RQOLQRXYVKJZBYQHTD5Q355MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 14:20:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商获准延长电动汽车税收抵免中使用中国石墨的期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五在电池矿物要求方面给予了汽车制造商更多的灵活性，以便对来自中国的一些关键微量矿物（如石墨）提供电动汽车税收抵免。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department on Friday gave automakers additional flexibility on battery mineral requirements for electric vehicle tax credits on some crucial trace minerals from China, such as graphite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/automakers-win-extension-use-chinese-graphite-ev-tax-credits-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ST5MOC6E2RLSPF2QFXPQQMCT4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 14:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国服务业 4 月份萎缩；价格压力再度加快]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份，美国服务业出现萎缩，而衡量企业投入品价格的指标却出现跳涨，这对通胀前景来说是一个令人担忧的迹象。【原文：The U.S. services sector contracted in March, while a measure of prices paid by businesses for inputs jumped, a worrisome sign for the outlook on inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-service-sector-contracts-april-price-pressures-reaccelerate-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MINMYUK2M5KMFPRJHZ3QBHI5VQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 14:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会指控 BF Borgers 审计公司欺诈，影响 1,500 多份申报文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周五表示，审计师 BF Borgers 及其所有者本杰明-博格斯（Benjamin Borgers）被美国证券交易委员会指控犯有 "大规模欺诈 "罪，影响到 1500 多份美国证券交易委员会文件。【原文：Auditor BF Borgers and its owner Benjamin Borgers, whose clients include Trump Media, were charged by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission with “massive fraud” that affected more than 1,500 SEC filings, the SEC said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-sec-charges-audit-firm-bf-borgers-with-fraud-affecting-more-than-1500-filings-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SH4I2E6ZTVIZZDDCD6TIETDJNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:56:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼支持当前政策立场，但仍认为存在通胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周五表示，即使美国央行将基准利率稳定在当前水平，通胀也应继续下降，同时她还重申，如果进展趋缓或出现逆转，她愿意提高政策利率。【原文：Inflation should continue to decline even as the U.S. central bank holds its benchmark interest rate steady at current levels, Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman said on Friday while also reiterating her willingness to raise the policy rate if progress peters out or reverses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-bowman-supports-current-policy-stance-still-sees-inflation-risks-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFW6XICIHRNGFGUPPJ7DHKXAPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:52:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金连续第五周出现资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至5月1日的七天时间里，美国投资者连续第五周净卖出股票基金，在美联储做出政策决定前保持谨慎，并缩减了年初盛行的降息预期。【原文：U.S. investors were net sellers of equity funds for a fifth successive week in the seven days to May 1, exercising caution ahead of the Federal Reserve's policy decision and scaling back expectations for interest rate cuts that were prevalent at the start of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-witness-outflows-fifth-week-row-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWWHJKOXO5JZXP4OHASM3KD3FQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金每周吸引大量资金流入，亚洲居首]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 5 月 1 日的七天里，投资者对全球股票基金的兴趣再次高涨，这主要是由于对亚洲，尤其是中国经济复苏的乐观情绪推动了亚洲资金流入量的激增。【原文：Global equity funds experienced renewed interest from investors in the seven days through May 1, buoyed by a surge in inflows to Asia amid optimism about an economic recovery in the region, particularly in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVQXL6ZWZ5KGJOLC3COP4U3SVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月份就业报告显示劳动力市场宽松，对美联储是个好消息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 4 月份的就业增长放缓幅度超过预期，年工资涨幅也有所降温，这些迹象表明劳动力市场趋于宽松，这对市场和美联储来说都是好消息。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed more than expected in April and annual wage gains cooled, signs of a looser labor market which are good news for markets and the Federal Reserve that will likely require more such signals before pivoting from a higher for longer policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-april-us-jobs-report-shows-looser-labor-market-good-news-fed-2024-05-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYX5SFOMZVK5NPIP5NFCHGPSYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>