<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:23:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:23:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[- 路透社 NEXT 会议上科技、人工智能领域发言人的精彩发言]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社将于本周三和周四在纽约举办为期两天的路透 NEXT 会议，700 多位国际商界领袖和政策制定者将齐聚一堂，共同探讨社会、商业和世界面临的最大问题。以下是会议技术和人工智能分会上发言人的一些精彩发言。【原文：Reuters is hosting a two-day Reuters NEXT conference in New York on Wednesday and Thursday, bringing together more than 700 international business leaders and policymakers to examine the biggest issues facing society, business and the world. The following are some notable quotes from speakers at the technology and AI sessions of the conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/notable-quotes-tech-ai-sector-speakers-reuters-next-conference-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DY7NRQJO5JMZXLT3XCK6XJAU74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和加拿大称与中国有联系的黑客利用后门进行潜在 "破坏活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和加拿大网络安全机构周四表示，与中国有关联的黑客利用复杂的恶意软件渗透并长期访问未具名的政府和信息技术实体。【原文：Chinese-linked hackers used sophisticated malware to penetrate and maintain long-term access to unnamed government and information technology entities, U.S. and Canadian cybersecurity agencies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-linked-hackers-use-back-door-potential-sabotage-us-canada-say-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAASVGLJTJL6JELDTUEATYWKLU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 索偿令美联储前景扑朔迷离]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，华尔街三大股指变化不大，美元和国债收益率上涨，此前美国劳动力市场指标出人意料地强劲，令人质疑美联储明年的降息幅度。【原文：Wall Street's big three indices were little changed on Thursday, while the dollar and Treasury yields rose, after a surprisingly strong U.S. labor market indicator called into question how much lower the Fed will cut interest rates next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZDFTXHIWBJPNI7L4D26ZUZ25I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 因化妆品需求而上调年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 周四上调了年度销售额和利润预期，寄希望于节假日期间化妆品和护肤品的强劲需求。【原文：Ulta Beauty raised its annual sales and profit forecast on Thursday, betting on strong demand for its makeup and skincare products going into the holiday season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ulta-beauty-lifts-annual-forecasts-demand-cosmetics-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHDD5D5655N7VN7RNABWNTBM3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:57:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能的崛起令人兴奋，也引发就业忧虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在纽约举行的路透社 NEXT 会议上，人工智能的变革性影响占据了讨论的主要内容，小组成员集中讨论了人工智能可能如何颠覆工作和就业增长，回避了对人工智能泡沫的担忧。【原文：The transformative effects of artificial intelligence dominated discussions at the Reuters NEXT conference in New York, with panelists concentrating on how it may upend work - and job growth - sidestepping concerns about an AI bubble.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ais-rise-stirs-excitement-sparks-job-worries-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LKKVOXRC25KERE6PYUHRGCOXGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:51:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 NEXTDC 与 OpenAI 签署谅解备忘录，共同开发超大规模人工智能园区和 GPU 超级集群]]></title><description><![CDATA[NEXTDC 周五表示，它已与 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 签署了一份谅解备忘录，双方将在悉尼的 S7 厂址共同规划、开发和运营一个超大规模的人工智能园区和图形处理器（GPU）超级集群。【原文：NEXTDC said on Friday it has inked a memorandum of understanding with ChatGPT maker OpenAI to jointly plan, develop and operate a hyperscale AI campus and graphics processing unit, or GPU, supercluster at its S7 site in Sydney.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-nextdc-signs-deal-with-openai-build-hyperscale-ai-campus-gpu-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3LY2BIXYNROZBJG25ZGHVNX6WA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[- SAP 首席执行官敦促欧洲团结起来，放宽人工智能规则，以保持竞争力]]></title><description><![CDATA[SAP 首席执行官克里斯蒂安-克莱因（Christian Klein）周四表示，随着美国和中国加速投资和部署人工智能，欧洲需要一个更加统一的市场和更加宽松的监管，以保持在人工智能领域的竞争力。【原文：Europe needs a more unified market and lighter-touch regulation to stay competitive in artificial intelligence as the U.S. and China accelerate investment and deployment, SAP CEO Christian Klein said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/sap-ceo-urges-europe-unite-ease-ai-rules-stay-competitive-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSDY5WJA6RPL7C747FCKR3Q3KQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:34:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SentinelOne 预测季度收入低于预期，首席财务官将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[网络安全公司 SentinelOne 周四预测第四季度营收低于分析师预期，并表示首席财务官芭芭拉-拉尔森（Barbara Larson）将离职。【原文：Cybersecurity firm SentinelOne on Thursday forecast fourth-quarter revenue below analysts' expectations and said Chief Financial Officer Barbara Larson will step down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sentinelone-forecasts-quarterly-revenue-below-estimates-cfo-step-down-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6IEKZELS5N55KO4IK5L2ZEOPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:18:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HPE 预测季度收入疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠普企业公司周四预测第一季度收入低于华尔街预期，原因是经济不确定性导致企业支出谨慎。【原文：Hewlett Packard Enterprise forecast first-quarter revenue below Wall Street estimates on Thursday, due to cautious enterprise spending amid economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hpe-forecasts-weak-quarterly-revenue-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RZVP3ZXEBOOPP5JX7O3S2IQGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:11:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国太阳能公司敦促国会解决特朗普冻结太阳能许可的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，数十家美国太阳能公司在给国会领导人的一封信中表示，他们敦促联邦立法者撤销特朗普政府的一项政策，该政策导致项目许可停滞不前。【原文：Dozens of U.S. solar companies urged federal lawmakers to revoke a Trump administration policy that has stalled project permits, they said in a letter to leaders in Congress on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-solar-companies-urge-congress-address-trumps-solar-permit-freeze-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3XAV67DHFIBDLZ5IHGTZOXSJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛以新品牌和全球重点推动增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球化妆品生产商雅诗兰黛公司首席执行官周四在路透社 NEXT 会议上表示，该公司正致力于通过开发新品牌和关注全球年轻消费者，以及定制产品以满足不同文化消费者的需求，来扩大市场份额和增加销售额。【原文：Global cosmetics maker Estée Lauder Companies is focused on expanding market share and growing sales by developing new brands and focusing on younger consumers worldwide, and customizing products to meet consumers' needs across cultures, its CEO said at the Reuters NEXT conference on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/este-lauder-driving-growth-with-new-brands-global-focus-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CHVSYF75RMP3JEBZN6QR4MMIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将提高面向企业和政府的生产力套件价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司周四表示，将从2026年7月起在全球范围内提高其面向商业和政府客户的Microsoft 365生产力套件的价格。【原文：Microsoft will increase prices for its Microsoft 365 productivity suites globally starting July 2026 for commercial and government clients, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-lift-productivity-suite-prices-businesses-governments-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUDNP32JE5JNLH5KYMK3V47HTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员提出法案，阻止特朗普放松对华人工智能芯片销售限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括著名共和党对华鹰派人物汤姆-科顿（Tom Cotton）在内的美国两党参议员周四公布了一项法案，该法案将阻止特朗普政府在两年半时间内放松限制中国政府获得人工智能芯片的规定。【原文：A bipartisan group of U.S. senators, including prominent Republican China hawk Tom Cotton, on Thursday unveiled a bill that would block the Trump administration from loosening rules that restrict Beijing's access to artificial intelligence chips for 2.5 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senators-unveil-bill-keep-trump-easing-curbs-ai-chip-sales-china-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THKZ7DTSDZOORH7M7SOAZA2ONA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌高管认为人工智能搜索是网络的扩展]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，谷歌搜索公司的一位高管回击了人们对其人工智能搜索将损害网络出版商及其广告业务的担忧，称这项技术是互联网的 "扩张时刻"。【原文：A Google search executive on Thursday pushed back against fears that its AI-powered search will harm web publishers and its advertising business, calling the technology an “expansionary moment” for the internet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/google-executive-sees-ai-search-expansion-web-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXWJABFDCFNVFBYOFGKLBV3I4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:42:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CNBC 与 Kalshi 签订协议，明年起增加预测数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[CNBC与预测市场运营商Kalshi周四表示，双方已签署一项多年协议，从明年开始将实时概率数据引入CNBC的电视广播和数字平台。【原文：CNBC has signed a multi-year deal with prediction-market operator Kalshi, bringing real-time probability data into the network's TV broadcasts and digital platforms starting next year, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/cnbc-signs-deal-with-kalshi-add-prediction-data-next-year-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SVWNTI23ZIH3IG4BUB274WXIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:32:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行扩大财富管理客户的加密货币访问权限]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（Bank of America）周四表示，将从下个月开始允许其财富顾问在客户投资组合中建议配置加密货币，这对数字资产领域来说是一个具有里程碑意义的时刻。【原文：Bank of America will begin allowing its wealth advisers to recommend allocations to crypto in client portfolios from next month, the U.S. lending giant said on Thursday, in a landmark moment for the digital assets sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-expands-crypto-access-wealth-management-clients-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBR54P7M5FLBZMWS3KQYJMKIMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:15:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，激进投资者埃利奥特接近与百事公司达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，激进投资者埃利奥特管理公司（Elliott Management）即将与百事公司达成和解协议。【原文：Activist investor Elliott Management is close to striking a settlement agreement with PepsiCo , the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/activist-investor-elliott-nears-settlement-with-pepsico-wsj-reports-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UACALDWUY5JMVEX3RYZ47DNCYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:48:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官们认为年轻消费者将在关税和人工智能变革中推动增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[几位首席执行官周四表示，尽管关税和其他经济压力导致价格上涨，但年轻购物者正在帮助推动一些消费品的增长，如Honest Co尿布和Kate Spade手袋，而人工智能则提高了效率和利润率。【原文：Younger shoppers are helping to drive growth in some consumer products like Honest Co diapers and Kate Spade handbags despite higher prices from tariffs and other economic pressures, while artificial intelligence boosts efficiencies and margins, several CEOs said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ceos-see-younger-consumers-driving-growth-amid-tariffs-ai-changes-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HOF4AA535PBXOMJOHD6YIMZCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD 首席执行官称公司已准备好为运往中国的 AI 芯片支付 15%的税款]]></title><description><![CDATA[先进微设备公司首席执行官苏丽莎周四表示，该公司已获得向中国运输部分 MI 308 芯片的许可，如果向中国运输这些芯片，该公司准备向美国政府缴纳 15%的税款。【原文：Advanced Micro Devices CEO Lisa Su on Thursday said the company has licenses to ship some of its MI 308 chips to China and is prepared to pay a 15% tax to the U.S. government if it ships them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/amd-chief-says-company-ready-pay-15-tax-ai-chip-shipments-china-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WHXZ52OIBMYJFQIETPLDL2554</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:28:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国联邦贸易委员会正在调查 TP-Link 在中国分拆一事上是否误导了美国消费者]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士周四透露，美国联邦贸易委员会正在调查路由器制造商TP-Link Systems Inc.自去年重组以来是否涉嫌隐瞒与中国的关系，从而欺骗了消费者。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is examining whether router maker TP-Link Systems Inc. may have deceived consumers by allegedly concealing its connections to China since its restructuring last year, a source familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ftc-examines-whether-tp-link-misled-us-consumers-about-its-china-split-source-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCRLP7DCNBKAZDYRKPKNJUKZN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大黄集团终止与 Blackstone 的交易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国自助仓储公司 Big Yellow Group 周四表示，没有继续与 Blackstone 讨论潜在交易的基础。【原文：British self-storage company Big Yellow Group said on Thursday that there was no basis of continuing discussions with Blackstone on a potential deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/big-yellow-group-terminates-deal-talks-with-blackstone-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXN7C2Q4MJPXZD66GLZO4IIMOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利对加密货币风险进行 "深入 "审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利银行和其他金融监管机构周四表示，意大利经济部已下令对现有的加密货币风险保障措施进行深入审查，因为加密货币风险有可能上升。【原文：Italy's Economy Ministry has ordered an in-depth review of existing safeguards against cryptocurrency risks, which are seen potentially rising, the Bank of Italy and other financial regulators said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/italy-launches-in-depth-review-cryptocurrency-risks-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHLEVKUGMFKEDJVWCJOJCKGVYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国调查 Waymo 自动驾驶汽车在得克萨斯州非法超越校车 19 次的报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州官员称，Alphabet 旗下公司 Waymo 的自动驾驶汽车自开学以来非法超越校车 19 次，美国一家机构周四表示，已要求 Waymo 回答更多问题。【原文：A U.S. agency said on Thursday it has asked Waymo to answer more questions after Texas officials said the Alphabet unit's self-driving vehicles had illegally passed school buses 19 times since the start of the school year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-probes-reports-waymo-self-driving-cars-illegally-passed-school-buses-19-times-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCKLN23U7VIAVDARXTATA4Y6WQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会敦促美国法官阻止国务院裁员 1,300 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国国务院雇员的工会要求联邦法官阻止国务院周五裁员1300多人，这是唐纳德-特朗普总统政府大规模裁员的最新一场法律战。【原文：Unions representing U.S. State Department employees have asked a federal judge to block the agency from laying off more than 1,300 workers on Friday, the latest legal battle over mass job cuts by President Donald Trump's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/unions-urge-us-judge-block-1300-state-department-layoffs-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHX5UFL35BMTLPH57C7J767JDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会批准 AT&T 10 亿美元收购美国蜂窝公司频谱]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（Federal Communications Commission）周四表示，已批准 AT&amp;T 公司以 10.2 亿美元从美国蜂窝公司（U.S. Cellular）购买部分无线频谱许可证的交易，此前这家总部位于德克萨斯州的运营商已承诺终止 DEI 计划。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission said Thursday it has approved AT&amp;T's deal to buy some wireless spectrum licenses from U.S. Cellular in a $1.02 billion deal after the Texas-based carrier committed to end DEI programs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/fcc-approves-att-1-billion-purchase-spectrum-us-cellular-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZG623CJVJ5JGRNMRXXHGK54GHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mercuria 从 LME 亚洲抢夺铜矿加剧了供应焦虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的消息人士称，大宗商品交易商摩科瑞（Mercuria）已发出通知，计划从伦敦金属交易所位于亚洲的仓库中提取大量铜。【原文：Commodity trader Mercuria has given notice of its plans to take significant amounts of copper from London Metal Exchange warehouses in Asia, four sources familiar with the matter said, as prices rise on expectations of short supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/mercurias-copper-grab-lme-asia-intensifies-supply-angst-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWQYH6SHG5PVPJUSQXEK3RLDLQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ferrovial 首席执行官表示，将在美国机场寻找更多机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙建筑巨头 Ferrovial 公司首席执行官 Ignacio Madridejos 周四表示，在对纽约肯尼迪机场航站楼进行大规模翻修后，该公司看到了投资美国各地机场的其他机会。【原文：Spanish construction giant Ferrovial sees other opportunities for investment in airports across the United States following its massive terminal overhaul at New York's John F. Kennedy Airport, Chief Executive Officer Ignacio Madridejos said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ferrovial-eyeing-more-opportunities-us-airports-ceo-says-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KBI76V2UYBMJJNFYN5D6RBXHLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现货加密产品将在 CFTC 注册交易所开始交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会（CFTC）周四表示，现货加密资产合约将首次在该机构注册的期货交易所开始交易。【原文：The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) said on Thursday that spot crypto asset contracts will begin trading for the first time on futures exchanges registered with the agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/spot-crypto-products-begin-trading-cftc-registered-exchanges-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHQFCISHI5LAXAQHMOSUPIZZAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，派拉蒙指责华纳兄弟 Discovery 公司出售过程不公平]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周四援引新合并的媒体公司发出的一封信报道，派拉蒙 Skydance 指责华纳兄弟发现公司的出售程序不公平，偏袒 Netflix 而不是其他竞标者。【原文：Paramount Skydance has accused Warner Bros Discovery of running an unfair sale process that favors Netflix over other bidders, CNBC reported on Thursday, citing a letter sent by the newly merged media company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-accuses-warner-bros-discovery-unfair-sale-process-cnbc-reports-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PX7H7KCGHNN57B5FX47NBGQLAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄新社报道，俄罗斯封杀 Snapchat]]></title><description><![CDATA[据国营新闻社 RIA 周四援引俄罗斯通信监管机构 Roskomnadzor 的消息报道，俄罗斯已阻止 Snapchat 的访问。【原文：Russia has blocked access to Snapchat, state-run news agency RIA reported on Thursday, citing the country's communications regulator, Roskomnadzor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russia-blocks-snapchat-ria-reports-2025-12-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTJZD5NDNFOBXBDYCZ4RXGDWEQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>