<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:14:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:14:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早盘竞价：涡轮增压版"高桥贸易"令市场紧盯日元动向]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔·班纳吉带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOZ2DGKG7JLSRLV5IMPSUSVAMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:32:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道：可口可乐放弃出售Costa Coffee计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[《金融时报》周三报道称，由于私募股权公司的报价低于预期，可口可乐公司已放弃出售其Costa咖啡连锁店的计划。【原文：Coca-Cola has abandoned plans to sell its Costa Coffee chain after offers from private equity firms came in below expectations, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cocacola-scraps-costa-coffee-sale-ft-reports-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYEMFQMXURJXJKP2EFBQVED3UA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨克斯全球公司申请破产，此前尼曼·马库斯收购导致其财务崩溃]]></title><description><![CDATA[高端百货集团萨克斯全球公司于周二深夜申请破产保护，这是疫情以来规模最大的零售业崩盘事件之一。【原文：High-end department store conglomerate Saks Global filed for bankruptcy protection late on Tuesday in one of the ​largest retail collapses since the pandemic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/saks-global-files-bankruptcy-after-neiman-marcus-takeover-leads-financial-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DC63RGXKINM25IRT6VX34RK2LA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行行长因支持美联储政策引发强烈反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰外交部长温斯顿·彼得斯周三公开斥责该国新任央行行长，因其与其他全球央行行长联名签署声明支持美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔。【原文：New Zealand's Foreign Minister Winston Peters on Wednesday publicly rebuked the country's new central bank governor for signing a statement alongside other global central bank chiefs in support of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealand-central-bank-governor-faces-backlash-fed-solidarity-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E22BQESI3ZJRFMNFKUSMUFLYOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾当局要求逮捕中国智能手机制造商一加公司首席执行官，指控其非法雇佣员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾检方周二对华硕旗下智能手机品牌一加的首席执行官签发逮捕令，指控其涉嫌在台湾从事非法商业及招募活动。【原文：Taiwan prosecutors on Tuesday issued an arrest warrant for the chief executive officer of Chinese smartphone maker OnePlus, alleging he was involved in illegal business and recruitment activities in Taiwan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-seeks-arrest-chinese-smartphone-maker-oneplus-ceo-over-illegal-hires-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NX5O3PFHYNOMNG4FAX6THF47TA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管存在出口限制，2025年中国稀土出口量仍创下至少2014年以来的最高纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025年中国稀土出口量达到至少2014年以来的最高水平，尽管北京自4月起开始限制多种中重稀土元素的出口。【原文：China's rare earth exports in 2025 hit the highest level since at least 2014, even as Beijing began restricting shipments of several medium to heavy elements from April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-2025-rare-earth-exports-hit-highest-since-least-2014-despite-restrictions-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QA4LPKGDK5MO7HVLVVHCCMADCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:23:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国经销商呼吁汽车品牌平衡库存水平以缓解供过于求局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车经销商协会表示，部分中国汽车品牌仍在向经销商推销过剩库存，并敦促其纠正这种做法以改善行业健康状况。【原文：Some Chinese auto brands are continuing to push excess inventories to dealers, the country's car dealers' association said, urging them to correct the practice to improve the industry's health.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-dealers-call-auto-brands-balance-inventory-levels-help-ease-glut-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4U3E7SIEV5JZRFNFOD74GD7LZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管面临特朗普关税，中国2025年贸易顺差仍创下万亿美元纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周三公布2025年出口强劲增长，贸易顺差创下万亿美元纪录。与此同时，生产商正为特朗普政府未来三年继续放缓中国生产引擎的政策做准备——该政策旨在将美国订单转移至其他市场。【原文：China on ​Wednesday reported a strong export run in 2025 with a record trillion-dollar surplus, as producers braced for three more years of a Trump ‌administration set on slowing the production powerhouse by shifting U.S. orders to other markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-trade-ends-2025-with-record-trillion-dollar-surplus-despite-trump-tariffs-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQR2YJ7AVJKAFON6J7CKDJGLKQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:15:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特首席执行官称与墨西哥和加拿大的贸易协议对行业"至关重要"]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特首席执行官吉姆·法利表示，北美自由贸易协定对这家汽车制造商和整个行业都至关重要。此前数小时，美国总统特朗普称该协定"无关紧要"。【原文：Ford CEO Jim Farley said a North American free trade deal is needed for the automaker and industry, hours after U.S. President Trump called it "irrelevant."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-ceo-says-trade-deal-with-mexico-canada-is-critical-industry-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGLQC6BEFVISLBUHXDE2XWIROM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:46:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉同意接受调解，或可解决美国机构的种族歧视诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉同意接受调解，以解决美国平等就业机会委员会的诉讼。该诉讼指控埃隆·马斯克的电动汽车制造商纵容其位于加州弗里蒙特的组装工厂对黑人员工实施严重且普遍的骚扰行为。【原文：Tesla agreed to enter mediation that could resolve the U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission's lawsuit accusing Elon Musk's electric car maker of tolerating severe and widespread harassment of Black employees at its Fremont, California, assembly plant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/tesla-agrees-mediation-that-could-resolve-us-agencys-racism-lawsuit-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XONTKM4MRMFPEPMZZ4T323YRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:34:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究机构称，全球电动汽车销量在经历2025年20%的强劲增长后，增速可能放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据显示，去年全球电动汽车注册量增长20%，但2026年增速可能放缓。由于中国市场增速放缓以及全球电动化目标的放宽，去年12月销量增幅创2024年2月以来最低水平。【原文：Global EV registrations grew 20% last year but are likely to lose pace in 2026, data showed on Wednesday, as a slowdown in China and a relaxation of electrification targets worldwide led in December to the smallest sales increase since February 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/global-ev-sales-growth-likely-slow-after-20-jump-rocky-2025-research-firm-says-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJSWOO7XEJLIFCTGZ7INY6KERU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:31:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市小幅走高，日元疲软引发干预担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周三上涨，受日本股市提振，投资者正为日本可能举行提前大选做准备，该选举或将带来更多财政刺激措施。与此同时，对央行独立性的担忧以及温和的美国通胀数据导致货币市场剧烈波动。【原文：Asian stocks rose on Wednesday, buoyed by Japanese shares, as investors braced for a snap election in Japan ​that could lead to more fiscal stimulus, while worries about central bank independence and benign U.S. inflation data whipsawed currencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XT5PN5Z6B5PVLHYQJN35MCACAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商恩智浦与中方控股方永达科技在荷兰法庭争夺控制权]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰芯片制造商恩智浦的欧洲管理层将于周三在阿姆斯特丹法庭与公司中国母公司旺达科技对簿公堂，这场争夺控制权的最新交锋已导致汽车制造商使用的芯片短缺。【原文：Dutch chipmaker Nexperia's European managers face the company's Chinese owner Wingtech in an Amsterdam court on Wednesday in the latest round of a fight for control that has led to a shortage of chips used by carmakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chipmaker-nexperia-chinese-owner-wingtech-fight-control-dutch-court-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPN5AOQFXFJ7HPWP2PUQNY3OGY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:20:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价涨势暂歇，委内瑞拉恢复石油运输，但伊朗问题阴云笼罩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三油价涨势暂歇，在连续四日攀升后出现回落，因委内瑞拉恢复出口。但中东主要产油国伊朗爆发致命骚乱后，市场仍笼罩在对伊朗供应中断的担忧之中。【原文：Oil prices paused their run of gains on Wednesday, slipping ​after four days of increases, as Venezuela resumed exports, but fears of Iranian supply disruptions following ‌deadly civil unrest in the major Middle Eastern producer loom over the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-pause-gains-venezuela-shipments-resume-iran-concerns-loom-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KYXMN4FNBJYXGQAFSAS4FQEJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:14:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA["你死了吗？"中国单身生活应用爆红]]></title><description><![CDATA[一款名为"你死了吗"的应用程序在中国引发热议，该应用专为独居人群设计，下载量激增且在社交媒体上引发广泛讨论，促使开发公司推出订阅收费模式，并为面向全球用户更改了名称。【原文：An app called "Are you dead" targeted at people living alone has gone viral in China, with surging downloads and widespread commentary on social media, prompting the company to introduce a subscription fee and change its name for a global audience.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/are-you-dead-chinese-app-single-living-goes-viral-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGY3OPMGTZKXTERYKEDCP776IA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 01:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示他认为中国可以向美国商品开放市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周二表示，他认为中国能够向美国商品开放市场，并再次强调自己与中国国家主席习近平保持着良好关系。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday he thinks China can open its markets to American goods, once again asserting he had a good relationship with Chinese leader Xi Jinping.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-thinks-china-can-open-its-markets-us-goods-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJJOOWIUPJPVDNADO2DWPDTMFA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元随符合预期的CPI数据反弹，银行家支持鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三亚洲早盘时段，美元汇率回升至近一个月高位。此前公布的美国消费者物价指数（CPI）数据基本符合预期，强化了市场对美联储本月将维持利率不变的预期——尽管白宫施加了前所未有的降息压力。 衡量美元兑六种货币汇率的美元指数最新上涨0.3%至99.18，收复了周一的跌幅。此前美国总统特朗普威胁要对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔提起刑事指控。周二，全球央行行长和华尔街顶级银行首席执行官们纷纷表态支持鲍威尔。 澳新银行伦敦G3经济部主管布莱恩·马丁表示："政界人士、前美联储主席及其他官员正形成强烈共识，认为美联储独立性神圣不可侵犯，不容干预。"他在播客中指出："干预可能引发通胀上升、政府融资成本攀升及经济活动波动加剧等负面后果。" "市场正采取谨慎态度：他们不会草率下结论，我认为这种审慎会占上风，美联储的独立性将得到保护。"周二数据显示，12月美国消费者价格环比上涨0.3%，主要受租金和食品成本上升推动——此前因政府停摆导致的通胀人为压低效应已逐渐消退。 该数据强化了市场对美联储本月维持利率不变的预期。芝商所集团FedWatch工具显示，联邦基金期货当前隐含美联储在1月28日结束的下次为期两天的会议上按兵不动的概率为95.6%，较前日持平。 资本经济研究所分析师指出："只要美国通胀保持可控，对美联储独立性的间接攻击不太可能引发金融市场动荡。"在最高法院可能就特朗普紧急关税合法性作出裁决前，亚洲早盘多数货币对波动性保持温和。荷兰国际集团分析师在研究报告中表示："裁决可能认定关税合法，若如此我们便继续前行。 "我们预计裁决将予以否决，但市场仍可能无动于衷。"荷兰国际集团分析师在研究报告中表示。 "当前美国国债市场展现出非凡的'漠不关心'能力。"美元兑日元最新报159.025日元基本持平，此前路透日银短观调查显示日本制造业信心指数1月跌至六个月低点（但仍处于正值区间）。 此前因市场猜测日本首相高市早苗可能提前举行国会选举以巩固权力，日元一度跌至2024年1月以来最低水平。读卖新闻周三报道称，她正考虑于2月8日举行众议院提前选举。 离岸人民币兑美元汇率报6.9708元，持平于前一交易日。中国12月贸易数据将于数小时后公布。澳元兑美元上涨0.1%至0.6688美元，纽元兑美元小幅攀升0.1%至0.5740美元。 欧元兑美元汇率持平于1.1642美元，英镑兑美元汇率同样维持在1.3423美元不变。比特币上涨1.8%至95,751.99美元，创下两个月来最高水平；以太币最新上涨4.0%至3,334.46美元。【原文：The U.S. dollar recovered ground to near a one-month high in early Asian trade ​on Wednesday after U.S. CPI data that was broadly in line with estimates, firming up expectations that the Federal Reserve ‌will remain on hold later this month despite unprecedented pressure from the White House to lower interest rates. The U.S. dollar index , which measures the greenback's strength against a basket of six currencies, was last up 0.3% at 99.18, retracing losses from Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened Fed Chair Jerome Powell with a criminal indictment. Global central bank chiefs and top Wall Street bank CEOs lined up in support of Powell on Tuesday. "There's a very loud chorus of opinion ‌coming from politicians, former Fed chairmen and other officials that Fed independence is sacrosanct and cannot be interfered with," ​said Brian Martin, head of G3 Economics at ANZ in London. "It risks having adverse consequences of higher inflation, higher funding costs for the government and more volatility in economic activity," he said on a podcast. "Markets are erring on the side of caution: They're not jumping to conclusions, and ‍I think that sense will prevail and that the independence of the Fed will be protected." On Tuesday, data showed U.S. consumer prices increased 0.3% in December compared to the previous month, lifted by higher costs for rents and food as some of the distortions related to the government shutdown that had artificially lowered inflation in November unwound. ⁠The print cemented expectations the Federal Reserve would leave interest rates unchanged this month, with Fed funds futures currently pricing an implied 95.6% probability ‍that the U.S. central bank will remain on hold when its next two-day meeting concludes on 28 January, unchanged from a day earlier, according to the CME ‌Group's FedWatch ‌tool. "Indirect attacks on the Fed’s independence aren’t likely to roil the financial markets in the U.S., so long as inflation there remains under control," wrote analysts from Capital Economics. Volatility in most currency pairs was subdued in early Asian trading ahead of a possible Supreme Court ruling on the legality of Trump's emergency tariffs. "It could rule them legit, and if so we just move on. We suspect they will be struck down, and we'll ⁠probably still just move on," analysts ⁠from ING wrote in a ​research report. "This Treasury market is showing a remarkable capacity to just not care too much about stuff." Against the yen , the U.S. dollar was last flat at 159.025 yen, little changed after the Reuters Tankan poll showed Japanese manufacturers' confidence slipped to a six-month low in January, albeit still in positive territory. The yen had earlier ‍fallen to its weakest levels since January 2024 on speculation that Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi may call parliamentary elections to consolidate her power. The Yomiuri newspaper reported on Wednesday that she is considering snap lower house elections on February 8. Against the Chinese yuan trading offshore in Hong Kong , the U.S. dollar was last flat at 6.9708 yuan ​ahead of the release of Chinese trade data for December in a few hours' time. The ‍Australian dollar was last up 0.1% at $0.6688, while the New Zealand dollar nudged 0.1% upwards to $0.5740. The euro was last flat at $1.1642, while the British pound also held steady at $1.3423. Bitcoin gained ​1.8% to $95,751.99, rising to the highest level in two months, while ether was last up 4.0% at $3,334.46.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-rebounds-with-cpi-data-line-bankers-back-powell-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4DATZ7VNVPW7JSPQAFRLDGZ4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的巴金称12月通胀数据令人鼓舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联邦储备银行行长汤姆·巴金周二称12月通胀数据"令人鼓舞"，但他同时指出通胀通常在年初出现飙升，并表示希望未来几个月通胀能保持温和水平。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Tom Barkin on Tuesday called December's inflation data "encouraging," though he noted inflation often spikes at the start of the year and said he hopes it will come in at modest levels for the next couple of months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-barkin-calls-december-inflation-data-encouraging-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HWMX27EA7BMX3CM64GTNFH6RA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:54:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚蓝星钢铁将通过特别股息向股东返还2.925亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚钢铁制造商博思高钢铁周三宣布，将通过每股1澳元的特别股息向股东返还4.38亿澳元（约合2.9254亿美元），资金来源于近期资产出售产生的盈余现金。【原文：Australian steelmaker BlueScope Steel said on Wednesday it would return A$438 million ($292.54 million) to its shareholders through a special dividend of A$1 per share, funded by surplus cash from its recent asset sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-bluescope-steel-return-2925-million-shareholders-via-special-dividend-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJB3TL74OJLHBMWU6HNQ5YPATU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：特朗普争议性议程引发市场震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二美国股市下跌，金融股拖累大盘走低，此前摩根大通警告称特朗普总统提议的信贷利率上限将损害经济。与此同时，地缘政治紧张局势引发油价急剧上涨，并推高黄金价格至新高。【原文：U.S. stocks fell on Tuesday, dragged lower by financials after JPMorgan warned that President Donald Trump's proposed cap on credit rates would harm the economy, while geopolitical tensions triggered a sharp rise in oil and lifted gold to new highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVICUPOP2BNBPGHIIJFGMADZVM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeatherTech创始人获联邦贸易委员会任命]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（FTC）主席安德鲁·弗格森周二在社交媒体平台X上发文称，WeatherTech创始人戴维·麦克尼尔已被提名为联邦贸易委员会委员候选人。【原文：WeatherTech founder David MacNeil has been nominated for a seat on the U.S. Federal Trade Commission, FTC Chairman Andrew Ferguson said in a post on social media site X on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/weathertech-founder-tapped-federal-trade-commission-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">732OT2M7KNMF3H2LKF7V2FPZYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国教师工会称将退出X平台，因其存在儿童性化AI图像]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国教师联合会宣布退出X平台，指责该社交媒体平台制造并传播了儿童处于不同程度衣着不整的"令人作呕"的图像。【原文：The American Federation of Teachers says it is leaving X, citing the social media site's creation and dissemination of "sickening" images of children in various states of undress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/teachers-union-says-its-leaving-x-calling-ai-images-children-the-last-straw-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7ZYHNNEJBNPLH3JD3CAFVD6LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:38:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国批准英伟达向中国出口H200芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周二批准向中国出口英伟达第二强劲的人工智能芯片，联邦公报显示，这项新规有望推动H200芯片的出货。【原文：The Trump administration on Tuesday gave the greenlight to exports to China of Nvidia's second most powerful AI chips, putting in place a rule that will likely kickstart shipments of the H200, the federal register showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-eases-regulations-nvidia-h200-chip-exports-china-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CGZP3W4JW5LXXLSRT45K7QGBQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道称，最高法院关税裁决前夕，亚马逊向供应商施压要求降价]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周二报道，亚马逊正寻求削减其在电商平台上销售商品的供应商付款金额。这家科技巨头此举旨在撤销此前为缓解美国总统特朗普关税冲击而作出的让步。【原文：Amazon is seeking to cut what it pays suppliers for goods it sells on its e-commerce platform, as the tech giant moves to reverse concessions intended to limit the shock of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-pushes-suppliers-cuts-ahead-supreme-court-tariff-ruling-ft-reports-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGS6PVJYF5OI7CGRNE5MN5NC2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对美联储主席的调查凸显全球多元化必要性]]></title><description><![CDATA[针对美联储主席的刑事调查强化了部分投资者的观点：他们担忧央行独立性持续受到侵蚀，因此需要将资产配置多元化至美国以外地区。尽管许多人认为对杰罗姆·鲍威尔的行动只是开端，最终可能只是虚张声势。【原文：The criminal investigation into the Fed chair has reinforced the case for diversifying holdings beyond the United States for some investors as ​they worry about the ongoing independence of the central bank, even though many saw the move against Jerome Powell as an opening shot that could end ‌up being more bark than bite.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-probe-fed-chair-stresses-need-global-diversification-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYYLGI3EBVKSROGMBRN4QB5SZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，奈飞正考虑修改对华纳兄弟的收购要约，将其转为全现金交易。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻周二报道，知情人士透露，奈飞正就华纳兄弟探索公司修订收购条款，并已讨论以全现金方式收购该公司的影视制作和流媒体业务。【原文：Netflix is working on revised ​terms for Warner Bros Discovery and ‌has discussed making its offer all cash for the company's studios and streaming businesses, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing ‌people familiar with the talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-weighs-amending-warner-bros-bid-make-it-all-cash-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQWGUKBVY5PXDNWT7ODZXJ2FWA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:50:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，萨克斯全球公司破产申请前筹备17.5亿美元融资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[深陷困境的奢侈品零售商萨克斯全球公司即将与债权人敲定17.5亿美元融资协议。据两位知情人士透露，该协议将确保其标志性品牌萨克斯第五大道、伯格多夫·古德曼和内曼·马库斯门店在破产重组期间保持营业。这家百货集团正着手重组债务与运营，最早可能于本周二正式申请破产。【原文：Beleaguered ​luxury retailer Saks Global is close to finalizing $1.75 billion in financing with creditors that ‌would allow its iconic Saks Fifth Avenue, Bergdorf Goodman and Neiman Marcus stores to remain open while the department stores conglomerate reorganizes its debt and operations in bankruptcy, which could be filed as soon as Tuesday, two people familiar with the negotiations said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/saks-global-nearing-175-billion-financing-plan-ahead-bankruptcy-filing-sources-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JZYDAYEWXFOAHPJKWJCA4S7F7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:12:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Minerva为日本后期初创企业基金筹集4400万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，总部位于东京的Minerva Growth Partners在第二期基金的首轮募资中已筹集约70亿日元（4400万美元），该基金旨在投资后期初创企业。【原文：Tokyo-based Minerva Growth Partners has secured around 7 billion yen ($44 million) at the first close for a second fund that aims to invest in late-stage startups, according to a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/minerva-secures-440-million-japan-late-stage-startup-fund-source-says-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HR7H5W3VJNW7IDBMXKGD3B664</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:01:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道，萨克斯全球首席执行官理查德·贝克即将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博社周二援引知情人士消息报道，奢侈品零售商萨克斯全球公司首席执行官理查德·贝克在接任不到两周后即将离职，这家深陷困境的企业正面临破产危机。【原文：Luxury retailer Saks Global's CEO Richard Baker is departing less than two weeks after taking over ​the top job, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing ‌people familiar with the situation, as the embattled company stares at bankruptcy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/saks-global-ceo-richard-baker-set-depart-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVKLP46EWRI5RKBHP5WJZMGF6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:14:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月财政赤字创纪录达1450亿美元，支出超过收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周二表示，12月联邦政府预算赤字达1450亿美元，较上年同期增长67%或580亿美元，主要原因是福利支付和收入因日历变动而膨胀，导致支出创下历史新高。【原文：The U.S. government posted a $145 billion budget deficit for December, up 67% or $58 billion from ​a year earlier due to record outlays that ‌were inflated by calendar shifts in benefit payments and receipts, the Treasury Department said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-posts-record-145-billion-december-deficit-outlays-outpace-receipts-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QCCSSUKXBLLLJPC5Q265WJVOY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>