<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:47:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:47:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月份消费者支出稳健增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份，美国消费者支出的增长略高于预期，使经济在第三季度继续保持稳健增长，同时通胀继续以一定的速度上升。【原文：U.S. consumer spending increased slightly more than expected in August, keeping the economy on solid ground as the third quarter progressed, while inflation continued to rise at a measured pace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-spending-increases-solidly-august-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46546EM4TBKHNGXXQSOL2XUEVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:39:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 7 月国内生产总值在连续三个月萎缩后出现反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的数据显示，由于采矿业、制造业和批发贸易促进了经济增长，加拿大7月份的月度国内生产总值从连续三个月的萎缩中反弹，增长了0.2%。【原文：Canada's monthly gross domestic product rebounded from three months of contraction to grow by 0.2% in July as mining, manufacturing and wholesale trade boosted growth, data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-gdp-rebounds-july-after-three-months-contraction-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHGWDNLJOVOB3DDAZU72NVV2VM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利邮政考虑收取数字身份识别费，分析师认为可能增加 1 亿欧元利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利邮政公司（Poste Italiane）的分析师在周五的每日报告中写道，在与公司管理层进行了一次情况通报后，意大利邮政公司正在考虑对其数字身份服务的用户收取年度管理费。【原文：Poste Italiane is considering introducing an annual management fee for users of its digital identity service, analysts wrote in their daily reports on Friday following a briefing with the company's management.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/poste-italiane-considers-digital-identity-fee-analysts-see-potential-100-mln-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGUGQ3JSWNLNJAN4AVXQLWVLHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道汉莎航空周一宣布裁员数千人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，汉莎航空将在周一举行的六年来首次全公司范围的资本市场日上宣布裁员数千人，以向市场表明其提高效率的决心。【原文：Lufthansa is expected to announce several thousand job cuts on Monday at its first company-wide capital markets day in six years, according to two sources close to the matter, as it seeks to show the market its commitment to increasing efficiency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/lufthansa-announce-thousands-job-cuts-monday-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKR24KXGO5JIVJV7QOA7LWFSS4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，FAA 将放宽波音 737 MAX 的生产限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，美国联邦航空管理局将放宽对波音737 MAX生产的限制。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration is set to ease restrictions on Boeing's 737 MAX production, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-ease-boeing-737-max-production-restrictions-wsj-reports-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M3RESJAP55MC3EVOGA6RW45U3I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的能源转向加速了美国太阳能和风能企业的兼并和资产出售]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士和分析师表示，特朗普政府在可再生能源领域的迅速退却，已经在美国较小的太阳能和风能公司中掀起了整合和资产出售的浪潮，因为这些公司正竭力维持生存。【原文：The Trump administration's rapid retreat from renewable energy has kicked off consolidation and asset sales among smaller U.S. solar and wind power companies as they scramble to stay afloat, industry insiders and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trumps-energy-pivot-accelerates-us-solar-wind-power-mergers-asset-sales-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEONRJRHZRIZDFNLX4PNMNKNLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:34:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将在英国推出无广告的 Facebook 和 Instagram 订阅服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周五表示，它将在未来几周内向英国的 Facebook 和 Instagram 用户提供无广告订阅选项。【原文：Meta Platforms said on Friday it would offer an ad-free subscription option to Facebook and Instagram users in the United Kingdom in the coming weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/meta-launch-ad-free-facebook-instagram-subscriptions-uk-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JC5VATZKABJLFPFP464APYIWLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国还要加征关税？中国的 "家具王国 "表示已经采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国的 "家具王国 "乐从，有一条巨大的购物中心带，商贩们对来自华盛顿的最新一轮关税避而不谈，称他们早已放弃了美国市场。【原文：In China's "Furniture Kingdom" of Lecong, home to a strip of cavernous malls, vendors shrugged off the latest round of tariffs from Washington, saying they've long given up on the U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/more-us-tariffs-chinas-furniture-kingdom-says-its-already-moved-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74AWVCCXMRJCDCZIQOWSLI2UHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:38:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标美联储的艰难工作变得更难]]></title><description><![CDATA[看看投资回报率团队周末要阅读、观看和收听什么节目。【原文：Check out what the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NL36YEMAJFILLN67HIAWV23GTU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布对卡车征收关税，戴姆勒卡车和特拉通股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对重型卡车征收关税后，戴姆勒卡车公司和特拉通公司的股价周五下跌，加剧了对汽车行业造成重创的贸易紧张局势。【原文：Shares in Daimler Truck and Traton fell on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump announced tariffs on heavy-duty trucks, adding to trade tensions that have hit the automotive sector hard.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/daimler-truck-traton-shares-fall-trump-announces-truck-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23AIJPYIFRITBMA4MUDIBHDBHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:11:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国表示推动美国制药关税取得更好结果]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，除非企业在美国建立生产基地，否则将对其征收 100% 的新关税，英国周五表示，正在就药品关税问题向美国施压，希望能取得有利的结果。【原文：Britain on Friday said it was pressing the United States on pharmaceutical tariffs in hope of a beneficial outcome, after President Donald Trump said a new 100% tariff would apply to firms unless they build a manufacturing presence in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/britain-says-pushing-better-outcome-us-pharma-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PB4Y6SLS65OOXMDQ2QNDY2INPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 投资者期待就业数据支持降息路径，股市价格高企]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周的美国就业数据对华尔街来说可能需要慎之又慎，既要显示劳动力市场降温，支持进一步降息，又不能加剧对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：Next week's U.S. jobs data may need to tread a fine line for Wall Street, revealing a cooling labor market that supports further interest rate cuts without fueling fears about a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-investors-look-jobs-data-support-rate-cut-path-pricey-stock-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5ABLSBCLNPJFCO5YTKHYH5CVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大天然气生产商在价格创历史新低之际削减产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些公司和分析师表示，加拿大西部的一些天然气生产商正在积极减产，以缓解持续过剩的天然气供应，本周天然气价格跌至创纪录的负值。【原文：Some natural gas producers in Western Canada are aggressively cutting output in an effort to ease an ongoing glut that this week tipped prices for the fuel into record negative territory, companies and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/canadian-natgas-producers-cut-output-amid-record-low-prices-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6OVDRSTXZNS3EQO6J5V3VY3ZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国防部门罢工持续第九周，波音公司感受不到经济痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周五，位于圣路易斯的波音防务公司的机械师罢工达到了53天，与去年西北地区的国际机械师和航空航天工人协会工会成员的罢工相同，他们为该公司制造了大部分商用喷气机。【原文：A strike by machinists at Boeing Defense in St. Louis reached 53 days on Friday, matching last year’s walkout by fellow International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers union members in the Northwest who make most of the company's commercial jets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeing-feels-little-economic-pain-strike-defense-unit-head-ninth-week-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4IXI37YQFPVVD7WTK33JXGB6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:02:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟和日本对美国药品关税上限表示信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，他将于下周对美国药品征收 100%的关税。【原文：The European Union and Japan expressed confidence on Friday that they had secured limits on U.S. tariffs on pharmaceuticals, which President Donald Trump said he would impose next week at a rate of 100%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eu-japan-express-confidence-in-capped-us-tariffs-drugs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVV57Q7DPVP7XNBLS7RQ7YLPHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为通胀数据做好准备，华尔街期货涨跌不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货涨跌不一，投资者在等待可能左右降息押注的关键通胀数据，同时也在权衡对多种进口商品征收新关税的影响。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were mixed on Friday, as investors awaited key inflation data that could sway bets on interest rate cuts, while also weighing the impact of fresh tariffs on a broad range of imported goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-mixed-investors-brace-inflation-data-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WQ6XQJCMJOOTKG2HSCEDVNAL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卫星合并在即，欧洲航天局警告反对垄断]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲航天局的一位高级官员说，要达到与美国和中国竞争对手竞争的规模，可能需要合并，但过于集中可能会限制选择。【原文：A senior official from the European Space Agency said mergers could be needed to reach the scale to compete with U.S. and Chinese rivals, but that too much concentration could limit choice.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/european-space-agency-warns-against-monopolies-satellite-merger-looms-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKZBQOJL3VOEXOQIT7GP2ZF3L4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚要求美国对家具、汽车和航空航天零部件实行零关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚贸易部一位官员周五表示，马来西亚已要求美国考虑对其出口的家具、汽车和航空航天产品征收零关税。【原文：Malaysia has asked the United States to consider imposing zero tariff rates on its exports of furniture, automotive and aerospace products, a Malaysian trade ministry official said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/malaysia-asks-us-zero-tariff-rate-furniture-automotive-aerospace-parts-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQKFZPSHBNO7DMLKTTSXEL3DCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行发出稳定币警告后，英国银行继续推行代币化存款]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国最大的贷款机构正在推进明年推出客户存款代币化版本的计划，此举是在英格兰银行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）呼吁优先考虑该技术而非稳定币之后采取的。【原文：Britain's biggest lenders are pushing ahead with plans to launch tokenised versions of customer deposits next year, a move that follows Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey's plea to prioritise the technology over stablecoins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/uk-banks-press-with-tokenised-deposits-after-boe-stablecoin-warning-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4TSTRQGL5MG3MS5F7JP7S6LJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 08:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行明年将进行新的数字欧元实验]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）周五表示，它将在明年就数字欧元可能实现的目标进行新的实验，这是它在一个被视为保持欧元区金融独立于美国的关键项目上迈出的又一步。【原文：The European Central Bank said on Friday it would conduct new experiments next year about what could be achieved through a digital euro, in a further step for a project it sees as key for preserving the euro zone's financial autonomy from the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ecb-conduct-new-digital-euro-experiments-next-year-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BNYJHSCJFPZXHFLGBUNE64YJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:35:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数字银行 NOBA 在斯德哥尔摩首次公开募股飙升 27]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字银行集团 NOBA 在斯德哥尔摩证券交易所首次公开发行股票，周五上市首日股价上涨 27%，公司估值达 445 亿瑞典克朗（约合 47.1 亿美元）。【原文：The share price of digital banking group NOBA rose 27% on its first day of trading on Friday following an initial public offering on the Stockholm bourse, valuing the company at 44.5 billion Swedish crowns ($4.71 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/digital-bank-noba-soars-27-stockholm-ipo-debut-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SD2NXRZGMBMHFLI4W5EHF4WREU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马因发动机启动器缺陷召回逾 19.6 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，宝马将在美国召回超过196,000辆汽车，因为发动机启动继电器可能会被腐蚀，导致过热和短路，增加起火风险。【原文：BMW is recalling over 196,000 vehicles in the U.S. as the engine starter relay may corrode, leading to overheating and short circuit, increasing the risk of a fire, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-recall-over-196000-us-vehicles-due-engine-starter-defect-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EFWXBNZPNMYXCBPYRK6L3K6MM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:18:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称中国 Momenta 考虑将 IPO 从纽约转移到香港]]></title><description><![CDATA[四名知情人士透露，中国自动驾驶汽车开发商 Momenta 正在考虑将其首次公开募股（IPO）地点从纽约转移到香港，在中美紧张局势加剧之际，选择在亚洲金融中心首次公开募股的中国公司越来越多。【原文：hinese autonomous driving developer Momenta is considering shifting its IPO to Hong Kong from New York, four people said, adding to a growing list of Chinese companies opting to debut in the Asian financial hub amid heightened U.S.-China tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-momenta-considers-shifting-ipo-hong-kong-new-york-sources-say-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4HEYLWE5RIBJEMEVHUWPJMDEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布对制药业征收关税后，罗氏指出美国的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士罗氏公司周五指出，该公司在美国的一个部门的新设施已于8月份破土动工，而且在唐纳德-特朗普总统最新宣布征收关税后，该制药公司已承诺在美国进行重大投资。【原文：Switzerland's Roche on Friday pointed to the fact that one of its U.S. units broke ground on a new facility in August and that the pharma company had pledged major U.S. investments after President Donald Trump's latest tariff announcement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/roche-points-us-plans-after-trump-pharma-tariff-announcement-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RATIL5O4TFKJDBUSZYTUP4F53A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前董事会成员预测，上田领导下的日本央行可能将利率上调至 1.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行前董事会成员樱井诚（Makoto Sakurai）告诉路透社记者，在行长上田一夫的任期于2028年初结束之前，日本央行可能会至少再上调基准利率四次至1.5%。【原文：The Bank of Japan will probably raise its benchmark interest rate at least four more times to 1.5% before Governor Kazuo Ueda's term ends in early 2028, former central bank board member Makoto Sakurai told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-likely-hike-rates-15-under-ueda-former-board-member-predicts-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOTXXJ7ZLVONPLB2G7K3MLDFGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:38:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易机构负责人称，随着美国需求增加，台湾寻求在印度扩大科技业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾的主要贸易机构负责人表示，由于美国的需求推动了台湾智能手机出货量的增长，台湾正寻求在未来五到七年内将其对印度的芯片和电子产品出口翻一番。【原文：Taiwan is seeking to double its exports of chips and electronics to India over the next five to seven years as smartphone shipments from the country ramp up thanks to demand from the U.S., the head of the island's main trade body said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-seeks-bigger-tech-presence-india-us-demand-rises-trade-body-chief-says-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGR3U2G33BOJHDUAA3T3MSLNMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威航空公司将增购 30 架波音 737 飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威航空班机公司（Norwegian Air Shuttle）周五表示，该公司已经行使了再购买30架波音737 MAX 8的选择权，从而使其确定订单总数达到80架。【原文：Norwegian Air Shuttle said on Friday it had exercised an option to buy an additional 30 Boeing 737 MAX 8, bringing its total firm order to 80 aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/norwegian-air-buy-an-additional-30-boeing-737-aircraft-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCUMG5HNXFJLJIXT27J5RU6E2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙学生公寓吸引全球投资者，海外入学人数激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着西班牙成为愿意支付高价租金的留学生的首选目的地，全球投资者纷纷涌入供应不足的西班牙学生住房市场。【原文：Global investors are piling into Spain's under-supplied student housing market as the country emerges as a top destination for international students willing to pay premium rents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/spains-student-housing-draws-global-investors-overseas-enrolment-booms-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX3DCXP3SNNRTEUF3DT7AEBKD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+有望进一步低于石油产出目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士和分析师称，自欧佩克+于4月开始增产以来，该组织已完成其目标额外石油产量的约四分之三，随着生产商达到产能限制，今年晚些时候这一水平可能会下降至接近一半。【原文：OPEC+ has delivered about three quarters of the extra oil output it targeted since the group started production hikes in April, and the level may fall closer to half later in the year as producers hit capacity limits, sources and analysts said and data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-is-poised-slip-further-below-oil-output-target-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QT6KM5TAIBLDHHQFVSYQ6VNAZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收更多关税后欧洲制药股下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普公布新一轮惩罚性关税（包括对品牌药品征收100%的关税）之后，欧洲最大制药公司的股票在周五早盘交易中下跌。【原文：Shares in Europe's biggest pharma companies fell in early trading on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled a new round of punishing tariffs, including 100% duties on branded drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/european-pharma-shares-drop-after-trump-threatens-more-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLUCSMGJZJO4ZJVSNE7APP5YFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>