<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 22:35:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 22:34:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[专家称波音罢工可能加剧全球喷气客机短缺]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内高管和分析师表示，波音公司16年来的首次罢工可能会进一步加剧全球喷气式客机的短缺，而这种短缺一直在推高机票价格，迫使航空公司延长老式喷气式客机的飞行时间。【原文：Boeing's first strike in 16 years could further compound global shortages of jetliners that have been pushing up airfares and forcing airlines to keep older jets flying longer, industry executives and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-could-exacerbate-global-jetliner-shortage-experts-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WC47EAY3TZOW3AS54I4N6N7P2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 22:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊坎企业赢得投资者诉讼驳回令]]></title><description><![CDATA[伊坎企业（Icahn Enterprises）赢得了一项诉讼的撤诉，该诉讼称伊坎企业通过发放不可持续的高股息来支持其主要投资者、亿万富翁卡尔-伊坎（Carl Icahn）的个人借贷和经济利益，从而人为抬高了股价。【原文：Icahn Enterprises won the dismissal of a lawsuit claiming it artificially inflated its share price by issuing unsustainably high dividends to support the personal borrowing and financial interests of billionaire Carl Icahn, its majority investor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/icahn-enterprises-wins-dismissal-investor-lawsuit-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXQS4DBJ2JMKJNAQV2PFI26Y7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 21:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美联储准备开始缩表，利率变动的规模和速度成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储是下周的焦点，因为美国央行将在货币政策会议上降息多少以及未来几个月降低借贷成本的步伐都存在不确定性。【原文：The Federal Reserve is in focus next week, as uncertainty swirls over how much the U.S. central bank will cut interest rates at its monetary policy meeting and the pace at which it will reduce borrowing costs in coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-size-speed-rate-moves-focus-fed-poised-start-cuts-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KS4L2V2JBKD7CRC7TN56HNWZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 21:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司面临 9 月 23 日的审查截止日期]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士称，美国一个强大的国家安全小组正在审查新日铁以 149 亿美元竞购美国钢铁公司的交易，该小组将在 9 月 23 日的最后期限前就白宫是否应阻止该交易提出建议。【原文：A powerful U.S. national security panel reviewing Nippon Steel's $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel faces a Sept. 23 deadline to recommend whether the White House should block the deal, two people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nippon-steel-bid-us-steel-faces-sept-23-review-deadline-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROXQ5FSAIJMUXMZ7F7G6NVG5OE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 21:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司寻求推迟恢复每天四班飞往中国的美国航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周五以中国市场持续面临挑战为由，请求美国交通部允许其推迟恢复每天四班飞往中国的航班。【原文：Delta Air Lines on Friday asked the U.S. Transportation Department to allow it to delay resuming four daily flights to China, citing ongoing challenges in the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-seeks-delay-resuming-four-daily-us-flights-china-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EZ6TJTOA5MDLPMDLJKJY7JFSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ADM 公司碳捕集项目发生泄漏，违反了美国水法和许可证规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护署（U.S. Environmental Protection Agency）发现，位于伊利诺伊州的美国首个大型地下碳封存设施发生泄漏，阿彻-丹尼尔斯-米德兰（Archer-Daniels-Midland）农业综合企业周五证实，该公司违反了联邦安全饮用水规定及其地下注入许可。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has found that Archer-Daniels-Midland violated federal safe drinking water rules and its underground injection permit with a leak at the first major U.S. underground carbon sequestration facility in Illinois, the agribusiness company confirmed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/adm-violates-us-water-laws-permit-after-leak-carbon-capture-project-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2OXTM3C35OG7LV2GZAXBX2ZXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[山姆-班克曼-弗里德的律师在上诉中称，陪审团只看到了 "一半的情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[山姆-班克曼-弗里德的律师周五在上诉中辩称，陪审团判定山姆-班克曼-弗里德从其 FTX 加密货币交易所的客户那里窃取了数十亿美元，但只看到了 "一半的情况"，因为法官不允许引入关键证据。【原文：The jury that convicted Sam Bankman-Fried of stealing billions of dollars from customers of his FTX cryptocurrency exchange only saw "half the picture" because the judge did not allow in critical evidence, his lawyer argued in their appeal on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/sam-bankman-frieds-jury-only-saw-half-picture-lawyer-says-appeal-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K36SGEKVZFMWTIFMLWANFRDFQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:05:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛仍认为美联储下周将降息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）周五表示，它继续呼吁在下周的联邦公开市场委员会会议上实行四分之一个百分点的宽松政策，这与新闻报道中有关更激进减息的猜测形成了鲜明对比。【原文：Goldman Sachs on Friday said it continues to call for a quarter percentage point easing at next week's Federal Open Market Committee meeting, which contrasted with news stories about refreshed speculation of a more aggressive cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/goldman-sachs-still-sees-25-basis-point-fed-cut-next-week-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AB57S2EMFRJC3K64DYAHKF7CLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 19:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔格林支付 1.068 亿美元了结美国对处方账单欺诈的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五表示，沃尔格林博姿联盟（Walgreens Boots Alliance）同意支付 1.068 亿美元，以了结其欺诈性地向美国政府开具从未配发的处方的指控。【原文：Walgreens Boots Alliance agreed to pay $106.8 million to settle charges it fraudulently billed the U.S. government for prescriptions that were never dispensed, the Department of Justice said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/walgreens-paying-1068-million-settle-us-charges-over-prescription-billing-fraud-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SA6DJCZ77JJGVLBEJX27KQD7GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 19:41:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达的股市主导地位助推标准普尔 500 指数大幅波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）股价的大幅上涨仍然对 S&amp;P 500 指数产生着巨大的影响，这加剧了人们的担忧，即如果这家芯片制造巨头的命运出现转折，更广泛的市场可能会受到损害。【原文：Nvidia's huge stock rally is still exerting an outsized influence over the S&amp;P 500 index , reinforcing concerns that broader markets could be hurt if the chipmaking giant's fortunes turn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidias-stock-market-dominance-fuels-big-swings-sp-500-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JO3DB4YDCRJHFCDRLNRDNHPCUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 19:35:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：加航罢工的可能性有多大，会产生什么影响？]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大航空公司（Air Canada）与其飞行员正就新的劳动合同僵持不下，并面临着在周日前达成协议以避免罢工行动的最后期限。【原文：Air Canada and its pilots are locked in a standoff over a new labor contract and face a deadline by Sunday to reach a deal that would avert strike action.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/how-likely-is-an-air-canada-strike-what-impact-would-it-have-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FVINSFPUZMANCISQ3BM5QO274</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 19:27:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔格林同意支付 1.068 亿美元，以了结美国对处方收费的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周五表示，沃尔格林博姿联盟（Walgreens Boots Alliance）同意支付 1.068 亿美元，以了结其向美国政府收取从未配发的处方药费用的指控。【原文：Walgreens Boots Alliance agreed to pay $106.8 million to settle charges it billed the U.S. government for prescriptions that were never dispensed, the Department of Justice said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/walgreens-agrees-pay-1068-mln-settle-us-charges-over-prescription-billing-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIFWHSSCLRJKVLW37F5SWOH2PQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 19:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示不会出售其在 Truth Social 公司的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普周五告诉记者，他不会出售自己在 Truth Social 公司的股份，也不会离开这个由他创建的社交媒体平台。【原文：Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump is not selling his shares of the company that owns Truth Social and will not leave the social medial platform that he created, he told reporters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-is-not-selling-his-shares-truth-social-company-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7ID5AHBEBMOHEC7WPS3P4RB5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 18:40:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，X 不太可能受具有里程碑意义的欧盟技术规则管辖]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位直接了解此事的人士周五表示，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 社交媒体平台不太可能受到欧盟旨在控制大科技公司权力的里程碑式科技规则的约束，因为它不符合规则中的 "守门人 "标准。【原文：Elon Musk's X social media platform is unlikely to be subjected to landmark EU tech rules which aim to rein in the power of Big Tech because it does not meet the rules' gatekeeper criteria, a person with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/x-unlikely-fall-under-landmark-eu-tech-rules-source-says-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7T2K2QBU5I2VM4BFZSHMOWCSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 18:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席财务官称波音罢工对 MAX 目标和供应链构成挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司首席财务官布赖恩-韦斯特（Brian West）周五表示，波音公司美国西海岸工厂3万多名工人周五开始的罢工将使该公司更难实现737 MAX的生产目标和稳定供应链。【原文：A strike beginning Friday by more than 30,000 of Boeing's U.S. West Coast factory workers will make it harder for the planemaker to meet a 737 MAX production target and stabilize its supply chain, CFO Brian West said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-poses-challenge-max-targets-supply-chain-cfo-says-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5NCCPD4J5IADGQWRYBPM3EG2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:45:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，欧盟计划于 9 月 25 日就提高对中国电动汽车的关税进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引熟悉该计划的人士的话报道称，欧盟计划于9月25日举行投票，对从中国进口的电动汽车征收明确的关税。【原文：The European Union is aiming to hold a vote to introduce definitive tariffs on electric vehicles imported from China on Sept. 25, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-plans-sept-25-vote-raising-tariffs-evs-china-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWWOTGQ4DBOJNOBCF7QNRAXSCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:38:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》报道：白宫官员发出推迟美国钢铁公司收购决定的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周五报道，白宫官员表示将推迟就日本新日铁公司收购美国钢铁公司一事做出决定。【原文：White House officials have signaled a delay in taking a decision regarding the takeover of U.S. Steel by Japan's Nippon Steel , the Washington Post reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/white-house-officials-signal-delay-us-steel-takeover-decision-washington-post-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYRVUKCHJFPLPG3UFZJNYYBRKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:12:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称贝恩资本为出售英国 esure 物色顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士告诉路透社，私募股权公司贝恩资本（Bain Capital）已为可能出售英国汽车和住宅保险公司 esure 物色了顾问。【原文：Private equity firm Bain Capital has lined up advisers for the possible sale of British motor and home insurer esure, three people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-capital-taps-advisers-sale-uks-esure-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">362YASQENVMSBIHGTUSPPDEELM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[评级机构惠誉称波音公司长期罢工带来降级风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉周五表示，波音公司的长期罢工可能会带来信用评级下调的风险。【原文：Fitch said on Friday an extended strike at Boeing could pose a risk for a credit ratings downgrade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ratings-agency-fitch-says-extended-strike-boeing-poses-downgrade-risk-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMJRMT6T65N7NJIUI7246ZFCWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:29:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，欧盟暂时不可能向谷歌下达分拆令]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接知情人士透露，欧盟反垄断官员正在考虑向 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌发出命令，要求其停止广告技术业务中的反竞争行为，但不会像他们最初警告的那样发出解散令。【原文：EU antitrust officials are considering an order to Alphabet unit Google to stop its anti-competitive practices in its adtech business but will not issue a breakup order as they had originally warned, people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-break-up-order-google-unlikely-now-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGOFCHG7NFJJZLGZHEQJWYMP6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息 50 个基点与降息 25 个基点的可能性几乎一样大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的利率期货合约交易显示，美联储下周大幅降息的可能性几乎与通常规模的降息一样大，因为金融市场认为美联储采取更激进行动的可能性更大。【原文：The Federal Reserve is nearly as likely to deliver an outsized interest-rate cut next week as a more-usual-sized reduction, trading in rate-futures contracts suggested on Friday, as financial markets priced in a bigger chance that the Fed will move more aggressively.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-seen-nearly-likely-cut-rates-by-50-bps-25-bps-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA5KKDCNZ5NZTC2QGLBYP7UVUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:09:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特鲁多称政府向加航和飞行员施压以避免罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理贾斯汀-特鲁多（Justin Trudeau）周五表示，加拿大政府将继续向加拿大航空公司及其飞行员工会施加一切压力，以避免可能最快于下周开始的罢工。【原文：The Canadian government will continue to put all the pressure it can on Air Canada and its pilots' union to avert a strike that could start as soon as next week, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trudeau-says-govt-pressuring-air-canada-pilots-avert-strike-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZR6PKHSGJOYBMPOJPXUJBQNGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:56:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注 "重植"，美国制造业 ETF 赢得资产青睐]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者纷纷涌入交易所交易基金，重点关注那些正在美国恢复或扩大生产并利用政府补贴的公司。【原文：Investors are piling into exchange traded funds focused on companies that are reviving or expanding production in the U.S. and taking advantage of government subsidies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-etfs-win-assets-investors-bet-reshoring-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7YRKTULYVLEJKHVDF7ZBKQAXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音罢工使等待交货的 737 MAX 客户成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司西海岸工厂的工人在一致拒绝了一份合同后，于周五早些时候离开了工作岗位，停止了该公司最畅销的 737 MAX 喷气式飞机的生产。【原文：Boeing's West Coast factory workers walked off the job early on Friday after they unanimously rejected a contract, halting production of the company's best-selling 737 MAX jet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-puts-spotlight-737-max-customers-waiting-deliveries-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO3PZLXRXRLP3MXBIK3D6NFDTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月消费者信心指数上升，通胀有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，尽管美国人在11月总统大选前仍持谨慎态度，但9月份美国消费者情绪在通胀消退的情况下有所改善。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment improved in September amid subsiding inflation, though Americans remained cautious ahead of the November presidential election, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-rises-september-inflation-eases-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWBEQXK4DBNAPLRNWUU5GNJV24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普京的商品禁令威胁令俄罗斯企业和官员感到困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗拉基米尔-普京总统出人意料地威胁要限制战略商品出口以应对西方制裁，俄罗斯官员和管理者对此感到困惑，不知道能否在不对俄罗斯造成比西方更大伤害的情况下实现这一威胁。【原文：Russian officials and managers are perplexed by President Vladimir Putin's surprise threat to limit exports of strategic commodities in response to Western sanctions, and wonder if it can be realised without hurting Russia more than the West.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/putins-commodities-ban-threat-puzzles-russian-firms-officials-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVFRHRAKAFJRTMBLOAK2GLTYEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:27:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，巴西 Azul 公司接近与出租人达成新的债务协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉谈判的人士称，巴西 Azul 航空公司已接近与出租人达成新协议，该公司将向他们提供股权，以偿还约 6 亿美元的债务。【原文：Brazilian airline Azul has moved closer to clinching a new deal with lessors, three people familiar with the talks said, as the company offers them equity to pay off some $600 million in debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-azul-close-new-debt-deal-with-lessors-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZU5PKVPWFPTJNMERPGBUQLJFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行将于 9 月 18 日加息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，巴西央行将在下周三将基准利率上调 25 个点，这很可能是为抑制持续通胀趋势而采取的短期紧缩政策的开始，其行动方向与同行相反。【原文：Brazil's central bank will raise its benchmark rate by 25 points next Wednesday at what will likely be the start of a short tightening campaign to quash persistent inflationary trends, moving the opposite way to its peers, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/brazil-central-bank-hike-rates-by-25-basis-points-sept-18-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F4ALGHTTJKCRPDPQ45FIEDZ5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步和 Waymo 将自动驾驶汽车引入奥斯汀和亚特兰大]]></title><description><![CDATA[打车平台优步（Uber Technologies）周五表示，将与 Alphabet 旗下的 Waymo 合作，在得克萨斯州奥斯汀和佐治亚州亚特兰大市推出自动驾驶打车服务。【原文：Ride-hailing platform Uber Technologies said on Friday it would bring autonomous ride hailing to Austin, Texas, and Atlanta, Georgia, in partnership with Alphabet's Waymo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-waymo-bring-autonomous-ride-hailing-austin-atlanta-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3ZFNSTLK5PGVJBDYSHU25GG4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金属资源丰富的哈萨克斯坦寻求在电池供应链中占据一席之地]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈萨克斯坦工业部长告诉路透社，哈萨克斯坦的目标是提高电动汽车（EV）电池所需金属的产量，并正在发放数百份新的勘探许可证，以吸引对该行业的新投资。【原文：Kazakhstan aims to boost output of metals needed for electric vehicle (EV) batteries and is issuing hundreds of new exploration licences to attract fresh investment in the sector, the country's industry minister told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/metals-rich-kazakhstan-seeks-niche-battery-supply-chain-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CK4JGP4B45IGVEBONPJP2UEYW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>