<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:05:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:05:20 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[DHL 首席执行官称竞争对手关于其违反反垄断规则的说法毫无根据]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国邮政服务集团 DHL 首席执行官周五表示，规模较小的竞争对手 Deutsche Versand Services GmbH 对其反竞争行为的指控毫无根据。【原文：The CEO of German postal services group DHL said on Friday that accusations of anti-competitive conduct brought by smaller rival Deutsche Versand Services GmbH were without any merit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/dhl-ceo-says-rivals-claim-it-broke-antitrust-rules-is-unfounded-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYU2JPBWGBJP7FPAFQUWKVMQII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商 Polestar 因后视影像问题召回 27816 辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周五表示，电动汽车制造商Polestar因后视摄像头问题在美国召回27816辆汽车。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Polestar is recalling 27,816 cars in the United States over an issue with the rearview camera, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestar-recalls-27816-us-vehicles-nhtsa-says-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4YUMHAQNAFJDHBGUCZ3BG6VIOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰称贸易动荡对全球经济增长构成严重风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行（HSBC）主席马克-塔克（Mark Tucker）周五表示，全球贸易关系的变化加剧了经济的不确定性，给经济增长带来了严重的潜在风险，阻碍了国际银行有效解读中期前景的努力。【原文：Shifting global trade relations have upped economic uncertainty with serious potential risks to growth, hampering attempts by international banks to read the medium term outlook effectively, HSBC Chairman Mark Tucker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-says-trade-turmoil-poses-serious-risks-global-growth-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6M27IOLDWROSBNSV67PPPGOY3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[更正： 联合国粮农组织称四月份世界粮食价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国粮食及农业组织周五表示，受谷物、肉类和乳制品价格上涨的推动，4月份全球食品商品价格上涨。【原文：Global food commodity prices increased in April, driven by higher prices for cereals, meat and dairy products, the United Nations' Food and Agriculture Organization said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/corrected-world-food-prices-increase-april-uns-fao-says-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3WXB6J4RRK5DAEXMLO7L3CDTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果股价下跌，关税成本将增加更多痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司股价周五在盘前交易中下跌近 3%，原因是这家 iPhone 制造商缩减了股票回购计划，而且首席执行官蒂姆-库克（Tim Cook）警告说，在中美贸易战肆虐的背景下，本季度与关税相关的成本将增加约 9 亿美元。【原文：Apple shares fell nearly 3% in premarket trade on Friday after the iPhone maker trimmed its share buyback program and CEO Tim Cook warned of additional tariff-related costs of about $900 million this quarter amid a raging Sino-U.S. trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-shares-fall-tariff-costs-add-more-agony-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M22HLB7HJFIDDF6BOOQSD6WY5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国 Lactalis 公司称未就可能的恒天然单位收购签署协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的乳制品集团 Lactalis 周五表示，它对国际投资感兴趣，但尚未签署收购新西兰乳制品巨头恒天然集团（Fonterra）部分股份的协议。【原文：Lactalis, the world's largest dairy group, is interested in international investments but has not signed an agreement to buy parts of New Zealand-based dairy giant Fonterra, it said on Friday following reports it was considering an offer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/frances-lactalis-says-no-deal-signed-possible-fonterra-units-purchase-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XE7JIUTZMBLYZD4R3QTI3Z73GQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧元区 4 月份通胀率保持稳定，服务价格飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元区 4 月份的通胀率保持稳定，略高于欧洲央行 2% 的目标，但潜在的价格压力比预计的要大，这可能会让欧洲央行的一些决策者感到紧张，即使贸易战可能成为更多降息的理由。【原文：Euro zone inflation held steady a touch above the ECB's 2% target in April but underlying price pressures picked up more than projected, likely making some ECB policymakers nervous, even if a trade war may justify more interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/euro-zone-inflation-holds-steady-april-service-prices-surge-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS5EZHHHDZMNVMOIQOXK5KGXZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国关税不确定性的背景下，日本贸易公司以健康回报吸引投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[从三菱商事到住友商事等日本商社都承诺，在美国关税不确定性的背景下，今年的股东回报将保持健康，同时对利润预测持谨慎态度，力图让包括沃伦-巴菲特在内的投资者感到满意。【原文：Japanese trading houses from Mitsubishi to Sumitomo Corp promised healthy shareholder returns this year amid cautious profit forecasts, trying to keep investors, including Warren Buffett, happy amid U.S. tariff uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japanese-trading-houses-lure-investors-with-healthy-returns-amid-us-tariff-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YODJBI35EVMFZINHPGEJWCGJHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 4 月份在欧洲主要市场的销量大幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着欧洲人购买更多的中国汽车以及一些人对马斯克政治观点的抗议，特斯拉 4 月份在一些欧洲市场的销量大幅下降，埃隆-马斯克的电动汽车品牌自今年年初以来的趋势有所加快。【原文：Tesla sales in some European markets fell sharply in April, in an acceleration of a trend seen since the beginning of the year for Elon Musk's EV brand, as Europeans buy more Chinese cars and some protest against his political views.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-sales-key-european-markets-plunge-april-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAMMWCOZ3FIZXKBOYBNRWBDO44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:26:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经指数》称，美国在与日本的谈判中几乎没有在关键关税问题上让步]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周五报道，在最近一次与日本同行的会谈中，美国关税谈判代表似乎不愿降低对汽车、钢铁和铝的征税--这一立场让日方感到合作可能会很困难。【原文：U.S. tariff negotiators appeared reluctant to lower levies on cars, steel and aluminium in a recent meeting with Japanese counterparts - a stance that made the Japanese side feel that cooperation could be difficult, the Nikkei newspaper reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-cedes-little-ground-key-tariffs-talks-with-japan-nikkei-says-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSPHDUTMZBIOPIRKLIEO4YGNO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行报告显示，上周抛售美股的投资者涌向日本和欧洲]]></title><description><![CDATA[博雅全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）周五表示，投资者在截至周三的一周内抛售了美国股票，买入了日本和欧洲股票。【原文：Investors sold U.S. stocks in the week ending Wednesday and bought Japanese and European shares, BofA Global Research said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-bofa-urgent-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QN53UYDPEFPSFJG2GV6UH54STQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:14:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 "评估 "美国提出的关税谈判提议；警告反对 "敲诈 "行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周五表示，北京正在 "评估 "华盛顿提出的就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收145%关税一事举行会谈的提议，但同时警告美国不要进行 "敲诈和胁迫"。【原文：Beijing is "evaluating" an offer from Washington to hold talks over U.S. President Donald Trump's 145% tariffs, China's Commerce Ministry said on Friday, although it warned the United States not to engage in "extortion and coercion."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-evaluating-us-offer-talk-tariffs-warns-against-extortion-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXDKI7UFV5IRHPNZLCCIH2J44I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚对 Lactalis 未宣布的恒天然资产竞购启动非正式审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚竞争监督机构已开始对 Lactalis 收购新西兰恒天然集团待售业务的提议进行非正式审查，尽管这家法国乳制品巨头尚未正式宣布收购要约。【原文：Australia's competition watchdog has begun an informal review of Lactalis’ proposed offer to buy New Zealand-based Fonterra’s businesses up for sale, even though the French dairy major is yet to make a formal announcement on the offer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-launches-informal-review-unannounced-lactalis-bid-fonterra-assets-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXYEUOZ7V5IZBEWO4W5P4NVCF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[壳牌第一季度利润下降 28%，但超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[壳牌周五公布的第一季度净利润为 55.8 亿美元，同比下降 28%，超出分析师预期；在油价下跌、炼油利润率低于去年的情况下，壳牌保持了股票回购计划的稳定步伐。【原文：Shell on Friday reported a 28% drop in first-quarter net profit to $5.58 billion, beating analyst expectations, and kept the pace of its share buyback programme steady amid falling oil prices and lower refining margins than last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-reports-q1-profit-558-billion-above-expectations-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWFICOOKJ5MAVJD3HGVW5OXENY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:09:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面对关税，亚马逊卖家正在备货，但这只是短期解决办法]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周四试图缓和投资者对特朗普政府关税对其电子商务业务影响的担忧，但该公司可能已没有多少选择来确保小型第三方卖家在面对巨额征税时保持不变。【原文：Amazon on Thursday tried to temper investor concerns about the impact of the Trump administration's tariffs on its e-commerce business, but the company may have few options left to ensure small third-party sellers stay put in the face of crushing levies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-sellers-are-stocking-up-face-tariffs-its-short-term-fix-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQF3TGRMSJOBZCPY2VVGP7WRBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易紧张局势缓解，日本投资者连续第六周增持外资股]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本投资者连续第六周增持海外股票，因为有迹象表明美国和中国愿意缓和贸易紧张局势，这进一步刺激了他们对海外股票的持续追捧。【原文：Japanese investors raised their foreign stock holdings for a sixth straight week as their sustained appetite for overseas equities was further bolstered by signs that the U.S. and China were willing to ease trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japanese-investors-raise-foreign-stock-holdings-sixth-week-easing-trade-tensions-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ32SFDNUJPCTEO34RYBNMX56U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moneycontrol 称凯雷集团出售印度 PNB 住房公司全部股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据商业新闻网站 Moneycontrol 周四援引条款表报道，美国私募股权投资集团凯雷集团已通过大宗交易出售了其持有的印度 PNB 住房金融公司全部 10.44% 的股份。【原文：U.S. private equity group Carlyle Group has sold its entire 10.44% stake in India's PNB Housing Finance via block deals, business news website Moneycontrol reported on Thursday, citing a termsheet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyle-group-sells-full-stake-indias-pnb-housing-moneycontrol-says-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXPVUBIPDJIUZP7H5SZHC5TX3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丹斯克银行第一季度净利润超预期，维持业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦最大的银行丹斯克银行周五公布的第一季度净利润超出预期，并维持全年利润展望不变。【原文：Denmark's biggest lender Danske Bank reported first-quarter net profit above expectations on Friday and kept its full-year profit outlook unchanged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/danske-banks-q1-net-profit-beats-forecasts-maintains-outlook-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DXFLHQ4EFM5JPMRVGEVDNJNZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行认为加息窗口正在缩小，但尚未关闭]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行的加息周期正面临着自行长上田一夫两年前执掌日本央行以来的最大考验，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税迅速缩小了进一步提高仍处于低位的借贷成本的窗口。【原文：The Bank of Japan's rate-hike cycle is facing its biggest test since Governor Kazuo Ueda took the helm two years ago, with U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs rapidly narrowing the window for further increases in still-low borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-sees-window-rate-hikes-narrowing-not-closed-yet-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFNZJBQV4VI7FIY773HHOIP4MU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三菱预计年度利润下降 26%，理由是缺乏资本收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本贸易公司三菱商事（Mitsubishi Corp）周五预测，截至 3 月份的全年净利润将下降 26%，降至 7000 亿日元（48.2 亿美元），理由是没有重大资本收益。【原文：Japanese trading house Mitsubishi Corp forecast on Friday its net profit for the year ending March would fall 26% to 700 billion yen ($4.82 billion), citing the absence of major capital gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-mitsubishi-annual-profit-down-1-misses-forecasts-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2E3AS66NVNKTLOAGUPKKXN47PA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:22:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普拟对小包裹征税，一些零售商放弃美国市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国终止了对小包裹的关税豁免，一些零售商停止了向美国客户的销售，而另一些零售商则在寻求临时变通办法，希望关税率能够降低。【原文：As the United States ends a tariff exemption for small parcels, some retailers have stopped selling to U.S. customers while others are seeking temporary workarounds in the hope the tariff rate may be reduced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trump-moves-tax-small-parcels-some-retailers-give-up-us-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDRZOJNBTFJW7LP3ILYZXYSWRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[StanChart 第一季度利润增长 10%，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[渣打银行周五公布的季度利润增长了 10%，原因是财富、市场和全球银行业务的强劲表现提高了收入，但渣打也表示，关税的增加可能会对信贷质量造成压力。【原文：Standard Chartered on Friday reported a 10% rise in quarterly profit as strong wealth, markets and global banking businesses boosted revenue, though it also said increased tariffs would likely weigh on credit quality.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/stanchart-books-10-rise-first-quarter-profit-beats-estimate-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WI3X5SLK5RORXHPYISNOD4JFFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:55:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻北京迹象明显，苹果凶多吉少]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23T3GXARNFM43DOXGLTQ6RGBUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令，旨在削减对 NPR 和 PBS 的拨款]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫表示，唐纳德-特朗普签署了一项行政命令，旨在削减对新闻机构全国公共广播电台（NPR）和公共广播公司（PBS）的拨款，这是美国总统最近一次试图利用联邦拨款作为打击他不看好的机构的筹码。【原文：Donald Trump signed an executive order that aims to cut funding to news outlets NPR and PBS, the White House said, marking the U.S. president's latest attempt to use federal funding as leverage against institutions he does not view favorably.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/trump-signs-order-that-aims-cut-funding-npr-pbs-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7R3BYGRIJJ2RL3TUOKQDGPWTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国低值套餐关税豁免结束，但美国收税问题依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府终止了美国对来自中国和香港的低价值货物的免税准入，取消了Shein、Temu和其他电子商务公司以及芬太尼和其他非法货物贩运者所享有的 "微量 "豁免。【原文：The Trump administration ended U.S. duty-free access for low-value shipments from China and Hong Kong, removing the "de minimis" exemptions availed of by Shein, Temu and other e-commerce firms as well as traffickers of fentanyl and other illicit goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-low-value-package-tariff-exemption-ends-questions-remain-over-us-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7ZM2XSKJZO23HNYE3DTPTI22I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴塞尔协议老板表示，资本规则的 "瑞士终结 "对瑞银并不不公平]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行业监管机构负责人表示，瑞士现行的银行资本规则并没有不公平地惩罚瑞士的贷款机构与其他地方的竞争对手，从而回击了瑞银集团为反对政府强化这些规则的计划而提出的论点。【原文：The head of the world's banking watchdog said Switzerland's existing rules on bank capital do not unfairly penalise its lenders versus rivals elsewhere, pushing back on arguments UBS has made to oppose government plans to toughen them up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/basel-boss-signals-swiss-finish-capital-rules-is-not-unfair-ubs-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3M5WWXKGJNTTEBS3IQYKVO3BE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税引发的不确定性被认为抑制了美国 4 月份的就业增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）激进的关税政策导致经济不确定性加剧，美国4月份的就业增长可能放缓，不过企业继续囤积工人，使劳动力市场暂时保持活跃。【原文：U.S. job growth likely slowed in April amid heightened economic uncertainty because of President Donald Trump's aggressive tariff policy, though companies continued to hoard workers, keeping the labor market humming for now.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/tariff-induced-uncertainty-seen-curbing-us-job-growth-april-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5KCRWNQK5N3BHIDF72XJGNODU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本第一季度国内生产总值可能因内需疲软、进口激增而萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易政策使经济增长前景黯淡，日本经济可能在第一季度出现一年来的首次萎缩，原因是内需疲软和进口超过出口。【原文：Japan's economy probably contracted for the first time in a year in the first quarter, weighed down by softer domestic demand and imports outperforming exports, a Reuters poll showed, as U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies dim the growth outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-q1-gdp-likely-contracted-soft-domestic-demand-import-surge-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5RBRBNR6FKBPA4WUEFPWDNSRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚航所有者 Capital A 寻求在香港上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚廉价航空公司亚航（AirAsia）的所有者 Capital A 公司周五表示，该公司正在探讨在香港证券交易所上市的事宜，因为该公司希望在摆脱财务困境后扩大获得全球资本的渠道。【原文：Malaysia's Capital A , the owner of budget carrier AirAsia, said on Friday it was exploring listing on the Hong Kong stock exchange, as it looks to broaden access to global capital once it exits its financially distressed status.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/malaysias-capital-exploring-hong-kong-listing-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGAW3C25UVIDFGI5BPQPRB3K4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对华黑名单错误百出、细节过时]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对 2023 年和 2024 年被列入美国实体名单的近 100 家中国和香港公司进行了审查，发现超过四分之一的公司包含错误的详细信息，如错误的名称和地址以及过时的信息。【原文：A Reuters review of almost 100 Chinese and Hong Kong companies added to the U.S. entity list in 2023 and 2024 found more than a quarter contained erroneous details, such as incorrect names and addresses and outdated information.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-blacklist-china-is-riddled-with-errors-outdated-details-2025-05-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6RRVFWPY5ILTMNQNPRU4XYADU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>