<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:12:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:12:04 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席米兰称预计 12 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）表示，他预计美国央行将在 12 月降息，尽管有许多无投票权的决策者可能并不希望降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran says he expects the U.S. central bank to cut interest rates in December, despite the number of non-voting policymakers who may not want to.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-miran-says-he-expects-rate-cut-december-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSA4NFQB4VMVFNOOB2NZ5WQTJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛提拔 638 名董事总经理，创 2021 年以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街贷款公司高盛（Goldman Sachs）在一份公司备忘录中表示，明年将有 638 名高管晋升为董事总经理，这是自 2021 年以来的最高值，因为该银行受益于整个行业投资银行业务的回暖。【原文：Wall Street lender Goldman Sachs will promote 638 executives to managing directors next year, the highest since 2021, a company memo said, as the bank benefits from a pick-up in investment banking across the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-promotes-638-managing-directors-highest-since-2021-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNIF3V4LJVMNLCXRICRJT2PHXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞波币称 "瘦身 "美联储主账户虽有限制但仍有吸引力]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币巨头瑞波公司（Ripple）的一位高管表示，该公司支持为非银行设立一个 "瘦身 "美联储支付账户的想法，这可能会改变游戏规则，同时解决银行对金融稳定性和竞争风险的担忧。【原文：Crypto giant Ripple supports the idea of a "skinny" Federal Reserve payments account for non-banks, which could still be a game changer while addressing banks' concerns over financial stability and competition risks, a top company executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ripple-says-skinny-fed-master-account-is-attractive-despite-limitations-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5V2NB5FOEJN7VBAGA4BTHT64TI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:49:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀高企，美联储哈莫克对美联储政策感到紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周四表示，她担心货币政策可能无法正确应对当前的通货膨胀。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack said Thursday she’s concerned monetary policy may not be in the right place to deal with current inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-hammock-is-nervous-about-fed-policy-given-high-inflation-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45NPZKUIGFJDTCMJJECGU3YUA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BillionToOne 在纳斯达克上市后股价大涨，估值达 44 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[BillionToOne 周四的估值为 44 亿美元，此前这家分子诊断公司的股价在纳斯达克首次亮相时大涨 66.67%，成为在政府停摆之际登陆美国股市的最新一家公司。【原文：BillionToOne was valued at $4.4 billion on Thursday, after the molecular diagnostics firm's shares jumped 66.67% in their Nasdaq debut, becoming the latest company to tap U.S. bourses amid a government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/billiontoone-valued-44-billion-shares-surge-blockbuster-nasdaq-debut-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQPQ6DH5ORKMPGE2MFYKAEOFUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:44:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，电力供应限制导致欧洲、中东和非洲地区数据中心推广放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[第一太平戴维斯（Savills）的一份报告显示，尽管需求激增，但到目前为止，2025 年欧洲、中东和非洲地区的数据中心容量增长速度与去年同期相比有所放缓，原因是可用电力的缺乏延误了项目的时间表。【原文：Data centre capacity growth across Europe, the Middle East and Africa has slowed down in 2025 so far compared to the same period last year, despite surging demand, as a lack of available power delays project timelines, a report from Savills found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/power-supply-constraints-slowing-emea-data-centre-rollout-report-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RBGRFUWLBNXPOMUZK5BDPO6ZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威廉姆斯称美联储的独立性具有全球意义]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周四表示，美联储的独立性不仅对美国经济，而且对全球经济都 "极其重要"，因为它使美国中央银行能够控制通货膨胀，而不必考虑短期的政治后果。【原文：The independence of the Federal Reserve is "incredibly important" not just for the U.S. economy but also for the global economy because it is what allows the U.S. central bank to control inflation without regard to short-term political consequences, New York Fed President John Williams said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-independence-has-global-importance-williams-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54C2JNCELJPFRMLAPUMMBUSOEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私人报告显示 10 月份美国劳动力市场疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的数据显示，10月份美国经济因政府和零售业的失业而减少了就业岗位，而企业削减成本和采用人工智能导致宣布的裁员人数激增。【原文：The U.S. economy shed jobs in October amid losses in the government and retail sectors, while cost-cutting and the adoption of artificial intelligence by businesses led to a surge in announced layoffs, data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/private-reports-suggest-us-labor-market-weakened-october-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5T2T456KNM2TLPYGAQYVS7WWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:27:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大银行表示将裁员 230 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大央行高级副行长周四表示，央行将裁员约 230 人，以减少开支。【原文：Bank of Canada's Senior Deputy Governor said on Thursday that the central bank will be reducing its workforce by around 230 people as part of a drive to reduce expenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/bank-canada-says-it-will-be-reducing-its-workforce-by-230-jobs-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IR2UCYT2Q5JD5DJQZ5XNNVWUNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈马克倾向于因通胀高企而不再降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联储主席贝丝-哈马克（Beth Hammack）周四表示，目前的高通胀水平不利于美国央行再次降息。【原文：Cleveland Federal Reserve President Beth Hammack said on Thursday ongoing high levels of inflation argue against the U.S. central bank cutting interest rates again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-hammack-leans-against-more-rate-cuts-because-high-inflation-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZXSDZIYSRPJNF3T4C52MZWPWY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞和诺和诺德竞购战的目标 Metsera 是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[辉瑞（Pfizer）和诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）正在对生物技术公司 Metsera 展开竞购战，因为这两家制药巨头正寻求在蓬勃发展的减肥药市场扩充其产品线。【原文：Pfizer and Novo Nordisk are locked in a bidding war for biotech firm Metsera as the pharmaceutical giants seek to augment their pipeline in the booming weight-loss drug market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/what-is-metsera-target-pfizers-novo-nordisks-bidding-war-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI7ICVBJGBJWXMYXMADDFRCJFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:01:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着博彩业的发展，Betclic 所有者 Banijay 的利润增长了 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国媒体集团 Banijay 周四公布的九个月利润增长了 10%，这主要得益于其博彩部门，该公司正准备完成一项重大收购，从而使其博彩业务翻番。【原文：French media group Banijay posted a 10% rise in nine-month profits on Thursday, driven by its betting division as it prepares to close a major acquisition that will double its gaming business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/betclic-owner-banijays-profit-rises-10-betting-gains-strength-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54EBFS3TDVITTKUADI6LB7NC6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:49:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿波罗支持的墨西哥航空公司在纽交所首次亮相估值 28 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿波罗支持的墨西哥航空公司集团周四在纽约证券交易所首次上市时股价上涨了 0.84%，墨西哥航空公司的估值接近 28 亿美元。【原文：Apollo-backed Grupo Aeromexico's shares rose 0.84% in their New York Stock Exchange debut on Thursday, valuing the Mexican airline at nearly $2.8 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/apollo-backed-grupo-aeromexico-valued-28-billion-open-nyse-debut-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XF45EWNFJFJE3DNSK4Z2YTDGBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:45:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 NRF 预测，美国假日销售额将首次突破 1 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国全国零售联合会周四预测，美国假日销售额有望首次突破1万亿美元，尽管宏观经济压力笼罩着消费者支出。【原文：U.S. holiday sales are expected to surpass $1 trillion for the first time, the National Retail Federation forecast on Thursday, even as macroeconomic pressures loom over consumer spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-holiday-sales-set-top-1-trillion-first-time-nrf-forecasts-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SD6JP54FYRMB5CV7NLMJ3C4T5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MEG Energy 股东投票支持 Cenovus 的收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大油砂生产商 MEG Energy 的股东周四投票赞成 Cenovus Energy 的收购，结束了长达数月的收购战。【原文：Canadian oil sands producer MEG Energy shareholders on Thursday voted in favor of a buyout by Cenovus Energy , ending a months-long takeover battle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/meg-energy-shareholders-vote-favor-cenovus-takeover-bid-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EI4EOFPQZVL4ZAJ7GPGS2YWZNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普扩大美国关键矿产清单，将铜、冶金煤纳入其中]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周四公布了一份其认为对美国经济和国家安全至关重要的新的重要矿产清单，其中增加了对电动汽车、电网和数据中心至关重要的铜，以及用于制造焦炭的冶金煤。【原文：The Trump administration on Thursday unveiled a new list of critical minerals it deems essential to the U.S. economy and national security, adding copper, which is vital to electric vehicles, power grids, and data centers, as well as metallurgical coal, which is used to make coke.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-expands-us-critical-minerals-list-include-copper-metallurgical-coal-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">765YQGJLWZJJPGDM5QQRE5PASA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:06:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙对人工智能生成未成年人性图像处以罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙数据保护机构周四表示，它已对一名分享人工智能生成的未成年人真实面孔性图像的人处以罚款，西班牙媒体称这是欧洲首个对此类内容进行经济处罚的案例。【原文：Spain's data protection agency on Thursday said it had fined a person for sharing AI-generated sexual images of minors using real faces, in what Spanish media said was the first case in Europe of a financial penalty for this type of content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/spain-issues-fine-ai-generated-sexual-images-minors-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UO764UDR7NKNJABHZD42DL45HQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:51:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 Ivey PMI 显示 10 月份经济活动扩张速度放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四公布的 Ivey 采购经理人指数（PMI）数据显示，10 月份加拿大经济活动增速放缓，价格指数走高。【原文：Canadian economic activity expanded at a slower pace in October as a measure of prices edged higher, Ivey Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-ivey-pmi-shows-activity-expanding-slower-pace-october-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PK7JS5LPNFNEVKFAL46FXKW2XQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国地区性银行经受住了 CRE 风暴的考验，但办公楼贷款仍处于落后状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师们表示，尽管少数贷款变质引发了担忧，但美国地区性银行的商业房地产贷款账簿被证明具有广泛的韧性，但办公楼行业仍然是一个痛点。【原文：U.S. regional banks' commercial real estate loan books are proving broadly resilient despite worries sparked by a handful of soured loans, but the office sector continues to be a pain point, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regional-banks-weather-cre-storm-office-loans-continue-lag-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNFLSBPF65KHLFF2HJCELWN45E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺推出新款经济型电动车 Twingo，以促进销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷诺周四发布了新款电动小型车 Twingo，这家法国汽车制造商试图利用这个广受欢迎的老车型名称和不足 2 万欧元（约合 2.3 万美元）的售价来促进其电动汽车的销售。【原文：Renault unveiled its new electric Twingo small car on Thursday as the French automaker seeks to leverage a popular old model name and a price tag of under 20,000 euros ($23,000) to boost its electric vehicle sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-revives-twingo-with-new-affordable-electric-version-boost-sales-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6IHDTFUQBOADLO3ZOBLCF5LMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国公司与嘉吉、LDC 等贸易商签署 52 亿美元农产品交易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国供应链运营商和房地产开发商厦门建发周四表示，该公司已与嘉吉公司（Cargill）和路易达孚公司（Louis Dreyfus Company）等七家农业企业和贸易公司在上海签订了总额超过 52 亿美元的合同。【原文：Chinese supply chain operator and property developer Xiamen C&amp;D said on Thursday it had signed contracts totalling over $5.2 billion with seven agribusinesses and trading houses including Cargill and Louis Dreyfus Company in Shanghai.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-firm-signs-52-billion-agricultural-deals-with-traders-including-cargill-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QK355NMDFFKUPHP6X5HWVKOU4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:57:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比：缺乏通胀数据支持放慢脚步]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周四表示，政府停摆期间缺乏通胀方面的官方数据 "凸显 "了他对进一步降息的谨慎态度。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee on Thursday said the lack of official data on inflation during the government shutdown "accentuates" his caution about cutting interest rates further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-lack-inflation-data-argues-going-slow-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZGSQVBHVFOILAFXXXNNUTRG3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:45:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官批准司法部撤销波音刑事案件的决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官周四批准了司法部提出的撤销对波音公司刑事案件的请求，允许这家飞机制造商避免因两起造成 346 人死亡的 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故而被起诉，但他严厉批评了政府的决定。【原文：A U.S. judge on Thursday approved a Justice Department request to dismiss a criminal case against Boeing, allowing the planemaker to avoid prosecution on a charge stemming from two fatal 737 MAX plane crashes that killed 346 people, but he harshly criticized the government's decision.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-judge-approves-doj-decision-drop-boeing-criminal-case-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3GNSOLZ4NPO3INGFS723G63HI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易谈判代表希望与瑞士达成贸易协议，并称与墨西哥的谈判正在进行中]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周四表示，美国贸易官员本周会见了来自瑞士的代表，并正在与墨西哥、中美洲和西半球其他国家的贸易官员进行讨论。【原文：U.S. trade officials met with representatives from Switzerland this week and are having discussions with trade officials from Mexico, Central America and others in the Western Hemisphere, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-trade-negotiator-eyes-trade-deal-with-switzerland-says-talks-underway-with-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV5VIVAPZNILDMPNPJLFC23Y2M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:42:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CarMax 长期首席执行官比尔-纳什将离职，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[CarMax公司周四表示，其首席执行官比尔-纳什（Bill Nash）将于本月底卸任，此前这家二手车零售商预计第三季度利润疲软，因为该公司正在努力削减成本，更好地应对汽车需求的下降。【原文：CarMax's CEO Bill Nash is stepping down by end of the month, the preowned car retailer said on Thursday, after it forecast a weak third-quarter profit as it battles to cut costs and better navigate lower vehicle demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/carmaxs-longtime-ceo-bill-nash-depart-shares-drop-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGEI55W5OBLPJLGKDQFLNUOO5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球调查显示，半数以上对冲基金投资加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球对冲基金对加密货币市场的投资正在增加、
 据一份行业报告称，随着美国政府对数字资产的支持，全球对冲基金对加密货币市场的投资正在增加，目前已有超过一半的对冲基金投资于这一领域。
 行业报告
 周四发布的
 周四发布的一份行业报告显示。【原文：Global hedge funds' exposure to crypto markets is increasing, 
 and more than half are now invested in the sector, with the U.S. government's embrace of digital assets boosting interest, according to an 
 industry report 
 published 
 on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/more-than-half-hedge-funds-invested-crypto-global-survey-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3D574FUGBLE7LIM4I6LYQ7RZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:36:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将于周五晚些时候详细说明主要机场的航班削减计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周四正在努力敲定一项史无前例的计划的细节，该计划将削减美国40个高流量机场10%的航班，以解决空中交通管制员在联邦政府创纪录停摆期间的安全问题。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration on Thursday was working to hammer out details of an unprecedented plan to cut 10% of flights at 40 high-traffic U.S. airports to address safety concerns regarding air traffic controllers amid a record-setting federal government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-detail-flight-cut-plan-major-airports-later-friday-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q27OI7IFRBM2HKEAD6BLYGOONI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Papa John's 首席执行官表示，公司专注于执行战略，但对其他选择持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[Papa John's 首席执行官托德-佩内戈（Todd Penegor）周四表示，这家美国比萨连锁店正专注于执行其战略，以提升价值，但他也指出，如果有其他选择，该公司也会考虑。【原文：Papa John's CEO Todd Penegor on Thursday said the U.S. pizza chain is focusing on executing its strategy to drive value, but noted it would consider alternatives if they were available.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/papa-johns-focused-executing-its-strategy-open-alternatives-ceo-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYSERXDWIFO7DNKP56S54ONB2A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大到难以下咽？卢克石油帝国对贡渥来说不是简单的收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家和内部人士称，俄罗斯能源集团卢克石油公司的外国帝国是贡渥集团迄今为止最大的收购目标，但看上去远远超出了瑞士交易商的借贷能力。【原文：Russian energy group Lukoil's foreign empire is suitor Gunvor's biggest acquisition target to date but looks far beyond the Swiss trader's borrowing capacity, bankers and insiders say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/too-big-swallow-lukoil-empire-no-simple-acquisition-gunvor-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3XCQFEM4BNN7LNLDTRKLRCTT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软成立 "超级智能 "团队，以医疗诊断为起点]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软正在组建一个新的团队，希望从医疗诊断开始，在某些领域打造能力远超人类的人工智能。【原文：Microsoft is forming a new team that wants to build artificial intelligence that is vastly more capable than humans in certain domains, starting with medical diagnostics, the executive leading the effort told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-launches-superintelligence-team-targeting-medical-diagnosis-start-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLWWFHNQA5LUXIC72D34QKHWLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>