<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:46:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:46:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据共同社报道，受中国稀土限制影响，日产将缩减新型电动汽车的生产计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据共同社周二报道，由于中国的稀土出口限制导致零部件短缺，日产汽车公司正在缩减其新型聆风电动车的生产计划。【原文：Nissan Motor is scaling back production plans for its new Leaf electric vehicle model because China's rare earth export restrictions have led to a shortage of parts, Kyodo News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-scale-back-production-plan-new-ev-due-china-rare-earth-curbs-kyodo-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QUK325IHFO5RNZ3ZAJWLEW2LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[戴姆勒卡车的目标是到 2030 年，工业业务的有机销售额增长 3-5]]></title><description><![CDATA[戴姆勒卡车公司（Daimler Truck）周二预计，在服务业的推动、欧洲向零排放车辆的转变、北美的职业卡车以及印度和国防部门的增长的推动下，到 2030 年，其工业业务的年有机收入将增长 3% 至 5%。【原文：Daimler Truck on Tuesday projected yearly organic revenue growth of 3% to 5% until 2030 in its industrial business, driven by a service push, a shift to zero-emission vehicles in Europe, vocational trucks in North America, and growth in India and the defense sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/daimler-truck-targets-3-5-organic-sales-growth-industrial-business-through-2030-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4WJBL7FSVJNTGG7XPF6XHQ5XA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔将在 2026 年分拆之前审查两大业务的替代方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔周二表示，在这家工业巨头准备进行三方分拆之际，将对其服务于运输和物流行业的两项业务进行战略评估。【原文：Honeywell said on Tuesday it would evaluate strategic alternatives for two of its businesses that serve the transportation and logistics industries as the industrial giant prepares for its three-way split.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honeywell-review-alternatives-two-businesses-ahead-2026-split-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAQVKIWLZVMLZLW2UEHIOYS24A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利将不得不放弃合并条件的报道引发联合信贷银行和 BPM 股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，布鲁塞尔将下令意大利政府撤回对该交易提出的条件，意大利第二大银行联合信贷银行及其收购目标 Banco BPM 的股价周二因此上涨。【原文：Shares in Italy's second biggest bank UniCredit and its takeover target Banco BPM rose on Tuesday on a media report that said Brussels will order the Italian government to withdraw the conditions it has put on the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-bpm-shares-up-report-italy-will-have-drop-merger-conditions-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YA5RP7TNQNOLVCMCETVA3BMX2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBM 推出新型芯片和服务器，致力于简化人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际商业机器公司（International Business Machines）周二宣布推出一系列新的数据中心芯片和服务器，并称这些产品将比竞争对手更省电，并将简化在企业运营中推广人工智能的过程。【原文：International Business Machines on Tuesday announced a new line of data center chips and servers that it says will be more power-efficient than rivals and will simplify the process of rolling out artificial intelligence in business operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ibm-rolls-out-new-chips-servers-aims-simplified-ai-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZNWUTH4DZMRNMHKER6MJEF4DQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预订公司告诉法庭，欧盟否决 ETraveli 没有令人信服的证据]]></title><description><![CDATA[Booking Holdings 周二批评了欧盟在近两年前否决其价值 16.3 亿欧元（19 亿美元）的 ETraveli 交易的反垄断决定，称监管机构未能提供明确、令人信服的证据来证明反竞争损害。【原文：Booking Holdings on Tuesday criticised an EU antitrust veto over its 1.63-billion-euro ($1.9 billion) ETraveli deal almost two years ago, saying regulators failed to provide clear, compelling evidence to show anti-competitive harm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/no-compelling-evidence-eu-veto-etraveli-booking-tells-court-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAF4V57EGFPJTP2WTPQK2RLU5E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[你有邮件！]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲、中东和非洲突发新闻市场通讯员 Lucy Raitano 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天。【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by EMEA Breaking News Markets Correspondent, Lucy Raitano.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKZGNNSQYJIFLDOZPIASIBXINI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私人投资平台 Linqto 在美国证券交易委员会审查下申请破产]]></title><description><![CDATA[Linqto是一个允许用户获取私有公司股票的投资平台，该公司于本周二申请破产，理由是涉嫌违反证券法。【原文：Linqto, the investment platform that allows users access to shares of privately held companies, filed for bankruptcy on Tuesday, citing challenges stemming from alleged securities law violations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/private-investment-platform-linqto-files-bankruptcy-amid-sec-scrutiny-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWN2VD2O25I3FC7JUU2OZ7UKCQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:52:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国专车公司与百度 Apollo 合作推出自动驾驶汽车租赁服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国专车公司周二表示，已与百度智能驾驶业务 Apollo 合作推出自动驾驶汽车租赁服务。【原文：China's Car Inc has launched an autonomous driving rental service with Baidu's smart driving business Apollo, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-car-inc-launches-self-driving-rental-service-with-baidus-apollo-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWGVVCQIK5MEZAMUX7L7OAAF2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:48:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南非称特朗普征收 30% 关税是基于对两国贸易关系的不正确认识]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非总统西里尔-拉马福萨（Cyril Ramaphosa）对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收30%的关税进行了反击，称这是基于对两国贸易的不准确理解，并表示将继续与美国进行谈判。【原文：South African President Cyril Ramaphosa pushed back against U.S. President Donald Trump's imposition of a 30% tariff, saying that it was based on an inaccurate understanding of the two countries' trade and that negotiations with the U.S. would continue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/south-africa-says-trumps-30-tariff-based-inaccurate-view-their-trade-relations-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVWQSCHTYZOBJHE4YYMG7BQ62Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:34:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Monzo 因金融犯罪过失被英国监管机构罚款 2800 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融监管机构对数字银行 Monzo 处以 2100 万英镑（2857 万美元）的罚款，原因是其反金融犯罪系统存在缺陷，其中包括在客户入职时将伦敦地标性建筑列为其地址。【原文：Britain's financial regulator has fined digital bank Monzo 21 million pounds ($28.57 million) for failings in its anti-financial crime systems, which included onboarding customers who had listed London landmarks as their address.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/monzo-fined-28-mln-by-uk-regulator-financial-crime-failings-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X23WYXX5PJI2DOQPEFKOHMULF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着交易的增加，激进投资者将推动变革]]></title><description><![CDATA[未来几个月，激进派股东将更加努力地推动企业变革，随着交易步伐的加快，他们将找到新的信心来发起运动。【原文：Activist shareholders are poised to push harder for corporate changes in the coming months, finding fresh confidence to launch campaigns as the pace of dealmaking picks up again.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/activist-investors-set-push-changes-dealmaking-picks-up-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5XVEDFWYJK3PHXPKYW72TXPDM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储寻找降息理由，调查和关税让答案难以捉摸]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近对全国和全球企业高管进行的调查凸显了美国联邦储备委员会在确定美国经济面临的更大风险是增长放缓还是通货膨胀方面的两难处境，而利率决定则取决于决策者如何在仍然动荡的贸易环境中调和相互矛盾的信息。【原文：Recent national and global surveys of business executives have highlighted the U.S. Federal Reserve's dilemma in determining if slowing growth or inflation is the greater risk to the U.S. economy, with interest rate decisions hinging on how policymakers reconcile conflicting information in a still volatile trade environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-hunt-reason-cut-rates-surveys-tariffs-make-answers-elusive-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLTXCHULCZL67FWOBASVE4WZR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:04:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普效应 "网站为拜登领导下的美国投资邀功]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年 1 月，唐纳德-特朗普总统在上任后数小时内就吹嘘美国吸引了 3 万亿美元的新企业投资。此后，特朗普称这些投资已增至 14 万亿美元，约占美国年度国内生产总值的一半。【原文：Within hours of taking office in January, President Donald Trump boasted about attracting $3 trillion in new corporate investments to the United States. Since then, Trump has said the investments have swelled to $14 trillion, or roughly half of the nation's annual gross domestic product.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-effect-website-takes-credit-us-investment-made-under-biden-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUWRZZA4V5NJRMD4HYD7WBGYZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月小型企业景气度下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[6 月份，美国小型企业信心下滑，原因是在贸易关系持续紧张和对销售前景的乐观情绪下降的情况下，企业总体上认为手头库存过多。【原文：U.S. small-business confidence slipped in June, as firms overall felt they had too much inventory on hand amid ongoing trade tensions and declining optimism over the outlook for sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-small-business-sentiment-ticks-down-june-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWESJDGQRFJNHEHK7PNPLYBV6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本和韩国寻求在 8 月最后期限前缓和关税打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本要求其大型汽车工业做出让步，而韩国则表示计划在未来几周内加强贸易谈判，"以达成互惠互利的结果"。【原文：Japan demanded concessions for its large automobile industry, while South Korea said it planned to intensify trade talks over the coming weeks "to reach a mutually beneficial result."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-south-korea-seek-soften-tariff-blow-before-august-deadline-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSUB64IKTVMLNODS7CD7LHNIMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航天工业敦促美国国会不要砍掉防止卫星碰撞的系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[数百家美国公司周二敦促国会放弃取消一个负责管理太空卫星交通的小型联邦办公室的计划，这是唐纳德-特朗普总统第一任政府发起的一项急需的民事工作，但现在却因削减经费而岌岌可危。【原文：Hundreds of U.S. companies on Tuesday urged Congress to back off a plan to kill a small federal office tasked with managing satellite traffic in space, a badly needed civilian effort initiated by President Donald Trump's first administration but now imperiled by cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/space-industry-urges-us-congress-not-axe-system-that-prevents-satellite-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UZ73USWPVPPVIPMGMVYTUKZAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[董事长称 M&S 网络攻击由 "DragonForce "实施]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国零售商玛莎百货公司（Marks & Spencer）董事长阿奇-诺曼（Archie Norman）周二告诉立法者，玛莎百货公司认为，在四月和五月迫使其暂停网上购物六周的网络攻击的煽动者是一个名为 "DragonForce "的组织。【原文：British retailer Marks & Spencer believes the instigator of the cyberattack which forced it to suspend online shopping for six weeks in April and May was a group called "DragonForce", chairman Archie Norman told lawmakers on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ms-cyberattack-was-carried-out-by-dragonforce-chairman-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6ELMNKT6FOYNM5LWNTINAEFTI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，印度计划从 2026 年起从美国进口约 10% 的厨用天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉此事的炼油行业消息人士称，印度计划从2026年开始从美国进口约10%的烹饪用天然气，这也是印度扩大能源采购以缩小与华盛顿贸易差距的努力的一部分。【原文：India plans to source about 10% of its cooking gas imports from the U.S. beginning in 2026 as part of a broader effort to boost energy purchases to narrow its trade gap with Washington, four industry refining sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-aims-import-about-10-its-cooking-gas-us-2026-say-sources-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SGGXJSK2VP47MFILA5XOLKAPQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税上调影响，6月份美国从中国进口的海产品下降了28]]></title><description><![CDATA[供应链技术提供商笛卡尔周二表示，6月份美国从中国进口的集装箱货物同比下降了28.3%，此前美国对来自中国这一最大远洋贸易伙伴的货物征收更高的关税，延续了5月份开始的急剧下降。【原文：U.S. imports of containerized goods from China tumbled 28.3% year-on-year in June, after higher tariffs on goods from the country's top ocean trade partner extended a steep drop that began in May, supply chain technology provider Descartes said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-ocean-imports-china-tumbled-28-june-tariff-hikes-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7LX5JKINRLQRK6ZUMPG4FHW5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从 "太棒了 "到 "被宠坏了"：日本向特朗普示好的贸易努力如何适得其反]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年 2 月，日本首相石破茂首次与唐纳德-特朗普会面时，他承诺在美国投资 1 万亿美元，以此来安抚这位保护主义总统长期以来在贸易问题上对东京的不满。【原文：When Japanese Premier Shigeru Ishiba first met Donald Trump in February, his plan to placate the protectionist president's long-held frustration with Tokyo on trade was a promise to invest $1 trillion in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fantastic-spoiled-how-japans-trade-effort-woo-trump-backfired-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JM4JQIKXEBNNXKQSVKWXYKKMU4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士：Jio BlackRock 将以低成本战略颠覆印度基金业]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉 Jio BlackRock 资产管理公司战略的人士表示，该公司计划在年底前在印度推出近十只股票和债务基金，重点关注小规模投资，并绕过分销商以降低成本。【原文：Jio BlackRock Asset Management plans to introduce nearly a dozen equity and debt funds in India by the year-end, focusing on small-ticket investments and bypassing distributors to reduce costs, three people familiar with the firm's strategy said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/jio-blackrock-disrupt-indias-funds-sector-with-low-cost-strategy-sources-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNNJBCWTMNMFFDF2OTAWJNLFJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:50:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国贸易机构称，新的贸易战最后期限延长了不稳定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合国贸易代表处执行主任周二表示，特朗普政府延长关税税率谈判期限的决定正在延长各国的不确定性和不稳定性。【原文：The Trump administration's decision to extend a negotiating deadline for tariff rates is prolonging uncertainty and instability for countries, the executive director of the United Nations trade agency said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/new-trade-war-deadline-prolongs-instability-un-trade-agency-says-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIDOB6V7DVNLHPYA5W455XNGNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:38:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[夏日炎炎抵消美国关税阴霾，日本服务业情绪高涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周二的一项调查显示，由于夏装和休闲需求强劲，抵消了美国关税带来的阴霾，6 月份日本服务业景气略有改善。【原文：Sentiment in Japan's service sector improved slightly in June, a government survey showed on Tuesday, as solid demand for summer clothing and leisure offset the gloom from U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-service-sector-mood-perks-up-summer-heat-offsets-us-tariff-gloom-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EEIF3DGW3RL7HLKWZEHAMX4LGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产提高可转换债券发行计划后股价大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周刚刚宣布扩大发行可转换债券后，陷入困境的日本日产汽车公司股票周二暴跌超过 6%，跌势延续到第二天。【原文：Shares of Japan's struggling Nissan Motor tumbled more than 6% on Tuesday, extending declines into a second day after it expanded an issuance of convertible bonds announced just this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nissan-shares-walloped-after-it-boosts-planned-issuance-convertible-bonds-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWEGBI5MGJIVZFXB6WCDKUPYIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 07:49:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者评估美国新关税提案，欧洲股市收平]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲股市周二表现低迷，因为投资者正在评估美国总统唐纳德-特朗普针对一系列国家提出的新关税提案。【原文：European shares were muted on Tuesday as investors assessed U.S. President Donald Trump's new tariff proposals for a spate of countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-shares-flat-investors-assess-new-us-tariff-proposals-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEHWZ7ZHCRIG5II2C5FRVDPWTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 07:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞安航空首席执行官表示，夏季预订火爆]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空公司首席执行官迈克尔-奥利里（Michael O'Leary）周二表示，夏季主要度假目的地的预订情况十分火爆。【原文：Ryanair has strong bookings for summer for major holiday destinations, Chief Executive Michael O'Leary said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ryanair-has-strong-bookings-summer-says-ceo-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIMMRRUXMNPYJD3JVS4OLPBU2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 07:14:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷上半年全球销量下滑，中国市场跌幅最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国豪华跑车制造商保时捷周二表示，该公司今年上半年的销售额出现下滑，并将中国市场下滑 28% 的原因归咎于严峻的市场环境和激烈的竞争。【原文：German luxury sports carmaker Porsche said on Tuesday its sales fell in the first half of the year, blaming challenging market conditions and intense competition for a 28% slump in the Chinese market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsches-sales-fall-globally-first-half-china-leads-slump-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWJCBCL4IBPNJGEYJ2NHX6JIRA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 07:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被特朗普关税吓到的东南亚力促更多谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[东南亚最大的经济体周二准备加强与华盛顿的贸易谈判，此前华盛顿对这些经济体征收了高额关税，尽管这些经济体在最后关头纷纷提出增加进口和削减对美国商品的征税。【原文：Southeast Asia's biggest economies prepared on Tuesday to step up trade negotiations with Washington after it hit them with steep tariffs, despite a last-ditch flurry of offers to boost imports and slash levies on U.S. goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/southeast-asia-spooked-by-trump-tariffs-presses-more-talks-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSGITLD73NJYJGZNID4NKUERJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 07:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税担忧持续，中国公司押注中国政府将继续严格控制人民币汇率]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国贸易紧张局势的持续，中国企业和投资者都希望人民币暂时保持稳定并最终贬值，而货币当局的一系列措施和暗示表明，他们的想法可能是正确的。【原文：Chinese businesses and investors are primed for the yuan to stay steady for now and eventually depreciate as U.S. trade tensions drag on, and a string of measures and hints from monetary authorities suggest they may be on the money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/china-inc-bets-beijing-will-keep-tight-grip-yuan-us-tariff-fears-persist-2025-07-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRCKLRUSNNLCNAWCXXW6FXYB3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 06:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>