<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:36:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:36:48 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[非洲制造商为延长美国贸易计划做最后努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位参与游说活动的肯尼亚工厂主告诉路透社，非洲制造商正在游说美国国会，希望能将将于 9 月底到期的免税贸易计划最后延长一到两年。【原文：African manufacturers are lobbying U.S. Congress to grant a last-ditch extension of one or two years to a duty-free trade programme due to expire at the end of September, a Kenyan factory owner involved in the campaign told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/african-manufacturers-last-ditch-bid-extend-us-trade-programme-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSZJOXQRRVOEZGB5RQFIL7P2OU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息可能为美股更广泛的上涨奠定基础]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者表示，美国央行恢复宽松货币政策可能会增加并扩大华尔街的涨势，尽管这种提振可能已经被定价，而且可能取决于较低的利率是否有助于经济避免大幅下滑。【原文：The resumption of monetary easing by the U.S. central bank could add to and broaden Wall Street's rally, investors say, though such a boost might already be priced in and could depend on whether lower interest rates help the economy avoid a significant downturn.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-rate-cuts-could-set-stage-broader-us-stock-gains-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNVMJMZ4YRL7NAVXIVNOCD7AC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储有望降息，并通过新预测更新对特朗普经济计划的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[多年来政治色彩最浓厚的美国联邦储备委员会会议将于本周三结束，人们普遍预期这次会议将降息四分之一个百分点，但这可能会引发一些决策者的异议，他们认为降息幅度太小、为时过晚，而另一些决策者则认为根本没有必要降息。【原文：The most politically charged U.S. Federal Reserve meeting in years wraps up on Wednesday with broad expectations for a quarter-percentage-point interest rate cut that may spark dissents from some policymakers who feel it is too small and too late and others who feel it is not warranted at all.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-expected-cut-rates-update-views-trump-economic-plan-with-new-projections-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGXOS4FTLVM2RB3ZRJUCVFEYJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递利润将受美国对此前豁免的包裹征收关税拖累]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递（FedEx）周四发布的财报显示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）决定终止对流行的直接面向消费者的货运免征关税待遇，这家全球快递公司的季度利润将受到冲击。【原文：FedEx will report a quarterly profit hit from President Donald Trump's decision to end tariff-exempt treatment for popular direct-to-consumer shipments when the global delivery firm reports results on Thursday, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fedex-profit-be-dragged-down-by-us-tariffs-previously-exempt-parcels-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BJ4TP4X3VPLXHFZWYCQD7J5GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行可能降息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[受疲软的就业报告和第二季度经济萎缩的刺激，加拿大央行预计将于周三降息 25 个基点。【原文：The Bank of Canada is expected to cut interest rates by 25 basis points on Wednesday, spurred by weak job reports and economic contraction in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-likely-cut-interest-rate-by-25-basis-points-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAY2DQXKUFMEBLASHHUDNPAHIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储新预测将考虑动荡时期，米兰参与辩论]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三政策会议的结束将向投资者传递三方面的信息，显示官员们为应对就业市场疲软而重新调整展望的程度、美国央行在利率路径问题上的分歧有多大，以及行长斯蒂芬-米兰的上任是否让这一切有了党派倾向。【原文：The end of the Federal Reserve's policy meeting on Wednesday will convey a three-part message for investors, showing how much officials have reshuffled their outlooks to account for a weakening job market, how divided the U.S. central bank is becoming over the interest rate path and whether the arrival of Governor Stephen Miran has given it all a partisan tilt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/feds-new-projections-account-turbulent-period-miran-joins-debate-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GW7GTVFLZZML3BBWDNPAK66ZWE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:05:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国媒体行业新领军者 YouTube 将人工智能视为内容创作的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[在其 20 岁生日之际，YouTube 已无法辨认出当初那个由年轻的业余用户发布未经加工的低成本短片的零散视频网站。【原文：On its 20th birthday, YouTube is unrecognizable as the scrappy video site that began as the domain of young amateur users publishing unpolished, low-budget clips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/youtube-new-leader-us-media-industry-bets-ai-key-creating-content-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52VK6KPUQNJHJEEXGZAJEZPU44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储将于 2025 年首次降息，美国各行业值得关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美联储有望在今年首次降低借贷成本，对利率敏感的美国企业部门将成为关注焦点，在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）上个月暗示将下调借贷成本后，大多数部门已经实现了上涨。【原文：U.S. corporate sectors that are sensitive to interest rates will be in focus as the Federal Reserve looks poised to lower borrowing costs for the first time this year, with most having already notched up gains after Chair Jerome Powell hinted at cuts last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-sectors-watch-fed-lines-up-first-rate-cut-2025-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFIUGRJ5QVJ5HL4USB75HJESEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储做出降息决定前谨慎情绪挥之不去，美国股指期货走势低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国股指期货变化不大，因为投资者在等待美联储为期两天的货币政策路径评估会议之后发布公告的同时，暂缓了大额押注。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were little changed on Wednesday as investors held back on big bets while awaiting an announcement after the Federal Reserve's two-day meeting to assess the monetary policy path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-stock-futures-muted-caution-lingers-ahead-feds-rate-cut-decision-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4YM6UKBNVNJRIAF4EU746KMDU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:57:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来制定以消费者为中心的战略，肥胖症药物领导地位将超越美国本土]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司国际总裁周三告诉路透社，礼来已在欧洲、亚洲和中东成为肥胖症药物市场的领导者，并希望在全球复制其在美国的主导地位。【原文：Eli Lilly has established itself as the market leader in obesity drugs in Europe, Asia and the Middle East and expects to replicate its U.S. dominance globally, the company's international president told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-sees-obesity-drug-leadership-beyond-us-it-leans-consumer-focused-strategy-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSQCPCUUHZIYPHULDCOOI3Y2AY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界贸易组织报告称，人工智能将改变全球贸易]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织周三的一份新报告警告说，到2040年，人工智能可将商品和服务贸易额提高近40%，但如果没有适当的政策，人工智能也可能加剧经济鸿沟。【原文：Artificial intelligence could boost the value of trade in goods and services by nearly 40% by 2040, but without adequate policies it could also exacerbate economic divides, a new World Trade Organization report warned on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-set-transform-global-trade-says-world-trade-organization-report-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXCSTDCDT5IN5G4GL7PIOKIXLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行首席执行官认为 "不友好 "的联合信贷银行交易可能导致收入减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行首席执行官贝蒂娜-奥尔洛普（Bettina Orlopp）周三称，联合信贷银行（UniCredit）对潜在合并的态度 "不友好"，并表示任何交易都可能损害收入。【原文：Commerzbank CEO Bettina Orlopp on Wednesday labelled UniCredit's approach for a potential merger as "unfriendly" and said that any deal would likely hurt revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commerzbank-ceo-sees-likely-revenue-hit-unfriendly-unicredit-deal-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMHCR7Z7IJLPHJBGQ6TGR6TYWA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚要求联合国航空机构制定保护飞机上宠物的全球标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[在发生狗在飞机上死亡的高调事件后，哥伦比亚要求联合国航空机构支持宠物跨境空运的全球标准。【原文：Colombia is asking the U.N.'s aviation agency to support global standards for transporting pets by air across borders, following high-profile cases of dogs dying on planes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-asks-un-aviation-agency-global-standards-protect-pets-planes-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEIWE6DXSNL5XKOLU6PGSDJY44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国要求科技公司停止购买英伟达的所有人工智能芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周三报道，中国互联网监管机构已指示中国最大的科技公司停止购买英伟达（Nvidia）的所有人工智能芯片，并终止现有订单。【原文：China's internet regulator has instructed the nation's biggest technology firms to stop buying all of Nvidia's artificial intelligence chips and terminate their existing orders, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/china-tells-tech-firms-stop-buying-all-nvidias-ai-chips-ft-reports-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRYUMDBCNBIGPJQBMXKV3D7Y5I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 08:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息称威托尔和嘉能可将正式竞购雪佛龙新加坡炼油厂股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位熟悉内情的人士透露，全球大宗商品贸易商维托尔（Vitol）和嘉能可（Glencore）有望正式竞购雪佛龙公司持有的新加坡第二大炼油厂 50%的股份。【原文：Global commodities traders Vitol and Glencore are expected to make formal bids for Chevron's 50% stake in Singapore's second-largest refinery, five people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/vitol-glencore-set-make-formal-bids-chevrons-singapore-refinery-stake-sources-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAMIO6G7CVICDFL3C3IHFAI2QA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 08:31:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康互联合资公司将于 12 月开始在中东建厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[富士康互联科技公司（FIT）的沙特阿拉伯合资企业将于 12 月开始建设其在中东的首个生产基地，该基地将生产电动汽车充电器。【原文：Foxconn Interconnect Technology's (FIT) 's Saudi Arabian joint venture will start constructing its first manufacturing base in the Middle East in December that will make electric vehicle chargers, the company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/foxconn-interconnect-joint-venture-start-building-middle-east-factory-december-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFDLCMFU2JOV5D7JNI6XXWQMCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 08:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司对使用 FDA 快速通道减重药券持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司国际总裁周三表示，现在就断定该公司将对其试验性减肥药orforglipron采用美国食品和药物管理局新的快速审查程序还为时过早。【原文：Eli Lilly's international president said on Wednesday it was too early to assume the company would use the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's new fast-track review process for its experimental weight-loss pill orforglipron.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eli-lilly-cautious-using-fda-fast-track-voucher-weight-loss-pill-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74T4DT5LABLN5HAN3ZU7U2HX6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 07:43:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：阿达尼领导的斯里兰卡集装箱码头将在截止日期前将吞吐量提高一倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团（Adani Group）及其合作伙伴公司约翰-基尔斯控股公司（John Keells Holdings）的一位高管告诉路透社，尽管放弃了 5.53 亿美元的美国资金，但他们将提前数月把科伦坡一个耗资 8.4 亿美元的集装箱码头的吞吐量提高一倍。【原文：India's Adani Group and its partners are set to double the capacity of a $840 million container terminal in Colombo months ahead of schedule, despite relinquishing $553 million in U.S. funding, an executive at partner firm John Keells Holdings told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/adani-led-sri-lanka-container-terminal-double-capacity-ahead-deadline-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOJZOVGZJNKRJONYNKGEVVNP6I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 07:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis因车门饰件脱落风险召回近16.4万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，Stellantis公司将在美国召回近16.4万辆吉普车，原因是这些车辆的驾驶员和乘客车门上的饰件可能会脱落。【原文：Stellantis is recalling nearly 164,000 Jeep vehicles in the U.S. due to issues causing a possible detachment of the trim on the driver and passenger doors, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-recall-nearly-164000-us-vehicles-over-risk-detached-door-trim-pieces-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FHHX7YXTNOY5GUDTABRWMIGLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 07:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯航天局局长承诺很快将为马斯克的 "星链"（Starlink）提供类似设备]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯国家通讯社周三援引俄罗斯航天局局长德米特里-巴卡诺夫（Dmitry Bakanov）的话说，俄罗斯将很快拥有与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的卫星互联网服务 "星链"（Starlink）类似的服务。【原文：Russia will soon have an analogue to Elon Musk's satellite internet service Starlink, Dmitry Bakanov, the head of Russia's Roscosmos space agency was quoted by state news agencies as saying on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/russias-space-chief-promises-an-analogue-musks-starlink-soon-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNZFPM4CHRN5JMMGW2GXVVEK4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 07:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意法半导体将向面临重组的法国工厂投资 6000 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商意法半导体公司（STMicroelectronics）周三宣布为其位于法国图尔的工厂投资 6000 万美元，计划在那里开发一条先进半导体制造技术的试验生产线。【原文：Chipmaker STMicroelectronics on Wednesday announced a $60 million investment for its plant in Tours, France, where it plans to develop a pilot line for advanced semiconductor manufacturing technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stmicro-invest-60-million-french-plant-facing-restructuring-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDBLQPIQ3ROJDN6MJQVBCOQGXQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 06:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[董事长提前离职后，雀巢股价小幅走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[在瑞士食品巨头雀巢公司宣布董事长保罗-布尔克（Paul Bulcke）将比预期更早移交给前 Inditex 首席执行官巴勃罗-伊斯拉（Pablo Isla）后，雀巢股价周三小幅走高。【原文：Nestle shares were indicated slightly higher on Wednesday after the Swiss food giant announced Chairman Paul Bulcke would hand over earlier than expected to former Inditex CEO Pablo Isla.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nestle-shares-indicated-slightly-higher-after-chairmans-early-departure-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4HKEIHNQBM3BNLLIMNAJMIKYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 06:23:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国重点展示使用国产芯片的大型数据中心项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国中央电视台（CCTV）称，中国联通已建成一个大型数据中心，由阿里巴巴和其他公司提供的国产人工智能芯片驱动，中国政府正努力摆脱外国技术的束缚。【原文：China Unicom has built a massive data centre powered by domestically developed artificial intelligence chips from Alibaba and other companies, state broadcaster CCTV said, as Beijing seeks to wean itself off foreign technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/china-spotlights-major-data-centre-project-using-domestic-chips-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDD7QCZPFRN7XDMMMUB473KV4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 06:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称美国关税不会对印度钢铁业造成直接影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度钢铁部长桑迪普-庞德里克（Sandeep Poundrik）在周三举行的英国《金融时报》印度能源转型峰会（FT Live Energy Transition Summit India）上表示，印度钢铁行业不会受到美国关税的直接影响。【原文：India's steel industry will not see much direct impact from U.S. tariffs, the country's steel secretary Sandeep Poundrik said at the FT Live Energy Transition Summit India on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-tariffs-wont-have-direct-impact-indias-steel-industry-official-says-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AEQECGBF5LPJD4TVVKPBFT3CM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 05:29:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PostNL 发布 2028 年战略，重点关注人工智能和电子商务增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[PostNL 周三在其资本市场日上宣布了新战略，目标是到 2028 年实现正常化息税前盈利超过 1.75 亿欧元（2.08 亿美元），这也是其推动可持续增长和创新愿景的一部分。【原文：PostNL announced its new strategy on Wednesday at its Capital Markets Day, targeting a normalized EBIT of over 175 million euros ($208 million) by 2028, as part of its vision to drive sustainable growth and innovation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/postnl-unveils-2028-strategy-with-focus-ai-e-commerce-growth-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UV4FZRUODBMUVJDDMM46ZVEMTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 05:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么特朗普推动取消季度报告制度这次可能会成功？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统再次推动取消企业季度信息披露，这在他的第一任政府中毫无进展，但随着白宫对证券交易委员会的议程有了更多的控制权，这一次有了更好的机会。【原文：President Donald Trump's renewed push to nix quarterly corporate disclosures, a drive that went nowhere in his first administration, has a better chance this time as the White House takes more control of the Securities and Exchange Commission's agenda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/why-trumps-push-nix-quarterly-reporting-may-succeed-this-time-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSLI55OJZBPFVMSC7Z3ADLPWK4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 05:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产寻求学习中国供应商的战略，作为削减成本行动的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车一位高级管理人员表示，日产汽车正在研究中国供应商的成本竞争力，并探索将其做法应用到全球的方法，其目标是在广泛的增效活动中削减 2,500 亿日元（17.1 亿美元）的可变成本。【原文：Nissan Motor is studying the cost competitiveness of Chinese suppliers and exploring ways to apply their practices globally, as it aims to cut variable costs by 250 billion yen ($1.71 billion) in a broad efficiency drive, a senior executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-seeks-learn-chinese-supplier-strategies-part-cost-cutting-drive-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWXXPRBTOVPIHMP4SUXAJBO3PE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 04:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行在中国的业务，高管因离职禁令离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，经过中美官员的谈判，被禁止离开中国数月之久的富国银行银行家毛晨越已获准返回美国。【原文：A Wells Fargo banker, Chenyue Mao, who had been barred from leaving China for several months, has been allowed to return to the United States following negotiations between U.S. and Chinese officials, according to two people with knowledge of the case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/wells-fargos-business-china-where-senior-executive-has-left-after-exit-ban-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQB6ZHN65BIQBK73RDQNX54LLY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 04:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 最后，美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4743DTCVVVM5RGQSB2NPXAY5MQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 04:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》：Ben & Jerry's 联合创始人辞职，称在联合利华旗下失去独立性]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周三报道，Ben & Jerry's 联合创始人杰瑞-格林菲尔德（Jerry Greenfield）已经退出了这个他在近半个世纪前帮助创立的冰淇淋品牌。【原文：Ben & Jerry's co-founder Jerry Greenfield has quit the ice cream brand he helped launch almost half a century ago, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ben-jerrys-co-founder-quits-cites-loss-independence-under-unilever-ft-says-2025-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5H552OLRBVLPLAIF2LHIHVBO54</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 04:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>