<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 12:08:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 12:08:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通年度利润创历史新高，交易商和交易员乘市场反弹之势而上]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周三公布了创纪录的年度利润，原因是其交易员和交易商在第四季度从反弹的市场中获得了意外之财。【原文：JPMorgan Chase on Wednesday posted record annual profit as its dealmakers and traders reaped a windfall from rebounding markets in the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-profit-jumps-dealmakers-traders-ride-market-rebound-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3A3TFAWKJK77AIJENOP44MBGA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LSEG 数据显示，俄罗斯石油产品因美国制裁被困海上]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦证交所集团（LSEG）周三的数据显示，近50万吨俄罗斯石油产品被困在受美国制裁影响的油轮上。【原文：Nearly 500,000 metric tons of Russian oil products are trapped on tankers hit by U.S. sanctions, LSEG data showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/russian-oil-products-trapped-sea-by-us-sanctions-lseg-data-shows-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUJ425NOMJOOBOODU46RIEJVQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:51:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资银行业务大放异彩，富国银行盈利攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）周三表示，受投资银行业务盈利增长的推动，第四季度利润攀升。【原文：Wells Fargo's profit climbed in the fourth quarter, buoyed by stronger investment banking earnings, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-earnings-climb-investment-banking-shines-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SMJIKCIMVN75EUBBMOMVPFYKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:49:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约银行第四季度利润因手续费收入增加而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约银行周三公布，由于从客户那里获得了更高的投资服务费，其第四季度利润猛增 27%。【原文：BNY reported a 27% jump in its fourth-quarter profit on Wednesday as it earned higher investment services fees from its clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-fourth-quarter-profit-rises-boost-higher-fee-income-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5AVU7NAQBPL5BHFZZSZNN5VFA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，I Squared Capital 考虑出价 10 亿美元收购香港宽频]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，总部位于美国的基础设施投资公司 I Squared Capital 正在权衡对香港上市的宽带运营商香港宽带的收购要约，其估值可能高达 10 亿美元。【原文：U.S.-based infrastructure investment firm I Squared Capital is weighing an offer for Hong Kong-listed broadband operator HKBN that could value it at up to $1 billion, two people with knowledge of the deal said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/i-squared-capital-weighs-up-1-bln-bid-hkbn-sources-say-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4AENSDNV6NLDDNWGG6ZWC5JMHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国央行行长称美国放松金融监管将增加危机风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国央行行长周三警告说，即将上任的美国政府放松金融监管的任何举动都将增加有朝一日发生金融危机的风险。【原文：Any moves to pursue financial deregulation by the incoming U.S. administration would increase the risk of a financial crisis occurring one day, France's central bank governor warned on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-financial-deregulation-would-raise-crisis-risks-french-central-bank-chief-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WDCLDDIEAZPCVCYIENFEJIQAYE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:32:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德 2024 年第四季度资产达到创纪录的 11.6 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年第四季度，贝莱德的资产规模达到 11.6 万亿美元，创下历史新高，全球最大的货币基金管理公司利润大幅增长 21%，主要得益于股市走强带来的手续费收入。【原文：BlackRock's assets hit a record high of $11.6 trillion in the fourth quarter of last year as the world's largest money manager posted a 21% profit jump, helped by fee income buoyed by stronger equity markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-assets-hit-record-116-trillion-fourth-quarter-2024-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7DN62FENRNWFEA3DDMGEYX5FY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高管遇害后，UnitedHealth 投资者等待 2025 年展望背后的细节]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）上个月因高管布莱恩-汤普森（Brian Thompson）在原定举行会议的纽约酒店外被谋杀而取消了投资者日演讲，分析师和投资者正等待该公司周四公布 2025 年业绩展望的细节。【原文：Analysts and investors are awaiting details behind UnitedHealth Group's 2025 outlook when it reports quarterly results on Thursday, after its investor day presentations were canceled last month by the murder of executive Brian Thompson outside the New York hotel where the meeting was set to take place.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-investors-await-details-behind-2025-outlook-after-execs-murder-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BI34WVCKJKG3FFLH32FXE5AQM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:22:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道巴西肉类加工企业 JBS 称净零排放承诺 "从未兑现过]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的肉类包装商 JBS 于 2021 年成为首家承诺在 2040 年前减少或抵消其所有排放量的同行，并承诺在其始于巴西亚马逊中心地带的漫长供应链中停止非法砍伐森林。【原文：The world's largest meatpacker, JBS, became in 2021 the first of its peers to commit to cutting or offsetting all its emissions by 2040, and to ending illegal deforestation across its long supply chain that starts in the heart of the Brazilian Amazon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/brazilian-meatpacker-jbs-says-net-zero-emissions-pledge-was-never-promise-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCMGN62NZFITDKPELX5DQMKTEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:21:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特 PIF 支持的 Avilease 对可能的飞机订单持 "投机取巧 "态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[快速增长的飞机租赁商 AviLease 首席执行官周三表示，他预计波音和空中客车公司将在未来四年内控制好供应问题，并表示他将在可能的飞机订单上投机取巧。【原文：The CEO of fast-growing aircraft lessor AviLease on Wednesday said he expects Boeing and Airbus to get their supply issues under control in the next four years and said he will be opportunistic about possible aircraft orders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/saudi-pif-backed-avilease-be-opportunistic-about-possible-plane-orders-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMNTRGZ75RJXZBHBW7UOGJ4XGQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:19:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共和党法案寻求削弱美国联邦贸易委员会的兼并破坏权力]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于保守派希望利用当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对限制政府的支持，美国联邦贸易委员会（U.S. Federal Trade Commission）破坏兼并的反垄断执法权正受到威胁。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission's merger-busting, antitrust enforcement powers are coming under threat as conservatives look to harness President-elect Donald Trump's support for limiting government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/republican-bill-seeks-curtail-us-ftcs-merger-busting-powers-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCGGUZILTNP4FN7LCJYIKFZ3DI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:15:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻通胀带来一丝安慰，大银行发布报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NSWQC3PYIFKC3IJZ45PEGCEYCQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数字主管表示，欧盟将全面执行社交媒体规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟数字事务负责人周三表示，欧盟委员会将全面执行其管理社交媒体和其他大型网络平台的规则，不会推迟任何行动。【原文：The European Commission will fully enforce its rules governing social media and other large online platforms and has not delayed any actions, the EU digital chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-will-fully-enforce-social-media-rules-says-digital-chief-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FY4FD27WH5L37GHRZB7MQ6YBCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车与 Vianode 签订电动汽车电池用合成石墨供应协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）与挪威维安诺公司（Vianode）周三表示，两家公司已签署了一项为期多年、价值数十亿美元的协议，由维安诺公司为美国汽车制造商的电动汽车电池提供合成石墨负极材料。【原文：General Motors has signed a multi-year, multi-billion dollar agreement for Norway's Vianode to provide the U.S. automaker with synthetic graphite anode materials for its electric vehicle batteries, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-signs-supply-deal-with-vianode-synthetic-graphite-ev-batteries-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZZLW7XQSFJNDFMIQZBYYGB5QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普能源部人选呼吁增加液化天然气和核电]]></title><description><![CDATA[克里斯-赖特（Chris Wright）是当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）挑选的美国能源部负责人，他将在周三举行的确认听证会上告诉美国参议员，他的首要任务是扩大国内能源生产，包括液化天然气和核能。【原文：Chris Wright, President-elect Donald Trump's pick to head the U.S. Energy Department, will tell U.S. senators in his confirmation hearing on Wednesday his first priority is expanding domestic energy production including liquefied natural gas and nuclear power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trumps-energy-department-pick-call-more-lng-nuclear-power-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DURYKYJF6RMKHBGTJTLL6TKLFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普重返美国总统宝座 迎来市场动荡新时代]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一的就职典礼可能预示着市场将进入一个更加动荡的时期，这位共和党人将在贸易和移民等一系列问题上迅速采取行动，预计这些问题将左右资产价格。【原文：Donald Trump's inauguration on Monday could herald a more volatile period for markets, with the Republican seen moving quickly on a wide swath of issues including trade and immigration that are expected to swing asset prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-us-presidency-return-ushers-new-era-volatile-markets-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSWOY4TPKBILJOY26PEUUFQKVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）结束对 313,101 辆戴姆勒美国卡车发动机线路问题的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，已结束对戴姆勒卡车公司 313,101 辆北美车辆发动机线路问题的调查。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday it has closed an investigation on Daimler Truck's 313,101 North American vehicles over an engine wiring concern.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-closes-probe-313101-daimler-us-trucks-over-engine-wiring-concern-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7OO5SD7LVKMBLJML5VC4V5DDA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特斯拉将暂停在中国的部分新型 Model Y 生产线的升级工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三援引知情人士的话报道称，特斯拉计划在春节期间暂停在上海生产最近更新的 Model Y 运动型多功能车的部分生产线，为期约三周。【原文：Tesla plans to suspend part of the lines manufacturing its recently refreshed Model Y sport utility vehicles in Shanghai for around three weeks over Chinese New Year, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-suspend-part-new-model-y-lines-china-upgrades-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZS7SAM32M5PD3A2CDT63SXKV2E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 10:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称 2025 年中美竞争将推动太空初创企业融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[据投资公司 Seraphim Space 发布的一份报告称，由于中美关系日益紧张，今年太空产业的资金将得到推动，而 2024 年该领域的初创企业将获得 86 亿美元的投资。【原文：Funding in the space industry is set to receive a boost this year from growing U.S.-China tensions, after startups in the sector clocked $8.6 billion in investments in 2024, according to a report by investment firm Seraphim Space.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/space-startup-funding-set-boost-us-china-rivalry-2025-report-says-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VOKQEHSKNRKPFMORSBLXB7G3IY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 10:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦为 COVID 支出辩护，称其避免了数百万人失业]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周三将为拜登政府应对 COVID 大流行的措施辩护，称其刺激性支出和其他政策带来了强劲的经济增长，避免了数百万人失业。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Wednesday will defend the Biden administration's response to the COVID pandemic, arguing that its stimulus spending and other policies led to robust growth and averted millions of job losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/yellen-defends-covid-spending-says-it-saved-millions-losing-jobs-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2YQZHYYEFIN5JH6T3MJOJMN4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在银行盈利和关键通胀数据公布前，市场谨慎，期货价格持平]]></title><description><![CDATA[追踪华尔街主要股指的期货周三表现平淡，因为投资者正在等待一系列大型银行的财报和一份至关重要的通胀报告，这可能会影响市场走向，尤其是对目前估值成熟的美股而言。【原文：Futures tracking Wall Street's main indexes were muted on Wednesday as investors awaited a slew of big bank earnings and a crucial inflation report that could influence market direction, especially for U.S. stocks currently sitting on ripe valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-flat-caution-ahead-bank-earnings-key-inflation-data-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XQ7ZIBU43RK53PMKN24X6VQAVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 09:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道Meta 警告说，印度的反垄断裁决可能会迫使功能后退，损害业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份美国公司向法院提交的文件，由于一项反垄断指令禁止其 WhatsApp 消息服务出于广告目的与 Meta 分享用户数据，Meta 可能不得不在印度 "回退或暂停 "某些功能。【原文：Meta may have to "roll back or pause" some features in India due to an antitrust directive which banned its WhatsApp messaging service from sharing user data with Meta for advertising purposes, according to a court filing by the U.S. company seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-warns-india-antitrust-ruling-could-force-roll-back-features-hurt-business-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SY2OZIVASBNGJETAXEB7D42Z6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 09:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺基亚与三星签署多年专利许可协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[芬兰诺基亚公司周三表示，它已与三星公司签署了一项多年期专利许可协议，将在这家韩国公司的电视机中使用诺基亚的视频技术。【原文：Finland's Nokia said on Wednesday it had signed a multi-year patent license agreement with Samsung , for the use of Nokia's video technologies in the South Korean company's televisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nokia-signs-multi-year-patent-license-agreement-with-samsung-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MG6MGT7TNZPSBOUQVYYQS4BEXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 09:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众斯柯达汽车公司 2024 年交付量增长 6.9]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车集团旗下捷克汽车制造商斯柯达汽车公司（Skoda Auto）周三表示，2024年该公司的全球汽车交付量增长了6.9%，达到92.66万辆，这主要得益于欧洲市场销量的增长，而其他市场则有所下滑。【原文：Global deliveries for Czech carmaker Skoda Auto, part of the Volkswagen Group , rose by 6.9% in 2024, to 926,600 vehicles, boosted by rising sales in Europe as other markets drop, the company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vws-skoda-auto-posts-69-rise-2024-deliveries-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFOKWJCQJNI6PP4BZ2RARRINIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 09:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源署称美国的新制裁可能会严重干扰俄罗斯的供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际能源署（IEA）周三在其月度石油市场报告中称，美国上周五宣布的对俄罗斯石油的最新一轮制裁可能会严重扰乱俄罗斯的石油供应和分销链。【原文：The latest round of U.S. sanctions against Russian oil, announced last Friday, could significantly disrupt Russia's oil supply and distribution chains, the International Energy Agency (IEA) said in its monthly oil market report on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/iea-says-new-us-sanctions-could-significantly-disrupt-russian-supply-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GM4BD7E77RKIVCIYGOMXQX3DKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 09:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最大的宜家零售商将向回收公司投资 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的宜家零售商英卡集团（Ingka Group）的投资部门表示，它将向回收公司投资 10 亿欧元（10.3 亿美元），目的是更好地管理宜家家具、床上用品或床垫被丢弃后产生的废物，这些废物最终会被焚烧或填埋。【原文：The investment arm of Ingka Group, the biggest global IKEA retailer, said it will invest 1 billion euros ($1.03 billion) into recycling companies as it aims to better manage the waste created when IKEA furniture, bedding or mattresses are thrown away and end up incinerated or in landfill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/biggest-ikea-retailer-invest-1-billion-recycling-firms-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3WB5GEV2BNKPP5IEGD65GSFVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 07:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾称不在美国新的人工智能技术限制范围内应 "给人信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾政府周三表示，台湾被排除在美国对人工智能（AI）芯片和技术出口的新限制之外，这应该 "让人对 "台北自身的控制和对法律的尊重 "充满信心"。【原文：Taiwan's exclusion from the new U.S. curbs on artificial intelligence (AI) chip and technology exports should "give confidence" about Taipei's own controls and respect for the law, the island's government said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/taiwan-says-exclusion-new-us-curbs-ai-tech-should-give-confidence-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPLUHH4PYFKZLC6QC5KUFMID3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 06:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国的 RedNote：关于 TikTok 用户趋之若鹜的应用程序，你需要了解什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近，50 多万 TikTok 用户加入红笔记平台，抗议美国可能即将对该短视频应用下达禁令，中国社交媒体应用红笔记因此成为舆论焦点。【原文：Chinese social media app RedNote has been thrust into the limelight after more than half a million TikTok users recently joined the platform in protest against a likely imminent ban on the short video app in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-rednote-what-you-need-know-about-app-tiktok-users-are-flocking-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W66QCQOETFOVPF2VVCXI2QNGRY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本财务大臣表示，日本将对过度外汇交易采取适当行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣加藤胜信周三重申，政府将对外汇市场上的过度举动采取适当行动。【原文：Japan Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato on Wednesday reiterated that the government would take appropriate action against excessive moves on the foreign exchange market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/japan-take-appropriate-action-against-excessive-fx-moves-finance-minister-says-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ULTFDCLLVJKRIOQF5RTQXRA2A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 06:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税威胁逼近，美国进口商抢购中国商品]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）计划征收新的关税之前，一些公司囤积了服装、玩具、家具和电子产品，这可能会重燃世界经济超级大国之间的贸易战。【原文：U.S. imports from China finished the year strong after some companies stockpiled shipments of apparel, toys, furniture and electronics ahead of President-elect Donald Trump's plan to impose new tariffs that could revive a trade war between the world's economic superpowers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-importers-rush-goods-china-trump-tariff-threat-looms-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R3O4HDGZGNLL3ETPKHMZMA7GCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 06:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>