<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 18:05:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 18:05:11 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[英国航空公司因罗尔斯-罗伊斯公司零部件延误而更改航班时刻表]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国航空公司（British Airways）周五表示，由于罗尔斯-罗伊斯公司（Rolls-Royce）的发动机和零部件交货延迟，特别是其 787 飞机上安装的遄达 1000 型发动机交货延迟，该公司已对其航班计划做出额外调整。【原文：British Airways said on Friday it has made additional changes to its schedule due to delays in the delivery of engines and parts from Rolls-Royce , particularly the Trent 1000 engines fitted to its 787 aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/british-airways-changes-schedule-due-rolls-royce-parts-delays-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCQLCY2YOJJYVPKTSCQ54A2WMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 17:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司被美国劳工委员会指控限制员工使用 Slack 和社交媒体]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家劳工关系委员会周五表示，苹果公司被美国劳工委员会指控限制工人使用社交媒体和工作场所消息应用程序 Slack，从而干涉了工人集体争取更好工作条件的权利。【原文：Apple has been accused by a U.S. labor board of interfering with workers' rights to collectively advocate for better working conditions by restricting their use of social media and workplace messaging app Slack, the National Labor Relations Board said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-accused-restricting-workers-slack-social-media-use-by-us-labor-board-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFJY43RGPZJZLGHYHLQY55LXDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 17:49:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Odyssey 正在就收购霍尼韦尔面罩部门进行深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，私募股权公司 Odyssey 正在就收购霍尼韦尔面罩部门进行深入谈判。【原文：Private equity firm Odyssey is in advanced negotiations to buy Honeywell's face mask unit, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/odyssey-advanced-talks-buy-honeywells-face-mask-unit-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TVXFJEOPRZLKLMJREWQ5PDUDKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 17:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大型银行称，尽管经济令人担忧，但消费者依然强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的两家贷款机构周五表示，尽管有迹象表明通胀率上升使一些收入较低的美国人捉襟见肘，但美国消费者在第三季度仍保持了强劲的消费势头。【原文：U.S. consumers remain resilient with solid spending in the third quarter, two of the country's biggest lenders said on Friday, although there are signs higher inflation has stretched some Americans on lower incomes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/big-us-banks-say-consumers-are-still-strong-despite-economy-fears-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEBXDZIZVBIYXNG43HX7LBF4HI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 16:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员要求电信公司就中国黑客攻击报告做出答复]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，中国黑客入侵了美国宽带服务提供商的网络，一个由美国两党议员组成的小组周五要求 AT&amp;T 、Verizon Communications 和 Lumen Technologies 回答相关问题。【原文：A bipartisan group of U.S. lawmakers asked AT&amp;T , Verizon Communications , and Lumen Technologies on Friday to answer questions after a report Chinese hackers accessed the networks of U.S. broadband providers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-lawmakers-seek-answers-telecoms-chinese-hacking-report-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLYJLQAIOBJD3MQCH3QEUAGENU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 16:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼集团首席执行官称美国基金对集团战略充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利能源集团首席执行官克劳迪奥-德斯卡尔齐（Claudio Descalzi）周五表示，美国投资基金对埃尼分拆成长型业务以吸引资金的战略充满信心。【原文：U.S. investment funds are showing confidence in Eni's strategy of spinning off growth businesses in order to attract financial resources, the Italian energy group's CEO Claudio Descalzi said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eni-ceo-says-us-funds-are-showing-confidence-groups-strategy-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7P7PSZFOENKXZBVUQDXA6UDMPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 16:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监督机构批评联邦航空局对波音生产的监督]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一个联邦监督机构批评了联邦航空管理局对波音飞机生产的监督，称其没有一个有效的系统来监督这家飞机制造商的各个生产设施。【原文：A federal watchdog on Friday criticized the Federal Aviation Administration's oversight of Boeing airplane production, saying it does not have an effective system to oversee the planemaker's individual manufacturing facilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-watchdog-criticizes-faa-oversight-boeing-production-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DY53TJYD6NN7TDWL23J5LZUGNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 15:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部呼吁国际货币基金组织和世界银行就流动性压力采取新措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部最高经济外交官周五呼吁国际货币基金组织和多边开发银行研究新的方法，为中低收入国家提供短期流动性支持，以避免债务危机。【原文：The U.S. Treasury's top economic diplomat on Friday called on the International Monetary Fund and multilateral development banks to work on new ways to provide short-term liquidity support to low- and middle-income countries to head off debt crises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-treasury-calls-new-imf-world-bank-steps-liquidity-pressures-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FEXVP6HBEVOVHC2XIBDODLEW6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 15:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份消费者信心指数下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，由于对高物价的不满情绪挥之不去，10月份美国消费者情绪下滑。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment slipped in October amid lingering frustration over high prices, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-slips-october-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45UPV6WOJZKUDE4HEEU2XFENIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 14:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称日本三井物产准备重返贵金属交易领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士告诉路透社，日本三井物产公司（Mitsui &amp; Co）计划在阔别九年后重新进入全球贵金属交易，以对冲客户风险。【原文：Japan's Mitsui &amp; Co plans to re-enter global precious metals trading to hedge client risk after a nine-year absence, three sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/japans-mitsui-prepares-comeback-precious-metals-trading-sources-say-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCVROKBE5NMSBMZ5V4P2JPW3U4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 14:03:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司动荡之年的五张图表]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司全年都深陷危机之中。【原文：Boeing has been mired in crisis all year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-year-turbulence-five-charts-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P4UUZ4P4QRNDNJJZO5BMFEU5SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 13:53:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科幻烟雾弥漫：投资者和专家对特斯拉推出机器人出租车的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周四展示了期待已久的机器人出租车，它有两个鸥翼车门，没有方向盘或踏板，但这场华丽的活动细节不多，令希望获得更多具体计划的投资者大失所望。【原文：Tesla on Thursday showcased its long-awaited robotaxi with two gull-wing doors and no steering wheel or pedals, but the glitzy event was light on detail, disappointing investors who had hoped for more concrete plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lot-sci-fi-smoke-mirrors-investors-experts-react-teslas-robotaxi-unveil-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W22JZUCO3BLXLGBRUNKDDTBI2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 13:29:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称德国正努力挫败联合信贷银行对德国商业银行的竞购]]></title><description><![CDATA[几位熟悉德国政府和监管机构想法的人士告诉路透社记者，德国正在努力阻止意大利竞争对手可能收购德国最大的银行之一，这一立场将柏林与罗马和欧洲监管机构对立起来。【原文：Germany is working to frustrate a possible takeover of one of its biggest banks by an Italian rival, a stance that pits Berlin against Rome and Europe's regulators, several people familiar with government and regulators' thinking told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/germany-working-thwart-unicredits-bid-commerzbank-sources-say-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MH6WNQTNCRI5PM7HFHNEARFGKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 13:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢拉抨击美国要求提供巴西购买战斗机的信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周五表示，美国司法部要求萨博公司提供有关巴西于2014年购买瑞典鹰狮战斗机的信息是 "毫无意义的"。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Friday it made "no sense" for the U.S. Department of Justice to request information from Saab over Brazil's purchase of the Swedish firm's Gripen fighter jets in 2014.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lula-slams-us-request-information-brazils-fighter-jet-purchase-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OD3CZRM4HBIJTFUCDTZWO4FH6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 13:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息观点导致美国股票基金资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 9 日的一周内，由于市场对美联储降息路径的预期发生变化以及债券收益率飙升，投资者纷纷获利了结，美国股票基金出现资金外流。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed outflows in the week to Oct. 9 as investors booked profits due to a shift in market expectations about the Federal Reserve rate cut path and a surge in bond yields.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-outflows-rate-cut-views-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFDAZPFS2BOMNFBIWM3KSPVLMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 12:53:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员继续押注美联储 11 月和 12 月降息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，一份报告显示，上个月的生产者价格与上个月相比没有变化，这表明通胀继续朝着美联储的目标迈进，因此在即将召开的美联储政策会议上将美国利率下调四分之一个百分点的理由似乎不攻自破。【原文：The case for quarter-point U.S. interest-rate cuts at upcoming Federal Reserve policy meetings appeared intact on Friday after a report showed producer prices were unchanged last month compared to the prior month, suggesting inflation continues on track toward the Federal Reserve's target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-keep-bets-25-bps-fed-rate-cuts-nov-dec-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHMIQOZXKFJANOMPMV4GIZPN5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 12:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因经营疲软，穆迪将大众汽车前景展望下调至 "负面]]></title><description><![CDATA[评级机构穆迪（Moody's）将大众汽车的评级展望从 "稳定 "下调至 "负面"，理由是欧洲第一大汽车制造商的经营业绩不断恶化，预计扭转局面将面临挑战。【原文：Rating agency Moody's has cut its outlook on Volkswagen to "negative" from "stable", citing a deteriorating operating performance at Europe's top carmaker and expected challenges to turn the situation around.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/moodys-cuts-volkswagens-outlook-negative-due-operating-weakness-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIQZPUA34ZPCDA25MLMNHHSQFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 12:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月份生产者价格保持不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国生产者价格在 9 月份保持不变，表明通胀前景依然有利，并支持了美联储将在下个月再次降息的观点。【原文：U.S. producer prices were unchanged in September, pointing to a still-favorable inflation outlook and supporting views that the Federal Reserve would cut interest rates again next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-producer-prices-unchanged-september-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTSOQY33IFLAZBF22QJ2ZOO6HI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 12:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于安全产品需求旺盛，Fastenal 季度利润略超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受益于对安全产品的持续需求，工业用品制造商法斯顿（Fastenal）周五公布的第三季度利润略高于分析师的预期。【原文：Industrial supplies maker Fastenal on Friday posted a third-quarter profit that marginally surpassed analysts' estimates, benefiting from a sustained demand for its safety products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fastenal-marginally-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-demand-safety-products-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NICF7ULNURP7HCBZERXITRY57Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:53:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典法院维持对特斯拉劳资纠纷的裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典一家地方法院周五维持了一项初步裁决，即瑞典邮政服务公司 Postnord 无需向特斯拉交付车牌，而特斯拉的车牌正受到邮政工人的阻挠，这也是更广泛的工会同情罢工的一部分。【原文：A Swedish district court on Friday upheld a preliminary ruling that Sweden's postal service Postnord does not need to deliver licence plates to Tesla , which are being blocked by the postal workers as part of a wider labour union sympathy strike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/swedish-court-upholds-ruling-against-tesla-labour-dispute-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HMZL4NX45JITCD26UCVBYDRDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球货币市场基金连续第三周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 9 日的一周内，受美联储降息预期减弱和对中东冲突保持谨慎的影响，全球投资者对货币市场基金进行了大量投资。【原文：Global investors made large investments in money market funds in the week to Oct. 9 driven by a push back in Federal Reserve rate cut expectations and caution over the Middle East conflict.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-money-market-funds-draw-inflows-third-week-row-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SREE6PFURNNN3HIMK53XYIUJXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:37:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管需求放缓，电动汽车公司 Polestar 预计第四季度毛利率仍将保持正增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Polestar 上周五表示，尽管第三季度电动汽车的交付量下降了 14%，但预计第四季度将实现正毛利率。【原文：Polestar said on Friday that it expected to achieve a positive gross profit margin in the fourth quarter despite its electric vehicle deliveries falling 14% in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-firm-polestar-expects-positive-fourth-quarter-gross-margin-despite-slow-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEWI2CZTXBLS7NTKIH2QW5NNXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:33:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在激烈的美国大选中，世界市场最关心的是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统大选还有几周就要举行了，这是大选年中对金融市场影响最大的一次投票。【原文：The U.S. presidential election, the most consequential vote for financial markets in an election-packed year, is weeks away.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/what-matters-most-world-markets-tight-us-election-race-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAPA3GARQNJ5JPGQVKZSZTBSAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 在摩尔多瓦总统选举前删除虚假账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms Inc 周五表示，在摩尔多瓦 10 月 20 日大选之前，该公司已经删除了一个针对该国俄语使用者的群组账户网络，原因是该账户违反了公司关于虚假账户的政策。【原文：Meta Platforms Inc said on Friday it had removed a network of group accounts targeting Russian-speakers in Moldova, ahead of the country's Oct. 20 election, for violation of the company's policy on fake accounts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-removes-fake-accounts-moldova-ahead-presidential-election-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNMOU2PKDJPJXP5RXCX5R5OH3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼要求苹果和谷歌封杀中国的特姆优，以保护小商户]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼一位部长周五表示，印尼已要求Alphabet旗下的谷歌和苹果公司在其应用商店中屏蔽中国快时尚电子商务公司Temu，使其无法下载。【原文：Indonesia has asked Alphabet's Google and Apple to block Chinese fast fashion e-commerce firm Temu in their application stores in the country so it cannot be downloaded, a minister said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/indonesia-asks-apple-google-block-chinas-temu-protect-small-merchants-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGAHYQAC4NKPBCTMBNDHYPTDEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 11:04:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行利润因利息收入减少而下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行第三季度利润下降，原因是贷款需求低迷和向储户支付的款项增加挤压了该行的利息收入。【原文：Wells Fargo's profit fell in the third quarter as the bank's interest income was squeezed by subdued loan demand and higher payments to depositors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargos-profit-falls-lower-interest-income-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CIGOJMULVPCXGD3PWZALWTQJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通利润下降，贷款损失准备金使投资银行业务黯然失色]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）周五表示，由于为潜在贷款违约计提的更多准备金抵消了投资银行业务的收益，该行第三季度利润下降。【原文：JPMorgan Chase's profit dropped in the third quarter as a bigger provision for potential loan defaults offset gains from investment banking, the bank said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-profit-drops-bigger-provisions-loan-losses-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFDJNVLEBZL5DHMRKYTZPZPJW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:53:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TomTom 首席执行官：中国贸易紧张局势给汽车制造商的投资计划蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字地图专家TomTom公司首席执行官周五表示，中国与西方之间的贸易紧张局势已经对汽车制造商的投资决策和长期前景造成了影响，给行业带来了一定程度的不确定性。【原文：Trade tensions between China and the West have put a dampener on carmakers' investment decisions and longer-term outlooks, creating a level of uncertainty in the industry, the CEO of digital mapping specialist TomTom said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-trade-tensions-cast-shadow-automakers-investment-plans-tomtom-ceo-says-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NEKPDQZX2NMXLADALG5WBK3L24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:49:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约银行第三季度利润增长，托管和管理资产规模突破 50 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的托管银行纽约银行周五表示，由于其托管和管理的资产首次突破 50 万亿美元大关，投资服务费增加，第三季度利润猛增 16%。【原文：BNY's profit jumped 16% in the third quarter on higher investment services fees as assets under its custody and administration exceeded the $50 trillion mark for the first time, the world's largest custodian bank said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-q3-profit-rises-assets-under-custody-administration-top-50-trillion-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FX5G5GX4CBMFPLBUCUO5ZAB2FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:36:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯法院在 VTB 诉讼案中下令扣押摩根大通 1.558 亿美元资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，俄罗斯一家法院已下令扣押摩根大通银行在俄罗斯的账户中总计 1.558 亿美元的资金，俄罗斯国有银行 VTB 因资金被冻结在国外而寻求赔偿。【原文：A Russian court has ordered the seizure of funds in JPMorgan Chase bank accounts in Russia totalling $155.8 million, court filings showed, as state-owned Russian bank VTB seeks damages over funds blocked abroad.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/russian-court-orders-seizure-1558-mln-jpmorgan-chase-funds-vtb-lawsuit-2024-10-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O66CEKZB2ZKE3JQ3YDOFKTWPNQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:34:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>