<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:10:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:10:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市受中国提振，黄金连续第八周上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市上涨，扭转了华尔街的不利局面，因为美国的例外论继续失去光芒，而一度不被看好的中国股市则因人工智能（AI）的乐观情绪而找到了更多买家。【原文：Asian shares rose on Friday, reversing Wall Street's negative lead as the U.S. exceptionalism narrative continued to lose its shine, while once unloved Chinese stocks found themselves more buyers thanks to optimism over artificial intelligence (AI).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VB5C24NLCJJ7XPQLHT3OZDCK6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:40:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 CATL 将与大众汽车深化电池研发合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车电池巨头 CATL 周五表示，已与大众汽车签署战略合作谅解备忘录，双方将在电池研发、新材料应用和零部件开发等领域深化合作。【原文：CATL has signed a strategic cooperation MOU with Volkswagen to deepen partnership in battery R&amp;D, new materials application and components development, the Chinese electric vehicle battery giant said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-catl-deepen-battery-rd-cooperation-with-volkswagen-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWITXHFIVJORRJB7RQT72UMW3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:31:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德在审查新的 ESG 指南后恢复监管会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[顶级资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock）周四表示，在审查了美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）的新指导意见后，该公司已恢复了与公司的监管合作。【原文：Top asset manager BlackRock said on Thursday it had resumed stewardship engagements with companies after reviewing new guidance from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/blackrock-resumes-stewardship-talks-after-reviewing-new-esg-guidance-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNHBYGFSHNIJVCAUXNTOFALARM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:16:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行对降息持谨慎态度，一切取决于数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行高级官员周五表示，鉴于劳动力市场火热带来的成本压力，澳大利亚央行对进一步降息持谨慎态度，但如果通胀放缓速度超过预期，澳大利亚央行将做出反应。【原文：Australia's central bank is cautious about cutting rates further given cost pressures in a hot labour market, but it will respond if inflation slows more quickly than expected, senior officials said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/australias-central-bank-cautious-rate-cuts-all-depends-data-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJCIGJBWO5JGXP56UWO4WVVAMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:09:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国需求希望强烈，俄罗斯供应令人担忧，石油延续涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国汽油和馏分油库存下降提高了人们对稳健需求的预期，同时对俄罗斯供应中断的担忧也为油价提供了支撑，油价周五扩大涨幅，有望实现单周上涨。【原文：Oil prices extended gains on Friday, headed for a weekly increase, as falling inventories of U.S. gasoline and distillate raised expectations of solid demand while concerns over supply disruptions in Russia lent support.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-extends-gains-strong-us-demand-hopes-russia-supply-concerns-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZYH3RAKMZPQPOQZ5OZR6UT7NU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国营媒体称，华为创始人告诉习近平，中国对缺乏芯片的担忧有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国国家媒体报道，华为创始人在中国国家主席与私营企业家举行的一次会议上告诉习近平，中国对缺乏国产芯片或操作系统的担忧有所缓解。【原文：Huawei's founder told Xi Jinping at a meeting the Chinese president held with private sector entrepreneurs that concerns China had about a lack of homegrown chips or operating systems had eased, Chinese state media reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/huawei-founder-told-xi-chinas-concerns-about-lack-chips-have-eased-state-media-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2RV2TTK3BLXXKWXNEOEFEWK54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 01:51:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元触及年内低点，多头开始紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于日本通胀率飙升，日元周五升至两个半月高点，而美元则将连续第三周下跌，因为交易商认为唐纳德-特朗普第二个任期的开始主要是在关税方面虚张声势。【原文：The yen shot to a 2-1/2 month high on Friday on the back of a jump in Japanese inflation, while the dollar was set for a third weekly drop in a row as traders calculated the start of Donald Trump's second term has been mostly bluster on the tariff front.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-hits-year-to-date-lows-bulls-get-nervous-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRFQ3TIMC5KWDDWENGGABRJW5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 01:18:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国重要的房地产救市工具太难使用，难以发挥作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国去年推出的稳定房地产市场的主要工具收效甚微，迫使中国政府为受危机影响的房地产行业寻找新的解决方案，分析人士认为，这必须涉及国家大规模直接购买空置公寓。【原文：Key tools China introduced last year to stabilise the property market are making very little impact, pressuring Beijing to find new solutions for the crisis-hit sector, which analysts say must involve large-scale direct state purchases of empty apartments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-key-property-rescue-tools-are-too-hard-use-make-an-impact-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VYSVHSOJTNP5NL7I44VSU3JHAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 01:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济增长令人担忧，韩国央行将于 2 月 25 日降息 25 个基点：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社（Reuters）调查的经济学家预计，韩国央行（BOK）将于周二将其关键利率下调 25 个基点，为上一季度几乎没有增长的经济提供支持。【原文：The Bank of Korea (BOK) will cut its key interest rate by 25 basis points on Tuesday, offering support to an economy which barely grew last quarter, according to economists polled by Reuters who expected a further 50 points of easing this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-korea-cut-rates-by-25-bps-february-25-amid-growth-worries-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWLF4GRNVZNOJCZYYZF6YBM3DI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本工厂活动连续第八个月萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项私营部门调查显示，日本 2 月份的工厂活动连续第八个月出现下滑，但下滑速度有所放缓，这表明陷入困境的工厂可能正在重新站稳脚跟。【原文：Japan's factory activity extended declines for an eighth straight month in February but at a slower pace, a private-sector survey showed on Friday, in a sign struggling factories may be finding their footing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-factory-activity-shrinks-8th-straight-month-pmi-shows-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJDJDLWWEROS3PRA5SI7QSL25U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国寻求特朗普关税豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国工业部周五在一份声明中表示，韩国官员在本周访问华盛顿期间请求豁免美国对等钢铝关税。【原文：South Korean officials have requested an exemption from U.S. reciprocal, steel and aluminium tariffs during their visit this week to Washington, the industry ministry said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/south-korea-seeks-exemption-trump-tariffs-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EE6QUXZIUBNABMJESUWLDYNF7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:31:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[初创公司创始人案开审，律师称摩根大通有 "买方悔意]]></title><description><![CDATA[查理-贾维斯（Charlie Javice）因涉嫌欺诈摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）收购她的大学财务援助初创公司弗兰克（Frank）而受到刑事审判，她的律师认为不存在欺诈，银行巨头只是 "买方反悔"。【原文：The criminal trial of Charlie Javice for allegedly defrauding JPMorgan Chase into buying her college financial aid startup Frank began on Thursday, with her lawyer arguing there was no fraud and the banking giant merely had "buyer's remorse."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-had-buyers-remorse-lawyer-says-startup-founders-trial-starts-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPZIT33JRBN2XHD57K5LO7Z5BQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称将撤销对太空探索技术公司的移民诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，将撤销指控埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空技术公司 SpaceX 拒绝雇用某些移民的案件。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice on Thursday said it would drop a case accusing Elon Musk's space technology company SpaceX of refusing to hire certain immigrants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-says-it-will-drop-immigration-case-against-spacex-2025-02-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YF45RX7N55PK3LYCSHZE3WO6QI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:08:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本核心通胀率创 19 个月新高，使日本央行加息押注继续存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，日本1月份核心消费者物价指数环比上涨3.2%，创下19个月以来的新高，这增强了人们对日本央行将继续从仍然较低的水平上调利率的预期。【原文：Japan's core consumer price index rose 3.2% in January from the previous year to hit a 19-month high, data showed on Friday, reinforcing expectations the central bank will continue to raise interest rates from still-low levels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-core-inflation-hits-19-month-high-keeps-boj-rate-hike-bets-alive-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7M4CLG22YVLQDJYU37IUZBDVBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:53:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 暂停加拿大工厂的换装工作，该工厂将生产吉普指南者]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯特兰蒂斯公司（Stellantis）周四表示，该公司将暂停下一代吉普车指南者（Compass）紧凑型 SUV 的研发工作，包括重新调整加拿大一家专门生产该车的工厂。【原文：Stellantis is pausing work on its next-generation Jeep Compass compact SUV including retooling a plant in Canada designated to build the vehicle, the company said Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-pauses-retooling-canada-factory-slated-build-jeep-compass-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGE26LMYPZKR3CVJ4FJAQPEIBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:53:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[L3Harris 推进阿肯色州火箭发动机工厂建设]]></title><description><![CDATA[L3Harris Technologies 公司周四表示，随着地缘政治紧张局势升级，导弹需求加速增长，该公司已开始在卡姆登基地建造四座固体火箭发动机生产设施。【原文：L3Harris Technologies said on Thursday it has begun constructing four solid rocket motor production facilities at its Camden site, as demand for missiles accelerates amid escalating geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/l3harris-pushes-ahead-arkansas-rocket-motor-factories-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2BIPPWNJVP5NCGYK2BMGL4SXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，尽管交易额屡创新高，但 Meta 还是减少了员工的股票期权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，尽管社交媒体巨头 Meta Platforms 的股价本月屡创新高，但该公司已将每年向数万名员工分配的股票期权削减了约 10%。【原文：Meta Platforms has cut back on its yearly distribution of stock options by about 10% for tens of thousands of employees despite the social media giant trading at record highs this month, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-reduces-stock-options-staff-despite-trading-record-highs-ft-reports-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJ7QI4RHIJIJDE5O3F36VZTMZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利雅得航空公司首席执行官称航空公司供应链问题开始改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特新成立的利雅得航空公司（Riyadh Air）首席执行官周四表示，主要飞机制造商波音公司和空中客车公司的供应链正显示出适度改善的迹象。【原文：Supply chains for major planemakers Boeing and Airbus are showing signs of moderate improvement, the chief executive of Saudi start-up Riyadh Air said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/riyadh-air-ceo-says-airline-supply-chain-issues-starting-improve-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZI5RIEWMXFKXDJNJO2JYYZWTXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马公司高管认为无需达成特别协议以避免美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝马首席采购官表示，宝马认为没有必要与美国谈判一项特殊协议以避免进口关税，并指出该汽车制造商在美国的业务规模庞大，而且与美国政府官员关系良好。【原文：BMW does not see the need to negotiate a special deal with the United States to avoid import tariffs, its chief purchasing officer said, pointing to the carmaker's sizeable presence in the country and good relations with U.S. government officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-sees-no-need-special-deal-avoid-us-tariffs-executive-says-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R55W7TB56ZLAFB5XMJZLAIM6LQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:06:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国炼油商考虑转用替代性轻质原油，因担心特朗普征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[高管们表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要对从美国最大原油供应国加拿大和墨西哥进口的原油征收关税，美国顶级炼油商准备寻求重质酸性原油的替代来源，包括生产更多的国产原油。【原文：Top U.S. refiners are poised to seek alternative sources for heavy, sour crudes, including running more domestic grades, as they await clarity around U.S. President Donald Trump's threatened tariffs on imports from the nation's top crude suppliers Canada and Mexico, executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-refiners-mull-switch-alternative-lighter-crudes-amid-trump-tariff-fears-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5P3KKUKR3ZN2JFEKYD2Q4VBSIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:04:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苏里南政府需要为 2025 年的大型能源项目筹资 15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[苏里南国有公司负责人告诉路透社，苏里南国有公司今年需要获得前所未有的 15 亿美元银行融资，以确保能够参与该国的 Gran Morgu 能源项目。【原文：Suriname's Staatsolie needs to secure an unprecedented $1.5 billion in bank financing this year to ensure it can participate in the country's Gran Morgu energy project, the head of the state-owned company told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/surinames-staatsolie-needs-raise-15-billion-major-energy-project-2025-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NXYD4SOT5LSTHCCVJ32S7DVTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国前能源部长格兰霍姆加入爱迪生国际公司和苏格兰爱迪生公司董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前能源部长、曾连任两届密歇根州州长的民主党人詹妮弗-格兰霍姆（Jennifer Granholm）已被任命为爱迪生国际公司及其子公司南加州爱迪生公司（Southern California Edison）的董事会成员，自 4 月 1 日起生效。【原文：Jennifer Granholm, the former U.S. secretary of energy and a Democratic two-term governor of Michigan, has been appointed to the boards of Edison International and its subsidiary, Southern California Edison, effective April 1, the company announced on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/former-us-energy-secretary-granholm-joins-edison-international-socal-edison-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYLVF2RC65J2JOMXOAD6SCMFWI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:44:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克说他正在考虑对美联储进行审计]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周四表示，他正在考虑对美联储进行审计，此前他曾呼吁加强对央行的审查。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk said on Thursday he is thinking of auditing the Federal Reserve, after calling for greater scrutiny of the central bank in the past.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/musk-says-he-is-thinking-auditing-fed-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAXXISPBKJKBLML7QCLNM3M5QY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥快餐连锁店古兹曼-约-戈麦斯 2025 年利润将超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[在澳大利亚上市的墨西哥主题快餐连锁店古兹曼-戈麦斯（Guzman y Gomez）周五表示，其上半年盈利几乎翻了一番，这使其有望超过上市不到一年前提出的 2025 财年盈利预期。【原文：Australia-listed Mexican-themed fast-food chain Guzman y Gomez said on Friday its first-half earnings nearly doubled, putting it firmly on track to surpass its fiscal 2025 profit forecast provided before its listing less than a year ago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mexican-fast-food-chain-guzman-y-gomez-set-2025-profit-ahead-forecast-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QS52RDXGTFJ7VAS4GQHDQAAQQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国泡沫红茶连锁企业 Mixue 拟在香港首次公开募股中融资 4.43 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周五提交的一份监管文件显示，中国最大的泡沫红茶和饮料公司美雪集团正寻求在香港首次公开募股中融资34.5亿港元（4.4366亿美元）。【原文：China's largest bubble tea and drinks firm, Mixue Group, is seeking to raise HK$3.45 billion ($443.66 million) in a Hong Kong initial public offering, according to a regulatory filing made on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/chinese-bubble-tea-chain-firm-mixue-aims-raise-443-million-hong-kong-ipo-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKI6LQSTDROQZONZRFQXXDL54Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[库格勒称，美联储应在 "一段时间内 "保持政策利率稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里亚娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周四表示，她认为美国央行应将短期借贷成本目标维持在目前的4.25%-4.50%区间，因为该区间对经济和仍然高企的通胀起到了适度的抑制作用。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler on Thursday said she believes the U.S. central bank should leave its target for short-term borrowing costs in its current 4.25%-4.50% range, where it is exerting moderate restraint on the economy and on still-elevated inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-should-hold-policy-rate-steady-some-time-kugler-says-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KED4P2CQ5FJVZAM4NL2E7A3NSQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:34:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空 7.95 亿美元债务交易获法院批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国破产法官周四批准了精神航空公司的债务重组，允许这家廉价航空公司将 7.95 亿美元的债务转为股权，并以私营公司的身份摆脱破产。【原文：A U.S. bankruptcy judge on Thursday approved Spirit Airlines' debt restructuring, clearing the budget airline to convert $795 million in debt to equity and emerge from bankruptcy as a private company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-gets-court-approval-795-million-debt-deal-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AOZDB3IEYFKVXFZ5BENHAVORCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际旅游需求强劲，Booking Holdings 第四季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受国际旅游需求旺盛的推动，在线旅行社 Booking Holdings 周四公布的第四季度利润和营收超出分析师预期，盘后股价上涨约 5%。【原文：Online travel agency Booking Holdings surpassed analysts' expectation for fourth-quarter profit and revenue on Thursday, helped by booming demand for international travel, sending its shares up about 5% after the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/booking-holdings-beats-fourth-quarter-estimates-strong-international-travel-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYOZLTGKJFPGVH3FPZBQHE54QQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:10:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒称通胀风险依然存在，并提到经济政策的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周四表示，美国通胀率要达到美联储2%的目标仍有 "一段路要走"，而且通往这一目标的道路依然崎岖不平。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said on Thursday U.S. inflation still has "some way to go" to reach the Fed's 2% target, and that its path toward that goal continues to be bumpy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-says-inflation-risks-remain-cites-economic-policy-uncertainty-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIKZQXQCGJIMXMRIZAT5MCKJTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲：关税和滞胀引发不安，谨慎情绪占据上风]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-2025-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G2J6GMW3FFMKZLXN4T3QXA5FMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>