<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:39:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:39:36 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会就前先锋公司首席执行官请求修改埃克森公司命令一事征求公众意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五表示，它正在就先锋自然资源公司（Pioneer Natural Resources）前首席执行官提交的一份请愿书征求公众意见，该请愿书要求委员会撤销一项涉及埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil Corp）收购先锋公司的命令。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Friday that it was seeking public comment on a petition filed by the former CEO of Pioneer Natural Resources asking the commission to set aside an order involving Exxon Mobil Corp's acquisition of Pioneer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/ftc-seeks-public-comment-ex-pioneer-ceos-petition-modify-exxon-order-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTHJJZF6GBJKTBXZP45EZ5GSNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，美国消费者局驳回了对 Comerica 银行的起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）周五驳回了对 Comerica 银行的诉讼，该机构此前曾指控该银行系统性地虐待了数百万主要是残疾人和老年人的客户。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau on Friday dismissed its lawsuit against Comerica Bank, after the agency previously accused the lender of systematically mistreating millions of mostly disabled and older customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumer-bureau-dismisses-case-against-comerica-bank-filing-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A6EEXOQA5JVRD3QMJKHT4ANU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:45:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车将停止在安大略省生产电动面包车，以适应市场需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司和工会表示，由于销售缓慢，通用汽车将暂时停止其位于安大略省的装配厂的电动商用厢式车生产，直至2025年10月。据代表该厂工人的工会 Unifor 称，底特律汽车制造商将因此暂时裁员 1200 人。【原文：GM is temporarily halting production of its electric commercial van through October 2025 at its assembly plant in Ontario amid slow sales, the company and union said. The Detroit automaker is temporarily laying off 1,200 workers at the plant as a result, according to Unifor, the union representing workers at the plant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-halt-ev-van-production-ontario-adjust-market-demand-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CB4SZOQ7ZZON5LW5A33653PUBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:44:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，特朗普对与中国达成协议持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫新闻秘书卡罗琳-利维特（Karoline Leavitt）周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对与中国达成贸易协议持乐观态度。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is optimistic about reaching a trade deal with China, White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt said on Friday, amid an escalating trade war between the two economic giants that has battered markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-optimistic-reaching-deal-with-china-white-house-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TY5Y7YLBN5IRHIXVAR6DKIWFEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:38:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部就 20 年期债券拍卖时间表和稳定币寻求交易商指导]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五表示，它正在寻求一级交易商对稳定币的指导，以及对 20 年期债券拍卖时间表的潜在改变，包括可能缩短何时发行期。【原文：The U.S. Treasury said on Friday it is seeking guidance from primary dealers on stablecoins as well as potential changes to the 20-year bond auction schedule, including possibly shortening the when-issued period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-treasury-seeks-dealer-guidance-20-year-bond-auction-schedule-stablecoins-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZL3VRQDA75IKZJ2LR56AEXM7AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国石油钻井平台数量创 2023 年 6 月以来单周最大降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周削减石油钻井平台的数量创下自2023年6月以来的单周之最，石油和天然气钻井平台总数连续第三周下降。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut oil rigs by the most in a week since June 2023, lowering the total oil and natural gas rig count for a third consecutive week, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-rig-count-falls-by-most-week-since-june-2023-baker-hughes-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOY256DJEVOWTORZQRPUJN2VRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:15:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美关税战引导黄金突破每盎司 3,200 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，金价首次突破每盎司 3,200 美元大关，原因是美中贸易紧张局势加剧，令全球市场惶恐不安，促使投资者纷纷涌向被视为不确定性避风港的黄金。【原文：Gold prices vaulted over the $3,200-per-ounce mark for the first time on Friday, as intensifying U.S.-China trade tensions rattled global markets and drove investors into the metal seen as a refuge from uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-china-tariff-war-steers-gold-through-3200-per-ounce-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4XAGH6P5NILBENEAVBYYP3YXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国自行车手竞相在可能的关税之前购买哈雷摩托]]></title><description><![CDATA[在巴黎郊外的维利耶-马恩河畔哈雷戴维森经销店，销售十分火爆，法国摩托车手们认为，如果想在贸易战爆发前买到梦寐以求的美国摩托车，最好抓紧时间。【原文：Sales are brisk at the Villiers-Sur-Marne Harley-Davidson dealership outside Paris, where French bikers reckon they had better hurry if they want the American motorcycle of their dreams before trade war puts them out of reach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/french-bikers-race-buy-harleys-before-possible-tariffs-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZZ2DRPMFRIFLPUYEILNVTGF3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构拒绝重审亚马逊数据中心能源协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[政府文件显示，美国能源监管机构本周拒绝了一项重新审议决定的请求，该决定阻止了亚马逊的一个数据中心提高用电量，该数据中心直接与宾夕法尼亚州的塔伦能源公司（Talen Energy）核电站相连。【原文：U.S. energy regulators this week denied a request to reconsider a decision that blocked an Amazon data center, connected directly to a Talen Energy nuclear power plant in Pennsylvania, from ramping up its power use, government filings show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-regulators-deny-rehearing-co-located-amazon-data-center-energy-pact-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CS674XMQAZJTZPNS6XED4MHBEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府 6 个月信用违约掉期利差扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国政府债务的短期保险成本进一步攀升，显示出投资者的紧张情绪。【原文：The short-term cost of insuring exposure to U.S. government debt climbed further on Friday in a sign of investor nervousness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-government-6-month-credit-default-swap-spreads-widen-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XQFWFOHSNOZTGDNHJWMCZKA7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:46:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度天然气公司 GAIL 寻求获得美国液化天然气公司 26% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度天然气公司（GAIL India Ltd）周五发布招标书，购买美国一个液化天然气项目最多 26% 的股份，同时达成一项为期 15 年的天然气进口协议，这有助于新德里努力缩小与华盛顿的贸易顺差。【原文：GAIL India Ltd issued a tender on Friday to buy an up to 26% stake in a liquefied natural gas project in the United States combined with a 15-year gas import deal, aiding New Delhi's efforts to narrow its trade surplus with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/indian-gas-firm-gail-seeks-26-stake-us-lng-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDPL5AQ2CNN6VLZ6A2HFQVIC7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，阿布扎比 ADNOC 考虑竞购 Aethon 的美国天然气资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，阿布扎比国有石油公司 ADNOC 正在考虑竞购投资公司 Aethon Energy Management 的天然气资产，潜在价值约为 90 亿美元。【原文：Abu Dhabi state oil company ADNOC is considering a bid for natural gas assets of investment firm Aethon Energy Management that could potentially be worth about $9 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/abu-dhabis-adnoc-mulls-bid-aethons-us-natgas-assets-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RSEO42CXNOMDI2PVSCEYJV4Y4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司首席执行官告诉《DN日报》，为避免关税，沃尔沃汽车公司可能需要长达两年的时间扩大在美国的生产规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典沃尔沃汽车公司（Volvo Cars）首席执行官哈坎-萨缪尔森（Hakan Samuelsson）周五告诉《每日邮报》（Dagens Nyheter），该公司由中国汽车制造商吉利汽车（GEELY.UL）控股，将需要长达两年的时间来扩大其在美国的汽车生产，以避免被征收高额进口关税。【原文：Sweden's Volvo Cars , which is controlled by Chinese auto maker Geely (GEELY.UL), will need up to two years to expand its U.S. car production in order to avoid hefty import tariffs, CEO Hakan Samuelsson told daily Dagens Nyheter (DN) on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-may-take-up-two-years-expand-us-production-avoid-tariffs-ceo-tells-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQ4CB3OILJKFNF3VGQWATVLRSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙委内瑞拉石油货物出口取消后滞留海上]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，两位知情人士透露，由于美国对欧佩克成员国的买家征收二级关税，委内瑞拉国家石油公司（PDVSA）取消了出口授权，目前至少有两艘雪佛龙公司租用的装载委内瑞拉原油的船只在委内瑞拉水域停滞不前。【原文：At least two vessels carrying Venezuelan crude chartered by Chevron are now stalled in Venezuelan waters due to state oil company PDVSA canceling their export authorizations after the U.S. imposed secondary tariffs on the OPEC member's buyers, two sources with knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevrons-venezuelan-oil-cargoes-stalled-sea-after-export-cancellations-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7NS7ZIZDVLAXFZUDGXIKCZ5DM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储威廉姆斯称关税将推高通胀和失业率]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周五表示，特朗普政府当前的贸易政策将加速今年的通胀，同时他还补充说，美国央行必须防止对物价压力的长期预期脱离实际。【原文：New York Federal Reserve President John Williams said on Friday the Trump administration's current trade policies will accelerate inflation this year, while adding that it's critical for the U.S. central bank to prevent longer-run expectations of price pressures from becoming unmoored.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-williams-says-tariffs-will-push-up-inflation-unemployment-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZOXPWYXTZIS7BHXGO4DN3M4WI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员降低对美联储降息的押注，但仍期待 6 月开始降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，由于密切关注的密歇根大学（University of Michigan）消费者情绪调查显示，3月底和4月初消费者信心和通胀预期进一步恶化，交易商继续放弃对美联储今年大幅降息的押注。【原文：Traders on Friday continued to pull back from bets on aggressive Federal Reserve interest-rate cuts this year, as the closely-followed University of Michigan surveys of consumer sentiment showed confidence and inflation expectations deteriorating further in late March and early April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/traders-lighten-bets-fed-rate-cuts-still-eye-june-start-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERV4YWY2LNIDDF5OM4L4D5HBDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员在国际货币基金组织（IMF）达成协议前纷纷下注，阿根廷外汇期货岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几天，阿根廷比索期货大幅走软，因为在与国际货币基金组织达成协议之前，汇率制度存在不确定性，交易商试探性地押注阿根廷比索将加速贬值。【原文：Argentine peso futures have weakened sharply in recent days as traders place tentative bets on a faster depreciation of the embattled currency amid uncertainty over the exchange rate regime ahead of a deal with the International Monetary Fund.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/argentina-fx-futures-jittery-traders-place-bets-ahead-imf-deal-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RG774XF4P5LTBO5B4TSPQXYSLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从接近 1 美元到关税战赢家，欧元让反对者大跌眼镜]]></title><description><![CDATA[在最近由关税引发的市场动荡中，欧元出人意料地成为赢家，一反早先的共识，兑美元汇率飙升至三年来的新高，因为欧洲在全球混乱中被证明是一个相对安全的赌注。【原文：The euro has emerged as a surprise winner of the recent tariff-induced market turmoil, confounding the earlier consensus by surging to a three-year high against the dollar as Europe proves a relatively safe bet amid the global chaos.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/near-1-tariff-war-winner-euro-confounds-its-naysayers-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYI6CARIOZIO5EOPHCQQRLSMJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:23:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月消费者情绪和通胀预期急剧恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对贸易紧张局势升级感到不安，美国消费者情绪在 4 月份急剧恶化，12 个月的通胀预期飙升至 1981 年以来的最高水平。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment deteriorated sharply in April and 12-month inflation expectations surged to the highest level since 1981 amid unease over escalating trade tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-inflation-expectations-deteriorate-sharply-april-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ILC6CKQFBMJ5LYWA5AGIW246Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆萨莱姆：美联储应 "倾向于 "关税驱动的持续通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆周五表示，他正在密切关注短期通胀预期的上升是否会渗入长期预期，这种情况可能会使对抗通胀变得更加困难，并降低美国中央银行应对劳动力市场疲软的灵活性。【原文：St. Louis Federal Reserve President Alberto Musalem said on Friday he's closely watching whether a rise in short-term inflation expectations seeps into longer-term expectations, a development that could make fighting inflation a much harder job and reduce the U.S. central bank's flexibility to respond to weakness in the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-should-lean-against-persistent-tariff-driven-inflation-musalem-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSF4QRIQTZP5RMRPGHTYRAUYGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:07:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国稀土出口因贸易战管制而停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士称，上周被中国政府列入出口管制清单的七种稀土的装运已经停滞，随着中国出口商开始漫长而不确定的等待政府许可证的过程，加剧了海外稀土短缺的风险。【原文：Shipments of seven rare earths placed on an export control list last week by Beijing have ground to halt, three sources said, raising the risk of shortages overseas as Chinese exporters begin the long, uncertain wait for government licenses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-rare-earth-exports-grind-halt-trade-war-controls-bite-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRNC24LYYFPTRBWXIM5CYOA6M4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:03:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称中国考虑向西方做市商开放 5,200 亿美元的 ETF 市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解此事的人士说，中国一直在考虑允许花旗证券（Citadel Securities）和简街证券（Jane Street）等西方公司在迅速发展的交易所交易基金（ETF）领域担任做市商。【原文：China has been looking at allowing Western firms such as Citadel Securities and Jane Street to act as market makers in its rapidly growing exchange-traded fund (ETF) sector, two people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-has-considered-opening-its-520-billion-etf-market-western-market-makers-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENMWGVZWEFP6FCEKDN7XD6B6WY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰监管机构就 X 使用欧盟个人数据训练 Grok 人工智能一事展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰数据监管机构周五表示，已对社交媒体平台 X 使用从欧盟用户收集的个人数据来训练其人工智能系统 Grok 的行为展开调查。【原文：Ireland's data regulator on Friday said it had opened an investigation into social media platform X over the use of personal data collected from European Union users to train its AI system Grok.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/irish-regulator-investigates-x-over-use-eu-personal-data-train-grok-ai-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7KDUJXP3BOUFG5A5EBHG4BYC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯告诉雅虎财经：市场暂时按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周五在接受雅虎财经（Yahoo Finance）采访时表示，一直承受巨大压力的金融市场似乎正在保持稳定。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said Friday that financial markets, which have been under massive pressure, appear to be holding in, in comments made in an interview with Yahoo Finance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/feds-collins-tells-yahoo-finance-that-markets-are-holding-now-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNSBSIAEABMVNFN3Z7RLXF4KRE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙橄榄油制造商酝酿美国投资，急于出口以避免关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙的一家主要橄榄油生产商正在考虑进军美国，以应对华盛顿发动的关税战。【原文：One of Spain's leading olive oil producers is pondering an expansion into the U.S. in response to the tariff war unleashed by Washington, just as its peers are rushing out exports while the bulk of new tariffs are still on hold.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/spanish-olive-oil-makers-mull-us-investment-rush-exports-avoid-tariffs-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BABS3VBPWFKCJGLDPNY3W24Z5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[品牌首席执行官表示，Stellantis将继续致力于玛莎拉蒂事业]]></title><description><![CDATA[玛莎拉蒂品牌负责人周五表示，尽管美国关税使汽车行业的总体形势变得更加复杂，但汽车制造商斯泰兰特仍将致力于发展其陷入困境的豪华品牌玛莎拉蒂。【原文：Carmaker Stellantis remains committed to its ailing luxury brand Maserati, although U.S. tariffs make the general situation for the automotive industry more complicated, the brand's head said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-remains-committed-maserati-brand-ceo-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APPVXWLFTNOVHJKYL4AL2GQAMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行利润增长，但高管们提出更多关税警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国主要银行第一季度的利润超过预期，股票交易也随之跃升，但高管们周五警告说，全面关税可能会加剧风险并拖累经济增长。【原文：Profits at major U.S. banks beat forecasts in the first quarter as stock trading jumped, but executives warned on Friday that sweeping tariffs could fuel risks and weigh on economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-profits-rise-executives-raise-more-tariff-warnings-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOHUS6UGZBOS5P6IWJGKSZXYMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易动荡阻碍新兴市场债券销售盛宴]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提高关税后引发的动荡，使新兴市场 4 月份的主权债务销售突然停滞，而此前发展中国家和公司的债务发行打破了第一季度的记录。【原文：Turmoil in the wake of U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff hikes has abruptly stalled emerging market sovereign debt sales in April, after issuance from developing nations and companies shattered first-quarter records.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trade-turmoil-stymies-emerging-market-bond-sale-bonanza-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSMNDPIHKBK75ESORBXWISW25U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国部长表示泰国将削减美国玉米进口关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国财政部长周五表示，泰国将削减从美国进口玉米的关税，但数量仍有待敲定。【原文：Thailand will cut tariffs on imports of corn from the United States, but volumes still need to be finalised, the finance minister said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/thailand-will-cut-tariffs-us-corn-imports-minister-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLOUGYDLDVOWBAO5SYFQ6UY6FM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃尼集团向 KKR 出售生物燃料部门股权，从中获利 36 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利能源集团埃尼（Eni）周五表示，已完成向美国基金KKR出售Enilive公司5%的额外股份，从而使出售其生物燃料部门两股少数股权的总收益达到36亿欧元（41亿美元）。【原文：Italian energy group Eni said on Friday it completed the sale of an additional 5% stake in Enilive to U.S. fund KKR, bringing the total proceeds from the disposal of two minority stakes in its biofuel unit to 3.6 billion euros ($4.1 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/eni-pockets-36-bln-euros-stake-sales-biofuel-unit-kkr-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KBJO33QY4VP23A7DUGNH3IF4BQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>