<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:41:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:41:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[关税不确定性挥之不去，企业盈利出现亮点]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括美国搜索巨头 Alphabet、韩国芯片制造商 SK Hynix 和印度 IT 服务提供商 Infosys 在内的一些世界顶级科技公司在其最新财报中提供了乐观的指导，摆脱了不确定的美国贸易政策。【原文：Some of the world's top tech firms, including U.S. search giant Alphabet, South Korean chipmaker SK Hynix and Indian IT services provider Infosys, have provided upbeat guidance in their latest earnings reports, shrugging off an uncertain U.S. trade policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bright-spots-emerge-corporate-earnings-tariff-uncertainty-lingers-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQQVHAUCR5OOZB7M3JVI562KKQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:28:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商意法半导体报告第二季度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的芯片制造商之一意法半导体公司（STMicroelectronics）周四公布了第二季度亏损报告，业绩低于市场预期。【原文：STMicroelectronics , one of Europe's largest chipmakers, reported a second-quarter loss on Thursday, a performance that was worse than market expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmaker-stmicro-reports-second-quarter-loss-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6GHP4U455NBHLOTJAS2ZXJNYA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大泰克资源公司季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大矿业公司泰克资源公司（Teck Resources）周四公布的第二季度利润超出预期，这主要得益于其特雷尔运营公司（Trail Operations）盈利能力的提高。【原文：Canadian miner Teck Resources beat second-quarter profit estimates on Thursday, helped by improved profitability at its Trail Operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-teck-resources-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTCXQV67C5MQRBLB2NEIX3YPHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:20:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税影响，现代汽车第二季度利润下降 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国开始对汽车和零部件征收关税，现代汽车公司周四公布第二季度营业利润下降，同比下降 16%。【原文：Hyundai Motor posted a decline in second-quarter operating profit on Thursday, down 16% from a year earlier, as U.S. tariffs on vehicles and parts started to weigh on its bottom line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-q2-profit-falls-16-us-tariffs-weigh-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FM5RQUIS5JMC7EXWBNVH77IESU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢上半年销售增长好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司周四公布的上半年有机销售额增长好于预期，原因是这家全球最大的包装食品公司提高了价格，以应对咖啡和可可相关品类的投入成本上涨。【原文：Nestle posted better-than-expected first-half organic sales growth on Thursday as the world's biggest packaged food company raised prices to address input cost inflation in coffee and cocoa-related categories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nestle-posts-better-than-expected-h1-sales-growth-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAYCQBDMAZPDRPTO44N2VY3ZEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:13:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第二季度业绩不佳，诺基亚下半年业绩将更强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺基亚首席执行官贾斯汀-霍塔德（Justin Hotard）周四表示，诺基亚预计 2025 年下半年的业绩将强于上半年，两天前，这家网络设备制造商因美元走弱和关税问题发布了盈利预警。【原文：Nokia's expects the second half of 2025 to be stronger than the first, CEO Justin Hotard said on Thursday, two days after the network equipment maker issued a profit warning due to a weaker U.S. dollar and tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nokia-sees-stronger-second-half-after-second-quarter-miss-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXZP55GMOJJRHJJAWE236UUIQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软件公司达索系统第二季度收入增长，但不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国软件制造商达索系统公司（Dassault Systemes）周四公布，其第二季度总收入增长了 6%，略低于市场预期。【原文：French software maker Dassault Systemes reported a 6% rise in its second-quarter total revenue on Thursday, slightly below market estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/software-firm-dassault-systemes-q2-revenue-rises-misses-estimates-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AI6EYX2YIRKEBF5RIWLKCKXC6Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国寻求在关税谈判中利用特朗普对造船业的关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国政府和业界消息人士称，韩国和美国一直在讨论造船合作事宜，其中可能包括投资美国造船厂的现代化改造，以及为美国海军舰队的维修提供更多帮助，因为首尔正在寻求更好的关税条件。【原文：South Korea and the United States have been discussing a shipbuilding tie-up that could include investments to modernise U.S. shipyards and more help to repair the U.S. naval fleet as Seoul seeks better tariff terms, government and industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/south-korea-seeks-leverage-trumps-focus-shipbuilding-tariff-talks-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5TW27SI4FKL5DDKLGGCAT2AUY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行第二季度利润好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管德意志银行全球投资银行部门的业绩喜忧参半，欧元升值也对其造成了冲击，但该行第二季度的利润仍好于一年前的预期。【原文：Deutsche Bank returned to a better-than-expected profit in the second quarter from a year ago despite mixed results at its global investment banking division and a hit from the jump in the euro's value.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/deutsche-bank-posts-better-than-expected-q2-profit-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNESCHMT25JRHJBAR5HLOF7JIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场震荡，中国选股者引领全球对冲基金收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[受港股反弹以及押注人工智能和 "新消费 "企业的推动，专注于中国股票的对冲基金在今年上半年取得了两位数的回报，表现优于全球同行。【原文：Hedge funds focused on Chinese equities posted double-digit returns in the first half of the year, outperforming global peers, fuelled by a rebound in Hong Kong stocks and bets on artificial intelligence and "new consumption" firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-stock-pickers-lead-global-hedge-fund-gains-markets-swing-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTDL3323EVMABOQM3NWBSC6T4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国支持 MP 材料公司后，林纳斯公司认为稀土价格将上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[稀土顶级生产商林纳斯稀土公司（Lynas Rare Earths）首席执行官表示，鉴于对西方材料的需求不断增长，稀土价格可能会进一步反弹。【原文：Prices of rare earths could rally further given growing demand for Western material, reflected in a recent deal by the United States that has shown its resolve to rebuild the sector outside China, the CEO of top producer Lynas Rare Earths said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/lynas-sees-higher-rare-earths-prices-after-us-backs-mp-materials-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5RU6ZYYCGBMG7OOFILSUPQLYSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 贸易协议再次带来欢乐时光]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWPROBDM7NKKFO72WU2IA7P5N4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：随着前景改善，高盛将放弃第二轮裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，在投行业务复苏好于预期之后，高盛决定今年不再进行第二轮基于业绩的大范围裁员。【原文：Goldman Sachs has decided not to go ahead with a second round of broad performance-based job cuts this year after a better than expected recovery in investment banking, Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-forgo-second-round-job-cuts-outlook-improves-ft-reports-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H32FSVK42VNTHNH3ABX6GOEA5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:12:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软称部分 SharePoint 黑客正在使用勒索软件]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软表示，一些参与针对美国科技巨头 SharePoint 服务器的网络间谍活动的黑客现在正在使用勒索软件，这可能是大范围间谍活动的升级。【原文：Microsoft said some of the hackers involved in the cyberespionage sweep aimed at the U.S. tech giant's SharePoint servers are now using ransomware, a potential escalation in the wide-ranging spy campaign.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-says-some-sharepoint-hackers-now-using-ransomware-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U4FSRDLHAZKL3NVX6YHWDZOIHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:29:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行行长：关税可能降低中期通胀风险，抑制支出]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰一位央行高官周四表示，虽然美国关税的全面影响仍不确定，但可能会缓解该国的中期通胀压力，尽管关税可能会抑制商业投资和家庭支出。【原文：A top New Zealand central banker said on Thursday that while the full impact of U.S. tariffs remains uncertain, they could ease medium-term inflation pressures in the country, although the tariffs might dampen business investment and household spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tariffs-may-lower-medium-term-inflation-risks-curb-spending-says-new-zealand-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQKTSLIYTFN3HG2CIV3SBLEO4Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行未对失业率上升感到震惊，将逐步降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚最高央行行长周四表示，由于劳动力市场只是略有缓解，因此采取有节制的渐进式宽松货币政策是合适的。【原文：Australia's top central banker said on Thursday a measured and gradual approach to monetary policy easing was appropriate as the labour market had only eased slightly, shrugging off concerns about a recent jump in the unemployment rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-not-shocked-by-jobless-rise-cut-rates-gradually-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDUANOPT2BMNRJUU7T3KSXBFJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:08:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府建议对人工智能芯片进行位置验证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府周三建议实施出口管制，以核实先进人工智能芯片的位置，此举受到美国国会参众两院两党议员的称赞。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration on Wednesday recommended implementing export controls that would verify the location of advanced artificial intelligence chips, a move that was applauded by U.S. lawmakers from both parties in both houses of Congress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-administration-recommends-location-verification-ai-chips-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6D32AEO6VOVVJNJ36RZPN56ZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:23:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市和澳元因贸易和盈利乐观情绪攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对盈利和贸易的乐观情绪支撑了对高收益资产的需求，周四亚洲股市上涨，澳元创下八个月新高。【原文：Shares in Asia rallied and the Australian dollar hit an eight-month high on Thursday as optimism over earnings and trade supported demand for higher yielding assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWAILKHJT5IF3PZFCLDLSIYPDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易乐观，原油库存下降，油价攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国贸易谈判将缓解全球经济压力的乐观情绪以及美国原油库存降幅超过预期的影响，油价周四上涨。【原文：Oil prices rose on Thursday, buoyed by optimism over U.S. trade negotiations that would ease pressure on the global economy and a sharper-than-expected decline in U.S. crude inventories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-climb-us-trade-optimism-drop-crude-stockpiles-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ245XAGKBK3FNM5LDODYSJJKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德克萨斯州陪审团称 Verizon 在专利侵权案中欠款 1.75 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州马歇尔市一家联邦法院周三表示，美国电信公司威瑞森无线（Verizon Wireless）必须支付 1.75 亿美元的赔偿金，因为该公司侵犯了一位发明家与无线通信技术有关的专利权。【原文：A federal court in Marshall, Texas, said on Wednesday that U.S. telecom company Verizon Wireless must pay $175 million in damages for violating an inventor's patent rights related to wireless communications technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/verizon-owes-175-million-patent-infringement-case-texas-jury-says-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FREDVALKHJM6PKZSPQ7BO5BTOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国贸易部称美韩贸易谈判因贝森特日程安排而取消]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部周四表示，由于美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）的日程安排冲突，韩美两国高官就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）关税问题进行谈判的会谈已被取消。【原文：Talks between top South Korean and U.S. officials to negotiate over U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs have been cancelled due to a scheduling conflict for U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent, South Korea's finance ministry said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-south-korea-trade-talks-cancelled-due-bessent-schedule-ministry-says-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWR5G6VXMVI6VFCLW653SWKZXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易进展提振日元和欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元周四升至近四年来的最高水平，而日元则在美国与其最大贸易伙伴之间的贸易协议取得更多进展后保持涨势，这反过来又提振了更广泛的市场情绪。【原文：The euro crept toward its highest level in nearly four years on Thursday while the yen held to gains following more progress on trade deals between the United States and its largest trading partners, which in turn lifted the broader market mood.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/yen-euro-lifted-by-progress-trade-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INXFMVI2FBMTPJP4JL6TB47C3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险市场 Accelerant 和支持者在美国首次公开募股中筹资 7.24 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国专业保险市场 Accelerant 及其部分现有股东周三表示，他们在美国首次公开募股（IPO）中筹集了 7.2369 亿美元。【原文：Accelerant and some of its existing shareholders raised $723.69 million in an initial public offering (IPO) in the U.S., the specialty insurance marketplace said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/insurance-marketplace-accelerant-backers-raise-724-million-us-ipo-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDLDCZ5CRBNNNINTE4KET4WGOI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本 7 月工厂活动陷入萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一项私营部门调查显示，受美国关税不确定性的影响，日本制造业活动在7月份陷入萎缩。【原文：Japan's manufacturing activity slipped into contraction in July, weighed down by uncertainties over U.S. tariffs, a private-sector survey showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-factory-activity-slips-into-contraction-july-pmi-shows-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WL2LJN2VTFKR7H5P55IDL7CG3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[出版商麦格劳-希尔在美国首次公开募股中筹资 4.15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国出版商麦格劳-希尔公司（McGraw Hill）在投资公司 Platinum Equity 的支持下于周三表示，该公司在美国的首次公开募股已筹集到 4.1463 亿美元。【原文：U.S. publisher McGraw Hill , backed by investment firm Platinum Equity, said on Wednesday it had raised $414.63 million in its initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/publisher-mcgraw-hill-raises-415-million-us-ipo-2025-07-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCJ65NA4YBMPVCCDJL74Z4CFTE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:24:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点：特斯拉称已开始制造经济型汽车的初始版本，销售额急剧下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉（Tesla）周三表示，该公司已制造出经济型汽车的初始版本，此举很可能是为了遏制该公司在全球市场销售额的急剧下降。【原文：Tesla said on Wednesday it has built initial versions of an affordable car, a move likely meant to stem the steep decline in sales the company has experienced in markets across the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/view-tesla-says-it-started-building-initial-versions-an-affordable-car-posts-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COM3JHL2YJIODHGX2QTKS4JOPY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦格理季度利润下降，首席财务官哈维决定辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚顶级投资银行麦格理集团（Macquarie Group）周四公布第一季度净利润下降，并宣布首席财务官亚历克斯-哈维（Alex Harvey）将于2025年底卸任。【原文：Australia's top investment bank, Macquarie Group , reported a decline in first-quarter net profit on Thursday and announced that Chief Financial Officer Alex Harvey will step down at the end of 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/macquaries-quarterly-profit-falls-cfo-harvey-decides-step-down-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OZZVJ3OK6BJBLBYUMHAXNIG3SY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fortescue 铁矿石发货量增加；取消美国和澳大利亚绿色能源项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚福特斯库公司（Fortescue）周四公布了创纪录的第四季度产量，帮助该矿业公司实现了全年指导目标的上限，并表示将取消其在美国和澳大利亚的绿色能源项目。【原文：Australia's Fortescue on Thursday posted record fourth-quarter production that helped the miner meet the top end of its full-year guidance, and said it would scrap its U.S. and Australian green energy projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/fortescue-iron-ore-shipments-rise-scraps-us-aussie-green-energy-projects-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZSGE3JBHNMO5IF5RBOWNR3QJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达供应商 SK 海力士第二季度利润增长 69%，略高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国 SK 海力士（SK Hynix）周四公布了创纪录的季度利润，原因是对用于生成人工智能芯片组的先进芯片的需求强劲，以及一些客户在美国可能征收关税前囤积了半导体。【原文：South Korea's SK Hynix posted on Thursday a record quarterly profit, driven by strong demand for advanced chips used in generative artificial intelligence chipsets and as some customers stockpiled semiconductors ahead of potential U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nvidia-supplier-sk-hynix-q2-profit-rises-69-slightly-above-forecasts-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWVHP2C7LFORTD2IB4XGW2K3RA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《每日电讯报》报道，英国电信将任命维珍媒体 O2 的科比安为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《每日电讯报》周三援引未具名消息人士的话报道，英国最大的宽带和移动服务提供商英国电信集团（BT Group）将任命维珍媒体 O2 的首席财务官帕特里夏-科比安（Patricia Cobian）为其首位女性财务总监。【原文：BT Group , Britain's biggest broadband and mobile services provider, is set to name Virgin Media O2's chief financial officer, Patricia Cobian, as its first female finance chief, The Telegraph reported on Wednesday, citing unnamed sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/bt-appoint-virgin-media-o2s-cobian-cfo-telegraph-reports-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQUIKRLJ2NLKXANH2UK3QM65IQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>