<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:08:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:08:47 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[惠灵顿主导的融资使 Vanta 的估值在一年内提高了 69]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线安全与合规管理平台 Vanta 在其最新一轮融资中的估值为 41.5 亿美元，高于一年前的 24.5 亿美元，这是因为投资者对风险缓解软件的吸引力随着网络攻击而上升。【原文：Online security and compliance management platform Vanta was valued at $4.15 billion in its latest fundraising round, up from $2.45 billion just a year ago, as investor appeal of risk-mitigating software rises in tandem with cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wellington-led-funding-boosts-vantas-valuation-by-69-year-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRX5AYDVORIJ3L4R2CBAMOT77Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波士顿科学公司因心脏设备需求稳定而上调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿科学公司（Boston Scientific）周三上调了年度利润预期，此前对其心脏设备的强劲需求帮助这家美国医疗设备制造商第二季度利润超出预期。【原文：Boston Scientific raised its annual profit forecast on Wednesday, after strong demand for its heart devices helped the U.S. medical device maker beat second-quarter profit estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/boston-scientific-lifts-annual-profit-view-steady-heart-devices-demand-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNJCWOVWK5N35C7ECMHQT5ER4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:58:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪公布第二季度利润增长，分析部门表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[评级机构穆迪（Moody's）周三报告称，受数据和分析部门的强劲收益以及政府借贷增加的推动，第二季度利润有所增长。【原文：Ratings agency Moody's reported a rise in second quarter profit on Wednesday, driven by robust gains in its data and analytics unit and an increase in government borrowing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/moodys-reports-higher-second-quarter-profit-analytics-unit-strength-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4PWREPSDJKA7CJEPAOH6LN36M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NextEra Energy 因可再生能源增长和人工智能驱动的电力需求，季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[NextEra Energy 周三公布的第二季度调整后利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于其可再生能源部门的强劲表现，以及人工智能数据中心和超大规模服务器不断增长的电力需求。【原文：NextEra Energy beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter adjusted profit on Wednesday, driven by strong performance in its renewables unit amid rising power demand from AI data centers and hyperscalers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nextera-energy-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-renewables-growth-ai-driven-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKPUUZA3P5NF7KORCVSNITS7RM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:44:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长贝森特：特朗普政府不急于撤换鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，特朗普政府并不急于提名新的美联储主席来接替杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that the Trump administration was not in a rush to nominate a new Federal Reserve Chair to replace Jerome Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-not-rush-replace-powell-treasury-chief-bessent-says-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUNATW6BPNN3TDFXPBCQ3QIWNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:40:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长贝森特：特朗普在关税税率问题上具有影响力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三在接受彭博电视采访时表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普就关税税率发表的信函为贸易问题创造了很多筹码。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has created a lot of leverage on trade with his letters on tariff rates, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Bloomberg Television in an interview on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasurys-bessent-says-trump-has-leverage-with-tariff-rates-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSIHZYRRH5JYTMU5HSZ56MOB6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:39:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第二季度利润超预期，通用电气弗诺瓦公司上调年度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[电力设备制造商通用电气弗诺瓦公司周三上调了本年度收入和自由现金流预期，此前该公司第二季度利润超出华尔街预期，使其股价在盘前交易中上涨超过 4%。【原文：Power equipment maker GE Vernova raised its current-year revenue and free cash flow forecast after beating Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit on Wednesday, sending its shares rising more than 4% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ge-vernova-raises-annual-forecasts-after-second-quarter-profit-beat-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDD2BQDBIFKOBMI3BQZCE7RIN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将提交针对美国商品的反制措施，以避免即将到来的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会计划向欧盟成员国提交对930亿欧元（约合1090亿美元）美国商品征收反关税的申请，同时其贸易负责人将与美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）举行会谈。【原文：The European Commission plans to submit counter-tariffs on 93 billion euros ($109 billion) of U.S. goods for approval to EU members, while its trade chief will hold talks with U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-submit-countermeasures-us-goods-avert-looming-tariffs-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCI4SKLV3ZNVPD6EAXT37R3KCQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:28:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟技术主管表示：没有计划让大科技公司支付数字法律合规成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟科技主管周三表示，欧盟委员会不会要求 Alphabet、亚马逊、苹果、ByteDance、Meta Platforms 和微软支付监督它们遵守新数字法律的费用。【原文：The European Commission will not ask Alphabet , Amazon , Apple , ByteDance, Meta Platforms and Microsoft to pay the cost of monitoring their compliance with a new digital law, the EU tech chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/no-plans-get-big-tech-pay-digital-law-compliance-costs-eu-tech-chief-says-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXHMKHESYJMDXDZIB4WEHK3IUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用动力公司因喷气机交付量增加而实现季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用动力公司（General Dynamics）周三公布的第二季度利润增长了近 15%，主要得益于公务机交付量的增长，该公司股价在收盘前上涨了 1.7%。【原文：General Dynamics on Wednesday second-quarter profit rose nearly 15% on the back of stronger business jet deliveries, sending the company's shares up 1.7% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/general-dynamics-quarterly-profit-rises-higher-jet-deliveries-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2LLVSBJ7RNRVO2YLE47RAMLMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CME 第二季度利润因交易活动增加而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[衍生品交易所 CME 集团周三公布第二季度利润增长，原因是创纪录的波动性刺激了对其产品的需求，这些产品通常用于对冲宏观经济的不确定性。【原文：Derivatives exchange CME Group reported a higher second-quarter profit on Wednesday, as record volatility boosted demand for its products, which are often used to hedge against macroeconomic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cmes-second-quarter-profit-rises-higher-trading-activity-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KDQWOEP2VMMZP7GDVR4TRTQHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:06:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济学家称美国联邦储备委员会的独立性受到威胁，但无人预计 7 月会降息--路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[接受路透社调查的大多数经济学家都认为，美国联邦储备委员会的独立性正受到日益加剧的政治干预的威胁，尽管最近政策制定者之间出现了意见分歧，但没有人预计 7 月份会降息。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve's independence is under threat from mounting political interference, according to a clear majority of economists polled by Reuters, although no one expects a July interest rate cut despite a recent divergence in views among policymakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-fed-independence-under-threat-say-economists-no-one-expects-july-rate-cut-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UULDY6OZ4ZOBHFUB74ZOKCEJIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标日本交易刺激市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PV7WHM7SPNMALPBKSOWJVACCDU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:48:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛默飞工具和服务需求强劲，季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[赛默飞（Thermo Fisher）周三公布的第二季度利润和收入超出华尔街预期，主要得益于市场对其用于开发疗法的产品和服务的稳定需求。【原文：Thermo Fisher on Wednesday beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit and revenue, helped by steady demand for its products and services used for developing therapies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/thermo-fisher-beats-quarterly-estimates-resilient-demand-its-tools-services-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53JSWD4CCZK5LCOD2X7CQ6Q6AE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[孩之宝因 "魔法集结 "游戏需求强劲而上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[孩之宝公司（Hasbro）周三上调了年度营收预期，这家玩具制造商将依靠 "魔法集结"（Magic: The Gathering）游戏的优势和削减成本的努力来抵御日益加剧的经济和关税不确定性带来的影响。【原文：Hasbro raised its annual revenue forecast on Wednesday, as the toymaker leans on strength of "Magic: The Gathering" games and cost-cutting efforts to weather the impact from mounting economic and tariff uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hasbro-lifts-annual-revenue-forecast-strong-demand-magic-gathering-games-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOZLHXNCLJNONC3AOGSFJWK7PQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AT&T 捆绑计划刺激用户激增，节税为光纤扩张提供资金支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[AT&amp;T 的季度利润超出预期，新增无线用户也超过预期，原因是客户纷纷购买其结合了 5G 移动和高速光纤计划的打折捆绑产品。【原文：AT&amp;T beat quarterly profit estimates and added more wireless subscribers than expected as customers flocked to its discounted bundles combining 5G mobile and high-speed fiber plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/atts-bundled-plans-spur-subscriber-surge-tax-savings-fund-fiber-expansion-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPSGZCXVNZKHLKHOXCRE5MDNAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果和谷歌在移动生态系统方面面临更多英国反垄断审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争监管机构表示，它计划因苹果和谷歌在移动生态系统中的作用而授予它们所谓的战略市场地位，同时加强对它们所谓的双头垄断的审查。【原文：Britain's competition regulator said it plans to designate Apple and Google with so-called strategic market status for their role in mobile ecosystems, as it steps up scrutiny of what it has described as their duopoly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/apple-google-face-more-uk-antitrust-scrutiny-over-mobile-ecosystems-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SICO3NKX6FLAPMBFGNA37MNF3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Infosys 受益于银行和金融部门实力增强，收窄了年度业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度 Infosys 公司周三发布的第一季度财报显示，在金融服务部门增长的推动下，该公司全年收入强于预期，但其全年业绩预期有所收窄。【原文：India's Infosys narrowed its full-year forecast on Wednesday after reporting stronger-than-expected revenue for the first quarter, driven by growth in its financial services segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-infosys-narrows-annual-forecast-helped-by-banking-financial-unit-strength-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZGVPR2RI5NSBIRNRY447ARSIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国称与俄语网络犯罪论坛有关的嫌疑人在乌克兰被捕]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国检察院周三表示，在法国警方和欧洲刑警组织的协助下，一名涉嫌担任俄语网络犯罪论坛 XSS.is 管理员的人在乌克兰被捕。【原文：A person suspected of being the administrator for the Russian language cybercriminal forum XSS.is was arrested in Ukraine, with the assistance of the French police and Europol, the French Public Prosecutor's Office said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/suspect-linked-russian-language-cybercriminal-forum-arrested-ukraine-says-france-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWKMKWUUUFMYPDUAL53723NKKE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:28:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[支付公司 Corpay 以 22 亿美元收购英国 Alpha 集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[商业支付公司 Corpay 周三表示，它将以 22 亿美元的价格收购英国金融服务提供商 Alpha Group。【原文：Business payments firm Corpay said on Wednesday it would buy British financial services provider Alpha Group in a $2.2 billion deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/payments-firm-corpay-signs-22-billion-deal-uks-alpha-group-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MU5ITDLNBRKTJIT5IHJLPDJMQI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:26:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美日贸易协议避免了全球经济的最坏情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家们表示，日本与美国达成的贸易协议可以作为目前正在与华盛顿谈判的许多其他协议的基准，全球经济差不多可以支持一夜之间达成的 15%的水平。【原文：Japan's trade agreement with the U.S. could serve as the benchmark for many other deals currently being negotiated with Washington, and the global economy could just about support the 15% level agreed overnight, economists said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-japan-trade-deal-averts-worst-global-economy-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITAH3UMQXZIJNOMEI6T33M6X7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美日贸易协议提振华尔街期货]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普总统与日本达成贸易协议后，美国股指期货周三跳涨，随着8月1日最后期限的临近，这增强了人们对达成更多此类协议的预期。【原文：U.S. stock index futures jumped on Wednesday after President Donald Trump struck a trade deal with Japan, bolstering expectations of more such agreements as the August 1 deadline approaches.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-lifted-by-us-japan-trade-deal-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWAKQWBEXZN2HBKNMI6OK4TELY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通全球并购主管艾扬格表示，更多巨型交易正在酝酿中]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）的交易人员预测，随着高管们越来越适应动荡的市场和变幻莫测的世界政治，今年下半年全球企业将寻求更大规模的交易。【原文：Companies worldwide are pursuing bigger deals in the second half of this year as executives get increasingly comfortable with volatile markets and unpredictable world politics, dealmakers at JPMorgan Chase forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/more-mega-deals-offing-says-jpmorgans-global-ma-head-aiyengar-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNWHFXTYXBIM3EQPXPOIJK5EPQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股巨头公布财报，市场集中度风险凸显]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街依靠少数高市值股票维持美国股市牛市势头的做法，将在未来几天的主要科技和成长型公司财报中经受考验。【原文：Wall Street's reliance on a small number of high market-value stocks to keep momentum going for the U.S. equities bull market will be tested in coming days as major technology and growth companies report earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-stock-market-concentration-risks-come-fore-megacaps-report-earnings-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AQTRNESB5RLOLHLUCGGG4HKQJU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:15:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国需求复苏，希尔顿上调 2025 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国的旅游需求从 3 月和 4 月的低迷中复苏，酒店运营商希尔顿全球上调了 2025 年的利润预期。【原文：Hotel operator Hilton Worldwide lifted its forecast for 2025 profit, as travel demand in the U.S. recovers from a downturn in March and April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hilton-lifts-2025-profit-forecast-us-demand-recovery-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CKTDAO7DFIP5JB6OS3V7E4QZU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:13:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[被高度做空的 Krispy Kreme、GoPro 跳涨，meme 股继续反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[在零售交易员纷纷涌入百货公司科尔（Kohl's）的前一天，包括 Krispy Kreme 和 GoPro 在内的一些高度缺货公司的股价在周三的盘前交易中跳涨，这得益于这些公司的名字在社交媒体论坛上成为热门话题。【原文：Shares of some highly-shorted companies, including Krispy Kreme and GoPro, jumped in premarket trading on Wednesday, aided by their names trending on social media forums a day after retail traders piled into department store company Kohl's.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/highly-shorted-krispy-kreme-gopro-jump-meme-stock-rally-continues-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43ZSLZPHXFM25OY6RXNZ57CXPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:11:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解释器：什么是代币化，它是加密货币的下一件大事吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[代币化一直是加密货币爱好者的热门词汇，他们多年来一直认为，基于区块链的资产将改变金融市场的底层基础设施。【原文：Tokenization has long been a buzzword for crypto enthusiasts, who have been arguing for years that blockchain-based assets will change the underlying infrastructure of financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/what-is-tokenization-is-it-cryptos-next-big-thing-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJQI7XB2GRNCTD26UB3AVV7Y6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:09:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[绿色债券发行量因气候问题出尔反尔而下降近三分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[新数据显示，在美国和欧洲气候变化政策倒退的背景下，今年政府、银行和公司出售的 "绿色 "债券数量下滑了近三分之一。【原文：The amount of "green" bonds sold by governments, banks and companies has slumped by almost a third this year amid the rollback of climate change policies in the United States and Europe, new figures show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/green-bond-issuance-dives-almost-third-amid-climate-backtracking-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGEUVSQLAJPULNL7V27M322JYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 预计第四季度业绩强劲，发布乐观的季度业绩报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[TE Connectivity 公司周三发布了对第四季度的乐观预期，此前在工业产品强劲需求的推动下，该公司第三季度的利润和收入均好于预期。【原文：TE Connectivity issued an upbeat forecast for the fourth quarter on Wednesday, following better-than-expected third-quarter profit and revenue results driven by strong demand for its industrial products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/te-connectivity-projects-robust-fourth-quarter-reports-upbeat-quarterly-results-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCKZPR6JONPGRPKDKR2OQJYPCM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:05:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在与中国的科技之争中，特朗普将概述人工智能的优先事项]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府将于周三发布一份新的人工智能蓝图，旨在放宽美国对这一处于中美经济竞争对手之间技术军备竞赛中心的产业的管理规定。【原文：The Trump administration is set to release a new artificial intelligence blueprint on Wednesday that aims to relax American rules governing the industry at the center of a technological arms race between economic rivals the U.S. and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-outline-ai-priorities-amid-tech-battle-with-china-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UUIR4GFN3BMBHFLRK4HERGPUPY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>