<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:04:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:04:50 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[联邦通信委员会驳回对美国广播公司总统辩论和哈里斯露面的投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦通信委员会周四表示，将驳回对美国广播公司主持的 9 月总统辩论以及副总统卡马拉-哈里斯在哥伦比亚广播公司的 "60 分钟 "和全国广播公司的 "周六夜现场 "节目中露面的投诉。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission said Thursday it is rejecting complaints over an ABC-moderated September presidential debate and Vice President Kamala Harris' appearances on CBS' "60 Minutes" and NBC's "Saturday Night Live."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fcc-rejects-complaints-over-abc-presidential-debate-harris-appearances-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KK7LAT44SRKJXOFKFQVO6M5OUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:58:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Cosan 公司卸下矿业公司淡水河谷的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西企业集团 Cosan 在周四提交的一份证券文件中称，该公司已卸下其持有的矿业巨头淡水河谷约 1.73 亿股股份，持股比例约为 4.05%。【原文：Brazilian conglomerate Cosan has unloaded some 173 million shares it owned in mining giant Vale , which accounted for a stake of roughly 4.05%, it said in a securities filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazils-cosan-unloads-stake-miner-vale-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXXMEP7LS5P73GS52F7IGMOET4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行将于1月29日降息，对美国关税的潜在影响持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对经济学家进行的一项调查显示，加拿大央行将于1月29日降息25个基点至3.00%，但鉴于美国威胁征收关税以及加拿大可能采取的应对措施等不确定性，许多经济学家对此后的前景没有信心。【原文：The Bank of Canada will cut interest rates by 25 basis points to 3.00% on Jan. 29, according to a Reuters poll of economists, but many were not confident about the outlook beyond that given uncertainty around threatened U.S. tariffs and possible Canada's response.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-canada-cut-rates-jan-29-cautious-over-potential-us-tariff-impact-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWZS4ZEKY5LA7DUUEFEBIRMYXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[费城联储工厂指数创 2020 年 6 月以来最大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[1 月份，美国中大西洋地区制造业活动的一项指标创下约四年半以来的最大涨幅，新订单和出货量双双激增，这可能表明工厂行业的长期低迷可能正在结束。【原文：A gauge of manufacturing activity in the U.S. Mid-Atlantic region shot up by the most in about four-and-a-half years in January, with new orders and shipments both surging, a potential indication that the factory sector's long slump may be ending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/philly-feds-factory-gauge-surges-by-most-since-june-2020-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVVZUQNG6ZN2JO6ENCN5YTYH5A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LIV Golf 与福克斯体育签订多年媒体转播权协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[福克斯体育频道（Fox Sports）周四宣布，已与 LIV Golf 签订多年媒体转播权协议，从下月起在美国转播其联赛比赛。【原文：Fox Sports has signed a multi-year media rights agreement with LIV Golf to broadcast its league competition in the U.S. starting next month, the network announced on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/liv-golf-signs-multi-year-media-rights-deal-with-fox-sports-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNXNKKP5ZROCDJAF7M6I7UZRLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[12 月美国进口价格保持平稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于燃料和食品成本的飙升被其他方面的疲软所抵消，12 月份美国进口价格连续第三个月勉强上涨，这对通胀前景来说是个好兆头。【原文：U.S. import prices barely rose for a third straight month in December as a surge in the costs of fuels ad foods was offset by weakness elsewhere, which bodes well for the inflation outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-import-prices-remain-tame-december-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCC77YKB3JLVTKRLOPUXXK5W6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:08:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，1 万亿美元回购可能提振华尔街]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者一直希望唐纳德-特朗普下周重返白宫将提振美国股市，而高盛（Goldman Sachs）则认为股市将受益于至少五年来最大的公司回购预期。【原文：Investors have been hoping Donald Trump's return to the White House next week will boost the U.S. stock market, while Goldman Sachs sees stocks benefiting from the biggest expected company buybacks in at least five years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-could-get-boost-1-trillion-buybacks-goldman-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTKYDSGOI5IOLFI7Y2MYNZRH3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数增加；劳动力市场状况依然健康]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数增幅超过预期，但仍保持在劳动力市场健康的水平。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased more than expected last week, but remained at levels consistent with a healthy labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-labor-market-conditions-still-healthy-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GULQNRSTU5N53KPREOLHB7KBMU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:41:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月零售额稳健增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 12 月份零售额稳健增长，表明经济需求强劲，进一步巩固了美联储今年降息的谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. retail sales increased solidly in December, pointing to strong demand in the economy and further reinforcing the Federal Reserve's cautious approach to cutting interest rates this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-retail-sales-rise-solidly-december-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42G2QXS2K5LJ3FPYIJQ5ELWHMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[任天堂称 Switch 2 将于 2025 年发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本游戏公司任天堂（Nintendo）周四表示，将于今年推出 Switch 2 游戏机，作为其热门设备 Switch 的后续产品。【原文：Japanese gaming company Nintendo will launch the Switch 2 console, successor to its hit Switch device, this year, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nintendo-says-switch-2-will-be-released-2025-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4V6Y5MBMXVIEDLXQUS57U6ORAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿尔巴尼亚批准与贾里德-库什纳的公司有关的豪华度假村项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿尔巴尼亚政府已授予一家与唐纳德-特朗普的女婿贾里德-库什纳（Jared Kushner）有关联的公司战略投资者地位，该公司将在一个曾经是军事前哨的无人居住的地中海岛屿上建造一个豪华度假村。【原文：Albania's government has granted strategic investor status to a company linked to Donald Trump's son-in-law Jared Kushner to build a luxury resort on an uninhabited Mediterranean island that was once a military outpost.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/albania-approves-luxury-resort-project-linked-jared-kushners-company-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6YIIIMW6JLFZEBK72L6WJQNBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自动化公司 Symbotic 签订 2 亿美元收购沃尔玛机器人部门的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Symbotic 周四表示，将以 2 亿美元现金收购沃尔玛的机器人业务，以帮助该零售商扩大自动化供应链，这使得这家仓库机器人公司的股价在盘前交易中上涨了 20%。【原文：Symbotic said on Thursday it would buy Walmart's robotics business for $200 million in cash to help expand the retailer's automated supply chain, sending shares of the warehouse robotics firm up 20% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/automation-firm-symbotic-signs-200-mln-deal-buy-walmarts-robotics-unit-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7HZHEKLKBKKNEDVRNDQQLM5BE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利息收入增长，雨天基金减少，PNC 财务公司利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[PNC Financial 周四公布第四季度利润增长，原因是该公司获得了更多的利息收入，并预留了更少的资本以应对潜在的贷款违约。【原文：PNC Financial on Thursday reported a higher fourth-quarter profit as it earned more in interest payments and set aside less capital to cover potential loan defaults.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/pnc-financials-profit-rises-interest-income-growth-lower-rainy-day-funds-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7X5M2Y4MO5K2HBXZLTFMT37XNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 12:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利因投资银行业务复苏而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利第四季度利润增长，主要得益于投资银行的交易热潮。【原文：Morgan Stanley's profit increased in the fourth quarter, fueled by a wave of dealmaking for the investment bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-profit-jumps-recovery-investment-banking-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVESMR6WYJMPLAZHQMX6JL5BRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 12:37:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车需求疲软，竞争加剧，Polestar 预计盈利能力将推迟]]></title><description><![CDATA[Polestar 首席执行官表示，这家瑞典电动汽车制造商需要更长时间才能实现盈利，此前该公司报告称，2024 年的汽车销量低于预期，这使得该公司在美国上市的股票在盘前交易中下跌了约 8%。【原文：Polestar CEO said it would take longer for the Swedish EV maker to be profitable after the company reported it sold fewer cars in 2024 than it had projected, sending the company's U.S.-listed shares down about 8% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ev-maker-polestars-full-year-car-sales-miss-forecast-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNEXXN3ZSBNNTI7KO73XAHLQME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 12:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行利润因投资银行业务和交易业务增长而飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行（Bank of America BAC.N）周四公布利润增长，原因是其投资银行家利用了第四季度交易复苏的机会，同时该银行预测 2025 年将获得更多的利息收入。【原文：Bank of America BAC.N reported higher profit on Thursday as its investment bankers capitalized on resurgence in dealmaking in the fourth quarter while the lender predicted it would earn more interest income in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-profit-rises-investment-banking-boost-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BH2QKU4MVKXVLC4XAJHHXWCB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Point72 的新人工智能基金收益率达到两位数，接近 15 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，史蒂文-科恩（Steven Cohen）的 Point72 资产管理公司（Point72 Asset Management）以人工智能（AI）为重点的新基金在三个月前刚刚推出后就取得了 14% 的收益，基金规模增至近 15 亿美元。【原文：Steven Cohen's Point72 Asset Management's new artificial intelligence (AI)-focused fund posted a 14% gain after launching just three months ago, growing the fund to nearly $1.5 billion, according to sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/point72s-new-ai-fund-near-15-bln-after-double-digit-returns-sources-say-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NFLCDDLTNMLFDRRJJ2GM5CZBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[服装和玩具需求强劲，塔吉特上调假日销售展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[受 11 月和 12 月服装、玩具和美容产品购物需求强劲的影响，塔吉特周四上调了假日季度可比销售额预期。【原文：Target raised its holiday-quarter comparable sales forecast on Thursday, buoyed by robust shopper demand for clothing, toys and beauty products during November and December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/target-revises-holiday-sales-outlook-strong-apparel-toy-demand-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPBKAXB7CFIR5GMPMV2HC2OASM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，凯雷为可能出售英国基金网络 Calastone 物色银行家]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟知内情的人士称，凯雷已与银行家商讨出售其英国基金网络和数据业务 Calastone 的事宜，这将是该行业吸引了数十亿英镑投资者的最新一笔交易。【原文：Carlyle has lined up bankers to explore a sale of its British funds network and data business Calastone, which would be the latest deal in a sector that has attracted billions of pounds from investors, four people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyle-lines-up-bankers-possible-sale-british-fund-network-calastone-sources-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E45PR7HHNZMZRAJQUJIALSVFCA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:30:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌签署协议购买印度农场的碳减排信用额度]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌（Google）周四表示，将购买印度一项计划的碳信用额度，该计划将大量农业废弃物转化为生物炭，生物炭是一种木炭，可以清除大气中的二氧化碳并将其返回土壤。【原文：Google will buy carbon credits from an Indian initiative that turns large amounts of agricultural waste into biochar - a form of charcoal that removes carbon dioxide from the atmosphere and returns it to the soil, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-signs-deal-buy-carbon-removal-credits-indian-farms-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NR7XGU7ODJNUBLV57B4DE7NJVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok 的禁令将如何生效--以及为什么用户不会使用变通办法]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国字节跳动公司（ByteDance）旗下的社交媒体应用 TikTok 将于周日在美国被禁用，除非达成协议将其出售给美国投资者或美国最高法院进行干预。【原文：Social media app TikTok, which is owned by China's ByteDance, will be banned in the United States on Sunday unless a deal comes together to sell it to a U.S. investor or the U.S. Supreme Court intervenes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/how-tiktok-ban-would-work-why-user-workarounds-wont-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQ4Q5BWVL5JPRJQSZNZ5IUBPGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国会共和党人警告说，美国债券收益率上升可能会打击特朗普的减税计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在唐纳德-特朗普重新执政的前几天，他在美国国会的一些共和党盟友警告说，当选总统激进的减税议程可能会成为债券市场担忧迹象的牺牲品。【原文：Just days before Donald Trump returns to power, some of his Republican allies in the U.S. Congress are warning that the president-elect's aggressive tax-cut agenda could fall victim to signs of worry in the bond market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/republicans-congress-warn-rising-us-bond-yields-could-hit-trumps-tax-cut-plans-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXXCOJE6BFMGBCBSOAWBLGB7WU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:17:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国联邦调查局（FBI）盯上华为老员工创办的中国科技公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息来源和文件显示，美国商务部和联邦调查局都在调查一家鲜为人知的电信硬件公司，该公司十多年前由华为高级资深员工在中国创办，可能存在安全风险。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department and FBI are both investigating a little-known telecoms hardware firm founded by senior Huawei veterans in China more than a decade ago over possible security risks, sources and documents show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-tech-firm-founded-by-huawei-veterans-fbis-crosshairs-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q3DFNPKBN5O3TPIUPJJNNHS7BU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:15:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价通胀缓解与银行盈利丰收]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZAN7MMWDVOEHLBZWQKVZCIMPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国宣布向 12 个州的能源公用事业提供近 230 亿美元贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部贷款办公室周四宣布为十几个州的几家能源公用事业公司提供 229.2 亿美元的有条件融资。【原文：The U.S. Energy Department's loan office on Thursday announced $22.92 billion in conditional financing for several energy utilities across a dozen states.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-announces-nearly-23-billion-loans-energy-utilities-across-12-states-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EH245DOFVOEHOJV3XTNAWCYRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普曾一度颠覆贸易，又将以新关税再次颠覆贸易]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普八年前来到华盛顿，发誓要改写美国的贸易关系，缩小巨大的货物贸易逆差，并通过新的关税重建美国的工业基础。【原文：Donald Trump came to Washington eight years ago vowing to rewrite U.S. trade relationships, shrink a massive goods trade deficit and rebuild America's industrial base with new tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-upended-trade-once-aims-do-so-again-with-new-tariffs-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTU3F3WX65PIPDKJ4QELBYEXDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者关注特朗普的经济政策，美元成为主宰]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普即将重返白宫，积极降息的希望逐渐破灭，这推动美元升至多年高位，投资者认为，在新政府支持增长和通胀政策的帮助下，美元将继续走强。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's imminent return to the White House and fading hopes for aggressive interest rate cuts have driven the dollar to multi-year highs, and investors see this strength continuing, aided by the new administration's pro-growth and inflationary policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-rules-investors-eye-trumps-economic-policies-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOQ2ALK4SJKQPPA3PQ46AOZ4OM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康（UnitedHealth）盈利超预期，医疗服务实力强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）周四公布的第四季度利润超过分析师预期，原因是其医疗服务部门表现强劲，但季度销售额未达预期。【原文：UnitedHealth Group reported a fourth-quarter profit on Thursday that beat analysts' estimates due to strength in its health services unit, but missed estimates for quarterly sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-beats-profit-estimates-lower-than-expected-costs-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZN6SMBVNFNABFKMVXJL73LDZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:05:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Codelco 提高 2024 年铜产量，但后期推进令工人吃紧，维护工作延迟]]></title><description><![CDATA[铜生产商 Codelco 在去年年底大力推动在 2023 年将年产量从 25 年来的最低点略微提高，但工会工人和分析师表示，在该公司力争在本十年末将年产量提高到 170 万公吨的过程中，所采用的策略是不可持续的。【原文：Copper producer Codelco pushed hard at the end of last year to lift annual output slightly from a 25-year-low in 2023, but union workers and analysts said the tactics used were unsustainable as the company strives for annual production of 1.7 million metric tons by the end of the decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/codelco-boosts-2024-copper-output-late-push-strains-workers-delays-maintenance-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNSCCCPOTJI2JCXKSM67LBQHBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际劳工组织称全球失业率将维持在 5%的历史最低水平附近]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际劳工组织（International Labour Organization）在周四的一份报告中说，去年全球失业率稳定在5%的历史最低水平，并将在2025年继续保持这一水平。【原文：Global unemployment remained steady last year at an historical low of 5%, where it is set to stay in 2025, the International Labour Organization said in a report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-unemployment-set-hold-near-historical-low-5-ilo-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFVKPMW4LNMAHOSHQYBBYQ2ID4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 10:48:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>