<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 02:48:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 02:48:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市因中国忧虑而震荡；美国长端债券收益率随美元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国市场疲软拖累亚洲股市周四走低，而较长期的美国债券收益率与美元一起上涨，因为投资者在评估世界最大经济体的货币政策和通胀前景。【原文：Weak China markets dragged broader Asian shares lower on Thursday, while longer-dated U.S. bond yields rose alongside the dollar as investors assessed the monetary policy and inflation outlook in the world's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXV4PRPLA5JBPI526PB4G25BOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 02:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价走低，石油产量增加和需求增长疲软的预测造成压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四早盘，油价小幅下跌，原因是在需求增长疲软的预测下，预计全球产量将增加，而美元走强也抑制了油价。【原文：Oil prices dropped slightly early on Thursday on expectations of higher global production amid forecasts for weak demand growth, while a firmer dollar also kept a lid on prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-edge-down-forecasts-higher-oil-output-weak-demand-growth-weigh-2024-11-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQYIU6OPGRI4DO2NX25PDSOYCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:43:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普贸易势头盖过美联储宽松观点，美元创一年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑主要货币周四重上一年高位，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）大选获胜所带来的势头使美元连续第四个交易日上涨，而对美联储宽松政策的押注则有所上升。【原文：The U.S. dollar revisited a one-year high against major peers on Thursday, as a fourth straight winning session from momentum sparked by Donald Trump's election victory eclipsed a rise in bets for Federal Reserve easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-one-year-high-trump-trade-momentum-eclipses-fed-easing-view-2024-11-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3UJS4VRMNOHJJLPHQQMN7QYQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚阿瓦尔集团第三季度利润猛增六倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚金融集团 Grupo Aval 周三报告称，其第三季度净利润增长了六倍多，攀升至 4,157 亿哥伦比亚比索（9,418 万美元）。【原文：Colombian financial conglomerate Grupo Aval reported on Wednesday a more than six-fold increase in its third-quarter net profit, climbing to 415.7 billion Colombian pesos ($94.18 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/profit-colombias-grupo-aval-jumps-six-fold-third-quarter-2024-11-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CGPIX4JWRILRGZ4AKDJUL2XDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:15:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲航空公司将运营中断归咎于供应链困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内高管表示，亚太地区的旅游需求已从大流行病中恢复过来，但供应链问题扰乱了运营，并使航空公司面临消费者保护规则不断加强的风险，因此该地区航空公司的盈利面临压力。【原文：Asia-Pacific travel demand has recovered from the pandemic, but earnings at the region's airlines are under pressure from supply chain problems disrupting operations and exposing them to strengthening consumer protection rules, industry executives say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/asias-airlines-blame-supply-chain-woes-disrupted-operations-2024-11-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EWHGEA7UZIZFC3HZPY3YPAEKA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强劲增长后澳大利亚 10 月份就业不及预期，失业率保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管失业率保持稳定，且劳动力市场的基本趋势仍有韧性，但澳大利亚的就业率在连续大幅增长后，10 月份仍不及预期。【原文：Australian employment missed forecasts in October after a run of outsized gains, though the jobless rate held steady and underlying trends in the labour market remained resilient.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-employment-rises-15900-oct-jobless-holds-41-2024-11-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN3MH3DJDFPDXMRX32DY2FXNJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国消费者组织就 iCloud 服务起诉苹果公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国消费者组织 Which? 将于周四对苹果公司提起法律诉讼，指控这家科技巨头违反竞争法，将数百万用户有效锁定在其 iCloud 服务中。【原文：British consumer group Which? will launch legal action against Apple on Thursday, alleging the tech giant breached competition law by effectively locking millions of its customers into its iCloud service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-consumer-group-takes-apple-over-icloud-service-2024-11-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YTUMIZCFZM5DDWZDVKDNEAD4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:08:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构警告银行家加强对金融犯罪的关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国监管机构周三警告银行家，政府将继续加大打击洗钱的力度，并执行 "了解你的客户 "规则。【原文：U.S. regulators warned bankers on Wednesday that the government will continue to beef up efforts to fight money laundering and enforce know-your-customer rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-regulators-warn-bankers-about-intensified-focus-financial-crime-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKHUSVUYR5PSNJV3JJ5OCWMPSY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 23:14:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贷款机构巴西银行公布利润增长 8%，贷款损失展望上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国营银行巴西银行（Banco do Brasil）周三公布，其第三季度调整后净利润同比增长 8.3%，同时该银行还表示，目前预计今年的贷款损失准备金将有所增加。【原文：Brazilian state-run lender Banco do Brasil posted on Wednesday an 8.3% increase in its third-quarter adjusted net profit from a year earlier, while it also said it now expects higher loan-loss provisions for this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/lender-banco-do-brasil-posts-8-profit-increase-higher-loan-loss-outlook-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ACPIS2SW3VNGRIT73XIWJD7PHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 23:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能蓬勃发展，苹果主要供应商富士康第三季度业绩预计强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾富士康是全球最大的合约电子制造商，预计将于周四公布第三季度利润同比增长 7%，原因是人工智能服务器需求强劲。【原文：Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker, is expected to report on Thursday that third-quarter profit rose 7% year-on-year on robust demand for artificial intelligence servers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/major-apple-supplier-foxconn-expected-report-strong-q3-results-ai-boom-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MY65UMUYPROTZAZYE3HFVFLT5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 23:04:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约邮报》报道，联邦调查局突袭了 Polymarket 首席执行官的住所，没收了电话和电子产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约邮报》报道，联邦执法人员周三突袭了 Polymarket 首席执行官 Shayne Coplan 位于纽约市中心的住所，没收了他的手机和电子产品。【原文：Federal law enforcement agents raided the downtown New York home of Polymarket CEO Shayne Coplan on Wednesday, seizing his phone and electronics, according to a story in the New York Post.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fbi-raids-polymarket-ceos-home-seizing-phone-electronics-ny-post-reports-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RT2D4RWM35OQFMKQ3TXCXVNMWI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[绿光的艾因霍恩预计特朗普执政期间通胀将回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[绿光资本（Greenlight Capital）总裁大卫-艾因霍恩（David Einhorn）周三表示，他已经为自己的对冲基金投资组合增加了一些通胀保护措施，因为他认为在当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府执政期间，通胀率将会上升。【原文：Greenlight Capital President David Einhorn said on Wednesday he has added some inflationary protection to his hedge fund portfolio as he believes that inflation will go up under the government of President-elect Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/greenlights-einhorn-expects-inflation-pick-up-under-trump-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OI6ENSDSKVKHHDUL4TLXT3NIRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visa 称欧盟监管机构正在调查向零售商收取的费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[支付巨头威士公司（Visa）周三表示，欧盟委员会（EC）已对向零售商收取的费用展开初步调查。【原文：Payments giant Visa said on Wednesday the European Commission (EC) had opened a preliminary investigation into fees charged to retailers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/visa-says-eu-regulator-probing-fees-charged-retailers-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDDXEGLNYFJNXOZ23YDIXYYLXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:32:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BMO 称，银行涌入美国债市，创 2016 年以来最大单日融资规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，银行通过发行投资级债券筹集了 235 亿美元，这是金融机构自 2016 年初以来单日最大的一次发债，因为它们预计明年的利率可能会提高。【原文：Banks raised $23.5 billion by issuing investment-grade bonds on Tuesday, the biggest debt issuance by financial institutions in a single day since the beginning of 2016, as they anticipate potentially higher interest rates next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/banks-flood-us-debt-market-biggest-single-day-raise-since-2016-bmo-says-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KT74SVN7RIYVJY6J22YX2D7N4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:07:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[班克曼-弗里德中尉为检察官开发欺诈侦查工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[前 FTX 高管编写了计算机代码，使他被监禁的前老板山姆-班克曼-弗里德（Sam Bankman-Fried）能够从加密货币客户那里窃取数十亿美元，这位前高管还开发了一款软件，帮助美国政府揭露股票市场的欺诈行为。【原文：The former FTX executive who wrote computer code that enabled his imprisoned former boss Sam Bankman-Fried to steal billions of dollars from cryptocurrency customers has built software to help the U.S. government uncover fraud in the stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bankman-fried-lieutenant-builds-fraud-detection-tool-prosecutors-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WIIYKLNLZIU7DQ7EQY5LAK6MQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲通胀形势严峻，请鲍威尔上台]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHHRF7OXBVLA7IMSCILOZF2T2U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佩尔茨称特朗普大选后股市涨势不会中断]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金经理纳尔逊-佩尔茨（Nelson Peltz）今年曾支持当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump），他表示，大选推动的股市涨势不可能一直持续下去。【原文：Hedge fund manager Nelson Peltz, who backed president-elect Donald Trump this year, said the election-fueled stock market rally cannot continue uninterrupted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/peltz-says-trump-election-stock-market-rally-cannot-continue-uninterrupted-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73QI3JSZ3BINLKWY5AUY4HB7Z4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西努班克第三季度调整后利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西数字贷款公司努班克（Nubank）周三表示，在外汇中性的基础上，该公司第三季度调整后净利润比去年同期增长了一倍多，以创纪录的回报率超过了分析师的预期。【原文：Brazilian digital lender Nubank's adjusted net profit more than doubled in the third quarter from year earlier on a foreign-exchange neutral basis, it said on Wednesday, beating analysts' estimates with record returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/brazils-nubank-beats-estimates-with-third-quarter-adjusted-profit-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPFPQUYNEJJFZJGBQUXPK27C5Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能刺激网络工具需求，思科上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[思科系统公司（Cisco Systems）周三上调了年度营收预期，这表明随着这家计算机网络设备制造商将重点转向网络安全、云系统和人工智能驱动的产品，市场需求正在改善。【原文：Cisco Systems raised annual revenue forecast on Wednesday, a sign of improving demand as the computer networking equipment maker shifts focus to cybersecurity, cloud systems and AI-driven products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cisco-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NTZ5RYLSJKEDAQECOVXATNTJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行首席执行官表示对交易和消费者金融充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周三于纽约举行的一次行业会议上，美国银行首席执行官们表示对交易前景和美国消费者的健康状况充满信心。【原文：U.S. bank CEOs expressed confidence in the dealmaking outlook and the health of U.S. consumers at an industry conference in New York on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bank-ceos-express-confidence-deals-consumer-finances-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CDUVW7FBFFJNVG37NC4VQTDKDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会在针对亚马逊的裁决中禁止强制性反工会会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳工委员会周三表示，亚马逊公司在纽约市一家仓库举行的强制会议上做出了非法承诺和威胁，以阻止工会的成立，同时禁止雇主继续举行此类会议。【原文：Amazon.com made unlawful promises and threats during mandatory meetings to discourage unionizing at a New York City warehouse, a U.S. labor board said on Wednesday while banning employers from holding such meetings moving forward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-labor-board-bans-mandatory-anti-union-meetings-ruling-against-amazon-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PORWSKJ4ARO4LGUUNM6MNICQKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:45:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普胜选后，美国消费者监督机构面临限制和审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行高管和律师预计，即将上任的特朗普政府将对美国消费者金融保护局（CFPB）施加重大限制，但总统的民粹主义倾向可能会为该监管机构的一些活动留下空间。【原文：Bank executives and lawyers anticipate the incoming Trump administration to place significant limits on the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB), but the president's populist leanings could leave room for some activity by the watchdog.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-watchdog-facing-curbs-scrutiny-following-trump-win-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJKCBTSZXRLC7MCYO2U7BFV3VM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[红色扫荡可能加速美国债务上限协议的达成，引发长期债券忧虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）领导下的统一政府可能会让投资者从近年来围绕美国债务上限的激烈争论中解脱出来，尽管这种争论会引发肆无忌惮的财政扩张前景，从而可能在较长时期内给债券带来压力。【原文：A unified government under Donald Trump may offer investors reprieve from the bruising battles around the U.S. debt ceiling that have roiled markets in recent years, even as it raises the prospect of unbridled fiscal expansion that could pressure bonds over the longer term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/red-sweep-may-speed-us-debt-ceiling-deal-stoke-long-term-bond-worries-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZKSGJGV3BLNVOYH57SIVK2QAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼尔森-佩尔茨称迪士尼新任董事长戈尔曼将找到一位 "值得尊敬的首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金经理纳尔逊-佩尔茨（Nelson Peltz）今年在华特-迪士尼（Walt Disney）的董事会上遭遇挫败，但他相信公司新任董事会主席将找到一位 "值得尊敬的首席执行官 "来接替鲍勃-艾格（Bob Iger）。【原文：Hedge fund manager Nelson Peltz, who lost a bruising boardroom challenge at Walt Disney this year, is confident the company's new board chairman will find a 'respectable CEO' to replace Bob Iger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nelson-peltz-says-new-disney-chairman-gorman-will-find-respectable-ceo-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPAVRPCSXBOBNNELOSSHMHW6IU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月预算赤字跃升至 2,570 亿美元，给特朗普带来巨大压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三表示，美国 10 月份的预算赤字猛增近四倍，达到 2,570 亿美元，这一数字被几个一次性因素夸大了，但在新财年开始时，这个大窟窿将在 1 月份移交给当选总统唐纳德-特朗普。【原文：The U.S. budget deficit jumped nearly four-fold to $257 billion in October, a figure inflated by several one-off factors, the Treasury Department said on Wednesday but starting a new fiscal year with a big hole that will be turned over to President-elect Donald Trump in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-october-budget-deficit-jumps-257-billion-handing-hole-trump-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3B2AYFRPRVPW3OAJX4AODXJWAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，由于成本激增，沙特阿拉伯将体育作为 NEOM 计划的优先事项]]></title><description><![CDATA[在该项目长期首席执行官突然离职一天后，三位消息人士告诉路透社，由于成本上升的压力，沙特阿拉伯已经缩减了其 NEOM 千兆工程的宏伟目标，以优先完成未来十年举办全球体育赛事的基本要素。【原文：Saudi Arabia has scaled back lofty ambitions for its NEOM gigaproject to prioritize completing elements essential to hosting global sporting events over the next decade as rising costs weigh, three sources told Reuters a day after the sudden departure of the project's longtime CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-arabia-prioritizes-sports-neom-plans-costs-balloon-sources-say-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMHYMVZWRFO3PLY2FMVJ5PKMU4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸港口雇主称关键合同问题无重大进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表 45,000 名东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸码头工人的工会和代表雇主的团体本周举行了新一轮合同谈判，但未能在一些关键问题上取得重大进展。【原文：The union representing 45,000 East Coast and Gulf Coast dockworkers and a group representing employers held a new round of contract talks this week but failed to make significant progress on some key issues, the employers group said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-east-coast-gulf-coast-ports-employer-says-no-significant-progress-key-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EGEQLKNOSVMOVJIVZ4OPSHX4QY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 18:53:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 X 公司聘请马哈茂德-礼萨-班基（Mahmoud Reza Banki）担任首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）拥有的社交媒体平台 X 任命马哈茂德-礼萨-班基（Mahmoud Reza Banki）为首席财务官，他在 LinkedIn 上的个人资料显示。【原文：Elon Musk-owned social media platform X named Mahmoud Reza Banki as its chief financial officer, his LinkedIn profile showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/musks-x-names-mahmoud-reza-banki-cfo-wsj-reports-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54NT4UG4LFOUPPAYK3HFOKPFE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 18:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德：进一步降息的幅度 "仍有待观察]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联邦储备银行行长杰弗里-施密德（Jeffrey Schmid）周三表示，美国央行迄今为止的降息行动表明，该行对通胀率正在下行的信心不断增强，但他并未就他认为可能适宜的更多次降息给出指导性意见。【原文：Kansas City Federal Reserve Bank President Jeffrey Schmid on Wednesday said the U.S. central bank's interest-rate cuts to date acknowledge its growing confidence that inflation is headed down, but gave no steer on how many more rate cuts he feels may be appropriate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-schmid-extent-further-rate-cuts-remains-be-seen-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHG3GRLSB5P2FCINY3G6QLHJQ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 18:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆萨莱姆称美联储正处于抗击通胀的 "最后一公里"，但近期数据引发风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联储主席阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆（Alberto Musalem）周三表示，美联储正处于抗击通胀的 "最后一英里"，物价压力正在向美国央行2%的目标靠拢，尽管最近的数据提高了进展可能放缓或逆转的风险。【原文：The Federal Reserve is in the "last mile" of its inflation fight, with price pressures converging towards the U.S. central bank's 2% target, though recent data have raised the risk that progress may slow or reverse, St. Louis Fed President Alberto Musalem said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/musalem-says-fed-last-mile-inflation-fight-recent-data-raise-risks-2024-11-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYJFACSVJFL6DIGKWYYU2LYFJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 18:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>