<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:10:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:10:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普扩大美国关键矿产清单，将铜、冶金煤纳入其中]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周四公布了一份其认为对美国经济和国家安全至关重要的新的重要矿产清单，其中增加了对电动汽车、电网和数据中心至关重要的铜，以及用于制造焦炭的冶金煤。【原文：The Trump administration on Thursday unveiled a new list of critical minerals it deems essential to the U.S. economy and national security, adding copper, which is vital to electric vehicles, power grids, and data centers, as well as metallurgical coal, which is used to make coke.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-expands-us-critical-minerals-list-include-copper-metallurgical-coal-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">765YQGJLWZJJPGDM5QQRE5PASA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:06:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙对人工智能生成未成年人性图像处以罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙数据保护机构周四表示，它已对一名分享人工智能生成的未成年人真实面孔性图像的人处以罚款，西班牙媒体称这是欧洲首个对此类内容进行经济处罚的案例。【原文：Spain's data protection agency on Thursday said it had fined a person for sharing AI-generated sexual images of minors using real faces, in what Spanish media said was the first case in Europe of a financial penalty for this type of content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/spain-issues-fine-ai-generated-sexual-images-minors-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UO764UDR7NKNJABHZD42DL45HQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:51:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 Ivey PMI 显示 10 月份经济活动扩张速度放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四公布的 Ivey 采购经理人指数（PMI）数据显示，10 月份加拿大经济活动增速放缓，价格指数走高。【原文：Canadian economic activity expanded at a slower pace in October as a measure of prices edged higher, Ivey Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-ivey-pmi-shows-activity-expanding-slower-pace-october-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PK7JS5LPNFNEVKFAL46FXKW2XQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国地区性银行经受住了 CRE 风暴的考验，但办公楼贷款仍处于落后状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师们表示，尽管少数贷款变质引发了担忧，但美国地区性银行的商业房地产贷款账簿被证明具有广泛的韧性，但办公楼行业仍然是一个痛点。【原文：U.S. regional banks' commercial real estate loan books are proving broadly resilient despite worries sparked by a handful of soured loans, but the office sector continues to be a pain point, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regional-banks-weather-cre-storm-office-loans-continue-lag-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNFLSBPF65KHLFF2HJCELWN45E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺推出新款经济型电动车 Twingo，以促进销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷诺周四发布了新款电动小型车 Twingo，这家法国汽车制造商试图利用这个广受欢迎的老车型名称和不足 2 万欧元（约合 2.3 万美元）的售价来促进其电动汽车的销售。【原文：Renault unveiled its new electric Twingo small car on Thursday as the French automaker seeks to leverage a popular old model name and a price tag of under 20,000 euros ($23,000) to boost its electric vehicle sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-revives-twingo-with-new-affordable-electric-version-boost-sales-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6IHDTFUQBOADLO3ZOBLCF5LMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国公司与嘉吉、LDC 等贸易商签署 52 亿美元农产品交易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国供应链运营商和房地产开发商厦门建发周四表示，该公司已与嘉吉公司（Cargill）和路易达孚公司（Louis Dreyfus Company）等七家农业企业和贸易公司在上海签订了总额超过 52 亿美元的合同。【原文：Chinese supply chain operator and property developer Xiamen C&amp;D said on Thursday it had signed contracts totalling over $5.2 billion with seven agribusinesses and trading houses including Cargill and Louis Dreyfus Company in Shanghai.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-firm-signs-52-billion-agricultural-deals-with-traders-including-cargill-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QK355NMDFFKUPHP6X5HWVKOU4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:57:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比：缺乏通胀数据支持放慢脚步]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周四表示，政府停摆期间缺乏通胀方面的官方数据 "凸显 "了他对进一步降息的谨慎态度。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee on Thursday said the lack of official data on inflation during the government shutdown "accentuates" his caution about cutting interest rates further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-goolsbee-lack-inflation-data-argues-going-slow-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ZGSQVBHVFOILAFXXXNNUTRG3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:45:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易谈判代表希望与瑞士达成贸易协议，并称与墨西哥的谈判正在进行中]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周四表示，美国贸易官员本周会见了来自瑞士的代表，并正在与墨西哥、中美洲和西半球其他国家的贸易官员进行讨论。【原文：U.S. trade officials met with representatives from Switzerland this week and are having discussions with trade officials from Mexico, Central America and others in the Western Hemisphere, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/us-trade-negotiator-eyes-trade-deal-with-switzerland-says-talks-underway-with-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV5VIVAPZNILDMPNPJLFC23Y2M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:42:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CarMax 长期首席执行官比尔-纳什将离职，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[CarMax公司周四表示，其首席执行官比尔-纳什（Bill Nash）将于本月底卸任，此前这家二手车零售商预计第三季度利润疲软，因为该公司正在努力削减成本，更好地应对汽车需求的下降。【原文：CarMax's CEO Bill Nash is stepping down by end of the month, the preowned car retailer said on Thursday, after it forecast a weak third-quarter profit as it battles to cut costs and better navigate lower vehicle demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/carmaxs-longtime-ceo-bill-nash-depart-shares-drop-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGEI55W5OBLPJLGKDQFLNUOO5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球调查显示，半数以上对冲基金投资加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球对冲基金对加密货币市场的投资正在增加、
 据一份行业报告称，随着美国政府对数字资产的支持，全球对冲基金对加密货币市场的投资正在增加，目前已有超过一半的对冲基金投资于这一领域。
 行业报告
 周四发布的
 周四发布的一份行业报告显示。【原文：Global hedge funds' exposure to crypto markets is increasing, 
 and more than half are now invested in the sector, with the U.S. government's embrace of digital assets boosting interest, according to an 
 industry report 
 published 
 on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/more-than-half-hedge-funds-invested-crypto-global-survey-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3D574FUGBLE7LIM4I6LYQ7RZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:36:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将于周五晚些时候详细说明主要机场的航班削减计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周四正在努力敲定一项史无前例的计划的细节，该计划将削减美国40个高流量机场10%的航班，以解决空中交通管制员在联邦政府创纪录停摆期间的安全问题。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration on Thursday was working to hammer out details of an unprecedented plan to cut 10% of flights at 40 high-traffic U.S. airports to address safety concerns regarding air traffic controllers amid a record-setting federal government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-detail-flight-cut-plan-major-airports-later-friday-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q27OI7IFRBM2HKEAD6BLYGOONI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:18:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Papa John's 首席执行官表示，公司专注于执行战略，但对其他选择持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[Papa John's 首席执行官托德-佩内戈（Todd Penegor）周四表示，这家美国比萨连锁店正专注于执行其战略，以提升价值，但他也指出，如果有其他选择，该公司也会考虑。【原文：Papa John's CEO Todd Penegor on Thursday said the U.S. pizza chain is focusing on executing its strategy to drive value, but noted it would consider alternatives if they were available.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/papa-johns-focused-executing-its-strategy-open-alternatives-ceo-says-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYSERXDWIFO7DNKP56S54ONB2A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大到难以下咽？卢克石油帝国对贡渥来说不是简单的收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家和内部人士称，俄罗斯能源集团卢克石油公司的外国帝国是贡渥集团迄今为止最大的收购目标，但看上去远远超出了瑞士交易商的借贷能力。【原文：Russian energy group Lukoil's foreign empire is suitor Gunvor's biggest acquisition target to date but looks far beyond the Swiss trader's borrowing capacity, bankers and insiders say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/too-big-swallow-lukoil-empire-no-simple-acquisition-gunvor-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3XCQFEM4BNN7LNLDTRKLRCTT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软成立 "超级智能 "团队，以医疗诊断为起点]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软正在组建一个新的团队，希望从医疗诊断开始，在某些领域打造能力远超人类的人工智能。【原文：Microsoft is forming a new team that wants to build artificial intelligence that is vastly more capable than humans in certain domains, starting with medical diagnostics, the executive leading the effort told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-launches-superintelligence-team-targeting-medical-diagnosis-start-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLWWFHNQA5LUXIC72D34QKHWLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大型央行的宽松政策即将结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[大型经济体的央行已接近其降息周期的尾声，尽管有些央行，如美国联邦储备委员会和英格兰银行在今年早些时候较为谨慎，但仍有余地再宽松一些。【原文：Central banks in big economies are nearing the end of their rate-cutting cycles, though some, like the U.S. Federal Reserve and Bank of England - which were more cautious earlier in the year - have scope to ease a little more.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-cenbank-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TY42LP7Y7NPFVBTO5SDTVPPIZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[发电需求强劲，康明斯季度业绩超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卡车发动机制造商康明斯（Cummins）周四公布的第三季度业绩高于华尔街预期，主要原因是发电系统和配电业务需求强劲，股价盘前上涨超过 7%。【原文：U.S. truck engine maker Cummins on Thursday reported third-quarter results above Wall Street estimates, driven by strong demand for its power generation systems and distribution segments, sending its shares up more than 7% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cummins-beats-quarterly-estimates-strong-power-generation-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BVYHBZAJ5JLLBHZ7S62QT3ZIZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:54:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在价值 100 亿美元的肥胖症药物争夺战中，美塞拉权衡辉瑞和诺和诺德的竞标价]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦制药商诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）与美国竞争对手辉瑞公司（Pfizer）为争夺 Metsera 的肥胖症药物资产而展开了一场价值 100 亿美元的竞购战。【原文：A bidding war over U.S. biotech Metsera was coming to a head on Thursday, with Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk locked in a $10 billion battle with U.S. rival Pfizer to win Metsera's obesity drug assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/metsera-weighs-rival-bids-pfizer-novo-10-billion-obesity-drug-battle-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQJMF33MVFLNNJP4QWMAOJ7NJQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室：如果最高法院驳回特朗普的关税要求，财政部将解决退款问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高贸易官员周四表示，如果美国最高法院裁定唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税无效，一些原告在某些情况下可以获得退款，但财政部必须制定付款时间表。【原文：Some plaintiffs could get a refund in certain situations if the U.S. Supreme Court rules against President Donald Trump's tariffs, but the Treasury would have to figure out any payment schedules, the nation's top trade official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ustr-treasury-would-sort-out-any-refunds-if-top-court-nixes-trumps-tariffs-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQH2EK4ZXNNZ3NLC5ZOZTOCMRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行的贝利如果市场对回报定价过高，人工智能将面临泡沫风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）周四表示，尽管人工智能技术可能会大幅提高生产率，但市场可能会出现人工智能引发的泡沫。【原文：Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey said on Thursday there could be an artificial intelligence-induced bubble in markets, notwithstanding the large productivity boost the technology would likely deliver.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/boes-bailey-risk-ai-bubble-if-markets-over-price-returns-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KILS7AJGJJM6LEVEUUGLS4YHN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥联储估计美国 10 月失业率回升至 4.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[据芝加哥联储周四公布的一项估计，由于失业工人的招聘率放缓，裁员和其他离职率上升，美国10月份的失业率可能升至四年来的最高点。【原文：The U.S. jobless rate likely edged up in October to the highest in four years as the hiring rate for unemployed workers slowed and the rate of layoffs and other job separations increased, according to an estimate by the Chicago Fed released Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-unemployment-rate-rounds-up-44-october-chicago-fed-estimates-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46ORHUP4INMFBBR3Z5FCSIYRNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受益于自动化需求，罗克韦尔第四季度利润和营收超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受成本削减和自动化需求持续增长的影响，罗克韦尔自动化公司周四公布的第四季度利润和收入均超过预期，股价在盘前交易中上涨约 5%。【原文：Rockwell Automation topped fourth-quarter estimates for profit and revenue on Thursday, helped by cost cuts and sustained demand for automation, sending its shares up about 5% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/rockwell-tops-fourth-quarter-profit-revenue-estimates-automation-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R55PWSEO7JNBXBXM3DIWB7AHFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:29:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Datadog 预测人工智能驱动的安全需求将带来强劲的第四季度收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[Datadog 周四预测第四季度盈利将高于华尔街预期，押注于采用人工智能技术的企业对其云安全产品的强劲需求。【原文：Datadog forecast fourth-quarter earnings above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, betting on strong demand for its cloud-security products from businesses adopting artificial intelligence technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/datadog-forecasts-strong-fourth-quarter-earnings-ai-driven-security-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSMGZAOGNZKOVD6TVENGCJQB4A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:26:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton 因座椅安全风险召回约 83.3 万辆自行车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费品安全委员会周四表示，Peloton Interactive公司将召回约83.3万辆PL02型Original Bike+自行车，因为这种自行车的座管组件在使用过程中可能会断裂，有摔倒和受伤的危险。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission said on Thursday Peloton Interactive is recalling about 833,000 units of its Original Bike+ Model PL02 as the bike's seat post assembly could break during use, posing a risk of falls and injuries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/peloton-recalls-about-833000-bikes-over-seat-safety-risk-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFBPPFWVX5JAHNOGWPPAWBXR4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州寻求在泰诺诉讼中阻止 Kenvue 分红]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州总检察长肯-帕克斯顿（Ken Paxton）周四要求州法官阻止 Kenvue 在本月支付近 4 亿美元的股东分红，因为他起诉这家制药商涉嫌隐瞒孕妇使用泰诺对儿童造成的风险。【原文：Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton on Thursday asked a state judge to block Kenvue from paying a nearly $400 million shareholder dividend this month, after suing the drugmaker for allegedly concealing risks to children from the use of Tylenol by pregnant women.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/texas-seeks-block-kenvue-dividend-amid-tylenol-lawsuit-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I37QOAZM2VMNTCRT7Q34IBPCPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉尔夫-劳伦（Ralph Lauren）上调年度收入预期，原因是需求恢复强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉尔夫-劳伦（Ralph Lauren）周四上调了年度收入预期，押注在经济不确定性上升的情况下，对其高价位 Polo 衬衫和棉质电缆针织毛衣的需求将出现恢复性增长。【原文：Ralph Lauren raised its annual revenue forecast on Thursday, betting on resilient demand for its high-priced Polo shirts and cotton cable knit sweaters amid rising economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ralph-lauren-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-resilient-demand-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWNC5V25HVI5FMGFUOPYW6J7XE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺维信凭借疫苗交易的优势上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺维信公司（Novavax）周四今年第三次上调了年度营收预期，主要得益于与日本武田制药公司（Takeda Pharmaceuticals）等达成的疫苗供应和许可协议所带来的里程碑付款。【原文：Novavax raised its annual revenue forecast for the third time this year on Thursday, banking on milestone payments from vaccine supply and licensing deals such as with Japan's Takeda Pharmaceuticals .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novavax-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-milestone-payment-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7K6FC3ARVMFPOTRWUXJ35NVYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Helios Towers 第三季度业绩超预期，推出 4 亿美元股东回报计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[电信塔运营商 Helios Towers 周四公布了强于预期的第三季度业绩，并启动了 7500 万美元的股票回购计划，作为新五年计划的一部分，该计划的目标是为投资者带来超过 4 亿美元的回报。【原文：Telecom towers operator Helios Towers on Thursday reported stronger-than-expected third‑quarter results and launched a $75 million share buyback as part of a new five‑year plan targeting more than $400 million in returns to investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/helios-towers-beats-q3-forecast-unveils-400-million-shareholder-returns-plan-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NDMRPTX5ZIMPMQ6D2JJTP4UDY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EPAM 上调 2025 年预测，因 IT 服务支出强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[EPAM Systems今年第三次上调了年度盈利预期，原因是企业为实现人工智能系统的现代化投入了更多资金，这使得这家IT咨询公司的股价在周四的盘前交易中上涨了4%。【原文：EPAM Systems raised its annual earnings forecast for the third time this year as businesses spend more to modernize their systems for artificial intelligence, sending shares of the IT consultancy firm 4% higher in premarket trading on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/epam-raises-2025-forecasts-strong-it-services-spending-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQW3WIOO6RKQREPA2NLGIZ2ORU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各国在世贸组织寻求延长电子商务关税暂停期]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界贸易组织周四的一份文件显示，一些国家正在寻求延长世界贸易组织关于不对数字传输征收关税的协议。【原文：A group of states is seeking to extend a World Trade Organization agreement to refrain from placing customs duties on digital transmissions, a World Trade Organization document showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/states-seek-extension-e-commerce-tariff-moratorium-wto-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECFB6GBM6NJMRJV2S637PEV5J4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ESPN 和 PENN Entertainment 将提前结束美国体育博彩合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国彭氏娱乐公司（PENN Entertainment）和沃尔特-迪斯尼公司（Walt Disney）旗下的 ESPN 周四表示，双方已同意终止其在美国的独家在线体育博彩合作关系，自 12 月 1 日起生效。【原文：PENN Entertainment and Walt Disney's ESPN have agreed to end their exclusive U.S. online sports betting partnership, effective December 1, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/espn-penn-entertainment-end-us-sports-betting-partnership-early-2025-11-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEXITZJZXFL2ZD3BIDDHLA6NOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:33:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>