<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:07:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:07:11 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[韩国将就芯片和生物制药关税问题回应美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部周一表示，政府将就半导体关税问题积极与美国沟通，并努力将生物制药关税的影响降至最低。【原文：South Korea's finance ministry said on Monday the government would actively communicate with the U.S. over semiconductor tariffs and make an effort to minimise the impact of biopharmaceutical tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/south-korea-respond-us-over-tariffs-chips-biopharmaceuticals-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNAVVLNWRNKVTKJ77JTE77WFJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对中美削减关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，中美两国表示同意暂停加征关税 90 天，对等关税将大幅下降，这给投资者带来了一些信心，认为可能已经避免了一场全面的贸易战，随后股市和美元大涨。【原文：Stocks and the dollar surged on Monday after the United States and China said they had agreed on a 90-day pause on tariffs and reciprocal duties would drop sharply, giving investors some confidence that a full-scale trade war may have been averted.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/view-us-china-agree-cut-tariffs-90-day-pause-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPVU4DJM4FOLRNBJTI3DFPUJOM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:33:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球市场动荡不定，日本 4 月外国股票购买量创 20 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[4 月份，日本投资者大幅增加了海外股票购买量，在美国关税引发的全球市场波动中，他们在重新平衡投资组合时不再购买债券，而是利用国际股票打折的机会。【原文：Japanese investors sharply ramped up their overseas equity purchases in April, shifting away from bonds as they rebalanced portfolios amid global market volatility triggered by U.S. tariffs, and capitalizing on discounted international shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japanese-foreign-equity-purchases-april-hit-20-year-high-global-market-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VDSTAJFZVMW3PAH7QVFAPYW2A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[官员称中美达成削减关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国周一表示，两国已就削减互惠关税达成协议，华盛顿和中国政府正努力结束这场扰乱全球经济、令金融市场惶恐不安的贸易战。【原文：The United States and China said on Monday they have agreed a deal to slash reciprocal tariffs as Washington and Beijing seek to end a trade war that has disrupted the global economy and set financial markets on edge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-reach-deal-slash-tariffs-officials-say-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPIM7G7VSNIFJE63VS3XKBCLQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果援助削减导致订单枯竭，诺华仍将继续生产疟疾药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士制药商诺华公司全球卫生总裁在接受路透社采访时表示，即使在全球卫生资金紧缩的情况下无法正常获得订单，该公司也将继续生产治疗疟疾和麻风病的药物。【原文：Swiss drugmaker Novartis will keep making medicines for malaria and leprosy, even if it does not get orders as normal amid the global health funding crunch, its president of global health told Reuters in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-keep-making-malaria-drugs-if-orders-dry-up-amid-aid-cuts-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZX5HKVWSVOKPCDUXQALVCRUKI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 South32 公司任命英美资源集团高管 Matthew Daley 于 2026 年出任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 South32 公司周一任命马修-戴利（Matthew Daley）在长期任职的首席执行官格雷厄姆-科尔（Graham Kerr）于 2026 年卸任后领导这家多元化矿业公司，戴利将在明年初暂时担任副首席执行官。【原文：Australia's South32 on Monday named Matthew Daley to lead the diversified miner when long-serving CEO Graham Kerr steps down in 2026, with Daley in the interim joining as deputy chief executive officer early next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australias-south32-names-anglo-american-executive-matthew-daley-become-ceo-2026-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUUAU7INV5LMNHL7777BOQSJLI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:13:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Confidencial 报道，西班牙电信聘请花旗出售智利业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据新闻网站 El Confidencial 周一援引未具名市场消息人士的话报道，西班牙电信公司 Telefonica 已聘请花旗银行担任顾问，以出售其智利业务。【原文：Spanish telecoms company Telefonica has hired Citi as an adviser to sell its Chilean business, news website El Confidencial reported on Monday, citing unidentified market sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/telefonica-hires-citi-sell-chilean-business-el-confidencial-reports-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMTNJXOJ4JKOHIR5YQ2KEXH754</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国收购委员会要求高通公司在 5 月 27 日前竞购 Alphawave]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国半导体公司 Alphawave IP Group 周一表示，英国收购委员会已将美国芯片制造商高通公司的收购要约截止日期延长至 5 月 27 日。【原文：British semiconductor company Alphawave IP Group on Monday said the UK takeover panel had extended the deadline for a takeover offer by U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm to May 27.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/uk-takeover-panel-gives-qualcomm-till-may-27-make-bid-alphawave-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRYKA4DBTBMGVCM4XQQZA22VPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利联合信贷银行上调利润展望，对交易保持谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利第二大银行意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）在公布季度利润意外增长后，周一上调了 2025 年业绩展望，但仍坚决表示不会不惜一切代价进行交易。【原文：Italy's second-biggest bank UniCredit lifted its 2025 outlook on Monday after posting a surprise increase in quarterly profit but remained resolute that it would not do deals at any cost.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-ups-profit-outlook-after-strong-quarter-says-be-selective-deals-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TS45KZZ6I5LSXA2DHJPDYIBE44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:25:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[酩悦轩尼诗的困境考验着亚历山大-阿尔诺的能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯纳德-阿诺特（Bernard Arnault）的儿子亚历山大（Alexandre）接到了一项艰巨的任务：在关税战中重振 LVMH 集团业绩最差的部门--著名的酩悦轩尼诗（Moet Hennessy）酒水业务。【原文：Bernard Arnault's son Alexandre has been handed a daunting task: reviving LVMH's worst-performing unit, the famed Moet Hennessy drinks business, in the midst of a tariff war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/moet-hennessy-woes-test-alexandre-arnaults-credentials-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDIC6ZKJOVK35DENBCCQKGCWVE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:05:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达能收购美国植物性有机配方奶粉制造商凯特农场]]></title><description><![CDATA[达能周一表示，已同意收购美国植物性有机饮料制造商凯特农场（Kate Farms）的大部分股份，该公司将纳入法国食品巨头的专业营养产品组合。【原文：Danone said on Monday it has agreed to buy a majority stake in Kate Farms, a U.S. maker of plant-based organic drinks that will fit into the French food giant's specialized nutrition portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/danone-acquires-us-plant-based-organic-formula-maker-kate-farms-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRCAUEKCT5L5JGJQS3H47LE5NQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在美国贸易战谈判之际接待拉美和加勒比国家]]></title><description><![CDATA[在北京和华盛顿试图化解贸易战之际，中国将于本周主办一次包括其主要拉美贸易伙伴在内的峰会，以努力提升在该地区的影响力和伙伴关系。【原文：China will host a summit that includes its key Latin American trade partners this week in an effort to advance influence and partnerships in the region, as Beijing and Washington try to defuse their trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-hosts-latin-american-caribbean-nations-amid-us-trade-war-talks-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOG7BECNFVNSJAXES656MWH6RU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 04:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 细节决定成败]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AW3FDCVP5PHTINQQDAB3JLHVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 04:34:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金重新进入中国股市，摩根士丹利称因对贸易谈判持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）的数据显示，由于中美贸易谈判有望取得进展，对冲基金，尤其是美国的对冲基金，上周增加了对中国股市的看涨押注。【原文：Hedge funds, especially U.S.-based ones, added bullish bets on Chinese stocks last week on hopes of progress in U.S.-China trade talks, according to Morgan Stanley.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-re-enter-chinese-equities-trade-talk-optimism-morgan-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNXBRM5EJFOWVG2IAKIYQSB4UM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 04:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银集团第四季度小幅亏损，愿景基金受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本科技投资者软银集团（SoftBank Group）周二预计将出现 269 亿日元（1.844 亿美元）的季度净亏损，原因是早期科技初创企业不受青睐，且主要投资组合公司的亏损扩大。【原文：Japanese technology investor SoftBank Group is expected to book a quarterly net loss of 26.9 billion yen ($184.4 million) on Tuesday as early-stage tech startups fell out of favour and losses widened at major portfolio firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-group-seen-booking-modest-fourth-quarter-loss-vision-fund-suffers-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UHBTUJJEJJ4DO5BLBLQAY4YEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 04:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士和油轮追踪者称，贸易商将运往中国的委内瑞拉石油改名为巴西石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两家油轮跟踪公司、公司文件和四家贸易商称，在过去一年中，贸易商已将运往中国的超过 10 亿美元委内瑞拉石油改装成巴西原油，帮助买家降低物流成本，规避美国制裁。【原文：Traders have rebranded more than $1 billion of Venezuelan oil shipments to China as Brazilian crude over the past year, according to two tanker tracking firms, company documents and four traders, helping buyers to cut logistics costs and circumvent U.S. sanctions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/traders-rebrand-venezuelan-oil-china-brazilian-sources-tanker-trackers-say-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEB7LEHNSFLK7LFSJPK5B442BQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 04:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待中美贸易谈判细节，股市和美元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周日，美国和中国以积极的姿态结束了高风险的贸易谈判，美国官员吹嘘双方就减少美国贸易逆差达成了 "协议"，而中国官员则表示双方已达成 "重要共识"。【原文：The United States and China ended high-stakes trade talks on a positive note on Sunday, with U.S. officials touting a "deal" to reduce the U.S. trade deficit while Chinese officials said the sides had reached "important consensus."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/stocks-dollar-up-investors-wait-details-sino-us-trade-talks-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EIH5RQFNCFLRBL5UMVNBBLDOMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 03:49:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[作为美国贸易谈判的一部分，日本石场发出增加玉米进口的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂周一表示，增加从美国进口玉米将是与华盛顿进行贸易谈判的选项之一。【原文：Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba on Monday signalled that increasing corn imports from the U.S. would be among options in trade negotiations with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/japans-ishiba-signals-increasing-corn-imports-part-us-trade-talks-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62ADVSGBEBNZ7AX6MF6PLMNKCM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 02:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[这家美国在华工厂为沃尔玛生产玩具。关税让它苟延残喘]]></title><description><![CDATA[4 月 9 日，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对中国进口商品征收 145% 关税的政策生效当天，邮件就开始纷至沓来。客户纷纷取消了亨达公司在中国广东省工厂的玩具订单。【原文：The emails started pouring in on April 9, the day President Donald Trump’s 145% tariff on Chinese imports took effect. Clients were canceling orders for toys from Huntar Company Inc.’s factory in Guangdong Province, China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/this-us-owned-factory-china-made-toys-walmart-tariffs-put-it-life-support-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UC7W5323M5I45HFBWPKXOAGYG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 01:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易谈判舒缓市场紧张情绪，油价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，中美贸易谈判双方均在周末宣布了谈判进展，这提升了市场情绪，认为全球最大的两个原油消费国可能正朝着解决贸易争端的方向迈进。【原文：Oil prices rose on Monday after both sides in U.S.-China trade talks over the weekend touted their progress, which lifted market sentiment that the world's two largest crude users may be moving toward a resolution of their trade dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-rise-us-china-trade-talks-soothe-market-jitters-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O56MSBRQONIRTP4FFDODFDBHRM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 01:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易前景乐观，美元兑日元上涨；奇异果汇率攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元在周一的亚洲早盘交易中攀升，此前美国和中国之间的周末会谈缓解了人们对世界两大经济体之间爆发贸易战的担忧，同时全球热点似乎降温。【原文：The dollar climbed in early Asian trade on Monday after weekend talks between the United States and China eased concerns of a trade war between the world's two biggest economies while global hot spots appeared to cool.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dollar-gains-versus-yen-us-china-trade-optimism-kiwi-climbs-2025-05-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NO4OU4OEDJM3RMF7HAKMQSZJ5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易谈判引发股市和美元上涨，但仍需详细说明]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，华尔街股票期货跳涨，美元兑避险货币走强，因为中美贸易谈判取得进展的迹象提振了避免全球经济衰退的希望，尽管任何协议的细节仍有待公布。【原文：Wall Street stock futures jumped and the dollar firmed against safe haven peers on Monday as signs of progress in U.S.-China trade talks boosted hopes a global recession might be avoided, though details of any deal were still to come.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75UAKRQZWZP4DGA4POF7BZWENM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 23:20:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 CATL 将在香港上市，最多融资 40 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一提交的招股说明书，中国电池巨头 CATL 计划在香港上市，融资 310.1 亿港元（39.9 亿美元）。【原文：Chinese battery giant CATL is aiming to raise HK$31.01 billion ($3.99 billion) in its Hong Kong listing, according to its prospectus filed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-catl-raise-up-4-billion-hong-kong-listing-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VFF6ZI6CZOB5HYSMIHCC4ZW64</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:22:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来的 Zepbound 在减肥试验中优于诺和诺德的 Wegovy]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来（Eli Lilly）周日援引一项正面交锋试验的数据表示，其药物 Zepbound 在减少腰围等五个减肥目标方面优于诺和诺德的 Wegovy。【原文：Eli Lilly said on Sunday its drug Zepbound was superior to Novo Nordisk's Wegovy across five weight-loss targets such as reducing waist circumference, citing data from a head-to-head trial.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eli-lillys-zepbound-outperforms-novo-nordisks-wegovy-weight-loss-trial-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6O6BD5SL2RI7JGQSSYGXNW5IGQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:06:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 投资者对中美贸易谈判取得进展的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）和贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周日表示，他们与中国达成了削减美国贸易逆差的协议，并称与中国官员的高风险会谈取得了 "实质性进展"，但在日内瓦结束为期两天的谈判时没有提供任何细节。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Sunday they reached a deal with China to cut the U.S. trade deficit, describing "substantial progress" in high-stakes talks with Chinese officials but offering no details as two days of negotiations concluded in Geneva.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/view-investor-reaction-us-china-progress-trade-talks-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQWKZSEPVNLPBHYJXNTAVK7AYM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 19:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国总统贝森特称赞与中国的贸易谈判取得 "实质性进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周日表示，他的团队与中国副总理何立峰的团队在日内瓦就化解世界两大经济体之间的贸易战举行的会谈取得了 "实质性进展"。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Sunday that there had been "substantial progress" in talks between his team and that of Chinese Vice Premier He Lifeng in Geneva on defusing a trade war between the world's two largest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-bessent-hails-substantial-progress-trade-talks-with-china-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MORKHTA7IFOF3LRS2JZPNRAEVI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 16:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长卢特尼克称中美谈判旨在缓和贸易紧张局势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周日表示，目前正在日内瓦举行的与中国的双边会谈旨在 "缓和 "两个超级大国之间的紧张局势，他预测未来几个月将达成多项贸易协议，但没有点名具体国家。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick on Sunday said bilateral talks with China now underway in Geneva are intended to "de-escalate" tensions between the two superpowers, as he predicted multiple trade deals over the next few months without naming specific countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-says-china-talks-aimed-lowering-trade-tensions-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7EDOZA36NOM7IADKANFINDI6E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：OpenAI 与微软谈判，以获得新资金并在未来上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周日报道，OpenAI 和微软正在重写双方价值数十亿美元的合作条款，这是一场高风险谈判，目的是让这家 ChatGPT 制造商能够在未来进行首次公开募股，同时保护这家软件巨头对尖端人工智能模型的使用权。【原文：OpenAI and Microsoft are rewriting the terms of their multibillion-dollar partnership in a high-stakes negotiation designed to allow the ChatGPT maker to launch a future IPO, while protecting the software giant's access to cutting-edge AI models, the Financial Times reported on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-negotiates-with-microsoft-unlock-new-funding-future-ipo-ft-reports-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53I7IOJSB5KUBHT6UWPF7C7F5A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 12:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[化解贸易争端的中美会谈在日内瓦重启]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，中美两国高级官员周日在日内瓦再次会晤，重启周末会谈，旨在为有可能严重损害全球经济的贸易战降温。【原文：Senior U.S. and Chinese officials met again on Sunday in Geneva, two sources familiar with the situation told Reuters, to resume weekend talks aimed at cooling the trade war that threatens to seriously damage the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-talks-defuse-trade-row-resume-geneva-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVVBAWO2LRMKVI4WXNHOPXPUHA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 09:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂再次呼吁取消与美国的所有关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂周日重申，他将致力于在与美国的贸易谈判中取消所有关税。【原文：Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba reiterated on Sunday that he will aim for the elimination of all tariffs in trade negotiations with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japan-pm-ishiba-reiterates-call-eliminate-all-tariffs-with-us-2025-05-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5AAWYTEMKJK5ND2ZOMSQV463QQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>