<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:05:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:05:34 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦航空局将在 9 月前部署新的飞行员信息数据库系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周一表示，在一系列故障引发安全担忧之后，该局计划在 9 月份之前部署一个新的飞行员信息数据库。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said Monday it plans to deploy a new pilot messaging database by September after a series of outages have raised safety concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/faa-deploy-new-pilot-messaging-database-system-by-september-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKUSWFNVGJN2NISWLDWQXT3IZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 19:07:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shopify 必须在美国面对数据隐私诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周一恢复了针对 Shopify 提出的数据隐私集体诉讼，这一决定可能使美国法院更容易对基于互联网的平台行使管辖权。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Monday revived a proposed data privacy class action against Shopify , in a decision that could make it easier for American courts to assert jurisdiction over internet-based platforms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/shopify-must-face-data-privacy-lawsuit-us-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7C3676KIAZNLJI6E37GF3C27OE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:22:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普抨击鲍威尔，美股延续跌势，标普 500 指数下跌 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普加倍攻击美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔，加剧了市场对美联储自主权的担忧，华尔街主要股指均跌至一周多来的低点。【原文：Wall Street's main indexes each slid to more than one-week lows on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump doubled down on attacks against Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, amplifying concerns about the central bank's autonomy and rattling markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-stocks-extend-slide-trump-harangues-powell-sp-500-down-3-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JSVZ23L6BP7RPJYOCW3BUJB4U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦贸易委员会指控优步误导用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周一起诉优步科技公司（Uber Technologies），指控该公司在一些用户不知情的情况下注册了 Uber One 用户，并对该服务进行了欺骗性宣传。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Monday sued Uber Technologies , accusing it of signing up some Uber One subscribers without their knowledge and making deceptive claims about the service.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/us-ftc-sues-uber-accusing-it-deceptive-practices-court-filing-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLKVKAXXJNKO5HMIGLDCBCLX6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:18:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金在财报发布前将 "Mag Seven "下调至两年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份摩根士丹利给客户的说明显示，全球对冲基金上周抛售了所谓的 "华丽七巨头 "股票，使其在这些股票盈利前的持仓量降至两年来的最低点。【原文：Global hedge funds last week dumped the so-called Magnificent Seven megacap stocks, bringing their exposure to the group to a two-year low just ahead of their earnings, according to a Morgan Stanley note to clients seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-cut-mag-seven-two-year-low-ahead-earnings-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDX74QEVG5IIRA5EQ4YOR2U4JM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储任命 Anna Nordstrom 为市场部主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周一表示，已任命 Anna Nordstrom 为市场部主管，立即生效。【原文：The Federal Reserve Bank of New York said on Monday that it has appointed Anna Nordstrom as the head of the markets group, effective immediately.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ny-fed-appoints-anna-nordstrom-markets-group-chief-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MCFDCIP5RPCZIU3N54IXG3KMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:46:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道：特朗普将会见沃尔玛、家得宝等零售商，讨论关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将与沃尔玛、家得宝、劳氏和塔吉特等大型零售商会面，讨论全面关税对其业务的影响。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is set to meet with major retailers, including Walmart , Home Depot , Lowe’s and Target , to discuss the impact of sweeping tariffs on their businesses, Bloomberg News reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trump-meet-retailers-including-walmart-home-depot-discuss-tariffs-impact-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSNSTR74Z5KKXIICSATGN6QX5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着许可证到期的临近，壳牌将完成委内瑞拉天然气田的勘测工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[与筹备工作关系密切的消息人士称，石油和天然气集团壳牌计划在美国设定的 5 月最后期限之前完成委内瑞拉海上龙气田的海洋勘测，该期限是关闭该国所有与能源项目有关的许可证。【原文：Oil and gas group Shell plans to complete a marine survey at Venezuela's offshore Dragon gas field before a U.S.-set May deadline to wind down all licenses related to energy projects in the country, sources close to the preparations said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/shell-complete-survey-venezuela-gas-field-license-wind-down-approaches-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCYYSSXF3ZPVLEJ54YBY3GDTAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空公司客机在奥兰多引擎起火，被迫撤离]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）称，达美航空公司一架载有近 300 名乘客的飞机周一在佛罗里达州奥兰多国际机场从登机口推回时引擎起火，迫使乘客使用滑梯撤离。【原文：A Delta Air Lines plane carrying nearly 300 passengers suffered an engine fire after pushing back from the gate at Orlando International Airport in Florida on Monday, forcing the passengers to evacuate using slides, the Federal Aviation Administration said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/delta-plane-suffers-engine-fire-orlando-forcing-evacuation-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DXNDV7LAHRMUTJWLJCSEJ6TX5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:19:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部称，沃尔格林公司以 3 亿美元的价格就填写无效阿片类药物处方的指控达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周一表示，沃尔格林博姿联盟（Walgreens Boots Alliance）及其子公司已同意支付 3 亿美元，以了结美国对该连锁药店非法开具数百万张阿片类药物和其他管制药物无效处方的指控。【原文：Walgreens Boots Alliance and its subsidiaries have agreed to pay $300 million to settle U.S. allegations that the pharmacy chain illegally filled millions of invalid prescriptions for opioids and other controlled substances, the U.S. Justice Department said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/walgreens-settles-allegations-filling-invalid-opioid-prescriptions-300-million-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AODQPLZZXBLQTBF4MRO47QS5NM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 出现故障，影响全球数千名用户，现已恢复运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Downdetector.com 网站报道，社交媒体平台 Reddit 在全球数千名用户于周一遭遇故障后已恢复正常。【原文：Social media platform Reddit was restored after thousands of users worldwide experienced outages on Monday, according to Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/reddit-down-thousands-users-worldwide-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZP5ILWRNNKYZPCL6F4IEP33OI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储发现美国人降低了对新工作的工资预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行的一项调查显示，3 月份美国人对劳动力市场的看法有所恶化，因为受访者大幅削减了他们认为能让他们接受新工作的薪资水平。【原文：Americans' view on labor markets soured in March as respondents to a Federal Reserve Bank of New York survey sharply trimmed back the payrate they said would get them to take a new job.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ny-fed-finds-americans-trimming-back-wage-expectations-new-jobs-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZSMLSEV4BJWJL5LFTY65QQUJM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 首席执行官必须面对 Bed Bath & Beyond 的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 的亿万富翁首席执行官 Ryan Cohen 必须面对曾被称为 Bed Bath & Beyond 的公司提起的诉讼，以收回在这家家居用品零售商破产前交易其股票所获得的 4720 万美元利润。【原文：Ryan Cohen, the billionaire chief executive of GameStop , must face a lawsuit by the company once known as Bed Bath & Beyond to recoup $47.2 million of profit from trading its stock before the home goods retailer went bankrupt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/gamestop-ceo-must-face-bed-bath-beyond-lawsuit-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6EVVTPFRARIF5HQAYCUVM6O25Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:49:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月领先指标在关税影响下大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[衡量美国未来经济活动的一项指标在 3 月份大幅下降，可能预示着今年的经济增长将在关税影响下变得乏力。【原文：A gauge of future U.S. economic activity fell sharply in March, potentially flagging tepid growth this year amid tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-leading-indicator-declines-sharply-march-amid-tariffs-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEQTOFIVIZNNTEQVNZPN2Z44PQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:26:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普警告称，除非美联储降息，否则经济将放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，除非立即降息，否则美国经济可能会放缓，并再次批评美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔行动迟缓。【原文：The U.S. economy can slow down unless interest rates are lowered immediately, President Donald Trump said on Monday, repeating his criticism of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell as being slow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-warns-economic-slowdown-unless-fed-cuts-rates-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGVQFUBBCZKVJGN4LCRY5UBRO4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回 CSX 恢复对诺福克南方公司反垄断诉讼的请求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一拒绝审理货运铁路巨头 CSX 提起的反垄断诉讼，该诉讼指控竞争对手诺福克南方公司（Norfolk Southern）非法限制其进入弗吉尼亚州东海岸的一个重要码头，导致 CSX 损失了数亿美元的利润。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Monday to hear freight rail giant CSX's bid to revive its antitrust lawsuit accusing rival Norfolk Southern of illegally restricting access to a key East Coast terminal in Virginia, costing CSX hundreds of millions of dollars in lost profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-rebuffs-csx-bid-revive-antitrust-suit-against-norfolk-southern-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKUMTIOTX5LEDOMJFSRV7A6VDI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chipotle 计划进军墨西哥市场，首家分店将于 2026 年开业]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chipotle Mexican Grill 公司周一表示，它将在墨西哥开设一家分店，并将于明年初开业，从而向国际市场扩张，首次为该地区的人们带来墨西哥卷饼和卷饼。【原文：Chipotle Mexican Grill is expanding internationally with a location in Mexico that is set to open early next year, it said on Monday, bringing its tacos and burritos to the people in the region for the first time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chipotle-plans-mexican-foray-with-first-outlet-2026-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYCN33IVFZI7BDMTH2LWL34HMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:38:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙宣布美国海湾巴利莫尔项目首次出油]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙（Chevron）石油公司周一表示，该公司在美国墨西哥湾的一个项目已开始生产石油和天然气，这使该公司向今年将该海盆的产量提高 50%的目标又迈进了一步。【原文：Chevron has started oil and gas production from a project in the U.S. Gulf of Mexico, the oil major said on Monday, bringing the company a step closer toward its goal of growing production from the ocean basin by 50% this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-announces-first-oil-ballymore-project-us-gulf-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLHY4QS5JVLEZGTW6XZM4BONQI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计俄罗斯央行将把关键利率维持在 21%：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[参与路透社民意调查的 25 位分析师周一均预测，俄罗斯央行将在 4 月 25 日的董事会上将基准利率维持在 21% 不变，因为全球经济动荡加剧了人们对俄罗斯经济状况的担忧。【原文：The Russian central bank will keep its benchmark rate on hold at 21% at a board meeting on April 25, all 25 analysts who took part in a Reuters poll predicted on Monday, as global economic turbulence adds to concerns about the state of the Russian economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russian-central-bank-expected-keep-key-rate-hold-21-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEXLZ3HRWFNUNE4EB2OPFIISUE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:06:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[因关税引发的通胀担忧，美国债券基金遭遇第五周资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至4月16日的一周里，美国债券基金面临着沉重的抛售压力，这凸显了人们对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税措施可能会加剧通胀并使经济陷入衰退的担忧。【原文：U.S. bond funds came under heavy selling pressure in the week to April 16, highlighting concerns that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariff measures could fuel inflation and push the economy into a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bond-funds-suffer-fifth-weekly-outflow-tariff-driven-inflation-fears-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWBZPITG2VMZ3OG56XUF4KFJPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国从美国私募股权投资中撤退]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周一报道，在全球最大的两个经济体之间贸易战不断升级的背景下，中国的国家支持基金正在撤出对总部设在美国的私人资本公司旗下基金的投资。【原文：China's state-backed funds are pulling back from investing in the funds of U.S.-headquartered private capital firms amid an escalating trade war between the world's two biggest economies, the Financial Times reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-retreats-us-private-equity-investments-ft-reports-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXZB2OR23NMXZK3MNWZATXI7DY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者涌入欧洲股票基金，因关税问题逃离美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月16日的一周里，欧洲股票基金吸引了大量资金流入，而美国基金则面临大量资金流出，原因是投资者对美国贸易关税的担忧以及对美国经济实力的担忧不断加剧，从而继续转移资金。【原文：European equity funds drew massive inflows in the week ended April 16, while U.S. funds faced hefty outflows, as investors continued to shift capital on concerns over U.S. trade tariffs and mounting worries over the strength of the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2XJQ6UH6NKOPOHEWIKWLWKKVQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:49:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟表示将不分首席执行官和所在地执行数字规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）告诉 Politico，无论 X、Meta、苹果和 Tiktok 等公司的负责人是谁，也无论这些公司的总部设在哪里，欧盟都决心执行其完整的数字规则。【原文：The European Union is determined to enforce its full digital rule book no matter who is in charge of companies such as X, Meta, Apple and Tiktok or where they are based, Commission President Ursula von der Leyen told Politico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/eu-says-it-will-enforce-digital-rules-irrespective-ceo-location-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Q6YLCVVXVJPFKO5NJ4JTJ5ZHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度竞争监管机构批准谷歌在安卓电视案中的和解计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度竞争监管机构周一表示，已批准谷歌就安卓电视案提出的和解方案。【原文：India's competition regulator said on Monday that it had approved Google's settlement proposal in Android TV case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/indias-competition-regulator-clears-googles-settlement-plan-android-tv-case-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6WAT23AQBPHNOHXPR32GJH6YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易战升温，多伦多证券交易所期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大主要股指期货周一下滑，原因是中国警告说，将对以牺牲美国利益为代价与美国达成交易的国家采取 "反制措施"，这加剧了投资者对贸易战经济影响的担忧。【原文：Futures for Canada's main stock index slipped on Monday as China's warning of "countermeasures" against countries striking deals with the U.S. at its expense increased investor worries about the economic fallout from the trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsx-futures-fall-us-china-trade-war-heats-up-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLBDYDK4I5II3GOK6L5BEJXVMU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:24:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道LG、三星就电子垃圾定价政策起诉印度政府]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，韩国的 LG 和三星公司已经起诉印度政府，要求撤销一项增加对电子垃圾回收商赔偿的政策，并加入其他大公司的行列，以商业影响为由对印度的环境规则提出质疑。【原文：South Korea's LG and Samsung have sued India's government to quash a policy which increases payouts to electronic-waste recyclers, court filings show, joining other major companies in contesting the country's environmental rules citing business impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/lg-samsung-sue-indian-government-over-electronic-waste-pricing-policy-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3CODBEBWE5PQ5FVYRDKDAWDGTI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩托罗拉解决方案公司推出人工智能工具和新设备，以缩短应急响应时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩托罗拉解决方案公司周一推出了一款名为 SVX 的设备，它集远程扬声器麦克风、车载摄像头和名为 Assist 的人工智能助手于一身，可帮助急救人员寻求节省时间和应对紧急情况的方法。【原文：Motorola Solutions on Monday launched the SVX, a device that combines a remote speaker microphone, body camera and AI assistant named Assist, to help first responders seeking ways to save time and react to emergencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/motorola-solutions-launches-ai-tool-new-device-cut-emergency-response-time-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZA6J4XUREFKBZDPNJFHSBNP43A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:06:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者涌向安全的美国短期政府债券基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国短期政府债券基金本月获得了大量资金流入，尽管其他大多数资产类别的基金在市场受到美国关税和经济衰退风险担忧打击时遭遇了大量抛售。【原文：U.S. short-term government bond funds have received large inflows this month even as most other funds across asset classes suffered heavy selling in markets hit by worries over U.S. tariffs and recession risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-flock-safety-us-short-term-government-bond-funds-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NHTSHTKAOJOQXPW4BXN3MJBMV4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达沃斯会议创始人克劳斯-施瓦布卸任世界经济论坛主席一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[克劳斯-施瓦布（Klaus Schwab）已辞去世界经济论坛董事会主席一职。【原文：Klaus Schwab, founder of the World Economic Forum which gathers the world's business and political elite in the Swiss mountain village of Davos every year, has resigned as chair of its board of trustees, the WEF said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos-meeting-founder-klaus-schwab-steps-down-world-economic-forum-chair-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DBR6ASJYJKG5LSVUFZMO262KU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 11:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道信件显示，美国投资者卡梅伦出价 50 亿美元收购哈萨克矿业巨头 ERG]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商人詹姆斯-卡梅隆（James Cameron）在给欧亚资源集团董事会的一封信中表示，他愿意以 50 亿美元的价格收购该公司，因为该公司准备参与哈萨克斯坦稀土产量的大规模扩张。【原文：U.S. businessman James Cameron has offered to buy mining giant Eurasian Resources Group for $5 billion, a letter he sent to its board showed, as the company prepares to participate in a major expansion of Kazakhstan's rare earths output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-investor-cameron-offers-5-billion-kazakh-mining-giant-erg-letter-shows-2025-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMC32BJHP5KQVHDT5GOMCWSQHI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>