<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:06:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:06:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[国会未能推进拨款法案，美国政府开始关闭大部分业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一条突发新闻。全面报道将很快发布。【原文：This is a breaking news story. Full coverage will be available soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-government-begins-shut-down-most-operations-after-congress-fails-advance-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWMQLGSSI5KMZMUIQASYVXBSIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 04:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球经济 中国和美国需求疲软，亚洲工厂举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的民间调查显示，9月份亚洲大多数主要经济体的工厂活动萎缩，原因是有迹象表明美国经济增长放缓，而且美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税预期影响加大了中国需求疲软带来的压力。【原文：Factory activity shrank in most of Asia's major economies in September, private surveys showed on Wednesday, as signs of a slowdown in U.S. growth and the expected impact of President Donald Trump's tariffs added to pressure from weak Chinese demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-economy-asian-factories-struggle-soft-china-us-demand-takes-toll-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNFWVDC4PJPEFLA4QP3H2ZASGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 03:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本最高贸易谈判代表称美国 5500 亿美元投资计划不会对外汇产生影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最高贸易谈判代表赤泽亮世周三表示，日本将在不影响外汇市场的情况下执行东京与华盛顿达成的关税协议中商定的对美投资 5500 亿美元的一揽子计划。【原文：Japan will run a $550 billion U.S.-bound investment package agreed in Tokyo's tariff deal with Washington without any impact on the foreign exchange market, its top trade negotiator Ryosei Akazawa said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/japans-550-billion-us-investment-package-have-no-fx-impact-top-trade-negotiator-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUAFNPA2NRJIRNHEWKRJQVBLMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 03:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示：中国 9 月新房价格上涨，转售市场下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项民间调查显示，尽管采取了一系列支持措施，但中国市场仍在努力寻找立足点。【原文：China's new home prices rose at a slower pace in September, traditionally a peak buying month, while resale home prices fell again, as the market struggled to find its footing despite a raft of support measures, a private survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-september-new-home-prices-edge-up-resale-market-falls-survey-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BWTDE4SORKR3NGRNEASEOJYQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arm计划就高通纠纷终审裁决提起上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arm Holdings 周二表示，它计划就法官在与高通公司的许可纠纷中做出的裁决提起上诉，该裁决使芯片制造商在陪审团中的胜利保持不变。【原文：Arm Holdings said on Tuesday it planned to appeal a judge's ruling in a licensing dispute against Qualcomm that left the chipmaker's jury victory intact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/arm-plans-appeal-final-ruling-qualcomm-dispute-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSFE424BPJII7CY3YRVMK5C2KM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:17:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府关门在即，华尔街期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国政府关门时间的临近，华尔街期货周三下滑，这将推迟关键就业数据的公布，并使利率前景变得模糊。【原文：Wall Street futures slipped on Wednesday as the clock ticked down to a U.S. government shutdown that would delay the release of crucial jobs data and muddy the interest rate outlook, while Asian markets hesitated after a solid quarter of gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CHVU5D6LNMVPIMEVBODWNEY7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，贝莱德的 GIP 接近以 380 亿美元收购公用事业集团 AES]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周二援引知情人士的话报道称，黑石集团旗下的全球基础设施合作伙伴公司（GIP）即将以 380 亿美元（含债务）的价格收购公用事业集团 AES。【原文：BlackRock-owned Global Infrastructure Partners (GIP) is nearing a $38 billion deal, inclusive of debt, to acquire utility group AES , the Financial Times reported on Tuesday, citing people briefed on the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/blackrocks-gip-nears-38-billion-takeover-utility-group-aes-ft-reports-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FNME2M3ZIZKGJJJO7IJAPTCH7Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 01:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[好莱坞演员工会谴责人工智能生成的 "女演员 "蒂莉-诺伍德]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近，人工智能生成的 "女演员 "蒂莉-诺伍德首次亮相，其制片人吹嘘制片厂高管对其感兴趣，这引发了 SAG-AFTRA 演员工会周二的反击，谴责用 "人造人 "取代人类演员的做法。【原文：The recent debut of an AI-generated "actress" dubbed Tilly Norwood, and its producer's boasts of interest from studio executives, sparked a backlash on Tuesday from the SAG-AFTRA actors union, condemning the replacement of human performers with "synthetics."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/hollywood-performers-union-condemns-ai-generated-actress-tilly-norwood-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGXGE7I5W5LATCRJ35KBHMUBHI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者权衡欧佩克+增产与美国原油库存，石油价格稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三早盘，油价在连续两日下跌后企稳，原因是投资者在权衡欧佩克+可能在下月增加产量的计划与美国库存缩减的前景后作出了判断。【原文：Oil prices steadied in early trade on Wednesday after two consecutive days of losses as investors weighed potential OPEC+ plans for a larger output hike next month against the prospect of shrinking inventories in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-steadies-investors-weigh-opec-output-hike-against-us-crude-inventories-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IMTY6UCEBPFBAQYC4N7UJVQBI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:52:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府关门在即，美元处于守势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元兑主要货币汇率徘徊在一周低点附近，因为美国政府可能面临关门，这将推迟重要就业数据的公布。【原文：The dollar hovered near a one-week low versus major peers on Wednesday as the U.S. government headed towards a likely shutdown, which would delay the release of crucial jobs data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-defensive-us-government-shutdown-looms-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JEJU5NLOAVP3HISJZCNMCUMVTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber 在美国首例司机性侵索赔案中被判无责]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一名原告律师称，加州陪审团周二表示，Uber 无需为一名妇女的性侵犯行为负责，这名妇女称她在使用该应用程序叫车时遭到了司机的袭击。【原文：Uber is not liable for the sexual assault of a woman who said she was attacked by her driver on a ride she ordered from the app, a California jury said on Tuesday, according to an attorney for the plaintiff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/uber-found-not-liable-first-us-trial-over-driver-sexual-assault-claims-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWCMSDNNTBOWNJNDEH2N75CRSY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美韩同意不以汇率为贸易优势目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周三发表的一份联合声明，美国和韩国一致认为，外汇干预应仅限于应对过度波动，而不应将汇率作为竞争目标。【原文：The United States and South Korea agreed that foreign exchange interventions should be reserved for combating excessive volatility, without targeting exchange rates for competitive purposes, according to a joint statement released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-south-korea-agree-not-target-fx-rates-trade-advantage-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZNQAPRI45O3RAZ4RGGD5RFSLU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:22:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谈判代表称台湾不会同意与美国达成五五分成的芯片生产协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾最高关税谈判代表周三回国后表示，台湾不会同意与美国达成的半导体生产半数在台湾进行的协议。【原文：Taiwan will not agree to a deal with the United States for half of all semiconductor production to take place in the country, the island's top tariff negotiator said on Wednesday after returning home.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-will-not-agree-50-50-chip-production-deal-with-us-negotiator-says-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LG34TIRZGBKANIY7CUPCEHTLHM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:20:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理对中国暂停购买必和必拓铁矿石的报道表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞周三表示，他对有关中国国有铁矿石买家已采取措施暂停向矿商必和必拓购买铁矿石货物的报道感到担忧。【原文：Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said on Wednesday he was concerned about a report that China's state iron ore buyer had taken steps to pause purchases of iron ore cargoes from miner BHP .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/australia-pm-concerned-about-chinas-reported-pause-bhp-iron-ore-purchases-2025-10-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JTXDKMFGYZNLHGP4RY5H3XO5W4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:10:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：特朗普与辉瑞的交易对药价意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统长期以来一直认为美国为处方药支付的费用超过了其应有的水平，他周二表示，辉瑞公司已同意降低其向美国低收入人群医疗补助计划（Medicaid）销售的药品价格，并确保美国不会为新药支付比其他高收入国家更高的费用。特朗普表示，他希望其他制药商也能效仿。【原文：President Donald Trump, who has long argued that the U.S. pays more than it should for prescription medicines, on Tuesday said Pfizer had agreed to cut prices for drugs it sells to the Medicaid program for low-income Americans and to ensure the U.S. would not pay more for new medicines than other high-income nations. Trump said he expects other drugmakers to follow suit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/what-does-trumps-deal-with-pfizer-mean-drug-prices-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7UCZVNNVFN65OOGLGX3E5LDMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:43:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管季度末美联储流动性机制需求不旺，但回购利率攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，随着第三季度的结束，华尔街对美联储流动性工具的兴趣远低于预期，尽管回购利率的攀升显示出一定的流动性压力。【原文：Federal Reserve liquidity facilities saw much less interest from Wall Street than expected on Tuesday as the third quarter came to a close, though a climb in repo rates showed some liquidity pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-liquidity-facilities-see-tepid-demand-despite-quarter-end-repo-rates-climb-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VU7X6K6JLZMYFCT6S7IKA3NSG4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:26:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫撤回安东尼领导 BLS 的提名]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周二表示，特朗普政府已撤回对保守派经济学家安东尼（E.J. Antoni）担任劳工统计局局长的提名。【原文：The Trump administration has withdrawn its nomination of conservative economist E.J. Antoni as head of the Bureau of Labor Statistics, the White House said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-withdraws-antonis-nomination-next-head-bureau-labor-statistics-cnn-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PM7BDWX3FJWLPV6E7FB6NV334</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:17:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储罗根：美国可能需要就业市场更加宽松才能实现 2% 的通胀率]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联储主席洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周二表示，美国劳动力市场可能需要进一步疲软，美联储才能实现2%的通胀目标，因为在不考虑新的进口关税影响的情况下，物价上涨速度更快。【原文：The U.S. labor market likely needs to weaken further for the Federal Reserve to achieve its 2% inflation target, as prices are rising even faster without factoring in the impact of new import tariffs, Dallas Fed President Lorie Logan said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-us-may-need-more-slack-job-market-hit-2-inflation-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6AJWU6KMZMNJD2LUVBRMU23XA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在工人签证会议上表示鼓励韩国投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院表示，美国和韩国正密切合作推进两国的贸易和投资伙伴关系，包括为合格的韩国工人办理适当的签证。【原文：The U.S. and South Korea are working closely to advance their trade and investment partnership including by processing appropriate visas for qualified South Korean workers, the U.S. State Department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-says-it-encourages-south-korean-investment-meeting-worker-visas-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NSCYU5PRBJEXMBMV7XR6LVT7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:10:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国总统将于周三会见 OpenAI 首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统办公室表示，OpenAI 首席执行官山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）周三计划会见韩国总统李在明，李在明希望通过促进人工智能投资的政策来推动亚洲第四大经济体的发展。【原文：OpenAI Chief Executive Sam Altman on Wednesday plans to meet with South Korean President Lee Jae Myung, who seeks to boost Asia's fourth-biggest economy through a policy of boosting investment in artificial intelligence, the presidential office has said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/south-korean-president-meet-with-openai-ceo-wednesday-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AKH3P7W3XRO25DRTJE4TERSXAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:49:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰政府支持能源公司的关键基础设施投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰政府周三表示，将为本国能源公司在关键电力基础设施方面的投资提供财政支持。【原文：The New Zealand government said on Wednesday that it would financially support investment by the country’s energy companies in critical electricity infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/new-zealand-government-back-energy-firms-critical-infrastructure-investments-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7QXSOP556JK7FLKJQDQ52BU6QQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:47:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子邮件称，美国消费者监督机构基本关闭，将在停摆期间继续工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封电子邮件，美国最高消费者财务监督机构周二告诉工作人员，如果政府在午夜后关门，该机构将继续运作。【原文：The top U.S. watchdog agency for consumer finances told staff on Tuesday it will continue to operate in the event of a government shutdown after midnight, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-consumer-watchdog-largely-shuttered-continue-work-during-shutdown-email-says-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWUY2JZMLVK2TCRHS2TRCSGYIU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:29:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果、谷歌和 Meta 必须面对赌场式赌博应用程序的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二驳回了苹果公司、谷歌公司和 Meta Platforms 公司提出的驳回诉讼的请求，这些公司声称它们通过托管和接受赌场式应用程序的佣金，使用户上瘾，从而助长了非法赌博。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday denied Apple , Google and Meta Platforms' requests to dismiss lawsuits claiming they promoted illegal gambling by hosting and accepting commissions from casino-style apps that addict users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/apple-google-meta-must-face-lawsuits-over-casino-style-gambling-apps-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRFGWQFWIVNK5FQSXNMM3XJ2XI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:24:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构起诉苹果公司涉嫌歧视犹太工人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国负责执行工作场所反歧视法的机构周二起诉苹果公司，称一家零售店的经理在解雇一名犹太裔员工之前发表了反犹太言论，并拒绝了他的休假请求。【原文：The U.S. agency that enforces workplace anti-discrimination laws sued Apple on Tuesday, claiming the manager of a retail store made antisemitic comments and denied a Jewish employee's requests for time off before firing him.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-agency-sues-apple-alleged-discrimination-against-jewish-worker-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHDIMPJFGBPRNL5R6TYW7SA24A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在人工智能数据中心蓬勃发展之际，里克-佩里支持的费米房地产投资信托基金（Fermi REIT）在美国首次公开募股中筹集到 6.82 亿美元资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[由美国前能源部长里克-佩里（Rick Perry）共同创办的数据中心房地产投资信托公司费米公司（Fermi）周二表示，该公司在美国首次公开募股中筹集了 6.825 亿美元。【原文：Fermi, a data center real estate investment trust co-founded by former U.S. energy secretary Rick Perry, said on Tuesday it raised $682.5 million in its U.S. initial public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/rick-perrys-data-center-reit-raises-682-million-us-ipo-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFFH5AGUIBLTDNVS43USH7GOAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:17:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国政府将持有美洲锂业公司 5%的股份，并与通用汽车成立合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉谈判情况的消息人士称，美国能源部将持有美洲锂业公司5%的股份，以及该公司与通用汽车公司合资的Thacker Pass锂矿公司5%的股份。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy will take a 5% stake in Lithium Americas and a separate 5% stake in the company's Thacker Pass lithium mine joint venture with General Motors , a source familiar with negotiations said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-government-take-5-stake-lithium-americas-joint-venture-with-general-motors-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXXO6USCMVLDXBGKNDCZOAVKDA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 21:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Axios 报道，迪士尼向 Character.AI 公司发出终止信]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Axios 周二报道，华特迪士尼已致函 Character.AI，要求这家人工智能初创公司立即停止未经授权使用其拥有版权的角色。【原文：Walt Disney has sent a letter to Character.AI demanding that the AI startup immediately stop the unauthorized use of its copyrighted characters, Axios reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/disney-sends-cease-and-desist-letter-characterai-axios-reports-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E25V2356NZOKTMD2MU2UUXLAYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:48:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊驳回黑人工人被列入改进计划的偏见诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）赢得了一项诉讼的驳回，该诉讼指控这家在线零售商歧视一名黑人前雇员，减少了她的职责，并将她列入绩效改进计划。【原文：Amazon.com won the dismissal on Tuesday of a lawsuit accusing the online retailer of discriminating against a Black former employee by reducing her duties and putting her on a performance improvement plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/amazon-defeats-bias-lawsuit-by-black-worker-placed-improvement-plan-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCPVYVMBUJMO7MWLAKTUHLFXIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:38:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空公司在破产程序中获得高达 4.75 亿美元的融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）的母公司周二表示，该公司已与现有债券持有人谈判达成高达 4.75 亿美元的融资，以支持其在破产保护重组期间的正常业务运营。【原文：Spirit Airlines has negotiated funding of up to $475 million with existing bondholders to support normal business operations during its Chapter 11 restructuring, its parent company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spirit-airlines-gets-up-475-million-financing-amid-bankruptcy-process-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PTWN4IRIRI4VKHFAGB5SLLWJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克扭亏为盈，首席执行官警告中国市场落后，未来仍需努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克周二公布第一季度营收意外增长，利润超出预期，尽管中国市场疲软和关税给利润率带来压力，但这家历史悠久的运动服饰品牌的扭亏为盈努力仍取得了进展。【原文：Nike on Tuesday reported a surprise rise in first-quarter revenue and beat profit expectations as the storied sportswear brand's turnaround effort gained traction despite weakness in China and tariffs pressuring margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nike-reports-surprise-rise-quarterly-revenue-2025-09-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KR2FL3QPJOWRDBRF6R4QHC7TI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:19:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>