<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:04:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:04:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国亿万富翁莱昂-布莱克击败强奸指控者的诽谤上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州一家上诉法院周四作出有利于亿万富翁投资者莱昂-布莱克的裁决，驳回了一名妇女提出的诽谤指控，这名妇女还指控这位阿波罗全球管理公司（Apollo Global Management）的联合创始人犯有强奸和性虐待罪。【原文：A New York state appeals court ruled in favor of billionaire investor Leon Black on Thursday, rejecting a defamation claim by a woman who also accused the Apollo Global Management co-founder of rape and sexual abuse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-billionaire-leon-black-defeats-rape-accusers-defamation-appeal-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JV3DG3CIOFLF5DQOAOUAZUZED4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行警告美国关税可能降低全球经济增长前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行周四警告说，如果美国的贸易伙伴以关税作为报复，美国征收10%的全面关税可能会使本已乏善可陈的2025年2.7%的全球经济增长率下降0.3个百分点。【原文：The World Bank on Thursday warned that U.S. across-the-board tariffs of 10% could reduce already lackluster global economic growth of 2.7% in 2025 by 0.3 percentage point if America's trading partners retaliate with tariffs of their own.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/world-bank-warns-that-us-tariffs-could-reduce-global-growth-outlook-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVXBUQGI2RMA3HT6PK7PGM5RFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际清算银行警告：关税推动的美元升值带来全球滞胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[央行伞式组织国际清算银行的工作人员警告说，如果即将上任的美国总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺的贸易关税继续推高美元，全球将出现滞胀。【原文：Staff at central bank umbrella group, the Bank for International Settlements, have warned of a global bout of stagflation if trade tariffs promised by soon-to-be-U.S. President Donald Trump continue to drive up the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tariff-fuelled-dollar-gains-pose-global-stagflation-risks-bis-warns-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSV4ZVRXHJPVBP4IHXQZFC7XRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部部长人选称美联储应保持独立]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部长人选周四在参议院小组会议上表示，美联储应保持独立。【原文：The Federal Reserve should stay independent, Trump's pick to be U.S. Treasury Secretary told a Senate panel on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-should-stay-independent-trumps-pick-us-treasury-secty-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A452K4EFCFIYBMZISO3MM3D5HI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部称，美国运通将支付 1.087 亿美元和解欺骗性营销指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，信用卡公司美国运通已同意支付 1.087 亿美元，以了结对其从事欺骗性营销行为的指控。【原文：Credit card company American Express has agreed to pay $108.7 million to settle allegations that it engaged in deceptive marketing practices, the U.S. Justice Department said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/american-express-pay-1087-mln-settle-deceptive-marketing-allegations-justice-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVB7QKOT6ZJKTMWN7TYBMQN5AA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:34:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪称洛杉矶大火可能给南加州爱迪生公司带来风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪评级公司（Moody's Ratings）在周四的一份报告中称，洛杉矶县中部的伊顿大火给电力供应商南加州爱迪生公司（Southern California Edison）带来了潜在的信用风险，该公司在大火最初引发的地区运营电力线路。【原文：The Eaton Fire in central Los Angeles County poses a potential credit risk to power provider Southern California Edison, which operates electrical lines in the area where the destructive blaze first started, Moody's Ratings said in a report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/moodys-says-la-fire-may-pose-risk-southern-california-edison-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCVBACWHPZNTRLRWDVJP2QE5XQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通预测，2025-2026 年数据中心支出可将美国国内生产总值提高 20 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（J.P.Morgan）估计，随着科技公司竞相从人工智能热潮中获益，数据中心的支出可能会在 2025-2026 年间为美国经济增长贡献 10-20 个基点。【原文：J.P.Morgan estimated spending on data centers could contribute between 10-20 basis points to U.S. economic growth in 2025-2026 as technology companies race to benefit from the artificial intelligence boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/jpmorgan-forecasts-spending-data-centers-could-boost-us-gdp-by-20-basis-points-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGF5XG6LBJIPTASDV26ZNY6LBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着 "TikTok 难民 "在禁令发布前加入，中国应用程序 RedNote 本周获得数百万美国用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析公司 Similarweb 的最新数据显示，随着大量自称为 "TikTok 难民 "的用户加入，中国社交媒体应用红笔记（RedNote，在中国被称为小红书）在本周早些时候的一天内增加了近 300 万美国用户。【原文：Chinese social media app RedNote, known in China as Xiaohongshu, gained nearly 3 million U.S. users in one day earlier this week as a flood of self-proclaimed "TikTok Refugees" joined, according to new data from analytics firm Similarweb.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-app-rednote-gained-millions-us-users-this-week-tiktok-refugees-joined-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A2X6RROMBJ2PEWQVRUC7WIV64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:10:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件显示，瑞银获得新的美国养老金许可证，纠正了文书工作中的错误]]></title><description><![CDATA[文件显示，美国劳工部批准了瑞银继续管理美国退休计划所需的豁免权，此前的文书工作错误曾使这家瑞士银行所监管的 110 亿美元资产面临风险。【原文：The U.S. Department of Labor granted UBS a waiver the Swiss bank needs to continue managing U.S. retirement plans after a paperwork error had put the $11 billion of assets the lender oversees at risk, documents show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-gets-fresh-us-pensions-licence-fixing-paperwork-error-filings-show-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHVA4EV2H5PXTPHK5W3EGXDL5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:41:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部人选贝森特表示延长减税是首要任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）选择的财政部负责人斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，延长特朗普将于今年年底到期的 2017 年减税政策是 "当前最重要的经济问题"。【原文：Scott Bessent, U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's choice to head the Treasury Department, on Thursday said that extending Trump's 2017 tax cuts that are set to expire at the end of this year is "the single most important economic issue of the day."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-us-treasury-pick-bessent-says-extending-tax-cuts-top-priority-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ER3EGQYIKFLVHJZ3NTS2OM32QQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊在开普敦开设随身携带中心，努力争取市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电子商务巨头亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周四在南非开设了一个随身购物中心，该中心将帮助其独立卖家吸引更多客户并拓展业务，同时亚马逊公司也在努力争取市场份额。【原文：U.S. e-commerce giant Amazon.com opened on Thursday a walk-in centre in South Africa that it says will help its independent sellers attract more customers and expand their businesses, while it also seeks to gain market share.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-opens-cape-town-walk-in-centre-strives-market-share-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKXILXL5LBPT5DSXDCJPE3ROA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技团体起诉美国联邦金融业委员会，要求阻止有关支付应用程序和数字钱包的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，两个技术贸易团体起诉美国消费者金融保护局，要求阻止一项新规定，该规定赋予监管机构对大型非银行支付应用和数字钱包的监管权。【原文：Two technology trade groups sued the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau on Thursday to block a new rule giving the regulator supervisory authority over payment apps and digital wallets from large non-banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tech-groups-sue-us-cfpb-block-rule-payment-apps-digital-wallets-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNZYBZVUFJKPZLQVUV5ZZRITTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:45:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顾问称，如果达成协议，特朗普将阻止 TikTok "消失]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的新任国家安全顾问周四表示，如果有可行的协议，新政府将让 TikTok 在美国继续存在。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's incoming national security adviser said Thursday the new administration will keep TikTok alive in the United States if there is a viable deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-will-keep-tiktok-going-dark-if-deal-is-table-adviser-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRJCSOG2LZNDPBIZDDQ3R7JUXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:35:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的沃勒：如果通货紧缩符合预期，美联储可能很快就会减息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯-沃勒（Chris Waller）周四发表评论称，通胀可能继续缓解，并可能允许美联储比预期更早、更快地降息，这与近期市场预期美联储降息路径较浅的走势背道而驰。【原文：Inflation is likely to continue to ease and possibly allow the Federal Reserve to cut rates sooner and faster than expected, Fed governor Chris Waller said Thursday in comments that pushed against recent market moves that anticipated a shallower Fed rate path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-waller-cuts-could-come-sooner-than-later-if-disinflation-meets-expectations-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBBNPXPOXBLVHK2Y2CXUA74R4Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市和债券在通胀推动下涨势不减]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在交易商消化了美国零售销售小幅增长的数据后，美国股市和债券价格守住了上一交易日受通胀提振的涨幅。【原文：U.S. shares and bond prices held on to their inflation-inspired gains from the previous session on Thursday as traders digested data showing a small increase in U.S. retail sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ZFQLVLWQFJYHDFS7FWXQ76MWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储称截至 1 月储备金水平依然充裕]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周四公布的数据显示，该行并没有马上面临停止缩减资产负债表规模的压力。【原文：The Federal Reserve Bank of New York released data Thursday that suggest it faces no imminent pressure to stop the process of shrinking the size of its balance sheet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/new-york-fed-says-january-reserve-levels-still-abundant-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USE6WNJRWBOPFGSLSSAM4WDS2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月商业库存增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[11 月份美国企业库存小幅上升，表明补货可能不会促进第四季度的经济增长。【原文：U.S. business inventories rose marginally in November, suggesting that restocking will probably not contribute to economic growth in the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-inventories-edge-up-november-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYBL77HRIZLRDCTM5YUUCSXVAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:27:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大部长称报复性关税可能包括关键矿产]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大能源和自然资源部长乔纳森-威尔金森（Jonathan Wilkinson）周四表示，加拿大正在准备一份美国可能征收报复性关税的清单，其中一些可能涉及关键矿产。【原文：Canada is preparing a list of potential US retaliatory tariffs and some of those could be on critical minerals, Energy and Natural Resources Minister Jonathan Wilkinson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-minister-says-retaliatory-tariffs-could-include-critical-minerals-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPBJG7NPT5JRZB5M3KPBCI2EGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:24:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者金融监管机构就现金应用业务对支付公司布洛克处以罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（CFPB）周四以其移动支付服务 Cash App 存在欺诈和安全协议薄弱为由，勒令支付公司 Block 支付罚款。【原文：The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) on Thursday ordered payments firm Block to pay a penalty citing fraud and weak security protocols on its mobile payment service Cash App.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-consumer-finance-watchdog-orders-payments-firm-block-pay-175-million-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3Q7YFJTILNPGPEJPOTMBNTWACA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦通信委员会驳回对美国广播公司总统辩论和哈里斯露面的投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦通信委员会周四表示，将驳回对美国广播公司主持的 9 月总统辩论以及副总统卡马拉-哈里斯在哥伦比亚广播公司的 "60 分钟 "和全国广播公司的 "周六夜现场 "节目中露面的投诉。【原文：The Federal Communications Commission said Thursday it is rejecting complaints over an ABC-moderated September presidential debate and Vice President Kamala Harris' appearances on CBS' "60 Minutes" and NBC's "Saturday Night Live."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fcc-rejects-complaints-over-abc-presidential-debate-harris-appearances-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KK7LAT44SRKJXOFKFQVO6M5OUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:58:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Cosan 公司卸下矿业公司淡水河谷的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西企业集团 Cosan 在周四提交的一份证券文件中称，该公司已卸下其持有的矿业巨头淡水河谷约 1.73 亿股股份，持股比例约为 4.05%。【原文：Brazilian conglomerate Cosan has unloaded some 173 million shares it owned in mining giant Vale , which accounted for a stake of roughly 4.05%, it said in a securities filing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazils-cosan-unloads-stake-miner-vale-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QXXMEP7LS5P73GS52F7IGMOET4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行将于1月29日降息，对美国关税的潜在影响持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对经济学家进行的一项调查显示，加拿大央行将于1月29日降息25个基点至3.00%，但鉴于美国威胁征收关税以及加拿大可能采取的应对措施等不确定性，许多经济学家对此后的前景没有信心。【原文：The Bank of Canada will cut interest rates by 25 basis points to 3.00% on Jan. 29, according to a Reuters poll of economists, but many were not confident about the outlook beyond that given uncertainty around threatened U.S. tariffs and possible Canada's response.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-canada-cut-rates-jan-29-cautious-over-potential-us-tariff-impact-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWZS4ZEKY5LA7DUUEFEBIRMYXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[费城联储工厂指数创 2020 年 6 月以来最大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[1 月份，美国中大西洋地区制造业活动的一项指标创下约四年半以来的最大涨幅，新订单和出货量双双激增，这可能表明工厂行业的长期低迷可能正在结束。【原文：A gauge of manufacturing activity in the U.S. Mid-Atlantic region shot up by the most in about four-and-a-half years in January, with new orders and shipments both surging, a potential indication that the factory sector's long slump may be ending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/philly-feds-factory-gauge-surges-by-most-since-june-2020-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VVVZUQNG6ZN2JO6ENCN5YTYH5A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LIV Golf 与福克斯体育签订多年媒体转播权协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[福克斯体育频道（Fox Sports）周四宣布，已与 LIV Golf 签订多年媒体转播权协议，从下月起在美国转播其联赛比赛。【原文：Fox Sports has signed a multi-year media rights agreement with LIV Golf to broadcast its league competition in the U.S. starting next month, the network announced on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/liv-golf-signs-multi-year-media-rights-deal-with-fox-sports-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNXNKKP5ZROCDJAF7M6I7UZRLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[12 月美国进口价格保持平稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于燃料和食品成本的飙升被其他方面的疲软所抵消，12 月份美国进口价格连续第三个月勉强上涨，这对通胀前景来说是个好兆头。【原文：U.S. import prices barely rose for a third straight month in December as a surge in the costs of fuels ad foods was offset by weakness elsewhere, which bodes well for the inflation outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-import-prices-remain-tame-december-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCC77YKB3JLVTKRLOPUXXK5W6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:08:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，1 万亿美元回购可能提振华尔街]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者一直希望唐纳德-特朗普下周重返白宫将提振美国股市，而高盛（Goldman Sachs）则认为股市将受益于至少五年来最大的公司回购预期。【原文：Investors have been hoping Donald Trump's return to the White House next week will boost the U.S. stock market, while Goldman Sachs sees stocks benefiting from the biggest expected company buybacks in at least five years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-could-get-boost-1-trillion-buybacks-goldman-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTKYDSGOI5IOLFI7Y2MYNZRH3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数增加；劳动力市场状况依然健康]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数增幅超过预期，但仍保持在劳动力市场健康的水平。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits increased more than expected last week, but remained at levels consistent with a healthy labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-labor-market-conditions-still-healthy-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GULQNRSTU5N53KPREOLHB7KBMU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:41:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月零售额稳健增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 12 月份零售额稳健增长，表明经济需求强劲，进一步巩固了美联储今年降息的谨慎态度。【原文：U.S. retail sales increased solidly in December, pointing to strong demand in the economy and further reinforcing the Federal Reserve's cautious approach to cutting interest rates this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-retail-sales-rise-solidly-december-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42G2QXS2K5LJ3FPYIJQ5ELWHMA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[任天堂称 Switch 2 将于 2025 年发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本游戏公司任天堂（Nintendo）周四表示，将于今年推出 Switch 2 游戏机，作为其热门设备 Switch 的后续产品。【原文：Japanese gaming company Nintendo will launch the Switch 2 console, successor to its hit Switch device, this year, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nintendo-says-switch-2-will-be-released-2025-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4V6Y5MBMXVIEDLXQUS57U6ORAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿尔巴尼亚批准与贾里德-库什纳的公司有关的豪华度假村项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿尔巴尼亚政府已授予一家与唐纳德-特朗普的女婿贾里德-库什纳（Jared Kushner）有关联的公司战略投资者地位，该公司将在一个曾经是军事前哨的无人居住的地中海岛屿上建造一个豪华度假村。【原文：Albania's government has granted strategic investor status to a company linked to Donald Trump's son-in-law Jared Kushner to build a luxury resort on an uninhabited Mediterranean island that was once a military outpost.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/albania-approves-luxury-resort-project-linked-jared-kushners-company-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L6YIIIMW6JLFZEBK72L6WJQNBM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>