<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:28:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:28:41 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[白宫将邀请科技巨头承诺控制电力成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，白宫计划于三月初邀请微软、Anthropic和Meta Platforms等领先的数据中心与人工智能企业，正式达成一项协议，以保护消费者免受不断上涨的电力成本影响。【原文：The White House plans to host leading data center and artificial intelligence companies including Microsoft , Anthropic and Meta Platforms in early March to formalize a deal to shield consumers from rising electricity costs, according to two sources familiar with the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/white-house-host-big-tech-pledge-rein-power-costs-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YD6HGNUMSVPWZKYXF4O4JJPH7A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Worldline称其处置计划已接近完成，此前该公司已达成年度业绩目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字支付服务集团Worldline宣布，其非核心业务的剥离工作即将完成。在经历了新任首席执行官领导下的转型之年后，该公司公布的年度业绩符合预期。【原文：Digital payment service group Worldline's disposal of non-core parts of the business is near completion, the company said as it reported annual results in line with guidance after a transformational year under its new CEO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/worldline-disposal-programme-nearly-complete-it-says-after-hitting-annual-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIQ435UOSZKITJDM65CCCOYDAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，部分"农达"集体诉讼原告试图推迟对拜耳公司72.5亿美元和解方案的初步批准。]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表近2万名原告的律师事务所周三敦促密苏里州法官推迟审议拜耳公司提出的72.5亿美元全国和解方案。这些原告指控拜耳除草剂"农达"导致其健康受损。律师们辩称，仓促推进和解将侵犯数万癌症患者及其家属的权利。【原文：Law firms representing nearly 20,000 people who sued Bayer over alleged injuries from its Roundup weedkiller urged a Missouri judge on Wednesday to delay reviewing the German company’s proposed $7.25 billion nationwide settlement, arguing that rushing would violate the rights of tens of thousands of cancer patients and their families.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/some-roundup-plaintiffs-seek-delay-preliminary-approval-proposed-725-bln-bayer-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5WOHO2J5VLTZJX3HLZOF7HOSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:51:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业裁员，投资转向人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着高盛周二警告称，人工智能加速普及可能推高今年美国失业率，且自动化影响最深的行业已出现就业岗位流失，投资者和经济学家对人工智能将颠覆传统产业的担忧正日益加深。【原文：Investors' and economists' concerns that artificial intelligence will upend established industries are deepening, as Goldman Sachs warned on Tuesday that accelerating AI adoption could push U.S. unemployment higher this year, with job losses already emerging in sectors most exposed to automation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/companies-cutting-jobs-investments-shift-toward-ai-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P664PNHW2VJRBGF3UEOMVWUE3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:38:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科迪华计划第四季度完成拆分为两家独立公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农化公司科迪华表示，此前宣布的拆分为两家上市公司的计划预计将于今年第四季度完成。【原文：U.S. agrichemicals company Corteva said it expects the previously announced planned separation into two listed companies to occur sometime in the fourth quarter of this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/corteva-targets-fourth-quarter-planned-split-into-two-companies-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JZUXOJLOBJIQXHGPVYMFS4RIPY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从约会诈骗到假律师：OpenAI在最新威胁报告中详述ChatGPT滥用案例]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI在报告中披露了其ChatGPT技术遭滥用的情况，称已封禁与中方执法部门、情感诈骗者及影响力行动相关的账户，其中包括针对日本首位女性首相的抹黑活动。【原文：OpenAI said it banned accounts linked to Chinese law enforcement, romance scammers and influence operations, including a smear campaign against Japan's first woman prime minister, in a report detailing the misuse of its ChatGPT technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dating-scams-fake-lawyers-openai-details-chatgpt-misuse-new-threat-report-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RR3LPUOIBJPZXBKYNJ7VCTZPO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国11个州敦促司法部彻底调查奈飞与华纳兄弟的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一封信函显示，美国11个州的共和党总检察长敦促美国司法部对奈飞收购华纳兄弟影视制作及流媒体资产的交易进行彻底审查，称该交易威胁到美国在电影领域的霸主地位。【原文：Republican attorneys general from 11 U.S. states have urged the U.S. Department of Justice to conduct a thorough review of Netflix's bid to acquire studio and streaming assets from Warner Bros., saying the deal threatens U.S. dominance in movies, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/11-us-states-urge-doj-thoroughly-probe-netflix-warner-bros-deal-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NFAIGRBFTJPQ3G2CPYT6MH4GQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，随着债券需求激增，美国一级信贷市场竞争达到历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据巴克莱银行对2017年以来逾百万份投资者记录的分析，美国一级信贷市场当前正处于有史以来最激烈的竞争状态，这主要源于市场对新发行公司债券的强劲需求。【原文：U.S. primary credit markets are now the most competitive on record, based on Barclays' analysis of over one million investor records since 2017, driven by high demand for new corporate bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-primary-credit-market-competition-hits-record-high-bond-demand-surges-report-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3HKYUI3MVPGNLSMQSARHJQSFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：知情人士称，在Donerail提出收购要约后，MarineMax吸引了更多收购意向]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士向路透社透露，包括黑石集团和Centerbridge Partners在内的私募股权公司、战略投资者及高净值人士均对收购休闲游艇零售商MarineMax或其部分业务表示兴趣。【原文：Private equity firms including Blackstone and Centerbridge Partners, strategic investors and wealthy individuals have expressed interest in buying recreational yacht retailer MarineMax or pieces of it, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/marinemax-attracts-more-buyout-interest-after-donerail-offer-sources-say-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNJOZWSUHJJU5HXRSU4FEFQMSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:52:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际金融协会称，政府支出将使全球债务在2025年攀升至创纪录的348万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球债务在2025年底攀升至创纪录的348万亿美元，此前该年度新增债务近29万亿美元，创下疫情暴涨以来最快的年度增幅。一家银行业贸易组织周三报告称。【原文：Global debt climbed to a record $348 trillion at the end of 2025, after nearly $29 trillion was added over the year in the fastest yearly build-up since the pandemic surge, a banking trade group reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/government-spending-lifts-global-debt-record-348-trillion-2025-says-iif-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2J6DV3NTDFKSPDEQR3H4OGKPQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:33:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国向南方公司提供265亿美元贷款，创下有史以来最大规模能源贷款纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部周三宣布，已向南方公司旗下子公司提供265.4亿美元贷款以提升电网可靠性，这是该部门贷款办公室迄今为止规模最大的此类融资项目。【原文：The U.S. Energy Department has offered a $26.54 billion loan to subsidiaries of Southern Co to increase grid reliability, the largest ever such financing by its loan office, the department said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-offers-largest-ever-energy-loan-with-265-billion-southern-co-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6W7KGSCWWBLAZC7SDHAK34PALA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:19:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通将黄金长期价格预测上调至4500美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通周三将黄金长期价格预测上调至每盎司4500美元，同时维持2026年底价格预测为6300美元。【原文：JP Morgan raised its long-term forecast for gold prices to $4,500 an ounce on Wednesday while keeping its 2026 year-end forecast at $6,300.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/jp-morgan-raises-long-term-gold-price-forecast-4500-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRZA7TVBW5PLTBO3ZGE74JXY3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与加拿大将于未来数周就贸易问题举行会谈，格里尔表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔周三表示，美加贸易官员已进行磋商，并计划在未来几周内举行会晤。他补充称，特朗普政府对双方就达成协议提出的建议持开放态度。【原文：U.S. and Canadian trade officials spoke on Wednesday and plan to meet in coming weeks, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said, adding that the Trump administration was open to their ideas on how to reach an agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-canada-meet-coming-weeks-trade-greer-says-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFHO2JSSL5L7XNQHSUHIL6J6V4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列人工智能网络安全公司Gambit Security完成6100万美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于特拉维夫的网络安全公司Gambit Security周三宣布，在结束长达一年的"隐身模式"后，已完成6100万美元的早期融资。【原文：Tel Aviv-based cybersecurity firm Gambit Security said on Wednesday it had raised $61 million in an early funding round as it emerged from more than a year in "stealth mode".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/embargoed-israeli-ai-cyber-firm-gambit-security-raises-61-million-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EP3LWZL4CRMCZGXHAPWST5LY4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:06:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利电信考虑在大型活动中对高性能网络连接实施溢价定价]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利电信公司首席执行官周三表示，该公司正考虑推出高价点播移动服务，以满足客户在大型体育赛事等大型聚会期间对快速稳定网络连接的需求。【原文：Telecom Italia is exploring the introduction of premium-priced on-demand mobile services for customers seeking guaranteed fast and stable connectivity during large gatherings such as major sports events, its boss said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/telecom-italia-mulls-premium-pricing-highperformance-connectivity-big-events-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24OWYG47NZL4JJHZ6YI52ZKZXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克上调核心业务部门中期营收目标，得益于资本接入平台业务的强劲增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克周三上调了其最大业务部门的中期营收预期，主要基于数据、上市和指数业务的强劲表现。【原文：Nasdaq raised the medium-term revenue forecast for its biggest division on Wednesday, banking on strength in its data, listing and index businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nasdaq-lifts-medium-term-revenue-target-key-unit-capital-access-platforms-boost-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4M6OUGJ6ZMU5M4MOXBED225HU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙反垄断监管机构称苹果、亚马逊耗时过长才完善反竞争合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙竞争监管机构周三裁定，苹果和亚马逊耗时过长才从合同中删除反竞争条款——此前监管机构已要求两家公司立即删除这些条款，这些条款规定了亚马逊作为苹果分销商的条件。【原文：Apple and Amazon took too long to remove anti-competitive clauses they were ordered to immediately remove from contracts outlining Amazon's conditions as an Apple distributor, Spain's competition regulator ruled on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spains-antitrust-watchdog-says-apple-amazon-took-too-long-refine-anti-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2G3H2VNBFFPKDKXRENRQM3PWFY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:22:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰瑟枪制造商Axon股价上涨，因政府支出提振其利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三盘前交易中，电击枪制造商Axon Enterprise股价飙升16%，此前该公司公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于其安防设备和软件产品需求强劲。【原文：Axon Enterprise shares jumped 16% in premarket trading on Wednesday after the Taser-maker reported fourth‑quarter profit above Wall Street expectations, on strong demand for its security devices and software products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/axon-shares-rise-taser-makers-profit-gets-boost-government-spending-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGIYX7SKLROA3ADGTDD2R7KZWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室称，对部分国家关税税率将升至15%或更高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表杰米森·格里尔周三表示，美国对部分国家的关税税率将从新实施的10%上调至15%或更高，但未具体说明涉及哪些贸易伙伴或提供其他细节。【原文：The U.S. tariff rate for some countries will go up to 15% or higher from the newly-imposed 10%, U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said on Wednesday, without naming any specific trading partners or other details.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-tariff-rate-hit-15-or-more-some-nations-ustr-says-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZL3WTEKLNOSPO6ZDQLX6XZMMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:11:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，欧佩克+将考虑4月增产13.7万桶/日]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，欧佩克+可能考虑将4月份的原油日产量提高13.7万桶，以结束为期三个月的增产暂停期。该组织正为夏季用油高峰做准备，而美国与欧佩克成员国伊朗之间的紧张局势推高了油价。【原文：OPEC+ will likely consider raising its oil output by 137,000 barrels per day for April to end a three-month pause in production increases, three sources with knowledge of OPEC+ thinking said, as the group prepares for peak summer demand and tensions between the U.S. and OPEC member Iran boost prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-consider-137000-bpd-oil-output-increase-april-sources-say-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APNDLK6DI5MIZMPMLCP242MOSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:04:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鞋履品牌Steven Madden因关税不确定性暂不发布盈利预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[鞋履与手袋制造商史蒂文·马登周三宣布暂缓发布2026年盈利预测，理由是近期关税政策存在不确定性。这是企业为应对华盛顿下一步动向而备战之际，首次显现的新一轮动荡迹象——此前该公司刚在上周遭遇最高法院裁决的挫败。【原文：Shoe and handbag maker Steven Madden on Wednesday withheld its 2026 earnings forecast, citing recent tariff uncertainty, in the first visible signs of fresh turmoil for companies as they brace for Washington's next move following last week's Supreme Court defeat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/steven-madden-withholds-annual-profit-forecast-due-uncertainty-around-us-tariffs-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZM4FGMVFFJNPLORHBBRAGEUHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:52:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华将在得克萨斯州建设放射性配体疗法基地以扩大美国生产能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺华周三宣布计划在得克萨斯州建设放射性配体疗法生产基地，此举将扩大其在美国的市场布局——该基地将成为该公司在得州的首个此类设施，也是全美第五个此类生产基地。【原文：Novartis said on Wednesday it intends to build a radioligand therapy manufacturing site in Texas, expanding its U.S. footprint with what will be its first such facility in the state and fifth nationwide.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-build-radioligand-therapy-site-texas-expand-us-manufacturing-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3CPKLMG35N2NIIAYUND4RXMEI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:41:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TJX公司预测全年销售额和利润将保持温和增长，因消费者削减开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[TJX公司周三公布的年度销售额和利润预期低于华尔街预期，尽管季度业绩超出预期，这表明在宏观经济不确定性背景下，注重预算的消费者在非必需品消费方面趋于谨慎。【原文：TJX Cos forecast annual sales and profit below Wall Street estimates on Wednesday despite a quarterly results beat, signaling strained discretionary spending among budget-conscious consumers amid macroeconomic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tjx-cos-beats-estimates-fourth-quarter-revenue-off-price-demand-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IO2DJ5U4ARNMLP6PIDY23MFSY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:39:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国寻求借助人工智能现代化安全机构以打击有组织犯罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国财政部、内政部和司法部周三宣布，该国计划对主要安全机构进行现代化改造，并引入人工智能技术打击有组织犯罪，重点打击金融犯罪、洗钱及涉毒案件。【原文：Germany plans to modernise its main security authorities and enlist AI in its fight against organised crime, as it cracks down on financial offences, money laundering and drug-related cases, the ministries of finance, interior affairs and justice said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/germany-seeks-enlist-ai-modernise-security-bodies-fight-against-organised-crime-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P72HL5XL3FLJHESPT253X32Y4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[《金融时报》报道称，英美科技协议谨慎重启，聚焦核能项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周三报道，美国和英国已初步重启价值数十亿英镑的"科技繁荣协议"谈判工作。该协议去年因美国总统特朗普向英国施压要求在更广泛的贸易谈判中让步而暂停。【原文：The U.S. and Britain have tentatively restarted work on their multi-billion-pound "tech prosperity deal", which was paused last year after President Donald Trump piled pressure on the UK to cede ground in wider trade talks, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/us-uk-tech-deal-cautiously-restarts-with-focus-nuclear-projects-ft-reports-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVDV6ONWRBKGLLQCYWPU3D4STE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:17:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政策不确定性加剧，First Solar业绩预测疲软，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[第一太阳能公司股价周三盘前交易中暴跌16.7%，此前该公司预测年度销售额将低于华尔街预期，原因是特朗普政府时期美国政策环境不确定以及审批延迟。【原文：Shares of First Solar slumped 16.7% in premarket trading on Wednesday, after the company forecast annual sales below Wall Street expectations amid U.S. policy environment uncertainty and permitting delays under the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/first-solar-shares-slump-after-weak-sales-forecast-amid-policy-uncertainty-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7PR42FCEFLO5JBAWDMJBJPZZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者气候组织以更宽松的规则重新启动，但美国成员减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[净零资产管理人倡议周三重启，在经历一年暂停后拥有超过250名成员，且规则有所放宽——此前美国政治反弹导致贝莱德退出该气候组织。【原文：The Net Zero Asset Managers initiative re-launched on Wednesday with more than 250 members after a year-long suspension and with looser rules after a U.S. political backlash prompted BlackRock to leave the climate group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/investor-climate-group-relaunches-with-looser-rules-fewer-us-members-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTVOQAWRHJNORICBX63EWXRKTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：又一天，又一次AI情绪波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RE3SZZ4KVND7EHDAPZ34JKVIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:39:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deliveroo意大利分部因涉嫌劳工剥削被置于监管之下]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周三看到的司法文件显示，米兰检察官已对食品配送平台Deliveroo的意大利分支机构实施司法监督，并对该公司首席执行官展开调查，指控其涉嫌剥削工人。【原文：Milan prosecutors have placed the Italian arm of food delivery platform Deliveroo under judicial supervision and its chief executive under investigation for alleged exploitation of workers, judicial documents seen by Reuters showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/deliveroos-italian-arm-placed-under-supervision-over-alleged-labour-exploitation-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TW7S5L5PVIBXGBZGN57ATY5AU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Circle第四季度营收因稳定币流通量强劲增长而上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Circle周三报告称第四季度营收增长，其稳定币USDC流通量上升推动储备收益提升，股价在盘前交易中上涨逾14%。【原文：Circle reported an increase in fourth-quarter revenue on Wednesday, as income from reserves got a boost from a rise in circulation of its stablecoin token, USDC, sending its shares up over 14% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/circles-fourth-quarter-revenue-rises-strong-stablecoin-circulation-2026-02-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TGINIRNJNIKJHHDJMKDCADMXQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>