<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:05:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:05:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标法庭曲折增加关税风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQUB5FCTQNI6XF7E2JMQLPTKCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 5 月制造业活动可能连续第二个月萎缩]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，5月份中国工厂活动可能连续第二个月萎缩，这表明在世界前两大经济体寻求摆脱关税战之际，与主要出口市场的贸易紧张局势正成为制造商的心头大患。【原文：China's factory activity likely contracted for a second month in May, a Reuters poll showed on Friday, suggesting trade tensions with major export markets are weighing on manufacturers' minds as the world's top two economies seek a way out of a tariff war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-may-manufacturing-activity-likely-contracted-second-straight-month-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYI3LDK5PVKJ7PFZZDOLZD3OLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行官员称，新西兰利率处于中性区间，数据将决定下一步行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰央行的一位高级官员周五表示，新西兰的利率处于2.5%-3.5%的中性区间，过去的宽松政策尚未流向经济，因此未来的利率走势将更多地取决于经济的发展情况。【原文：New Zealand's interest rates are in the 2.5%-3.5% neutral band, with past policy easing yet to flow through to the economy to make future moves more dependent on how the economy evolves, a senior central banker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-interest-rates-neutral-zone-data-decide-next-move-central-bank-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD3YMYH24ROJFNJ735K3JA4W5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:34:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁将斥资 60 亿美元在三家工厂开展去碳化工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[新日本制铁公司周五表示，该公司计划投资近8700亿日元（60.5亿美元），在国内三家工厂引进电炉，以减少碳排放。【原文：Nippon Steel plans to invest nearly 870 billion yen ($6.05 billion) to introduce electric furnaces at its three domestic plants to reduce carbon emissions, the company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/nippon-steel-will-spend-over-6-bln-decarbonisation-efforts-nhk-reports-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GA52NIVNNNLD7BUN66Y2VUO7BA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:32:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市下滑，美元下挫，特朗普关税在最新法庭转折后依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市下滑，美元随国债收益率下跌，原因是投资者消化了上诉法院维持唐纳德-特朗普总统关税有效的消息，一天前，市场因另一项阻止大部分关税的裁决而反弹。【原文：Stocks slipped in Asia on Friday and the U.S. dollar drooped with Treasury yields as investors digested an appeals court kept President Donald Trump's tariffs in effect, a day after markets rallied on a separate ruling blocking most of them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SU322X2RYFPRLHAIP5R25GK62M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受贸易和财政不确定性影响，美元有望连续第五个月下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元走软，连续第五个月下跌，原因是交易商为贸易和财政健康方面的进一步不确定性做准备，而投资者则在等待当天晚些时候的一份关键性通胀报告。【原文：The U.S. dollar softened on Friday, heading for its fifth-straight monthly decline as traders braced for further bouts of uncertainty around trade and fiscal health, while investors awaited a pivotal inflation report later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-poised-fifth-straight-monthly-drop-trade-fiscal-uncertainty-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FKXIBKESRVLBTB6UMKHYGBNUZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 4 月零售销售下滑，消费者保持节俭]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周五的数据显示，由于温暖的天气打击了冬装消费，澳大利亚4月份的零售额意外下滑，而百货公司也因打折活动稀少而受到影响，这进一步证明了消费者的谨慎态度。【原文：Australian retail sales slipped unexpectedly in April as warm weather hit spending on winter clothing, data showed on Friday, while department stores suffered from a dearth of discounting events in further evidence of a cautious consumer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/australia-retail-sales-dip-01-april-miss-forecasts-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TWV4R7OOVMBZC6ELXTZE3JE7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 01:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税官司、欧佩克+成为焦点，油价将迎来周度下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在美国关税裁决的鞭策下，以及在市场为欧佩克+可能增产做准备之际，油价有望在本周结束时下跌超过1%。【原文：Oil prices were on track to end the week down more than 1% on Friday amid whipsawing tariff rulings in the U.S. and as the market braced for a potential OPEC+ output hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-set-weekly-drop-with-tariff-legal-battles-opec-focus-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZRBMFAJ3NJJXNA7GL524M6VJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 01:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：中国科技公司为没有英伟达的人工智能未来做准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》周四报道，中国最大的科技公司已经开始转用国产芯片，以应对英伟达（Nvidia）处理器库存不断减少和美国不断收紧的出口管制。【原文：China's biggest technology companies have begun the process of switching to homegrown chips as they contend with a dwindling stockpile of Nvidia processors and tightening United States export controls, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-tech-companies-prepare-ai-future-without-nvidia-ft-reports-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3KA6HELCJOX5OD5T3BNOQVUPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 01:26:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：特朗普政府考虑允许在 150 天内征收最高 15%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑采取权宜之计，根据一项现行法律对全球经济的大部分地区征收关税，该法律包括允许在150天内征收最高15%关税的措辞。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering a stopgap effort to impose tariffs on large parts of the global economy under an existing law that includes language allowing for tariffs of up to 15% for 150 days, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-considers-allowing-tariffs-up-15-150-days-wsj-reports-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUUMEHS24NKEXNZQSLEXWPQWCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 01:25:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球航空公司将在年度峰会上应对贸易战和净零增长的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[在印度举行的年度峰会上，全球航空公司老板们将不可预测的贸易战和艰巨的环保目标提上了议事日程，因为他们担心地缘政治的不确定性将抑制旅行需求并提高成本，从而给航空业的前景蒙上阴影。【原文：An unpredictable trade war and daunting environmental targets are on the agenda for global airline bosses at an annual summit in India, as the industry's outlook is clouded by concerns that geopolitical uncertainty will dampen travel demand and raise costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/global-airlines-address-trade-war-net-zero-uncertainties-annual-summit-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAJJHLQYTBJJPN3AOMIRRIFRR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 01:06:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国调查假冒白宫办公厅主任的行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，美国联邦当局正在调查一起假冒白宫办公厅主任苏茜-怀尔斯（Susie Wiles）的事件。【原文：U.S. federal authorities are investigating an effort to impersonate White House Chief of Staff Susie Wiles, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-probes-effort-impersonate-white-house-chief-staff-wsj-reports-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6TSXTR6TJOO5JL3KIVQWQRQZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克计划在 2026 年底前将无人驾驶的 "星际飞船 "送上火星]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的大型新型火星飞船 "星际飞船"（Starship）在试飞中遭遇了一系列挫折，两天后，他在周四表示，他预计该未来派飞船将于明年年底首次无人驾驶前往红色星球。【原文：Two days after the latest in a string of test-flight setbacks for his big new Mars spacecraft, Starship, Elon Musk said on Thursday he foresees the futuristic vehicle making its first uncrewed voyage to the red planet at the end of next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/musk-aiming-send-uncrewed-starship-mars-by-end-2026-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCMXRNEG2ZJF5CIMVDBR5MREIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:37:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根称 "可能需要相当长一段时间 "才能看到风险平衡发生变化]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周四表示，在等待数据显示唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易、税收和监管政策组合是否会推高通胀或降低就业率的同时，该央行可能需要在相当长的一段时间内维持短期利率不变。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan on Thursday signaled that the central bank may need to keep short-term interest rates where they are for quite some time as it waits for the data to show if President Donald Trump's mix of trade, tax and regulatory policies pushes up inflation or down on employment】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-says-it-could-take-quite-some-time-see-shift-balance-risks-2025-05-30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JNLLGB7KNNN5DMAOMR7HBSSCWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：美中关税谈判 "有点停滞不前"，需要特朗普和习近平献计献策]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，美国与中国的贸易谈判 "有点停滞不前"，达成协议可能需要美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和中国国家主席习近平的直接参与。【原文：U.S. trade talks with China are "a bit stalled" and getting a deal over the finish line will likely need the direct involvement of President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-tariff-talks-a-bit-stalled-needs-trump-xi-input-bessent-says-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVTBVEUBHBJ7HMDK33WUODOUBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首都核心通胀率创两年新高，保持加息机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，由于食品成本持续上涨，日本首都的核心通胀率创下了两年多来的新高，这使得日本央行继续面临进一步加息的压力。【原文：Core inflation in Japan's capital hit a more than two-year high on persistent rises in food costs, data showed on Friday, keeping the central bank under pressure to hike interest rates further.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/core-inflation-japan-capital-hits-36-keeps-boj-rate-hike-chance-alive-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNZ6OH5F5NMGRMQQTHLBGCLZLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:53:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席戴利称通胀是其目前的主要关注点]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联储主席玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周四表示，美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）的政策制定者们仍有可能像他们在3月份预计的那样在今年降息两次，但目前利率应保持稳定，以确保通胀率能如期达到央行2%的目标。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve policymakers could still cut interest rates twice this year as they projected in March, San Francisco Fed President Mary Daly said on Thursday, but for now rates should remain steady to make sure inflation is on track to reach the central bank's 2% goal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-daly-says-inflation-her-main-focus-right-now-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33QGOTOEAVPFHAHCKKUXP25LPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:26:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[节日临近，特朗普关税官司延长了托运人的不确定性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最繁忙港口的执行董事周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的贸易关税问题爆发法庭争论之际，进口商在重要的假日海运季节到来之前的不确定性仍然很高。【原文：Importer uncertainty ahead of the vital holiday ocean shipping season remains high, the executive director of the busiest port in the U.S. said on Thursday, as a court battle broke out over President Donald Trump's trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/court-battle-over-trump-tariffs-prolongs-shipper-uncertainty-holiday-season-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKQ253BQURND3H25NFWNUZ3ITE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 22:56:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称法院裁决后美国贸易伙伴仍在真诚谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，包括日本在内的贸易伙伴正在继续与美国进行真诚的谈判，自美国贸易法院裁定特朗普政府的最新关税措施无效以来，他们的态度没有任何变化。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday that trading partners including Japan were continuing to negotiate with the U.S. in good faith, and there has been no change in their attitudes since a U.S. trade court ruled against the Trump administration's latest tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-us-trading-partners-still-negotiating-good-faith-after-court-ruling-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5WVZE4MPFOARLIVGDTPMI4SAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 22:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dentinger 退出后，Skyworks 任命内部人士 Robert Schriesheim 担任临时首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商 Skyworks Solutions 周四任命内部人士 Robert Schriesheim 担任临时财务总监，此前 Mark Dentinger 已宣布不再加入这家苹果供应商。【原文：Chipmaker Skyworks Solutions on Thursday named insider Robert Schriesheim as interim finance chief, after Mark Dentinger decided not to join the Apple supplier as previously announced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/skyworks-names-insider-robert-schriesheim-interim-cfo-after-dentinger-withdraws-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGKOWZXBPRM7RO5AD7XTSD6BQI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 22:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街担心预算法案中的外国税可能会降低美国资产的吸引力]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街分析师警告说，美国国会正在审议的预算法案中针对外国投资者征收的税最终可能会抑制对美国国债和美元的需求。【原文：Wall Street analysts are cautioning that a tax targeting foreign investors in the U.S. budget bill progressing through Congress could end up weighing on demand for U.S. Treasuries and the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-fears-foreign-tax-budget-bill-may-reduce-allure-us-assets-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VSCXQQJXGJKW5EDNQJSZBDHMGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行签署出售 44 亿美元铁路资产组合的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）周四表示，已签署协议将其铁路设备租赁业务出售给铁路车辆租赁商 GATX Corporation 和 Brookfield Infrastructure 新成立的合资企业。【原文：Wells Fargo said on Thursday it has signed a deal to sell its rail equipment leasing business to a newly formed joint venture between railcar lessor GATX Corporation and Brookfield Infrastructure .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wells-fargo-signs-deal-sell-44-billion-rail-assets-portfolio-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4S67I44EYBJ5VKXQHENEVBXKIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:48:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果贸易法庭的裁决成立，特朗普将转向其他关税攻击方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易和法律专家表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的全球关税攻势可能会因法院裁决而放缓，但不会停止，法院裁决最终可能会迫使他转向其他法律依据，以迫使各国做出贸易让步。【原文：President Donald Trump's global tariff assault may be slowed but won't be stopped by court rulings that may ultimately force a shift to other legal authorities for his campaign to pressure countries into trade concessions, trade and legal experts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/if-trade-court-ruling-stands-trump-seen-shifting-other-options-tariff-assault-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7Q45KRDYFPX5J5OKUY7MESI3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:47:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国鹰服装公司（American Eagle Outfitters）报告亏损大于预期，预计收入将下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国鹰服装公司（American Eagle Outfitters）周四报告了超出预期的季度亏损，预计第二季度收入将低于预期。【原文：American Eagle Outfitters forecast second-quarter revenue below estimates after reporting a wider-than-expected quarterly loss on Thursday, due to rising input costs and sluggish demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/american-eagle-outfitters-reports-bigger-than-expected-loss-forecasts-downbeat-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">736IXH5VVNMYDGBUHVC57ZVLRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:42:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合利华旗下的 Ben & Jerry's 将加沙战争称为 "种族灭绝]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ben & Jerry's（本杰瑞）公司的独立董事会称，加沙正在发生的冲突是一场种族灭绝，这使得这家冰淇淋生产商与其总部位于伦敦的母公司联合利华公司（Unilever）再次陷入争论。【原文：The independent board of Ben & Jerry's said the ongoing conflict in Gaza is a genocide, setting up the ice cream maker for another tussle with its London-based corporate parent Unilever .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/unilevers-ben-jerrys-calls-war-gaza-genocide-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6K7XX4HUYFIZXAVN3UV5P5NWYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:34:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业产品公司称，由于许可证要求，其对华出口可能下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业产品合伙公司（Enterprise Products Partners）周四表示，美国商务部要求该公司申请对华出口许可证，这可能会影响其乙烷和丁烷的出口。【原文：Enterprise Products Partners on Thursday said its ethane and butane exports could be hurt by a U.S. Department of Commerce requirement that it apply for a license to export to China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/enterprise-products-says-its-china-exports-could-fall-due-license-requirement-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XVVWVBUZVMCRMLA34RKXEPAGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会主动驳回对 Binance 的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份法庭文件显示，美国证券交易委员会自愿撤销了对全球最大加密货币交易所 Binance 的诉讼。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission voluntarily dismissed its lawsuit against Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, a Thursday court filing shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-sec-voluntarily-dismisses-lawsuit-against-binance-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMNHPPFLAFM75PM3OURIZKL3QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:15:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日求购困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4Z4NSZOCRKJVBWP4IKBC4KJYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 上调年度利润预期，本季度业绩因需求回升而向好]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 周四上调了年度利润预期，原因是库存损失减少以及新推出的 Milk Makeup 和 K-Beauty 护肤品牌等产品有助于拉动门店需求。【原文：Ulta Beauty raised its annual profit forecast after beating quarterly results on Thursday, as lower inventory losses as well as new launches such as Milk Makeup and K-Beauty skincare brands helped drive demand at its stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ulta-beauty-raises-annual-profit-forecast-posts-upbeat-quarter-resilient-demand-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUOXQEOF2RKC3JXDOSWNCBGXBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[男子在纽约被控绑架三周试图窃取比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[检察官周三表示，大陪审团已经起诉了一名 37 岁的加密货币投资者，他被指控在曼哈顿高档的 Soho 区绑架了一名商业伙伴长达三周，用电线电击他，并把他吊在楼梯上，试图让他交出比特币密码。【原文：A grand jury has indicted a 37-year-old cryptocurrency investor accused of kidnapping a business partner in Manhattan's upscale Soho neighborhood for three weeks, shocking him with electric wires, and dangling him over a staircase to try to get him to give up his Bitcoin password, prosecutors said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/man-charged-new-york-with-3-week-kidnapping-try-steal-bitcoin-2025-05-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZDZ4QSIFZPIRLCFT7XTX2LSAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 20:59:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>