<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:08:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:08:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官瑞士宝盛预计在减记 1.56 亿美元后不会再出现重大损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士宝盛银行首席执行官斯特凡-博林格（Stefan Bollinger）周三表示，预计不会出现额外的重大信贷损失，此前该银行在对其信贷组合的审查中披露了1.3亿瑞士法郎（约合1.5636亿美元）的净支出。【原文：Julius Baer does not expect additional major credit losses, CEO Stefan Bollinger said on Wednesday, after the Swiss bank revealed a net charge of 130 million Swiss francs ($156.36 million) in a review of its credit portfolio.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ceo-julius-baer-does-not-expect-additional-major-losses-after-156-million-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TZC73DRL3ZPG3BA47GVPAQ6R4Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:59:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯沃琪家族哈耶克面临考验，投资者力邀其加入董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，斯沃琪集团的主宰家族将面临一次不同寻常的考验，一位美国投资者将试图在这家瑞士制表商的董事会中占据一席之地，以求在其业绩下滑之后扭转颓势。【原文：The family that dominates Swatch Group faces an unusual test on Wednesday when an American investor tries to secure a place on the Swiss watchmaker's board, bidding to shake up its performance after a slide in its fortunes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/swatch-family-hayek-faces-test-investor-presses-join-board-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4S6MACDYVZPH3MC3KY3HFEELXE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:13:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际能源署称，关键矿产市场多样性不足可能会损害工业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际能源署（IEA）在周三的一份报告中指出，随着矿产市场的集中化，特别是在精炼和加工领域，以及出口限制的扩大，关键矿产市场正面临着令人痛苦的混乱风险。【原文：Critical mineral markets are at risk of painful disruptions after becoming more concentrated, particularly in refining and processing, and with the spread of export restrictions, the IEA said in a report on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/low-diversity-critical-mineral-markets-could-hurt-industry-iea-says-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6J6YBFPMJLZPFBE72YBFWXN4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，国际货币基金组织（IMF）戈皮纳斯敦促美国遏制财政赤字]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周三发表的一篇采访报道称，国际货币基金组织第一副总裁吉塔-戈皮纳特（Gita Gopinath）表示，美国财政赤字过大，需要解决 "不断增加的 "债务负担。【原文：International Monetary Fund First Deputy Managing Director Gita Gopinath said U.S. fiscal deficits are too large and the country needs to tackle its "ever-increasing" debt burden, according to an interview published by the Financial Times on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/imfs-gopinath-urges-us-curb-fiscal-deficit-ft-reports-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDQ6TCFLVJLVFMDGHMIOF3W5IM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：紧张的投资者令美元承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNC2MFPRHFPONME6HWOY7RIMIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:37:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易谈判之际，特朗普组织在越南的高尔夫俱乐部将破土动工]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的活动邀请函，特朗普组织及其当地合作伙伴将于本周三在越南首都河内附近为一个豪华高尔夫度假村举行奠基仪式。【原文：The Trump Organization and its local partner will hold a groundbreaking ceremony on Wednesday for a luxury golf resort close to Vietnam's capital Hanoi, according to invitations to the event seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-organization-break-ground-golf-club-vietnam-amid-trade-talks-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWXIOQPDVFJGLILOGLHKDJP54M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wi-Fi 产业与移动运营商就新增欧盟频谱发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[由 58 家互联网服务提供商和行业协会组成的一个小组周三敦促欧盟技术负责人亨娜-维尔库宁（Henna Virkkunen）为 Wi-Fi 服务释放更多频谱，从而引发了与为移动网络寻求相同频率的运营商之间的冲突。【原文：A group of 58 internet providers and industry associations urged EU tech chief Henna Virkkunen on Wednesday to free up additional spectrum for Wi-Fi services, setting up a clash with operators seeking the same frequencies for mobile networks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/wi-fi-industry-clashes-with-mobile-operators-over-additional-eu-spectrum-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPGG2LUE35JWRAMZ6FDO3UZOZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:15:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南部长访美期间与洛克希德-马丁公司和 SpaceX 公司举行关税会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南国家媒体周三报道称，越南贸易部长阮鸿献（Nguyen Hong Dien）在前往华盛顿与特朗普政府进行关税谈判期间，会见了Excelerate Energy、洛克希德-马丁、SpaceX和谷歌等美国公司的官员。【原文：Vietnam's Trade Minister Nguyen Hong Dien met officials of U.S. firms such as Excelerate Energy , Lockheed Martin , SpaceX and Google during a trip to Washington for tariff negotiations with the Trump administration, state media said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietnam-minister-meets-lockheed-martin-spacex-us-visit-tariff-talks-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGQIO2EHLJOV3EWRDUMFWRECKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普减税法案面临美国众议院共和党人罕见的隔夜压力测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的减税和支出法案周三将面临一次关键的压力测试，因为美国众议院的共和党人正试图克服关于削减医疗补助计划（Medicaid）和沿海高成本州税收减免的内部分歧。【原文：President Donald Trump's tax cut and spending bill faces a critical stress test on Wednesday as Republicans in the U.S. House of Representatives try to overcome internal divisions about cuts to the Medicaid health program and tax breaks in high-cost coastal states.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-tax-cut-bill-faces-rare-overnight-stress-test-with-us-house-republicans-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQK543THXZPLJN6VFJJXML25KQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普的攻击下，南非总统拉马福萨提出贸易协议作为回应]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非总统西里尔-拉马福萨（Cyril Ramaphosa）周三将前往白宫，执行一项危险的任务，即说服美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）与南非达成交易，而不是像他第二个任期开始以来所做的那样对南非进行斥责和惩罚。【原文：South African President Cyril Ramaphosa heads to the White House on Wednesday on a perilous mission to persuade U.S. President Donald Trump to make deals with his country rather than scold and punish it as he has done since the start of his second term.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/under-attack-by-trump-south-africas-ramaphosa-responds-with-trade-deal-offer-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEF6VWNLLNMYDEXYIAC2JFEBF4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:04:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 JIC 称，JSR 财务状况不佳不影响芯片制造整合目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[国家支持的 JIC 私募股权投资部门表示，其通过投资组合公司 JSR 推动日本芯片制造行业整合的目标不受光刻胶生产商财务业绩疲软的影响。【原文：State-backed JIC's private equity arm said its goal of driving consolidation in Japan's chipmaking sector through portfolio firm JSR is unaffected by weak financial performance at the photoresist maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/japans-jic-says-jsrs-weak-financials-do-not-affect-chipmaking-consolidation-goal-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5PQKVX54ZNR7H7UTDE5UUWTNE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 03:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢公司首席执行官表示，美国消费者对经济放缓感到不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士食品集团首席执行官在周三出版的一份报纸采访中说，美国消费者因经济放缓而感到不安，但雀巢正在恢复在美国的市场份额。【原文：Consumers in the United States are unsettled by a slowdown in the economy, but Nestle is recovering market share there, the CEO of the Swiss food group was quoted as saying in a newspaper interview published on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumers-unsettled-by-economic-slowdown-nestle-ceo-says-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZKNQ6ESSVJ25PN6TZU3NGESFM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 03:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国中西部大型咖啡烘焙商在关税冲击下提高价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙咖啡公司（Paramount Coffee Company）是美国中西部地区最大的咖啡烘焙商和经销商之一，该公司因美国关税而提高了价格。【原文：Paramount Coffee Company, one of the largest roasters and distributors of coffee in the United States' Midwest region, has hiked prices due to U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/large-us-midwest-coffee-roaster-hikes-prices-tariffs-hit-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJ3IE66JUFNC7GGHPYH5KR55JA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 03:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[进口商竞相将美国仓库变为免关税区]]></title><description><![CDATA[从中国向美国进口商品的公司正在抓紧时间将仓库改建成可豁免唐纳德-特朗普总统关税的设施，直到他们准备好销售商品为止。【原文：Companies importing goods into the United States from China are rushing to convert warehouses into facilities that are exempt from President Donald Trump's tariffs until they are ready to sell the merchandise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/importers-race-turn-us-warehouses-into-tariff-free-zones-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEUFBYMBTFJSBOM7FJMETIRQFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 03:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易协议和财政健康成为焦点，亚洲股市走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周三走高，由于投资者对主要发达经济体的财政前景和新的贸易协议缺乏进展仍然感到紧张，债券收益率上升抑制了风险偏好。【原文：Asian equities edged higher on Wednesday, with risk appetite contained by elevated bond yields as investors remained nervous about the fiscal outlook of major developed economies and the lack of progress on fresh trade deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KDN5KXB3VL3FAKPRSMBUHGCAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 02:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达称美国对华人工智能芯片出口管制 "失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）周三表示，美国对中国的人工智能芯片出口管制是 "失败的"。【原文：U.S. export controls on artificial intelligence chips to China were "a failure", Nvidia Chief Executive Jensen Huang said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-says-us-export-controls-ai-china-were-a-failure-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSXLVAXQE5LBBF5SL5JCD2555I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[收益率创纪录飙升后，日本超长期债券难获缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，日本长期国债拍卖结果不佳，收益率创下历史新高，而且未来几周还将有更多的国债出售。【原文：Long-dated Japanese government bonds saw little relief on Wednesday after a poor auction result sent yields to record levels and as more debt sales loomed in the weeks ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-super-long-bond-get-little-relief-after-record-yield-surge-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJ6M2BORCJI2XEGH4DECSU2WPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:44:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员关注特朗普税改法案和 G7 货币谈判，美元处于守势]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）未能说服共和党顽固派支持他的全面税收法案，美元汇率周三走低，延续了两天来兑主要货币的跌势。【原文：The U.S. dollar edged lower on Wednesday, extending a two-day slide against major peers, as President Donald Trump failed to convince Republican holdouts to back his sweeping tax bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-defensive-traders-eye-trump-tax-bill-g7-currency-talks-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6EK3VCFBBMU5HS2IDQKAKCBBI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国警告参与美国芯片措施者将承担法律后果]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国表示，它可能会对任何协助或执行美国建议公司不要使用来自中国的先进半导体的措施的个人或组织采取法律行动。【原文：China said it could take legal action against any individual or organisation assisting or implementing U.S. measures that advise companies against using advanced semiconductors from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-warns-legal-consequences-those-involved-us-chip-measures-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPNZD2JVORI77PBFGUL75DVLG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:31:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田为全球发布的 RAV4 SUV 进行改款，并首次推出新的软件系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田公司周三发布了经过全面改装的 RAV4，并表示这款紧凑型运动型多功能车将是丰田公司首款配备日本汽车制造商 Arene 软件开发平台的车型。【原文：Toyota unveiled an overhauled RAV4 on Wednesday and said the compact sport utility vehicle would be the first Toyota model to be equipped with the Japanese automaker's Arene software development platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/toyota-revamps-rav4-suv-global-launch-debuts-new-software-system-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3SGADS7FJP65BGTQLBDSHWRZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:06:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会指控 Unicoin 及其高管欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）周三指控加密货币公司 Unicoin 及其包括首席执行官兼董事会主席亚历克斯-科纳尼金（Alex Konanykhin）在内的三名高管发布虚假和误导性声明，从数千名投资者那里筹集了 1 亿多美元。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Wednesday charged cryptocurrency company Unicoin and three of its top executives, including its CEO and Board Chairman Alex Konanykhin, for false and misleading statements that raised more than $100 million from thousands of investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/sec-charges-unicoin-executives-fraud-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXRKTURZR5MJRDTH3QCL5WH3DI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:49:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据报道以色列准备打击伊朗核设施，石油上涨 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，以色列正准备对伊朗核设施实施打击，这引发了人们对冲突可能扰乱中东重要产区供应的担忧，油价周三跳涨逾1%。【原文：Oil prices jumped more than 1% on Wednesday after reports Israel is preparing a strike on Iranian nuclear facilities, raising fears that a conflict could upset supply availability in the key Middle East producing region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-1-reports-israel-preparing-strike-iranian-nuclear-facilities-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZFA72VGERMAVC4V2VGDSMOFKM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 4 月出口增长，对美出口下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的数据显示，日本4月份出口同比增长2%，但对美国的出货量却有所下降，这凸显了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策可能对脆弱的经济复苏造成的影响。【原文：Japanese exports rose 2% in April from a year earlier but shipments to the U.S. fell, data showed on Wednesday, highlighting the toll President Donald Trump's tariffs could take on the fragile economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-exports-rise-april-shipments-us-slump-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OLZ6DGX4ZNGTKTUYR2TFHRFRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 4 月出口同比增长 2%，对美出口下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务省周三公布的数据显示，日本 4 月份出口同比增长 2%，但对美出口下降 1.8%。【原文：Japanese exports rose 2% in April from a year earlier but shipments to the U.S. fell 1.8%, data from the Ministry of Finance showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/japans-exports-rise-2-year-april-shipments-us-slump-2025-05-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUQVXXYEYVOOZDSVKATS5SMPAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，韩国誓言支持生物制药和汽车行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国政府周三承诺为包括生物制药和汽车行业在内的主要出口行业提供更多支持措施，预计这些行业将受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面关税措施的冲击。【原文：South Korea's government pledged on Wednesday more support measures for key export industries, including the biopharmaceutical and auto sectors, which are expected to be hit by U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/south-korea-vows-support-biopharmaceutical-auto-sectors-over-us-tariffs-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZUC4XYA2NMW3HD6WSSGS764OE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥部长称运往美国的汽车将面临平均 15%，而非 25%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥经济部长马塞洛-埃布拉德（Marcelo Ebrard）周二表示，在墨西哥组装并出口到美国的汽车平均关税将为 15%，而不是 25%，理由是当地产品可享受额外折扣。【原文：Mexican Economy Minister Marcelo Ebrard said on Tuesday that cars assembled in Mexico and exported to the United States will face an average tariff of 15%, not 25%, citing additional discounts that local products benefit from.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mexico-minister-says-cars-shipped-us-face-average-15-tariff-not-25-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YLUN6PI6JNFNDV5YJGMNSJKXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:33:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[路透社 Tankan 民意调查：特朗普关税行动导致日本制造商信心下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社 Tankan 民意调查显示，与 4 月份相比，日本制造商对 5 月份的经营状况信心不足，而且由于美国不断变化的关税行动削弱了乐观情绪，他们预计未来三个月的信心将减弱。【原文：Japanese manufacturers were less confident about business conditions in May compared with April and they expect sentiment to weaken over the next three months as changing U.S. tariff action saps optimism, a Reuters Tankan poll showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japanese-manufacturers-less-confident-due-trump-tariff-action-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4DL3OS6KRJS7FEXLYUAUDI65M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚电力公司将从挪威国家电力公司收购 10 家可再生能源公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚国营石油公司 Ecopetrol 周二表示，该公司已与挪威国家电力公司（Statkraft）签署协议，收购 10 家风能和太阳能项目开发公司。【原文：Colombia's state-run oil company Ecopetrol said on Tuesday it had signed an agreement with Norway's Statkraft to buy 10 wind and solar energy project development companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/colombias-ecopetrol-buy-10-renewable-energy-firms-norways-statkraft-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4W73EKYBIVLJVGWKHTKQENEY6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 22:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[史诗游戏公司的《堡垒之夜》重新登陆美国苹果应用商店和欧盟 Epic 游戏商店]]></title><description><![CDATA[Epic Games 周二表示，该公司的视频游戏 "堡垒之夜"（Fortnite）在美国的苹果应用商店以及欧盟的 Epic Games Store 和 AltStore 上再次上架。【原文：Epic Games' "Fortnite" video game was available again in the U.S. on Apple's App Store and on the Epic Games Store and AltStore in the European Union, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/epic-games-fortnite-back-up-apple-app-store-us-epic-gamestore-eu-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6ZRGBYCIVPK3F2PYEUTHKUO2E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 22:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Wolfspeed 准备在数周内申请破产]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周二援引熟知内情的消息人士的话报道，半导体供应商 Wolfspeed 正准备在几周内申请破产，因为该公司正努力解决债务问题。【原文：Semiconductor supplier Wolfspeed is preparing to file for bankruptcy within weeks, as it struggles to address its debt pile, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wolfspeed-prepares-file-bankruptcy-within-weeks-wsj-reports-2025-05-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TGHNYPJBRNP3MT7GN2SDBJPKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 22:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>