<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 05:05:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 05:05:36 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行就未来加息对收益的影响做出估计]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行首次公布了对未来利率上调可能对其盈利产生的影响的估计，结果显示，如果短期借贷成本上升到 2%，日本央行将短暂蒙受高达 130 亿美元的亏损。【原文：The Bank of Japan released for the first time estimates on how future interest rate hikes could affect its earnings, which showed it will briefly suffer red ink of up to $13 billion if short-term borrowing costs were to go up to 2%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-produces-estimates-how-future-rate-hikes-affect-earnings-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26I2MHQOQNIM5KSNQFMVZOIDPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 03:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国比亚迪提供最高 11.5% 的年终折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车巨头比亚迪公司网站称，该公司的两款混合动力车和电动车将在1月26日前打折促销。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle giant BYD is offering discounts until Jan. 26 on two of its hybrid and EV models, according to its website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-byd-offers-year-end-discounts-up-115-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJ7ZWCW26BL5NGM4SRKGVRZW64</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对中国刺激政策持乐观态度，油价将迎来周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，油价变化不大，但由于人们乐观地认为经济刺激措施将促使全球最大的石油进口国中国经济复苏，油价本周将上涨。【原文：Oil prices were little changed on Friday but were set for a weekly rise amid optimism economic stimulus efforts will prompt a recovery in China, the world's biggest oil importer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-set-weekly-gain-china-stimulus-optimism-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R325YSVAVZPW5I6KIY5QIRIIGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[年末交易清淡，亚洲股市漂移，日元创 5 个月新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市震荡，美元持稳，在清淡的年末交易中，日元维持在五个月低点附近，因为投资者展望2025年，预计美联储将有节制地降息。【原文：Asian stocks wobbled on Friday while the dollar was steady, keeping the yen rooted near five-month lows in thin year-end trading as investors looked ahead to 2025, when the Federal Reserve is expected to be measured in its interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XHUXURB7VLN7IVFG4YBO2SG2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 02:01:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 11 月工业利润降幅放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的官方数据显示，中国 11 月份工业利润降幅放缓，政策制定者承诺加大支持力度，以支撑摇摇欲坠的经济复苏。【原文：China's industrial profits fell at a slower clip in November, official data showed on Friday, as policymakers pledged stronger support to prop up a faltering economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-industrial-profits-decline-slower-pace-nov-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVQQDKVM5NIZTMBN7RBOVN3JCQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 01:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元徘徊在 5 个月低点附近，日本央行的谨慎立场造成影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元兑美元汇率徘徊在五个月低点附近，因为美国联邦储备委员会的鹰派信息与日本央行对进一步收紧政策的谨慎态度形成了鲜明对比。【原文：The yen hovered near a five-month low to the dollar on Friday as the U.S. Federal Reserve's hawkish messaging contrasted with the Bank of Japan's cautious approach to further policy tightening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yen-hovers-near-5-month-low-bojs-cautious-stance-weighs-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SZFSKE6ZFPZHFI2NCKKQ3425Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 01:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[气候议程步履维艰，大石油公司在推动可再生能源方面出尔反尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲主要能源公司在 2024 年加倍努力开采石油和天然气，专注于近期利润，放缓--有时甚至逆转--气候承诺，这种转变在 2025 年很可能会坚持下去。【原文：Major European energy companies doubled down on oil and gas in 2024 to focus on near-term profits, slowing down - and at times reversing - climate commitments in a shift that they are likely to stick with in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/big-oil-backtracks-renewables-push-climate-agenda-falters-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBVIPMHKRNIGRKND34BE3SM4KM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 01:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西法院暂缓执行为承诺砍伐森林的大豆企业减税的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，巴西最高法院的一名法官暂停执行巴西最大的大豆生产州的一项法律，该法律将终止为那些同意不购买亚马逊雨林砍伐区大豆的企业提供税收减免。【原文：A justice on Brazil's top court on Thursday suspended a law from the country's top soy-producing state that would end tax breaks for firms following an agreement to not purchase soy from deforested areas of the Amazon rainforest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-court-suspends-law-cutting-tax-breaks-firms-with-deforestation-soy-2024-12-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5C6Q42CKZKGHAW43WTC5OUA3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首都通胀加速，加息前景不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，随着物价压力的扩大，日本首都的核心通胀率在12月份加速上升，这使市场对近期加息的预期保持了活力。【原文：Core inflation in Japan's capital accelerated in December as price pressures broadened, data showed on Friday, keeping alive market expectations for a near-term interest rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/inflation-japans-capital-accelerates-keeps-rate-hike-prospects-intact-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOIDPOF6JBOG3OMUXMPHA44LYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 23:50:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本电产宣布以 16 亿美元主动竞购牧野铣削公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本制造业巨头日本电产周五表示，无论目标公司是否批准，该公司都计划以比周四收盘价高出 42% 的溢价对牧野铣床发起要约收购。【原文：Japanese manufacturing giant Nidec said on Friday it planned to launch a tender offer for Makino Milling Machine at a 42% premium to Thursday's closing share price, with or without the target company's approval.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japans-nidec-announces-16-billion-tender-offer-makino-milling-machine-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4Q22KZN2NNBJMOTZMOMMNEQCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 23:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国媒体和金融问题专家理查德-帕森斯逝世，享年 76 岁]]></title><description><![CDATA[理查德-D-帕森斯（Richard D. Parsons）于周四去世，享年 76 岁。他是一位长期的银行高管，曾在时代华纳陷入困境时执掌这家通信公司，并帮助花旗集团渡过金融危机。【原文：Richard D. Parsons, a longtime banking executive who took the helm of Time Warner during a troubled time for the communications company and who helped Citigroup navigate the financial crisis, died on Thursday at age 76.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/richard-parsons-american-media-finance-troubleshooter-dies-76-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPJ7U4XWEFK23GTIHIF5EZMZLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 23:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利率走势将决定澳大利亚银行能否在 2025 年维持高估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，澳大利亚央行的利率轨迹及其对通胀的影响将决定澳大利亚银行股在经历了丰收的一年后，能否在2025年实现增长，而这一年的丰收已经让估值捉襟见肘。【原文：The Australian central bank's rate trajectory and its effect on inflation will decide if Australian bank shares can eke out growth in 2025 after a bumper year that has left valuations stretched, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/interest-rate-path-determine-if-aussie-banks-can-sustain-rich-valuations-2025-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJLJX4YIANNGVJBLDYYEKDXQ3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 22:33:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约将根据新气候法对化石燃料公司罚款 750 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据纽约州州长凯西-霍楚尔（Kathy Hochul）周四签署的一项法案，纽约州将在未来 25 年内对化石燃料公司处以总额达 750 亿美元的罚款，以赔偿对气候造成的破坏。【原文：New York state will fine fossil fuel companies a total of $75 billion over the next 25 years to pay for damage caused to the climate under a bill Governor Kathy Hochul signed into law on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/new-york-fine-fossil-fuel-companies-75-billion-under-new-climate-law-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AT73WEMTBRPBXEG4FV7H7LYAUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 20:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LL Bean 同意禁令，结束 Skechers 鞋类诉讼案]]></title><description><![CDATA[服装和户外用品公司 LL Bean 同意停止销售一系列休闲鞋，以解决 Skechers 美国公司指控其抄袭自己鞋子设计的诉讼。【原文：LL Bean, the clothing and outdoor gear company, agreed to stop selling a line of casual shoes to settle a lawsuit in which Skechers USA accused it of copying a design for its own shoes, which have sold in the millions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ll-bean-agrees-injunction-end-skechers-shoe-lawsuit-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GTNXWXMOFMRPPM6PLRFF6DU44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 19:23:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局建议采用标准化测试检测滑石粉产品中的石棉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周四在联邦登记簿上公布的文件显示，该局建议对含有滑石粉的化妆品进行标准化检测，以检测潜在污染物石棉。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration is proposing that cosmetic products containing talc should be tested using standardized methods to detect asbestos, a potential contaminant, according to documents posted on the federal register on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-fda-proposes-standardized-testing-detect-asbestos-talc-products-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCVQCS7S35NJPL7UQW3Y64AL2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 15:42:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[押注美国经济增长和通胀，美元走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周四走高，原因是人们预期美元明年将受到即将上任的唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）政府政策的提振，这些政策有望促进经济增长并提高通胀率。【原文：The U.S. dollar edged higher on Thursday on expectations the currency would be boosted next year by policies by the incoming Donald Trump administration that are expected to boost growth and lift inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-edges-up-bets-us-growth-inflation-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4T35MQDIFP6PH4B32QWDVCK2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 14:48:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 CATL 将寻求在香港上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[深圳证券交易所的一份文件显示，中国电池制造商CATL周四表示，它计划寻求在香港上市。【原文：Chinese battery manufacturer CATL said on Thursday it plans to seek a listing in Hong Kong, a Shenzhen Stock Exchange filing showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-catl-seek-hong-kong-listing-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EL7ULXRQHBLLJFZY2JTZO5UG44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 14:36:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数略有下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，新申请失业救济金的美国人数量降至一个月以来的最低点，这与美国劳动力市场降温但仍保持健康的态势相一致。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for jobless benefits dipped to the lowest in a month last week, consistent with a cooling but still-healthy U.S. labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-slightly-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4323Q7KOVPUPCFEFKZG6KCIDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 13:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[万事达卡称美国假日零售销售额高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[万事达卡（Mastercard）周四发布的一份报告显示，11月1日至12月24日期间，美国零售销售额增长了3.8%，原因是节假日期间促销活动密集，顾客转而进行最后一分钟购物。【原文：U.S. retail sales rose 3.8% between Nov. 1 and Dec. 24, as customers turned to last minute shopping due to intense holiday season promotions, a Mastercard report showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-holiday-retail-sales-come-above-forecast-mastercard-says-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXFICVWSDFM6ZBPUMTFL5AIKII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[期货在假日清淡的交易中走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣诞节假期结束后，美国股指期货周四在清淡的交易中走低，原因是投资者对其投资组合进行了评估，并希望在今年最后一个月从所谓的圣诞老人反弹中获得提振。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were lower on Thursday in light trading volumes after the Christmas holiday, as investors took stock of their portfolios and looked for a boost for the final month of the year from the so-called Santa Claus rally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-lower-holiday-thinned-trading-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXBHFHG6IVPCHJJ5ESSJ6AEJUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪承包商否认巴西当局 "类似奴役条件 "的说法]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国电动汽车生产商比亚迪的承包商锦江集团周四表示，巴西当局将其员工描述为奴隶的说法与事实完全不符。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle producer BYD's contractor Jinjiang Group stated on Thursday that the Brazilian authorities' portrayal of their employees as enslaved is completely inconsistent with the facts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-contractor-denies-slavery-like-conditions-claims-by-brazilian-authorities-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSWJ3DDJWFPYDPTCTX3I626CCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 08:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国新世界集团将与阿里巴巴国际公司成立合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国零售商新世界集团（Shinsegae Group）的关联公司易买得（E-Mart）周四表示，该集团计划与阿里巴巴国际公司（Alibaba International）成立一家合资企业。【原文：South Korean retailer Shinsegae Group plans to set up a joint venture with Alibaba International, Shinsegae affiliate E-Mart said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/south-koreas-shinsegae-set-up-joint-venture-with-alibaba-international-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV5QMQX7ENONBJEJO2ABR6MJ7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将 2023 年 GDP 上调至 17.73 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家统计局局长康义周四在北京举行的新闻发布会上表示，中国将2023年的国内生产总值（GDP）上调了2.7%，达到129.4万亿元人民币（合17.73万亿美元）。【原文：China on Thursday revised up its 2023 gross domestic product (GDP) by 2.7% to 129.4 trillion yuan ($17.73 trillion), the head of the National Bureau of Statistics Kang Yi said at a press conference in Beijing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-revises-up-2023-gdp-1773-trillion-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GDMYAMN3ZNXHL75Q4E4DPVMPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:38:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本新日铁修改收购美国钢铁公司的截止日期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本新日铁公司（Nippon Steel）周四表示，该公司修改了收购美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）的截止日期，并表示相信此次收购将保护和发展这家美国公司。【原文：Japan's Nippon Steel said on Thursday it revised the closing date for its purchase of U.S. Steel, expressing confidence that the acquisition will protect and grow the American company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/japans-nippon-steel-revises-closing-date-us-steel-acquisition-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6FPGZK7BBI2FMVD3GECBLGVHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元保持坚挺，亚洲股市节日大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲股市在假日清淡的交易中小幅上涨，延续了本周早些时候的涨势，但没有什么消息或数据能改变其走势，而美元则在两年高点附近徘徊。【原文：Asia shares rose slightly in holiday-thinned trade on Thursday, extending gains from earlier in the week with little news or data in the way to alter their direction of travel, while the dollar was perched near a two-year high.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5TQBUFGX5N4HJRWX6WT6GQI7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因希望中国采取更多刺激措施而走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四在清淡的假日交易中走高，原因是全球最大的石油进口国中国希望采取更多财政刺激措施，同时美国原油库存预期下降也为油价提供了支撑。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Thursday in thin holiday trading, driven by hopes for additional fiscal stimulus in China, the world's biggest oil importer, while an anticipated decline in U.S. crude inventories also provided support.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-edge-higher-hopes-more-china-stimulus-2024-12-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVKGSWBTURNCLIO5OFQGOZDR2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯财政部长称俄罗斯在对外贸易中使用比特币]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯财政部长安东-西卢安诺夫（Anton Siluanov）周三表示，在允许使用比特币和其他数字货币以对抗西方制裁的立法改革之后，俄罗斯公司已开始在国际支付中使用比特币和其他数字货币。【原文：Russian companies have begun using bitcoin and other digital currencies in international payments following legislative changes that allowed such use in order to counter Western sanctions, Finance Minister Anton Siluanov said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/russia-is-using-bitcoin-foreign-trade-finance-minister-says-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QK47K5BTENIS5BRXMNQVJAPMJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 11:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将欧盟白兰地反倾销调查延长三个月]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周三表示，将把对原产于欧盟的白兰地的反倾销调查延长三个月，少于之前指导意见允许的全部延长时间。【原文：China's commerce ministry said on Wednesday it would extend its anti-dumping investigation into brandy originating from the European Union by three months, less than the full extension allowed under its previous guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-extends-eu-brandy-anti-dumping-investigation-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSARECUQOZPAFLJ4Y2JN3MUVUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 07:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，台湾阻止了优步斥资 9.5 亿美元收购 Foodpanda 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周三援引台湾官方中央社（CNA）的报道称，出于反竞争考虑，台湾已阻止优步科技公司（Uber Technologies）以 9.5 亿美元收购外卖英雄（Delivery Hero）在台湾的 Foodpanda 业务。【原文：Taiwan has blocked Uber Technologies' $950 million purchase of Delivery Hero's Foodpanda business on the island because of anti-competition concerns, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing Taiwan's official Central News Agency (CNA).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/taiwan-blocks-ubers-950-mln-foodpanda-deal-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JV7PGUMKRLXFL3OE5MIV42YVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国骗子借鉴 "乌贼游戏 "向负债者下手]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国的 "鱿鱼游戏 "中，骗子们以奖金、债务重组和其他并不总是如约而至的计划为诱饵，欺骗经济不景气中的经济困难者。【原文：In China's take on Squid Game, fraudsters are preying on the financially distressed in a slumping economy with promises of prize money, debt restructuring and other schemes that are not always what is promised.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-tricksters-take-cue-squid-game-prey-indebted-2024-12-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LENXHRT37FKCVGVLALIS37PNC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>