<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:04:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:04:54 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称华为 Mate 70 手机热度减退]]></title><description><![CDATA[券商杰富瑞（Jefferies）表示，华为新推出的Mate 70智能手机在中国受到的消费者追捧正在减少，这可能会影响这家中国科技巨头今年的整体出货量，从而使苹果和其他中国品牌受益。【原文：Huawei is seeing less consumer excitement in China for its newly launched Mate 70 smartphone, which could impact the Chinese tech giant's overall shipments for the year to benefit Apple and other Chinese brands, brokerage Jefferies said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/huawei-sees-excitement-mate-70-phone-wane-analysts-say-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XALI4VUD3NNOFCSAXIKIIZP5Z4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:49:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，中国万达旨在创建规模高达 124 亿美元的基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，中国房地产巨头大连万达已告知一些投资者，该公司计划建立一个规模约为 500 亿至 900 亿元人民币（约合 69.1 亿至 124.4 亿美元）的基金，用于支付税款和债务。【原文：Chinese property giant Dalian Wanda has told some investors it plans to establish a fund of about 50 billion yuan to 90 billion yuan ($6.91 billion - $12.44 billion) to pay taxes and debt, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-wanda-aims-create-fund-up-124-bln-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XM3LFCGINBLKTC42WSYYYXRJXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将延长对部分美国产品的关税豁免至2025年]]></title><description><![CDATA[国务院关税税则委员会周五表示，中国将延长部分美国产品的进口关税豁免期限至2025年2月28日。【原文：China will extend tariff exemptions for the import of some U.S. products until Feb. 28, 2025, the Customs Tariff Commission of the State Council said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/china-extend-tariff-exemptions-some-us-products-2025-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRVKEG2K45MZDJX6JOVIROOFZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 03:50:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国房价下跌放缓后将于 2026 年趋于稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，随着一系列旨在扭转长达数年之久的房地产低迷局面的支持措施初见成效，预计今明两年中国房价的下跌速度将有所放缓，并在2026年趋于稳定。【原文：China's home prices are expected to fall at a slower pace this year and next, and stabilise in 2026, a Reuters poll showed, as a slew of support measures to reverse a years-long property slump start to bear fruit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-home-prices-set-stabilise-by-2026-after-slower-falls-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHAOL327FZIE7AKDODIWZKVSW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 02:47:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列-真主党停火协议遭破坏，油价涨跌不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于以色列和真主党相互指责对方违反停火协议，以及欧佩克+会议推迟举行，投资者正在等待欧佩克就其产量政策做出决定，潜在的供应风险再次出现，油价周五涨跌不一。【原文：Oil prices were mixed on Friday following a potential renewal of supply risk as Israel and Hezbollah traded accusations of ceasefire violations, and as a delay to an OPEC+ meeting left investors awaiting a decision on its output policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-mixed-amid-accusations-breaches-israel-hezbollah-ceasefire-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7X7YJSN53VINZPFAUEUBONI3ME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 02:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受日本央行加息押注影响，亚洲股市下滑，日元创四个月来最佳一周表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于当地通胀数据强劲，交易商倾向于日本央行即将加息，周五亚洲股市下滑，而日元则有望创下四个月来最好的一周。【原文：Asian shares slipped on Friday while the yen was aiming for its best week in four months as strong local inflation data had traders favouring an imminent rate hike from the Bank of Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWCKE4ZG5ZMDZHWLN23TMZMOJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 01:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 11 月制造业活动连续第二个月扩张：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[11 月份，中国的工厂活动可能连续第二个月温和增长，最近的一系列数据表明，大规模的经济刺激措施终于开始发挥作用，为世界第二大经济体的生产商带来了急需的动力。【原文：China's factory activity likely expanded modestly for a second straight month in November, adding to a string of recent data suggesting that a blitz of stimulus is finally trickling through and giving producers in the world's No.2 economy a much needed boost.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-nov-manufacturing-activity-seen-expanding-second-month-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3WIJQLLOFNDRBKEJKYFCOHPEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 01:43:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元飙升至 1 美元兑 150 日元，日本央行加息押注不断升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元跳涨多达 1%，创下六周新高，收于 1 美元兑 150 日元，此前东京的通胀率快于预期，支持了对日本央行下月加息的押注。【原文：The yen jumped as much as 1% to a six-week high at 150 per dollar on Friday, after faster than expected inflation in Tokyo supported bets for a Bank of Japan interest rate hike next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yen-surges-150-per-dollar-amid-growing-boj-rate-hike-bets-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDAOBDJCQFMCRDMNZ2L4D4LMHQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 01:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚临时批准维珍航空与卡塔尔航空结盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚竞争监管机构周五表示，已临时批准卡塔尔航空公司收购维珍澳大利亚公司 IPO-VIR.AX 25% 的股份，并批准这两家公司从明年 6 月起开始销售两国间的往返航班。【原文：Australia's competition watchdog said on Friday it had given Qatar Airways interim approval to take a 25% stake in Virgin Australia IPO-VIR.AX and for the duo to start selling return flights between the countries starting in June of next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/australias-competition-regulator-gives-interim-approval-virgin-qatar-airways-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2QSBSL5PNNPTFPCOWO3BSX6J4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 01:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[部长表示，渥太华必须确保特朗普理解加拿大石油对美国的重要性]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁对来自美国的进口商品征收25%的关税之后，加拿大政府的一位部长周四表示，渥太华必须确保特朗普政府了解美国和加拿大的能源市场是如何相互关联的。【原文：Ottawa must ensure the Trump administration understands how inter-related energy markets are in the U.S. and Canada, a Canadian government minister said on Thursday, following President-elect Donald Trump's threat to impose a 25% tariff on imports from the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ottawa-must-ensure-trump-understands-importance-canadian-oil-us-minister-says-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRO4X6BOTZOA7MYV6FNUG7CJJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应紧张和利率下调将推高澳大利亚房价--路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，受供应紧张和澳洲储备银行预期的适度宽松周期推动，未来两年澳大利亚的房价将稳步上涨。【原文：Home prices in Australia will rise steadily over the coming two years, driven by tight supply and an expected modest easing cycle from the Reserve Bank of Australia, according to a Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tight-supply-lower-interest-rates-lift-australia-home-prices-2024-11-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVBJFPHIVVL5NJQSGC266NA2BU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:21:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本首都核心通胀率回升，日元因加息押注而跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，由于物价压力扩大，日本首都的核心消费通胀率在11月份加速上升，并保持在央行2%的目标之上，从而使市场对近期加息的预期保持活力。【原文：Core consumer inflation in Japan's capital accelerated in November and stayed above the central bank's 2% target, data showed on Friday, as price pressures broadened, keeping alive market expectations for a near-term interest rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/core-inflation-japans-capital-accelerates-november-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NE36UGCWPRPQVOR7FTBTF5N5GE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 23:50:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚在世界上首次禁止 16 岁以下儿童使用社交媒体，引起了不同的反响]]></title><description><![CDATA[在悉尼，人们对禁令的反应不一。而孩子们则表示，他们会想办法绕过禁令。【原文：In Sydney, reaction to the ban was mixed. Children, meanwhile, said they would try to find a way around the ban.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-pm-albanese-says-social-media-firms-now-have-responsibility-protect-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZVTQGQFARJNZEIU7NUZZ77J2Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 21:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，今年感恩节迄今为止美国网络销售额增长约 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[Salesforce 周四的数据显示，美国感恩节假期前半段的在线销售额增长了约 4%，而去年同期仅增长了 2%，这是购物者正在享受零售商大幅折扣的一个新迹象。【原文：Online sales in the U.S. were up about 4% for the first half of the Thanksgiving holiday, compared to a 2% rise last year, Salesforce data showed on Thursday, a fresh sign that shoppers are lapping up steep discounts from retailers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-thanksgiving-online-sales-up-about-4-so-far-this-year-data-shows-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RM2Y6CM2QNPAZPX7BPKLKFD2HY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 21:28:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大反垄断监管机构起诉谷歌，指控其在广告业务中存在反竞争行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大反垄断监督机构周四表示，加拿大竞争局正在起诉 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司，指控其在网络广告领域存在反竞争行为。【原文：Canada's Competition Bureau is suing Alphabet's Google over alleged anti-competitive conduct in online advertising, the antitrust watchdog said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/canadas-antitrust-watchdog-sues-google-alleging-anti-competitive-conduct-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JAL4ECKHBNDBLD6UGZMDUU7P4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:34:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各国如何规范儿童使用社交媒体的行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚批准了一项针对 16 岁以下儿童的社交媒体禁令，这是世界上针对大科技公司最严厉的法规之一。以下是澳大利亚、欧洲国家和科技公司在规范儿童使用社交媒体方面所做的工作。【原文：Australia has approved a social media ban for children aged under 16, one of the world's toughest regulations targeting Big Tech. Here is what Australia, European countries, and tech companies have been doing to regulate children's access to social media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/what-countries-do-regulate-childrens-social-media-access-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAYOCZXIINNIZIRK6HPYEARDE4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 16:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登表示希望特朗普重新考虑对墨西哥和加拿大征收关税的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登周四表示，他希望当选总统唐纳德-特朗普重新考虑其对墨西哥和加拿大征收关税的计划，称这可能会 "搞砸 "与亲密盟友的关系。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden on Thursday said he hoped President-elect Donald Trump would rethink his plan to impose tariffs on Mexico and Canada, saying it could "screw up" relationships with close allies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/biden-says-he-hopes-trump-rethinks-tariffs-mexico-canada-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22SB2I26RFNSPOWC7CGZVDZJPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 16:35:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 "星链 "公司被勒令停止在纳米比亚的运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳米比亚通信管理局（Communications Regulatory Authority of Namibia）周四表示，已向埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的卫星互联网服务提供商 Starlink 下达了停止令，原因是该公司在纳米比亚无照经营。【原文：The Communications Regulatory Authority of Namibia said on Thursday it has issued a cease-and-desist order to Elon Musk's satellite internet provider Starlink for operating in the country without a license.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/musks-starlink-ordered-cease-operations-namibia-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X33O42X35JMCHIGTB6HUUEIRCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 16:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥总统称与特朗普通话时未讨论关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）周四表示，在一天前与美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普通电话时，她没有具体讨论关税问题，此前特朗普威胁要征收25%的进口税，这似乎违反了自由贸易协定。【原文：Mexico's President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Thursday she did not specifically discuss tariffs in a call with U.S. President-elect Donald Trump a day earlier, after Trump threatened a 25% import tax that appears to contravene a free trade pact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexican-president-says-did-not-discuss-tariffs-call-with-trump-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRGLWGJVARMQFOAGMQNVAYQYQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:05:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度竞争监督机构将调查谷歌游戏应用政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度竞争监督机构周四下令调查谷歌对其平台上真钱游戏的限制性政策，此前在线游戏平台 WinZO 投诉称该政策具有歧视性。【原文：India's competition watchdog on Thursday ordered a probe into Google's restrictive policies for real-money games on its platform, following a complaint by online gaming platform WinZO that called it discriminatory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/india-competition-watchdog-investigate-googles-gaming-app-policy-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DX3WU2BVJBNTJHA27OLZMH7E3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国恒大清盘人对恒大集团旗下公司提出清盘申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，房地产开发商中国恒大的清算人提交了一份针对天基地产的清盘申请，天基地产是风光之旅（Scenery Journey）发行的若干境外优先票据的担保人，而风光之旅也是该集团的成员之一。【原文：Liquidators of property developer China Evergrande on Thursday presented a winding-up petition against unit Tianji Holding, a guarantor for certain offshore senior notes issued by Scenery Journey which is also a member of the group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/liquidators-china-evergrande-file-winding-up-petition-against-cos-unit-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3V4OFFLMZMD7AZTDWR7234CPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:21:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伍德赛德首席执行官表示，将在 3 月前为路易斯安那液化天然气项目引入多个合作伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[伍德赛德能源公司（Woodside Energy）首席执行官告诉路透社记者，该公司预计在 2025 年第一季度对美国液化天然气项目进行财务审批时，将有几个合作伙伴加入其路易斯安那液化天然气开发项目。【原文：Woodside Energy expects to bring several partners into its Louisiana liquefied natural gas development by the time the company gives the financial go-ahead to the U.S. project in the first quarter of 2025, its CEO told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/woodside-bring-several-partners-louisiana-lng-project-by-march-ceo-says-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRKFBBOWYZIT5KVJV5JKBQIWAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 13:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚立法禁止青少年使用社交媒体后，还得想办法强制执行]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些欧盟国家和美国各州规定了社交媒体的年龄限制，但缺乏执行力度。【原文：Some EU countries and US states set age limits for social media but lack enforcement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/after-australia-legislated-teen-social-media-ban-it-has-figure-out-how-enforce-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5QUPOLM6NLZDBVSPTMCATIXQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:51:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚通过 16 岁以下儿童社交媒体禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[该法预计将于 2025 年 11 月生效，它设定了一些世界上最严格的社交媒体控制措施，并将迫使平台采取合理措施，确保年龄验证保护措施到位。【原文：The law, expected to take effect in November 2025, sets some of the toughest social media controls in the world and will force platforms to take reasonable steps to ensure age-verification protections are in place.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/australia-passes-social-media-ban-children-under-16-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUDIQCE37BPSDGVBZ5DWVIQXGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管特朗普发出关税威胁，美国银行仍看好墨西哥 "近岸外包 "带来的长期增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行墨西哥分行负责人表示，美国银行看好在墨西哥的发展前景，即使在美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁对出口到美国的产品征收关税之后，美国银行仍将从所谓的 "近岸外包 "趋势中获益。【原文：Bank of America is bullish on its future in Mexico, according to the head of the bank's unit in the country, and stands to benefit from the so-called "nearshoring" trend even after threats of tariffs on exports to the U.S. by President-elect Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-bets-long-term-growth-mexico-due-nearshoring-despite-trump-tariff-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCPKG4FVM5MFBDEKIFLDDYKYZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:11:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[信实集团美国分公司斥资 1200 万美元收购氦气勘探公司 Wavetech Helium 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[信实工业集团（Reliance Industries）周四表示，该集团的美国子公司以 1200 万美元收购了美国氦气生产公司 Wavetech Helium 21% 的股份，此举旨在扩大其低碳能源部门。【原文：Reliance Industries' U.S. unit has bought a 21% stake in U.S.-based helium production company Wavetech Helium for $12 million, the conglomerate said on Thursday, in a move aimed at expanding its low-carbon energy segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/reliances-us-unit-buys-12-mln-stake-helium-explorer-wavetech-helium-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HCN3ZVJZRK7ZDXNPLH5EBGL2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国人感恩节用手机购物，沙发成为购买点]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年感恩节，美国假日购物者大有利用小屏幕抢占先机的计划，零售商花了几周时间为他们做铺垫，在 "黑色星期五 "之前在网上兜售从电视、玩具到蓝牙扬声器等各种商品的折扣。【原文：U.S. holiday shoppers have big plans to use small screens for a head start this year on Thanksgiving Day, and retailers have spent weeks priming them, touting pre-Black Friday online discounts for everything from TVs and toys to Bluetooth speakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/sofas-become-points-purchase-americans-shop-with-their-phones-thanksgiving-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UC6QNB7CI5JLRMTNALOZ77LDRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上台一个月后，世界市场面临现实考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[11 月是唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）11 月 5 日赢得美国大选后胜负分明的一个月。【原文：November was a month of clear winners and losers from Donald Trump's Nov. 5 U.S. election victory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-graphic-graphic-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WESAHSGJO5ISTOJFD6F3FL5KG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:32:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国警告称，如果美国升级芯片限制，将采取 "必要行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[在有报道称拜登政府可能最快于本周公布新的出口限制措施后，中国周四警告说，如果美国升级芯片控制措施，中国将采取 "必要行动 "保护中国企业。【原文：China warned on Thursday it would take "necessary actions" to protect Chinese firms if the U.S. escalated chip control measures, following reports that the Biden administration could unveil new export restrictions as soon as this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/china-warns-necessary-actions-if-us-escalates-chip-curbs-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLZQIMUQ5JMCBE2NOYZK6WA2WQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称，联合信贷银行竞购 BPM 银行引发对劳动力的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行业的主要工会周四表示，联合信贷银行（UniCredit）对 Banco BPM 的竞购令人担忧该交易对就业的潜在影响。【原文：UniCredit's bid for Banco BPM raises concerns about the potential impact of the deal on jobs, the banking sector's main union said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/unicredit-bid-banco-bpm-raises-concerns-workforce-union-says-2024-11-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EV6T6X7PZJYDC7TAGBWO5ZZ6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>