<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:33:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:33:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，华特迪士尼将削减电视部门的工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周三援引知情人士的话报道称，华特迪士尼计划裁撤电视部门的部分工作岗位，以在业务萎缩的情况下削减成本。【原文：Walt Disney plans to eliminate some jobs in its TV unit to cut costs in an eroding business, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/walt-disney-cut-jobs-television-unit-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRYHLKDKXROVVALQZ5764A24YU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:21:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示反对人人拥有电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三表示，尽管亿万富翁、电动汽车制造商特斯拉公司首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）表示支持，但他反对每个人都拥有电动汽车。【原文：Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump said on Wednesday that he was against everyone having an electric car despite the endorsement of billionaire Elon Musk, the CEO of electric carmaker Tesla .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-says-he-is-against-everyone-having-an-electric-car-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWKOH34DX5LZTNMOYGYP2JGGE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司暂停飞往特拉维夫的航班]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周三表示，由于安全原因，该公司已暂停飞往特拉维夫的航班。【原文：United Airlines said on Wednesday it has suspended its flights to Tel Aviv due to security reasons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-suspends-flights-tel-aviv-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDY2DSV42VLQHHID7UFQX24CUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:03:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿克曼的美国潘兴广场撤出美国 IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[在对冲基金经理比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）在美国的新投资组合披露将筹集约 20 亿美元资金后一天，美国潘兴广场公司（Pershing Square USA）周三表示将撤回首次公开募股。【原文：Pershing Square USA said on Wednesday it was withdrawing its initial public offering, a day after hedge fund manager Bill Ackman's new portfolio in the United States disclosed it would raise roughly $2 billion in capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ackmans-pershing-square-usa-withdraws-us-ipo-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJQU72NLYZIKFBINEKSOUKMCJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席鲍威尔近期物价数据增强通胀缓和的信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）表示，近期的通胀数据正在增强央行的信心，即通胀压力正在重回2%的目标。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said recent inflation data is increasing the central bank's confidence that inflation pressures are moving back to the 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-recent-price-data-bolstering-confidence-inflation-moderating-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OUYHNQUVBLHFLS4S3MAZPAGLI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FOMC 不改变利率，但为 9 月降息创造条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三维持利率稳定，但开放了降低借贷成本的大门，最快将在9月份举行的下一次会议上降低借贷成本，因为通胀率将继续与美国央行2%的目标保持一致。【原文：The Federal Reserve held interest rates steady on Wednesday but opened the door to reducing borrowing costs as soon as its next meeting in September as inflation continues coming into line with the U.S. central bank's 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-fomc-does-not-change-rates-sets-stage-september-cut-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PF7HRL6EYNJDXNM6WDMULVGAVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:24:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员认为美联储将于 9 月开始放松政策，降息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，交易商继续押注美联储将在 9 月份开始缩减限制性政策，首先在当月会议上降息 25 个基点，并在 11 月和 12 月各再降息两次，此前美联储承认在实现 2% 通胀目标方面取得了 "一些进一步进展"。【原文：Traders on Wednesday kept bets the Federal Reserve will start dialing back on restrictive policy in September, starting with a 25 basis-point interest-rate cut at that month's meeting and delivering two more like-sized rate cuts in each of November and December, after the Fed acknowledged "some further progress" towards its 2% inflation goal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-see-sept-start-fed-easing-with-25-bps-rate-cut-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D33VZSTRX5N2FMRNAODMB32HNE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:18:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社：美国考虑对中国获取人工智能存储芯片实施新限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，美国正考虑最快于下月单方面限制中国获得美光科技（Micron Technology）和韩国SK海力士（SK Hynix）等公司生产的人工智能内存芯片以及能够生产此类半导体的设备。【原文：The U.S. is considering unilateral restrictions on China's access to AI memory chips such as those made by Micron Technology and South Korea's SK Hynix and equipment capable of making such semiconductors, as soon as next month, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/us-mulls-new-curbs-chinas-access-ai-memory-chips-bloomberg-news-says-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2WV6XBT5VN25OUK52RTSW7IKM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:13:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[警方称，特斯拉在完全自动驾驶模式下撞死西雅图摩托车手]]></title><description><![CDATA[警方称，今年 4 月在西雅图地区，一辆特斯拉 Model S 汽车在 "全自动驾驶 "模式下撞死了一名 28 岁的摩托车手，这至少是特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克寄希望于该技术的第二起事故。【原文：A Tesla Model S car was in "Full Self-Driving" mode when it hit and killed a 28-year-old motorcyclist in the Seattle area in April, police said, making it at least the second accident involving the technology on which Tesla CEO Elon Musk is pinning his hopes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-was-full-self-driving-mode-when-it-hit-killed-seattle-motorcylist-police-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJKCJ7QTJJMB3NUVW7VLS3LJPY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构坚持 5100 万个安全气囊气体发生器存在安全风险的决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，将坚持其最初的决定，即 13 家汽车制造商生产的 4,900 万辆美国汽车中的 5,100 万个安全气囊气体发生器存在严重的安全隐患。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said Wednesday it was standing by its initial decision that 51 million air bag inflators in 49 million U.S. vehicles built by 13 automakers pose serious safety risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-agency-stands-by-decision-51-million-air-bag-inflators-pose-safety-risks-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZVFDUV5V5NGNLFXHK33MFPGFA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利 Bending Spoons 收购文件共享服务 WeTransfer]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利应用程序开发商 Bending Spoons 周三发表联合声明称，公司已收购文件共享平台 WeTransfer。【原文：Italian app developer Bending Spoons has bought file-sharing platform WeTransfer, the companies said in a joint statement on Wednesday, as the Milan-based tech company presses ahead with a string of deals for software firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/italys-bending-spoons-buys-file-sharing-service-wetransfer-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQEPP45JHVKAVGBEZOVRW47IRQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:55:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CarShield 因欺骗性广告（包括名人广告）被美国联邦贸易委员会罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（U.S. Federal Trade Commission）周三表示，CarShield 已同意以 1,000 万美元的和解协议解决其车辆服务合同欺骗性广告的指控，并被禁止允许 Ice-T 等名人代言人进行不实陈述。【原文：CarShield has agreed to a $10 million settlement to resolve charges of deceptive advertising of its vehicle service contracts, and has been barred from allowing misrepresentations by celebrity endorsers like Ice-T, the U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/carshield-is-fined-by-us-ftc-deceptive-ads-including-by-celebrities-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EX4IXS6N3JNVBOFDG3KK23HEBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员将提出法案，要求联邦航空局开展新的安全工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院商务委员会主席玛丽亚-坎特韦尔（Maria Cantwell）表示，在联邦航空管理局对波音公司的监管行动引发质疑后，她计划于周四提出立法，要求联邦航空管理局采用先进的安全措施。【原文：U.S. Senate Commerce Committee chair Maria Cantwell said she plans to introduce legislation on Thursday to require the Federal Aviation Administration to use advanced safety measures after its actions overseeing Boeing have raised questions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-senator-propose-bill-require-new-faa-safety-efforts-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KKAIOAGS2VO3ZCUQGZ2SK4JODM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:26:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行的转变引发日元震荡，并导致对热门外汇交易的重新评估]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行将利率上调至15年来的最高点，使日元兑美元汇率飙升至3月以来的最强水平，并有望进一步走高，因为投资者正在重新评估利差交易，而这一度是今年最受欢迎的交易品种。【原文：The Bank of Japan's move to raise interest rates to their highest in 15 years has jolted the yen to its strongest against the dollar since March and left it poised for further gains, as investors reassess carry trades, once the year's favoured play.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/boj-shift-gives-yen-shake-causes-reassessment-popular-fx-trade-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y42FH2OWH5O4NB7EHN5YER2GHM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:17:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音新老板凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）拥有工程背景和航空航天背景]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）是前罗克韦尔柯林斯公司（Rockwell Collins）的老板，退休后执掌波音公司，他是众所周知的航空航天老兵，其工程背景与这家陷入困境的飞机制造商的前领导层形成鲜明对比。【原文：Kelly Ortberg, the former Rockwell Collins boss coming out of retirement to take the reins of Boeing , is known as an aerospace veteran with an engineering background that contrasts with the troubled planemaker's former leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/new-boeing-boss-kelly-ortberg-brings-engineering-background-aerospace-roots-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLBXZ3PFMZJLLLYHTUOT6JCCOY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西零售商不再具有战略意义，赌场对出售 GPA 股份持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国零售商卡西诺财务通讯部的一位高管表示，卡西诺不再将巴西 GPA 公司视为战略控股公司，并对出售其持有的 22.5% 的剩余股份持开放态度。【原文：French retailer Casino no longer considers Brazil's GPA a strategic holding and is open to selling its remaining 22.5% stake in the company, an executive at Casino's financial communications department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/casino-open-selling-stake-gpa-brazil-retailer-no-longer-strategic-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">726OTZY6IBJR3PEDVFGYO2PDAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉评级预测 2024 年美国将两次降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周三表示，预计美国联邦储备委员会将在今年 9 月和 12 月两次降息。【原文：Fitch Ratings said on Wednesday it expects the U.S. Federal Reserve to cut interest rates twice this year - in September and December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fitch-ratings-forecasts-two-us-interest-rate-cuts-2024-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MEE2LJ4GZLHREDEL3RID4Z57Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:51:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博格华纳第二季度利润因汽车零部件需求而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于汽车零部件供应商受益于持续的需求，博格华纳周三公布的第二季度利润超出华尔街预期，并上调了全年盈利预期，使其股价上涨了约 9%。【原文：BorgWarner beat Wall Street expectations for second-quarter profit and raised its annual earnings forecast on Wednesday as the auto parts supplier benefited from sustained demand, sending its shares up about 9%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/borgwarners-second-quarter-profit-beats-auto-parts-demand-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6B67C2EMVNAVFXZUZJKKDIPMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银就危机时期的抵押贷款成本起诉美国银行，索赔 2 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银周三起诉美国银行，要求赔偿 2 亿美元，称这家美国第二大银行拒绝承担与 2008 年全球金融危机前发放的高风险抵押贷款有关的法律费用。【原文：UBS sued Bank of America for $200 million on Wednesday, saying the second-largest U.S. bank refused to cover its legal costs related to risky mortgages issued before the 2008 global financial crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-sues-bank-america-200-mln-over-crisis-era-mortgage-costs-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5TZSS6O5BOFLJFJKP2V437IMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:42:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月待售房屋销量激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于供应量的增加和抵押贷款利率的一定程度放缓，吸引了购房者的观望，美国旧房购买合同在 6 月份大幅反弹。【原文：Contracts to buy U.S. previously owned homes rebounded sharply in June as an improvement in supply and some moderation in mortgage rates pulled buyers in from the sidelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-pending-home-sales-surge-june-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66R3DC53RFN7JOAM64TSX5F5UE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称现代汽车美国公司将召回超过49,000辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周三表示，现代汽车美国公司将召回4.9万多辆美国汽车，原因是安全气囊意外失效或展开。【原文：Hyundai Motor America is recalling over 49,000 U.S. vehicles over unintentional air bag deactivation or deployment, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-america-recall-over-49000-us-vehicles-nhtsa-says-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HDJ6QIDSFFL5DHN3GDDD5U3KFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apex 资本信托公司提交收购派拉蒙全球公司的标书，价格高达 430 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司 Apex Capital Trust 周三表示，该公司已经提交了一份竞争性报价，希望以高达 430 亿美元的全现金交易收购派拉蒙全球公司（Paramount Global）。【原文：Apex Capital Trust has submitted a competing offer to acquire Paramount Global in an all-cash deal for up to $43 billion, the investment firm said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/apex-capital-trust-submits-bid-acquire-paramount-global-up-43-bln-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2HMTD33VVMJ5JZOW6M6DN4WXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔在与 R2 的全球芯片专利战中赢得英国站的胜利]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔周三在与美国竞争对手 R2 半导体公司的全球专利纠纷中赢得了伦敦站的胜利，R2 半导体公司一直在寻求可能阻止英特尔部分芯片销售的禁令。【原文：Intel on Wednesday won the London leg of a global patent dispute with U.S. rival R2 Semiconductor, which had been seeking an injunction potentially preventing the sale of some of Intel's chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-wins-uk-leg-global-patent-battle-with-r2-over-chips-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFB4C2QDSJOMVPPZ4E2RX5FO6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:48:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[捷蓝航空购买可持续喷气燃料供纽约机场使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）周三表示，该公司同意从美国炼油厂瓦莱罗能源公司（Valero Energy Corp）的一个部门采购可持续航空燃料（SAF），由能源公司World Kinect分销，用于从纽约机场起飞的航班。【原文：JetBlue Airways said on Wednesday it agreed to procure sustainable aviation fuel (SAF) from a unit of U.S. refiner Valero Energy Corp , which would be distributed by energy firm World Kinect , for use in flights from New York's airport.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/jetblue-buy-sustainable-jet-fuel-use-new-york-airport-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIIMQPA3EFOZNFRCXGEPMOJTMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:34:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯对谷歌和 TikTok 的违禁内容处以罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[莫斯科法院新闻处称，俄罗斯周三对 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌和 TikTok 公司处以罚款，原因是它们未能遵守通信监管机构 Roskomnadzor 就违禁内容下达的命令。【原文：Russia fined Alphabet's Google and TikTok on Wednesday for failing to comply with an order from communications regulator Roskomnadzor over banned content, the Moscow courts' press service said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russia-fines-google-tiktok-over-banned-content-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2W4YERQQJLRXFSSBMXJLBYSKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:16:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司新任首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司任命前罗克韦尔柯林斯公司高管凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）为新任总裁兼首席执行官，让这位航空业资深人士负责扭转这家陷入困境的飞机制造商的局面。【原文：Boeing named former Rockwell Collins executive Kelly Ortberg as its new President and CEO, tasking the aerospace industry veteran with turning the struggling planemaker around.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/who-is-boeings-new-ceo-kelly-ortberg-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EBPT4KAEJO6XOBEPSVZORANA4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Garmin 第二季度营收超出预期，上调全年预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Garmin 周三公布的第二季度营收超过预期，并上调了全年业绩预期，主要得益于导航设备制造商在健身和汽车领域推出和升级的产品需求强劲。【原文：Garmin beat second-quarter revenue estimates and raised full-year forecast on Wednesday, helped by strong demand for the navigation device makers' product launches and upgrades in the fitness and auto segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/garmin-beats-second-quarter-revenue-estimates-raises-full-year-forecast-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ES3VI7VODFPM5P5QDSVVJXN75E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第二季度劳动力成本增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于私营部门工资增长放缓，美国劳动力成本在第二季度温和增长，这进一步证明通胀重回下降趋势，并可能有助于在 9 月份降息。【原文：U.S. labor costs increased moderately in the second quarter as private sector wage growth cooled, more evidence that inflation was back on a downward trend and could help facilitate an interest rate cut in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-labor-cost-growth-slows-second-quarter-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DKSDXBTW5JMNFE4RZSANC6ASAI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ADP 称美国 7 月私营部门就业人数不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[7 月份美国私营企业薪资增幅远低于预期，但这可能并不是劳动力市场继续逐步放缓的真实反映。【原文：U.S. private payrolls increased far less than expected in July, but that likely is not a true reflection of a labor market that continues to moderate gradually.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-private-payrolls-miss-expectations-july-adp-says-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHVDTB4SORJ3XKFT5EHQYRYJ7Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[万事达卡季度利润因弹性消费而大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[万事达卡第二季度利润增长 17%，原因是客户继续通过万事达卡进行大量消费，这使得这家支付巨头的股价在周三开盘前上涨近 3%。【原文：Mastercard's second-quarter profit rose 17% as customers kept up spending heavily via its cards, sending shares of the payments giant nearly 3% higher before the open on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mastercards-quarterly-profit-jumps-buoyant-spending-2024-07-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66642TSABRNGFNE6NVEKLKZ4BI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>