<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:37:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:37:25 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[机器人人工智能初创公司 Physical Intelligence 从贝索斯和 OpenAI 那里融资 4 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[物理智能公司（Physical Intelligence）是一家为机器人开发基础软件的初创公司，该公司周一表示，它已从亚马逊的杰夫-贝索斯（Jeff Bezos）、OpenAI、风险投资公司 Thrive Capital 和 Lux Capital 那里筹集到 4 亿美元的早期资金。【原文：Physical Intelligence, a startup that is developing foundational software for robots, said on Monday it has raised $400 million in early-stage funding from Amazon's Jeff Bezos, OpenAI, venture capital firms Thrive Capital and Lux Capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/robot-ai-startup-physical-intelligence-raises-400-mln-bezos-openai-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNN22FQTPBPH7HG3E4ATRFAXQQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:37:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密世界美国大选投机者玩转预测市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普显然是击败卡马拉-哈里斯的热门人选--前提是你相信预测市场，这是不屈不挠的加密货币投机者的最新领域。【原文：Donald Trump is a clear favorite to beat Kamala Harris - that's if you put your faith in prediction markets, the latest frontier for the indefatigable crypto speculator.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/cryptoverse-us-election-punters-play-prediction-markets-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2MRNRBJDNM5VCTAYEDVVX3CJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:47:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大选为美联储会议蒙上阴影，债券投资者尽量减少押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[在本周美联储政策会议召开之前，债券投资者在管理投资组合时保持着防御性的中性立场，而美国总统大选的悬而未决则让这次会议黯然失色。【原文：Bond investors are keeping a defensive but neutral stance in managing portfolios ahead of this week's Federal Reserve policy meeting, which is being eclipsed by the too-close-to-call U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bond-investors-minimize-bets-us-election-overshadows-fed-meeting-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3OIGYBZLRL7LO5XCDIRWSAPBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:44:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国立法者可能在明年初就工人权利问题向谢因提出质询]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一个议会委员会的负责人称，英国立法者最早可能会在 1 月份就工人权利问题向在线快速时尚集团 Shein 的高管提问，因为该集团可能会在伦敦上市。【原文：British lawmakers could question executives of online fast-fashion group Shein on workers' rights as early as January, ahead of a possible London listing, according to the head of a parliamentary committee.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/uk-lawmakers-could-question-shein-over-workers-rights-early-next-year-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UUYDXXA3RMKVDP5ZIBUMFI5ZY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:31:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员平仓特朗普交易，美元下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周一下滑，原因是投资者退出了因猜测共和党前总统唐纳德-特朗普更有可能在周二的总统大选中获胜而获益的头寸。【原文：The U.S. dollar slipped on Monday as investors exited from positions that have benefited from speculation Republican former President Donald Trump is more likely to win the presidential election on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-slips-traders-unwind-trump-trades-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QKRN4EG3NMF5I2M2CF64NCXFY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟官员表示，中国电动汽车价格协议需要与关税一样有效]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟未来可能的贸易负责人周一表示，与中国生产商就电动汽车最低价格达成的任何协议都必须与欧盟上周征收的关税一样有效和可执行。【原文：Any agreement reached with Chinese producers on minimum prices for electric vehicles would need to be as effective and enforceable as the EU tariffs that were imposed last week, the likely future European Union trade chief said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-ev-price-deal-needs-be-effective-tariffs-says-eu-official-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSHCQM54B5MXTMK4VFYLCTDZ2A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:26:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月份工厂订单连续第二个月下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[9 月份，美国制成品的新订单连续第二个月下降，企业的设备支出似乎在第三季度有所回落。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods fell for a second straight month in September, and business spending on equipment appears to have pulled back in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-factory-orders-fall-second-straight-month-september-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJ3IJKGWJFPRDFPUO7UBLTR4BM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:23:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特汽车 10 月份美国销量增长约 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车周一公布，受F系列卡车和混合动力车型需求的推动，10月份美国汽车销量同比增长约15%。【原文：Ford Motor on Monday reported an about 15% rise in U.S. auto sales during October from a year earlier, aided by demand for its F-series trucks and hybrid models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/fords-us-sales-rise-about-15-october-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPGIXF73LZPVPOUQGUHH43NOJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:44:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗从佩雷拉公司聘请顶级交易员杰夫-斯图特（Jeff Stute），加强医疗并购队伍]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，在 Perella Weinberg Partners 和摩根大通工作了三十年的资深投资银行家杰夫-斯图特（Jeff Stute）将加入花旗集团，担任副主席一职，主要负责北美地区的医疗保健兼并业务。【原文：Jeff Stute, a veteran investment banker with a career spanning three decades at Perella Weinberg Partners and JPMorgan Chase, is joining Citigroup as a vice chair focused on healthcare mergers in North America, according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-hires-top-dealmaker-jeff-stute-perella-bolster-healthcare-ma-ranks-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QGN62RDJ5JVPGIEFV4TIAXMOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:14:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，今年美国首席执行官因股价过低被解雇的速度加快]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一发布的一份报告显示，股价滞后的美国公司现在会更快地指责管理层并解雇其高层管理人员，但在过去十年中，寻找替代者的过程基本保持不变。【原文：U.S. companies with lagging stock prices are now quicker to blame management and fire their top executive, but the process of finding a replacement has remained largely unchanged for the last decade, according to a report released on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-ceos-fired-more-quickly-over-low-stock-prices-this-year-report-says-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ5ZLCQE3RIYZEXE7ZYUB47OC4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资公司 Stonepeak 将以 31 亿美元收购航空运输服务集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[航空运输服务集团（Air Transport Services Group）周一表示，该公司将被投资公司 Stonepeak 收购，包括债务在内的交易价值为 31 亿美元。【原文：Air Transport Services Group said on Monday it was being acquired by investment firm Stonepeak in a deal valued at $3.1 billion, including debt, sending the aircraft lessor's shares up 22.9% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/investment-firm-stonepeak-acquires-air-transport-services-group-31-billion-deal-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J7ZDDBQO6VMFFLHZK6BTTWHASI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:39:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福克斯公司因强劲的政治广告收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[福克斯公司周一公布的第一季度营收超出华尔街预期，原因是该媒体公司在美国总统大选前受益于其流媒体服务广告收入的增加。【原文：Fox Corp beat Wall Street expectations for first-quarter revenue on Monday, as the media company benefited from higher advertising revenue from its streaming service ahead of the U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fox-corp-beats-revenue-estimates-robust-political-advertising-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4FRMLO5KRLBVK3ZJIEMY5H6DQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空任命航空业资深人士 Gangwal 担任董事会主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国西南航空公司周一任命航空业资深人士 Rakesh Gangwal 担任董事会主席。【原文：Southwest Airlines on Monday named aviation industry veteran Rakesh Gangwal as the chairperson of its board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-names-aviation-veteran-gangwal-board-chairperson-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFDNGP3RZBIF5CXFX7BQBIKG7A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:43:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普获胜，欧洲防务迎来 "买跌 "机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[鉴于唐纳德-特朗普警告要缩减美国在该地区的军事支持，并迫使北约成员国将其国内生产总值的 2% 或更多用于国防开支，唐纳德-特朗普在白宫竞选中获胜被普遍认为是欧洲国防股的利好因素。【原文：A Donald Trump victory in the race for the White House is widely seen as bullish for European defence stocks, given his warnings to scale back U.S. military support in the region and force NATO members to spend 2% or more of their GDP on defence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/trump-win-buy-the-dip-opportunity-seen-european-defence-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNF3UXK2HBN77HZ5BOZHU436PU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:41:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于投资收入增加，Loews 第三季度利润大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Loews Corp 周一公布季度利润增长，得益于较高的投资收益和保险部门的强劲表现。【原文：Loews Corp reported an increase in quarterly profit on Monday, helped by higher investment income and strong performance in its insurance unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loews-third-quarter-profit-jumps-investment-income-boost-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGIRAYXFEFKL3CQ5GFIEYLWTOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金创下五周来最大单周流出记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 10 月 30 日的一周内，美国股票基金资金大幅流出，原因是投资者在周二的总统大选和周三的美联储政策决定前保持谨慎。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw substantial outflows in the week to Oct. 30 as investors exercised caution ahead of Tuesday's presidential election and a Federal Reserve policy decision on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-record-biggest-weekly-outflow-five-weeks-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOF722XOQ5OYFGGL7N323UFAV4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:23:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》第三季度新增数字用户数量减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约时报》公布的第三季度数字用户数量低于预期，抵消了广告销售的强劲增长。【原文：New York Times posted fewer-than-expected digital subscribers for the third quarter, offsetting strong growth in advertising sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/new-york-times-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQLRDLCXHNI53NIJEOIJ4OZF7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:13:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国和中国国内旅游需求拖累，万豪下调 2024 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国和中国国内旅游需求依然疲软，万豪国际集团周一下调了年度利润预期，导致其股价在盘前交易中下跌了 4.1%。【原文：Marriott International cut its annual profit forecast on Monday, as domestic travel demand in the U.S. and China remains weak, sending its shares down 4.1% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/marriott-lowers-2024-profit-forecast-us-china-domestic-tourism-drags-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUK4E3K5WJLKTL6DYLWQ7L73NA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片需求强劲，英伟达和台积电 10 月市值飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着越来越多的公司将人工智能整合到日常运营中，市场对其新型超级计算人工智能芯片的需求不断增加，英伟达公司（Nvidia）的市值在 10 月份领涨全球企业。【原文：Nvidia led a surge in market value among global firms in October, buoyed by unrelenting demand for its new supercomputing artificial intelligence chips as more companies integrate AI into their daily operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-market-data/global-markets-marketcap-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F72PQVUIA5NSFMQEA6EV4LRR4Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国民调和美联储利率决议笼罩市场，期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，与美国股指挂钩的期货价格走高，本周全球市场走势活跃，美国人准备选举新总统，而美联储将决定进一步下调基准政策利率。【原文：Futures tied to the U.S. stock indexes edged higher on Monday in an action-packed week for global markets as Americans gear up to elect a new president, while the Federal Reserve will decide on more cuts to its benchmark policy rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-gain-us-polls-fed-rate-decision-loom-large-over-markets-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XK2FCAN77BP5FHLVXOR7MSIW3U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大选前的谨慎情绪导致全球股票基金五周来首次出现单周资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至10月30日的一周内，投资者从全球股票基金撤出资金，原因是在周二美国总统大选和美联储本周晚些时候的政策决定之前，投资者持谨慎态度。【原文：Investors withdrew money from global equity funds in the week ended Oct. 30, amid caution ahead of Tuesday's U.S. presidential election and the Federal Reserve's policy decision later in the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PISPMIRXFZPYDNLGXJBBHGOVJQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟：苹果操作系统 iPadOS 必须符合欧盟《数字市场法]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周一表示，苹果公司必须确保其操作系统 iPadOS 符合欧盟《数字市场法》（DMA）规定的所有相关义务。【原文：Apple must ensure its operating system iPadOS complies with all relevant obligations under the European Union's Digital Markets Act (DMA), the European Commission said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-apples-operating-system-ipados-must-comply-with-eus-digital-markets-act-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DG7WPZAE2FPQ5HYPT75ANITXWA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:24:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标艾奥瓦州的异常数据和薪资水平带来困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDC6TL4MGBPTNPCPWA6CTFM7WQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:15:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）结束对 411,000 多辆福特汽车动力损失的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国安全监管机构周一表示，已经结束了对约 411,315 辆福特 SUV 和皮卡车动力损失的调查。【原文：The U.S. safety regulator said on Monday it has closed a probe into an estimated 411,315 Ford SUVs and pickup trucks over a loss of motive power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-closes-probe-into-more-than-411000-ford-vehicles-due-loss-power-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSFREITXJ5LWVL5HFZZY5W4IJA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:15:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税将重新安排贸易流向、提高成本并招致报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱荷华州农民鲍勃-海姆萨特（Bob Hemesath）担心，如果唐纳德-特朗普赢得周二的总统大选，并兑现迅速对中国商品征收 60% 关税、对所有其他进口商品征收至少 10% 关税的誓言，美国农业将付出沉重代价。【原文：Iowa farmer Bob Hemesath is worried that U.S. agriculture will pay dearly if Donald Trump wins Tuesday's presidential election and makes good on a vow to swiftly impose a 60% tariff on Chinese goods and at least a 10% levy on all other imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-tariffs-would-reorder-trade-flows-raise-costs-draw-retaliation-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZKB6IFP7JPSRKWWHGMDABI5DY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:11:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在不断变化的气候中，零售商转向天气战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛等大牌零售商正越来越多地利用分析技术来消除购物中最难以预测的业绩变量之一：天气的影响。【原文：Big-name retailers such as Walmart are increasingly using analytics to blunt the impact of one of the most unpredictable performance variables of shopping: weather.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/changing-climate-retailers-turning-weather-strategies-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2M5KNXBCOJOA3NU6UIGLO3PDXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对交易商而言，监管混乱将削弱特朗普的亲商倾向]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果换成其他任何一位总统，减少监管和降低企业税率的承诺都会让华尔街的交易机器垂涎欲滴。而唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）可能就任总统后，情况就不一样了。【原文：With any other president, promises of less regulation and lower corporate taxes would have Wall Street's deal machine salivating at the prospect of a feeding frenzy. Not so with a potential Donald Trump presidency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/dealmakers-regulatory-chaos-would-undercut-trumps-pro-business-tilt-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4P46XE3MXJPPHLM6CWHSBOBCII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音工人就可能结束罢工的工资协议进行投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音美国西海岸工厂的工人将于周一就一份改进后的合同要约进行投票，该要约可能会结束为期七周的罢工，并重新启动这家陷入困境的飞机制造商的喷气机生产。【原文：Boeing U.S. West Coast factory workers will hold a vote on an improved contract offer on Monday that could end a seven-week strike and restart jet production at the troubled planemaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-workers-vote-wage-deal-that-could-end-strike-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZERGE2QRRMU3AT2TAC2FLSERU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook 和 Nvidia 请求美国最高法院免于证券欺诈诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院将审议两家科技巨头--Meta's Facebook 和 Nvidia--在不同案件中抵御联邦证券欺诈诉讼的请求，这可能会使私人诉讼当事人更难追究公司的责任。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court is set to consider bids by two tech giants - Meta's Facebook and Nvidia - to fend off federal securities fraud lawsuits in separate cases that could make it harder for private litigants to hold companies to account.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/facebook-nvidia-ask-us-supreme-court-spare-them-securities-fraud-suits-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E76HLSBW75MG7D7DVKFESKVRJQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:03:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金的流动 高盛集团称，对冲基金 10 月份受到欧洲股市的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周一看到的一份高盛（Goldman Sachs）周五发给客户的说明显示，受更广泛的市场抛售拖累，专注于欧洲股市的对冲基金在 10 月份遭遇了一年多来最大的月度亏损。【原文：Hedge funds focused on European stock markets suffered their largest monthly losses in over a year in October, dragged down by a broader market sell off, according to a Goldman Sachs note sent to clients on Friday and seen by Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-stung-by-european-stock-markets-october-goldman-sachs-2024-11-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3DLSGTTRRN75CGMIFM5UWCC5U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:12:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>