<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 05:35:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 05:35:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价市场在英伟达数据公布前受到惊吓]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTPKZSOJTNK37JIJUZDLT2PMNY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 04:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北欧航空公司 SAS 完成重组，退出美国破产程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯堪的纳维亚航空公司 SAS 周三表示，该公司已完成重组，摆脱了美国破产保护程序。【原文：Scandinavian airline SAS has completed restructuring and emerged from Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings in the United States, it said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airline-sas-completes-restructuring-emerges-us-bankruptcy-proceedings-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VM6GU3F5DJO6NE7BFOVUHRTJSU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 04:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元走强导致黄金下跌，市场等待美国通胀数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，金价因美元走高而下滑，而投资者则在等待本周将公布的一份关键的美国通胀报告，以进一步明确 9 月份可能降息的幅度。【原文：Gold prices slipped on Wednesday as the dollar ticked up, while investors awaited a key U.S. inflation report due this week for more clarity on the size of a likely September rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-edges-down-stronger-dollar-market-awaits-us-inflation-data-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MOSPNPLDJBIRZISP2JYDXEWLME</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 03:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示，全球数千名用户的社交媒体平台 X 出现故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[据停电跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 称，社交媒体平台 X 在周二晚些时候出现停电，高峰时美国有超过 3.65 万份报告。【原文：Social media platform X experienced outages late on Tuesday, with over 36,500 reports in the U.S. at the peak of the outage, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/social-media-platform-x-down-thousands-users-downdetector-shows-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UV45MNYMCZPKLN5C36RBYMFNOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 03:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果公司服务部门裁员约 100 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，苹果公司已在其服务部门裁员约 100 人，其中负责苹果图书应用程序和苹果书店的团队裁员幅度最大。【原文：Apple Inc has cut about 100 jobs in its services division, with the biggest cuts in the team responsible for the Apple Books app and Apple Bookstore, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-cuts-about-100-jobs-its-services-division-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5N4GUHZ2NNE7IYMB6MB25CNZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 03:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达财报在即，股市止步于历史最高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，全球股市接近历史高点，下一步走势取决于芯片制造市场宠儿英伟达（Nvidia）的业绩，而英镑则创下了两年半以来的新高，因为交易商押注英国将在降息方面落后于美国。【原文：Global stocks were poised near record highs on Wednesday, with the next move riding on results at chipmaking market darling Nvidia, while sterling notched a 2-1/2 year high as traders bet that Britain will lag the U.S. in cutting interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMOCXOVH5JOVJHOXXLPBPSWN3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 02:22:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治和需求担忧引发投资者恐慌，石油反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者对利比亚和中东地区可能出现的供应损失感到担忧，同时又对全球燃料需求感到忧虑，石油在上一交易日大幅下跌后于周三反弹，结束了连续三天的涨势。【原文：Oil rebounded on Wednesday after a sharp drop in the previous session ended a three-day streak of gains as investors have whipsawed between concerns about potential supply losses from Libya and the Middle East and worries about global fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rebounds-geopolitics-demand-concerns-whipsaw-investors-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TT2C72TDANMGHDTIYZ3BBNV6AE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 02:18:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚伍尔沃斯公司在派发特别股息后股价上涨，利润符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，伍尔沃斯（Woolworths）股价攀升，此前这家澳大利亚杂货商宣布派发特别股息，并表示由于削减货架价格以与竞争对手科尔斯（Coles）竞争，其全年利润降幅与分析师预测一致。【原文：Shares of Woolworths climbed on Wednesday after the Australian grocer declared a special dividend and also said its full-year profit dropped in line with analysts' forecast as it slashed shelf prices to compete with rival Coles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/australias-woolworths-rises-after-special-dividend-profit-line-with-forecast-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SVFXYIWDTBOTZPDDDIKGJGJJNQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 02:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 7 月消费价格通胀率降至 4 个月低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于政府的电费退税带来了暂时性的拖累，澳大利亚 7 月份的消费者物价上涨速度为四个月来最慢，而核心通胀率则降至六个月来的最低点，这表明成本正在逐步降温。【原文：Australian consumer prices rose at the slowest pace in four months in July as government rebates on electricity provided a temporary drag, while core inflation dipped to its lowest in six months in a sign costs were gradually cooling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-consumer-price-inflation-slows-4-month-low-july-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRRVSHYHK5J3VFVWJF5XOJU6C4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 01:53:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场等待更多的美国利率线索，货币保持紧张区间波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元兑一篮子同业货币保持在一年多以来的最低点附近，英镑的交易价格略低于多年来的高点，因为市场聚焦于普遍预期的美国下月降息规模的线索。【原文：The U.S. dollar held near its lowest in more than a year against a basket of peers on Wednesday, with sterling trading just off multi-year highs, as markets focussed on clues to the size of a widely expected U.S. interest rate cut next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/currencies-hold-tight-ranges-market-awaits-more-us-rate-cues-2024-08-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7OJBCGKCVJLJB736QJ3MF2XQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 01:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西财政部长表示，他建议在 9 月前选出中央银行新行长]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西财政部长费尔南多-哈达德（Fernando Haddad）周二表示，他建议巴西总统在 8 月至 9 月间公布下一任央行行长的提名。【原文：Brazil's Finance Minister Fernando Haddad said on Tuesday that he suggested to the country's president that the nomination of the next central bank head should be revealed between August and September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-finance-chief-says-he-suggested-new-cenbank-head-be-picked-by-september-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IA7MIVU445L4BNFEPGHIJFIONU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 23:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HMD 与美泰合作推出芭比娃娃手机]]></title><description><![CDATA[生产诺基亚品牌手机的 HMD Global 公司表示，它已与玩具制造商美泰公司合作推出 HMD 芭比手机--一款复古设计的小巧粉色功能翻盖手机。【原文：HMD Global, which makes Nokia -branded phones, said it has teamed up with toymaker Mattel to launch the HMD Barbie Phone - a pint-sized pink feature flip phone with a retro design.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/hmd-launches-barbie-phone-partnership-with-mattel-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NIQBRSE7ZPBLET43ALTGJSHOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 23:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星 SDI 与通用汽车达成协议，将在美国建造价值 35 亿美元的电动汽车电池联合工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国三星 SDI 公司周三表示，它已与通用汽车公司达成协议，将在美国印第安纳州联合建设一家电动汽车（EV）电池工厂。【原文：South Korea's Samsung SDI said on Wednesday it has completed an agreement with General Motors to build a joint electric vehicle (EV) battery factory in the U.S. state of Indiana.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/samsung-sdi-signs-deal-with-gm-its-joint-ev-battery-factory-us-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HAI3C5NVAFPDDC32SXWREXUGYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 22:43:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币下跌 6.4% 至 58,777 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[格林尼治标准时间周二22时18分，比特币下跌6.4%，至58777美元。【原文：Bitcoin fell 6.4% to $58,777 at 2218 GMT on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-falls-64-58777-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35LIBVMTOJL2FFZMZBNF7GNQ7Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 22:29:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[淡水河谷矿业公司董事长称董事会优先选择首席执行官以避免市场噪音]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷董事会主席丹尼尔-斯蒂勒（Daniel Stieler）周二告诉路透社，董事会已将确定公司新任首席执行官的工作列为优先事项，以避免市场上出现更多有关潜在候选人的声音。【原文：The board of directors of Brazil miner Vale has prioritized the works of defining a new chief executive for the company to avoid further noises in the market regarding potential candidates, its Chairman Daniel Stieler told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/miner-vales-chairman-says-board-prioritized-ceo-choice-avoid-market-noises-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6U7A5GZVVK45BZS3NCOAKVDBM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 21:57:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国宏观经济、英伟达阴影挥之不去，亚洲看局部]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KLOOEU6355NFJNMIFHRCFTLSGM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 21:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛推出新的市场卖家服务，为假日促销助力]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛周二表示，它将为市场卖家提供服务，将他们的商品从亚洲直接运到美国仓库，并履行订单和管理来自任何电子商务网站的退货，这是它在假日季到来之前加强市场业务的一种新方法。【原文：Walmart said on Tuesday it would provide marketplace sellers its services to handle transportation of their goods from Asia directly to its U.S. warehouses, as well as fulfill orders and manage returns from any e-commerce website, in a new approach to bolstering its marketplace business ahead of the holiday season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-unveils-new-marketplace-seller-services-holiday-boost-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBLRZ2G37ZNEJP5FKZTBK3ARZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 21:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，TikTok 内容战略主管将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周二援引一份发给员工的说明报道，TikTok 的内容战略和政策主管妮可-伊科佩蒂（Nicole Iacopetti）将于 9 月 6 日离职。【原文：TikTok's head of content strategy and policy, Nicole Iacopetti, will leave the company on Sept. 6, The Information reported on Tuesday, citing a note sent to staff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktoks-head-content-strategy-leave-information-reports-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJ6PFS5QX5OAZEVCSX4ZLETKRI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 21:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺德斯特龙（Nordstrom）第二季度收入因销售活动的推动而增长，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺德斯特龙（Nordstrom）周二公布的第二季度销售增长好于预期，这主要得益于其关键的周年促销活动，尽管消费者在通胀压力下仍持谨慎态度，但该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨了 11%。【原文：Nordstrom reported a better-than-expected growth in second-quarter sales on Tuesday, buoyed by its crucial Anniversary Sale event, even as consumers remain cautious amid inflationary pressures, sending its shares up 11% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nordstrom-posts-higher-quarterly-sales-buoyed-by-demand-anniversary-sale-event-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBIKUREPPNPFNLK5JHZLOT6D5Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 20:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称转基因小麦可安全种植，但尚待试验]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部周二表示，阿根廷 Bioceres Crop Solutions 公司开发的一种转基因小麦可以在美国安全种植和培育。【原文：A type of genetically modified wheat developed by Argentina's Bioceres Crop Solutions may be safely grown and bred in the United States, the U.S. Department of Agriculture said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-says-genetically-modified-wheat-safe-grow-pending-trials-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIGZOAPYOFLFDGMTINOXNHBGXQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 19:53:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商品期货交易委员会：TOTSA TotalEnergies Trading 将为企图操纵市场支付 480 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商品市场监管机构周二勒令瑞士能源交易商 TOTSA TotalEnergies Trading SA 支付 4800 万美元的罚款，指控该公司试图操纵欧洲基准汽油期货市场。【原文：The U.S. commodity markets regulator on Tuesday ordered the Swiss energy trader TOTSA TotalEnergies Trading SA to pay a $48 million fine, alleging that the company had attempted to manipulate the market for European benchmark gasoline futures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-cftc-totsa-totalenergies-trading-pay-48-mln-attempted-market-manipulation-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EC2SGTOCVVMJHBCIJLH4ATG3VQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 19:48:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自动驾驶卡车公司 TuSimple 以 1.89 亿美元和解欺诈诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[TuSimple就一起诉讼达成了 1.89 亿美元的和解协议，该诉讼指控这家自动驾驶卡车技术公司通过夸大其安全记录和隐瞒三名内部人士对一家中国卡车运输竞争对手的控制权来欺骗股东。【原文：TuSimple reached a $189 million settlement of a lawsuit accusing the self-driving truck technology company of defrauding shareholders by overstating its safety record and concealing three insiders' control of a Chinese trucking rival.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/self-driving-truck-company-tusimple-settles-fraud-lawsuit-189-million-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AWFL4LLGWBJMDMW4YCBNQR6FFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 19:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国缉毒局将大麻重新分类听证会推迟到 12 月举行，大麻股下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国缉毒署（DEA）将大麻重新分类听证会推迟到美国总统大选后的 12 月 2 日，大麻公司股价下挫。【原文：Shares of cannabis companies sank on Tuesday after the U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) postponed its cannabis reclassification hearing to Dec. 2, after the U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/pot-stocks-fall-us-dea-pushes-cannabis-reclassification-hearing-december-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6E3T47N6ZVOVXCWTERBNTZP4CE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 18:49:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度 Bharti Airtel 宣布与苹果公司建立内容合作关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bharti Airtel 电信公司周二表示，该公司已与苹果公司合作，将在今年晚些时候为印度用户带来 Apple Music 和 Apple TV+ 的独家优惠。【原文：Bharti Airtel has partnered with Apple to bring exclusive offers for Apple Music and Apple TV+ to customers in India later this year, the telecom company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/indias-bharti-airtel-announces-content-partnership-with-apple-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4BVJ54QLRPEPDSQBJVDZOKAYA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 18:43:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥和纽约联储理事赞成 7 月下调贴现率]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二公布的会议记录显示，负责监管芝加哥和纽约联邦储备银行的董事会成员投票赞成在 7 月份将中央银行的贴现率下调四分之一个百分点。【原文：Members of the boards of directors overseeing the Chicago and New York Federal Reserve banks voted in favor of lowering by a quarter percentage point the central bank’s discount rate during July, according to meeting minutes released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/chicago-ny-fed-directors-favored-discount-rate-cut-july-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5Z4OGGHQ5OPNIXNAEZ6DGL6GE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 18:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IDC 上调全球智能手机年度出货量预期，看好 GenAI]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司 IDC 周二上调了对全年全球智能手机出货量的预测，理由是随着消费电子产品需求的复苏和人工智能功能吸引买家，上半年全球智能手机出货量增长强劲。【原文：Research firm IDC raised its forecast for full-year global smartphone shipments on Tuesday, citing strong growth in the first half of the year as consumer electronics demand recovers and artificial intelligence features attract buyers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/idc-raises-annual-global-smartphone-shipments-forecast-genai-optimism-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6NDPKK6P4ZNMBOO3UEI2EWP4LA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 17:50:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将关闭第三方创作者使用的增强现实工作室]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体巨头 Meta Platforms 周二表示，将关闭第三方创作者用于制作 Instagram 和 Facebook 定制特效的增强现实工作室，因为该公司将优先考虑包括人工智能在内的其他领域的支出。【原文：Meta Platforms will shut down the augmented reality studio that third-party creators used for making custom Instagram and Facebook effects, the social media giant said on Tuesday, as it prioritizes spending in other areas including AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-shut-augmented-reality-studio-used-by-third-party-creators-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSIZTDEUOJP4PAZZESAHRNFXHY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:52:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络安全公司称中国黑客利用漏洞入侵互联网公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家网络安全公司周二表示，一个中国黑客组织利用一个软件漏洞入侵了美国和国外的几家互联网公司。【原文：A Chinese hacking group exploited a software bug to compromise several internet companies in the U.S. and abroad, a cybersecurity firm said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/chinese-hackers-exploited-bug-compromise-internet-companies-cybersecurity-firm-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VW55GJ6G55NBTHRAWEOPHWJZTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:38:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩可能刺激创纪录的 3000 亿美元股票波动，期权显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股票期权市场的交易员们预计，Nvidia 即将发布的财报将引发这家全球最主要人工智能芯片制造商的股价出现超过 3000 亿美元的波动。【原文：Traders in the U.S. equity options market are expecting Nvidia's upcoming earnings report to spark a more than $300 billion swing in the shares of the world's most dominant artificial intelligence chipmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-results-could-spur-record-300-billion-swing-shares-options-show-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3DH4RWSGB5OQTCKS7UZ4GT6G2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场欢迎首席执行官的任命，淡水河谷股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[淡水河谷股价周二上涨，分析师和投资者对任命古斯塔沃-皮门塔（Gustavo Pimenta）从明年开始担任这家巴西矿业公司的下一任首席执行官表示欢迎。【原文：Shares of Vale rose on Tuesday as analysts and investors welcomed the appointment of Gustavo Pimenta as the Brazilian miner's next CEO, starting next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/vale-shares-rise-markets-welcome-ceo-appointment-2024-08-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7FIANRY64RPYJAKLFTIGLQOX2M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:12:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>