<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:35:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:35:41 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政状况令人担忧，美元将结束四周连涨势头]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周五走软，对欧元和日元的汇率将出现五周以来的首次单周下跌，原因是对美国财政健康状况恶化的担忧使投资者纷纷寻找避风港。【原文：The U.S. dollar was soft on Friday, poised to make its first weekly drop in five weeks against the euro and the yen as worries over the United States' worsening fiscal health sent investors scurrying for safe havens.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-set-snap-4-week-winning-streak-us-fiscal-health-worries-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5I7VD3NKCJNXDL5N7USY5G6DYI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:14:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市谨慎上扬，受挫的国债寻求支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的税收法案在下议院以微弱优势获得通过后，尽管债务忧虑仍挥之不去，但受挫的国债找到了买家，亚洲股市周五出现了一些试探性上涨。【原文：Asian shares made some tentative gains on Friday as beaten-down Treasuries found buyers after U.S. President Donald Trump's tax bill narrowly passed the lower house, although debt worries still lingered.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4HYXT2GTIBJNPLOEC7KQHDQWJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡央行官员：亚洲绝不能屈服于关税报复]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡金融管理局副总经理周五表示，亚洲经济体必须保持灵活，不能屈服于针锋相对的关税报复。【原文：Asian economies must remain agile and not succumb to tit-for-tat tariff retaliation, a deputy managing director of the Monetary Authority of Singapore said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asia-must-not-succumb-tariff-retaliation-singapore-cbank-official-says-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24DMPMWMZBKZXOFNPHWQ7IVWKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：一些美国银行探索通过联合稳定币涉足加密货币领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国一些最大的银行正在探讨是否联手发行一种联合稳定币。【原文：Some of the biggest U.S. banks are exploring whether to team up to issue a joint stablecoin, The Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/some-us-banks-explore-venturing-into-crypto-with-joint-stablecoin-wsj-reports-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNQMPWPZMZNJHPODMACJ55U3E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本超长收益率徘徊在纪录高位附近，原因是通胀和财政担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府债券周五保持稳定，此前一周波动剧烈，由于通胀和财政担忧削弱了债务需求，超长收益率创下历史新高。【原文：Japanese government bonds remained stable on Friday, after a volatile week in which super-long yields hit record highs as inflation and fiscal concerns sapped demand for debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-super-long-yields-hover-near-record-highs-inflation-fiscal-concerns-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6SEWWUX6RPHRHKLCQ2HWZDR5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚对中国网络商品的新一轮采购有助于抑制通胀]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球企业都在担心美国的天价关税会导致通胀率飙升，而在澳大利亚，中国廉价商品的转向有望缓解消费者和决策者对顽固成本压力的担忧。【原文：As businesses globally fret about sky-high U.S. tariffs reviving rampant inflation, in Australia, the redirection of cheap Chinese goods is expected to provide relief for consumers and policymakers worried about stubborn cost pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/australias-new-haul-chinese-online-goods-helps-tame-inflation-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OORZ5EELJMS3O5BYUK5UAJO3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:27:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元走强，欧佩克+产量可能增加，石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美元走强和欧佩克+可能进一步增加原油产量的影响，周五油价下滑。【原文：Oil prices slipped on Friday, weighed down by a stronger U.S. dollar and the possibility that OPEC+ will further increase its crude oil output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-falls-stronger-us-dollar-possibility-higher-opec-output-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHP5TSROXNIUDJFXY2C2BE3XUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:54:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，日本关税特使赤泽可能于 5 月 30 日前后访美]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士周五称，日本最高关税谈判代表赤泽亮世打算在 5 月 30 日前后访问美国，进行第四轮贸易谈判。【原文：Japan's top tariff negotiator Ryosei Akazawa intends to visit the United States around May 30 for a fourth round of trade talks, two sources familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-tariff-envoy-akazawa-may-visit-us-around-may-30-sources-say-2025-05-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJVINEGOZFK3VGGBWKMTSO75AU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本核心通胀率创逾两年新高，可能迫使日本央行年底加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，日本 4 月份核心通胀率以两年多来最快的年增长率加速增长，从而提高了年底前再次加息的可能性。【原文：Japan's core inflation accelerated at its fastest annual pace in more than two years in April, data showed on Friday, raising the odds of another interest rate hike by year-end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/japans-core-inflation-hits-more-than-2-year-high-keeps-boj-under-pressure-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4IJJ5QSXFNWTEVRDTJYUFKB74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:53:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，墨西哥石油公司将裁员 3000 多人，以节省超过 5.4 亿美元的开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社援引一份日期为 4 月份的公司文件报道，墨西哥国家石油公司 Pemex 计划裁减 3000 多名长期员工，并在此过程中节省约 105 亿比索（约合 5.434 亿美元）的开支。【原文：Mexican state oil company Pemex plans to layoff over 3000 tenured employees and save up around 10.5 billion pesos ($543.40 million) in the process, Bloomberg reported citing a company document dated April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/pemex-cut-over-3000-jobs-save-more-than-540-million-bloomberg-reports-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JG5ZMTTKZJNRFAAR6VEKPJAFVQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:22:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院称美联储是独一无二的，缓解了对特朗普能否解雇鲍威尔的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周四就唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇两名联邦劳工委员会成员的法律诉讼案作出裁决，其中的一句话暂时缓解了人们的担忧，即这些案件可能为特朗普随意解雇美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔打开大门。【原文：A U.S. Supreme Court ruling Thursday in a legal battle over President Donald Trump's firing of two federal labor board members contained a line that eased, for now, worries that the cases could open the door for Trump to fire Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell at will.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-supreme-court-says-fed-is-unique-easing-worries-over-trumps-ability-fire-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X7U5O323J5ISVDYQ5UNQMA7J4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:22:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银上调标普年底目标，预计 2026 年涨幅更大]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银全球财富管理公司（UBS Global Wealth Management）周四将 S&amp;P 500 指数的年底目标从 5,800 点上调至 6,000 点，并将 2026 年 6 月的目标定为 6,400 点。【原文：UBS Global Wealth Management on Thursday raised its year-end target for the S&amp;P 500 to 6,000 from 5,800 and initiated a June 2026 target of 6,400.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ubs-raises-sp-year-end-target-eyes-more-gains-2026-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PYFWJOPCWFLRNFJ3KXFN66A4YY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[为阿片类药物制造商普渡制药提供咨询的前麦肯锡合伙人被判入狱]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，麦肯锡公司的一名前合伙人因销毁与该咨询公司向普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）提供的关于如何 "加速 "阿片类止痛药奥施康定（OxyContin）销售的建议有关的记录而妨碍司法公正，被判处六个月监禁。【原文：A former McKinsey & Co partner was sentenced on Thursday to six months in prison for obstructing justice by destroying records related to advice the consulting firm gave Purdue Pharma on how to "turbocharge" sales of the opioid painkiller OxyContin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ex-mckinsey-partner-who-advised-opioid-maker-purdue-pharma-sentenced-prison-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PE3GEDUHGRJPNL42HHKEUKN3BY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，菲利普斯 66 洛杉矶炼油厂将于 12 月开始裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士周四透露，菲利普斯 66 预计将于 12 月解雇洛杉矶地区日产量 13.9 万桶炼油厂的大部分工人。【原文：Phillips 66 is expected to lay off most workers at its 139,000-barrel-per-day Los Angeles-area refinery in December, sources familiar with the matter said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/phillips-66s-los-angeles-refinery-layoffs-begin-december-sources-say-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SRMPU4Q4MVP6DBKA57FUKILY2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:19:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[YouTube 聘用前迪士尼资深员工负责体育和媒体业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的 YouTube 周四表示，该公司已聘请迪士尼的长期高管贾斯汀-康诺利（Justin Connolly）担任媒体和体育部门的全球主管，因为该视频服务正在进一步进军体育和传统媒体领域。【原文：Alphabet's YouTube has hired long-time Walt Disney executive Justin Connolly to serve as its global head of media and sports, the company said on Thursday, as the video service pushes further into sports and traditional media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/youtube-hires-former-disney-veteran-oversee-sports-media-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJ4W6MWSGNNK7DEBA4BE5ILDHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国专家小组对新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司意见不一，但官员称已看到前进的道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员周四告诉路透社记者，一个强大的国家安全小组在就新日铁竞购美国钢铁公司对国家安全的影响向唐纳德-特朗普总统提出建议时意见不一。【原文：A powerful national security panel was divided in its recommendation to President Donald Trump on the national security implications of Nippon Steel's bid for U.S. Steel , a White House official told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-panel-divided-over-nippon-steel-bid-us-steel-path-forward-seen-says-official-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTAEHUKSZVJZLA6A5KGG55PFJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国起诉被控勒索软件攻击的俄罗斯人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四公布了对一名俄罗斯人的指控，他被指控在十多年间领导开发和部署了感染数千台电脑的恶意软件。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice on Thursday unsealed charges against a Russian national accused of leading the development and deployment of malicious software that infected thousands of computers over more than a decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-indicts-russian-accused-ransomware-attacks-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLCNGCVKYZOVPBQOEW3EZG34TM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:55:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿克曼的对冲基金潘兴广场押注亚马逊，退出加拿大太平洋公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁投资人比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）周四告诉客户，他的对冲基金上个月买入了亚马逊股票，押注这家在线零售商的盈利将继续增长，因为唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税影响比消费者最初担心的要小。【原文：Billionaire investor Bill Ackman told clients on Thursday that his hedge fund bought Amazon shares last month, betting earnings will continue to grow at the online retailer as President Donald Trump's tariffs bite less than consumers initially feared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/ackmans-hedge-fund-pershing-square-bets-amazon-exits-canadian-pacific-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLI2LAK6G5MRTD27LS5ED3RZQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，OnlyFans 所有者正在洽谈以约 80 亿美元的价格出售给投资集团]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的消息人士告诉路透社，OnlyFans 的所有者 Fenix International Ltd 正在洽谈将这家色情驱动的公司出售给一个投资集团，估值约为 80 亿美元。
消息人士称，该集团由总部位于洛杉矶的投资公司 Forest Road Company 牵头。路透社无法确认该集团投资者的身份。【原文：OnlyFans owner Fenix International Ltd is in talks to sell the porn-driven company to an investor group at a valuation of around $8 billion, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.
The group is led by the Forest Road Company, a Los Angeles-based investment firm, the sources said. Reuters could not identify the investors in the group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/onlyfans-owner-talks-sell-investor-group-about-8-billion-value-sources-say-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMWMTSENTZJTRAOIPOJ2JVJA3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：紧张维持的抛售]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EX4KN74GJRIPPK23VIG5OQOM2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:13:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Workday 预测季度订阅收入冷淡，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，Workday 预测第二季度订阅收入与华尔街预期一致，预计由于经济不确定性，客户在其人力资本管理软件上的支出将减弱，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌 5%。【原文：Workday forecast second-quarter subscription revenue in line with Wall Street expectations on Thursday, anticipating weakening client spending on its human capital management software due to economic uncertainty, sending its shares down 5% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/workday-forecasts-lukewarm-quarterly-subscription-revenue-shares-fall-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6BBPU3TBRO4TK5Y6VTJS2VL6Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于特朗普税收法案中的 SALT 扣除，您需要了解什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[生活在房产税和所得税较高的州的富裕阶层可能会在唐纳德-特朗普总统的税收计划中得到一些减免。【原文：Affluent earners who live in states with high property and income taxes may see some relief in President Donald Trump's tax plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/what-you-need-know-about-salt-deduction-trumps-tax-bill-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNA3J5AUWFLELFQS6F6BX5NPJE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易商为欧佩克+价格战做好准备，美国原油存储需求激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据储油经纪商 The Tank Tiger 的数据，最近几周美国原油储油需求激增，达到了类似于 COVID-19 大流行时的水平，因为交易商们正在为石油输出国组织及其盟国未来几个月供应量的大量增加做好准备。【原文：U.S. crude oil storage demand has surged in recent weeks to levels similar to the COVID-19 pandemic, according to data from storage broker The Tank Tiger, as traders brace for a flood of increased supply in coming months from the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries and its allies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-crude-oil-storage-demand-surges-traders-brace-opec-price-war-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5CPO3KJJFO7BDGPZ4RZ3CUJWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构称内华达大盆地的地热能源可发挥更大作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国地质调查局（U.S. Geological Survey）周四表示，内华达州大盆地及邻近各州的地热能源可生产相当于美国目前电力供应10%的电力。【原文：Geothermal energy in the Great Basin of Nevada and adjoining states could produce electricity equivalent to 10% of the current U.S. power supply, the U.S. Geological Survey said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-agency-says-geothermal-energy-nevadas-great-basin-could-play-larger-role-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRIEKLBCTBKT3ICPS5QAHM4LP4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会撤销微软 690 亿美元动视暴雪交易案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）周四撤销了一项试图阻止微软以 690 亿美元收购《使命召唤》制造商动视暴雪公司（Activision Blizzard）的诉讼，称继续对这一关闭已久的交易提起诉讼不符合公众利益。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission dropped a case that sought to block Microsoft's $69-billion purchase of "Call of Duty" maker Activision Blizzard, saying on Thursday that pursuing the case against the long-closed deal was not in the public interest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ftc-drops-case-over-microsofts-acquisition-activision-blizzard-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2MTRBUNSJNLXLPM4PBUVJAEDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:46:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软件需求强劲，欧特克上调年度业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧特克（Autodesk）周四上调了 2026 财年的收入和调整后利润预期，预计各行业对其设计和工程软件的需求强劲，股价在盘后交易中上涨约 2%。【原文：Autodesk raised its forecast for fiscal 2026 revenue and adjusted profit on Thursday, anticipating strong demand for its design and engineering software used across various industries, sending its shares up around 2% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/autodesk-raises-annual-results-forecast-strong-software-demand-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N72ESA5VVBJT7JXX5ON7P2G52I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:44:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦贸易委员会撤销指控百事可乐价格歧视的案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周四撤销了指控百事可乐公司对沃尔玛实行价格歧视的案件，并批评前主席莉娜-汗（Lina Khan）匆忙结案。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Thursday dropped its case accusing PepsiCo of price discrimination that favored Walmart , and criticized former Chair Lina Khan for rushing the case out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ftc-drops-case-against-pepsi-alleging-price-discrimination-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVJSU6CI5ZLV3IXZLVF7YVLRQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:42:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受关税压力影响，罗斯百货撤回年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[折扣店运营商罗斯百货公司（Ross Stores）周四撤回了 2025 财年的销售和利润预期，并表示关税可能会影响其今年的盈利能力，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌 8%。【原文：Discount store operator Ross Stores on Thursday withdrew its fiscal 2025 sales and profit forecasts and said tariffs could take a toll on its profitability this year, sending its shares down 8% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ross-stores-withdraws-annual-forecasts-due-tariff-pressures-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLWMC4WLHRJHXAS7XRWVXB6G7I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:21:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪拉德百货公司就联名卡关系起诉富国银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[百货连锁店迪拉德百货公司（Dillard's）周四起诉富国银行（Wells Fargo），称该银行多次违反已经放弃的联名信用卡关系，给连锁百货公司造成了数千万美元的损失。【原文：The department store chain Dillard's sued Wells Fargo on Thursday, saying the bank repeatedly breached a since-abandoned co-branded credit card relationship, causing the department store chain tens of millions of dollars in losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dillards-sues-wells-fargo-over-co-branded-card-relationship-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TEVYXODFONMZNLS5KAWCAJ7KBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:13:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intuit 预计在税季提振后实现强劲的季度利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[Intuit 周四预计第四季度营收和利润将高于华尔街预期，这表明市场对其人工智能驱动的财务管理工具的需求不断增长，并使其股价在延时交易中上涨超过 5%。【原文：Intuit forecast fourth-quarter revenue and profit above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, signaling growing demand for its artificial intelligence-driven financial management tools and sending its shares up more than 5% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intuit-forecasts-strong-quarterly-profit-after-tax-season-boost-2025-05-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7FZD54Y6RLRFJZSDNO5AW62OQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>