<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:35:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:35:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[数字银行 NOBA 在斯德哥尔摩首次公开募股飙升 27]]></title><description><![CDATA[数字银行集团 NOBA 在斯德哥尔摩证券交易所首次公开发行股票，周五上市首日股价上涨 27%，公司估值达 445 亿瑞典克朗（约合 47.1 亿美元）。【原文：The share price of digital banking group NOBA rose 27% on its first day of trading on Friday following an initial public offering on the Stockholm bourse, valuing the company at 44.5 billion Swedish crowns ($4.71 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/digital-bank-noba-soars-27-stockholm-ipo-debut-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SD2NXRZGMBMHFLI4W5EHF4WREU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马因发动机启动器缺陷召回逾 19.6 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，宝马将在美国召回超过196,000辆汽车，因为发动机启动继电器可能会被腐蚀，导致过热和短路，增加起火风险。【原文：BMW is recalling over 196,000 vehicles in the U.S. as the engine starter relay may corrode, leading to overheating and short circuit, increasing the risk of a fire, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-recall-over-196000-us-vehicles-due-engine-starter-defect-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EFWXBNZPNMYXCBPYRK6L3K6MM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:18:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称中国 Momenta 考虑将 IPO 从纽约转移到香港]]></title><description><![CDATA[四名知情人士透露，中国自动驾驶汽车开发商 Momenta 正在考虑将其首次公开募股（IPO）地点从纽约转移到香港，在中美紧张局势加剧之际，选择在亚洲金融中心首次公开募股的中国公司越来越多。【原文：hinese autonomous driving developer Momenta is considering shifting its IPO to Hong Kong from New York, four people said, adding to a growing list of Chinese companies opting to debut in the Asian financial hub amid heightened U.S.-China tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-momenta-considers-shifting-ipo-hong-kong-new-york-sources-say-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4HEYLWE5RIBJEMEVHUWPJMDEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布对制药业征收关税后，罗氏指出美国的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士罗氏公司周五指出，该公司在美国的一个部门的新设施已于8月份破土动工，而且在唐纳德-特朗普总统最新宣布征收关税后，该制药公司已承诺在美国进行重大投资。【原文：Switzerland's Roche on Friday pointed to the fact that one of its U.S. units broke ground on a new facility in August and that the pharma company had pledged major U.S. investments after President Donald Trump's latest tariff announcement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/roche-points-us-plans-after-trump-pharma-tariff-announcement-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RATIL5O4TFKJDBUSZYTUP4F53A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前董事会成员预测，上田领导下的日本央行可能将利率上调至 1.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行前董事会成员樱井诚（Makoto Sakurai）告诉路透社记者，在行长上田一夫的任期于2028年初结束之前，日本央行可能会至少再上调基准利率四次至1.5%。【原文：The Bank of Japan will probably raise its benchmark interest rate at least four more times to 1.5% before Governor Kazuo Ueda's term ends in early 2028, former central bank board member Makoto Sakurai told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-likely-hike-rates-15-under-ueda-former-board-member-predicts-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOTXXJ7ZLVONPLB2G7K3MLDFGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:38:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易机构负责人称，随着美国需求增加，台湾寻求在印度扩大科技业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾的主要贸易机构负责人表示，由于美国的需求推动了台湾智能手机出货量的增长，台湾正寻求在未来五到七年内将其对印度的芯片和电子产品出口翻一番。【原文：Taiwan is seeking to double its exports of chips and electronics to India over the next five to seven years as smartphone shipments from the country ramp up thanks to demand from the U.S., the head of the island's main trade body said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-seeks-bigger-tech-presence-india-us-demand-rises-trade-body-chief-says-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGR3U2G33BOJHDUAA3T3MSLNMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威航空公司将增购 30 架波音 737 飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威航空班机公司（Norwegian Air Shuttle）周五表示，该公司已经行使了再购买30架波音737 MAX 8的选择权，从而使其确定订单总数达到80架。【原文：Norwegian Air Shuttle said on Friday it had exercised an option to buy an additional 30 Boeing 737 MAX 8, bringing its total firm order to 80 aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/norwegian-air-buy-an-additional-30-boeing-737-aircraft-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FCUMG5HNXFJLJIXT27J5RU6E2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙学生公寓吸引全球投资者，海外入学人数激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着西班牙成为愿意支付高价租金的留学生的首选目的地，全球投资者纷纷涌入供应不足的西班牙学生住房市场。【原文：Global investors are piling into Spain's under-supplied student housing market as the country emerges as a top destination for international students willing to pay premium rents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/spains-student-housing-draws-global-investors-overseas-enrolment-booms-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX3DCXP3SNNRTEUF3DT7AEBKD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克+有望进一步低于石油产出目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士和分析师称，自欧佩克+于4月开始增产以来，该组织已完成其目标额外石油产量的约四分之三，随着生产商达到产能限制，今年晚些时候这一水平可能会下降至接近一半。【原文：OPEC+ has delivered about three quarters of the extra oil output it targeted since the group started production hikes in April, and the level may fall closer to half later in the year as producers hit capacity limits, sources and analysts said and data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-is-poised-slip-further-below-oil-output-target-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QT6KM5TAIBLDHHQFVSYQ6VNAZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收更多关税后欧洲制药股下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普公布新一轮惩罚性关税（包括对品牌药品征收100%的关税）之后，欧洲最大制药公司的股票在周五早盘交易中下跌。【原文：Shares in Europe's biggest pharma companies fell in early trading on Friday, after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled a new round of punishing tariffs, including 100% duties on branded drugs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/european-pharma-shares-drop-after-trump-threatens-more-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DLUCSMGJZJO4ZJVSNE7APP5YFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称韩日将 "预付 "数十亿美元投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普坚称韩国将 "先期 "提供数十亿美元的投资，尽管首尔声称如果在没有保障措施的情况下满足美国的要求，韩国将遭遇金融危机。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump insisted South Korea will provide billions of dollars in investments "upfront", despite Seoul's assertion that it would suffer a financial crisis if it meets the U.S. demands without safeguards.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trump-says-south-korea-japan-will-pay-billions-upfront-investment-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFM7BPZLRVJI5E2MAULWHRAQJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 05:47:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prosus 旗下 OLX 将以 13 亿美元收购法国分类信息平台 La Centrale]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线市场 OLX 的所有者 Prosus 周五表示，OLX 将以 11 亿欧元（13 亿美元）的价格收购法国汽车分类平台 La Centrale。【原文：Online marketplace OLX will buy French motors classified platform La Centrale for 1.1 billion euros ($1.3 billion), its owner Prosus said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/prosus-olx-buy-french-classified-platform-la-centrale-13-billion-deal-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYVFCMUJB5J25CNAWTR7NPNLMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 05:14:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价股市一击即中]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFV5HW2TS5JURGXSNP46EQJCQI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[土耳其航空公司同意订购 225 架波音飞机，但尚需进行发动机谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[土耳其航空公司周五表示，决定从波音公司购买 75 架飞机，其中包括 50 架 B787-9 和 B-787-10 机型的确定订单和 25 架选择订单。【原文：Turkish Airlines said on Friday it decided to purchase 75 aircraft from Boeing , consisting of 50 firm and 25 option orders for B787-9 and B-787-10 models.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/turkish-airlines-agrees-225-boeing-aircraft-orders-subject-engine-talks-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IT43MUKP7ZPCBE2OCRWJ3JIN74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国计划规定国产芯片与进口芯片的比例为 1:1]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，特朗普政府正计划要求芯片公司在美国生产与其客户从海外生产商进口的数量相同的半导体。【原文：The Trump administration is planning to ask chip companies to manufacture the same number of semiconductors in the U.S. as their customers import from overseas producers, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-plans-mandate-11-ratio-domestically-manufactured-imported-chips-wsj-reports-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAXINZV2ZZK7TDU3GJ623RS24E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，近一半在欧美国公司预计经济联系将下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的一项调查显示，近一半在欧洲运营的美国公司认为跨大西洋经济关系将恶化，尽管这与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普第二个任期之初相比已有明显改善。【原文：Almost half of U.S. companies operating in Europe believe transatlantic economic relations will worsen, although that is a marked improvement from the start of U.S. President Donald Trump's second term, according to a survey published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nearly-half-us-companies-europe-expect-declining-economic-ties-survey-shows-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUPHDUCCJBMG7KLL7ZMIWTJQSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普新关税的相关信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[所有新职责将从 10 月 1 日起生效。【原文：All the new duties will take effect from October 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/what-know-about-trumps-tariffs-branded-drugs-furniture-other-goods-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWDXXBK5QJKZTGNKE235XUKXTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:46:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行将于 9 月 30 日维持利率不变，但可能在第三季度通胀之后降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，澳大利亚储备银行下周将把现金利率维持在 3.60% 的水平，所有经济学家都这么认为，因为劳动力市场依然紧张，政策制定者正在等待通胀缓解的确切迹象。【原文：The Reserve Bank of Australia will keep its cash rate at 3.60% next week, all the economists in a Reuters poll said, as the labour market remains tight and policymakers wait to see firm signs that inflation is easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rba-hold-rates-september-30-cut-likely-after-q3-inflation-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMDKYWYY75OUPDFEXJJ37JYXTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本将启动机制支持美国贸易协定下的 5,500 亿美元投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财政部周五表示，将在一家国有开发银行设立一个投资基金，以支持东京与华盛顿达成的关税协议中商定的 5,500 亿美元的一揽子投资计划。【原文：Japan's finance ministry said on Friday that it will set up an investment facility at a state-owned development bank to support a $550 billion investment package agreed in Tokyo's tariff deal with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-launch-facility-support-550-billion-investment-under-us-trade-deal-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQQ3AQGFGJMTHBLVCXGGIQ2KIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收关税后亚洲制药商股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁从10月1日起对进口品牌药品征收100%的关税，除非这些药品的生产商在美国的生产工厂已经破土动工，在此之后，周五亚洲制药商的股票大多下跌。【原文：Shares of Asian drugmakers mostly fell on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened 100% tariffs on imports of branded pharmaceuticals from October 1, unless their producers had already broken ground on U.S. manufacturing plants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/shares-asian-drugmakers-drop-after-trump-threatens-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6SS3J4IBVN4NMNSMDG6S3PURQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:52:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特斯库董事长福雷斯特加倍重视可再生能源，向特朗普发起挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚矿业公司 Fortescue 执行主席安德鲁-福雷斯特（Andrew Forrest）在接受采访时表示，人们对其脱碳相关产品兴趣浓厚，他对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于气候变化是世界上最大骗局的说法提出了质疑。【原文：Australian miner Fortescue is experiencing strong interest in its decarbonization-related offerings, Executive Chairman Andrew Forrest said in an interview, as he challenged U.S. President Donald Trump's claim that climate change is the greatest con job in the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/fortescue-chairman-forrest-doubles-down-renewables-challenge-trump-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4CJAW7SGVMFLGJKFUI3F26EGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元守住涨幅，关注支出数据为美联储提供线索]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国数据好于预期，抑制了美联储今年进一步宽松的预期，美元周五继续大幅上涨。【原文：The dollar held on to steep gains on Friday after better-than-forecast U.S. data dampened expectations for further easing by the Federal Reserve this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-holds-gains-attention-turns-spending-data-fed-clues-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3CWXENZWVODHG4MUR77RIEMXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯削减燃料出口，石油将创三个月来最大单周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于乌克兰对俄罗斯能源基础设施的袭击促使莫斯科限制燃料出口，并接近削减原油产量，油价周五上扬，有望创下自6月初以来的最大涨幅。【原文：Oil prices edged up on Friday, on track to rise at their steepest rate since early June as Ukraine's attacks on Russia's energy infrastructure push Moscow to restrict fuel exports and close to cutting crude output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-set-biggest-weekly-gain-three-months-russia-cuts-fuel-exports-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMBTLZAMRZJI3FBDLNFFEXPTSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司控制人结束与 Azul 的潜在合并谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gol 航空公司周四表示，其控股股东 Abra 集团已通知同行 Azul 公司，决定终止两家巴西航空公司之间潜在的业务合并谈判。【原文：Airline Gol said on Thursday that its controlling shareholder, Abra Group, has notified peer Azul of its decision to end talks for a potential business combination between the two Brazilian carriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazilian-airline-gols-controller-ends-talks-potential-merger-with-azul-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ4JABFZHNMZLEU33B2CAQLUBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征新关税，美联储减息押注解除，股市陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）公布新一轮惩罚性关税之后，以及在经济数据强于预期之后交易商减少了对美国大幅降息的押注之后，周五亚洲股市开局不稳。【原文：Asia shares got off to a shaky start on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled a fresh round of punishing tariffs and as traders pared bets of sharp U.S. rate cuts following stronger-than-expected economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HKY3T6HSNP4ZMH52N24BZUAFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:26:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Perpetua Resources 正与嘉能可（Glencore）等商谈美国锑矿加工事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[Perpetua Resources公司周四表示，该公司正在与嘉能可（Glencore）、创富集团（Trafigura）（TRAFGF.UL）和其他公司就在美国提炼锑的合作事宜进行谈判，这是为促进西方国家对中国封锁出口的一种重要矿产的供应所做努力的一部分。【原文：Perpetua Resources said on Thursday it is in talks with Glencore , Trafigura (TRAFGF.UL) and others about a partnership to refine antimony in the U.S., part of a push to boost Western supplies of a critical mineral whose exports China has blocked.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/perpetua-resources-talks-with-glencore-others-us-antimony-processing-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYWMA3HZFZOVBDKB4532HEFMDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国计划全天候外汇交易，美国谈判打击韩元]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国总统誓言开放货币市场进行全天候交易，为外国投资者提供更便利的准入条件，因为韩国正努力提振国内股市，同时美国贸易谈判停滞不前也对韩元构成了压力。【原文：South Korea's president vowed to open its currency market for around-the-clock trading, giving easier access to foreign investors as the country seeks to boost the domestic stock market and as stalled U.S. trade talks weigh on the won.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-plans-open-around-the-clock-fx-trade-president-says-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EAJL2MAEAJNEROMAOZPSUUQU6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:45:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国监管机构调查公司发布加密货币公告前的股票走势]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国监管机构已经检查了一些公司在宣布融资购买加密货币计划之前股价的剧烈波动，以寻找潜在的内幕交易和信息披露违规迹象。【原文：U.S. regulators have examined sharp movements in the stock prices of companies before they announced plans to raise money to buy cryptocurrency for signs of potential insider trading and disclosure violations, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-regulators-probe-stock-moves-before-companies-made-crypto-treasury-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLCILK2V3JIJ7H4JRTRNGFFV6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布自 10 月 1 日起对进口品牌或专利药品征收 100%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美国将从10月1日起对进口品牌或专利药品征收100%的关税，除非制药公司在美国建厂。【原文：The United States will impose a 100% tariff on imports of branded or patented pharmaceutical products from October 1, unless a pharmaceutical company is building a manufacturing plant in the U.S., President Donald Trump said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-announces-100-tariff-imports-branded-or-patented-pharmaceuticals-october-1-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XAHE3YJNRRPV7BXALBCAKSZ3JE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:39:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[条款书显示，中国地平线机器人公司通过香港增发配股融资约 8.21 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份条款书显示，中国自动驾驶解决方案供应商地平线机器人公司（Horizon Robotics）通过香港增发配售筹集了约 8.21 亿美元。【原文：Chinese autonomous driving solutions provider Horizon Robotics has raised about $821 million through a Hong Kong top-up placement, according to a term sheet seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-horizon-robotics-raises-about-821-million-via-hong-kong-top-up-share-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JH2SGQ3L3ZPSRCL5U2S3RLUIME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>