<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:37:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:37:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标到底谁需要政府？]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MG2W63HFBROARK7GKVZVJCN6FA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:33:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国需求强劲，丰田 8 月销量连续第八个月增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周一称，由于美国市场对其部分混合动力车型的需求持续强劲，抵消了日本市场的疲软，8月份全球销量连续第八个月增长。【原文：Toyota Motor said on Monday its global sales grew for an eighth straight month in August, as continuing strong demand for some of its hybrid models in the United States offset a weaker performance in Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyotas-august-sales-grow-eighth-month-robust-us-demand-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5ZB3B34PRNVNLJZSFS7SC6GA4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:31:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》称，美国证券交易委员会主席阿特金斯誓言快速废除公司季度报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（SEC）主席保罗-阿特金斯（Paul Atkins）周一在为《金融时报》撰写的一篇评论文章中写道，他承诺将追求最低 "剂量 "的监管，并快速推进唐纳德-特朗普总统提出的取消企业季度报告的建议，让企业可以选择每半年报告一次。【原文：U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Paul Atkins pledged to pursue a minimum "dose" of regulation and fast-track President Donald Trump's proposal to scrap quarterly corporate reporting, giving companies the option to report on a semi-annual basis, he wrote in an opinion piece for the Financial Times on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-sec-chairman-atkins-vows-fast-track-scrapping-quarterly-corporate-reports-ft-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QX2OIMKQMNNPPAH26VITGNPMOY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:21:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南华早报》报道：中国比亚迪预计出口将占 2025 年销售额的 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《南华早报》周一报道，中国电动汽车制造商比亚迪公司预计，在新车型推出的推动下，今年出口将占其全球销量的20%左右。【原文：Chinese electric vehicle maker BYD Co forecast exports will make up about 20% of its global sales this year helped by new model launches, the South China Morning Post reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-byd-forecasts-exports-top-20-2025-sales-scmp-reports-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YJKGKIGLIBMW5CGEPC5EO56KKQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚电信公司 Optus 再次发生紧急电话故障]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚电信公司 Optus 周一表示，在悉尼南部地区发生紧急电话中断事件 10 天后，又发生了更大范围的中断事件，该公司称，由于客户无法得到及时救助，可能已造成 4 人死亡。【原文：Australian telco Optus said on Monday it had suffered an emergency call outage in an area south of Sydney, 10 days after a broader disruption that it said had probably caused four deaths when customers were unable to get timely aid.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australian-telco-optus-suffers-fresh-emergency-call-outage-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSPWDIDPBBJOFPB3JXLNH73FKA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据公布前美元处于守势，美国政府面临关门风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，在一系列美国经济数据公布之前，美元处于守势，这些数据可能会进一步明确美联储的利率路径，而美国政府停摆的风险日益增加也成为焦点。【原文：The dollar was on the defensive on Monday ahead of a slew of U.S. economic releases that could provide further clarity on the Federal Reserve's rate path, while the growing risk of a government shutdown there also came into sharp focus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-defensive-before-data-releases-risk-us-government-shutdown-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZSZ6ASQM5JZXP4VXYXQRDNXS4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行董事会的鹰派灵活性降低了 10 月加息的门槛]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行在本月的政策会议上出现了鹰派董事会的分裂，这增加了其鸽派行长上田一夫加快加息步伐的压力，从而提高了下一次紧缩政策最快可能在10月份出台的前景。【原文：A hawkish board split at the Bank of Japan's policy meeting this month has increased pressure on its dovish governor Kazuo Ueda to move faster on interest rate hikes, raising the prospect the next tightening could come as soon as October.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-boards-hawkish-flex-lowers-bar-an-october-rate-hike-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O75TLALV5JO27IG7GM73HHM6XY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府面临关门风险，亚洲股市表现谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲股市谨慎开盘，因为投资者担心美国政府可能关门，进而推迟公布九月份的就业报告和其他一系列关键数据。【原文：Share markets got off to a cautious start in Asia on Monday as investors braced for a possible shutdown of the U.S. government, which would in turn delay publication of the September payrolls report and a raft of other key data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4T3FTED2JLQPDA2ORQELW2JZA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[库尔德斯坦恢复原油出口，欧佩克+计划提高产量，石油价格下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[伊拉克库尔德斯坦地区周末恢复了经由土耳其的原油出口，欧佩克+计划在11月再次提高石油产量，从而增加了全球供应，油价周一下滑近1%。【原文：Oil prices slipped nearly 1% on Monday after Iraq's Kurdistan region resumed crude oil exports via Turkey over the weekend and as OPEC+ plans another oil output hike in November, adding to global supplies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-slips-kurdistan-crude-exports-resume-opec-plans-output-hike-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIDWZQX3VFPAPGAUZGO5JVW7GM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国数据中心火灾后恢复部分服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国安全部长 Yun Hojung 周一表示，在一个数据中心发生火灾导致网站和数字公共设施中断后，韩国已恢复了 46 项政府服务。【原文：South Korea has restored 46 government services after a fire at a data centre disrupted websites and digital public amenities, Safety Minister Yun Hojung said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-restores-46-services-after-data-centre-fire-safety-minister-says-2025-09-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TPGXC3KA6ZOIBNNUCNLUGDKRUY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称巴西丰田工人批准临时裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西丰田汽车公司工会发表声明称，该公司位于圣保罗州的一家工厂因暴风雨受损，巴西工人周日以压倒性票数通过了临时裁员计划。【原文：Workers for Toyota in Brazil voted overwhelmingly on Sunday to approve a plan for temporary layoffs following storm damage to one of the Japanese carmaker's factories in the state of Sao Paulo, according to a statement from the workers union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/toyota-workers-brazil-approve-temporary-layoff-plan-union-says-2025-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABUIDC3ZU5J3NPU3OBVTGIRN3U</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:48:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究发现，匿名 TikTok 账户在捷克投票前支持激进党派]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个非政府组织周日表示，在捷克共和国 10 月 3-4 日大选之前，视频共享平台 TikTok 上的数百个匿名账户在传播亲俄言论和支持激进政党方面日益活跃。【原文：Hundreds of anonymous accounts on video-sharing platform TikTok have been increasingly active in spreading pro-Russia narratives and backing radical parties ahead of the Czech Republic's October 3-4 election, a non-governmental group said on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/anonymous-tiktok-accounts-backing-radical-parties-before-czech-vote-study-finds-2025-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N32RVQVHU5M6TEAVBCVUXFQWSE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Telegram 的杜罗夫称法国要求从应用程序中删除部分摩尔多瓦频道]]></title><description><![CDATA[Telegram 消息应用程序的亿万富翁创始人帕维尔-杜罗夫（Pavel Durov）周日指责法国情报部门通过中间人要求他在去年的总统投票前审查一些摩尔多瓦的声音，以换取在他在法国的法庭案件中提供帮助。【原文：Pavel Durov, the billionaire founder of the Telegram messaging app, accused French intelligence on Sunday of asking him through an intermediary to censor some Moldovan voices ahead of a presidential vote last year in return for help with his court case in France.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/telegrams-durov-says-france-asked-remove-some-moldovan-channels-app-2025-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQO7DQQ47FL7XIQP6FF3UUMFPY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称欧佩克+计划在 11 月再次提高石油产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉会谈情况的消息人士称，欧佩克+组织可能会在下周日的会议上批准再次增产石油，日产量至少增加13.7万桶，因为油价上涨促使该组织试图进一步夺回市场份额。【原文：OPEC+ will likely approve another oil production increase of at least 137,000 barrels per day at its meeting next Sunday, as rising oil prices encourage the group to try to further regain market share, three sources familiar with the talks said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-plans-another-oil-output-hike-november-sources-say-2025-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K62ADQKDSBIQFKOMDWKVCQI46A</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 12:11:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首尔：韩美就外汇交易达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国财政部长 Koo Yun-cheol 表示，韩国和美国已达成外汇协议，并计划很快宣布该协议。【原文：South Korea and the United States have reached a foreign exchange agreement and plan to announce the deal soon, South Korean Finance Minister Koo Yun-cheol said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-us-reach-an-agreement-over-foreign-exchange-deal-seoul-says-2025-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OE6QTHHBCFMTNHYZH6LXAIULPY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿联酋总统会见 OpenAI 首席执行官，讨论人工智能合作事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[据阿联酋国家通讯社报道，阿联酋总统周六在阿布扎比会见了 OpenAI 首席执行官 Sam Altman。【原文：The president of the United Arab Emirates, which has been spending billions in its push to become a global player in AI, met OpenAI Chief Executive Sam Altman in Abu Dhabi on Saturday, the UAE state news agency reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/uae-president-meets-openai-ceo-discuss-ai-collaboration-2025-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUXRSIZW7FKYJOTUBDQR55CRNU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 22:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国承诺为捷豹路虎提供 20 亿美元贷款担保]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国将为捷豹路虎提供 15 亿英镑（约合 20 亿美元）的贷款担保，以在这家豪华汽车制造商因网络攻击而停产后帮助支持其供应链。【原文：Britain will back Jaguar Land Rover with a 1.5 billion pound ($2 billion) loan guarantee to help support its supply chain in the wake of the luxury carmaker's production shutdown following a cyberattack.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/britain-pledges-2-billion-loan-guarantee-jaguar-land-rover-2025-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXF3FZPYQNITDI3SEY2BYKFBO4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利收到 10 份伊尔瓦钢铁竞标书，主要竞争者纷纷退出]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利国家钢铁制造商 Acciaierie d'Italia 周六在一份声明中说，意大利已收到 10 份对前 Ilva 钢厂的竞标书，但只有两家竞标者有意购买该公司的全部资产。【原文：Italy has received 10 bids for the former Ilva steel plant, but only two of the bidders are interested in purchasing all of the company's assets, national steelmaker Acciaierie d’Italia said in a statement on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/italy-receives-10-bids-ilva-steel-major-contenders-withdraw-2025-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6B7G5JPJJL23M6NBIL7P3XCCQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:53:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高级助手称韩国无法像特朗普建议的那样向美国支付 3500 亿美元以达成关税协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[首尔总统顾问周六表示，韩国无法按照美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在削减关税协议中提出的建议，为在美国的投资预付 3500 亿美元，因此正在寻求替代解决方案。【原文：South Korea is unable to pay $350 billion upfront in investment in the United States as President Donald Trump suggested under a deal to cut tariffs and is seeking an alternative solution, Seoul's presidential adviser said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-cannot-pay-350-billion-us-tariff-deal-trump-suggests-top-aide-says-2025-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEJ75ZUXUZP35LM36VVHASWJBI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 13:18:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis因装饰件脱落风险召回逾12.3万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周六表示，Stellantis公司将在美国召回123,396辆汽车，原因是驾驶员和乘客车窗上的装饰件脱落，可能对其他车辆造成道路危险，增加撞车风险。【原文：Stellantis is recalling 123,396 vehicles in the U.S. due to detached trim pieces on the driver and passenger windows that can create a road hazard for other vehicles, increasing the risk of a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-recall-over-123000-us-vehicles-over-detached-trim-pieces-2025-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HK2QIUEYHVMBDLPNTOXRWPPXJE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 07:19:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司就与已故举报人有关的非正常死亡索赔诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周五就约翰-巴尼特（John Barnett）的母亲提起的过失致死诉讼提交了一份和解协议，约翰-巴尼特是波音公司的一名前员工，他曾对波音公司的生产提出过担忧，认为这可能会给乘客带来危险。【原文：Boeing filed a settlement on Friday in a wrongful death lawsuit brought by the mother of John Barnett, a former Boeing worker who raised concerns about the planemaker's production that was potentially putting passengers at risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/boeing-settles-lawsuit-wrongful-death-claim-related-deceased-whistleblower-2025-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JS76HIBY6RIWNNZ2FYG5PPKOP4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蜘蛛侠》创作者斯坦-李的人工智能全息图在洛杉矶动漫展上首次亮相]]></title><description><![CDATA[漫威漫画超级英雄的创造者斯坦-李（Stan Lee）将身着绿色毛衣和棕褐色裤子，在明亮的蓝色屏幕上以全息形式重返洛杉矶动漫展，与他的蜘蛛侠、绿巨人、钢铁侠和雷神等角色的粉丝见面。【原文：Wearing a green sweater and tan pants against a bright blue screen, Marvel comic book superhero creator Stan Lee will return to L.A. Comic Con in holographic form to meet fans of his characters including Spider-Man, Hulk, Iron Man and Thor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ai-hologram-spider-man-creator-stan-lee-debuts-la-comic-con-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR4E6U74E5PL5BM6D5PTJUV4PY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 22:21:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司的西科斯基公司获得约 110 亿美元的美国海军合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛克希德-马丁公司周五表示，其子公司西科斯基公司已从美国海军获得一份价值近110亿美元的合同，将建造多达99架CH-53K "种马王 "直升机。【原文：Lockheed Martin said on Friday its subsidiary, Sikorsky, has secured a nearly $11 billion contract from the U.S. Navy to build up to 99 CH-53K King Stallion helicopters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lockheed-martins-sikorsky-secures-about-11-billion-us-navy-contract-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3GPSQ3SZNKKNJ3644TJD3LJME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:34:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称微软应解雇全球事务总裁丽莎-摩纳哥]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，微软公司应解雇该公司全球事务总裁丽莎-摩纳哥（Lisa Monaco），她曾在前总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）政府中担任副检察长。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday that Microsoft Corp should fire the firm's Global Affairs President Lisa Monaco, who was the deputy attorney general in former President Joe Biden's administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-microsoft-should-fire-its-global-affairs-president-lisa-monaco-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCPFOS6LVFMTPCEOFZKDYQJ47E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:28:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空将停飞 40 条航线，聘用前亚马逊网络高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录，精神航空将暂停 11 月份计划中的 40 条航线，并聘请亚马逊前高管 Andrea Lusso 担任网络规划副总裁。【原文：Spirit Airlines will suspend 40 routes in its November schedule and has hired former Amazon executive Andrea Lusso as vice president of network planning, according to a memo seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spirit-airlines-halt-40-routes-hires-ex-amazon-network-executive-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KU4CQCJFUVON7KYNURRG6Q5ZCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:24:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[核能公司宣布与纽柯公司合作促进美国核电供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[核电公司周五表示，它已与美国钢铁制造商纽柯公司签署了一项战略协议，以促进该国的核电供应链并支持国内制造业。【原文：The Nuclear Company said on Friday that it has signed a strategic agreement with U.S. steelmaker Nucor Corporation to boost the country's nuclear power supply chain and support domestic manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nuclear-company-announces-partnership-with-nucor-boost-us-nuclear-power-supply-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMQYQ5FYJ5NQHCCVW6H7WDK4ZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PGIM高管称，如果特朗普能左右美联储的鸽派立场，美元将面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国资产管理公司PGIM Fixed Income的一位高级主管表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普施加的压力可能会使美联储转向过度鸽派的立场，这种风险是美元近期的主要担忧。【原文：The risk that pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump could shift the Federal Reserve to an overly dovish stance is the main near-term concern for the U.S. dollar, said a senior executive at U.S. asset manager PGIM Fixed Income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-dollar-risk-if-trump-can-sway-fed-more-dovish-stance-says-pgim-exec-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QH3OIBHYSRO75PLO3NJOSG4O6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[房利美宣布董事会成员辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦国民抵押贷款协会（又称房利美）周五表示，董事会成员卡琳-金布罗（Karin Kimbrough）已于 9 月 22 日辞职。【原文：The U.S. Federal National Mortgage Association, known as Fannie Mae, said on Friday that board member Karin Kimbrough resigned from her position on September 22.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/fannie-mae-announces-resignation-board-member-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B6APDOVC7JOTBMX35LEFUC2Z2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美国劳工委员会撤回对苹果公司首席执行官侵犯员工权利的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引其看到的一封信报道称，美国劳工委员会已撤回对苹果公司首席执行官蒂姆-库克（Tim Cook）违反联邦劳动法的指控。【原文：The U.S. labor board has withdrawn its allegations that Apple CEO Tim Cook violated federal labor law, Bloomberg News reported on Friday citing a letter it had seen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-labor-board-withdraws-claims-apple-ceo-violated-employee-rights-bloomberg-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTXUNBZSEVK2DACQVNNWRAX6AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称美国证券交易委员会员工无需担心停摆裁员问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）的一名高级工会官员告诉该机构的工作人员，如果政府下周关门，他们不应该对可能出现的大规模裁员感到 "焦虑"。【原文：U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission workers should not be "anxious" about potential mass layoffs if the government shuts down next week, a top union official has told agency staff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-sec-staff-should-not-worry-about-shutdown-layoffs-union-says-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7IAMKNIEVRMKZDWOTRWLGWRQZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>