<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:15:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:15:12 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称宝马将在美国召回36,922辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周五表示，宝马将在美国召回36922辆汽车，原因是车辆静止时方向盘意外移动。【原文：BMW will recall 36,922 vehicles in the United States as over unintended steering wheel movement while the vehicle is stationary, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-recall-36922-vehicles-us-nhtsa-says-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2Q3UIC6QJIYFDBO2BF3NEA4JM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特因驻车功能丧失召回逾 27.2 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ford is recalling 272,645 vehicles in the U.S. due to a loss of park function, causing the vehicle to roll away and increasing the risk of a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-over-272000-us-vehicles-due-loss-park-function-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4UQZPGMKBMLNGEYTYDDKKCRL4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债务繁荣预示着人民币将成为融资货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者正在抢购人民币信贷，人民币贷款激增，有望超过中国银行的海外美元贷款，因为有吸引力的定价有助于推动中国政府持续推动人民币走向全球舞台。【原文：Investors are snapping up yuan credits and surging yuan lending is poised to overtake overseas dollar loans at Chinese banks as attractive pricing helps drive a sustained push by Beijing to put the yuan on the global stage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/debt-boom-signals-yuans-arrival-funding-currency-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEI6PMUZRFJXRFNAOPPARECYEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:13:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japan holds economic view steady in monthly report]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Japanese government revised down its view on public investment but largely kept its overall outlook on the economy intact in a monthly report published on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japan-holds-economic-view-steady-monthly-report-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WC4O4VWFEBOC3LGNYATTPWFHA4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China set to keep rates steady for seventh month despite slowing economy]]></title><description><![CDATA[China is expected to leave benchmark lending rates unchanged for a seventh consecutive month in December, a Reuters survey showed, despite a depressed economy and deepening woes in the property sector.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-set-keep-rates-steady-seventh-month-despite-slowing-economy-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OFLIGURQKNK6HBTDNXFG2FJUJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK government was hacked in October, minister confirms]]></title><description><![CDATA[British trade minister Chris Bryant said the government had been hacked in October, partly confirming a report in the Sun newspaper, which said a Chinese group had breached systems to access foreign office data.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-government-was-hacked-october-minister-confirms-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6RIF7S24ZNH7IRUMBXILY35V4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PUBG maker Krafton leads South Korean trio in $666 million India tech bet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gaming giant Krafton will lead a new $666 million investment fund in Asia, partnering with South Korean peers Naver and Mirae Asset to diversify beyond gaming into a wider pool of tech startups, primarily in India.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/pubg-maker-krafton-leads-south-korean-trio-666-million-india-tech-bet-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTRTUJPE3VNP5CWAVNIDL54EAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Coty 将向 KKR 出售 Wella 剩余的 25.8% 股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，Coty 将以 7.5 亿美元的价格向 KKR 出售其在 Wella 的剩余股份，并有权分享该护发品牌未来出售或首次公开募股的收益。【原文：Coty is selling its remaining stake in Wella to KKR for $750 million and the right to a share of future proceeds from a sale or initial public offering of the hair care brand, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/coty-sell-remaining-258-stake-wella-kkr-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCDJ4OSFV5ODFIREJF25PRIA4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田在新闻发布会上的讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五将利率上调至三十年来从未见过的水平，并表示准备进一步加息，在结束数十年的巨额货币支持和近乎零的借贷成本方面又迈出了具有里程碑意义的一步。【原文：The Bank of Japan raised its interest rates on Friday to levels unseen in three decades and signalled its readiness for further hikes, taking another landmark step in ending decades of huge monetary support and near-zero borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/boj-governor-uedas-comments-news-conference-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFWS6Y6UDJODLJ73GNJGF4QY7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:51:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道富山县计划建设日本最大的数据中心枢纽 - 文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份文件显示，日本西部的一个城市计划启动该国第三个也是最大的数据中心集群，总发电能力达 3.1 千兆瓦，因为这个亚洲国家正在努力满足人工智能相关服务的激增需求。【原文：A city in western Japan plans to launch the country's third and largest data centre cluster with total power capacity of 3.1 gigawatts, a document showed, as the Asian nation races to meet surging demand for artificial intelligence-related services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/japans-biggest-data-centre-hub-planned-toyama-prefecture-document-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GG4LP3QGVKJVKQYLY26DGRW6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:22:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[神奇 "的新兴市场有望在 2026 年再创辉煌]]></title><description><![CDATA[2025 年，新兴市场不畏关税、贸易战和全球动荡，取得了两位数的出色回报，投资者希望明年能再创佳绩。【原文：Emerging markets defied tariffs, trade wars and global turmoil to notch up stellar double-digit returns in 2025, and investors are hopeful of a repeat performance next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/marvellous-emerging-markets-tipped-another-star-showing-2026-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5G5MFLVWTJLDROLGLFEQDI4HGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标日本储蓄者可以像 1999 年一样狂欢]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KKDTF5GZPFMLLBVXJY7RERVJWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 05:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克在华困境加深，扭亏为盈停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克已经没有时间来证明其在中国的策略是有效的了。这家美国运动服装巨头在中国的销售额连续第六个季度下滑，其中鞋类销售额下降了 20%，这凸显出这个曾被视为增长引擎的市场已成为其最大的压力点。【原文：Nike is running out of time to prove its China playbook works. The U.S. sportswear giant’s sixth straight quarterly sales decline in the country - including a 20% drop in footwear - underscores how a market once seen as a growth engine has become its biggest pressure point.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nikes-china-conundrum-deepens-turnaround-stagnates-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEOYT3AHOJPWLKRAIJ2244PSGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构对澳新银行系统性不当行为处以 1.65 亿澳元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构周五表示，澳新银行集团因在处理 140 亿澳元政府债券交易中的不当行为，以及影响纳税人和零售客户的其他行为，被联邦法院罚款 2.5 亿澳元（1.653 亿美元）。【原文：An Australian regulator said on Friday that ANZ Group was fined A$250 million ($165.3 million) by a Federal Court for misconduct in handling a A$14 billion government bond deal, as well other actions that affected taxpayers and retail customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australian-regulator-fines-anz-165-million-systemic-misconduct-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KFUZXSHWJKMTLLCVFACF4JLKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着全球审查的加强，中国企业希望把新加坡作为家]]></title><description><![CDATA[越来越多的中国公司希望在新加坡落户，因为他们相信，迁往这个以贸易为重点的城市国家，可以降低其业务受中美地缘政治紧张局势干扰的风险。【原文：A growing number of Chinese companies are looking to domicile in Singapore, betting a move to the trade-focused city-state would reduce risks their operations get disrupted by Sino-U.S. geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-scrutiny-grows-chinese-firms-look-call-singapore-home-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4R4U3ZSQJROCDI5BJHIR3SBX7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，墨西哥航空公司 Volaris 和 Viva Aerobus 即将达成合并协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士周四透露，Volaris 和 Viva Aerobus 接近达成合并协议。【原文：Volaris and Viva Aerobus are close to agreeing a merger, sources familiar with the matter said on Thursday, a move that would combine two of Mexico's largest airlines and create a low-cost champion in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexican-airlines-volaris-viva-aerobus-near-merger-agreement-sources-say-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Q6HD2PAZJOQTBENHKSQ5XRJWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称美国对英伟达向中国销售先进人工智能芯片展开审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位消息人士称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已经启动了一项审查，这可能导致英伟达（Nvidia）功能第二强大的人工智能芯片首次运往中国，兑现了他允许这种有争议的销售的承诺。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has launched a review that could result in the first shipments to China of Nvidia's second-most powerful AI chips, five sources said, making good on his pledge to allow the controversial sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-launches-review-advanced-nvidia-ai-chip-sales-china-sources-say-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47FTLDKERNOABIBOZ37VDEE4FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:39:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田计划从 2026 年起在日本销售 3 款美国制造的车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周五表示，该公司的目标是从明年开始在日本销售美国制造的凯美瑞轿车、汉兰达越野车和Tundra皮卡，希望以此帮助改善日美贸易关系。【原文：Toyota Motor said on Friday that it aims to begin selling its U.S.-made Camry sedan, Highlander SUV and Tundra pickup truck in Japan starting next year as it hopes to help improve Japan―U.S. trade relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-aims-begin-selling-3-us-made-models-japan-2026-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R56IQZSWRZL7LNZY6BEU5CNLZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油将连续第二周收低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五早盘，油价下跌，并将连续第二周收低，原因是俄乌和平协议前景的上升抵消了对委内瑞拉油轮被封锁导致供应中断的担忧。【原文：Oil prices fell in early trading on Friday and were set to close lower for a second straight week, as rising prospects of a Russia-Ukraine peace deal offset concerns over supply disruptions from a blockade of Venezuelan oil tankers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-set-close-lower-second-straight-week-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CT5BC3D5OZKGZHMAGR37HVPY7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:30:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司股东 Harris Associates 表示对派拉蒙修改后的竞购方案持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司的第五大股东哈里斯联合公司（Harris Associates）周四表示，如果派拉蒙天空舞蹈公司（Paramount Skydance）提出更高的出价并解决交易条款方面的问题，该公司将对派拉蒙天空舞蹈公司的修订报价持 "非常开放的态度"。【原文：Harris Associates, the fifth largest shareholder in Warner Bros Discovery , said on Thursday it would be "very open" to a revised offer from Paramount Skydance if the company presents a superior bid and addresses issues with deal terms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/warner-bros-discovery-shareholder-harris-associates-says-open-revised-paramount-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPHNHZJM6ROMROZUKOPLEYEPZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[脆弱的日元在日本央行会议前惶惶不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元在近期低点附近震荡，交易员们在等待日本央行能否说服市场明年继续加息，而欧元在日本央行没有暗示加息后略有下滑。【原文：The yen was pinned near recent lows on Friday while traders waited to see whether the Bank of Japan can convince the market it can keep hiking interest rates into next year, while the euro slipped a bit after the central bank didn't hint at rate hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fragile-yen-tenterhooks-ahead-boj-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAP3X4X7NZNGNGJUZTJF7GPPEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市追随华尔街涨势，为日本央行加息做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市反弹，因为科技股的反弹提振了华尔街，让投资者开始期待日本央行可能加息，这可能会给货币和债券带来波澜。【原文：Asian share markets rebounded on Friday as a turnaround in tech lifted Wall Street, leaving investors counting down to a likely hike in interest rates from the Bank of Japan that could cause waves for currencies and bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEFHESFEEJLTJAKWGSNLCBH7HM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:36:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳新银行调查显示，新西兰商业信心达到30年来的最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳新银行（ANZ Bank）周五的一项调查显示，新西兰12月份的商业信心指数飙升至30年来的最高水平，前瞻性活动指标再次回升，部分指标达到数十年来的新高。【原文：New Zealand's business confidence surged in December to hit its highest level in 30 years, with forward-looking activity indicators lifting again with some reaching multi-decade highs, an ANZ Bank survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-business-confidence-hits-highest-level-30-years-anz-survey-shows-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PHQ4MZILJM4RJ2Y6UPQ4VU2TI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cannabis companies face hurdles accessing big banks despite reclassification, experts say]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump's move to relax marijuana regulations could ease some burden for cannabis companies, but will likely keep doors to access capital from big banks closed, experts said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/cannabis-companies-face-hurdles-accessing-big-banks-despite-reclassification-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATO67UKGRJKZTM2EJTLBYH32WI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japan's core inflation steady in November, stays above BOJ target]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's core consumer prices rose 3.0% in November from a year earlier, data showed on Friday, staying above the central bank's 2% target for the 44th straight month.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-core-inflation-steady-november-stays-above-boj-target-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4T7OPKEXVJIHIAMJRQXRYF6VQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wanxiang to pay $53 million to resolve US probe into imported Chinese auto parts, DOJ says]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，已与中国汽车零部件供应商万向集团的美国分公司就五年内对从中国进口的轮毂总成和其他零部件征收进口关税一事达成和解。【原文：The Justice Department said Thursday it had reached a settlement with the U.S. arm of Chinese auto parts supplier Wanxiang over import tariffs owed on wheel hub assemblies and other parts imported from China over a five-year period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/wanxiang-pay-53-million-resolve-us-probe-into-imported-chinese-auto-parts-doj-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6PCOQR76BMV7LXKS7ZM6VFIPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:21:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑莓因网络安全需求上调年度收入预期下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[黑莓公司（BlackBerry）周四上调了 2026 财年收入预期的下限，表明随着企业加大支出以应对日益复杂的网络攻击，对其网络安全软件的需求强劲。【原文：BlackBerry on Thursday raised the lower end of its fiscal 2026 revenue forecast, signalling strong demand for its cybersecurity software as companies ramp up spending to counter increasingly sophisticated cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackberry-lifts-lower-end-annual-revenue-forecast-cybersecurity-demand-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKCUZJMDBFIWHK2KTGJTS3HINM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦监督员报告后，UAW 总裁办公室主任将离开工会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车工人联合会（UAW）的一位重要战略家和工会 2023 年汽车厂罢工的策划者即将离开该工会组织，因为负责监督 UAW 的联邦监督员在一份报告中认为他
 
 他参与了一场不当解除另一位工会领导人职务的运动。【原文：A key United Auto Workers strategist and architect of the union’s 2023 auto-factory strike is leaving the labor group, after a report by the federal monitor overseeing the UAW concluded that he
 
 was part of a campaign to improperly remove duties from another union leader.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/uaw-presidents-chief-staff-leave-union-following-federal-monitor-report-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYDDX4PSBJKN3ARJKH2AWNVS44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok signs deal to sell US unit to American investor-led venture]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份 TikTok 首席执行官的备忘录，字节跳动旗下的 TikTok 已签署协议，将其美国实体出售给一家由美国投资者控制的合资企业。【原文：ByteDance's TikTok has signed a deal to sell its U.S. entity to a joint venture controlled by American investors, according to a memo from TikTok CEO seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/american-investor-consortium-acquire-tiktok-us-entity-axios-reports-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2RA7QD745MLRNVGHPRSIBM6OI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚桑托斯公司任命内部人士拉克兰-哈里斯为财务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[Santos said on Friday it has appointed insider Lachlan Harris as its CFO, as the Australian gas producer navigates a transition period tied to its key Barossa and Pikka projects.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-santos-names-insider-lachlan-harris-finance-boss-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2OK6GE4NJPAXH3DYTRXKTILS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>