<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:12:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:12:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Trump to press defense giants on delays, mulls curbs on executive pay]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he will meet major defense contractors next week to address production delays and cost overruns while the administration plans an executive order to limit dividends, buybacks and executive pay.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-press-defense-giants-delays-mulls-curbs-executive-pay-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4ONL5J2NBKX7NHPWE7WWL47DI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goodman Group, Canada's CPPIB strike $9.3 bln deal for Europe data centres]]></title><description><![CDATA[Australian data centre landlord Goodman Group said on Tuesday it had signed a A$14 billion ($9.32 billion) partnership agreement with Canada Pension Plan Investment Board to develop data centre projects in Frankfurt, Amsterdam and Paris.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/goodman-group-canada-pension-plan-establish-93-billion-european-data-center-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRXVDU4CTVP53NFC2F67YSQIIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democratic-led states sue to block US consumer watchdog's defunding under Trump]]></title><description><![CDATA[A coalition of Democratic-led states filed a lawsuit on Monday seeking to prevent President Donald Trump's administration from defunding the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau by refusing to request money from the Federal Reserve.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/democratic-led-states-sue-block-us-consumer-watchdogs-defunding-under-trump-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3QTGDEFRRNERBSRWFDODBRDH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US farm agency lost 20,000 staff in first five months of Trump administration]]></title><description><![CDATA[More than 20,300 employees left the U.S. Department of Agriculture in the first five months of the administration of President Donald Trump, about a fifth of staff, according to a report from the agency's inspector general.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-farm-agency-lost-20000-staff-first-five-months-trump-administration-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PDMWNWN4JJ6HKHETDDBFC6KHQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:59:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil oil union set to accept Petrobras labor offer, end strike]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian oil workers union FUP said on Monday it plans to accept a counteroffer from state-run company Petrobras for a labor deal, paving the way to end a week-long strike.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/brazil-oil-union-set-accept-petrobras-labor-offer-end-strike-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMWWVG3IKZKPJCWOUSMLZZ2UX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:42:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US business equipment borrowings down more than 4% y/y in November, ELFA says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. companies borrowed 4.4% less to finance equipment investments in November compared with the same period a year earlier, the Equipment Leasing and Finance Association (ELFA) said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-business-equipment-borrowings-down-more-than-4-yy-november-elfa-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIT4BOHD4ZNVHCNZD2H4JVB7IM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US adds DJI, other foreign drones to national security list]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Communications Commission said on Monday it is adding China's DJI and all foreign made drones and components to a list of companies determined to pose unacceptable risks to U.S. national security and will bar approvals of new types of drones for import or sale in the United States.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-adds-dji-other-foreign-drones-national-security-list-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4YO45F3KNLKXGXBOBPORBW3YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[South Korea online retailer Coupang faces US securities class action over massive data breach]]></title><description><![CDATA[South Korean e-commerce company Coupang has been sued in a U.S. court in an investor class action alleging violations of securities laws after a cybersecurity breach exposed personal information of more than 33 million customers.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/south-korea-online-retailer-coupang-faces-us-securities-class-action-over-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHNYYG5WQFNAFBOKHEHGJWDSOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FanDuel, CME Group launch prediction markets in five US states]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sports betting firm FanDuel and derivatives exchange heavyweight CME Group on Monday announced the launch of their prediction markets platform in five U.S. states, as the red-hot asset class continues to draw in new entrants.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fanduel-cme-group-launch-prediction-markets-five-us-states-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KQOHEC6JJI75BGALSUELFO3YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[United Launch Alliance CEO Tory Bruno resigns]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tory Bruno has resigned as United Launch Alliance's chief executive officer after leading the space venture for nearly 12 years, the firm said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/united-launch-alliance-ceo-tory-bruno-resigns-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MJSZAB2MBOCJJ65DV4L3OXVKA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lawmakers want US to disclose any approvals of Nvidia H200 China licenses]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two senior Democratic lawmakers on Monday asked the U.S. Commerce Department to disclose details and any approvals of ongoing license reviews for potential sales to Chinese firms of Nvidia's second-most powerful AI chips.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/lawmakers-want-us-disclose-any-approvals-nvidia-h200-china-licenses-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJGRIXTZJZNWFFTX75LBKYXB5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waymo resumes San Francisco service after power outage pause]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet unit Waymo said on Monday it resumed its ride-hailing service in the San Francisco Bay Area on Sunday, a day after temporarily suspending operations due to a widespread power outage that snarled traffic and gridlocked parts of the city.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/waymo-resumes-san-francisco-service-after-power-outage-pause-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D56P7MJ6AJODDGYIVRX3ACEBUY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:45:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Driverless future gains momentum with global robotaxi deployments]]></title><description><![CDATA[Uber and Lyft are teaming up with Chinese tech company Baidu to test self-driving taxis in the UK in 2026, making them the latest ride-hailing platforms to partner with self-driving vehicle firms.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/driverless-future-gains-momentum-with-global-robotaxi-deployments-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAPAUOXMXNOGFLK2ELRYX24UEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:42:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase doubles down on prediction markets with deal for The Clearing Company]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase said on Monday it will buy prediction markets startup The Clearing Company, as the crypto exchange looks to expand beyond its core digital assets business.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/coinbase-doubles-down-prediction-markets-with-deal-clearing-company-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53MAPEST6VKKNEMXFRVEVEQTSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mercedes agrees $150 million settlement with US states over diesel scandal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz has reached a $149.6 million settlement with U.S. states to resolve a long-running investigation into allegations of diesel emissions cheating by the German automaker, New York Attorney General Letitia James said Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/mercedes-benz-agrees-1496-million-settlement-with-us-states-over-excess-diesel-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STJ33CGFJNNPRL3PSYQXUKKHDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mercedes reaches $120 million settlement with US states over emissions scandal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz said on Monday it will pay out $120 million to multiple U.S. states over emissions-rigging software in its vehicles, which the German carmaker says resolves the remaining Dieselgate proceedings against it in the U.S.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/mercedes-reaches-120-million-settlement-with-us-states-over-emissions-scandal-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F7VPBRT7JI2NLNUARUWAXQDVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Warner Bros bidding war and red hot M&A market has dealmakers working through holidays]]></title><description><![CDATA[This has turned out to be an extraordinary year for dealmakers after a trade war kicked off by Donald Trump derailed activity in the second quarter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/warner-bros-bidding-war-red-hot-ma-market-has-dealmakers-working-through-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFKQKGCSYZPJZOHAES23MLFCRM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alphabet to buy data center firm Intersect in $4.75 billion deal amid AI push]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet said on Monday it would buy data center and energy infrastructure provider Intersect for $4.75 billion in cash, plus assumed debt, as tech giants ramp up spending to expand computing and power capacity necessary for developing AI.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alphabet-buy-data-center-infrastructure-firm-intersect-475-billion-deal-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUTWAYFLIBPHLDLRWIXBTGU6B4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW Ellison steps in with personal guarantee as Paramount fights for Warner Bros]]></title><description><![CDATA[Oracle co-founder Larry Ellison has stepped in to personally guarantee $40.4 billion in Paramount Skydance's latest effort to pry Warner Bros Discovery away from selling its prized Hollywood assets to streaming giant Netflix .]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/view-ellison-steps-with-personal-guarantee-paramount-fights-warner-bros-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DS2EYLRP7BJQ7EGFUG7EOU6H3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israeli high-tech funding rises to nearly $16 billion in 2025, report says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israeli high-tech companies raised $15.6 billion in private funding in 2025, up from $12.2 billion in 2024, Startup Nation Central said in a report on Monday citing preliminary data.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-high-tech-funding-rises-nearly-16-billion-2025-report-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOWOSSEKMJNH5EZ3TYYLVGMI2U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:57:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US watchdog says paycheck advances no longer subject to lending law]]></title><description><![CDATA[A U.S. consumer finance agency said on Monday that popular "earned wage" advances on worker paychecks do not resemble consumer loans, reversing course from guidance the regulator put out last year under then President Joe Biden.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-watchdog-says-paycheck-advances-no-longer-subject-lending-law-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQZLYRGPVNLPXISCVB4HVLGJAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:53:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI spending spree drives global tech debt issuance to record high]]></title><description><![CDATA[Global technology companies have ramped up debt issuance this year to record levels, as an intensifying race to build artificial intelligence capacity forces even cash-rich firms to borrow heavily to fund that investment.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-tech-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6MB77OZ7BN2HGMGZUNMWL3PEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:50:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI boom is pressuring videogame console industry in race for memory chips]]></title><description><![CDATA[Videogame console sales were already under pressure owing to tariff turmoil and weak consumer spending. Now a surge in the prices of memory chips is threatening to make the devices costlier in what could be another blow to the industry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-ai-boom-is-pressuring-videogame-console-industry-race-memory-chips-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HO2O5TBNGNONHLY5J7SKAW5ITU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mexico antitrust commission to revise Volaris-Viva Aerobus tie-up]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexico's antitrust commission will revise a planned tie-up between low-cost airlines Viva Aerobus and Volaris , the country's President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Monday, adding she considered the deal good news for Mexico's airline sector.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mexico-antitrust-commission-revise-volaris-viva-aerobus-tie-up-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KBPBYZD3XZJO3BWJYGI5WHRQWE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:04:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daiwa to raise M&A revenue target to 100 billion yen by 2031, CEO says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's Daiwa Securities is aiming to generate 100 billion yen ($635.61 million) in M&amp;A-related revenue by the financial year ended March 2031, its CEO said, as Japan undergoes a dealmaking boom that neared record levels in 2025.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/daiwa-raise-ma-revenue-target-100-billion-yen-by-2031-ceo-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHD4BNJFLJMFXCNX4ENTZPHCIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Union Pacific, Norfolk Southern merger faces pushback from signalmen's union]]></title><description><![CDATA[A rail workers' union on Monday opposed Union Pacific's proposed $85 billion acquisition of Norfolk Southern , warning that the deal could undermine safety and impact the workforce.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/union-pacific-norfolk-southern-merger-faces-pushback-signalmens-union-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AWBGZZ7HBNCLFYHSADP3DL2EM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China confirms talks between Wingtech, Nexperia BV, urges further negotiations]]></title><description><![CDATA[China on Monday confirmed that Wingtech and Nexperia B.V. had held the first round of talks last week, with both sides agreeing to maintain communications, according to a statement released by China's commerce ministry.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-confirms-talks-between-wingtech-nexperia-bv-urges-further-negotiations-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRQCVJQWYRLA7MGNIL3NJYPWYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instacart ends AI-driven price experiments after criticism]]></title><description><![CDATA[Instacart is ending price tests that resulted in different shoppers being shown different prices for groceries, the online retail platform said on Monday after criticism of its artificial intelligence-driven pricing tool.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/instacart-ends-ai-driven-price-experiments-after-criticism-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5SDBGDM5FPC7MTMRFHFDSUKWA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trian, General Catalyst to buy Janus Henderson for $7.4 billion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nelson Peltz's Trian and VC firm General Catalyst have agreed to buy asset manager Janus Henderson for $7.4 billion, the companies said on Monday, bringing to close a more than five-year activist campaign by the billionaire's hedge fund.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/trian-general-catalyst-buy-janus-henderson-74-billion-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LKROVXG6RLPDOW5N2PATAP4TE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed's Miran says he'll likely stay after term ends until his seat is filled - Bloomberg]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran on Monday said he is likely to remain on the central bank's Board of Governors beyond the expiration of his term until whoever President Donald Trump nominates as the next Fed chair is confirmed by the Senate.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-miran-says-hell-likely-stay-after-term-ends-until-his-seat-is-filled-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGIP2N76YJK2NOF45XLFM5IEPU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:11:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>