<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:05:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:05:12 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 内政部长称美国可削减 20-30% 的监管措施以促进能源发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国内政部长道格-伯格姆（Doug Burgum）周三表示，美国可能会削减20%至30%的法规，以消除更多能源和采矿项目的障碍。【原文：Interior Secretary Doug Burgum said on Wednesday that the United States could cut 20% to 30% of its regulations as it seeks to remove obstacles to more energy and mining projects.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ceraweek-us-can-slash-20-30-regulation-boost-energy-interior-secretary-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIUUBNOL3FNE7C7QIXLRZYCUBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府开始努力推翻美国环保署的汽车法规]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护局（U.S. Environmental Protection Agency）周三表示，该局正着手推翻拜登政府的汽车尾气排放规定，该规定将迫使汽车制造商生产越来越多的电动汽车。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency said on Wednesday it is beginning the effort to reverse the Biden administration's vehicle emissions rules that would force automakers to build a rising number of electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-begins-effort-reverse-epa-vehicle-rules-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4D2PHNRCK5N3ZIAQFWMZM4FPQ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:24:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国陆军工程兵部队为 3% 的文职人员提供买断服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国陆军工程兵团发言人表示，该兵团周三开始通知 1068 名员工（约占其文职人员总数的 3%），他们有资格参加特朗普政府为联邦工作人员推出的买断计划。【原文：The U.S. Army Corps of Engineers on Wednesday began notifying 1,068 employees, representing about 3% of its civilian workforce, of their eligibility for the Trump administration's buyout program for federal workers, a spokesperson said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-army-corps-engineers-offers-buyouts-3-civilian-staff-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG5SHUIQJNMGJNZA3ZHWLU62RM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普上任首月美国预算赤字达 3,070 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三表示，在唐纳德-特朗普总统上任后的第一个完整月里，美国预算赤字总额为 3070 亿美元，比一年前增长了 4%，即 110 亿美元，尽管收入的增长速度超过了支出的增长速度。【原文：The U.S. budget deficit totaled $307 billion for President Donald Trump's first full month in office, up 4%, or $11 billion, from a year ago, the Treasury Department said on Wednesday, even as growth in receipts outpaced that of spending.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-budget-deficit-trumps-first-full-month-office-reaches-307-billion-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIDLXGQXWRKZJLHHDHGJJ6UOJI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国环保局将重新考虑拜登清洁电厂规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[环境保护局周三宣布，计划重新审议拜登政府的一项法规，该法规旨在减少发电厂的温室气体排放，这也是新政府在更大范围内解除电力行业法规的努力的一部分。【原文：The Environmental Protection Agency announced on Wednesday it plans to reconsider a Biden administration regulation that sought to reduce greenhouse gas emissions from power plants, part of the new administration's broader efforts to unwind regulations for the power sector.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-epa-reconsider-biden-clean-power-plant-rule-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UA4DWYLYYZOKLO7DPJ5VPTVFHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:59:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普政府计划让美国肮脏的煤电厂暂缓排放烟尘]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府打算推翻旨在减少美国燃煤电厂烟尘排放的污染规定，此举旨在帮助美国一些最脏的电厂继续运营。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration intends to overturn pollution rules aimed at reducing soot emissions from U.S. coal-fired power plants in a move intended to help keep some of the nation's dirtiest plants operational, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-plans-give-dirty-us-coal-plants-reprieve-soot-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I42DLTNJINO2DA4SJ6LVYWFT3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普的疾病预防控制中心人选表示将推荐儿童接种麻疹疫苗]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的疾病控制和预防中心负责人大卫-韦尔登将于周四告诉立法者，他计划推荐儿童接种麻疹疫苗。【原文：President Donald Trump's nominee to run the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, David Weldon, will tell lawmakers on Thursday he plans to recommend the measles vaccines for children, Bloomberg News reported.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trumps-cdc-pick-says-he-would-recommend-measles-vaccine-children-bloomberg-news-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLFQJ3S3XZP5HFOA4XDMYSQB5Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将把无人陪伴移民儿童从最大的收容所提供者那里带走]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫生与公众服务部（U.S. Department of Health and Human Services）周三表示，联邦政府已停止将孤身移民儿童安置在西南关键项目（Southwest Key Programs）运营的避难所，并将那里的所有儿童转移到其他避难所。【原文：The federal government has stopped the placement of unaccompanied migrant children in shelters operated by the Southwest Key Programs and moved all children there to other shelters, the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services said Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-remove-unaccompanied-migrant-children-largest-shelter-provider-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGGHWZR4VRK4DC2XVSH6HDCSDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:11:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，美国社会保障机构考虑削减电话服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周三报道，美国社会保障局正在考虑大幅削减 7300 万退休和残疾美国人赖以申请和获取政府福利的电话服务。【原文：The U.S. Social Security Administration is considering dramatically curtailing the phone services that 73 million retired and disabled Americans rely on to apply for and access their earned government benefits, the Washington Post reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-social-security-weighs-phone-service-cuts-report-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARQO4B463RNE3BKO344K2ZYPMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，美国社会保障机构考虑削减电话服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周三报道，美国社会保障局正在考虑大幅削减 7300 万退休和残疾美国人赖以申请和获取政府福利的电话服务。【原文：The U.S. Social Security Administration is considering dramatically curtailing the phone services that 73 million retired and disabled Americans rely on to apply for and access their earned government benefits, the Washington Post reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-social-security-weighs-phone-service-cuts-report-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARQO4B463RNE3BKO344K2ZYPMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国环保局缩小对美国水道的监管范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环保署周三宣布，将根据最高法院 2023 年的一项判决，缩小可由联邦政府监管的水域的定义范围，此举受到了农业州共和党立法者的欢呼。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency on Wednesday announced that it will narrow the definition of waters that can be federally regulated to comply with a 2023 Supreme Court decision, a move cheered by Republican lawmakers in agricultural states.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/environment/epa-moves-narrow-regulation-us-waterways-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUBUMJDSCZOSRIHVYI7DBO66QM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[移民及海关执法局官员称美国移民拘留人数已达 4.76 万人]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国移民和海关执法局（U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement）的一位高级官员周三在与记者的通话中表示，美国移民拘留所的容量已达到 47600 人，特朗普政府正在寻求更多的床位。【原文：U.S. immigration detention is filled to capacity at 47,600 detainees, a senior U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement official said on a call with reporters on Wednesday, adding that the Trump administration was seeking more bed space.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-immigration-detention-maxed-out-47600-detainees-ice-official-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5FDLML6SJNTZBFAR7K736PO2I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫官员称，特朗普将提名鲍曼为美联储最高银行官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最早将于周三提名美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）担任负责监管事务的副主席。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will nominate Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman as vice chair for supervision as early as Wednesday, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-nominate-bowman-feds-top-bank-cop-white-house-official-says-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGONITZUP5J5HMBQQ27XQUT3CE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:24:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长表示不会停止征收金属关税，将增加铜保护措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）表示，在美国国内生产得到加强之前，任何措施都无法阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统扩大征收25%的钢铝关税，而且特朗普将在其贸易保护措施中加入铜。【原文：U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said nothing would stop President Donald Trump's expanded 25% tariffs on steel and aluminum until U.S. domestic production is strengthened, and that Trump will add copper to his trade protections.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-commerce-chief-says-nothing-will-stop-metals-tariffs-will-add-copper-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6R5QNO43RMVTIMUSOQNHMB66Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员沙欣将不再寻求 2026 年连任]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员珍妮-沙欣（Jeanne Shaheen）周三表示，她将不再寻求在 2026 年竞选连任，并称这是一个艰难的决定，因为她面临着紧迫的挑战。【原文：Democratic U.S. Senator Jeanne Shaheen said on Wednesday that she will not seek re-election in 2026, saying it was a difficult decision while there were urgent challenges ahead.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-us-senator-shaheen-says-she-will-not-seek-reelection-2026-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOFSFFBSQNLGPHCJ3VR5UAT4L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府收回 200 亿美元气候基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府终止了 200 亿美元的温室气体减排项目资金，气候倡导者和民主党人称此举非法扣押了分配给弱势社区的清洁能源和交通资金。【原文：The Trump administration has ended $20 billion in funding for greenhouse gas reduction projects in a move that climate advocates and Democrats say illegally seizes money allocated for clean energy and transportation for disadvantaged communities.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-claws-back-20-billion-climate-funds-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKBUBLYX6NMUTOT2HEV526GQZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 12:23:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 支持特朗普的关税举措，称这将促进美国制造业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blackstone 首席执行官 Stephen Schwarzman 周三支持美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策，称这将促进美国的制造业活动，刺激世界最大经济体的增长。【原文：Blackstone chief executive Stephen Schwarzman on Wednesday backed U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, saying they will boost manufacturing activity in the United States and spur growth in the world's largest economy.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackstone-backs-trumps-tariff-move-says-it-will-boost-us-manufacturing-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FVA472IE65PSJH3FSWOCD5KQTU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 12:14:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员沃伦要求医疗保险提名人奥兹博士断绝与行业的联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）周三表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的医疗保险监管机构领导人应剥离与医疗保健和制药公司的财务关系，因为这些公司可能会从特朗普的政策决定中获益。【原文：President Donald Trump's nominee to lead the agency overseeing Medicare should divest financial ties to healthcare and pharmaceutical companies that could benefit from his policy decisions, Democratic U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-senator-warren-demands-medicare-nominee-dr-oz-sever-industry-ties-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SU7LRTLIRL2VEZBDUGG2PZ3GY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:09:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官将就哥伦比亚大学学生抗议者质疑逮捕举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，一名美国法官将就哥伦比亚大学一名学生质疑移民局逮捕他的案件举行听证会，此案已成为特朗普政府承诺驱逐亲巴勒斯坦大学生活动分子的导火索。【原文：A U.S. judge on Wednesday will hold a hearing over a Columbia University student's challenge to his arrest by immigration authorities, a case that has become a flashpoint of the Trump administration's pledge to deport pro-Palestine college activists.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/judge-hold-hearing-over-columbia-student-protesters-challenge-arrest-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KH4XSUTORNXZLESVQRJDLY63Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院民主党人就政府拨款法案的未来之路展开辩论]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国参议院民主党人在如何应对共和党控制的众议院通过的临时拨款法案的问题上进行了角力，他们在投票支持他们中许多人反对的法案或允许政府关门之间做出了选择。【原文：U.S. Senate Democrats were wrestling on Wednesday with how to respond to a stopgap funding bill passed by the Republican-controlled House of Representatives, choosing between voting for a bill many of them oppose or allowing a government shutdown.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-democrats-debate-path-forward-government-funding-bill-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZOVDYJ2WNKKTGKH6QD3E2DC64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通经济学家认为美国经济衰退的可能性为 40%，存在 "过高特权 "的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通首席经济学家表示，今年美国经济衰退的可能性约为40%，如果政府破坏了人们对美国治理的信任，那么美国作为投资目的地的地位就有可能受到持久损害。【原文：There is about a 40% chance of a U.S. recession this year and a risk of lasting damage to the country's standing as an investment destination if the administration undermines trust in U.S. governance, according to J.P. Morgan's chief economist.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/jp-morgan-economist-sees-40-us-recession-chance-risks-exorbitant-privilege-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO6UUZQTHRKT7CADLXIZXNFGSQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:22:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局发射 SPHEREx 望远镜，研究宇宙起源]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，美国国家航空航天局（NASA）的一架望远镜从加利福尼亚发射升空，执行探索宇宙起源的任务，并在银河系中寻找隐藏的水源，水是生命的关键成分。【原文：A NASA telescope was launched into space from California on Tuesday for a mission to explore the origins of the universe and to scour the Milky Way galaxy for hidden reservoirs of water, a key ingredient for life.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/science/nasa-spherex-telescope-is-launched-study-universes-origins-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X77YHMKEKJPPJJEORQA4VKJ5ZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普就变性运动员引发争论后，美国农业部暂停对缅因州大学的资助]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）因缅因州拒绝禁止变性运动员参加女子运动项目而与州长珍妮特-米尔斯（Janet Mills）发生冲突后，缅因大学周二表示，美国农业部已暂停对该校研究和项目的资助。【原文：The U.S. Department of Agriculture has suspended funding for research and programs at the University of Maine, the school said on Tuesday, after President Donald Trump clashed with Governor Janet Mills over the state's refusal to ban transgender athletes from girls' sports.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-suspends-maine-university-funding-after-trump-row-over-transgender-athletes-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WFVIFTVKNOFTG2XIOFVIKQSZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 02:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 弗吉尼亚州州长称美国必须发展核聚变，否则将在能源方面落后于中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗吉尼亚州州长格伦-扬金（Glenn Youngkin）周二在休斯敦举行的CERAWeek能源会议上说，美国必须加快聚变能源的开发，否则就有可能在能源主导地位上落后于中国。【原文：The United States must expedite its development of fusion energy or risk falling behind China on energy dominance, said Virginia Governor Glenn Youngkin at the CERAWeek energy conference in Houston on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-virginia-governor-say-us-must-develop-fusion-or-fall-behind-china-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEVPXFQDRRI3XDL6TGUYDGO2DE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 01:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士称，特朗普政府正考虑削减司法部公共腐败部门的编制]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的人士周二表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑裁减美国司法部处理公共腐败案件部门的大部分律师。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering cutting most of the lawyers in the U.S. Justice Department unit that handles public corruption cases, four people familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-eyes-cuts-justice-department-public-corruption-unit-people-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOESDS7CVFLHZFCJJMS76BGROI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:51:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院确认特朗普的司法部反垄断主管盖尔-斯莱特的任命]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，唐纳德-特朗普总统任命的美国司法部反垄断部门主管盖尔-斯莱特（Gail Slater）获得了美国参议院的确认。【原文：Gail Slater, President Donald Trump's pick to oversee the U.S. Department of Justice's antitrust division, was confirmed by the U.S. Senate on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-confirms-trumps-justice-department-antitrust-head-gail-slater-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FEAILVXNBPNRELZKOVRXIR23Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:58:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[证人称特朗普政府仍计划撤销消费者金融局]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周二提供的证人证词，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府仍计划解雇美国消费者金融保护局的所有工作人员，从而有效地使其中立化。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration still plans to fire all workers at the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, effectively neutralizing it, according to witness testimony delivered Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-still-plans-eliminate-consumer-finance-bureau-witness-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5GWTHC23NPOJNUUQ2SPCV4S7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:50:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼迪要求美国食品公司去除人工染料]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封电子邮件称，美国卫生部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪在周一的一次会议上告诉包括百事可乐和卡夫亨氏在内的食品公司，特朗普政府希望在肯尼迪卸任前食品供应中不再使用人工染料。【原文：U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. told food companies including PepsiCo and Kraft Heinz in a meeting on Monday that the Trump administration wants artificial dyes out of the food supply before Kennedy leaves office, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kennedy-tells-us-food-companies-remove-artificial-dyes-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LNOS6QNXRO7HCIMORHGXP5FAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院通过法案避免政府关门]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党控制的美国众议院周二以 217 票对 213 票的表决结果通过了一项立法，该立法将避免政府在周末关门。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives on Tuesday passed legislation, by a vote of 217-213, that would avert a weekend government shutdown.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-passes-bill-avert-government-shutdown-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZLOK4TDWBOWRID2HU5PWJI454</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[众议院共和党人阻止国会挑战特朗普关税的能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[由共和党控制的美国众议院周二投票决定，阻止国会迅速对唐纳德-特朗普总统征收的关税提出质疑。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives voted on Tuesday to block the ability of Congress to quickly challenge tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump that have rattled financial markets.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/house-republicans-block-congress-ability-challenge-trump-tariffs-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSHWXLWUKBLZDO5OY6GJ3EX5LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>