<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 09:09:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 09:09:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行研究发现：中国商品倾销始于关税之前]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）周二的一份研究报告认为，国内需求疲软而非美国加征关税是中国以最低价格向欧洲市场倾销过剩产品、牺牲国内生产商利益的主要原因。【原文：Weak domestic demand rather than U.S. tariffs is the main reason China is dumping surplus product on European markets at rock-bottom prices at the expense of domestic producers, a European Central Bank study argued on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-goods-dumping-started-before-tariffs-ecb-study-finds-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QISBLE65WFNBXEATPGEMJEFRW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 09:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度金融科技公司 Pine Labs 的 4.4 亿美元首次公开募股在最后一天获得认购]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度金融科技公司 Pine Labs 4.4 亿美元的首次公开募股（IPO）在周二投标的最后一天获得足额认购，尽管对盈利能力和估值的担忧让一些投资者望而却步。【原文：Indian fintech firm Pine Labs' $440 million IPO was fully subscribed on the final day of bidding on Tuesday, even as concerns over profitability and valuations kept some investors at bay.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indian-fintech-firm-pine-labs-440-million-ipo-subscribed-final-day-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WSS77TEYGFIFNAW24SYJ5YDV3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 09:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯利康创历史新高，巩固英国最大股票领先地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，阿斯利康的股价突破了 2024 年 9 月的最高点，创下历史新高，巩固了该公司作为英国市值最大上市股票的地位。【原文：Shares in AstraZeneca rose past their September 2024 peak on Tuesday, hitting a fresh record high and cementing the company's position as the largest UK-listed stock by market value.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-hits-record-high-cements-lead-uks-biggest-stock-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUZPPNM2IZKLXE3FBZTS4DGVC4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:42:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士制表商因对特朗普可能降低关税持乐观态度而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，历峰集团和斯沃琪集团股价上涨，此前美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，他正与瑞士就降低瑞士面临的39%出口关税达成协议。【原文：Richemont and Swatch Group shares rose on Tuesday, after U.S. President Donald Trump said he was working with Switzerland on a deal to lower the 39% tariff rate it faces on exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/swiss-watchmakers-rise-optimism-over-possible-reduction-trump-tariffs-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GEFLL7CPIJPEBP2UBH4JNICJEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:34:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：壳牌在纽约最高法院挑战风险投资公司的仲裁决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份法律文件，在竞争对手英国石油公司（BP）赢得类似的价值 10 多亿美元的仲裁案几周后，壳牌在纽约最高法院对其在与美国液化天然气生产商 Venture Global 的仲裁案中的败诉提出质疑。【原文：Shell has challenged its defeat in an arbitration case against U.S. liquefied natural gas producer Venture Global in the New York Supreme Court, according to a legal filing seen by Reuters, weeks after rival BP won a similar $1 billion-plus arbitration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/shell-challenges-venture-global-arbitration-decision-new-york-supreme-court-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTU2BM55UVI2BIFNHX4MYVWNGY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:10:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷股份公司危机影响保时捷 SE 盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[保时捷控股公司周二表示，豪华汽车制造商保时捷公司（Porsche AG）的危机打击了第一大股东保时捷股份公司（Porsche SE）今年前九个月的盈利，调整后的税后利润下降了三分之一以上。【原文：A crisis at luxury carmaker Porsche AG hit earnings at top shareholder Porsche SE in the first nine months of the year, with adjusted profit after tax falling by over a third, the holding company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/porsche-se-reports-drop-profit-after-tax-hit-by-volkswagen-woes-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LHJAMNR2FKUXD6VHW2TLZZVVQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将为美国公司提供新的投资机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[商务部周二发表声明称，中国高级贸易谈判代表李成钢表示，中国将继续推动扩大市场准入，特别是在服务业领域，这将为包括美国在内的企业带来新的投资机会。【原文：China will continue to promote the expansion of market access, particularly in the service sector, which will bring new investment opportunities to companies including those from the United States, senior Chinese trade negotiator Li Chenggang said, according to a statement from the Ministry of Commerce on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-provide-new-investment-opportunities-us-companies-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S27UTBAGFJKYNMXXPMRR4OPS2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，埃利奥特持有丰田工业近 5%的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道称，激进投资者埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）已将其在丰田工业公司的持股比例增至近 5%。【原文：Activist investor Elliott Investment Management has increased its stake in Toyota Industries to almost 5%, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/elliott-takes-toyota-industries-stake-almost-5-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPMIMQ5TWVNLLKLKXX5RTYPC5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银集团第二季度利润达 166 亿美元，得益于 OpenAI 的收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本软银集团（SoftBank Group）周二公布，该公司 7-9 月份实现净利润 2.5 万亿日元（约合 166 亿美元），这是该公司连续第三个季度实现盈利。【原文：Japan's SoftBank Group reported on Tuesday a net profit of 2.5 trillion yen ($16.6 billion) for the July-September quarter, its third consecutive quarter of profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/softbank-group-posts-166-billion-net-profit-q2-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYARJE4XUVPKXCZMXGMD5XCK5Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，瑞银推迟迁移瑞士信贷的部分超级富豪客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士告诉路透社，瑞银将把瑞士信贷的一些超级富豪客户迁移到自己平台的时间推迟几个月，这是迄今为止进展相对顺利的整合过程中罕见的挫折。【原文：UBS is delaying the migration of some super-rich Credit Suisse clients to its own platforms by several months, sources told Reuters, a rare setback in an integration process that has so far progressed relatively smoothly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-delays-migration-some-super-rich-credit-suisse-clients-sources-say-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46TS2GYTYBJHJCH632OVLYRIA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 "巨型银行 "第二季度利润稳健，全年盈利有望创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管地缘政治存在不确定性，日本新首相也持鸽派态度，但预计日本三大银行集团周五将公布健康的第二季度财报，本财年的年度利润预期仍将创下历史新高。【原文：Japan's three largest banking groups are expected to post healthy second-quarter earnings on Friday, staying on track for record annual profit forecasts for this financial year despite geopolitical uncertainty and a dovish new Japanese prime minister.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-megabanks-seen-posting-solid-q2-profits-track-record-annual-earnings-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCN6QLQANNJPXDWAY7VACYONIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:45:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价  重开反弹持续，降息在望]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JIL3XVHK5J53H65BNQO5XKQC4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[说明：什么是气候融资？]]></title><description><![CDATA[各国在努力向清洁能源转变的同时，也在为气候变暖带来的极端天气和其他影响做准备，这就需要钱--大量的钱。随着全球变暖的成本和风险不断攀升，气候融资的话题也变得更加紧张。以下是您需要了解的内容：【原文：Countries trying to shift to clean energy while also preparing for extreme weather and other impacts in a warmer world will need money - a lot of it. As the costs and risks of global warming escalate, the topic of climate finance has become more tense. Here's what you need to know:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/what-is-climate-finance-why-does-it-matter-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ELCVKNWYZLNFGVYBVC3TO66ZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于关税影响降低，索尼将利润预期上调 8]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼周二将截至 2026 年 3 月的年度营业利润预期上调 8%，至 1.43 万亿日元（合 94.8 亿美元），理由是美国关税的影响较小，以及音乐和芯片业务的强劲表现。【原文：Sony on Tuesday raised its operating profit forecast for the year ending March 2026 by 8% to 1.43 trillion yen ($9.48 billion) citing a smaller impact from U.S. tariffs and the strength of its music and chips businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/sony-raises-profit-forecast-by-8-lower-tariff-impact-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQZFNRES2BJRNIRCFB7P5DHL7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者监督机构称其无法合法获取资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高消费者监督机构周一表示，法律禁止该机构从美联储提取现金以支持持续运营，但其目前的资金 "至少 "应持续到今年年底。【原文：The top U.S. consumer watchdog said on Monday it was legally prohibited from drawing cash from the Federal Reserve to support continuing operations, but that its current funding should last through the end of this year "at least."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-consumer-watchdog-says-it-is-legally-blocked-accessing-funds-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASFMZ63ZCVON7ODS26CBBEVLKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓将为澳大利亚煤炭工人的圣诞轮班提供补偿]]></title><description><![CDATA[矿业与能源工会周二表示，澳大利亚联邦法院已下令必和必拓向其在昆士兰州的劳务雇佣部门雇佣的 85 名煤矿工人提供赔偿，因为必和必拓非法要求他们在圣诞节和节礼日假期工作，且未提供合理的拒绝权。【原文：BHP has been ordered by Australia's Federal Court to compensate 85 coal mine workers employed by its labour hire arm in Queensland for unlawfully requiring them to work Christmas and Boxing Day holidays without providing a reasonable right of refusal, the Mining and Energy Union said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/bhp-compensate-australian-coal-workers-christmas-shifts-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUIJWHDNGZJHHLUPGYVT3DOGLI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:25:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：中国制定计划阻止美军获得稀土磁铁]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周一援引熟悉内情的人士的话报道称，中国计划通过一个系统放宽稀土和其他受限制材料对美国的流通，该系统将排除与美国军方有关系的公司，同时快速审批其他公司的出口。【原文：China plans to ease the flow of rare earths and other restricted materials to the U.S. via a system that will exclude companies with ties to the U.S. military while fast-tracking export approvals for other firms, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-devises-plan-keep-us-military-getting-its-rare-earth-magnets-wsj-reports-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6DGUD4B6JNN5EWPFRRG4KI4TE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国部委称推迟就谷歌地图数据传输请求作出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国周二表示，已推迟就谷歌出口地图数据的申请做出决定，并称将在该公司提交补充文件后做出最终裁决。【原文：South Korea said on Tuesday it has delayed a decision on Google's request for permission to export map data, saying it will make a final ruling once the company submits additional documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-delays-decision-googles-request-map-data-transfer-says-ministry-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KS26CQGPMRK3DAQREZ56NR2SCE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:10:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称东南亚数字经济的私人资金投入落后于全球水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份行业报告周二称，在截至2025年6月的12个月里，东南亚互联网经济的私人资金同比增长15%，达到77亿美元，落后于全球私募股权和风险投资25%的增长率。【原文：Private funding for Southeast Asia's internet economy grew 15% from a year earlier to $7.7 billion in the 12 months to June 2025, lagging the global growth rate of 25% for private equity and venture capital investments, an industry report said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/private-funding-southeast-asia-digital-economy-lags-global-level-report-says-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHFJ7CV4P5KD3A7IOBBOULERAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与韩国的协议因潜艇细节问题陷入僵局]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和韩国总统李在镕会晤并宣布他们已经解决了数月来有关关税和安全问题的谈判两周后，双方仍未达成任何书面协议。【原文：Two weeks after U.S. President Donald Trump and South Korea's Lee Jae Myung met and announced they had resolved months of negotiations over tariffs and security issues, the two sides have yet to release any agreement on paper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/trumps-deal-with-south-korea-bogged-down-details-over-submarine-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMWKQ7FVSZJQZIEXKNMO77OBLM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[预计美国将达成停摆协议，黄金和股市上扬]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市上涨，黄金和纳斯达克指数创下几个月来的最大涨幅，这得益于有迹象表明，结束美国政府关门的协议即将达成。【原文：Asian stocks rose on Tuesday while gold and the Nasdaq were basking in their sharpest gains for months thanks to signs a deal to end the U.S. government shutdown was in the offing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZPDMD4UYBKO3LH2WL6M5TY4GE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 02:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[供应过剩忧虑令石油价格回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二亚市早盘，油价下跌，缩减了上一交易日的涨幅，原因是对供应过剩的担忧超过了对美国政府可能解决停摆问题的乐观情绪。【原文：Oil prices dipped in early Asian trade on Tuesday, trimming gains from the previous session as oversupply concerns outweighed optimism over a potential resolution to the U.S. government shutdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-retreats-oversupply-worries-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQG6UGBG4NLNXB4NCTCUGUGT64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 01:46:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《时事航空》报道，波音公司获准推进 777X 的认证工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《航空周刊》周一援引熟悉该项目进展的人士的话报道，波音公司上周获得了美国联邦航空管理局的批准，开始对其777-9进行五个主要阶段中的第三阶段认证飞行测试。【原文：Boeing received approval last week from the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration to begin the third of five major phases of certification flight tests for its 777-9, the Air Current reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the program's progress.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-gets-nod-moving-777x-forward-certification-air-current-reports-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSWLP4U5FFL5NEDGECEW6QELYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 01:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员关注美国停摆结束，避险日元承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，避险货币日元接近几个月来的最弱水平，而风险货币兑美元则表现坚挺，交易商在等待美国立法者是否能在未来几天内结束政府关门。【原文：The safe-haven yen was pinned near its weakest levels for months on Tuesday while riskier currencies were firm against the dollar, as traders waited to see whether U.S. lawmakers could secure an end to the government shutdown in coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/safe-haven-yen-under-pressure-traders-eye-end-us-shutdown-2025-11-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6YMGGBAEBNP5G3ELZXK7KVBLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[舒默因政府拨款协议再次陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[周末达成的结束美国政府史上最长停摆的协议使参议院民主党人产生分歧，并激怒了该党声势浩大的自由派支持者，他们今年第二次将矛头转向参议院少数党领袖查克-舒默（Chuck Schumer）。【原文：A weekend deal to end the longest U.S. government shutdown in history divided Senate Democrats and angered the party's vocal liberal base, who turned their vitriol on Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer for the second time this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/schumer-hotseat-again-over-deal-fund-government-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EVSQ6TBRJLJHIPM6R6UQDPFTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师上调目标股价，软银的 OpenAI 赌注成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，科技投资商软银集团（SoftBank Group）公布了第二季度财报，该公司在人工智能领域的投资热潮使其股价一路飙升。【原文：Technology investor SoftBank Group reports second quarter earnings results on Tuesday in the midst of feverish investment in artificial intelligence that has sent its share price soaring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbanks-openai-wager-focus-analysts-upgrade-share-price-target-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C42YTQHO5FKJVCXV6DT2KM4KNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国航空旅行何时恢复正常？本周不会]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管联邦政府关门有望在本周结束，但美国的航空旅客仍将经历几天的艰难旅程，在天空飞行恢复正常之前，全国范围内的航班都将取消或延误。【原文：Despite hopes the federal government shutdown could end this week, air travelers in the United States are still in for a rough few days of cancellations and delays nationwide before taking to the skies gets back to normal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/when-will-us-air-travel-be-back-normal-not-this-week-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCBD5K2YBJNH7JE46JFQGQ2RNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI高管离职后，英特尔首席执行官将监管公司的人工智能工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔在一份声明中表示，在公司首席技术官离职加入 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 之后，英特尔首席执行官陈立武将负责监管芯片制造商的人工智能工作。【原文：Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan will oversee the chipmakers artificial intelligence efforts after the firm's chief technology officer departed for ChatGPT maker OpenAI, Intel said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intel-ceo-oversee-companys-ai-efforts-after-departure-exec-openai-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Z23R5IQLVJ7NHQ2TT63EXRP5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Natura 公司第三季度出现亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西化妆品生产商 Natura 周一公布，第三季度经常性净亏损为 1.19 亿雷亚尔（2202 万美元），扭转了去年同期 3.01 亿雷亚尔的净利润。【原文：Brazilian cosmetic maker Natura posted on Monday a third-quarter recurring net loss of 119 million reais ($22.02 million), reversing a 301 million real net profit recorded in the same period a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-natura-swings-loss-third-quarter-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4TDTYIFOFPILMA4UK244R4SGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:43:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[成本增加、需求下滑导致 Beyond Meat 第三季度亏损扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，Beyond Meat 公布了第三季度的更大亏损，因为这家植物肉生产商正努力应对产品需求持续低迷和成本增加的问题。【原文：Beyond Meat posted a bigger loss for the third quarter on Monday, as the plant-based meat maker grappled with persistent sluggish demand for its products and mounting costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/beyond-meat-third-quarter-loss-widens-costs-mount-demand-slumps-2025-11-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PISYKUFQCBPHHECN77GB5S4ANU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>