<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:18:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:18:31 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥谢因鲍姆因在关税问题上应对特朗普而赢得早期赞誉]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）周一似乎通过了她在世界舞台上的最大考验，赢得了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁征收关税的喘息空间。【原文：Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum on Monday appeared to pass her biggest test yet on the world stage by winning breathing room from U.S. President Donald Trump's threatened tariffs, which risked ramming a wrecking ball through Mexico's economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-sheinbaum-wins-early-praise-handling-trump-tariffs-2025-02-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EASKAXAE5N2HMTJATC2JUCCRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[央行机构敦促修改政策以吸取 COVID 的教训]]></title><description><![CDATA[央行机构国际清算银行敦促美联储和欧洲央行等机构改革利率制定方式，避免出现大流行病后通胀飙升的集体失误。【原文：Central bank body the Bank for International Settlements has urged the likes of the Federal Reserve and European Central Bank to revamp the way they approach interest rate setting to avoid the collective failures that allowed inflation to soar after the pandemic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/central-bank-body-urges-policy-revamps-heed-covid-lessons-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAEQTSYPUZPZBMOJXZG2ZH4MQU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 23:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥和加拿大称特朗普同意暂停征收关税后，WTI 油价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在墨西哥和加拿大领导人表示美国总统唐纳德-特朗普已同意在一个月内暂停征收高额关税之后，美国西德克萨斯中质原油（WTI）价格在格林尼治标准时间23时09分下跌1.1%，或0.81美分，至72.35美元。【原文：U.S. West Texas Intermediate (WTI) crude prices were down by 1.1%, or 0.81 cents, to $72.35 at 2309 GMT after leaders of Mexico and Canada said U.S. President Donald Trump has agreed to pause imposing steep tariffs for one month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/wti-oil-prices-down-after-mexico-canada-say-trump-agrees-pause-tariffs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKAE27GUJNMKLERSDGX2B5M6MI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 23:17:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拥有 6 万亿欧元的投资者警告欧盟不要削弱绿色规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[在布鲁塞尔制定削减绿色金融繁文缛节的计划之际，管理着 6.6 万亿欧元资产的投资者敦促欧盟不要削弱其可持续发展规则。【原文：Investors with 6.6 trillion euros in assets under management have urged the European Union not to weaken its sustainability rules, as Brussels draws up plans to cut red tape around green finance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/investors-with-6-trillion-euros-warn-eu-not-weaken-green-rules-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRWZS6CCWRMWPOJ6AQTHMOHKFA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 23:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔吉特因在 DEI 问题上欺骗股东而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[塔吉特因涉嫌隐瞒其多元化和社会倡议的风险而被起诉，导致顾客逃离，这家总部位于明尼阿波利斯的零售商股价暴跌。【原文：Target has been sued for allegedly concealing the risks of its diversity and social initiatives, leading to a backlash that caused customers to flee and the stock price of the Minneapolis-based retailer to plummet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/target-is-sued-defrauding-shareholders-about-dei-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEKMNNCVUNKYNN5QE63NS4X3ZM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:49:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长接管消费者监督机构，冻结所有活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一宣布，任命新确认的财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）为消费者金融保护局代理局长。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday tapped newly confirmed Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent as acting director of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, the agency announced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasury-chief-takes-over-consumer-watchdog-freezes-all-activity-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6QVKS4MARNMTCIUXOYAUFIN74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:30:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名的人选将审查拜登对枪支出口的限制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的商务部负责人周一表示，他将审查拜登政府实施了一年之久的枪支出口限制措施，该措施旨在限制外国犯罪集团获取美国枪支。【原文：President Donald Trump's nominee to head the Commerce Department said on Monday he will review the Biden administration's year-old restrictions on firearms exports that were aimed at limiting foreign criminal groups acquiring U.S. guns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-nominee-will-review-biden-restrictions-firearms-exports-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBUCKNF35FIPZI4N2QM5PYNJ44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:23:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的消费者监督机构上任第一天就冻结了 CFPB 的活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封电子邮件，美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）已停止了美国消费者金融保护局几乎所有未决的活动，包括调查、规则制定、诉讼和公共沟通。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent, who took over on Monday as President Donald Trump's new acting consumer finance watchdog, has halted virtually all pending activities at the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, including investigations, rule making, litigation and public communications, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-consumer-watchdog-freezes-cfpb-activity-first-day-job-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZASGQQWFROKRJLJO2VJ6QITJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官延长特朗普冻结联邦拨款和贷款计划的暂停期]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名美国法官周一延长了特朗普政府冻结联邦贷款、赠款和其他财政援助计划的暂停期，称其似乎 "粗暴 "地践踏了国会对政府支出的权力。【原文：A U.S. judge on Monday extended a pause on the Trump administration's plan to freeze federal loans, grants and other financial assistance, saying it appeared to have "run roughshod" over Congress's authority over government spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-extends-pause-trumps-plan-freeze-federal-grants-loans-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YLLYBV6CE5JJFDYGQQ5NNDXSTY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税缓和减轻最初打击，亚洲有望反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphics-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZBSZ7WQINLUHGSTHBTMJWWX6A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:47:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PIMCO 关注特朗普在通胀风险下调整市场政策的举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[PIMCO首席投资官丹-伊瓦辛（Dan Ivascyn）周一表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普根据市场信号调整经济政策的意愿将是美国通胀和经济增长前景的关键，此前美国对贸易伙伴征收关税令市场动荡不安。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's willingness to calibrate economic policies based on market signals will be key for U.S. inflation and growth prospects, PIMCO's Chief Investment Officer Dan Ivascyn said on Monday, after tariffs on U.S. trade partners roiled markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pimco-focuses-trumps-market-tuned-policy-tweaks-amid-inflation-risks-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPJTQU5JLNMKXHEMI2BQQHZ7DA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:45:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特鲁多称特朗普将暂停对加拿大征收关税至少 30 天]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理贾斯汀-特鲁多（Justin Trudeau）周一在 X 上发帖称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）将把威胁对加拿大进口商品征收关税的时间至少推迟 30 天。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will postpone threatened tariffs on Canadian imports for at least 30 days, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said in a post on X on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trudeau-says-trump-will-pause-canada-tariffs-least-30-days-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBKS3PDKPBKHDAP264SBEHGEQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:41:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西雷亚尔创 20 年最长连涨纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西雷亚尔对美元汇率周一收盘连续第 11 个交易日走强，创下自 2005 年 4 月以来最长的连涨纪录。【原文：Brazil's real closed trading on Monday stronger versus the U.S. dollar for the 11th consecutive session, marking its longest streak of gains since April 2005.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/brazils-real-sets-longest-streak-gains-20-years-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJOMI5HMERISVDLNIXMA6NUEVI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir 预测 2025 年收入高于预期，原因是人工智能强劲，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据分析公司 Palantir 周一预测第一季度和全年营收将高于华尔街预期，押注于采用生成式人工智能的公司对其软件的强劲需求，盘后股价上涨约 12%。【原文：Data analytics firm Palantir forecast first-quarter and annual revenue above Wall Street estimates on Monday, betting on robust demand for its software from companies adopting generative AI, sending its shares up about 12% after the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/palantir-forecasts-2025-revenue-above-estimates-ai-strength-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFJTPEVKMJLUDAGDT5G2BE4SQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:06:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[说明：什么是主权财富基金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统周一签署了一项行政命令，命令美国财政部和商务部为美国创建一个主权财富基金。【原文：President Donald Trump on Monday signed an executive order ordering the U.S. Treasury and Commerce Departments to create a sovereign wealth fund for the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/what-is-sovereign-wealth-fund-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONVULKNHT5MUVO2BX3INXGPW6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卢拉告诉国会，巴西通胀今年将进一步缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周一在给国会的书面致辞中说，预计今年巴西的通货膨胀率将进一步缓解，到2026年中期将接近央行3%目标的中点。【原文：Inflation in Brazil is expected to ease further this year and near the mid-point of the central bank's 3% target by mid-2026, President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said in a written message to Congress on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-inflation-ease-further-this-year-lula-tells-congress-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPZIX5NPGFNVJFFZ74UTJI7DC4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:56:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税意味着加拿大威士忌进口商可能将成本转嫁给美国人]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国关税的征收，像帝亚吉欧这样的全球酒精饮料制造商陷入了一场重大贸易战的交火之中，这给本已因销售额下滑而举步维艰的该行业带来了沉重打击。【原文：Global makers of alcoholic drinks like Diageo are caught in the cross-fire of a major trade war as U.S. tariffs deal a hefty blow to an industry already struggling with falling sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trump-tariffs-mean-canadian-whisky-importers-may-pass-costs-americans-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCPOEJOV6BM6LLI2NAY2ICVUDY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美国国会能否干预特朗普的关税政策？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会一些议员对唐纳德-特朗普总统威胁对加拿大、中国和墨西哥征收新关税表示失望，但他们阻止特朗普的力量有限。【原文：Some lawmakers in the U.S. Congress have expressed dismay at President Donald Trump's threat to slap new tariffs on Canada, China and Mexico, but they have limited power to stop him.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/can-us-congress-intervene-trumps-tariffs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVKOKLZHNJLU3G3J724AQ63XOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称巴西税务部门罢工威胁政府财政计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[工人工会表示，巴西联邦税务局因工资要求而举行的罢工正在破坏政府通过税收结算增加收入的努力，去年有近150亿雷亚尔（约合26亿美元）的收入因这一争端而悬而未决。【原文：A strike by Brazil's federal tax agency over wage demands is undermining government efforts to raise revenue through tax settlements, the workers' union said, with nearly 15 billion reais ($2.6 billion) pending last year due to the dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-tax-revenue-service-strike-threatens-governments-fiscal-plans-union-says-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3B4NBFVDRN45J4WTMJT36T4Y4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌云计算增长放缓，Alphabet人工智能支出面临审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，谷歌母公司 Alphabet 将公布财报，由于广告和云计算业务放缓，谷歌在假日季度的收入增长可能放缓，Alphabet 在人工智能方面的巨额支出将面临投资者的审查。【原文：Alphabet will face investor scrutiny over its massive spending on AI when it reports earnings on Tuesday, as revenue growth at the Google parent likely slowed in the holiday quarter due to a slowdown in its advertising and cloud businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alphabet-faces-scrutiny-ai-spending-google-cloud-growth-slows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XJFVOHULFI4XE2UZPJBP3OVIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:46:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示希望乌克兰向美国供应稀土]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，他希望乌克兰向美国提供稀土矿物，作为对美国在财政上支持该国对俄战争努力的一种补偿。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he wants Ukraine to supply the United States with rare earth minerals as a form of payment for financially supporting the country's war efforts against Russia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-says-he-wants-ukraine-supply-us-with-rare-earths-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OISZCJLC3RLQ5MFKL5QT4ORY4U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行称第四季度企业贷款需求上升--美联储调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周一的一项调查显示，美国银行表示第四季度企业贷款需求增强，报告净增长的银行比例两年来首次转为正值【原文：U.S. banks say demand for business loans strengthened in the fourth quarter, with the net share of banks reporting an increase turning positive for the first time in two years, a Federal Reserve survey on Monday showed】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-banks-say-demand-business-loans-rose-q4-fed-survey-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCMHB3AJCVIT3IJ7AFXLHJ2Y5M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，2024 年特斯拉在加州的汽车注册量将下降 12]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业数据显示，去年特斯拉电动汽车在加州的注册量下降了约 12%，这表明该汽车制造商在美国这一重要市场面临的挑战日益严峻。【原文：Tesla's electric-vehicle registrations in California fell about 12% last year, according to industry data, indicating mounting challenges for the automaker in the key U.S. market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-california-car-registrations-down-12-2024-report-shows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5SMZLUWIZMX3JG6RXM4FRYV6Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Engie 仍认为美国对可再生能源的需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国电力集团 Engie 执行副总裁 Edouard Neviaski 周一表示，Engie 仍认为美国对可再生能源项目有着强烈的需求，并预计美国仍将是该公司投资组合中不可或缺的一部分。【原文：French power group Engie still sees strong appetite in the U.S. for renewable energy projects and expects the country to remain an integral part of the company's portfolio, Executive Vice President Edouard Neviaski said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/engie-still-sees-strong-us-appetite-renewables-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELTWDYHLIJMW5KJRO2IX7RH2ZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:54:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙全球公司与尼尔森签署新合作协议，结束争端]]></title><description><![CDATA[媒体巨头派拉蒙全球公司与尼尔森公司签署了一项新协议，尼尔森将为哥伦比亚广播公司的母公司提供跨平台的测量和分析服务，结束了双方长期以来的争执。【原文：Media giant Paramount Global and Nielsen have signed a new deal that would see the research firm provide measurement and analytics services across the CBS parent company's platforms, ending a long-running dispute.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-global-nielsen-sign-new-partnership-ending-dispute-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTHJFNBQGVL3PJ4OKH5CPQP3DQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:50:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[厄瓜多尔总统宣布对墨西哥商品征收 27% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[厄瓜多尔总统丹尼尔-诺沃亚周一宣布，厄瓜多尔政府将对墨西哥商品征收 27% 的关税，以促进厄瓜多尔企业获得公平待遇。【原文：Ecuador's President Daniel Noboa announced on Monday that his government will apply a 27% tariff on Mexican goods in an effort to promote fair treatment for his country's companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/ecuador-president-announces-27-tariff-mexican-goods-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6E5Q7SSEOBKATJUJY5MMPF5KMQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:49:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北美航空航天联盟敦促特朗普暂停对加拿大征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[北美最大的航空航天工会负责人周一告诉路透社记者，美国应该像对墨西哥那样暂停对加拿大征收关税，因为行业高管们正在权衡对飞机零部件和喷气式飞机征收新关税的影响。【原文：The United States should pause tariffs on Canada as it did on Mexico, the head of the largest North American aerospace union told Reuters on Monday, as industry executives weighed the impact of fresh duties on plane parts and jets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/north-american-aerospace-union-presses-trump-pause-tariffs-canada-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XM4IELDUL5NO3J2Y3GL2QHX7RQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普警告可能增加对华关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一警告说，他可能会在周六对中国征收的10%关税基础上再增加关税，而且 "我们将在未来24小时内与中国对话"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump warned on Monday he might increase tariffs on China beyond the 10% he imposed on Saturday and that "we will speak to China" probably over the next 24 hours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-warns-tariffs-china-may-increase-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BROJFHF225ISZPEMEJGUTBWR5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称马斯克只是在获得批准后才采取行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）只是在做获得批准的事情。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said billionaire Elon Musk, who the president had charged with shrinking the U.S. government, is only doing things that have approval.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-musk-only-acting-with-approval-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QWM74NMTKNLLXEUINZIUDAKAB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:17:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称新成立的美国主权财富基金可能收购 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一签署了一项行政命令，命令美国财政部和商务部创建一个主权财富基金，并表示该基金可能会收购 TikTok。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Monday ordering the U.S. Treasury and Commerce Departments to create a sovereign wealth fund and said it may purchase TikTok.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/trump-signs-executive-order-create-sovereign-wealth-fund-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5OE4GQQB5IQFDOPOC2IJRUW5I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>