<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:47:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:47:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌推出新型铁木芯片，加速人工智能应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 周三发布了名为 "铁木 "的第七代人工智能芯片。【原文：Alphabet's on Wednesday unveiled its seventh-generation artificial intelligence chip named Ironwood, which the company said is designed to speed the performance of AI applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-launches-new-ironwood-chip-speed-ai-applications-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKKIDAEAUVK7XGWIIR7PKS7QZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:12:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税忧虑引发印尼盾和股市暴跌，印尼人抢购黄金]]></title><description><![CDATA[数以百计的印尼人蜂拥购买金条，押注贵金属的价值可以使他们在这个东南亚最大经济体的货币和股市暴跌时免受未来更艰难的经济时期的影响。【原文：Hundreds of Indonesians are flocking to buy gold bars, betting that the precious metal's value could shield them from tougher economic times ahead as the currency and the stock market tumble in South East Asia's largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/indonesians-rush-gold-rupiah-stocks-plunge-amid-us-tariff-worries-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LI2D52P2W5KYZH7V2QMGPGXDTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Verizon称谷歌人工智能客服人员带动销售额跃升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Verizon 称，该公司利用谷歌模型为客户服务代表打造的人工智能助理缩短了通话时间，使他们有时间向客户销售产品，从而导致销售额激增。【原文：Verizon said an AI assistant for the company's customer service representatives built using Google models had cut down on call times and freed them up to sell products to customers, leading to a surge in sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/verizon-says-google-ai-customer-service-agents-has-led-sales-jump-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GIJQCGBZ5PQNI3LBY5IEWMYA4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 JD Sports 未受关税影响，利润增长乏力]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国体育用品零售商 JD Sports 周三预测，即使在美国关税的潜在影响尚未显现之前，今年的利润增长也将微乎其微，主要市场的贸易环境预计将 "动荡不安"。【原文：British sportswear retailer JD Sports on Wednesday forecast little or no profit growth this year, even before any potential impact from U.S. tariffs, with the trading environment in its key markets expected to be "volatile".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/britains-jd-sports-flags-little-profit-growth-before-any-tariff-hit-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BS5PAMP4ZPE7JEFPRQGP2347E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 12:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长称中国贸易升级是不幸的，也是他们的损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，中国对美国征收84%报复性关税的举动对中国政府来说是不幸的，也是一个失败的主张。【原文：China's move to impose 84% retaliatory tariffs against the United States is unfortunate and a losing proposition for Beijing, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-trade-escalation-unfortunate-loss-them-us-treasury-secretary-says-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7NVKWONFFPN5GYCAXL6NEDVGA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰硝基化学公司签署 3.1 亿美元协议，为美国军方供应 TNT]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰国防部副部长说，波兰炸药制造商硝化公司（Nitro-Chem）周三签署了一项协议，将向一家美国公司供应价值 12 亿兹罗提（约合 3.1 亿美元）的炸药，供美国军方使用。【原文：Polish explosives maker Nitro-Chem signed a deal on Wednesday to supply explosives worth 1.2 billion zlotys ($310 million) to a U.S. firm, intended for the U.S. military, the deputy defence minister said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/polands-nitro-chem-signs-310-mln-deal-supply-tnt-us-military-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JDSY7YF3NJIBBI76BQEXXOP6Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:40:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将美国公司列入出口管制不可靠实体名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据中国商务部的声明，中国商务部周三将12家美国公司列入出口管制名单，将6家美国公司列入不可靠实体名单，并于周四生效。【原文：China's commerce ministry on Wednesday added 12 U.S. companies to its export control list and six to its unreliable entities list, effective Thursday, according to ministry statements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china-adds-us-companies-lists-export-control-unreliable-entities-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2VOFKKTTJJ4XFKCO5KPVIUDRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在世贸组织对特朗普 "鲁莽 "征收关税表示 "严重关切]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周三告诉世界贸易组织，美国决定对北京征收所谓的对等关税，这有可能进一步破坏全球贸易的稳定。【原文：China told the World Trade Organization on Wednesday that the United States' decision to impose what it has called reciprocal tariffs on Beijing threatens to further destabilise global trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-expresses-grave-concern-wto-about-reckless-trump-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMZ3OXAETBOYNI5TWO2BT4KFPM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:25:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士称，在美国提高关税之际，印度正在权衡出口支持措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位政府消息人士称，在美国提高关税后全球不确定性增加的情况下，印度正在考虑采取延长银行贷款利息补贴和提供奖励等措施，以帮助出口商实现多样化。【原文：India is considering measures such as extending interest subsidies on bank loans and offering incentives to help exporters to diversify amid rising global uncertainty after the U.S. tariff hikes, two government sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-weighs-export-support-measures-amid-us-tariff-hike-say-government-sources-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3LEH6CFSRKGDN7DN4XIYXYMFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:17:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在沙特的首次亮相中，特斯拉面临着沙漠高温、充电桩数量少的问题，但马斯克没有提出抗议]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周四开始在沙特阿拉伯销售汽车，在该国连接首都利雅得和圣城麦加的一条东西向主干道上，长达 900 公里（559 英里）的路段上没有一个充电站。【原文：Tesla starts selling cars in Saudi Arabia on Thursday, a country where on a 900-kilometre (559 mile) stretch of its main east-west highway linking the capital Riyadh and the holy city of Mecca there isn't a single charging station.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/saudi-debut-tesla-faces-desert-heat-few-chargers-no-musk-protests-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLVZXP5FEZKAFOQRSA4AHP623E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期抵押贷款利率上周下降，申请量激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，最受欢迎的美国住房贷款利率降至 6.61%，为 10 月份以来的最低利率，从而推动了抵押贷款申请，即使在唐纳德-特朗普总统决定对全球贸易伙伴征收全面关税导致全球股市暴跌的情况下也是如此。【原文：The interest rate for the most popular U.S. home loan dropped to 6.61% last week, the lowest rate since October, giving a boost to mortgage applications even as global stocks tumbled in the wake of President Donald Trump's decision to impose sweeping tariffs on trading partners the world over.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-mortgage-rate-dropped-last-week-applications-surged-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CJUAWWEMZPCVFG5BNHJZXEK4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛重申年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛在周三的投资者日之前表示，将坚持其年度销售额和营业收入增长预期。【原文：Walmart is sticking to its annual sales and operating income growth forecast, the retailer said ahead of its investor day on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-reaffirms-annual-sales-forecast-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQIH4GRKDJO4TEEPP5GUEQGJB4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普取消了圣诞节？中国装饰品制造商报告没有美国订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[塑料圣诞树和其他节日装饰品的中国生产商说，美国客户的订单对他们的业务至关重要，现在应该已经开始收到订单了。但由于进口关税激增，它们还没有收到订单。【原文：Chinese producers of plastic Christmas trees and other festive decorations say orders from U.S. clients, which are crucial for their business, should have started to come in by now. But because of surging import tariffs, they haven't.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/has-trump-cancelled-christmas-chinas-decorations-makers-report-no-us-orders-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBEFCKWFZ5O6TPPEO63R4AY5IU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税阻碍旅游需求，达美航空利润前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[达美航空公司（Delta Air Lines）周三预测本季度利润低于预期，称由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的全面关税政策导致经济不确定性，旅游需求 "基本停滞"。【原文：Delta Air Lines on Wednesday forecast a lower-than-expected profit in the current quarter, saying travel demand has "largely stalled" due to economic uncertainty caused by U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/deltas-profit-outlook-dims-tariffs-stall-travel-demand-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7IFSAM4Y6RNPFILF64YCFLWPOE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称 TikTok 交易需接受政府审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[针对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将 TikTok 出售期限延长 75 天一事，中国商务部周三表示，包括技术出口在内的具体商业安排必须经过中国政府的审查。【原文：Specific business arrangements including technology exports must be reviewed by the Chinese government, China's commerce ministry said on Wednesday, in reference to U.S. President Donald Trump's 75-day extension of the TikTok sale deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/china-says-tiktok-deal-subject-government-review-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUAM4VDHO5IIVMCGWIJTWAZ6K4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:23:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标现在是 "债券故事]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKMTQ3NJCFM3TETNQFMWD4VJKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管加征关税，美国大豆仍将运抵中国海岸]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据消息来源和航运数据，中国将在4月至5月期间接收约300万吨美国大豆，尽管对美国产品征收新的更高关税可能会阻碍中国最大的美国农产品进口项目。【原文：China is set to receive about 3 million metric tons of U.S. soybeans in April-May, according to sources and shipping data, despite new higher tariffs on American products that are poised to choke off flows of China's largest U.S. farm import item.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/wave-us-soybeans-set-reach-chinas-shores-despite-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FINLGK3MY5JJ5J7CAYMRFI2LSI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙将在 2025 年对二叠纪的一半油井进行 "三重压裂"，以削减成本和时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油巨头雪佛龙公司（Chevron）告诉路透社记者，该公司计划在二叠纪盆地更多地使用一种可以一次在三口油井中压裂地下岩石的技术，以努力缩短石油生产的时间并降低成本。【原文：U.S. oil major Chevron plans to increase the use of a technique that allows it to fracture subterranean rock in three wells at a time in the Permian basin, the company told Reuters, in an effort to cut the time and cost of producing oil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-triple-frac-half-permian-oil-wells-2025-cut-costs-time-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBTJ6XEHSVJJ7GMQHFWVJU7PSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:09:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储会议纪要或显示特朗普 "解放日 "前关税辩论的范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）4月2日宣布加征关税的消息震动市场并使通胀上升和增长放缓的预测更为普遍之前，美联储官员在上个月开会时对滞胀风险的担忧程度可能会在本周三的会议上变得更加清晰。【原文：How concerned Federal Reserve officials were over stagflation risks as they met last month may become more clear on Wednesday in a readout of a gathering held before President Donald Trump's April 2 tariff announcement shook markets and made forecasts for higher inflation and slower growth more widespread.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-minutes-may-show-scope-tariff-debate-ahead-trumps-liberation-day-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7W5EMO4FFPI3DMKAZA4PJQ4HU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[个人投资者纷纷致电顾问，但仍留在市场中]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布全面征收关税，引发了对经济衰退的担忧，个人投资者纷纷打电话寻求建议。其中最紧张的是那些即将退休的人，因为市场下滑对他们的投资组合造成了严重破坏。【原文：Individual investors have been working the phones for advice in the wake of U.S. President Donald Trump's sweeping tariff announcements which have sparked fears of a recession. Among the most nervous are those approaching retirement, as the market slide wreaks havoc with portfolios.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/individual-investors-flood-advisers-with-calls-stay-market-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QKM7F7XVYNIGLJTEJHY3AZLYUI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 10:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对华加征关税，人民币跌至 2007 年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于不断升级的中美贸易战令货币市场惶恐不安，中国离岸人民币隔夜跌至历史新低，周三收于逾17年来最弱水平。【原文：China's yuan ended at its weakest level in more than 17 years on Wednesday after its offshore counterpart fell to a record low overnight, as an escalating Sino-U.S. trade war rattled currency markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yuan-falls-2007-lows-us-tariffs-china-kick-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUZ5IOKZOBKKJHMZVQNU3MVMFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行警告英国面临特朗普关税对全球打击的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦，4月9日（路透社）--英国央行表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收进口关税，全球经济受到冲击和金融市场进一步暴跌的风险已经增加，英国也面临着这一后果。【原文：LONDON, April 9 (Reuters) - Risks of a hit to the global economy and further sharp falls in financial markets have grown due to U.S. President Donald Trump's import tariffs and the UK is exposed to the fallout, the Bank of England said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/bank-england-warns-uk-is-exposed-risks-global-hit-trump-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBDGHFCFQJMCJPI2J77IURBEDY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航运集团三井物产抓住关税推动贸易路线转变的机遇--首席执行官称]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本第二大航运公司三井物产航运（Mitsui O.S.K.Lines，MOL）首席执行官桥本武（Takeshi Hashimoto）表示，该公司的目标是抓住美国新关税导致贸易路线发生变化所带来的机遇。【原文：Mitsui O.S.K. Lines (MOL) , Japan's second-largest shipping company, aims to capitalise on opportunities that emerge from a shift in trade routes driven by new U.S. tariffs, CEO Takeshi Hashimoto said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shipping-group-mitsui-osk-seize-opportunities-tariffs-drive-trade-route-shift-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UG7D4HHI5VIBHEHH26W4GQNLDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对等关税撼动全球贸易，期货市场步履维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的对等关税生效，加深了人们对其对全球经济造成损害的担忧，美国股指期货在前一交易日遭到严重抛售后，周三陷入困境。【原文：U.S. stock index futures struggled on Wednesday after a heavy sell-off in the previous session, as President Donald Trump's reciprocal tariff took effect, deepening worries about their damage to the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-struggle-trumps-reciprocal-tariffs-shake-up-global-trade-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVNX3CBQNRNJFD67QSZP25ODFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:44:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道苹果供应商 Luxshare 考虑在美国生产以应对关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果供应商力士德公司董事长周三在电话中告诉分析师，该公司正在与客户商讨如何应对美国关税，将更多生产转移到中国以外的地区，包括美国。【原文：Apple supplier Luxshare is in talks with customers on ways to respond to U.S. tariffs by shifting more production outside China, including the United States, its chairwoman told analysts in a telephone call on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-supplier-luxshare-weighs-manufacturing-us-tackle-tariffs-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REIXYO5ZL5IDFAX3QW6DTFNLKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国审查社交媒体上与关税相关的部分内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国对数十个国家的 "对等 "关税生效（包括对中国商品征收104%的巨额关税）之后，中国于周三开始审查社交媒体上一些与关税相关的内容，而批评美国的帖子则成为热门话题。【原文：China began censoring some tariff-related content on social media on Wednesday after U.S. "reciprocal" tariffs on dozens of countries took effect, including massive 104% duties on Chinese goods, while posts criticising the U.S. were top hits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-censors-some-tariff-related-content-social-media-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGEUJK75V5N3FMOGUQX34JN5TI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场环境严峻，大众汽车公司的特拉托第一季度销售额下降 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，大众汽车卡车部门特拉托（Traton）报告称，第一季度交付量下降了 10%，原因是市场环境充满挑战。【原文：Volkswagen's truck unit Traton reported a 10% drop in first-quarter deliveries on Wednesday, citing a challenging market environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/vws-traton-posts-10-drop-q1-sales-challenging-market-environment-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2EAUPF4JZPUVG3XSN33TJOHKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:16:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 为 110 亿美元的欧洲房地产收购狂潮做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blackstone 表示，尽管市场动荡加剧，但该公司已完成 98 亿欧元（108 亿美元）的欧洲房地产基金，押注该行业的复苏迹象。【原文：Blackstone has said it has closed a 9.8 billion euro ($10.8 billion) European property fund, as it bets on signs of recovery for the sector despite deepening market turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstone-gears-up-11-billion-european-property-buying-spree-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63FQSDQY2BNOVK7A3AM6Q66VE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本最高货币外交官敦促全球合作应对关税困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最高货币外交官周三表示，日本将与七国集团发达经济体和国际货币基金组织合作，帮助稳定美国关税引发的市场崩溃。【原文：Japan will cooperate with the Group of Seven advanced economies and the International Monetary Fund to help stablise a market rout unleashed by U.S. tariffs, the country's top currency diplomat said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-top-currency-diplomat-urges-global-cooperation-fight-tariff-woes-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COB2SSK5TNIWFLJAERYUIED2L4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国监管机构在达成补救措施后结束对谷歌车载服务的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国联邦卡特尔局周三表示，在美国科技巨头承诺采取补救措施解决其对竞争的担忧后，该局已结束了对谷歌汽车服务的诉讼程序。【原文：Germany's Federal Cartel Office has closed proceedings into Google's automotive services after the U.S. tech giant committed to remedies addressing its concerns over competition, the regulator said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/german-regulator-ends-probe-into-googles-in-car-services-after-agreed-remedies-2025-04-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNNLW3WKXJPEFMCTSVAPL5C2XU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 09:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>