<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:12:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:12:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Boeing's biggest 737 MAX model moves to next stage in certification but still faces hurdles]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Aviation Administration has approved Boeing's largest variant of its best-selling 737 MAX jet, the MAX 10, to move to the second phase of flight testing on the plane's long-delayed certification campaign, according to a source familiar with the program.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-biggest-737-max-model-moves-next-stage-certification-still-faces-hurdles-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SIAUEBXX5PKVMH3KPEBEB4HVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:50:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FCC approves SpaceX plan to deploy additional 7,500 Starlink satellites]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Communications Commission said on Friday it has approved SpaceX's request to deploy another 7,500 second-generation Starlink satellites as it works to boost internet service worldwide.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/fcc-approves-spacex-plan-deploy-additional-7500-starlink-satellites-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UY2ZCMHDZOT5PIQ3WCFNBX6FY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:33:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Casino operator Wynn CFO Julie Cameron-Doe retires]]></title><description><![CDATA[Casino operator Wynn Resorts said on Friday that CFO Julie Cameron-Doe would retire and that company insider Craig Jeffrey Fullalove would replace her as finance chief.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/casino-operator-wynn-cfo-julie-cameron-doe-retires-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNYODPERB5MCNEUOULETKQQZGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US SEC dismisses lawsuit against Rio Tinto ex-CFO]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday dismissed its lawsuit against a former Rio Tinto , chief financial officer, ending a long-running fraud case over a bad investment in a Mozambique coal project by one of the world's largest mining companies.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-sec-dismisses-lawsuit-against-rio-tinto-ex-cfo-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5JY7M2O5NKZ3ILKWYD4662SAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Commerce Department drops plan to impose restrictions on Chinese-made drones]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Commerce Department said on Friday it has withdrawn a plan to impose restrictions on Chinese drones to address national security concerns after an earlier crackdown on passenger cars and trucks.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-commerce-department-drops-plan-impose-restrictions-chinese-made-drones-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBNQK5YA7FPUVILPJLTZCYH3SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Supreme Court to hear suit claiming Cisco helped China pursue Falun Gong]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Supreme Court on Friday agreed to hear an appeal by Cisco Systems in which the tech company and President Donald Trump's administration are asking the justices to limit the reach of a federal law that has been used to hold corporations liable for human rights abuses committed abroad.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-hear-suit-claiming-cisco-helped-china-pursue-falun-gong-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JHXBYSQ2CNLQLBOTB42D5OOH6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:57:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Supreme Court to weigh FCC's power to fine wireless carriers]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Supreme Court agreed on Friday to hear a dispute involving fines imposed by the Federal Communications Commission on major U.S. wireless carriers for sharing customer location data without consent in the latest case to reach the justices challenging the powers of a U.S. regulatory agency.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-supreme-court-weigh-fccs-power-fine-wireless-carriers-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7NOD32QWPRJRLEPFS37O25CQU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump's oil strategy for Venezuela leaves Citgo auction in limbo]]></title><description><![CDATA[As U.S. President Donald Trump moves quickly to put together a $100 billion effort to revive Venezuela's oil industry, the administration has yet to finalize the fate of the crown jewel of the country's foreign assets, U.S. refining company Citgo Petroleum, sources close to the matter said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trumps-oil-strategy-venezuela-leaves-citgo-auction-limbo-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEP2S64JGVMJZEN6WG46EREAZY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US FTC wins ruling blocking Edwards Lifesciences' acquisition of JenaValve]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission won a ruling on Friday blocking Edwards Lifesciences' acquisition of JenaValve Technology, court records showed.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/ftc-wins-ruling-blocking-edwards-lifesciences-acquisition-jenavalve-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YG7UUG7AWNNAPGC2RCCGPIXRXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two Fed officials say key to fixing US housing more about supply than financing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two Federal Reserve officials on Friday expressed some skepticism that a Trump administration plan to lower housing costs by buying billions in mortgage-backed bonds will do much to lift the troubled sector.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/two-fed-officials-say-key-fixing-us-housing-more-about-supply-than-financing-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q7IXQRYMBNM63D2YSIM3JOHAP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exxon CEO says prepared to evaluate reentering Venezuela]]></title><description><![CDATA[Exxon Mobil CEO Darren Woods said on Friday the U.S. oil major could hit the ground running in Venezuela and evaluate potentially returning to Venezuela.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-ceo-says-prepared-evaluate-reentering-venezuela-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UF6CHDQLYJK6TDXINTXOBJYS3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:48:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[California governor proposes $200 million in new state EV tax rebates]]></title><description><![CDATA[California Governor Gavin Newsom is proposing $200 million in new state electric-vehicle tax rebates after Congress earlier this year ended a federal $7,500 state tax deduction on new EVs, the state said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/california-governor-proposes-200-million-new-state-ev-tax-rebates-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVAMC3AEOVPYTBO7FAULNXD3VA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Musk's X sues music publishers over alleged licensing conspiracy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elon Musk's X Corp sued 18 major music publishers and a leading U.S. music industry trade association on Friday, alleging they conspired to block competition and force the social media platform to purchase licenses for musical works at inflated rates.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/musks-x-sues-music-publishers-over-alleged-licensing-conspiracy-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2PDXAD6EVJERAX35IRLSLUFPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:20:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump pushes 'drill baby drill' agenda to Venezuela, hurts producers at home]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. oil producers already reeling from low oil prices are facing renewed pressures, as President Donald Trump pushes them to boost output in Venezuela - a move that would weaken the oil market, cut revenues and hurt industry at home.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-pushes-drill-baby-drill-agenda-venezuela-hurts-producers-home-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4ZDAFDUGVPJBOPB5OBLTYL35M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI, SoftBank invest $1 billion in SB Energy as Stargate buildout expands]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI and SoftBank Group will jointly invest $1 billion in SB Energy, a SoftBank-owned provider of data-center and power infrastructure, as part of their $500 billion Stargate initiative aimed at building out AI infrastructure.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/openai-softbank-invest-1-billion-sb-energy-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSGQURZP7BIP5CVWGDHUM6NFHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:26:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis scraps US plug-in hybrid sales, citing weak demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chrysler parent Stellantis said on Friday it will stop selling plug-in hybrid versions of the Jeep Wrangler and Grand Cherokee, and the Chrysler Pacifica minivan, in the United States as it navigates soft demand and shifts its North American electrification strategy.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-scraps-us-plug-in-hybrid-sales-citing-weak-demand-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZ5TTPXMMVI77ELSRFZWBBGPSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:19:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed's Bostic says high inflation still central bank's main challenge -radio interview]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔·博斯蒂克周五在电台访谈中表示，通胀问题仍是其经济关切的核心焦点。他同时指出，在更广泛的不确定性背景下，就业市场仍处于低招聘、零裁员的状态。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic said on Friday in a radio interview inflation issues are still at the forefront of his economic concerns, in comments that added the job market continues to be in a low-hire, no-fire mode amid broader uncertainties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bostic-says-high-inflation-still-central-banks-main-challenge-radio-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JX2KM2CEQRJ5VP7LEIN2QVVWHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷已就货币互换协议向美国偿还债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Argentina has repaid the United States for a currency swap framework it provided to the South American country last year to stabilize its economy, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and Argentina's central bank said on Friday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-has-repaid-us-currency-swap-deal-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HG2GGJZAKNNVFJHMFHDMNAABQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:30:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储数据显示，2025年第三季度美国家庭财富创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周五公布的数据显示，在股市人工智能热潮和房价持续上涨的推动下，2025年第三季度美国家庭财富达到创纪录的180万亿美元以上。【原文：U.S. household wealth hit a record high of more than $180 trillion in the third quarter of 2025 on the back of an AI-boom in the stock market and continued gains in home prices, data from the Federal Reserve showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-household-wealth-hit-record-third-quarter-2025-fed-data-shows-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7CKXTGP65KK7L6ZLYEKEPPIKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:21:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储任命地区银行董事会主席和副主席]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve Board on Friday announced the chairs and vice chairs of its 12 regional banks for this year, a list that includes Emerson Electric Co's chief executive Lal Karsanbhai as chair of the St. Louis Fed, and Liberty Mutual Insurance CEO Tim Sweeney as deputy chair of the Boston Fed.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fed-appoints-regional-bank-board-chairs-vice-chairs-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BR36VB3YHZLAZGTDSBSTKJR7AA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:13:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街争相为力拓-嘉能可交易提供咨询，瞄准1亿美元佣金]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rio Tinto's ambition to acquire Glencore and create the world's largest mining company worth more than $200 billion could see Wall Street advisers share more than $100 million in fees.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-jostles-advise-rio-glencore-eyes-100-million-prize-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNR4SU2NIZNHJBKFMCF4ACMJ44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:01:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[委内瑞拉债券持有人团体寻求授权启动债务重组谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[A key group of Venezuelan bondholders said on Friday they were ready to start debt restructuring talks with the country once authorisation for such discussions was granted.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venezuela-bondholder-group-eyes-authorisation-start-debt-restructuring-talks-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BD3BSHFGFZOCVOBTVNI6PMPM4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:21:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫就委内瑞拉问题召开石油会议，与会者包括独立人士，且与丹佛存在密切联系]]></title><description><![CDATA[The White House is summoning oil executives to discuss potential investment in Venezuela on Friday, and while a preliminary list of attendees features the big names of American oil - Chevron , Exxon Mobil and ConocoPhillips - it also includes several smaller independents and private equity-backed players.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/white-house-oil-meeting-venezuela-includes-independents-strong-links-denver-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CWQQWTFNBP5NJNDXVUABBCWB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mercosur bloc to sign EU trade deal on January 17]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷外交部周五表示，南方共同市场将于1月17日与欧盟签署长期延宕的贸易协定，标志着历经多年谈判后取得重大突破。【原文：The Mercosur bloc will sign its long-delayed trade agreement with the European Union on January 17, Argentina’s foreign ministry said Friday, marking a breakthrough after years of negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mercosur-bloc-sign-eu-trade-deal-january-17-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXIJCTYAJJNLZN7HTXNSXQQQEI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部在明尼苏达州欺诈调查期间通知部分企业，贝森特称]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部金融犯罪执法网络（FinCEN）已通知部分企业，因涉嫌利用新冠疫情期间的税收优惠政策实施欺诈行为，这些企业正接受调查。财政部长斯科特·贝森特周五表示。【原文：The U.S. Treasury Department's Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) has notified some businesses that they are under investigation for alleged fraud involving COVID-era tax incentives, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/treasury-notifies-some-businesses-amid-minnesota-fraud-probe-bessent-says-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XYTBRTABNOQBPVINPWUBM7GGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行瞄准委内瑞拉投资，摩根大通被认为具有优势]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国在委内瑞拉石油领域的介入为国际银行提供了潜在机遇，其中摩根大通凭借其在该国的深厚历史积淀及过往参与国际贸易融资的经验，占据了有利地位。【原文：The U.S. involvement in Venezuela's oil sector offers a potential opportunity for international banks, with JPMorgan Chase in an advantageous spot due to its history in the country and past involvement with international trade financing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/banks-eye-venezuela-investment-jpmorgan-seen-with-advantage-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">423TVW4ICRLP7GYVPBMIZJQG2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:51:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democratic senators demand Apple, Google take X and Grok off app stores over sexual images]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名美国民主党参议员呼吁苹果公司和谷歌母公司Alphabet将X平台及其内置聊天机器人Grok从各自应用商店下架，原因是该平台上存在大量未经同意传播的女性和未成年人性影像。【原文：Three Democratic U.S. senators are calling on Apple and Alphabet's Google to remove X and its built-in chabot Grok from their respective app stores over the spread of nonconsensual sexual images of women and minors on the platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/democratic-senators-demand-apple-google-take-x-grok-off-app-stores-over-sexual-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLX6CCXKJZN6PDDJFQSOWSPGSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:29:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管特朗普承诺制造业将蓬勃发展，美国工厂员工人数仍在下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年12月，美国制造业就业岗位延续了自去年春季以来的连续八个月下滑态势。此前，特朗普总统推行了激进的进口关税政策，他曾承诺此举将通过重塑全球贸易格局以利于美国工人，从而推动蓝领岗位复苏。【原文：U.S. manufacturing jobs in December continued an eight-month skid that began last spring after President Donald Trump rolled out aggressive import taxes that he pledged would lead to a resurgence of blue-collar jobs by reshuffling world trade to favor U.S. workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-factory-headcount-falling-despite-trumps-promised-manufacturing-boom-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URT34B5XKVMUBNEFTADCQJZM24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普似乎提前发布了部分就业数据。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周四晚间在其社交媒体账户上发布了一张图表，其中包含的就业市场数据直至周五上午才正式公布。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump posted a chart on his social media account late Thursday that included job-market data that was not publicly released until Friday morning.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-appears-have-posted-some-jobs-data-early-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USMMURRN6VKY7LJZWJOJVSN2DQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗行业并购专家齐聚旧金山，期待2026年迎来巨额并购交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[据十余位顶级银行家和律师透露，医疗保健领域的交易撮合者本周末将齐聚旧金山，押注2026年将掀起新一轮巨额并购浪潮。届时行业规模或将超越2019年和2021年——这两年该领域并购交易总额曾逼近5000亿美元，堪称行业巅峰。【原文：Healthcare dealmakers are heading to San Francisco this weekend betting on a new wave of mega-mergers in 2026 that could eclipse the industry’s standout years of 2019 and 2021 when such tie-ups approached half a trillion dollars, according to more than a dozen top bankers and lawyers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/healthcare-dealmakers-head-san-francisco-hoping-megamergers-2026-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTTIQ2BHABI7ZMVV4BR65ZO7TA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:19:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>