<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:16:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:16:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行员工在布鲁塞尔表达对联合信贷银行交易的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周四社交媒体上的一篇帖子和两位知情人士透露，德国商业银行的一个员工代表代表团会见了欧洲议会议员，表达了他们对联合信贷银行可能收购德国商业银行的担忧。【原文：A delegation of employee representatives from Commerzbank met with members of the European Parliament to voice their concerns about a possible takeover by UniCredit , according to a social media post on Thursday and two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commerzbank-employees-voice-unicredit-deal-concerns-brussels-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6K6UHPWWTRISPN52RSBVAUAPEE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数下降；7 月份就业增长趋于稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量有所下降，表明 7 月份就业稳步增长，尽管由于招聘放缓，一些下岗工人经历了长时间的失业。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for jobless benefits fell last week, pointing to steady job growth in July, though some laid off workers are experiencing long spells of unemployment because of a moderation in hiring.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-weekly-jobless-claims-fall-job-growth-appears-steady-july-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RGLBGYVVAZPTFOX3OMZH6NUUBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月零售销售超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 6 月份零售额的反弹幅度超过预期，但部分增幅可能反映了受关税影响的一些商品的价格上涨。【原文：U.S. retail sales rebounded more than expected in June, but some of the increase likely reflected higher prices for some goods exposed to tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-retail-sales-beat-expectations-june-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTGX3S2WMBPHDK42IHCS6HF3XE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯沃琪首席执行官准备接受上半年艰难经营后利润下降的事实]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯沃琪首席执行官尼克-海耶克（Nick Hayek）周四表示，希望中国市场在 2025 年下半年有所改善，但也准备接受瑞士制表商上半年利润骤降后的利润下降。【原文：Swatch Chief Executive Nick Hayek is counting on improvements in China in the second half of 2025, he said on Thursday, but is also ready to accept lower profits after the Swiss watchmaker's first half profit plunged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/swatch-ceo-ready-accept-lower-profit-after-tough-first-half-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQHEU7C4QBOD3DMT4AFDZVBRBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[作为机器人出租车交易的一部分，优步将向电动汽车制造商 Lucid 投资 3 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步（Uber）和 Lucid 周四表示，优步将向电动汽车制造商 Lucid 投资 3 亿美元，双方计划明年晚些时候在美国一个主要城市开始机器人出租车业务。【原文：Uber will invest $300 million in electric vehicle maker Lucid in a robotaxi deal that aims to start with one major U.S. city late next year, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-invest-300-million-ev-maker-lucid-part-robotaxi-deal-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC4V7YKABBOX3FV2EVVOVZNWOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:36:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国央行行长：美国关税将吞噬德国今明两年的经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国央行行长约阿希姆-纳格尔（Joachim Nagel）在接受路透社采访时表示，德国央行预计2026年德国经济将增长0.7%，但如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁要征收30%的关税，这一增长可能会被吞噬。【原文：The Bundebank expects growth of 0.7% in Germany in 2026 but this could be eaten up if U.S. tariffs of 30% threatened by President Donald Trump were implemented, the central bank's President Joachim Nagel told Reuters in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/us-tariffs-would-eat-up-german-growth-this-year-next-bundesbank-chief-says-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYJBDN6P6BLOFBNM63OFPAW7UA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第五第三银行公司季度利润因利息收入增加而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fifth Third Bancorp 周四公布第二季度利润增长，原因是较低的存款成本增加了该地区性银行的利息收入，缓冲了更大的贷款损失。【原文：Fifth Third Bancorp reported a rise in second-quarter profit on Thursday, as lower deposit costs boosted the regional bank's interest income, cushioning a larger buffer for loan losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fifth-third-bancorps-quarterly-profit-rises-higher-interest-income-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U3CP5M642VJGTHLGD65UCLV2UM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:38:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小特朗普支持的 GrabAGun 在纽交所上市首日大幅下跌后略有回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[小唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump Jr.）支持的 GrabAGun 公司的股价在周四的盘前交易中上涨了 2%，在纽约证券交易所首次亮相时因空头支票合并而暴跌 24% 后略有回升。【原文：Donald Trump Jr.-backed GrabAGun's shares inched up 2% in premarket trading on Thursday, recovering slightly after tumbling 24% in their New York Stock Exchange debut following a blank-check merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trump-jr-backed-grabagun-recovers-slightly-after-sharp-nyse-debut-drop-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7B4JLQNUVP7HD7C7UFJVNDJYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:36:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅培因医疗器械需求超预期获利，股价因预期下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[雅培周四公布的第二季度利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于对其医疗设备（包括连续血糖监测仪）的强劲需求。【原文：Abbott beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit on Thursday, driven by strong demand for its medical devices including continuous glucose monitors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/abbott-beats-profit-estimates-medical-devices-demand-shares-fall-forecast-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQNAPFXEBNKM7OWQLMLPAFDBVA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Teneo 收购普华永道澳大利亚重组部门，扩大金融咨询业务范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[Teneo 周四表示，它已经收购了审计公司普华永道在澳大利亚的业务重组服务部门，这家管理咨询公司正努力扩大其在该地区的金融咨询业务。【原文：Teneo said on Thursday it has acquired the Australia business restructuring services unit of auditing firm PwC, as the management consultancy seeks to expand its financial advisory presence in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/teneo-acquires-pwcs-australia-restructuring-unit-expand-financial-advisory-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2FPC3UM7BNUZLNO3EJQJZK34E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：鲍威尔装腔作势后市场趋于平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E27C24A25FOR5FDTGTJIVCOJEU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:23:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百时美施贵宝和辉瑞将直接向患者销售血液稀释剂 Eliquis]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国制药商百时美施贵宝和辉瑞公司周四表示，它们将通过一项新计划，以折扣价直接向现金支付的患者提供血液稀释剂 Eliquis。【原文：US drugmakers Bristol Myers and Pfizer said on Thursday that they will make their blood thinner, Eliquis, available directly to cash-paying patients at discounted rate through a new program.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bristol-myers-pfizer-sell-blood-thinner-eliquis-directly-patients-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLH55R7AEVLPZLUYSUK6AFVHGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:21:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保险业领头羊旅行者因承保能力增强而利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[旅行者保险公司（Travelers Companies）周四发布报告称，受承保能力增强和投资回报率提高的推动，该公司第二季度利润猛增近三倍。【原文：Travelers Companies' profit surged nearly three-fold in the second quarter, the insurance bellwether reported on Thursday, boosted by stronger underwriting and higher investment returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/insurance-bellwether-travelers-posts-profit-surge-stronger-underwriting-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3KOZYQPZ5IOXEJOZ55JRCZRKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司股价下跌，纽瓦克机场故障影响盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）股价在周四的盘前交易中下跌了 3%，此前该公司表示纽瓦克机场的运营障碍将影响其第三季度的盈利。【原文：United Airlines shares fell 3% in premarket trading on Thursday, after the U.S. carrier flagged a hit to third-quarter earnings from operational snags at Newark airport.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/united-airlines-shares-fall-newark-snags-weigh-profit-forecast-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2XNG6YZVZISDD7YLMHUMDE67I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:54:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用电气航空航天集团（GE Aerospace）因老式喷气机维修需求上升而上调 2025 年利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用电气航空航天集团周四上调了 2025 年的利润预期，原因是由于飞机交付持续推迟，航空公司对老式喷气式飞机的保留时间延长，因此对售后维修服务的需求强劲。【原文：GE Aerospace raised its 2025 profit forecast on Thursday, buoyed by strong demand for aftermarket maintenance services as airlines hold on to older jets longer due to persistent aircraft delivery delays.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ge-aerospace-lifts-2025-profit-view-rising-demand-fixing-older-jets-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUE6V3YBT5MSJMYQGMP3LFAROI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:42:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在汽车制造商马自达的家乡，日本选民看不到关税缓和的希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商马自达的家乡日本西部广岛的人说，马自达打喷嚏时，每个人都会感冒，但最近，汽车零部件制造商山口雄二担心，一场深寒即将来临。【原文：When car maker Mazda sneezes, everyone catches a cold, say people in its hometown of Hiroshima in western Japan, but these days, auto parts maker Yuji Yamaguchi fears a deep chill is on the way.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/japan-voters-see-little-hope-tariff-reprieve-car-maker-mazdas-hometown-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGJQV2DQARM3VHJAN5RL64X7BA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:33:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国赢得英国对三星合并案仲裁裁决的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国电子集团董事长李在镕（Jay Y. Lee）被韩国最高法院宣布无罪后不久，韩国周四在与美国对冲基金埃利奥特（Elliott）就 2015 年三星两家关联公司合并案的最新上诉中胜诉。【原文：South Korea on Thursday won its latest appeal in its dispute with U.S. hedge fund Elliott over the 2015 merger of two affiliates of Samsung, shortly after the electronics group's Chairman Jay Y. Lee was cleared by South Korea's top court.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/south-korea-wins-uk-appeal-over-arbitration-ruling-samsung-merger-case-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAQ6L5VQYJK4RJ4S4IHSDYCSZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:29:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克指数、标准普尔指数期货在疯狂交易后受芯片股提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，纳斯达克和 S&amp;P 500 指数上涨，原因是台湾台积电的强劲业绩提振了芯片制造商，而此前美联储的独立性问题引发了市场的担忧。【原文：Futures tracking the Nasdaq and the S&amp;P 500 rose on Thursday, as strong results from Taiwan's TSMC boosted chipmakers after a rollercoaster session marked by concerns about the Federal Reserve's independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nasdaq-sp-futures-lifted-by-chip-stocks-after-wild-session-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HV3J53MBURP7ZLYPEVI4TS274M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:23:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受益于美国客户需求，Wipro 第一季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度第四大 IT 服务公司 Wipro 表示，预计 2026 财年第二季度的收入将介于 25.6 亿美元至 26.1 亿美元之间，此前该公司 6 月份的销售额超过了分析师的预期，这主要得益于其部分美洲业务的增长。【原文：India's fourth-largest IT services player Wipro said it expects revenue in the second quarter of fiscal year 2026 to range between $2.56 billion and $2.61 billion, after sales in the June quarter topped analysts estimates, helped by growth in a part of its Americas business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-wipro-beats-first-quarter-revenue-estimates-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2IGMSM3TNNU5EX43CEBMATWWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Seven & i 表明，即使加强了管理，日本的并购仍不容易]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本零售商 Seven & i 控股公司（Seven & i Holdings）又一次辜负了投资者要求改善回报的呼声。这一次，它也提醒人们，即使在公司治理全面改革的情况下，大手笔的收购在日本也绝非易事。【原文：Japanese retailer Seven & i Holdings has again lived up to a reputation for shrugging off investor calls for better returns. This time, it also provides a reminder that even amid a corporate governance overhaul, big-ticket acquisitions are far from easy in Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/seven-i-shows-japan-ma-is-still-not-easy-even-with-better-governance-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVRFO7U3KZJLPMVMM337FFOY2M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百事公司预计年度核心盈利降幅较小]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事公司（PepsiCo）周四表示，受惠于美国市场对其能量饮料和健康汽水品牌需求的回升，以及有利汇率带来的好处，该公司预计年度核心利润的降幅将有所收窄。【原文：PepsiCo said on Thursday that it was expecting a smaller drop in annual core profit, helped by a rebound in demand for its energy drinks and healthier soda brands in the United States as well as benefits from favorable foreign exchange rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/pepsico-expects-smaller-decline-annual-core-earnings-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDSGUZESWRN2DO7Z2F2ULNVHKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:11:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者安德森将出庭为自己在 Facebook 隐私案中的角色辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[著名投资人马克-安德森（Marc Andreessen）定于周四出庭作证，为他在 2019 年脸书董事会因涉嫌违反与美国监管机构达成的保护用户隐私协议而被处以 50 亿美元罚款时所扮演的角色进行辩护。【原文：Famed investor Marc Andreessen is scheduled to take the stand on Thursday to defend his role on the Facebook board of directors when it was hit with a $5 billion fine in 2019 for alleged violations of an agreement with a U.S. regulator to protect user privacy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/investor-andreessen-take-stand-defend-his-role-facebook-privacy-case-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJDICKLGIBNGTIX5DMTZJLTOCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市的高估值依赖于强劲的盈利能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着华尔街飙升至历史新高，美国股市看起来几乎和以往一样昂贵，投资者们正在争论这种高估值究竟是看跌信号，还是重科技的市场盈利前景所证明的合理性。【原文：With Wall Street's surge to record highs, the U.S. stock market looks nearly as expensive as ever, and investors are debating whether the lofty valuations are a bearish signal or justified by the technology-heavy market's profit outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lofty-us-stock-market-valuations-bank-earnings-strength-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A723YXK56FNM5AK6NXKIA2GY44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citadel 证券公司称，美国企业有望通过回购提振股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[Citadel 证券公司股票和股票衍生品战略主管斯科特-鲁布纳（Scott Rubner）表示，预计 2025 年美国公司将购买价值 1 万亿美元的自家股票，并仍将是美国股票的最大买家。【原文：Companies in the U.S. are expected to buy $1 trillion worth of their own stock in 2025 and remain the largest buyers of U.S. equities, according to Scott Rubner, Citadel Securities' head of equity and equity derivatives strategy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-corporates-expected-buoy-stock-markets-with-buy-backs-says-citadel-securities-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULBLQZ4ZDZLJ5BOBZAV7664HHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丹麦希望拥有世界上最强大的量子计算机]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德基金会（Novo Nordisk Foundation）和丹麦国有信贷基金（Denmark's state-owned credit fund）周四表示，他们将投资于据称是世界上最强大的量子计算机，旨在彻底改变药物发现和材料科学等领域。
量子计算有望完成今天的系统需要数百万年才能完成的计算，并能开启医学、化学和许多其他领域的发现。【原文：The Novo Nordisk Foundation and Denmark's state-owned credit fund said on Thursday they will invest in what they say will be the world's most powerful quantum computer, aiming to revolutionize areas such as drug discovery and materials science.
Quantum computing holds the promise of carrying out calculations that would take today's systems millions of years and could unlock discoveries in medicine, chemistry and many other fields where near-infinite seas of possible combinations of molecules confound classical computers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/denmark-aims-host-worlds-most-powerful-quantum-computer-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBWNCYLDGVMHFAXGQE3F5FFTG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普将新日铁评级下调至 "BBB"，原因是美国钢铁交易导致债务紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球评级机构S&amp;P周四将新日铁的评级从 "BBB+"下调至 "BBB"，前景展望为 "负面"，理由是这家日本钢铁制造商在上个月收购美国钢铁公司后财务状况日益紧张。【原文：Global rating agency S&amp;P downgraded Nippon Steel to 'BBB' from 'BBB+' with a 'negative' outlook on Thursday, citing an increasing financial strain following the Japanese steelmaker's acquisition of U.S. Steel last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sp-downgrades-nippon-steel-bbb-debt-strain-us-steel-deal-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5OPNOZMRVOPJLSGYULCJU4LZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:54:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃首席执行官希望欧盟削减 "不必要的 "汽车关税，以化解特朗普的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司（Volvo Cars）首席执行官周四在接受路透社采访时，敦促欧盟削减对美国制造汽车征收的 10%关税，认为欧洲汽车制造商不需要受到美国竞争对手的保护。【原文：The chief executive of Volvo Cars urged the European Union to cut its 10% tariff on American-made cars, arguing that European automakers do not need protection from U.S. competitors, in an interview with Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-ceo-wants-eu-cut-unnecessary-auto-tariffs-defuse-trump-threat-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTE34JT25RPNDO54COL56KYPBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国乐可兰公司股价上涨，原因是数据中心需求促使公司上调业绩展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[在北美数据中心业务强劲增长的推动下，这家法国电气和数字楼宇基础设施集团上调了年度销售目标。【原文：Shares of Legrand gained more than 8% in early trading on Thursday, after the French electrical and digital building infrastructure group hiked its annual sales target driven by strong growth in the data centre segment in North America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/frances-legrand-shares-rise-data-centre-demand-prompts-outlook-hike-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXUYR4CINZMXPDGSRGE6HA6CUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Ocado 公司表示，当务之急是在 2025/26 年实现现金流转正]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国网上超市和技术集团 Ocado 公布上半年基本盈利增长 76.5%，并表示下一财年的首要任务是创造现金，而不是消耗现金。【原文：Ocado , the British online supermarket and technology group, said its priority was to generate cash, rather than consume it, in its next financial year, as it reported a 76.5% rise in underlying earnings in its first half.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/britains-ocado-says-core-priority-turn-cash-flow-positive-202526-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SQ4FW5I3X5KXPEH52HZTFOEBBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第二季度利润大增 60%，创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[受益于人工智能应用领域对半导体的需求激增，全球最大的合约芯片制造商台积电周四公布第二季度净利润大增 60.7%，超出市场预期，创下历史新高。【原文：TSMC , the world's largest contract chipmaker, posted a 60.7% jump in second-quarter net profit on Thursday, beating market forecasts and hitting a historic high as it benefited from surging demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tsmc-q2-profit-surges-60-reaches-historic-high-2025-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMBVIH6SWVNLDDIRTSTZTFNWWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 05:38:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>