<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:40:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:40:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[英国石油公司股价上涨，原因是英国《金融时报》报道有更多竞争对手正在研究收购可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国石油公司（BP）股价周五走高，此前《金融时报》报道称，一些竞争对手已经就收购这家在伦敦上市的石油公司的可能性进行了 "测算"。【原文：Shares in BP edged higher on Friday after the Financial Times reported a number of rivals have "run the numbers" about a possible takeover of the London-listed oil company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bp-shares-rise-ft-reports-more-rivals-looking-possible-takeover-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4QC77EL65LPRPFVBXZ3KXS7SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:33:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国以外的投资者抢购亚洲基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者纷纷抛售美股，涌入亚洲股票基金，因为特朗普政府的关税给美国经济增长前景蒙上了一层阴影，美国市场多年来傲视全球的涨势是否会画上句号。【原文：Investors have been selling U.S. shares and piling into Asian equity funds, as the Trump administration's tariffs cast a cloud over the U.S. growth outlook and whether years of world-beating gains in U.S. markets may be drawing to an end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-looking-beyond-us-scoop-up-asian-funds-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANSZ35JWU5M27MKCBZER7PQC7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易谈判开始，中国出口商准备再次向美国出口商品]]></title><description><![CDATA[在北京和华盛顿即将在瑞士举行贸易谈判之际，中国的船运代理公司在一系列因美国加征关税而导致的取消订单后，已恢复为运往美国的货物购买集装箱舱位。【原文：China-based shipping agents have resumed buying container space for goods headed for the United States after a series of U.S. tariff-induced cancellations, as Beijing and Washington head for trade talks in Switzerland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trade-talks-begin-chinese-exporters-prepare-get-goods-moving-us-again-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JISLFS5EKBPQHLIGJAH4KYLEUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本新日铁年度利润下降 36%，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本第一大钢铁制造商新日铁周五公布，在截至 3 月份的一年中，该公司实现净利润 3,502 亿日元（约合 24.1 亿美元），同比下降 36%，但高于分析师的预期。【原文：Nippon Steel , Japan's top steelmaker, posted on Friday 350.2 billion yen ($2.41 billion) in net profit for the year ended in March, down 36% from a year ago but beating analysts' forecasts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-nippon-steel-annual-profit-down-36-beats-forecasts-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TFYYGZ5Y7FLPVG7G76ZQYVD2IE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:44:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海关延误导致贸易中断，中国 4 月份大豆进口量创十年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易商和分析师称，由于长期通关延误，以及巴西因收获放缓和物流问题而延迟装运，扰乱了正常的货物流动，中国 4 月份的大豆进口量骤降至 10 年来的最低点。【原文：China's soybean imports plunged to a 10-year low in April as prolonged customs clearance delays and late Brazilian shipments caused by harvest slowdowns and logistics issues disrupted the usual flow of cargoes, traders and analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-april-soybean-imports-hit-decade-low-customs-delays-disrupt-trade-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ENS2RQFWT5IRJB4BTAXIWNCGHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:43:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[透视：中国决定就特朗普关税问题坐到谈判桌前的内幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[自美国总统唐纳德-特朗普上个月对中国征收高额关税以来，中国政府做出了回应。它在国家和社交媒体上张贴毛泽东的图像，抨击 "帝国主义者"，并发出信息：向恶霸屈服是危险的，中国不会退让。【原文：Since U.S. President Donald Trump imposed steep tariffs on China last month, Beijing has responded in kind. On state and social media, it posted images of Mao Zedong, lambasted "imperialists," and sent a message: capitulation to bullies is dangerous, and it wouldn't back down.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/inside-chinas-decision-come-table-trump-tariffs-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LNPT2AIWNJZPMV6ZNODYLUAPU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:35:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国央行行长称美国关税影响的不确定性很高]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国中央银行行长周五表示，美国关税政策对泰国的影响将是长期的，潜在影响的不确定性非常高。【原文：The effect on Thailand from the United States' tariff policy will be prolonged, with a very high degree of uncertainty over the potential impact, its central chief bank said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/very-high-degree-uncertainty-thailand-over-us-tariffs-central-bank-chief-says-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4A5D4PV7AJNZDODEXXJIRYE3RQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:19:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国航空公司所有者 IAG 订购 53 架新的空中客车和波音长途客机]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国航空公司（British Airways）的所有者 IAG 周五表示，它已订购了 53 架新的空中客车和波音长途飞机。【原文：British Airways owner IAG on Friday said it had placed an order for 53 new Airbus and Boeing long-haul aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/british-airways-owner-iag-orders-53-new-airbus-boeing-long-haul-aircraft-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O6L52NEOQVKHHL7AZUWZ3VBESM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[抵御联合信贷银行，德国商业银行利润意外增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行（Commerzbank）周五表示，第一季度净利润增长近 12%，打破了人们对其净利润下降的预期，从而避免了被意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）收购的可能。【原文：Germany's Commerzbank , fending off a possible takeover by Italy's UniCredit , said on Friday that net profit rose nearly 12% in the first quarter, defying expectations for a drop.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commerzbank-posts-surprise-profit-increase-it-fends-off-unicredit-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUTLDELJJNJTXCOPJL7UVKVN4A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 05:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国防需求强劲，三菱重工今年营业利润增长 10]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本三菱重工（MHI）周五预计，由于国防需求强劲，该公司今年的营业利润将增长9.6%，但不会将美国关税的影响考虑在内，此前该公司2024-25财年的盈利不及分析师预期。【原文：Japan's Mitsubishi Heavy Industries (MHI) on Friday projected a 9.6% growth in operating profit this year on robust defence demand without weaving in impact of U.S. tariffs, after its fiscal 2024-25 earnings missed analyst expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mitsubishi-heavy-sees-10-operating-profit-growth-this-year-robust-defence-demand-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4SOSA7ITJJ4LMGH7YXCNDGCDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 05:04:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标中美谈判激起希望与怀疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LT3VY2YTFIALCC6PNU5IEDKGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 04:43:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称英伟达为中国修改H20芯片以克服美国出口管制]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，在美国对原始型号的人工智能芯片实施出口限制后，英伟达计划在未来两个月内面向中国发布其 H20 人工智能芯片的降级版本。【原文：Nvidia plans to release a downgraded version of its H20 artificial intelligence chip for China in the next two months, following U.S. export restrictions on the original model, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-modifies-h20-chip-china-overcome-us-export-controls-sources-say-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YNTLSWCSBMMPBVCOOJ6PEXWMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 04:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：明星健康》黑客称他们向印度高管发出死亡威胁和子弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年泄露印度医疗保险公司 Star Health 所掌握的敏感个人数据的黑客已对向该公司首席执行官和财务主管发送死亡威胁和子弹的行为负责。【原文：The hacker who leaked sensitive personal data held by Indian health insurer Star Health last year has taken responsibility for sending death threats and bullets to the company's chief executive and finance head.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/star-health-hacker-says-they-sent-death-threats-bullets-india-executives-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JHHZGM665OIZCGOSDWIIE4YSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 4 月进出口均超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的海关数据显示，中国4月份出口增长快于预期，而进口降幅收窄，这在本周末与美国进行破冰关税谈判之前给中国政府带来了一些宽慰。【原文：China's exports rose faster than expected in April, while imports narrowed their declines, customs data showed on Friday, giving Beijing some relief ahead of ice-breaker tariff talks with the U.S. this weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-exports-imports-beat-expectations-april-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVEJY7TOPNNVJO6TJ2BHZC33TY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 4 月出口好于预期，进口降幅收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的海关数据显示，中国4月份出口同比增长8.1%，进口萎缩0.2%，均未达到贸易大幅放缓的预期。【原文：China's exports expanded 8.1% year-on-year in April, while imports contracted 0.2%, customs data showed on Friday, both defying expectations for a much sharper slowdown in trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-april-exports-beat-expectations-imports-narrow-declines-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7CTQQ5FRFMOFPLGFHES3KVVRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国称对美国处理贸易问题的能力充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国外交部副部长华春莹周五表示，中国对其管理美国贸易问题的能力充满信心，此前一天，中美双方官员将在瑞士举行会议，讨论彼此加征关税的问题。【原文：China has full confidence in its ability to manage U.S. trade issues, Vice Foreign Minister Hua Chunying said on Friday, a day before officials from both sides are set to meet in Switzerland to discuss the tariffs they have imposed on each other.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-says-it-has-full-confidence-ability-manage-us-trade-issues-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQX54OGWS5PFFFZAZWIE2V7L6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本股市跳涨，美元因贸易希望而走强；比特币飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国与英国达成的贸易协议燃起了日本与其他国家的关税谈判取得进展的希望，受美元兑日元大涨的支撑，日本股市周五跳涨。【原文：Japanese stocks jumped on Friday, supported by the dollar's surge against the yen, after a U.S. trade deal with Britain fuelled hopes of progress in tariff talks with other countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27ECRZ4YTNJZDGD7KCNGY5VSOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美贸易会议前油价变化不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五早盘，油价变化不大，上一交易日上涨超过3%，原因是主要石油消费国美国和中国之间的贸易紧张局势出现缓和迹象，而且英国宣布与美国达成一项 "突破性 "贸易协议。【原文：Oil prices were little changed early on Friday after rising more than 3% in the previous session, as trade tension between top oil consumers U.S. and China showed signs of easing and Britain announced a "breakthrough" trade deal with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-little-changed-ahead-sino-us-trade-meeting-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NE6ZYC74G5LKVA6T6YWSPASDZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:24:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，贝恩资本将出售中国数据中心业务，估值可能超过 40 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士透露，美国投资公司贝恩资本正在寻求出售数据中心运营商WinTriX DC集团在中国的业务，交易价值可能超过40亿美元。【原文：U.S. investment firm Bain Capital is seeking to sell the China business of data centre operator WinTriX DC Group, in a deal that could value the business at over $4 billion, two people with knowledge of the situation said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bain-capital-sell-china-data-centre-business-likely-valued-over-4-billion-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R6EULNW7ZVP3HOTSRFVFFHWRYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:19:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中芯国际联合首席执行官表示将密切关注关税对需求的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国半导体代工企业--中芯国际集成电路制造有限公司（SMIC）联席首席执行官赵海军周五表示，将密切关注关税对需求的影响，并补充说目前尚不清楚第二季度的情况。【原文：China's semiconductor foundry, Semiconductor Manufacturing International Corporation (SMIC), will closely monitor the impact of tariffs on demand, co-CEO Zhao Haijun said on Friday, adding that visibility for the second quarter was not clear at the moment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/smic-closely-monitor-impact-tariffs-demand-says-co-ceo-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H6V2UYXO6ZPPNBBYXPSSUKCITI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 01:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[进入中美贸易谈判，美元有望实现周线上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元兑大多数主要同业货币实现周度上涨，原因是美英贸易协议提高了人们对即将举行的中美谈判取得进展的希望，而在美联储表示不急于降息后，人们对美国即将降息的押注有所减弱。【原文：The dollar headed for a weekly gain on most major peers on Friday as a U.S.-UK trade deal raised hopes of progress in looming U.S.-China talks, while bets of imminent U.S. rate cuts receded after the Federal Reserve indicated it was in no hurry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/dollar-eyes-weekly-rise-into-us-china-trade-talks-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSESKQAD7NIE7I7IS4S7JZFCXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 01:35:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称 Hellman & Friedman 启动出售美国软件制造商 Enverus 的程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，私募股权公司 Hellman & Friedman 已经启动了对总部位于得克萨斯州的能源软件制造商 Enverus 的出售程序，该交易可能会使该公司的估值达到 60 亿美元左右。【原文：Private equity firm Hellman & Friedman has launched a sale process for Texas-based energy software maker Enverus in a deal that could value the company at around $6 billion, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/hellman-friedman-launches-sale-process-us-software-maker-enverus-sources-say-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IKXAWDWVXVORXB3MPMBJU77S2Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国房地产公司 CoStar 将以 19 亿美元收购澳大利亚 Domain 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Domain 控股公司周五表示，美国在线房地产公司 CoStar 将收购这家房地产分类公司，隐含企业价值为 30 亿澳元（19.2 亿美元）。【原文：Australia's Domain Holdings said on Friday U.S. online real estate firm CoStar would acquire the property classifieds company for an implied enterprise value of A$3 billion ($1.92 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-real-estate-firm-costar-buy-australias-domain-19-billion-deal-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">URNYZBEP4FLARMFXIQZQGSEFRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:25:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产放弃耗资 11 亿美元在日本南部建造电动汽车电池厂的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车周五表示，将放弃在日本西南部九州岛建造一座耗资 11 亿美元的电动汽车电池工厂的计划，这标志着这家陷入困境的汽车制造商的计划发生了最新变化。【原文：Nissan Motor said on Friday it would abandon a plan to build a $1.1 billion factory for electric vehicle batteries on Japan's southwestern island of Kyushu, marking the latest change of plans for the troubled automaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/nissan-abandons-plan-ev-battery-plant-southern-japan-nikkei-reports-2025-05-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RLX76GIMNJKVABDZUZ5Q7453E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 3 月实际工资连续第三个月下降，加班费减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周五公布的数据显示，在通胀持续高企的背景下，日本 3 月份实际工资连续第三个月下降，加班工资的下降速度为近一年来最快。【原文：Japanese real wages decreased for a third consecutive month in March against the background of relentless inflation, while overtime salaries fell at the fastest pace in almost a year, government data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/japan-march-real-wages-down-third-month-overtime-pay-falls-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCJT5H4FHJM27G6EDBT2YR4PNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 23:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新闻集团季度业绩超出预期，得益于道琼斯和数字房地产服务部门的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[受道琼斯业务和在线房地产服务增长的推动，新闻集团周四公布的第三季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，股价在延时交易中上涨约 3%。【原文：News Corp beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue and profit on Thursday, driven by growth in its Dow Jones business and online real estate services, sending its shares up about 3% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/news-corp-beats-quarterly-estimates-dow-jones-digital-real-estate-services-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4C4BREFXZLEXF4AKJTRPQYHTU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:49:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microchip 预测第一季度利润和收入高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片制造商微芯科技（Microchip Technology）继周四公布乐观的第四季度收入后，预计第一季度收入和利润将高于预期，这表明市场对其芯片的需求正在复苏。【原文：Chipmaker Microchip Technology forecast first-quarter revenue and profit above estimates following an upbeat fourth-quarter revenue on Thursday, signaling a recovery in demand for its chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microchip-forecasts-first-quarter-profit-revenue-above-estimates-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ELWASYEJJKEZEUPLSJIW367JE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[怪物饮料因需求不振，季度净销售额意外下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[怪物饮料公司（Monster Beverage）周四公布的第一季度收入意外下降，表明在经济不确定的情况下，美国消费者减少了对价格昂贵的能量饮料的消费。【原文：Monster Beverage reported a surprise fall in first-quarter revenue on Thursday, signaling consumers in the U.S. pared back spending on pricey energy drinks amid economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/monster-beverage-posts-surprise-fall-quarterly-net-sales-choppy-demand-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMU7RUDOJVL7FFN6BGB6XCIVK4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:27:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚麦格理全年利润增长近 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，澳大利亚麦格理公司（Macquarie）发布公告称，受资产管理部门业绩费用增加的推动，全年利润增长近 5%。【原文：Australia's Macquarie posted a nearly 5% rise in its full-year profit on Friday, driven by increased performance fees recorded by its asset management segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australias-macquarie-posts-near-5-rise-full-year-profit-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBXYWROZAFIQNMY2WB2XE2KO5Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:22:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商务部长称下月将推出数十项贸易协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）周四对 CNBC 表示，华盛顿将在未来一个月内推出数十项贸易协议，但对大多数国家征收的 10%关税可能会继续保留。【原文：Washington will roll out dozens of trade deals over the next month, but a 10% tariff imposed on most countries will likely stay, U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick told CNBC on Thursday】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-commerce-chief-says-dozens-trade-deals-be-rolled-out-over-next-month-2025-05-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NSEL44JFZIORBCYUFXMLNXAIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>