<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:12:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:12:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[星座品牌公司警告啤酒销量承压，因拉美裔消费者减少消费]]></title><description><![CDATA[星座品牌公司高管周四表示，由于经济不确定性持续存在，以及核心客户群拉美裔消费者失业率居高不下，啤酒销售可能继续面临波动和压力，这些因素持续抑制着消费支出。【原文：Constellation Brands executives said on Thursday beer sales could remain volatile and under pressure as economic uncertainty and high unemployment among Hispanic consumers, its core customer base, continue to weigh on spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/constellation-brands-warns-beer-sales-under-pressure-hispanic-consumers-cut-back-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KE7K6KYS5LFRPV57PKZQNAGLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:04:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通将为大众汽车新平台提供车载信息娱乐技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车计划与美国芯片设计公司高通达成长期供货协议，为这家德国汽车制造商的新软件平台提供车载娱乐信息技术。【原文：Volkswagen plans a long-term supply deal with U.S. chip designer Qualcomm to deliver infotainment technology for the German carmaker's new software platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/qualcomm-provide-infotainment-tech-new-volkswagen-platform-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWVWWE2CCBOZFNMAAJZXGJWUXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将在未来一两个月内决定房利美和房地美上市事宜，联邦住房金融局局长普尔特向CNBC透露。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦住房金融局局长威廉·普尔特周四表示，他预计特朗普总统将在未来一两个月内决定是否通过首次公开募股（IPO）出售美国房利美和房地美部分股权。【原文：U.S. Federal Housing Finance Agency Director William Pulte said on Thursday he expects President Donald Trump will make a decision in the next month or two on whether to sell a piece of the U.S. mortgage agencies Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac in an initial public offering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-decide-freddie-fannie-ipo-next-month-or-two-fhfas-pulte-tells-cnbc-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SC4Q6PGQPNO33CY7X7NEWJTEBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:48:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：四位消息人士称，维托尔公司已获得美国初步许可，可就委内瑞拉石油进出口事宜展开谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位消息人士周四透露，全球最大大宗商品贸易商之一维托尔公司已获得美国政府颁发的初步特别许可，可就未来18个月从委内瑞拉进出口石油展开谈判。【原文：Vitol, one of the world's largest commodity traders, has received a preliminary special license from the U.S. government to begin negotiations to import and export oil from Venezuela for 18 months, four sources said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/vitol-gets-preliminary-us-license-begin-negotiations-venezuelan-oil-imports-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUVBDWOSQJMFFIQZHETX6AEL44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:22:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨克斯百货摇摇欲坠，百货公司押注购物体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[从巴黎到纽约，各大百货公司正着力打造精心策划的购物体验——包括冰上表演、品酒会和建筑导览——以期重新吸引顾客。【原文：From Paris to New York, department stores are sharpening their focus on curated shopping experiences - ice-skating shows, wine tasting and architectural tours - to try to win back shoppers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/saks-teeters-department-stores-bet-shopping-experiences-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDWVQ3JDUZP3NBGC3T65BNZHXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:20:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储报告称，12月美国消费者对就业市场担忧加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周三发布的报告显示，尽管对个人财务状况的担忧有所缓解，但美国民众在12月对就业市场的忧虑加剧，同时短期通胀预期有所上升。【原文：Americans grew more worried about the job market in December even as anxieties over personal finances faded, while near-term inflation expectations increased, a report from the New York Federal Reserve showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumers-more-worried-about-job-market-december-new-york-fed-report-says-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BCXD5APVRVNHZGCBD6ZFF4XJKM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：知情人士称，中国安踏体育已提出收购皮诺家族持有的彪马29%股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，中国安踏体育已提出收购法国皮诺家族持有的德国运动品牌彪马29%股权，该德国运动服饰企业目前经营陷入困境。【原文：China's Anta Sports Products has offered to buy 29% of struggling German sportswear firm Puma from France's Pinault family, three people with knowledge of the talks said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinas-anta-sports-has-offered-buy-pinault-familys-29-puma-stake-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OL6ZTGOHUVKZZCTVOC7LLRGHKY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:49:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国10月批发库存进一步增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国批发库存10月再度增长，这表明在连续两个季度拖累经济增长后，库存可能在第四季度为国内生产总值贡献正向影响。【原文：U.S. wholesale inventories increased again in October, suggesting inventories could add to gross domestic product in the fourth quarter after being a drag for two straight quarters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-wholesale-inventories-increase-further-october-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QRP2KT5M7JOIHOOB57GWCUOC5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列亚基亚航空与捷蓝航空达成美国境内航班衔接协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列阿基亚航空公司周四宣布，已与美国低成本航空公司捷蓝航空达成协议，允许其乘客在美国境内以及前往拉丁美洲和加勒比地区的航线上转乘捷蓝航班。【原文：Israel's Arkia Airlines said on Thursday it signed a deal with low-cost U.S. carrier JetBlue Airways that would allow its customers to connect on JetBlue flights in the United States and to Latin America and the Caribbean.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israels-arkia-forges-deal-with-jetblue-flight-connections-us-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SXZQYY2FZFK3DIMWSFV7QICJFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:30:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创企业MiniMax集团在香港IPO募资6.19亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创企业MiniMax集团周四宣布，其香港首次公开募股最终定价为每股165港元，募集资金48.2亿港元（约合6.186亿美元）。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence startup MiniMax Group said on Thursday it has set the final offer price for its Hong Kong initial public offering at HK$165 per share, raising HK$4.82 billion ($618.60 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-ai-startup-minimax-group-raises-619-million-hong-kong-ipo-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PJW4GX4K5IJNEAWSV4JM5J5CA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:53:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍金路伟任命米兰诉讼业务新合伙人]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍金路伟宣布，随着该律所全球范围内任命28名新合伙人和53名新顾问，其米兰诉讼部门的亚历山德罗·博雷洛已晋升为合伙人。【原文：Hogan Lovells said it had promoted Alessandro Borrello as partner in its litigation department in Milan as the law firm named 28 new partners and 53 new counsels globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hogan-lovells-names-new-partner-litigation-milan-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUSO7JXYHFLORMIEA7BKN5K2JY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:48:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国国防部授予Mistral AI框架协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国国防部周四宣布，已与人工智能公司Mistral AI签订框架协议。【原文：France's Ministry of the Armed Forces has awarded a framework agreement to artificial intelligence company Mistral AI, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frances-armed-forces-ministry-awards-mistral-ai-framework-agreement-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y76VFE5V4VOQNJJVRXQ2OUNQZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:45:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国10月贸易赤字降至2009年以来最低水平，因进口减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国10月贸易逆差大幅收窄，降至2009年中期以来的最低水平，主要因进口减少。若这一趋势得以延续，贸易有望在第四季度再次为经济增长作出贡献。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit contracted sharply in October, hitting the lowest level since mid-2009 as imports declined, a trend that if sustained could see trade again adding to economic growth in the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-october-trade-deficit-lowest-since-2009-imports-decline-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KNL6XSZQVNABLTG2NA2BKICMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员米兰表示，他预计今年将降息150个基点。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬·米兰周四表示，他预计今年将降息150个基点以提振美国劳动力市场。米兰的任期将于1月底结束。【原文：Stephen Miran, a Federal Reserve governor whose term ends at the end of January, said Thursday that he is looking for 150 basis points of interest-rate cuts this year to boost the U.S. labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-miran-says-hes-looking-rate-cut-150-basis-points-this-year-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYLI4N2NTRPKVHJGYEL6V7BWPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛亚公司估值达90亿美元，这家数据安全企业完成4亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据安全公司Cyera周四宣布完成4亿美元后期融资，其估值在短短一年多时间内翻了三倍，达到90亿美元，凸显出市场对人工智能驱动的数据保护工具需求激增。【原文：Data security firm Cyera said on Thursday it raised $400 million in a late-stage funding round, with its valuation tripling in little over a year to $9 billion, highlighting the surge in demand for AI-driven data protection tools.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/cyera-valued-9-billion-data-security-firm-raises-400-million-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5ZFF6ELVNJTXMU44GVJUFWJZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙重申其对华纳兄弟的收购要约优于奈飞的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙与天空舞蹈公司周四重申，其对华纳兄弟探索公司1084亿美元的收购要约优于竞争对手网飞，并补充称网飞要约核心部分——有线电视业务分拆的价值实际上毫无价值。【原文：Paramount Skydance reiterated that its $108.4 billion bid for Warner Bros Discovery was superior to rival Netflix on Thursday, adding that the value of the cable spinoff central to the Netflix offer is effectively worthless.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/paramount-sticks-30-per-share-bid-warner-bros-discovery-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZOLETALYRLBNNEJB6H7CBBJVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界经济论坛调查显示，2025年经商环境趋严]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界经济论坛周四发布的一项调查显示，由于全球在贸易、气候、技术和安全等议题上的合作恶化，2025年企业经营环境更为艰难。【原文：Companies found it harder to do business in 2025 due to a deterioration in global cooperation on issues including trade, climate, technology and security, a survey published by the World Economic Forum showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/world-economic-forum-survey-shows-doing-business-got-tougher-2025-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZT6JOFSEOBINLKQ3PGA7OYAPYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度生产率增速创两年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国第三季度劳动生产率增速创两年新高，企业对人工智能的大规模投资有效抑制了劳动力成本。【原文：U.S. worker productivity grew at its fastest pace in two years in the third quarter as businesses invested heavily in artificial intelligence, depressing labor costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-third-quarter-productivity-rises-fastest-pace-two-years-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC4EQHR66BI2JCFTVW6G6QL6ME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税与库存短缺推高铝价，美国消费者面临创纪录成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铝消费者的支付价格已创历史新高，远超进口关税和运输成本应有的水平。全球供应紧张加剧了关税和美国库存低位的负面影响。【原文：Aluminium consumers in the United States are paying record high prices, significantly above the level import levies and transport costs would warrant, as tight supplies globally aggravate the impact of tariffs and low U.S. inventories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tariffs-low-stocks-propel-aluminium-costs-records-us-consumers-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NPDY7YDBVPLBHL35OHFGJYWWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周初请失业金人数小幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周美国初请失业救济人数小幅上升，表明2025年底裁员规模相对较小，但劳动力需求依然疲软。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits rose moderately last week, suggesting that layoffs were relatively low at the end of 2025, though demand for labor remained sluggish.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-marginally-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RATQ4FZBBZMQTOLBHKN4UFENHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:41:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈维利将收购合同软件公司Sirion的多数股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权公司Haveli Investments已同意对Sirion进行多数股权投资。Sirion是一家提供人工智能驱动的商业合同起草、存储和管理软件的公司。双方于周四宣布了这一消息。【原文：U.S. private equity firm Haveli Investments has agreed to make a majority investment in Sirion, which provides software that uses artificial intelligence to draft, store and manage business contracts, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/haveli-buy-majority-stake-contract-software-firm-sirion-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMHFEIXMZ5LETCSZW3LWR2QI2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥联储称美国12月失业率可能为4.6%]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行周四预估，美国12月失业率维持在4.6%不变。该数据表明劳动力市场仍陷于低招聘、低解雇的状态，可能为美联储未来进一步降息提供更多依据。【原文：The U.S. unemployment rate was unchanged at 4.6% in December, the Chicago Federal Reserve estimated on Thursday, a figure that suggests the labor market remained stuck in a low-hire, low-fire mode and may add to the case for more Fed interest rate cuts ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-december-jobless-rate-likely-46-chicago-fed-says-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NY73HWZIJNO7NFMPZHNHWKUHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:33:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[边疆航空母公司任命新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[边疆集团（Frontier Group）——边疆航空（Frontier Airlines）的母公司——周四宣布，董事会已任命詹姆斯·G·登普西（James G. Dempsey）为公司首席执行官。【原文：Frontier Group , parent company of Frontier Airlines, said on Thursday the board appointed James G. Dempsey as its Chief Executive Officer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/frontier-airlines-parent-company-appoints-new-ceo-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNUK6ICV4BPNHC4OAXXYKJS5GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西12月年度通胀率可能进一步放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，巴西12月年度通胀率可能进一步放缓，连续第二个月跌破央行目标区间的上限。【原文：Brazil's annual inflation rate likely slowed further in December, a Reuters poll showed, falling further below the upper limit of the central bank's target range for a second month in a row.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-annual-inflation-rate-likely-slowed-further-december-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CD6RAOVLCRI4ZG5NNK4HRG52NI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:11:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电力公司签署26.5亿美元燃料电池协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电力公司周四宣布，其子公司将以约26.5亿美元的价格收购固体氧化物燃料电池的大部分期权，此举是该公司开发和建设燃料电池发电设施计划的一部分。【原文：American Electric Power said on Thursday its unit will buy a substantial portion of its option for solid oxide fuel cells in a deal worth about $2.65 billion as part of its plans to develop and build a fuel cell power generation facility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/american-electric-power-signs-265-billion-deal-fuel-cells-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XIAFFJ43L5JRFHZ6TYDYZ4US2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:46:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，维托尔和托克正就委内瑞拉石油销售事宜与美国进行磋商]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，全球两大商品贸易商维托尔和托克正与美国总统特朗普政府就委内瑞拉石油的营销事宜进行磋商。【原文：Vitol and Trafigura, two of the world's largest commodity traders, are in talks with the administration of U.S. President Donald Trump about the marketing of Venezuelan oil, four sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/vitol-trafigura-talks-with-us-venezuelan-oil-sales-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VOMI7DFXZVIB3GV3VX54QXZ2RU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯利康任命内部人士里克·苏亚雷斯为美国生物制药部门负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康周四任命公司内部人士里克·苏亚雷斯为美国生物制药部门负责人，领导这家制药商在其最大市场实施500亿美元的投资计划。【原文：AstraZeneca on Thursday appointed company insider Rick Suarez as the head of its U.S. biopharmaceuticals unit to lead the drugmaker's $50 billion investment plan in the company's largest market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-names-rick-suarez-head-us-biopharmaceuticals-unit-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CBBHKPDHZOZTL6MWBFD3NSRHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会已要求X公司将所有Grok文件保留至2026年底，发言人表示。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人周四表示，该机构已要求埃隆·马斯克旗下的社交媒体平台X保留其内置人工智能聊天机器人Grok的所有内部文件和数据，直至2026年底。【原文：The European Commission has ordered Elon Musk's social media site X to retain all internal documents and data relating to its built-in artificial intelligence chatbot, Grok, until the end of 2026, a commission spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eu-commission-has-ordered-x-retain-all-grok-documents-until-end-2026-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y75EA6GH7JOU7MUR2DTPKBXVBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，蒙太奇科技计划于明年1月在香港进行最高达10亿美元的股票发售。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，中国半导体设计公司蒙特吉科技计划最早于本月在香港进行二次上市，拟发行8亿至10亿美元股票，这将进一步加剧香港融资市场的火热态势。【原文：Chinese semiconductor designer Montage Technology plans a second listing in Hong Kong via a $800 million to $1 billion share offering as soon as this month, said two people with knowledge of the matter, adding to the hectic pace of fundraising in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/montage-technology-plans-up-1-billion-hong-kong-share-sale-january-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIZWW7T35NOWLJB4OKPKYEJQCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:01:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞标：特朗普的可见之手]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STBEBJ5FXRPC7GAJUQU7LKA3XU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>