<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:12:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:12:19 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊推出基于欧洲的新云服务以解决用户担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊旗下AWS云服务周四推出全新云服务，该服务完全部署于欧洲。此举旨在解决用户对主要美国供应商数据安全性的担忧，为欧洲大陆提供独立的替代方案。【原文：Amazon's AWS launched a new cloud service located entirely in Europe on Thursday, addressing user concerns about the data security delivered by mainly U.S.-based providers by offering the continent's own independent alternative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-launches-new-europe-based-cloud-service-address-user-concerns-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2CPM2AU7VM5DEVL6KFLYV7OQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士竞争监管机构对微软许可费展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士竞争委员会周四表示，已对微软在该国的许可费问题启动初步调查。【原文：Switzerland's competition commission said on Thursday it launched a preliminary investigation into Microsoft's licensing fees in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swiss-competition-authority-opens-probe-into-microsoft-licensing-fees-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIBFWXCSIFMQZHZSQWQJBNLQUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨克斯全球公司获得美国法院批准4亿美元纾困融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名破产法官周三初步批准了萨克斯全球公司的破产融资方案，允许该公司提取4亿美元新资金，尽管其分道扬镳的商业伙伴亚马逊公司对此提出异议。【原文：A U.S. bankruptcy judge on Wednesday granted ​initial approval of Saks Global’s bankruptcy financing, allowing the company to draw on $400 million in new ‌cash despite an objection from Saks' estranged business partner Amazon.com 
 .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/saks-global-obtains-us-court-approval-400-million-rescue-financing-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PEAQ6BA7HZOIVB5G6NHF3YJ6NE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普总统接受路透社采访的五大看点]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三在椭圆形办公室对美国总统唐纳德·特朗普进行了专访。以下是这场30分钟对话的若干要点：【原文：Reuters sat down with U.S. President Donald Trump for an interview in the Oval Office on Wednesday. Here are some takeaways from the 30-minute exchange:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/five-takeaways-reuters-interview-president-trump-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBQ4S7JW6VIXVMZMY6TC4WNY2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第四季度利润跃升35%创纪录，超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大代工芯片制造商台积电周四公布，第四季度净利润飙升35%，不仅超出市场预期，更创下历史新高。这得益于人工智能应用领域对半导体需求的激增。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest contract chipmaker, posted a 35% jump in fourth-quarter net profit on Thursday, beating market forecasts and hitting a record as it benefited from surging demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsmc-q4-profit-jumps-35-record-beats-expectations-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWJYUNMIARNMVGS3BLXIIISJH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞价：大盘轮动持续进行]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文·巴克兰带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q35MC6ZJV5PVZOJFLVT4CEGLIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚力拓投资者对潜在嘉能可交易的合理性提出质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚历史最悠久、规模最大的投资机构之一，近日加入了国内日益高涨的质疑声浪，对力拓集团潜在收购嘉能可的交易提出质疑，质疑该拟议合并的合理性及时机。【原文：One of Australia's oldest and largest investors has added to the growing local chorus of concerns about Rio Tinto's , potential acquisition of Glencore , questioning the proposed tie-up's merits and timing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-rio-tinto-investor-raises-concerns-over-merits-potential-glencore-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJRPJHDMBZJAXOIJRU2OM7DH2E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:12:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软创纪录收购土壤碳信用额，数据中心激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软已与Indigo Carbon达成协议，将购买创纪录的285万份与美国再生农业相关的土壤碳信用额。尽管人工智能相关的排放量激增，这家科技巨头仍致力于在2030年前实现"碳负排放"目标。【原文：Microsoft has agreed with Indigo Carbon to buy a record 2.85 million soil carbon credits linked to regenerative agriculture in the United States, as the tech giant aims to become "carbon negative" by 2030 despite surging emissions linked to AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/microsoft-record-deal-soil-carbon-credits-data-centres-surge-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JICVRS4IGRNXJBTJYKV2N3FKOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将在9月底前再次加息至1%或更高水平，可能提前至7月实施。]]></title><description><![CDATA[经济学家表示，日本央行很可能等到7月才会再次上调关键利率，其中超过75%的经济学家预计，该利率将从当前三十年来的低点0.75%升至9月的1%或更高水平。【原文：The Bank of Japan will likely wait until July before raising its key interest rate again, economists say, with more than 75% of them expecting it to climb to 1% or higher by September from the current three-decade high of just 0.75%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-raise-rates-again-1-or-higher-by-end-september-possibly-by-july-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6WOMW5X6ZPYVODQJYV7VN53GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经亚洲报道：中国拟制定英伟达H200芯片采购规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经亚洲》周四报道，中国正着手制定规则，限制国内先进人工智能芯片企业从英伟达等外国制造商处采购的数量。该报道援引了两位知情人士的消息。【原文：China is working to set rules on how many advanced artificial intelligence chip companies can buy from foreign makers such as Nvidia , Nikkei Asia reported on Thursday, citing two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-drafting-purchase-rules-nvidia-h200-chips-nikkei-asia-reports-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IL72LVLW5IJLP45P6XKHIV7CM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:21:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR为第二只亚洲私募信贷基金筹集25亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球投资公司KKR周四宣布，其第二只信用基金已完成25亿美元的募资，该基金专注于亚太地区私营部门发起的优质信贷投资。【原文：Global investment firm KKR said on Thursday that it has completed a $2.5 billion fundraising for its second credit fund focused on privately originated performing credit investments in the Asia-Pacific region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kkr-secures-25-billion-second-asia-private-credit-fund-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MU4XT77VNP2TBHLRONLCCPPRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田工业股价因收购要约提高而创历史新高，埃利奥特回应尚待公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，丰田汽车公司提高收购报价后，叉车制造商丰田工业的股价飙升至历史新高，并略高于新报价水平，市场预期可能还会出现更优报价。【原文：Shares of forklift maker Toyota Industries surged to a record high on Thursday after a sweetened bid from Toyota Motor , trading slightly above the new offer on hopes that a better price might be forthcoming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/toyota-industries-shares-hit-record-market-hopes-higher-buyout-offer-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OHUANSLDBM5DD6RCXUGIW4GFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:48:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价下跌，因特朗普缓解伊朗担忧；亚洲科技股走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，油价从数月高点回落，避险资产黄金也从历史峰值回落，此前美国总统特朗普缓解了市场对美国可能对伊朗采取军事行动的担忧。【原文：Oil prices retreated from multi-month highs on Thursday and safe-haven gold ​eased back from a record peak after U.S. President Donald Trump calmed market anxiety about potential U.S. military ‌action against Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOL77U4YEVJYNC7K6M4MPWKGLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴升级Qwen应用，支持订餐与旅行预订]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴周四对其Qwen人工智能应用进行了重大升级，称该应用现可执行订餐、预订旅行等任务，标志着其正更积极地进军面向消费者的AI领域。【原文：Alibaba on Thursday launched significant upgrades to its Qwen artificial intelligence app, saying it could now execute tasks such as order food delivery and make travel bookings as it more aggressively pushes into consumer-facing AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/alibaba-upgrades-qwen-app-order-food-book-travel-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VE3VDWQZFVMLPHYFPQYJFGE4GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元汇率持稳，交易员为大选做准备，干预担忧隐现]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四日元维持隔夜涨幅，但仍徘徊在18个月低点附近。因日本大选前强硬警告可能引发更多财政刺激，令交易员对干预保持警惕，日元汇率持续承压。【原文：The yen held onto overnight gains on Thursday but was pinned near 18-month lows as traders remained wary of intervention after strong warnings ahead of an election in Japan that could usher in more fiscal stimulus and keep the currency constrained.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-steadies-traders-gird-election-intervention-fears-lurk-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AINA2ET2CBLEXHCBCJ4ALGVRCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:38:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普总统接受路透社采访的精彩片段]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三在椭圆形办公室接受了路透社的专访。以下是部分关键引语：【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump sat for an interview with Reuters in the Oval Office on Wednesday. Here are some key quotes:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/key-quotes-president-trumps-interview-with-reuters-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7E3OEBAEVML7GKYDLRY3VI4DI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普支持委内瑞拉留在欧佩克]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，他认为委内瑞拉留在石油输出国组织（OPEC）会更好，但补充说他不确定这对美国是否更有利。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Wednesday that he believes it would be better for Venezuela to remain in the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries, or OPEC, but added he was unsure if that would be a better situation for the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-backs-venezuela-staying-opec-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KBZS3ZBBRJH7CUEHHBTF7TZ4M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase首席执行官阿姆斯特朗表示，公司无法支持当前形式的加密货币法案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase首席执行官兼联合创始人布莱恩·阿姆斯特朗周三表示，该公司无法支持美国参议员本周早些时候提出的一项立法草案，该草案旨在为加密货币建立监管框架。【原文：Coinbase CEO and co-founder Brian Armstrong said on Wednesday the company cannot support a draft legislation U.S. senators introduced earlier this week aimed at creating a regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/coinbase-cannot-support-crypto-bill-current-form-ceo-armstrong-says-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R57CSD5KA5JVNNHUK6D2KKGATA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称无意解雇美联储主席鲍威尔，尽管存在调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，尽管司法部对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔展开刑事调查，但他目前没有解雇鲍威尔的计划，但称现在说他最终会采取什么行动还"为时过早"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Wednesday he has no plans to fire Jerome Powell despite a Justice Department criminal investigation into the Federal Reserve chair, but it was "too early" to say what he would ultimately do.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-has-no-plan-fire-feds-powell-despite-investigation-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEFJSJRD4ZIZ5G5SFSELAIXBUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚银称全球贸易紧张局势加剧，贸易融资缺口达2.5万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲开发银行最新调查显示，全球金融机构去年未能满足企业贸易所需的2.5万亿美元融资需求，拖累了全球经济增长。【原文：Financial institutions globally failed to meet $2.5 trillion in financing that companies needed for trade last year, holding back the global economy, according to a new survey by the Asian Development Bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/global-trade-finance-gap-25-trillion-global-trade-tensions-rise-adb-says-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLMWIEASLNMZRHJU6KYHU5ARAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音就737 MAX坠机相关诉讼达成初步和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司已与一名加拿大男子达成初步和解协议，该男子在2019年埃塞俄比亚航空737 MAX客机起飞后不久的坠机事故中失去了六位亲人。【原文：Boeing has reached tentative settlements with a Canadian man who lost six relatives in the 2019 crash of an Ethiopian Air 737 MAX jet shortly after takeoff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-reaches-tentative-settlements-related-737-max-crash-lawsuits-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HYDUBHWARPHTH7JIIOCINXRMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特敦促日本央行采取"稳健"政策以应对过度外汇波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三发表声明称，财政部长斯科特·贝森特周一与日本财务大臣片山萨茨基会晤时，"强调了审慎制定和沟通货币政策的必要性"。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent met Japanese Finance Minister Satsuki Katayama on Monday and "emphasized the need for sound formulation and communication of monetary policy," the U.S. Treasury Department said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bessent-urges-sound-boj-policy-address-excess-fx-volatility-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTUFTV7PRJM7RDMOXUHBJVKLVI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:44:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌表示，美国输电系统是连接数据中心面临的最大挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌一名能源高管周三表示，接入美国输电系统已成为该公司在电网中为数据中心供电面临的最大难题，因为在某些地区，接入等待时间已激增至十多年。【原文：Connecting to the U.S. electrical transmission system has become the biggest problem for powering up Google data centers on the grid, as the wait times to connect surge to more than a decade in some parts of the country, an energy executive with Google said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-says-us-transmission-system-is-biggest-challenge-connecting-data-centers-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZOH3YBHCVO45BMPSOLCQT2NJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:40:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国油价下跌逾1美元，特朗普言论缓解对伊朗的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四亚洲早盘交易时段，美国油价下跌逾1美元。此前美国总统特朗普表示，伊朗镇压全国抗议活动中的杀戮行为正在减少，这缓解了市场对供应中断及可能对伊朗采取军事行动的担忧。【原文：U.S. oil prices fell more than $1 in early Asian trade on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump said killings in Iran's crackdown on nationwide protests were subsiding, easing fears of supply disruptions and possible military action against Iran.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-prices-dip-more-than-1-trump-remarks-reduce-fears-about-iran-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U7NSJ3NXXRPEJKCG3BRHX2YCI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:32:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称暂不征收关键矿产关税，将寻求海外供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周三表示，他目前决定暂不对稀土、锂等关键矿产征收关税，转而要求政府寻求从国际贸易伙伴处获取供应。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Wednesday he had opted for now against imposing tariffs on rare earths, lithium and other critical minerals, and instead ordered his administration to seek supplies from international trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-says-no-critical-minerals-tariffs-now-will-seek-overseas-supplies-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SO5XTWPYRIWBPELI4OIZDYV4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:25:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻报道称，Temporal正就将估值翻倍至50亿美元进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[软件初创企业Temporal Technologies正就新一轮融资进行深入谈判，估值达50亿美元，较三个月前融资时的估值翻倍。彭博社周三援引知情人士消息报道称。【原文：Software startup Temporal Technologies is in advanced talks ​to raise fresh capital ‌at a $5 billion valuation, double of what it was valued at in a financing three ‌months ago, Bloomberg News reported ​on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/temporal-talks-double-valuation-5-billion-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ESOMAHVC7BKOXGJ4MQU4DEMTBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第四季度利润有望大幅增长，得益于人工智能热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的人工智能芯片制造商台积电预计，受人工智能基础设施需求持续强劲推动，其第四季度净利润将跃升28%，创下历史新高。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest manufacturer of advanced artificial intelligence chips, is expected to post a 28% jump in fourth-quarter net profit to a record high on Thursday driven by ongoing strong demand for AI infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-profit-leap-driven-by-ai-boom-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W76TAPLVWVMBTBL2VAXVUZJ7VQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：SK海力士加速新芯片厂投产以满足内存需求，高管称]]></title><description><![CDATA[SK海力士高管表示，由于内存需求激增导致全球供应紧张，该公司计划将新工厂的投产时间提前三个月，并将于2月启动另一座新工厂的运营。【原文：SK Hynix plans to accelerate the opening of a new factory by three months and will also begin operating another new plant in February, a senior executive said, as surging memory demand pressures global supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/sk-hynix-speeds-up-new-chip-fab-opening-meet-memory-demand-executive-says-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DB6P7N6VYFJGDPKCFGEGN5EWMM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：实物资产创下新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，围绕伊朗与美国的地缘政治紧张局势持续升温，笼罩全球市场。尽管美国零售销售数据表现强劲，但该局势仍令华尔街股市下挫，推高油价，并使黄金及其他金属价格创下新高。【原文：Rising geopolitical tensions centering on Iran and the U.S. loomed large over world markets on Wednesday, overshadowing strong U.S. retail sales figures to push Wall Street lower, lift oil prices and send gold and other metals prices to new highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQENDR444ZISXPLHMPE2W7OBAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜克能源旗下公司将提前一个月取消客户账单中的风暴恢复费]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公用事业公司杜克能源旗下佛罗里达分公司周三表示，风暴损失回收费将比原计划提前一个月从客户账单中移除。【原文：U.S.-based utility Duke Energy's Florida unit said on Wednesday that the storm cost recovery charge would be removed from customer bills a month earlier than originally scheduled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/duke-energy-unit-drop-storm-recovery-charge-customer-bills-month-early-2026-01-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2BWXAYYVJPUBKXMIFB7TZC6I4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:59:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>