<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 21:05:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[哈里斯表示，她将为新的工会岗位提供税收抵免]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国副总统卡马拉-哈里斯（Kamala Harris）表示，她将为增加 "良好的工会工作 "的公司提供税收减免，就像钢铁行业为宾夕法尼亚州带来的工作一样。【原文：US Vice President Kamala Harris said she would offer tax credits to companies that increase "good union jobs" like the ones that the steel industry brought to Pennsylvania.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/harris-says-she-will-offer-tax-credits-new-union-jobs-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3SJM7BZFRLYPPLELBFHI4L26E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称，Alphabet、高盛等公司将就逾期提交文件的指控达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周三表示，Alphabet、高盛（Goldman Sachs）和其他一些公司同意支付合计 380 万美元的民事罚款，以了结美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）对逾期提交文件的指控。【原文：Alphabet , Goldman Sachs and a group of other firms agreed to pay a combined $3.8 million in civil penalties to settle U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charges over late filings, the regulator said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/alphabet-goldman-sachs-others-settle-charges-over-late-filings-sec-says-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SGGFKJJL2NJ7JJRCP55IHICYP4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，OpenAI 将取消非营利性控制，并给予 Sam Altman 股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉此事的人士告诉路透社，聊天软件制造商 OpenAI 正在制定一项计划，将其核心业务重组为一家营利性福利公司，不再受非营利性董事会的控制，此举将使该公司对投资者更具吸引力。【原文：ChatGPT-maker OpenAI is working on a plan to restructure its core business into a for-profit benefit corporation that will no longer be controlled by its non-profit board, people familiar with the matter told Reuters, in a move that will make the company more attractive to investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-remove-non-profit-control-give-sam-altman-equity-sources-say-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJWPA2BIY5KAPGS5EHC3FDIGI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[存储芯片需求强劲，美光预计第一季度收入可观]]></title><description><![CDATA[美光科技（Micron Technology）周三预测第一季度营收将高于华尔街预期，押注于人工智能行业对其高带宽内存（HBM）芯片的强劲需求，盘后该公司股价上涨 10%。【原文：Micron Technology forecast first-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, betting on strong demand for its high bandwidth memory (HBM) chips used by the AI industry, sending the company's shares up 10% after the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/micron-forecasts-first-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QERYHPXFGRIIVPEJLLLKLF3XTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储库格勒强烈支持降息半个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周三表示，她 "强烈支持 "美国央行将利率下调半个百分点的决定，这是新出现的对就业市场关注的一部分。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said on Wednesday that she "strongly supported" the U.S. central bank's decision to cut interest rates by half a percentage point as part of an emerging focus on the job market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-strongly-supported-half-percentage-point-rate-cut-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMFUJFAVRFINHEMLRQM3BIAECI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 在 "连接 "活动上发布的五大公告]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 首席执行官马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）周三在公司年度 Connect 大会上发布了一款经济实惠的混合现实头戴式耳机和首款增强现实眼镜的原型。【原文：Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg on Wednesday unveiled an affordable mixed reality headset and the prototype of its first augmented reality glasses at the company's annual Connect conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/metas-top-five-announcements-connect-event-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCSDCSJDUNO45IXK3S665V7OSM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:44:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 技术主管米拉-穆拉提将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软支持的 OpenAI 首席技术官米拉-穆拉提（Mira Murati）在 X 网站上发文称，将离开这家人工智能公司。【原文：Microsoft-backed OpenAI's Chief Technology Officer Mira Murati will leave the AI firm, the executive said in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openais-technology-chief-mira-murati-leave-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXWJVER7RJM5VKICVQIQ4C46RI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:42:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 和 Orano 放弃回收电动汽车电池的合资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[法意汽车制造商 Stellantis 和法国核燃料公司 Orano 周三表示，两家公司已放弃合资回收电动汽车电池的计划。【原文：Franco-Italian automaker Stellantis and French nuclear fuels firm Orano have dropped their planned joint venture to recycle electric car batteries, both companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/stellantis-orano-drop-planned-jv-recycle-electric-car-batteries-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F2OV66OMMVJIZLODIZFAUSHKC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:38:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝宝将允许企业账户购买、持有和出售加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝宝控股公司（PayPal Holdings）周三宣布，将允许美国商户通过其商业账户购买、持有和出售加密货币。【原文：PayPal Holdings announced on Wednesday it is enabling U.S. merchants to buy, hold and sell cryptocurrency from their business accounts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/paypal-let-business-accounts-buy-hold-sell-cryptocurrency-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TL35MAKZFI4JJIKQ2WCNOP7WQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FAA 警告说，如果波音公司不改进，其盈利能力将受到威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局局长周三告诉美国参议院一个小组，波音公司必须先解决一系列安全问题，然后他才会允许波音提高737 MAX的产量，并警告说这一问题可能会影响公司的利润。【原文：The head of the Federal Aviation Administration told a U.S. Senate panel on Wednesday that Boeing must address a series of safety issues before he will let them boost 737 MAX production, warning the issue could impact company profits.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-warns-boeing-profitability-stake-if-they-do-not-improve-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBFZ3PSQRVNEXPZQM4TJCHXGGE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:10:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普媒体公司股价反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的媒体公司股价在上周内幕抛售限制到期后从历史低点反弹，周三回升超过 6%。【原文：Shares of former U.S. President Donald Trump's media company sprang back over 6% on Wednesday, rebounding from all-time lows after restrictions on insider selling expired last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/shares-trumps-media-company-rebound-all-time-low-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6M4THXPXDNM7JJF2M6HAGSOAGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:14:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MercadoLibre 的金融科技部门在墨西哥申请银行执照]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉丁美洲电子商务巨头 MercadoLibre 的金融科技部门 Mercado Pago 周三表示，已向墨西哥监管机构提交了银行执照申请。【原文：Latin American e-commerce giant MercadoLibre's fintech arm, Mercado Pago, has submitted its request for a banking license to the Mexican regulator, the unit said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/mercadolibres-fintech-arm-applies-banking-license-mexico-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZCIK5GHTZOKFMWZU4WP2WSEG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利分析师下调评级后福特和通用汽车股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）分析师周三下调了福特汽车公司和通用汽车公司的评级，称这两家美国汽车制造商面临的市场环境充满挑战，其特点是价格下降和竞争威胁不断增加，尤其是来自中国的威胁。【原文：Shares of Ford Motor and General Motors fell about 5% on Wednesday after Morgan Stanley analysts downgraded the U.S. automakers, citing a challenging market environment marked by falling prices and growing competitive threats particularly from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-gm-shares-fall-after-morgan-stanley-analyst-downgrade-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HQQSPLYFNKTZBLTOAF5ICOFHE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员敦促货运铁路公司保障带薪病假]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周三呼吁三大货运铁路公司保证为所有员工提供带薪病假，称仍有 1 万名员工没有享受到这一福利。【原文：The Biden administration on Wednesday called on three major freight railroads to guarantee paid sick leave for all workers, saying 10,000 employees still do not have the benefit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-officials-urge-freight-railroads-guarantee-paid-sick-leave-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5D5BQ6HBRFM7RFCBGX5JJZ6H6I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:53:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新东家橡树公司向国际米兰注资 5200 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国投资基金橡树资本管理公司（Oaktree Capital Management）向国际米兰注资 4700 万欧元（5200 万美元），这家意大利足球冠军俱乐部周三在公布财务业绩时表示。【原文：U.S. investment fund Oaktree Capital Management has injected a total of 47 million euros ($52 million) in capital into Inter Milan, the Italian soccer champions said on Wednesday, presenting financial results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/new-owner-oaktree-injected-52-million-into-inter-milan-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3EFWUEEP7BPA7L5GT5F3KFNHAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:42:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罢工威胁逼近，美国港口延长交货时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国东海岸和墨西哥湾沿岸的港口正在延长进口商的交货时间，因为他们要赶在码头工人可能于 10 月 1 日举行罢工之前清关货物。【原文：U.S. ports along the East and Gulf Coasts are extending delivery hours for importers as they rush to clear cargo ahead of a potential strike by dockworkers on Oct. 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-ports-extend-delivery-hours-strike-threat-looms-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RM62NEDS5OVXJIMBB3ONWZ6F4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[先锋集团新任首席执行官关注固定收益产品的拓展]]></title><description><![CDATA[先锋集团（Vanguard）新任总裁萨利姆-拉姆吉（Salim Ramji）周三表示，考虑到市场规模和机遇，他计划扩大这家美国顶级资产管理公司的固定收益产品。【原文：Vanguard's new chief, Salim Ramji, said on Wednesday that he plans to expand the fixed income offering of the U.S. top asset manager given the market's size and opportunities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/vanguards-new-ceo-eyes-fixed-income-offering-expansion-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALQE6NZDB5OLFBRYR5XZGNJ454</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 15:54:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司称仲裁委员会裁定新日铁 149 亿美元收购交易胜诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）周三表示，该公司与美国钢铁工人工会（United Steelworkers union）为解决双方争议而共同选定的仲裁委员会已作出裁决，支持新日铁 149 亿美元的收购交易。【原文：U.S. Steel said on Wednesday the board of arbitration, jointly selected by the steelmaker and the United Steelworkers union to settle disputes between them, has ruled in favor of Nippon Steel's $14.9 billion buyout deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-says-arbitration-board-rules-favor-nippon-steels-149-bln-buyout-deal-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YVDOSX4U3FNAHHPNQOJYWSZ45M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 15:31:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会宣布打击欺骗性人工智能声明和计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）周三表示，它将对五家公司采取行动，称这些公司以欺骗性和不公平的方式使用人工智能。【原文：The Federal Trade Commission said on Wednesday it was taking action against five companies that it said used artificial intelligence in deceptive and unfair ways.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ftc-announces-crackdown-deceptive-ai-claims-schemes-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4SOOELCIZOYNESPDVZOGYS7QA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:48:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示美国大选风险打击企业投资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[近三分之一的公司财务总监表示，围绕11月5日美国总统大选的风险已导致他们推迟或缩减投资计划，这至少在短期内对经济增长是一个潜在的打击。【原文：Nearly a third of company financial officers say that risks around the Nov. 5 U.S. presidential election have caused them to delay or scale back investment plans, a potential blow at least in the short-term to economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-election-risk-hitting-corporate-investment-plans-survey-says-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSKZN6TSXROAPHULRIYD2IJOFQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:37:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行业贸易组织称，全球债务达到创纪录的 312 万亿美元，气候融资是一项挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家银行业贸易集团的数据显示，受美国和中国借贷的推动，全球债务在第二季度末达到 312 万亿美元，创历史新高，而新兴市场的一个关键债务比率也达到了新的峰值。【原文：Global debt hit a record high of $312 trillion at the end of the second quarter, driven by borrowing in the United States and China, while a key debt ratio in emerging markets also scaled a fresh peak, data from a banking trade group showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-debt-hits-record-312-trillion-climate-finance-challenge-banking-trade-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FOLAXFLC45MA5J3GSBIT6BLE5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美林证券、嘉实波动率管理公司将支付 930 万美元以了结美国证券交易委员会的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner &amp; Smith Inc. 和 Harvest Volatility Management LLC 已同意支付合计 930 万美元，以了结美国证券交易委员会有关投资限制和费用的指控。【原文：Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner &amp; Smith Inc. and Harvest Volatility Management LLC have agreed to pay a combined $9.3 million to settle U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charges related to investment limits and fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/merrill-lynch-harvest-volatility-management-pay-93-mln-settle-sec-charges-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4VTF55E4JKHXPL4ED6D53QTAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月新屋销售下降；房价中位数下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份美国新建独户住宅的销售量有所下降，但抵押贷款利率和房价的下降可能会刺激未来几个月的需求。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell in August, but declining mortgage rates and house prices could stimulate demand in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-august-median-house-price-drops-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5DCAKJAGONNSNF427W5PC3IUGE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解释：加州称埃克森公司的回收索赔造成了 "公害"。这是什么意思？]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州周一提起诉讼，指控埃克森公司误导公众回收塑料垃圾的局限性，助长了全球塑料垃圾污染，这是最近一系列基于具有数百年历史的 "公害 "法律理论的案件中的最新一起。下面将介绍公害索赔的运作方式、此类索赔的结果以及它对加利福尼亚州的努力可能意味着什么。【原文：California's lawsuit on Monday accusing Exxon of fueling global plastic waste pollution by misleading the public about the limitations of recycling is the latest in a line of recent cases based on a centuries-old legal theory known as public nuisance. Here is a look at how public nuisance claims work, how such claims have fared and what it might mean for California's effort.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/california-says-exxons-recycling-claims-created-public-nuisance-what-does-that-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KU4AEDRHLBPPPDYYXZRYJJ2DQE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国立法者寻求向畜牧业者支付费用，让他们采用更有利于气候的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据众议院和参议院周三提出的议案，美国大型工业化养殖牲畜的农民可以从乔-拜登总统签署的气候法中获得资金，以过渡到更环保的做法。【原文：Farmers in the United States who raise livestock in large industrial operations could get funding from President Joe Biden's signature climate law to transition to more environmentally friendly practices under bills introduced in the House and Senate on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/us-lawmakers-seek-pay-livestock-farmers-use-climate-friendlier-practices-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LBDPLKSHBKA5BCIBDAD5UDABU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:36:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，西南航空计划减少亚特兰大航线，裁员 300 多人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周三报道，西南航空公司计划明年减少往返亚特兰大的服务，并裁减 300 多个飞行员和空乘人员职位。【原文：Southwest Airlines plans to reduce service to and from Atlanta next year and cut more than 300 pilot and flight attendant positions, CNBC reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-plans-reduce-atlanta-service-cut-over-300-jobs-cnbc-reports-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWCUVPTO2VJ2HNMNDSPO4YQLUQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌就微软云计算做法向欧盟投诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下公司谷歌（Google）周三向欧盟委员会（European Commission）提交了一份诉状，控诉微软将客户锁定在微软云平台 Azure 上的反竞争做法。【原文：Alphabet unit Google filed a complaint to the European Commission on Wednesday against what it said were Microsoft's anti-competitive practices to lock customers into Microsoft's cloud platform Azure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-files-complaint-eu-over-microsoft-cloud-practices-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AES3464ZARLMZATGUPFEAH46WQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于购物者债台高筑，美国 "先买后付 "的假日消费将创纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据数据公司 Adobe Analytics 周三发布的预测，今年最后一个季度，美国购物者使用第三方 "先买后付 "服务进行假日购物的花费预计将达到创纪录的 185 亿美元。【原文：U.S. shoppers are expected to spend a record $18.5 billion using third-party buy now, pay later services for holiday purchases in the last quarter of the year, according to projections by data firm Adobe Analytics released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-holiday-spending-buy-now-pay-later-hit-record-due-debt-laden-shoppers-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2SILX5UUJPWDFJBOPUK6O3K7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合信贷银行的姿态让德国中小型企业无所畏惧]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行（Commerzbank）表示，作为推动欧洲经济发展的中型企业 "Mittelstand "的主要贷款机构，该行有理由抵制联合信贷银行（UniCredit）的姿态。但 "中型企业 "的领导者们自己却不这么认为。【原文：Germany's Commerzbank says its role as a key lender to the swathe of "Mittelstand" midsize companies that drive Europe's top economy is grounds to resist UniCredit's overtures. But Mittelstand leaders themselves are less convinced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-overtures-hold-few-fears-germanys-mittelstand-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YDYITK2BSVP6FAETYANE4TQ6SQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士称，印度要求泰米尔纳德邦介入三星工人罢工事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士周三称，印度联邦劳工部长要求南部泰米尔纳德邦解决三星电子工人长达数周的罢工问题。【原文：India's federal labour minister asked the southern state of Tamil Nadu to resolve a weeks-long strike by workers at Samsung Electronics , a government source said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-asks-tamil-nadu-state-find-resolution-samsung-workers-strike-govt-source-2024-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHTBXLOHCJKCNKB6LM4O7TDW7U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:15:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>