<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:41:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:41:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[降息呼之欲出，黄金再创新高，特朗普言论打击台湾股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，随着市场为全球利率下降做好准备，黄金创下历史新高，债券也出现反弹，而台湾股市则在美国总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普对台湾国防承诺态度冷淡后出现下滑。【原文：Gold hit a record and bonds rallied on Wednesday as markets prepared for global interest rates to fall, while stocks in Taiwan slipped after U.S. presidential candidate Donald Trump sounded lukewarm in his commitment to the island's defence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQCF4F5UVJNKPGTZ7SEQGC7I2Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:14:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称台湾应支付防务费用后，台积电股价下跌逾 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）称台湾应支付国防费用后，合约芯片制造商台积电的股价周三下跌超过 2%。【原文：Shares of contract chip manufacturer TSMC fell more than 2% on Wednesday after U.S. presidential candidate Donald Trump said Taiwan should pay for defence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-shares-fall-more-than-2-after-trump-says-taiwan-should-pay-defence-2024-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NDV5Y6OSDRPKTBIK7YKD6SPNIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储再次降息，美元摇摆不定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元汇率涨跌不一，此前，美国零售销售数据好于预期，美元汇率受到了短暂的小幅提振，交易员们关注美联储最早将于 9 月份降息的前景。【原文：The dollar was mixed on Wednesday after a modest but short-lived boost following better-than-expected U.S. retail sales data, as traders focused on the prospect of Federal Reserve rate cuts as early as September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-wobbles-with-fed-rate-cuts-back-view-2024-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCJ6PGY67VL2BN25MNHCZMA2JA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将于 8 月发布限制中国汽车软件的拟议规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位高级官员周二表示，美国商务部计划在下个月发布有关联网汽车的拟议规则，并预计将对中国和其他被视为对手的国家制造的一些软件施加限制。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department plans to issue proposed rules on connected vehicles next month and expects to impose limits on some software made in China and other countries deemed adversaries, a senior official said Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-issue-proposed-rules-limiting-chinese-vehicle-software-august-2024-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QB3PGQP6SVMDZIXZWGRSC6LYOA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求放缓抵消供应紧缩，油价保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中国需求增长减弱的迹象与美国石油库存下降的前景发生冲突，周三亚洲早盘油价持稳，全球基准布伦特油价在上一交易日创下的一个月低点附近徘徊。【原文：Oil prices were steady in early Asian trade on Wednesday, with global benchmark Brent hovering near the one-month low it hit in the prior session, as signs of weakening demand growth in China clashed with the prospect of declining U.S. oil stockpiles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-steady-slowing-demand-offsets-tightening-supply-2024-07-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQKU7267NRNPVANCWG2WTOL6UQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 "我支持 TikTok"，美国可能禁用 TikTok]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，他支持 TikTok，尽管如果中国母公司字节跳动未能剥离该短视频应用在美国的资产，TikTok 可能会被禁止。【原文：Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump said he supports TikTok even as a potential ban looms if Chinese-parent company ByteDance fails to divest the short video app's U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-says-im-tiktok-potential-us-ban-looms-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5FQIXPWMZKI7LHEVNF7RFLWBA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉恢复达美航空投资级评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周二将达美航空的信用评级上调至投资级，理由是其资产负债表在过去三年中有所改善。【原文：Fitch Ratings on Tuesday upgraded Delta Air Lines' credit rating to investment grade, citing improvements in its balance sheet in the past three years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fitch-restores-deltas-investment-grade-rating-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NCUMPOBX35K6TKAPB4MMI5G7BY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本商业景气喜忧参半凸显经济前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社 Tankan 月度调查周三显示，日本制造商对 7 月份的经营状况更有信心，而服务业的信心则有所减弱，这反映出经济前景并不乐观。【原文：Japanese manufacturers became more confident about business conditions in July whereas those in the service sector cooled, the monthly Reuters Tankan survey showed on Wednesday, reflecting a patchy economic outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-mixed-business-sentiment-highlights-patchy-economic-outlook-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OH3VPZQ4AJJQJLRYLMDAMQOJBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:03:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前铂金伙伴公司总裁在欺诈案中避免入狱]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，现已解散的 Platinum Partners 对冲基金的创始人被判处 6 个月的家庭监禁，因为他参与了检察官所说的欺诈一家石油天然气公司债券持有人的计划。【原文：The founder of the now-defunct Platinum Partners hedge fund was sentenced on Tuesday to six months of home confinement over his role in what prosecutors called a scheme to defraud bondholders of an oil and gas company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/ex-platinum-partners-chief-avoids-prison-fraud-case-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOTVE5GHIVIUFIOEJJM2QVHQJQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲：全球信号不一，印尼呼吁加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDGEZH5PY5OK3O7VK2SEAHW3IQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于比索走软，美国移动公司第二季度转为亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥电信巨头 America Movil 周二公布净亏损为 10.9 亿墨西哥比索（6,000 万美元），原因是当地比索贬值，尽管收入有所增长。【原文：Mexican telecommunications giant America Movil on Tuesday posted a swing to a net loss of 1.09 billion Mexican pesos ($60 million), citing the depreciation of the local peso even as revenues edged up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/america-movils-second-quarter-swings-loss-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52V5ZJIGX5JE5IFEWGP75DFN5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院小组就医疗成本问题与药房福利经理举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国众议院监督小组周二表示，将与美国药房福利管理公司的高管举行听证会，讨论这些公司在医疗成本上升中的作用。【原文：The U.S. House of Representatives oversight panel said on Tuesday it will hold a hearing with executives from U.S. pharmacy benefit managers on the role of the firms in rising healthcare costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-house-panel-hold-hearing-with-pharmacy-benefit-managers-healthcare-costs-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B734HR6NHFM25BYQUK5IZD6ZVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空第二季度营收预计为 12.8 亿美元，低于此前预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）周二表示，第二季度的收入预计约为 12.8 亿美元，低于此前的预期，原因是非机票收入低于预期。【原文：Spirit Airlines on Tuesday said revenue for the second quarter is estimated to be around $1.28 billion, lower than previously projected, citing lower-than-expected non-ticket revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-expects-q2-revenue-128-bln-lower-than-previously-projected-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOMT5MLUDFKHJDQGUUNGJDBZRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:39:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员要求美国电话电报公司就大规模黑客攻击美国客户通话数据一事做出答复]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名美国参议员周二要求 AT&amp;T 公司回答有关 4 月份发生的大规模黑客攻击事件的问题，该事件导致该美国无线公司约 1.09 亿个客户账户被非法下载。【原文：Two U.S. senators on Tuesday asked AT&amp;T to answer questions about a massive hacking incident in April that resulted in the illegal downloading of about 109 million customer accounts at the U.S. wireless company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/senators-seek-answers-att-massive-hacking-us-customer-call-data-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4RUG75NFE5N7FGUQR25EUGZH7M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:24:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克称 SpaceX 将把总部从加利福尼亚州迁往德克萨斯州]]></title><description><![CDATA[火箭公司 SpaceX 首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）周二在 X 网站上发表文章称，公司总部将从加利福尼亚州迁往德克萨斯州的星际基地。【原文：Rocket company SpaceX will move its headquarters to Starbase, Texas from California, CEO Elon Musk said on Tuesday in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/musk-says-spacex-will-move-headquarters-texas-california-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTDS3V2QJRJQ7HTIQQZYUNAEKM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[流亡中国商人郭文贵在美国欺诈案审判中被定罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[郭文贵是一名流亡海外的中国商人，也是北京共产党政府的直言不讳的反对者，周二他在美国的审判中被判有罪，罪名是从网上追随者那里窃取数亿美元。【原文：Guo Wengui, an exiled Chinese businessman and outspoken opponent of Beijing's communist government, was convicted on Tuesday in his U.S. trial on charges of stealing hundreds of millions of dollars from online followers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/jury-reaches-verdict-exiled-chinese-businessman-guos-us-fraud-trial-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQVR4YLX5BIFVO7LNDJE7TMFAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司在美国银行称可能出售资产有利后上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，华纳兄弟发现公司股价上涨超过 6%，此前美国银行（BofA）全球研究部称，如果该公司探索战略选择，包括潜在的出售，可以为股东创造更多价值。【原文：Shares of Warner Bros Discovery rose more than 6% on Tuesday after Bank of America (BofA) Global Research said the company could create more value for its shareholders if it explored strategic options, including a potential sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-discovery-rises-after-bofa-says-possible-sale-assets-likely-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EMZYHX74Q5I4LFN5PIF3VBLLO4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:01:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒称近期数据表明通胀率将向 2% 的目标迈进]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周二表示，最近的数据表明，通胀率将继续下降至美国央行设定的2%的目标，她提到了最近几个月价格压力的加速下降、工资的放缓以及企业对工人的需求与求职人数之间正在出现的平衡。【原文：Recent data suggests inflation will continue to decline to the U.S. central bank's 2% target, Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said on Tuesday, citing the faster drop in price pressures in recent months, moderation in wages, and an emerging balance between businesses' demand for workers and the number of people looking for jobs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-says-recent-data-indicates-inflation-headed-2-target-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NIFM6MYEZJLPNSVTLGDH5QJMY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:49:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空业敦促国会解决 FAA 设施 "被忽视 "的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一系列报告引起人们对空中交通管制设施老化的警觉之后，美国主要航空团体和工会敦促国会解决联邦航空管理局设施资金持续短缺的问题。【原文：Major U.S. aviation groups and unions urged Congress to address persistent shortfalls in funding for Federal Aviation Administration facilities after a series of reports raised alarm about aging air traffic control facilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-aviation-industry-urges-congress-address-neglected-faa-facilities-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3PXU4SVABORDPQEPPBHSDXY4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:44:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[史酷比制造商可就涉嫌山寨产品起诉 Build-A-Bear]]></title><description><![CDATA[Build-A-Bear Workshop 声称其 Skoosherz 毛绒玩具未经授权山寨了沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下一家公司生产的流行毛绒玩具 Squishmallows。【原文：A U.S. judge rejected Build-A-Bear Workshop's effort to dismiss a lawsuit claiming that its Skoosherz plush toys were unauthorized knockoffs of Squishmallows, the popular plush toys made by a unit of Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/squishmallows-maker-can-sue-build-a-bear-over-alleged-knockoffs-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FH3MAI7FVJJWJGHKWULPHY3HX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行高管讨论消费者前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行从更高的贷款利息支出中获得了一笔意外之财，但一些高层管理人员的评论表明，他们可能会面临前途未卜的困境。【原文：U.S. banks have reaped a windfall from higher interest payments on loans, but commentary from some top executives suggests they could face an uncertain path ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-executives-discuss-consumer-outlook-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQGACVG6DFPOVDJ6F7XTMMPOQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:21:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TC 能源公司称美国法庭驳回其对 Keystone XL 项目提出的 150 亿美元索赔要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大 TC 能源公司周二称，自由贸易仲裁法庭驳回了该公司要求美国政府就取消其 Keystone XL 项目赔偿 150 多亿美元的申诉。【原文：Canada's TC Energy said on Tuesday a free trade arbitration tribunal had tossed out its claim to recover more than $15 billion from the U.S. government for the cancellation of its Keystone XL project.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/tc-energy-says-its-15-bln-claim-keystone-xl-project-thrown-out-by-us-tribunal-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMJI377DBBLC3HKZC656UVJ6L4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁企业面临季度利润不振、价格进一步下跌的局面]]></title><description><![CDATA[据分析师称，美国顶级钢铁制造商预计第二季度盈利将出现下滑，并可能在进入夏季淡季时面临钢材价格进一步回落的额外压力。【原文：Top U.S. steelmakers are expected to post a decline in second-quarter earnings and could face additional pressure from a further retreat in steel prices heading into a slow summer season, according to analysts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-steelmakers-brace-tepid-quarterly-profit-further-price-declines-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QJV76PQZ5MWHOZRHPOD5Y5XAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:44:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司空乘人员将就罢工授权进行投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）空乘人员工会周二表示，如果无法就新的雇佣合同达成协议，空乘人员将投票决定是否授权罢工。【原文：United Airlines flight attendants will vote whether to authorize a strike if agreement on a new employment contract cannot be reached, their union said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-flight-attendants-will-vote-strike-authorization-union-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RL5XIVQTHFMIFPPQY5J6F2TYUY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球邮轮业需求增长，对港口抗议保持警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[到 2028 年，全球邮轮业的乘客人数预计将比 2023 年的 3170 万人多出 10%，届时邮轮业的乘客人数将超过大流行前的水平。【原文：The global cruise industry expects to carry 10% more passengers by 2028 than the 31.7 million who took cruise holidays in 2023, when the sector surpassed pre-pandemic levels, but sees some routes exposed to protests over overtourism.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-cruise-industry-sees-growing-demand-wary-port-protests-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TULGV64OINKGVMGVMR6SDUJMZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:20:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯第二季度业绩超预期，上调 2024 年盈利指引]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国运动服装制造商阿迪达斯周二表示，由于第二季度业绩好于预期，该公司将上调全年盈利指导。【原文：German sportswear maker Adidas is increasing its full-year earnings guidance after a better than expected second quarter, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-increases-2024-earnings-guidance-after-second-quarter-beat-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZMNSE5VLPVMCBN5BUHXWJ7NCPM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，欧盟成员国对中国电动汽车关税意见不一]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周二透露，在一次不具约束力但仍有影响力的投票中，欧盟各国政府对欧盟对进口中国产电动汽车（EV）征收关税的利弊看法不一。【原文：European Union governments have given a divided view on the merits of EU tariffs on imports of China-built electric vehicles (EVs) in a non-binding but still influential vote, sources with knowledge of the vote said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-members-give-mixed-view-vote-chinese-ev-tariffs-sources-say-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQBZFIWT7ZPG3OEFSSUVEO3I2Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲汽车和清洁能源感受到特朗普 2.0 赌注的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，一些欧洲汽车制造商和可再生能源公司的股票进入了第二天的抛售期，原因是人们对美国潜在政策风险的担忧与日俱增，而此前的一次暗杀企图增加了唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在总统竞选中的胜算。【原文：A sell-off in the shares of some European carmakers and renewable energy firms entered a second day on Tuesday on growing concerns over potential U.S. policy risks after an assassination attempt boosted Donald Trump's chances in the presidential race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-autos-clean-energy-feel-pinch-trump-20-bets-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3AA64SWIZMT7NXBOE6DQ3D6TI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，布鲁塞尔或将重新考虑对大众和宝马征收中国电动汽车进口关税的问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，欧盟委员会已向大众和宝马发出信号，可能会考虑降低这两家汽车制造商进口中国产电动汽车的关税。【原文：The European Commission has signalled to Volkswagen and BMW that it may consider lowering tariffs on the two carmakers' imports of China-made EVs, two sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/brussels-may-rethink-china-ev-import-tariffs-volkswagen-bmw-sources-say-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMA6PXIIEFOUJL3IHGEKJQN7WE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月商业库存增幅略高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于批发商和零售商的库存大幅增加，5 月份美国商业库存的增幅略高于预期。【原文：U.S. business inventories increased slightly more than expected in May amid solid rises in stocks at wholesalers and retailers, a trend that could see inventory investment contributing to economic growth in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-inventories-increase-slightly-above-expectations-may-2024-07-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPFIYZOWXJLRFBEZSAKDGA2OIU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:26:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>