<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:10:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:10:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[随着数据流的恢复，美联储主席巴金期待经济形势更加明朗]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周二表示，美国央行决策者仍面临通胀与就业目标之间的矛盾，他希望未来的数据和正在进行的社区访谈将有助于明确经济的走向。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said on Tuesday he hopes coming data and ongoing community interviews will help clarify where the economy is heading, with U.S. central bank policymakers still facing tension between their inflation and employment goals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-barkin-looks-forward-more-clarity-economy-data-flow-resumes-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ESVR67XG5LYVGKTWCRD53UJ5I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯计划对电子产品征收新税以提高国防能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯正计划对电子产品（主要是进口产品和消费品）征收新税，27 亿美元的收入将在未来三年内专门用于支持国内电子产业，包括国防部门。【原文：Russia is planning a new tax on electronics, primarily imported and consumer items, with $2.7 billion in proceeds earmarked to support the domestic electronics industry, including in the defence sector, over the next three years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/russia-plans-new-tax-electronics-boost-its-defence-capacity-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEOLP57PDFIGHLE6CXHFKHPIVE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市下跌，美国企业信贷息差扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国股市几个月来首次收盘低于一项关键技术指标，美国企业信贷息差周一有所扩大。【原文：U.S. corporate credit spreads widened on Monday as the U.S. stock market closed below a key technical indicator for the first time in months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-corporate-credit-spreads-widen-equities-market-falls-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUCO5VSAZFJF7MC4VVV27QM57M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌推出 "双子座 3"，立即在搜索中嵌入人工智能模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周二推出了最新版本的人工智能模型 "双子座"（Gemini），并强调新功能将立即应用于其搜索引擎等多个创利产品中。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Tuesday launched the latest version of its artificial intelligence model Gemini, emphasizing that the new capabilities will be immediately available in several profit-generating products like its search engine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/google-launches-gemini-3-embeds-ai-model-into-search-immediately-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2WVHT3SEJN4RB5YSW5XHMWQHU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软推出追踪器，管理工作场所的自主人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软认为，在工作场所，需要管理的不仅仅是人类。人工智能也需要管理者。【原文：In Microsoft's view, humans are not the only ones to manage in a workplace. Artificial intelligence needs a manager, too.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsoft-launches-tracker-manage-autonomous-ai-workplace-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QROJEGR455ML5CKLNNNJ3AC73E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国梅尔茨警告说，欧洲绝不能将数字领域拱手让给美国和中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国总理弗里德里希-梅尔茨（Friedrich Merz）周二呼吁欧洲迅速采取行动，避免今后将日益重要的数字领域拱手让给美国和中国。【原文：German Chancellor Friedrich Merz on Tuesday called on Europe to take swift action to avoid ceding the increasingly important digital sphere to the United States and China in future.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/europe-must-not-cede-digital-sphere-us-china-warns-germanys-merz-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PAXJI36T3FNERGOIDS4PYJOIII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:48:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LPL 表示，标普 500 指数跌破关键技术水平可能预示着更深层次的挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[LPL Financial 的研究周二显示，美国 500 指数跌破了一个受到密切关注的技术临界点，这可能预示着未来会有更大幅度的回调，凸显出随着全球科技和人工智能交易的平仓，股市面临着越来越大的压力。【原文：The S&amp;P 500's drop below a closely watched technical threshold could signal a deeper pullback ahead, research from LPL Financial showed on Tuesday, underscoring growing pressure on equities as tech and AI trades unwind globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/sp-500s-slip-below-key-technical-level-may-foreshadow-deeper-setback-lpl-says-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BBRGNMW2JLDJBOUWBPCEZLPHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:48:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特开发商希望向美国散户投资者出售特朗普酒店代币]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特豪华房地产开发商 Dar Global 的首席执行官周二告诉路透社，该公司希望通过向美国散户投资者出售基于区块链的加密代币，为其在马尔代夫最新开业的特朗普酒店提供大部分资金。【原文：Saudi luxury real estate developer Dar Global hopes to fund much of its latest Trump hotel in the Maldives by selling blockchain-based crypto tokens to U.S. retail investors, its CEO told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-developer-wants-sell-trump-hotel-tokens-us-retail-investors-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCNFUZ3ZEVMXHBTLPOUE4UJS64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:48:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员反对 FCC 撤销在盐台风袭击后通过的网络规则的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院商业委员会的头号民主党人周二呼吁联邦通信委员会放弃废除在大规模 "盐台风 "中国黑客事件后通过的网络安全要求的计划。【原文：The top Democrat on the Senate Commerce Committee on Tuesday called on the Federal Communications Commission to abandon plans to rescind cybersecurity requirements adopted after the massive Salt Typhoon Chinese hacking incident.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/senator-opposes-fcc-plan-reverse-cyber-rules-adopted-after-salt-typhoon-attack-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZYJBYIYYRIAVLIZ2EA3UBDDA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Renault to produce two new Geely-based cars in Brazil]]></title><description><![CDATA[雷诺集团周二表示，随着在高增长市场的进一步扩张，该集团将利用其中国合作伙伴吉利汽车的基地，于 2026 年下半年在巴西生产两款新车。【原文：Renault Group will produce two new cars in Brazil in the second half of 2026, using the base of its Chinese partner Geely's vehicles, as it further expands in a high growth market, it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/renault-produce-two-new-geely-based-cars-brazil-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JHMMHPU7LNMXXHGHIC7M7MFXQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球炼油利润激增并可能保持强劲势头]]></title><description><![CDATA[LSEG 数据和分析师称，由于对俄罗斯的制裁、炼油厂停工和维护，全球炼油利润率在 11 月份创下多年新高。【原文：Global refining margins have hit multi-year highs in November due to sanctions on Russia, refinery outages and maintenance, according to LSEG data and analysts, and some see little respite without more plants being built in the Western world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/global-oil-refining-profits-surge-may-stay-strong-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPWKUZJYZ5LH7MUHRRDDH2OKPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:29:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月份工厂订单如期反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[8 月份美国制成品的新订单出现反弹，但企业的设备支出并不像最初想象的那样强劲。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods rebounded in August, though business spending on equipment was not as strong as initially thought.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-factory-orders-rebound-expected-august-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V2LIDQMT3NPSTPGYC4U7LAUNNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:27:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microsoft, Nvidia to invest in Anthropic as Claude maker commits $30 billion to Azure]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软和英伟达（Nvidia）计划根据一项新的合作协议对Anthropic进行投资，其中包括克劳德制造商承诺出资300亿美元使用微软的云服务。【原文：Microsoft and Nvidia plan to invest in Anthropic under a new tie-up that includes a $30 billion commitment by the Claude maker to use Microsoft's cloud services, the latest high-profile deal binding together major players in the AI industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/anthropic-commits-30-billion-microsoft-azure-compute-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BURN7FGTOJL4TBYNN2X7FJ2M5U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[劳动力市场忧虑引发 11 月美国住宅建筑商情绪低迷]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对劳动力市场和家庭财务状况的担忧拖累了需求，导致建筑商为减少新房库存而降价的比例激增，11 月份美国住宅建筑商的情绪依然低迷。【原文：U.S. homebuilder sentiment remained subdued in November as concerns about the labor market and household finances weighed on demand, contributing to a surge in the share of builders slashing prices to reduce new housing inventory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-home-builder-sentiment-subdued-november-amid-labor-market-worries-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMDRTJZGRBM43CLOCB6NNMIOZM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格关闭部分自动化设施，将产生 26 亿美元费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国杂货商克罗格（Kroger）周二表示，该公司将在 2025 年第三财季关闭某些自动履行设施，并计提约 26 亿美元的减值费用。【原文：U.S. grocer Kroger said on Tuesday it would close certain automated fulfillment facilities and incur an impairment charge of about $2.6 billion in the third fiscal quarter of 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/kroger-close-some-automated-facilities-incur-26-billion-charge-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXRURZMW2JOZ5FIRSAT5QS4YNE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intuit 达成 1 亿美元协议，将 OpenAI 模型整合到金融工具中]]></title><description><![CDATA[Intuit 周二表示，它已与 OpenAI 签订了一份价值超过 1 亿美元的多年期协议，将使用这家 ChatGPT 制造商的人工智能模型为其应用程序（如报税软件 TurboTax）中的人工智能代理提供支持。【原文：Intuit said on Tuesday it has signed a multi-year deal worth more than $100 million with OpenAI to use the ChatGPT maker's artificial intelligence models to power AI agents across its apps such as tax-preparation software TurboTax.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intuit-strikes-100-million-deal-integrate-openai-models-into-financial-tools-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJKKUENWZFML5I5C2ZLQV6WXUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:24:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ocado 因美国合作伙伴 Kroger 表示将关闭三个机器人仓库而下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国在线超市和技术集团 Ocado 周二股价暴跌，此前其美国合作伙伴克罗格（Kroger）表示将在一月份关闭三个自动化仓库。【原文：Shares in British online supermarket and technology group Ocado slumped on Tuesday after U.S. partner Kroger said it would close three automated warehouses in January.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ocado-get-250-million-krogers-planned-closure-some-automated-facilities-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJXFMT4LGRJLDKMQP6V772T3XE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:23:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国劳工部称，10 月中旬美国失业救济人数创 8 月份以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月中旬，领取失业救济金的美国人数创下了两个月来的新高，当时劳工部正在对美国家庭进行调查。【原文：The number of Americans receiving unemployment benefits stood at a two-month high in mid-October at the time when the Labor Department would have been conducting its survey of U.S. households.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-jobless-benefits-rolls-mid-october-were-highest-since-august-labor-dept-says-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Y4PYTRNC5PRTEMLVODKPUBMJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国 Autonomy 诉讼案后，惠普向迈克-林奇的遗产索赔 18 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技巨头惠普公司的律师周二在伦敦高等法院表示，惠普公司正就惠普收购已故英国科技公司 Autonomy 事宜向已故迈克-林奇的遗产索赔近 18 亿美元。【原文：Hewlett Packard Enterprise is seeking nearly $1.8 billion from the estate of the late Mike Lynch over HP's acquisition of his British tech firm Autonomy, the U.S. technology giant's lawyers told London's High Court on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hp-seeking-18-billion-mike-lynchs-estate-after-uk-autonomy-lawsuit-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P53C6BKJCNPJ7O6DNPOHQ77B3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PVH's finance chief Zac Coughlin to step down, insider named interim replacement]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tommy Hilfiger and Calvin Klein's parent company PVH said on Tuesday that its Chief Financial Officer Zac Coughlin will be leaving at the end of the year, to be replaced by company veteran Melissa Stone as interim CFO.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pvhs-finance-chief-zac-coughlin-step-down-insider-named-interim-replacement-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VC6DP6ANZBOIJLZYAU64HSFI2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:51:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK measures to counter China's threat to lawmakers, business, universities]]></title><description><![CDATA[Britain's domestic intelligence service, MI5, warned lawmakers and parliamentary staff on Tuesday about Chinese agents who were targeting democratic institutions, including through networking sites.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-measures-counter-chinas-threat-lawmakers-business-universities-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QHB5U3BUE5LDBFJ6BHRCPXFTJE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:44:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Italy considers 5G telecoms licence extensions with lower costs tied to investment pledges]]></title><description><![CDATA[Italy is considering extending 5G licences while limiting costs for operators in return for investment pledges, a cabinet undersecretary said on Tuesday, as the telecom sector contends with falling revenue and lower margins.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/italy-considers-5g-telecoms-licence-extensions-with-lower-costs-tied-investment-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTGYAYMY2RI3NPAZUTHY76RGIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:37:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Klarna strikes $6.5 bln loan deal with Elliott funds to boost US push]]></title><description><![CDATA[Klarna said on Tuesday it will sell up to $6.5 billion of loans to funds managed by Elliott Investment Management over a two-year period, as part of efforts to expand its buy-now-pay-later business in the U.S.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/klarna-strikes-65-bln-loan-deal-with-elliott-funds-boost-us-push-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MV7TCJGTXNLCZITCY57WM3FQ5Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bosch struggling with production snags despite hopes of chip supply detente]]></title><description><![CDATA[German automotive supplier Bosch (ROBG.UL) is struggling with disruption at three production sites despite signs of movement in a trade dispute around the chipmaker Nexperia, with thousands of workers impacted, the company said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bosch-struggling-with-production-snags-despite-hopes-chip-supply-detente-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RI5S7QM2GNNFLBK6YNW263ZRKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI accounting startup Maxima raises $41 million in Kleiner Perkins-backed round]]></title><description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence startup Maxima has raised about $41 million from investors including Redpoint Ventures and Kleiner Perkins as it looks to automate accounting for businesses, the company said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-accounting-startup-maxima-raises-41-million-kleiner-perkins-backed-round-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSRXIKOPI5IFVP4HC26M5JA6GY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Klarna Q3 revenue beats estimates in first earnings report after IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[Swedish fintech Klarna on Tuesday reported a 26% jump in third-quarter revenue, beating expectations in its first report as a public company, and forecast revenue to cross $1 billion in the current quarter, backed mainly by growth in U.S. markets.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/klarna-q3-revenue-beats-estimates-first-earnings-report-after-ipo-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SN7UYN46JBJJZJWJYIUYRX4YSI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Nissan to cut more output at Kyushu plant on chip supply troubles]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's Nissan will cut production by another 1,400 vehicles at its Kyushu plant next week, as the fallout from chip supply disruptions linked to Chinese-owned Nexperia continues to affect its domestic operations, a person familiar with the matter said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-cut-more-output-kyushu-plant-chip-supply-troubles-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ID6WWF52RNLMFCBWLTCH3EIHLU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:31:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cash allocation strategies across US companies could be missing out on millions, report shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Corporations across the U.S. could potentially be leaving millions on the table depending on their cash management strategies, according to research published by Clearwater Analytics on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cash-allocation-strategies-across-us-companies-could-be-missing-out-millions-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PJLM4NGW5M4FOW4LLBCIDDOA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:17:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币跌破 90,000 美元，交易者日趋谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，比特币七个月来首次跌破 90,000 美元，这是整个金融市场投资者风险偏好正在枯竭的最新迹象。【原文：Bitcoin fell below $90,000 for the first time in seven months on Tuesday in the latest sign that investor appetite for risk is drying up across financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-drops-below-90000-sign-souring-mood-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWTRLIBE4FJL3NKZKR2DHWDEH4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:13:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downdetector 显示，数以千计的美国用户无法使用埃隆-马斯克的 X 系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据故障跟踪网站 Downdetector.com 的数据，埃隆-马斯克的 X 系统周二在美国有数千名用户出现故障。【原文：Elon Musk's X was down for thousands of users in the U.S. on Tuesday, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/elon-musks-x-down-thousands-us-users-downdetector-shows-2025-11-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXVMF3TZENIVRIUP6TLBZPN2I4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:05:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>