<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:36:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:36:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[受网络攻击报告影响，中国瓜子网跌至近五周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，中国短视频平台周一遭遇网络攻击，导致露骨内容突然激增，瓜子二手车股价周二下跌多达 6%，至 62.70 港元（8.06 美元），创 11 月 21 日以来新低。【原文：Shares of Kuaishou Technology dropped by as much as 6% on Tuesday to HK$62.70 ($8.06), their lowest since November 21, after media reported that the Chinese short video platform experienced a sudden surge of explicit content because of a cyberattack on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-kuaishou-falls-near-five-week-low-report-cyberattack-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWQNBP3GJM2TN46Q7W6RRG5GA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市、贵金属上涨；日元受到干预观察]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市与贵金属齐涨，原因是投资者在节日假期前延续了买盘势头，预计当天晚些时候将公布美国国内生产总值（GDP）的预估数据。【原文：Asia shares rose alongside precious metals on Tuesday as momentum buying from investors extended ahead of the festive holidays, with an advanced reading on U.S. GDP expected later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGWUTPU52VM27GIUZ4V5QWOBP4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 02:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[干预威胁席卷而来，日元岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在美元广泛走软的背景下，日元小幅上扬，此前东京当局发出了迄今为止最严厉的警告，表明东京准备采取干预措施，日元兑主要同业货币在近期低点附近徘徊。【原文：The yen perked up slightly on Tuesday amid broad U.S. dollar weakness after the severest warning yet from authorities signalled Tokyo's readiness to intervene as the Japanese currency hovered near recent lows against major peers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/frail-yen-whipped-around-intervention-threat-swirls-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3CKXV52CJLF3NZUYMKHYE53QM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 02:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场权衡委内瑞拉和俄罗斯供应风险，石油价格下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二早盘，油价在上一交易日上涨超过2%后有所回落，原因是美国表示可能出售其扣押的委内瑞拉原油，而乌克兰对俄罗斯船只和码头的袭击加剧了市场对供应中断的担忧。【原文：Oil prices eased in early trade on Tuesday after rising more than 2% in the previous session as the U.S. said it might sell Venezuelan crude it has seized, while Ukraine's attacks on Russian vessels and piers heightened supply disruption fears.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-slips-market-weighs-venezuela-russia-supply-risks-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AICGIAFNX5OQPNEYC7WEFCQIYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 01:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，字节跳动计划在 2026 年斥资 230 亿美元建设人工智能基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周一援引知情人士的话报道称，TikTok 的所有者字节跳动已初步计划在 2026 年投入 1600 亿元人民币（约合 227.4 亿美元）的资本支出，用于建设人工智能基础设施。【原文：TikTok owner ByteDance has made preliminary plans for capital expenditure of 160 billion yuan ($22.74 billion) in 2026 to build artificial intelligence infrastructure, the Financial Times reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bytedance-plans-spend-23-billion-towards-ai-infrastructure-2026-ft-reports-2025-12-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LOUDIIMEZLLBPXYAGRVNMILJE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 01:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，萨克斯全球公司正考虑将破产作为最后手段]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道，高端连锁百货公司萨克斯第五大道（Saks Fifth Avenue）的母公司萨克斯全球公司（Saks Global）正在考虑将破产保护作为最后的手段。【原文：Saks Global, parent of high-end department store chain Saks Fifth Avenue, is weighing Chapter 11 bankruptcy as a last resort, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/saks-global-is-considering-bankruptcy-last-resort-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6QMZOUM3K5PGDKOUTF3ZA7TWOM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约时报》记者就聊天机器人培训问题起诉谷歌、xAI 和 OpenAI]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位因揭露硅谷血液检测初创公司Theranos欺诈行为而闻名的调查记者周一起诉埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的xAI、Anthropic、谷歌、OpenAI、Meta Platforms和Perplexity，指控它们未经许可使用受版权保护的书籍来训练人工智能系统。【原文：An investigative reporter best known for exposing fraud at Silicon Valley blood-testing startup Theranos sued Elon Musk's xAI, Anthropic, Google , OpenAI, Meta Platforms and Perplexity on Monday for using copyrighted books without permission to train their artificial intelligence systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/new-york-times-reporter-sues-google-xai-openai-over-chatbot-training-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TVTQ4HQ7J5I55E62WB3SVPJ3UU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:06:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德减肥药获美国批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局周一批准了诺和诺德公司的减肥药，使这家丹麦制药商在销售一种强效减肥口服药物的竞争中占得先机，并希望从竞争对手礼来（Eli Lilly）手中夺回失地。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved Novo Nordisk's weight-loss pill on Monday, giving the Danish drugmaker a leg up in the race to market a potent oral medication for shedding pounds as it looks to regain lost ground from rival Eli Lilly .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/novo-nordisk-wins-us-approval-weight-loss-pill-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFSOGEWWHBN7PIM5GVRTF6UWMM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump to press defense giants on delays, mulls curbs on executive pay]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he will meet major defense contractors next week to address production delays and cost overruns while the administration plans an executive order to limit dividends, buybacks and executive pay.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-press-defense-giants-delays-mulls-curbs-executive-pay-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X4ONL5J2NBKX7NHPWE7WWL47DI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goodman Group, Canada's CPPIB strike $9.3 bln deal for Europe data centres]]></title><description><![CDATA[Australian data centre landlord Goodman Group said on Tuesday it had signed a A$14 billion ($9.32 billion) partnership agreement with Canada Pension Plan Investment Board to develop data centre projects in Frankfurt, Amsterdam and Paris.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/goodman-group-canada-pension-plan-establish-93-billion-european-data-center-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRXVDU4CTVP53NFC2F67YSQIIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democratic-led states sue to block US consumer watchdog's defunding under Trump]]></title><description><![CDATA[A coalition of Democratic-led states filed a lawsuit on Monday seeking to prevent President Donald Trump's administration from defunding the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau by refusing to request money from the Federal Reserve.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/democratic-led-states-sue-block-us-consumer-watchdogs-defunding-under-trump-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3QTGDEFRRNERBSRWFDODBRDH4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US farm agency lost 20,000 staff in first five months of Trump administration]]></title><description><![CDATA[More than 20,300 employees left the U.S. Department of Agriculture in the first five months of the administration of President Donald Trump, about a fifth of staff, according to a report from the agency's inspector general.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-farm-agency-lost-20000-staff-first-five-months-trump-administration-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PDMWNWN4JJ6HKHETDDBFC6KHQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:59:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil oil union set to accept Petrobras labor offer, end strike]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian oil workers union FUP said on Monday it plans to accept a counteroffer from state-run company Petrobras for a labor deal, paving the way to end a week-long strike.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/brazil-oil-union-set-accept-petrobras-labor-offer-end-strike-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMWWVG3IKZKPJCWOUSMLZZ2UX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:42:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US business equipment borrowings down more than 4% y/y in November, ELFA says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. companies borrowed 4.4% less to finance equipment investments in November compared with the same period a year earlier, the Equipment Leasing and Finance Association (ELFA) said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-business-equipment-borrowings-down-more-than-4-yy-november-elfa-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIT4BOHD4ZNVHCNZD2H4JVB7IM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US adds DJI, other foreign drones to national security list]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Federal Communications Commission said on Monday it is adding China's DJI and all foreign made drones and components to a list of companies determined to pose unacceptable risks to U.S. national security and will bar approvals of new types of drones for import or sale in the United States.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-adds-dji-other-foreign-drones-national-security-list-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4YO45F3KNLKXGXBOBPORBW3YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[South Korea online retailer Coupang faces US securities class action over massive data breach]]></title><description><![CDATA[South Korean e-commerce company Coupang has been sued in a U.S. court in an investor class action alleging violations of securities laws after a cybersecurity breach exposed personal information of more than 33 million customers.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/south-korea-online-retailer-coupang-faces-us-securities-class-action-over-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MHNYYG5WQFNAFBOKHEHGJWDSOE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FanDuel, CME Group launch prediction markets in five US states]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sports betting firm FanDuel and derivatives exchange heavyweight CME Group on Monday announced the launch of their prediction markets platform in five U.S. states, as the red-hot asset class continues to draw in new entrants.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fanduel-cme-group-launch-prediction-markets-five-us-states-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KQOHEC6JJI75BGALSUELFO3YY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[United Launch Alliance CEO Tory Bruno resigns]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tory Bruno has resigned as United Launch Alliance's chief executive officer after leading the space venture for nearly 12 years, the firm said on Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/united-launch-alliance-ceo-tory-bruno-resigns-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MJSZAB2MBOCJJ65DV4L3OXVKA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lawmakers want US to disclose any approvals of Nvidia H200 China licenses]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two senior Democratic lawmakers on Monday asked the U.S. Commerce Department to disclose details and any approvals of ongoing license reviews for potential sales to Chinese firms of Nvidia's second-most powerful AI chips.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/lawmakers-want-us-disclose-any-approvals-nvidia-h200-china-licenses-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJGRIXTZJZNWFFTX75LBKYXB5Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waymo resumes San Francisco service after power outage pause]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet unit Waymo said on Monday it resumed its ride-hailing service in the San Francisco Bay Area on Sunday, a day after temporarily suspending operations due to a widespread power outage that snarled traffic and gridlocked parts of the city.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/waymo-resumes-san-francisco-service-after-power-outage-pause-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D56P7MJ6AJODDGYIVRX3ACEBUY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:45:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Driverless future gains momentum with global robotaxi deployments]]></title><description><![CDATA[Uber and Lyft are teaming up with Chinese tech company Baidu to test self-driving taxis in the UK in 2026, making them the latest ride-hailing platforms to partner with self-driving vehicle firms.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/driverless-future-gains-momentum-with-global-robotaxi-deployments-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAPAUOXMXNOGFLK2ELRYX24UEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:42:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase doubles down on prediction markets with deal for The Clearing Company]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase said on Monday it will buy prediction markets startup The Clearing Company, as the crypto exchange looks to expand beyond its core digital assets business.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/coinbase-doubles-down-prediction-markets-with-deal-clearing-company-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53MAPEST6VKKNEMXFRVEVEQTSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mercedes agrees $150 million settlement with US states over diesel scandal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz has reached a $149.6 million settlement with U.S. states to resolve a long-running investigation into allegations of diesel emissions cheating by the German automaker, New York Attorney General Letitia James said Monday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/mercedes-benz-agrees-1496-million-settlement-with-us-states-over-excess-diesel-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STJ33CGFJNNPRL3PSYQXUKKHDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mercedes reaches $120 million settlement with US states over emissions scandal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz said on Monday it will pay out $120 million to multiple U.S. states over emissions-rigging software in its vehicles, which the German carmaker says resolves the remaining Dieselgate proceedings against it in the U.S.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/mercedes-reaches-120-million-settlement-with-us-states-over-emissions-scandal-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F7VPBRT7JI2NLNUARUWAXQDVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Warner Bros bidding war and red hot M&A market has dealmakers working through holidays]]></title><description><![CDATA[This has turned out to be an extraordinary year for dealmakers after a trade war kicked off by Donald Trump derailed activity in the second quarter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/warner-bros-bidding-war-red-hot-ma-market-has-dealmakers-working-through-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFKQKGCSYZPJZOHAES23MLFCRM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alphabet to buy data center firm Intersect in $4.75 billion deal amid AI push]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet said on Monday it would buy data center and energy infrastructure provider Intersect for $4.75 billion in cash, plus assumed debt, as tech giants ramp up spending to expand computing and power capacity necessary for developing AI.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/alphabet-buy-data-center-infrastructure-firm-intersect-475-billion-deal-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUTWAYFLIBPHLDLRWIXBTGU6B4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW Ellison steps in with personal guarantee as Paramount fights for Warner Bros]]></title><description><![CDATA[Oracle co-founder Larry Ellison has stepped in to personally guarantee $40.4 billion in Paramount Skydance's latest effort to pry Warner Bros Discovery away from selling its prized Hollywood assets to streaming giant Netflix .]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/view-ellison-steps-with-personal-guarantee-paramount-fights-warner-bros-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DS2EYLRP7BJQ7EGFUG7EOU6H3E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israeli high-tech funding rises to nearly $16 billion in 2025, report says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israeli high-tech companies raised $15.6 billion in private funding in 2025, up from $12.2 billion in 2024, Startup Nation Central said in a report on Monday citing preliminary data.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-high-tech-funding-rises-nearly-16-billion-2025-report-says-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOWOSSEKMJNH5EZ3TYYLVGMI2U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:57:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US watchdog says paycheck advances no longer subject to lending law]]></title><description><![CDATA[A U.S. consumer finance agency said on Monday that popular "earned wage" advances on worker paychecks do not resemble consumer loans, reversing course from guidance the regulator put out last year under then President Joe Biden.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-watchdog-says-paycheck-advances-no-longer-subject-lending-law-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQZLYRGPVNLPXISCVB4HVLGJAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:53:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI spending spree drives global tech debt issuance to record high]]></title><description><![CDATA[Global technology companies have ramped up debt issuance this year to record levels, as an intensifying race to build artificial intelligence capacity forces even cash-rich firms to borrow heavily to fund that investment.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-tech-2025-12-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6MB77OZ7BN2HGMGZUNMWL3PEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:50:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>