<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:06:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:06:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普如果鲍威尔不降低利率，美联储董事会应掌握控制权]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，如果美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）继续拒绝降低利率，那么美联储理事会就应该掌握控制权。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday the Federal Reserve board should assume control if Fed Chair Jerome Powell continues to refuse to lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-fed-board-should-assume-control-if-powell-wont-lower-interest-rates-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPQNXHCSWJIGFH2Z7HTPJJV2JM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opera 遭投诉后，微软成了巴西反垄断监管机构的靶心]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西反垄断执法机构CADE周四晚些时候在其网站上发表声明称，在挪威浏览器Opera投诉微软Edge几天后，CADE已对微软展开调查。【原文：Brazil's antitrust enforcer CADE has opened an investigation into Microsoft , days after Norwegian browser Opera complained about Microsoft's Edge, according to a CADE statement published late Thursday on its website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/microsoft-brazilian-antitrust-regulators-crosshairs-after-opera-complaint-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T24SQO4MZBPYVBNTECGQJSGTOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟最高法庭裁定大众汽车应对失效装置负责]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲法院周五裁定，即使车辆符合欧盟标准，大众等汽车制造商仍需对使用非法失效装置（如对温度敏感的排放软件）承担责任，这并不能保证该技术的合法性。【原文：The European Court of Justice on Friday ruled that carmakers like Volkswagen remain liable for using unlawful defeat devices, such as temperature-sensitive emissions software, even if the vehicles met EU standards, which doesn't guarantee the technology's legality.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/volkswagen-liable-defeat-devices-top-eu-court-rules-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWUHNKX265LYVA7IREILUKGTDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:57:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国家媒体称英伟达必须提供 "安全证明 "才能重获信任]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国营媒体《人民日报》周五发表评论文章称，英伟达必须拿出 "令人信服的安全证明"，才能消除中国用户对其芯片安全风险的担忧，重新赢得市场信任。【原文：Nvidia must produce "convincing security proofs" to eliminate Chinese users' worries over security risks in its chips and regain market trust, a commentary published China's state-run media People's Daily said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-state-media-says-nvidia-must-provide-security-proofs-regain-trust-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCFRMNVURNPCXPAMJHPP5UDPE4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:52:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 首席财务官 Doug Ostermann 将兼任金融服务部门主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 首席财务官道格-奥斯特曼（Doug Ostermann）周五在 LinkedIn 上发帖称，他将在集团内担任另一个职务，即 Stellantis 金融服务部门主管。【原文：Stellantis Chief Financial Officer Doug Ostermann will take an additional role in the group as head of Stellantis Financial Services, the executive said in a LinkedIn post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-cfo-doug-ostermann-will-also-head-financial-services-unit-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYDLSIHPINKBJAIJZGWXK525YY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国机器人制造商AGIBot完成新一轮融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国仿人机器人制造商AGIBot在给路透社的一份声明中说，该公司已完成新一轮战略融资，投资者包括LG电子和未来资产。【原文：Chinese humanoid robot maker AGIBot has completed a new round of strategic financing with investors including LG Electronics and Mirae Asset, the company said in a statement to Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-robot-maker-agibot-completes-new-round-financing-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDK6UZBCTBLOLC2YXEQTHCYV6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:48:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[设计软件制造商 Figma 在纽交所上市首日大涨后扩大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[设计软件制造商 Figma 的股价在周五的盘前交易中又上涨了 10%，延续了在美国首次公开募股后首日的强劲涨势，这也重新点燃了科技股上市市场的热情。【原文：Design software maker Figma's shares rose another 10% in premarket trading on Friday, extending strong debut-day gains after a blowout U.S. initial public offering that has reignited the tech listing market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/design-software-maker-figma-extends-gains-after-blockbuster-nyse-trading-debut-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3S6N3YUVRPGLKLQOLNV3Z2UW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:45:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价关税日来临，亚马逊步履蹒跚]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INK44Z56GRI5VHMDED424OG26A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普新关税和亚马逊的影响导致华尔街期货下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国对数十个贸易伙伴征收新关税以及亚马逊财报不尽如人意的影响，华尔街期货周五下跌，而投资者则在等待一份关键的就业报告，以判断美联储的下一步行动。【原文：Wall Street futures declined on Friday, hammered by new U.S. tariffs on dozens of trading partners and Amazon's unimpressive earnings, while investors awaited a key jobs report to gauge the Federal Reserve's next move.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-slide-trumps-new-tariffs-amazon-weigh-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YLIPBMUWVNLBFS6DVPTXZWWKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:38:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于需求强劲，面巾纸制造商金佰利公司的季度销售额大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[金佰利公司周五公布第二季度有机产品销售额增长，主要得益于国内外市场对 Huggies 纸尿裤和 Kleenex 纸巾等产品的稳定需求。【原文：Kimberly-Clark on Friday posted a rise in second-quarter organic sales, led by steady demand for products such as Huggies diapers and Kleenex tissues in domestic and international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kleenex-tissue-maker-kimberly-clarks-quarterly-sales-jump-strong-demand-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45ZL3MBRRBM5RLCADKZGRHUIAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管油价疲软，埃克森公司产量增加，利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚周五公布的第二季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，原因是石油和天然气产量的增加帮助这家美国最大的石油生产商克服了原油价格下跌的困难。【原文：Exxon Mobil beat Wall Street estimate for second-quarter profit on Friday as higher oil and gas production helped the top U.S. oil producer overcome lower crude prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-beats-profit-estimates-with-higher-production-despite-weak-oil-prices-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YS7YTYPBB5JJHFIHKFJPR54BZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:34:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦格纳上调销售额预期，因削减成本而超出季度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受惠于成本削减措施，加拿大汽车零部件供应商麦格纳国际公司周五上调了全年销售预期，第二季度业绩超出预期。【原文：Canadian auto parts supplier Magna International raised annual sales forecast and topped second-quarter estimates on Friday, benefiting from its cost-cutting measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/magna-raises-sales-forecast-beats-quarterly-view-cost-cuts-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCJYLN2ZIFLRRJJFR67UGB3API</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉 7 月在西班牙的新销量增长 27%，其他电动车销量增长一倍多]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业组织 ANFAC 周五公布的登记数据显示，特斯拉 7 月份在西班牙的新车销量比 2024 年同期增长了 27%，达到 702 辆，而电动汽车的整体销量则猛增了 155%。【原文：Tesla's new car sales in Spain rose 27% in July from the same month in 2024 to 702 vehicles, registration data released by industry group ANFAC showed on Friday, while sales of electrified cars as a whole skyrocketed, with a 155% rise.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/new-tesla-sales-spain-rise-27-july-other-ev-sales-more-than-double-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HD372UKWPZOJLFYDTNARJRIMCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:23:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙产量创新高，利润超出华尔街预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙周五公布的第二季度利润超过了分析师的预期，原因是创纪录的油气产量和较低的资本支出帮助这家美国石油生产商在原油价格疲软的情况下提高了盈利。【原文：Chevron beat analyst estimates for second-quarter profit on Friday as record oil and gas production and lower capital expenditure helped the U.S. oil producer boost earnings despite weaker crude prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-beats-wall-street-profit-estimates-with-record-production-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXMWVV7RYRJNLOPFFQMNNRRWAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:19:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税忧虑导致欧洲股票基金资金大幅流出；美国基金吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 7 月 30 日的一周内，欧洲股票基金面临抛售压力，原因是该地区股市的涨势降温，投资者对美国-欧盟贸易协议的不确定经济影响以及企业盈利疲软的迹象日益谨慎。【原文：European equity funds came under selling pressure in the week through July 30 as a rally in regional stocks cooled, with investors growing cautious over the uncertain economic implications of the U.S.–EU trade deal and signs of weakening corporate earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4OIDFKB3Q5MRBLKDHMFELZGNJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，Alphabet 的 CapitalG 和 Nvidia 正在洽谈为 Vast Data 提供估值高达 300 亿美元的资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，Alphabet 的成长期风险投资部门 CapitalG 和 Nvidia 正在洽谈投资人工智能基础设施提供商 Vast Data 的新一轮融资，该初创公司的估值可能高达 300 亿美元。【原文：Alphabet's growth-stage venture arm CapitalG and Nvidia are in talks to invest in artificial intelligence infrastructure provider Vast Data in a new funding round that could value the startup as high as $30 billion, two sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/alphabets-capitalg-nvidia-talks-fund-vast-data-up-30-billion-valuation-sources-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NM64F5HKROGTHYEU3QKCRCTCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[别管华尔街的记录，投资者重新思考美国市场的霸主地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街和美元的反弹并未消除投资者对美国资产能否跑赢海外市场的担忧，即使特朗普政府达成的一系列贸易协议足以提振市场情绪，使股市创下历史新高。【原文：A rebound on Wall Street and in the dollar has not allayed investor concerns about the ability of U.S. assets to outperform overseas markets, even as a string of trade deals struck by the Trump administration sufficiently perked up sentiment for equities to set record highs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/never-mind-wall-street-records-investors-rethink-us-market-supremacy-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSCGPU7QDJL7XML77PKLX2ZPKA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞和 BioNTech 在英国上诉推翻 Moderna 的 COVID 疫苗专利胜诉败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[辉瑞及其德国合作伙伴 BioNTech 周五在伦敦上诉法院推翻了关于其 COVID-19 疫苗侵犯 Moderna 一项专利的裁决，但最终败诉。【原文：Pfizer and its German partner BioNTech on Friday lost their bid to overturn a ruling that their COVID-19 vaccine infringed one of Moderna's patents at London's Court of Appeal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/pfizer-biontech-lose-uk-appeal-overturn-modernas-covid-vaccine-patent-win-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNINEFO45RKXRKDQ22LTUXIXME</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:59:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳高管表示，计划到 2027 年 "加倍 "投资人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦当劳的一位高管周五告诉路透社，麦当劳计划在2027年前 "加倍 "加大人工智能投资，并将印度作为数据治理、工程设计和平台架构的关键中心。【原文：McDonald's plans to "double down" on its artificial intelligence investment by 2027 and is betting on India as a key hub for data governance, engineering and platform architecture, a senior executive told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mcdonalds-plans-double-down-ai-investment-by-2027-senior-exec-says-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXPLGGUETFK6FK2HFZFC3GYU7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:37:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[孟加拉国服装获得美国 20% 的关税，出口商松了一口气]]></title><description><![CDATA[孟加拉国已就对美出口 20% 的关税进行了谈判，低于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最初提出的 37% 的关税，这为世界第二大服装供应国的出口商带来了宽慰。【原文：Bangladesh has negotiated a 20% tariff on exports to the U.S., down from the 37% initially proposed by U.S. President Donald Trump, bringing relief to exporters in the world's second-largest garment supplier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bangladesh-secures-20-us-tariff-garments-exporters-relieved-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37GFD66GEBM73KDOWJW5ICBK5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:22:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧元区通胀率保持在欧洲央行目标水平，为稳定利率提供支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元区 7 月份的通胀率稳定在欧洲央行 2% 的目标水平上，这证实了该行对物价的良性看法，并加强了决策者在快速削减借贷成本后在一段时间内继续按兵不动的理由。【原文：Euro zone inflation held steady at the ECB's 2% target in July, confirming the bank's benign view on prices and strengthening the case for policymakers to keep interest rates on hold for some time after rapidly cutting borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/euro-zone-inflation-holds-ecb-target-supporting-case-steady-rates-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S4KDGFDI7RMODIMENNFBCDU62A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提高美国药品降价赌注后，欧洲制药商下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在签署了一项旨在降低药价的全面行政命令数月后，致函各大制药公司要求降低美国的药品价格，欧洲制药商的股价周五下滑。【原文：Shares of European drugmakers slipped on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump sent letters to major pharmaceutical firms to cut drug prices in the United States, months after signing a sweeping executive order aimed at lowering prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/european-drugmakers-fall-after-trump-raises-stakes-over-us-drug-price-cuts-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TML6MNDIPFMSHKBJ4VQZD2WF6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行警告美国关税可能打击企业利润，推迟资本支出计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五表示，由于美国加征关税，日本企业今年的利润可能会下降，从而导致它们下调资本支出计划，这表明日本对依赖出口的经济受到打击的预期持谨慎态度。【原文：Profits of Japanese firms are likely to fall this year because of U.S. tariffs, leading them to downgrade capital expenditure plans, the central bank said on Friday, signalling caution over an expected hit to the export-dependent economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-warns-us-tariffs-could-hit-firms-profits-delay-capex-plans-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQXYGRZ5EVL2TLAXFFJB7LBH6E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧元区 7 月制造业趋于稳定，PMI 创三年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项调查显示，尽管新订单减少、产出增长放缓，但欧元区制造业在 7 月份仍以三年来最慢的速度收缩，从而更接近于稳定。【原文：Euro zone manufacturing moved closer to stabilization in July as factory activity contracted at its slowest pace in three years, despite a dip in new orders and slower output growth, a survey showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/euro-zone-manufacturing-approached-stability-july-pmi-hits-three-year-high-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKFUSGIBPVOCRPS5RTRYXMAATQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，福特将因动力制动辅助系统失灵召回超过 31.2 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，福特将在美国召回312,120辆汽车，因为在行驶过程中失去动力制动辅助装置会延长停车距离，增加撞车风险。【原文：Ford is recalling 312,120 vehicles in the U.S. as loss of power brake assist while driving can extend stopping distance and increase the risk of a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recall-over-312000-us-vehicles-over-loss-power-brake-assist-nhtsa-says-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PB67N2TT5PSJBHOUAXDLKOXD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德股价创四年新低，特朗普敦促美国药品降价]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普致函各大制药公司要求削减美国药品价格之后，Wegovy生产商诺和诺德公司的股价周五下跌了约4%，创下了2021年8月以来的新低。【原文：Shares in Wegovy maker Novo Nordisk fell around 4% on Friday to their lowest since August 2021, after U.S. President Donald Trump sent letters to major pharmaceutical firms to cut drug prices in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-shares-hit-4-year-low-trump-urges-us-drug-price-cuts-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MZQ4AWNTHNNEZATXYU77DZEAOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行准备再次加息，但在时机选择上留有余地]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行本周为恢复加息奠定了基础，首次明确指出了食品价格持续上涨会引发广泛通胀的风险。【原文：The Bank of Japan laid the groundwork this week for resuming interest rate hikes by spelling out explicitly for the first time the risks that persistent food price rises fan broad-based inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/boj-gears-up-hike-rates-again-leaves-free-hand-timing-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUWGD5AVPVNUNFI6LHXONUM5CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:12:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲航空公司股价在关税动荡中超越美国同行]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管地缘政治和经济存在不确定性，但欧洲航空公司的股价在过去六个月中仍一路飙升，而美国航空公司的股价则在旅游支出回落的情况下遭到抛售。【原文：European airline shares have soared in the last six months despite geopolitical and economic uncertainty, while those of U.S. airlines have sold off amid a pullback in travel spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/europes-airline-shares-outpace-us-peers-amid-tariff-turbulence-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIZZC52BIVPLNK6CMNJZWA46YU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税风暴席卷全球市场，投资者鲜见赢家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周五宣布的关税最后期限几乎没有给市场带来任何缓和，韩国和台湾的科技股受到重创，因为投资者对扰乱全球供应链的成本以及与中国谈判的结果感到担忧。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's Friday tariff deadline brought little reprieve for markets, with tech stocks in South Korea and Taiwan hit hard as investors fretted over the cost of disrupting global supply chains and the outcome of talks with China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/investors-see-few-winners-tariff-storm-lashes-global-markets-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOEUAD3JEFNT5LE5NLV5LVAQCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁第一季度亏损 13 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本最大的钢铁制造商新日铁周五表示，截至 6 月 30 日的三个月内，新日铁亏损 1,958.3 亿日元（13.0 亿美元），亏损额超出分析师预期。【原文：Nippon Steel , Japan's biggest steelmaker, posted 195.83 billion yen ($1.30 billion) in losses for the three months to June 30, it said on Friday, wider than analysts' expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nippon-steel-posts-13-billion-q1-loss-2025-08-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44V5D3MVFZLBVLH2K44VTXACMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:43:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>