<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:33:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:33:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[关税冲击下服装零售商推迟订单、冻结招聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周三对从越南和中国进口的产品加征关税生效之前，美国各地的服装和配饰零售商正在推迟订单并冻结招聘。【原文：Clothing and accessories retailers across the United States are delaying orders and freezing hiring ahead of tariff hikes that take effect Wednesday on products imported from Vietnam and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/clothing-retailers-delay-orders-freeze-hiring-tariffs-hit-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3TACSOV75MYJKJJ3UZEE3YVRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普将签署行政命令促进煤炭行业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将于周二签署旨在促进美国煤炭工业发展的行政命令。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will sign executive orders on Tuesday aimed at boosting the nation's coal industry, sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-sign-executive-orders-boost-coal-industry-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THMIALX5BJPPJL2574ZI7K47QI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[断崖式下跌后，台湾启动 150 亿美元股票稳定基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾周二授权启动 150 亿美元的股票稳定基金，以支撑因美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收新进口关税而连续两天暴跌的市场。【原文：Taiwan authorised the activation of its $15 billion stock stabilisation fund on Tuesday to prop up the market after two days of sharp falls in reaction to U.S. President Donald Trump's new import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/taiwan-activates-15-billion-stock-stabilisation-fund-after-precipitous-falls-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R7A5R4XDTNL3JB3XOTSCLEDTNI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RTX 的普惠公司开发增材制造技术，缩短发动机维修时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[RTX 公司周二表示，其发动机制造子公司普惠公司已为齿轮传动涡扇（GTF）发动机部件开发出一种增材制造维修工艺，可将加工时间缩短 60% 以上。【原文：RTX said on Tuesday its engine making subsidiary Pratt & Whitney has developed an additive manufacturing repair process for its geared turbofan (GTF) engine components, which would reduce process time by more than 60%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/rtxs-pratt-whitney-develops-additive-manufacturing-reduce-engine-repair-time-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKLVWGRMPZL4VA3FQG5KMK7EOU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:13:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：股市喘息，人民币和国债震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFQWNH2QSRKLRBIEUL7C3WRP3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:09:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔格林在 Sycamore Partners 交易完成前实现季度盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔格林公司（Walgreens）正在被 Sycamore Partners 私有化，该公司的季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，因为这家连锁药店运营商受益于扭亏为盈的努力，包括关闭业绩不佳的门店。【原文：Walgreens , which is in the process of being taken private by Sycamore Partners, beat Wall Street estimates for quarterly profit as the pharmacy chain operator benefited from a turnaround effort that included closing underperforming stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/walgreens-second-quarter-profit-beats-ahead-sycamore-partners-deal-close-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A7CE3KHYFIJ3DVZSL6Z4M7QK4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国股市在巨额关税引发抛售后回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，英国主要股指从一年多来的最低水平回升，因为投资者正在寻找任何迹象，表明华盛顿在过去几天激怒全球市场的激进关税问题上立场有所软化。【原文：Britain's main indexes recovered from their lowest levels in more than a year on Tuesday, as investors look for any indication of Washington softening its stance on the aggressive tariffs that have roiled global markets over the last few days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/uk-stocks-recover-after-sell-off-triggered-by-hefty-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2VU6KHXTBIKBBRKB5USTBTEUQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:06:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国将增加美国进口并降低税率以应对关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国财政部长周二表示，泰国将增加美国进口，降低对美国商品征收的部分高额税款，并解决非关税壁垒问题，因为泰国政府正寻求通过谈判就美国新关税达成更好的协议。【原文：Thailand will increase U.S. imports, lower some of the higher taxes on American goods and address non-tariff barriers, the finance minister said on Tuesday, as the government seeks to negotiate a better deal on new U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thailand-increase-us-imports-lower-taxes-tariff-response-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UL6H7B6XSRNWFM7WSGNSCE2PQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:44:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CVS 任命 UPS 高管布莱恩-纽曼为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，CVS Health 任命联合包裹服务公司高管布莱恩-纽曼（Brian Newman）为新任首席财务官，这是这家医疗保险公司在首席执行官大卫-乔伊纳（David Joyner）领导下的首次高层管理变动。【原文：CVS Health named United Parcel Service executive Brian Newman its new chief financial officer on Tuesday, the first top management change for the health insurer under CEO David Joyner's leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/cvs-names-ups-executive-brian-newman-cfo-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75KU7XRYTZL5RAKUONT5XHZRJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:37:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，制药商警告欧盟美国关税将进一步削弱欧洲制药业]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位业内消息人士告诉路透社，欧洲制药公司在周二的一次会议上警告欧盟委员会主席，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税将加速该行业从欧洲转向美国。【原文：European pharma companies warned the European Commission president in a meeting on Tuesday that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs would expedite the industry's shift away from Europe and toward the United States, two industry sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/drugmakers-warn-eu-that-us-tariffs-further-weaken-sector-europe-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZE63AYVZ5ZN6PDLBIYJFZPQL6Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[有限选择将中国推向与特朗普的贸易 "消耗战]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对中国和任何购买或组装中国商品的国家加紧征收关税，北京感到被逼入绝境，正准备迎接一场经济消耗战。【原文：Beijing, feeling boxed into a corner by the United States' intensifying tariff assault on China and any country that buys or assembles Chinese goods, is bracing for an economic war of attrition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/limited-options-push-china-into-trade-war-attrition-with-trump-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWIGWHAMI5KHPAJ54BFVFCVA3Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:28:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，马斯克的 DOGE 使用人工智能窥探美国联邦政府工作人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士说，特朗普政府官员已告诉一些美国政府雇员，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 DOGE 技术专家团队正在利用人工智能监控至少一个联邦机构的通信，以寻找对唐纳德-特朗普总统及其议程的敌意。【原文：Trump administration officials have told some U.S. government employees that Elon Musk's DOGE team of technologists is using artificial intelligence to surveil at least one federal agency’s communications for hostility to President Donald Trump and his agenda, said two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/musks-doge-using-ai-snoop-us-federal-workers-sources-say-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7EBDCBQQRLQZMKIKEOCGVXKLQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:19:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长斯托纳拉斯称美国关税带来的通胀上升可能推迟货币政策正常化进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）决策者亚尼斯-斯托纳拉斯（Yannis Stournaras）周二表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税后可能出现的通胀走高和全球贸易战可能会推迟欧元区货币政策的正常化。【原文：European Central Bank policymaker Yannis Stournaras said on Tuesday that likely higher inflation and a global trade war following U.S. President Donald Trump's imposition of tariffs could delay normalization of euro zone monetary policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecbs-stournaras-says-higher-inflation-us-tariffs-could-delay-monetary-policy-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IFUFGP3UGVLVLH2BRR5AXSNNF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[反垄断负责人称，欧盟将在未来几周内对苹果和 Meta 做出决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断局长特雷莎-里贝拉（Teresa Ribera）周二告诉欧洲议会立法者，欧盟将在未来几周内就苹果和 Meta 公司是否违反了旨在遏制其市场力量的具有里程碑意义的技术规则做出决定。【原文：An EU decision on whether Apple and Meta have breached landmark tech rules aimed at curbing their market power will be issued in the coming weeks, antitrust chief Teresa Ribera told European Parliament lawmakers on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/eu-decisions-apple-meta-due-coming-weeks-antitrust-chief-says-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKVRXFRGE5JHHP6TMNUOI2XFGE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗保险支付率 "最佳情况 "下，医疗保险股上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国医疗保险公司股价跳涨，原因是政府对 2026 年医疗保险优势计划的报销比例上调幅度大于预期，这为医疗成本高企的医疗行业带来了一些缓解。【原文：Shares of U.S. health insurers jumped on Tuesday after a bigger-than-expected increase in the government's reimbursement rates for Medicare Advantage plans in 2026, bringing some relief to a sector burdened with elevated medical costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/health-insurance-stocks-rise-best-case-scenario-medicare-payment-rates-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LP2VZJIAVLXHF4F6NOP6KPYWQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:11:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国小型企业信心下降，经济前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国小企业的信心在 3 月份连续第三个月下降，侵蚀了唐纳德-特朗普总统在 11 月大选获胜后取得的大部分涨幅，因为尽管人们早期对预期的减税和放松管制可能带来的商业推动持乐观态度，但对政府贸易政策的担忧却在增加。【原文：U.S. small-business confidence dropped for a third straight month in March, eroding most of the gains that followed President Donald Trump's election victory in November, amid rising concerns over the administration's trade policy despite early optimism about a potential business boost from expected tax cuts and deregulation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-small-business-confidence-drops-economic-outlook-dims-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IR5YGFKVQNMYBNN45SWUOYJ2ZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）"堆积如山的美元 "是解除阿根廷外汇管制的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷即将与国际货币基金组织达成的 200 亿美元协议将为自由主义总统哈维尔-米莱伊带来他想要的工具，以解除阻碍投资的资本管制，重返全球市场："堆积如山的美元"。【原文：Argentina's pending $20 billion deal with the International Monetary Fund will bring libertarian President Javier Milei the tool he wants to unlock investment-blocking capital controls and a return to the global market: a "mountain of dollars".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/imf-mountain-dollars-key-unlock-argentinas-fx-controls-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEQBZIJ7YVK4XNA6LRQ7MMHX6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在儿童网络安全监管的推动下，Meta 将 "青少年账户 "扩展至 Facebook 和 Messenger]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 周二将在 Facebook 和 Messenger 上推出 "青少年账户 "功能，因为该公司在保护青少年用户免受网络伤害方面做得不够，因而受到了持续的批评。【原文：Meta Platforms is rolling out its "Teen Accounts" feature to Facebook and Messenger on Tuesday, as it faces sustained criticism about not doing enough to protect young users from online harms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/meta-expands-teen-accounts-facebook-messenger-amid-childrens-online-safety-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M776AYIZ6VL4PCZZUU55C5OQTY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西、埃及和新加坡是关税冲击下的潜在赢家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布全面征收关税的消息震惊了美国的多个贸易伙伴和全球市场，几天之后，少数几个国家正在成为潜在的赢家，尽管关税引发的经济衰退风险将限制其上升空间。【原文：Days after U.S. President Donald Trump's announcement of sweeping tariffs shocked multiple U.S. trading partners and global markets, a handful of countries are emerging as potential winners although the risk of a tariff-induced recession will limit the upside.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/brazil-egypt-singapore-among-potential-winners-tariff-onslaught-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4NAFTGOIIJJHPLGOXNWHWY3WHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员质疑谷歌和微软的人工智能交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位美国民主党参议员要求微软和谷歌提供信息，说明它们与人工智能公司的云计算合作关系，并对这些安排可能扼杀尖端产业的竞争表示担忧。【原文：Two Democratic U.S. senators demanded information from Microsoft and Google about their cloud computing partnerships with artificial intelligence companies, expressing concern the arrangements could stifle competition in the cutting-edge industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/democratic-us-senators-question-google-microsofts-ai-deals-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AJFGVN5OAZI3JFKI4RZHLK6KW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一些美国消费者在特朗普征收新关税前囤积商品]]></title><description><![CDATA[53 岁的托马斯-詹宁斯（Thomas Jennings）推着购物车走在沃尔玛超市的过道上，他买了很多果汁、调味品和他能想到的任何东西。【原文：Pushing a shopping cart down the aisle of a Walmart Supercenter, Thomas Jennings, 53, loaded up on juices, condiments and whatever he could think of.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/some-us-consumers-stockpile-goods-ahead-trumps-new-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBHQS4UKHRJR3DPTNOHVZUGMF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[突然抛售震撼美国债券市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国债周二继续大幅回落，投资者不得不抛售债券以弥补其他资产的损失，并争相解除对美国大幅降息的预期，这是金融市场可能面临压力的最新令人不安的迹象。【原文：U.S. Treasuries extended a sharp retreat on Tuesday as investors were having to sell bonds to cover losses in other assets and scrambled to unwind expectations for deep U.S. rate cuts, in the latest unsettling sign of possible stress in financial markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/sudden-selloff-shakes-us-bond-market-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVXE7RJH55NSDIAXLXNOLTLCSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价暴跌如何使沙特阿拉伯的经济议程复杂化]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯的财富与石油收入密不可分，在原油价格暴跌之后，沙特阿拉伯面临着越来越大的举债或削减开支的压力，这使得为雄心勃勃的经济多元化议程提供资金的计划变得更加复杂。【原文：Saudi Arabia, with its wealth linked inextricably to oil revenue, faces mounting pressure to raise debt or cut spending after a plunge in crude prices, complicating plans to fund an ambitious agenda to diversify its economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/how-oil-price-plunge-complicates-saudi-arabias-economic-agenda-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UMTIAONZ5JR7G4J3IXVROGX7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼在谈判前宣布对美贸易减让措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[在与华盛顿就唐纳德-特朗普总统的全面关税进行贸易谈判之前，印度尼西亚周二宣布了一系列针对美国进口的优惠措施，包括降低电子产品和钢铁的税率。【原文：Indonesia announced a spate of concessions for U.S. imports on Tuesday, including reducing taxes on electronic goods and steel, ahead of trade negotiations with Washington over President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/indonesia-announces-trade-concessions-us-ahead-talks-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITKPNAPTQZIJ5BYBSS7UODXWNE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税谈判有望重启，期价重挫后上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货自上周以来遭受了数万亿美元的损失，周二股指走高，预示着美国股指将反弹，因为投资者正翘首以待美国就一些激进关税问题展开谈判的任何迹象。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Tuesday after taking in trillions of dollars in losses since last week, signaling a rebound as investors keenly await any sign of the U.S. opening up for negotiations over some of the aggressive tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-rise-after-heavy-losses-hopes-talks-over-tariffs-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATROCDNTOBPTLBAMP6AVEQLZEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:10:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟冯德莱恩呼吁中国确保采取负责任的关税应对措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）周二呼吁中国确保通过谈判解决美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收全面进口关税所造成的问题。【原文：EU Commission President Ursula von der Leyen called on Tuesday for China to ensure a negotiated solution to problems caused by the sweeping import tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eus-von-der-leyen-calls-china-ensure-responsible-tariff-response-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5USVJHMAVOXRI5LTTKOITGYU4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 08:44:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国国有资产监管机构支持企业回购股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国有资产监管机构周二表示，将支持中央企业增持和回购股票，以减轻全球贸易战升级对中国股市的影响。【原文：China's regulatory body for state assets said on Tuesday it would support central government-owned companies to increase their stock holdings and share buybacks to mitigate the impact of an escalating global trade war on the country's stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-state-asset-regulator-support-firms-with-share-buybacks-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JQDMRQQZ5MEFFVWVK4XIPKXZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 08:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司与亚马逊签署临时协议，为航空公司提供连接服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司（Airbus）周二表示，它已与亚马逊公司（Amazon）签署了一项临时协议，通过这家科技巨头计划中的 "柯伊伯"（Kuiper）卫星星座为航空公司提供连接服务。
空中客车公司在汉堡举行的一次大型客舱内饰展览会上宣布了这项加强 "高带宽连接增强"（High Bandwidth Connectivity Plus）计划的计划。【原文：Airbus said on Tuesday it had signed a provisional deal with Amazon to provide connectivity to airlines via the tech giant’s planned Kuiper constellation of satellites.
The plan to enhance Airbus’ High Bandwidth Connectivity Plus programme was announced at a major cabin interiors exhibition in Hamburg.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-signs-provisional-deal-with-amazon-provide-connectivity-airlines-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UKATFE2XZJARDM4RQGRU3J7GA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 08:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普下令利用煤炭为数据中心供电]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引一位白宫高级官员的话报道称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普正在寻求扩大国内煤炭的开采和使用，以推动数据中心的蓬勃发展。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is seeking to expand the mining and use of coal inside the country in a bid to power the boom in data centers, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a senior White House official.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-order-looks-tap-coal-quest-power-data-centers-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XY4NGX6BDROSNDCHI3F6LVY45Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 08:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国大陆集团称将分离橡胶部门，并可能将其出售]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国大陆集团（Continental AG）周二表示，将把旗下的康迪泰克（ContiTech）橡胶和塑料分部转变为一个独立实体，并有可能将其出售。【原文：Germany's Continental AG on Tuesday said it would turn its ContiTech rubber and plastics division into an independent entity that would likely be put up for sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/continental-ag-says-it-will-separate-rubber-unit-likely-put-it-up-sale-2025-04-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZUOEXDEDFO6LPQSAU4PLYXW5I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 08:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>