<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:39:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:39:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国已为 TikTok 找到买家]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，美国和中国已达成协议，短视频应用TikTok将继续在美国运营，其美国资产将从中国的字节跳动公司（ByteDance）移交给美国所有者，从而可能解决萦绕近一年的争议。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that the U.S. and China have a deal that will keep the short-video app TikTok operating in the United States, transferring its U.S. assets to U.S. owners from China's ByteDance, potentially resolving a saga that has lingered for nearly a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-says-us-has-buyer-tiktok-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GELS33I6ANIEZOHUVIORXS7MN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称欧佩克+官员将在维也纳讨论产能问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[两名代表周二告诉路透社，欧佩克+代表计划于周四和周五在维也纳举行会议，讨论由 22 个成员国组成的生产国集团最大生产能力的评估方法。【原文：OPEC+ delegates are planning to meet in Vienna on Thursday and Friday to discuss the methodology for assessing maximum production capacities for the 22-member producer group, two delegates told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-officials-discuss-production-capacity-vienna-sources-say-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AEXSXRLRFM5DPQUJWHD5YRY3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[图：最新一轮融资估值 390 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能机器人公司Figure周二表示，该公司在最新一轮融资中获得了超过10亿美元的承诺资金，融资后公司估值达390亿美元。【原文：AI robotics company Figure said on Tuesday it had received over $1 billion in committed capital in its latest funding round that valued the firm at $39 billion post money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/figure-valued-39-billion-latest-funding-round-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWENWLEV4FME5FUCIML536CDE4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊拉拢费伊，在远程医疗平台上提供营养师服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周二表示，已与 Fay 合作，通过这家电子商务巨头的数字健康平台提供个性化的、保险范围内的营养师服务。【原文：Amazon has teamed up with Fay to provide personalized, insurance-covered dietitian services through the e-commerce giant's digital health platform, the nutrition care startup said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/amazon-ropes-fay-offer-dietitian-services-telehealth-platform-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I33UHD4W3NN5LIOWIHLJ5IB6SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:10:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Workday 将以 11 亿美元收购人工智能公司 Sana]]></title><description><![CDATA[人力资源软件供应商 Workday 周二表示，将以约 11 亿美元的价格收购人工智能公司 Sana。【原文：Human resources software provider Workday said on Tuesday it would acquire artificial intelligence firm Sana for about $1.1 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/workday-acquire-ai-firm-sana-11-billion-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WUUB2PRPL5LLRIWHKKQTZBBVMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月份资本和消费品进口价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[受资本和消费品成本大幅上涨的推动，8月份美国进口价格意外上涨，这表明未来几个月国内通胀有望加速。【原文：U.S. import prices unexpectedly rose in August, boosted by strong increases in the costs of capital and consumer goods, suggesting domestic inflation was poised to accelerate in the coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-import-prices-increase-august-capital-consumer-goods-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3LU4GZRNZJDBEKJFUAGFRO3XU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高利率扼杀需求，美国房地产市场仍将陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对房地产专家进行的一项调查显示，由于高抵押贷款利率抑制了需求，美国低迷的房地产市场到明年仍将持续疲软，预计到2027年才会出现小幅反弹。【原文：The United States' sluggish housing market will remain weak through next year as high mortgage rates stifle demand with only a modest rebound expected in 2027, a Reuters survey of property experts showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-housing-market-remain-stuck-rut-high-rates-choke-demand-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYLWSXB6RZO5FHGNLQ6L5GCFGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:58:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月零售销售超预期；劳动力市场疲软令前景黯淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 8 月份零售额增幅超过预期，但在劳动力市场疲软和进口关税导致商品价格上涨的情况下，增长势头可能会有所缓解。【原文：U.S. retail sales increased more than expected in August, but momentum could ease amid labor market weakness and rising goods prices because of tariffs on imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-retail-sales-beat-expectations-august-weakening-labor-market-dims-outlook-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7WKVL2TERM5VCMVNTK2WXJMNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络安全公司 Netskope 提高首次公开募股价格区间，估值达 73 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[网络安全公司Netskope周二表示，在上调了首次公开募股的价格区间后，该公司目前的目标是在美国首次公开募股中获得高达72.6亿美元的估值，这凸显了投资者对高增长科技股的追捧。【原文：Cybersecurity firm Netskope is now aiming for a valuation of up to $7.26 billion in its U.S. initial public offering after raising the proposed price range, it said on Tuesday, underscoring investor appetite for high-growth tech stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cybersecurity-firm-netskope-lifts-ipo-price-range-eyes-73-billion-valuation-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J2Y4VVNS3ZPEJF5RVOXRCWFO2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:27:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马耳他金融监管机构反对推动欧盟加密货币监管集中化]]></title><description><![CDATA[马耳他金融监管局发言人周二表示，该局反对其他国家推动赋予欧盟证券监管机构更多权力来监管加密货币公司。【原文：Malta's financial watchdog is opposed to a push by other countries to give the European Union's securities regulator more powers to supervise crypto companies, a spokesperson said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/maltas-financial-regulator-opposes-push-centralise-eu-crypto-supervision-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHREGU3FVRMBDFYDBLGEKNQJZA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:26:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称查理-贾维斯因诈骗摩根大通应被判 12 年监禁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国检察官表示，因诈骗摩根大通以 1.75 亿美元收购其大学财务援助初创公司 Frank 而被定罪的企业家查理-贾维斯（Charlie Javice）应因其罪行在监狱服刑 12 年。【原文：Charlie Javice, the entrepreneur convicted for defrauding JPMorgan Chase into buying her college financial aid startup Frank for $175 million, should spend 12 years in prison for her crimes, U.S. prosecutors said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/charlie-javice-deserves-12-years-prison-defrauding-jpmorgan-us-says-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGSFT2P4RZO57G44YNQAKQVYNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:22:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salesforce 预测：随着购物者紧缩预算，美国在线假日销售将放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 Salesforce 周二发布的预测，2025 年假日季美国网上销售额的增长预计将比去年放缓，因为在生活成本上升的情况下，注重价格的购物者会继续挑剔消费。【原文：U.S. online sales growth during the 2025 holiday season is expected to slow from last year, as price-conscious shoppers stay picky with their spending amid rising living costs, according to a Salesforce forecast released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-online-holiday-sales-slow-shoppers-tighten-budgets-salesforce-forecasts-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZS3CYZIANBJLRBS7FIWPYWEI4Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，特朗普政府将对法院阻止解雇美联储理事库克的裁决提起上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周二表示，特朗普政府将对法院阻止唐纳德-特朗普总统解雇美联储理事丽莎-库克的决定提出上诉。【原文：The Trump administration will appeal the court decision blocking President Donald Trump's bid to fire Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook, the White House said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-administration-appeal-court-decision-blocking-firing-fed-governor-cook-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VRRYAIYFKZJ5VJ7GUJDUKNAMBM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:15:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，美国消费者正感受到通胀和利率带来的压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国信用评分公司费尔-艾萨克公司（Fair Isaac Corporation）周二表示，由于通货膨胀和利率上调影响了借款人的经济承受能力，导致借款人的经济压力增大，一些美国消费者正显示出越来越多的压力迹象。【原文：Some U.S. consumers are showing increased signs of stress as inflation and higher interest rates are affecting affordability and leading to financial strain on borrowers, credit scoring company Fair Isaac Corporation , widely known as FICO, said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumers-are-feeling-stress-inflation-interest-rates-report-shows-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COM5RZJKDVLRRDNIWHZUE6PZBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普与习近平会谈后，美国财长预计将达成最终嘀嗒协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，他预计美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五与中国领导人习近平通话时将就短视频应用 TikTok 达成最终协议。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Tuesday he anticipated a final deal on the short-video app TikTok when President Donald Trump speaks with Chinese leader Xi Jinping on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-treasury-secretary-anticipates-final-tiktok-deal-after-trump-xi-talk-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F34K2SWCZRMCVLVYBPTQMI664E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:55:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国防部长称丹麦可能购买波音飞机用于北极监控]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦国防部长周二表示，丹麦军方可能会购买一支波音 P-8 潜艇猎杀海上巡逻机机队，以帮助加强对法罗群岛和格陵兰岛的监视。【原文：Denmark's defence minister said on Tuesday the country's military may buy a fleet of Boeing P-8 submarine-hunting maritime patrol aircraft to help boost the surveillance of the Faroe Islands and Greenland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/denmark-may-buy-boeing-aircraft-arctic-surveillance-defence-minister-says-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZR27D5NYXZPL3AJWZ2YPAGBHV4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:36:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财长贝森特在美联储主席人选中称赞布拉德]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周二表示，他与前美联储官员詹姆斯-布拉德（James Bullard）进行了一次很好的会谈，这是他寻找美联储新主席的工作之一。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Tuesday he had a good session with former Fed official James Bullard as part of his search for a new Fed chairman.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-treasury-secretary-bessent-praises-bullard-search-fed-chief-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HNBH4XTT4VOTLOYW57BFZIJ3WU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:28:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对超过 17.4 万辆特斯拉 Model Y 汽车的门把手故障报告进行评估]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周二表示，已开始对约174290辆特斯拉Model Y汽车的电子门把手失灵报告进行初步评估。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Tuesday it had opened a preliminary evaluation into about 174,290 Tesla Model Y cars over reports of their electronic door handles becoming inoperative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-evaluating-over-174000-tesla-model-y-cars-door-handle-failure-reports-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4FH6ERCOOVMFRJKORIB7XJYGFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:26:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国付费电视集团天空电视台将裁员约 600 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士周二表示，康卡斯特（Comcast）旗下的英国付费电视集团天空电视台（Sky）将裁员约 600 人，因为该公司将完成为期三年的产品和平台投资。【原文：Sky, the British pay-TV group owned by Comcast , will cut around 600 jobs as the company completes a three-year period of investment in its product and platforms, a person familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/uk-pay-tv-group-sky-set-cut-around-600-jobs-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z644AJS3ZJKCPA72AWLAKRPO6A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行预测以太币年底目标价为 4,300 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团将全球第二大加密货币以太坊的年终目标价定为 4300 美元，理由是投资者的需求以及对稳定币和代币化等基于以太坊的用例日益增长的兴趣。【原文：Citigroup has set a year-end price target of $4,300 for ether, the world's second-largest cryptocurrency, citing investor demand and growing interest in ethereum-based use cases such as stablecoins and tokenization.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-forecasts-ethers-year-end-target-4300-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26Y6JNVHWZKH5KPEXVLWIY3HMQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日经新闻》称，由于电池短缺，日产减少了新聆风的产量计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[日经商业日报》（Nikkei business daily）周二称，由于电池采购延迟，日产汽车已将其新款聆风电动车 9-11 月份的生产计划下调了一半以上。【原文：Nissan Motor has revised down its production plan for the new model of its Leaf electric vehicle by more than half for September-November due to delays in battery procurement, the Nikkei business daily said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-reduces-output-plan-new-leaf-due-battery-shortage-nikkei-says-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZHI5F6OUBKG7LW6UQZWT2BGNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:53:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美元受到美联储热捧]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPXSZPO3W5NWTK44TFBGUHLLKQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:37:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国恒大清算人被任命为创始人资产接管人]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港高等法院在周二的一项裁决中表示，中国恒大集团的清算人已获委任，以确认和保全创始人许家印的资产。【原文：China Evergrande Group's liquidators have been appointed to identify and preserve the assets of founder Hui Ka Yan, the Hong Kong High Court said in a ruling on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-evergrande-liquidators-appointed-receivers-over-founders-assets-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2IY73NLTJLLNC7DNGS6H234FU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构调查 Global Payments 以 240 亿美元收购 Worldpay 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国竞争与市场管理局（CMA）周二对环球支付公司（Global Payments）斥资 242.5 亿美元收购世界支付公司（Worldpay）一事展开合并调查，评估该交易是否可能削弱英国市场的竞争。【原文：Britain' Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) on Tuesday launched a merger inquiry into Global Payments' $24.25 billion acquisition of Worldpay, assessing whether the deal could potentially lessen competition in UK markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-watchdog-investigates-global-payments-24-billion-purchase-worldpay-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PX72CABVCRLE5FQA3ZOQDFKOOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[得克萨斯州的一家炼油厂如何将破坏亚马逊的牛变成 "绿色 "航空燃料]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社对政府跟踪数据、采访和目击者描述的审查，一家为美国航空公司供应绿色燃料的得克萨斯州炼油厂一直在购买来自亚马逊雨林非法开垦土地上饲养的牛的动物脂肪。【原文：A Texas refinery that supplies green fuel to U.S. airlines has been purchasing animal fat from cattle raised on illegally cleared lands in the Amazon rainforest, according to a Reuters review of government tracking data, interviews and eyewitness accounts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/how-texas-refinery-turns-amazon-destroying-cattle-into-green-jet-fuel-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3AEGF2M4XJKTJESPDQULQFJF7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:13:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街和美国企业为更多关税动荡做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[最高法院即将就关税是否符合宪法做出裁决，这可能会使美国企业陷入混乱，并引发对国家财政健康的质疑。【原文：Wall Street is bracing for another bumpy ride ahead of a forthcoming Supreme Court decision on the constitutionality of tariffs that could throw Corporate America into turmoil and raise questions over the country's fiscal health.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/wall-street-corporate-america-brace-more-tariff-turmoil-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FL5JGU3XHVLHTL5GXHJFMIYJWU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来减肥药可能在年底前获得 FDA 批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[几位华尔街分析师说，礼来公司的实验性减肥药可能会在美国食品药品管理局最近启动的一到两个月的审查程序中得到快速审批。【原文：Eli Lilly 's experimental weight-loss pill could be fast-tracked under a one- to two-month review process recently launched by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration, several Wall Street analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/lilly-weight-loss-pill-could-be-fda-approved-by-year-end-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44CMYZOI2RM55NN3EF2VH3GVMI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息的乐观情绪令债券投资者关注期限和更陡峭的收益率曲线]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于预计美联储将在暂停九个月后于本周降息，债券投资者正在买入10年期以下的较长期债券，并加大了对收益率曲线陡峭化的押注。【原文：Bond investors are buying longer-term maturities up to 10-year debt and ramping up bets on a steeper yield curve, anticipating that the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates this week after a nine-month pause.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-rate-cut-optimism-has-bond-investors-focusing-duration-steeper-yield-curve-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFUOOMOANVKGHMWNQMLTW6NV3Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从 Alphabet 到 Visa，美国巨头推动欧元债券大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公司正在排队用欧元借贷，今年迄今为止的债券销售额达到了创纪录的 1,000 亿美元，这反映了欧洲具有吸引力的融资条件，以及发行人和投资者越来越愿意从美元转向欧元。【原文：U.S. companies are lining up to borrow in euros with bond sales hitting a record $100 billion so far this year, reflecting attractive European funding conditions and a growing willingness among issuers and investors to shift away from the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/alphabet-visa-us-giants-drive-euro-denominated-bond-surge-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSZUB76QVFKLJMLNORLGKLBEQE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储暂时避免对独立性造成冲击，库克将出席会议；米兰确认出任空缺席位]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国中央银行将于周二召开为期两天的政策会议，虽然暂时躲过了美国总统有史以来首次罢免美联储现任理事的努力，但仍面临着来自白宫的前所未有的压力，要求将货币政策更多地置于行政部门的直接影响之下。【原文：The U.S. central bank opens a two-day policy meeting on Tuesday having skirted, for now, a first-ever effort by the U.S. President to remove a sitting Fed governor, but still facing unprecedented pressure from the White House to bring monetary policy more under the direct influence of the executive branch.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-avoids-shock-independence-now-with-cook-attend-meeting-miran-confirmed-open-2025-09-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FC5OM47TBZICNMVNUDD67NVVZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:04:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>