<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:36:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:36:20 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[研究称，资产管理公司将迎来日益萧条的几年]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项新的研究显示，资产管理公司的盈利能力在过去两年里有所下滑，而且随着投资者越来越多地选择交易所交易基金（ETF）等费用较低的产品，到2028年可能会进一步下降。【原文：Profitability at asset managers has slipped for the past two years and is likely to decline further through 2028 as investors increasingly opt for products with lower fees, such as exchange-traded funds (ETFs), according to a new study.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asset-managers-headed-increasingly-lean-years-study-says-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5553UOUFUJJNVABOAV2P63C4ME</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德的芬克看好美国高赤字下的私人市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德公司首席执行官兼董事长拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）说，私人市场的发展可以减轻美国巨额赤字和高额政府债务对经济的影响。【原文：The growth of private markets could mitigate the economic impact of wide U.S. deficits and high government debt levels, said Larry Fink, CEO and chairman at BlackRock.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackrocks-fink-bullish-private-markets-amid-high-us-deficit-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIGUPO3R5RMNJB2HUWHKISYCX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:52:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默多克旗下道琼斯和《纽约邮报》起诉 Perplexity AI 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[媒体大亨鲁珀特-默多克（Rupert Murdoch）旗下的道琼斯公司和《纽约邮报》周一对 Perplexity AI 提起诉讼，称这家人工智能初创公司 "大量非法复制 "其版权作品。【原文：Media baron Rupert Murdoch's Dow Jones and New York Post filed a lawsuit against Perplexity AI on Monday, claiming the AI startup engages in a "massive amount of illegal copying" of their copyrighted work.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/murdoch-firms-dow-jones-new-york-post-sue-perplexity-ai-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BZPZL4EIBMXXIRV2LHUW2HD6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员质疑石油服务公司SLB对俄罗斯制裁的例外情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[来自两党的数十名美国众议员敦促拜登政府加强对俄罗斯石油运输的制裁，并对世界最大的油田公司 SLB 在俄罗斯的例外经营权提出质疑。【原文：Dozens of U.S. Representatives from both political parties urged the Biden administration to toughen sanctions on Russian oil shipments and questioned an exception issued to the world's largest oilfield company SLB to operate in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-lawmakers-question-oil-service-companys-slbs-exception-russian-sanctions-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WDJTFYJ5BOHDMXAEE3GWEWHEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道墨西哥新政府酝酿税收优惠政策吸引外国公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥一位高级贸易官员在接受采访时表示，墨西哥正在考虑针对电动汽车（EV）、半导体、稀土矿、电池和电子行业提供税收减免，以吸引外国企业在国内投资和生产。【原文：Mexico is considering tax credits to attract foreign firms to invest and produce domestically, targeted at electric vehicle (EV), semiconductor, rare earth minerals, battery and electronics sectors, a top Mexican trade official said in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/mexicos-new-government-mulls-tax-incentives-lure-foreign-companies-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KG3JTDWVJRNYRCE46OVNYRMPCY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国即将遏制对华人工智能投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府发布的一份公告显示，美国禁止在中国投资人工智能领域的某些规定正在接受最后审查，这表明这些限制措施即将出台。【原文：U.S. rules that will ban certain U.S. investments in artificial intelligence in China are under final review, according to a government posting, suggesting the restrictions are coming soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/us-soon-curb-ai-investment-china-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHSWE2W435JGLHEPVD3Q4AQCBY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将向 Hemlock Semiconductor 提供 3.25 亿美元用于多晶硅生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一表示，计划向 Hemlock Semiconductor 公司拨款 3.25 亿美元，用于大幅提高半导体级多晶硅的生产能力，以改变芯片供应链。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Monday it plans to award $325 million to Hemlock Semiconductor to significantly expand production capacity of semiconductor-grade polysilicon as it seeks to shift the chips supply chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-set-award-hemlock-semiconductor-325-million-polysilicon-production-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XKJHEG26WBM7HCKYSXIV5T7PFQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:04:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场强劲，马士基上调利润展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦航运集团 A.P. 穆勒-马士基（A.P. Moller-Maersk）周一表示，由于第三季度业绩强劲、需求旺盛以及红海航运中断持续，该公司上调了全年利润、收入和现金流预期。【原文：Danish shipping group A.P. Moller-Maersk said on Monday it had raised its full-year profit, revenue and cash flow forecasts on the back of strong third quarter results, strong demand and the continuation of the Red Sea shipping disruption.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/maersk-raises-profit-outlook-strong-market-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FO4O6BTYVJKN3GDUBTEWA26FGA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:46:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜嘉班纳首席执行官未来可能考虑首次公开募股，现在的首要任务是做强业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品集团 Dolce &amp; Gabbana 首席执行官周一表示，Dolce &amp; Gabbana 还没有做好首次公开募股的准备，但准备在未来考虑。【原文：Dolce &amp; Gabbana is not ready for an initial public offering but is prepared to consider it in the future, the Italian luxury group's chief executive said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/dolce-gabbana-ceo-could-look-ipo-future-priority-now-is-stronger-business-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B33VWIA7VNMTPFHQHUADCKYEQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，如果三分之一的劳动力接受人工智能培训，葡萄牙的生产力将得到提高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一项研究显示，葡萄牙必须重新培训 130 万名工人（约占其就业人口的 30%）使用生成式人工智能工作，才能在 2030 年之前缩小与欧盟平均生产率的差距。【原文：Portugal must retrain 1.3 million workers, or around 30% of its employed population, to work with generative artificial intelligence in order to close the productivity gap with the European Union's average by 2030, a study showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/portugal-could-boost-productivity-if-third-workforce-trained-ai-study-shows-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNJRYNTMC5JHJCKJEHAK6R73YI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多头锁定新纪录，黄金魅力扩散]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，随着地缘政治局势紧张、美国大选激烈角逐以及有利的宏观背景吸引了更多投资者，黄金正在延续连续创新高的态势，每盎司3,000美元的心理里程碑也渐行渐近。【原文：Gold is extending a period of successive record highs, moving the psychological milestone of $3,000 per ounce into view, analysts said, as geopolitical tension, a tight U.S. electoral race and favorable macro backdrop attract more investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/golds-allure-spreads-bulls-lock-fresh-records-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OVP7CHER5BKPZDZMDH45J6I54U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金在股市中支持 "特朗普交易"，摩根大通称]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（JPMorgan）上周末在一份分析提名前定位如何变化的报告中称，全球对冲基金对共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）赢得大选后可能表现良好的股票表现出 "强烈偏好"。【原文：Global hedge funds have shown "a strong preference" for stocks that could perform well if Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump wins the election, JPMorgan said in a note late last week analyzing how positioning is changing ahead of the nomination.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-side-with-trump-trades-equities-says-jpm-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYRT465FY5I4RPNBCXEX624BAE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[延长债务再融资期限，精神航空股价大涨 46]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）与信用卡处理商达成协议，将债务再融资期限延长两个月至 12 月 23 日，该公司股价周一大涨 46%。【原文：Shares of Spirit Airlines surged as much as 46% on Monday after the ultra low-cost carrier reached a deal with its credit card processor to extend a debt refinancing deadline by two months until Dec. 23.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-shares-jump-46-extension-debt-refinancing-deadline-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG2LM3JEHZPVDFY47ONPIVK7SA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:07:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Vedomosti 报道，尽管存在安全隐患，但俄罗斯政府的 iPhone 购买量仍在上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《Vedomosti》日报周一报道，尽管某些官员被禁止使用苹果设备，但俄罗斯政府 1 月至 9 月的 iPhone 购买量仍比 2023 年同期高出四倍。【原文：The Russian government's purchases of iPhones for January through September were four times higher than the same period in 2023, the Vedomosti daily reported on Monday, despite certain officials being banned from using Apple devices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/russian-government-iphone-purchases-rise-despite-security-concerns-vedomosti-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RFGV3M2ELBM77KRSC6SPQ3LVWY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔与谷歌合作，将数据与生成式人工智能相结合]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍尼韦尔（Honeywell）与谷歌（Google）周一表示，双方已签署协议，将人工智能技术与其工业数据相连接，以期为客户提供简化的自主操作。【原文：Honeywell has signed a deal with Google to connect artificial intelligence technology with its industrial data, both companies said on Monday, with a view to offer streamlined autonomous operations for its customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/honeywell-partners-with-google-integrate-data-with-generative-ai-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQQJSV6IEZJ3HIN57JNZYRKWJM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行行长强调通胀预期的 "巨大 "脱锚效应]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行行长罗伯托-坎波斯-内托（Roberto Campos Neto）强调了该国通胀预期的 "巨大 "脱锚现象，并补充说，使通胀率回归目标 "非常重要"，而决策者们正致力于实现这一目标。【原文：Brazil's central bank chief Roberto Campos Neto highlighted a "huge" deanchoring of inflation expectations in the country, adding that it is "very important" to bring inflation back to target, and that policymakers are committed to doing so.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/brazil-central-bank-chief-highlights-huge-deanchoring-inflation-expectations-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RR4B5THZQFKADP5WQG4322TSIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录显示，摩根大通重新聘用科学家萨拉-卡普尼克（Sarah Kapnick）推动气候发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周一看到的一份内部备忘录，摩根大通重新聘用了科学家萨拉-卡普尼克（Sarah Kapnick）为其企业和投资银行客户提供咨询，因为这家华尔街巨头正在加强其气候咨询产品。【原文：JPMorgan Chase has rehired scientist Sarah Kapnick to advise its corporate and investment banking clients, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Monday, as the Wall Street giant ramps up its climate advisory offerings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-rehires-scientist-sarah-kapnick-climate-push-memo-shows-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SOXIK45CZRK4DJU6YQCDB3UO3A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:01:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院驳回对美国消费者监督机构领导人工作保护的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周一拒绝听取保守派对联邦消费品安全监督机构领导人的工作保护提出的质疑，此案本可以让大法官们有机会重新评估 1935 年的一个先例，即限制总统解雇某些机构负责人的能力。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court declined on Monday to hear a conservative challenge to job protections for the leaders of the federal consumer product safety watchdog in a case that would have given the justices a chance to reassess a 1935 precedent that limits a president's ability to fire certain agency heads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/supreme-court-rebuffs-challenge-job-protections-us-consumer-watchdog-leaders-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6UIB6KNOZNIBKKHRBRKP2TMBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 13:43:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价上周下跌 7% 后收复失地]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一油价上涨，收复了上周超过 7% 的跌幅，原因是对世界第一大石油进口国中国需求的担忧，以及对中东潜在供应中断的担忧有所缓解。【原文：Oil prices rose on Monday, recouping some of last week's more than 7% decline on worries about demand in China, the world's top oil importer, and easing concerns about potential supply disruptions in the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-regain-some-ground-after-7-loss-last-week-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4SH7VJEOFFP25D4YSBLHKXMNPA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 13:15:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[桑坦德银行在美国推出数字银行，以获得更低廉的汽车贷款资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙桑坦德银行（Santander）美国首席执行官蒂姆-温尼斯（Tim Wennes）告诉路透社，该公司周一在美国推出了数字银行，这将有助于该公司为超过 300 亿美元的汽车贷款资产提供资金，并拓宽其在美国的零售业务。【原文：Spain's Santander launched its digital bank in the United States on Monday, which will help it to fund over $30 billion of auto lending assets and broaden its retail business in the country, U.S. CEO Tim Wennes told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/santander-launches-digital-bank-us-gain-cheaper-funding-auto-loans-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUN6VWGLXJOFXGBKZRZE67EXNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 13:03:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根：在削减更多资产负债表的同时，关注更多渐进式降息措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周一表示，她认为央行未来还会有更多的降息举措，并表示她认为美联储没有理由不继续缩减资产负债表。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan said Monday she sees more rate cuts ahead for the central bank and suggested she sees no reasons why the Fed can’t also press forward with shrinking its balance sheet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-logan-eyes-more-gradual-rate-cuts-amid-more-balance-sheet-cuts-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYBX6SDWARISTHOHJZH4BQHAQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 13:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道欧盟将为关键矿产联合采购平台选择公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[文件显示，欧盟正急于建立一个价值 900 万欧元的关键矿产和能源联合采购机制，欧盟正在八家竞标者中做出选择，以开发一个平台，直接知情人士告诉路透社。【原文：The European Union, rushing to develop a 9 million euro joint purchasing mechanism for critical minerals and energy, is choosing between eight bidders vying to develop a platform, documents showed and sources with direct knowledge told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/eu-set-choose-firm-critical-minerals-joint-buying-platform-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQBY6BL6XVIVBID4GQZDZ6HTUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 12:47:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼任命詹姆斯-戈尔曼（James Gorman）为新董事长，将于 2026 年初宣布下一任首席执行官人选]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼周一表示，已任命詹姆斯-戈尔曼（James Gorman）为董事会主席，自 1 月 2 日起生效，接替在公司任职 9 年后离职的马克-帕克（Mark Parker）。【原文：Walt Disney said on Monday it has named James Gorman as chairman of the board, effective Jan. 2, replacing Mark Parker, who is leaving the company after nine years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-names-james-gorman-new-chairman-announce-next-ceo-early-2026-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2TWPKTIGV5PH7JEZQ3WUZ4UHSE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 12:39:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼日利亚未能批准壳牌向复兴公司出售资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼日利亚上游监管机构周一表示，尼日利亚未能批准壳牌将其在尼日尔三角洲地区的全部陆上和浅水石油天然气出售给复兴公司。【原文：Nigeria has failed to approve the sale of Shell's entire onshore and shallow-water oil and gas in the Niger Delta region to Renaissance, the country's upstream regulator said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nigeria-fails-approve-shell-asset-sale-renaissance-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AF4SAW5JJPXRIXEBLDS4BZK2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 12:06:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Northvolt 在获得一揽子融资计划方面取得进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典电池制造商 Northvolt 周一告诉路透社，该公司在筹集新的一揽子融资计划方面正在取得重大进展。【原文：Swedish battery maker Northvolt is making significant progress towards raising a new financing package, it told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/northvolt-making-progress-towards-securing-financing-package-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OEM3HLMF5MHPOZESNF2NOUPIA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 11:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼日利亚在两年多后批准埃克森-塞普拉特公司的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[尼日利亚上游监管机构首席执行官周一表示，尼日利亚已批准将埃克森美孚公司的陆上资产出售给 Seplat Energy 公司，这距离首次达成 12.8 亿美元的交易已有两年多时间。【原文：Nigeria has approved the sale of Exxon Mobil Corp's onshore assets to Seplat Energy , the chief executive officer of the country's upstream regulator said on Monday, more than two years after the $1.28 billion deal was first agreed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nigeria-approves-exxon-seplat-128-billion-deal-oil-regulator-says-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6S4OIDNCPJJ37OBDEQPRO7LBMY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 11:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德被收购后，康泰伦特首席执行官将继续掌管合同药品生产商]]></title><description><![CDATA[康泰伦特首席执行官亚历山德罗-马塞利（Alessandro Maselli）周一表示，在减肥药生产商诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）的控股股东诺和诺德控股公司（Novo Holdings）收购康泰伦特之后，他将继续掌舵这家美国合同药品生产商。【原文：Catalent CEO Alessandro Maselli said on Monday he will remain at the helm of the U.S.-based contract drugmaker after it is acquired by Novo Holdings, the controlling shareholder of weight-loss drug manufacturer Novo Nordisk .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/catalent-ceo-remain-charge-contract-drugmaker-after-novo-holdings-buyout-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QL3UFTCEHRPATECFAK2UBFBJYM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 11:31:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司的新提案可能导致四年内与工资相关的成本增加 10 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师称，尽管波音公司股价在周一上涨了 4%，有望结束一场严重的罢工，但预计其拟议的劳资合同将带来超过 10 亿美元的工资相关支出。【原文：Boeing is expected to book more than $1 billion in wage-related expenses from its proposed labor contract, analysts said, although its shares rose 4% on Monday on hopes of an end to a crippling strike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeings-new-proposal-may-lead-1-bln-wage-related-costs-over-four-years-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAODYOGPPBLB3JKTSO5UXAFHVE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 11:11:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国玉米和大豆收获迅速，给农民和仓储能力带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农民正在以多年来最快的速度收获历史上最大的两批玉米和大豆作物，这给他们的体力和粮食储存能力带来了压力。【原文：U.S. farmers are harvesting two of the largest corn and soybean crops in history at the fastest pace in years, straining their physical capabilities and their grain storage capacity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/speedy-us-corn-soy-harvests-strain-farmers-storage-capacity-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G54H7BR2VFPWFNI7GDI4SV5UCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 10:44:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：卡塔尔向亚洲主要市场销售液化天然气面临美国和阿联酋的竞争]]></title><description><![CDATA[卡塔尔发现很难达成向日本和韩国供应液化天然气（LNG）的新协议，因为来自美国和其他合同条款更灵活的国家的竞争日益激烈，这对多哈数十年来的市场主导地位构成了挑战。【原文：Qatar is finding it hard to agree new deals to supply liquefied natural gas (LNG) to Japan and South Korea as rising competition from the U.S. and elsewhere with more flexible contract terms challenges Doha's decades-old dominance of the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/qatar-lng-sales-key-asian-markets-confronted-by-us-uae-rivalry-2024-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WU6VZOM5AFIMHN25DHTVZZWJIE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 10:40:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>