<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:33:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:33:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国运通升级白金卡，每年可享 3500 美元优惠，并将手续费提高 200 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运通周四公布了期待已久的美国白金卡升级计划，增加了每年价值超过 3500 美元的新优惠，同时将年费提高了 200 美元。【原文：American Express unveiled long-awaited upgrades to its U.S. Platinum cards on Thursday, adding new perks worth over $3,500 annually while raising the annual fee by $200.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/amex-upgrades-platinum-cards-with-3500-annual-perks-hikes-fee-by-200-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7EZD7WD7VIZJFZAFTRRGKLUYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国小型国防股因抢购下一代战场技术而大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年，在为现代战争量身定制的低成本、下一代军事技术需求激增，以及五角大楼转向灵活、适应性强的作战系统的推动下，美国小型国防公司在华尔街表现突出。【原文：Smaller U.S. defense firms have emerged as standout performers on Wall Street this year, fueled by surging demand for low-cost, next-generation military tech tailored for modern warfare and the Pentagon's pivot toward agile and adaptable combat systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/small-us-defense-stocks-soar-rush-next-gen-battlefield-tech-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC6PWSZ5ZZNWFAU64P3ZGGLWDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:19:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管出口蓬勃发展，但特朗普贸易战的影响还是打击了阿根廷的大豆压榨商]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）与中国的贸易战在阿根廷引起了反响，尽管该国大豆的总体销售量创下了六年来的新高，但却削弱了该国规模庞大的大豆压榨业。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war with China has reverberated in Argentina, denting the country's massive soy crushing industry even though overall soybean sales hit a six-year high.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-trade-war-fallout-hits-argentine-soy-crushers-despite-export-boom-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Q34THOUD5JY3AAK5XAJETNBQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:11:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森寻求美国政治帮助，呼吁废除欧盟气候法]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚（Exxon Mobil）正在加大对欧盟企业可持续发展法的攻击力度，并直接向美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表达了自己的担忧，警告说该法规将导致更多企业离开欧洲。【原文：Exxon Mobil is stepping up attacks against a European Union corporate sustainability law and has taken its concerns directly to U.S. President Donald Trump, warning that the regulation will lead to more businesses leaving Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/exxon-seeks-us-political-help-call-quash-eu-climate-law-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5FHG7TACRITNPH7K2YKGZSBHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达 50 亿美元入股英特尔并建立芯片合作关系，豪赌英特尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周四表示，将向英特尔投资 50 亿美元，为这家陷入困境的美国芯片代工厂提供强有力的支持，但不会向英特尔提供关键的生产协议。【原文：Nvidia on Thursday said it will invest $5 billion in Intel , throwing its heft behind the struggling U.S. chip foundry, but stopped short of giving Intel a crucial manufacturing deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nvidia-bets-big-intel-with-5-billion-stake-chip-partnership-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTT4RG2B4BKPTGV7VREGTHIUGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行放缓量化宽松政策步伐，偏向于销售长期国债]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦，9月18日（路透社）--英国央行周四维持利率不变，并表示正在放缓量化紧缩计划的步伐，并将销售重点从长期金边债券上移开，以尽量减少对动荡的债券市场的影响。【原文：LONDON, September 18 (Reuters) - The Bank of England kept rates unchanged on Thursday and said it was slowing the pace of its quantitative tightening programme and skewing sales away from long-dated gilts to minimise the impact on turbulent bond markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/bank-england-slows-pace-qt-skews-away-long-dated-gilt-sales-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLV43LONVBNN5GWVRBQEJ4LEHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜邦修订 2025 年净销售额预测，以反映 Qnity 的分拆情况]]></title><description><![CDATA[工业材料生产商杜邦公司周四预测，2025 年净销售额约为 68.7 亿美元，调整了此前的展望，以反映计划中的电子产品部门分拆和芳纶业务剥离。【原文：Industrial materials maker DuPont on Thursday forecast 2025 net sales of about $6.87 billion, recasting its prior outlook to reflect the planned spin-off of its electronics unit and the divestiture of its Aramids business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dupont-revises-2025-net-sales-forecast-reflect-qnity-spin-off-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IWNOJMMKZVN3XDR4LRZPXLAXUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Meta 正与 Axel Springer、福克斯等公司就人工智能新闻授权进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，近几个月来，Meta Platforms 一直在与包括 Axel Springer、福克斯公司和新闻集团在内的媒体公司洽谈新闻内容授权事宜，以便将这些内容整合到其人工智能产品中。【原文：Meta Platforms has been in talks in recent months with media firms including Axel Springer, Fox Corp and News Corp to license news content for integration into its AI products, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-talks-with-axel-springer-fox-others-ai-news-licensing-wsj-reports-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGSO3SBBNFKM5FJDR7CG2GQWSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美联储会议后华尔街反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUAEBRYFRBPONPHD33JBEZR7DI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道土耳其出人意料地与欧罗巴航空公司达成协议，关键在于控制权]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位消息人士告诉路透社，土耳其航空之所以能出人意料地击败欧洲竞争对手汉莎航空和法航-荷航，收购西班牙航空公司欧洲航空（Air Europa）的股份，在很大程度上是因为土耳其航空愿意与该航空公司的伊达尔戈（Hidalgo）家族所有者分享对该航空公司的控制权。【原文：Turkish Airlines' surprise deal for a stake in Spanish carrier Air Europa, outlasting European rivals Lufthansa and Air France-KLM , was in large part down to its willingness to share control of the carrier with the airline's Hidalgo family owners, four sources told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/turkeys-surprise-air-europa-deal-came-down-one-key-thing-control-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMKRRRZ7NVM3BJON6YXSQANBUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:24:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为人工智能芯片和计算能力路线图中的主要产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国华为公司（HWT.UL）结束了多年的保密状态，详细介绍了其芯片和计算能力系统的产品路线图，首次讨论了它打算如何挑战全球行业领导者英伟达公司（Nvidia）。【原文：China's Huawei (HWT.UL) has ended years of secrecy to detail its product roadmap for chips and computing power systems, discussing for the first time how it intends to challenge global industry leader Nvidia .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/key-products-huaweis-ai-chips-computing-power-roadmap-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGKQP72TQFNI7K2X62HPSJLMPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储指出将进一步降息后，标普 500 指数和纳斯达克指数期货创下历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国股指期货上涨，在美国央行今年首次降息四分之一点后，与 S&amp;P 500 指数和纳斯达克指数挂钩的股指期货创下历史新高。【原文：U.S. stock index futures gained on Thursday, with those tied to the S&amp;P 500 and the Nasdaq at record highs a day after the U.S. central bank delivered a quarter-point interest rate cut, its first this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sp-500-nasdaq-futures-hit-record-high-after-fed-points-further-rate-cuts-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CMQNQSOFJORJFERLFUHF7ZOFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商一直在抵制因关税而提高汽车价格。这种情况可能不会持续太久。]]></title><description><![CDATA[自美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策于今年 4 月生效以来，汽车制造商一直在吸收数十亿美元的额外开支，从而使美国汽车消费者免受价格冲击。到目前为止【原文：Automakers have been absorbing billions in added expenses since U.S. President Donald Trump’s tariffs took effect in April, sparing American car shoppers from sticker shock. So far.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/automakers-have-resisted-raising-car-prices-because-tariffs-that-might-not-last-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDVCNUEUERPBBLITC25WWDWLTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从 Skechers 到 Foot Locker：关税混乱刺激鞋类和服装交易创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的贸易战正助推美国服装和鞋类企业今年的并购创下历史新高，一些企业通过合并来帮助抵消关税成本，而另一些企业则通过私有化在公开市场之外度过其总统任期的未来 3 年半。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war is helping to push U.S. clothing and footwear acquisitions to all-time highs this year, with some companies merging to help offset tariff costs while others go private to weather the next 3-1/2 years of his presidency outside of the public market, dealmakers say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/skechers-foot-locker-tariff-chaos-spurs-record-high-footwear-apparel-deals-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NMCBFDNFVZPNBFYVUVONIACKLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税后，瑞士对美出口下降超过五分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[官方数据周四显示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对瑞士征收39%关税的8月份，瑞士对美国的商品出口下降了五分之一以上。【原文：Swiss goods exports to the United States dropped by more than a fifth in August, the month in which President Donald Trump imposed 39% tariffs on the country, official data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swiss-exports-us-drop-over-fifth-after-trump-tariffs-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JH2QQEGUIVKXDAJLAXVAR7SRV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度首席经济顾问称美国可能放宽对印度的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度首席经济顾问阿南塔-纳格斯瓦兰（V. Anantha Nageswaran）周四表示，美国可能很快取消对印度商品征收的惩罚性进口关税，并将互惠关税从目前的25%降至10%-15%。【原文：The U.S. may soon scrap the penal import tariff on Indian goods and also cut reciprocal tariff to 10-15% from the existing 25%, India's Chief Economist Adviser V. Anantha Nageswaran said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/us-may-ease-india-tariffs-indias-chief-economic-adviser-says-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RCETZJ2Z5JE3JYPXZXAISMY7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 09:57:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国校园吸引力下降，印度 upGrad 着眼于亚洲扩张]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度教育科技初创公司upGrad的一位高层管理人员表示，由于签证限制和成本障碍，选择去美国和英国留学的学生越来越少，因此该公司正在探索与中东和亚太地区的更多大学建立合作关系。【原文：Indian edtech startup upGrad is exploring more university tie-ups in the Middle East and the Asia-Pacific as fewer students are opting to study in the U.S. and the UK due to visa restrictions and cost hurdles, a top executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/indias-upgrad-eyes-asia-expansion-us-campuses-lose-appeal-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIRDA2MUAFKRTEZRZTNGGZG2FQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 09:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业协会负责人表示，日本应实现石油来源多样化，但加拿大的供应被认为十分困难]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本炼油行业协会负责人周四表示，由于日本 95% 的原油进口来自中东，日本炼油企业应考虑实现供应来源多样化，但由于加拿大石油的重质特性，进口加拿大石油可能具有挑战性。【原文：Japanese oil refiners should consider diversifying supply sources as 95% of its crude imports come from the Middle East, but importing Canadian oil could be challenging due to its heavy characteristics, the head of the industry association said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/japan-should-diversify-oil-sources-canadian-supply-seen-tough-industry-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">235IL52MHZI5XPFYIIJ2F4SGEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 09:29:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查发现：过去一年，网络攻击导致德国经济损失 3,000 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四公布的一项调查显示，网络攻击越来越多地由外国情报机构而非犯罪分子发起，在过去一年里，德国经济损失近 3,000 亿欧元（3,549.9 亿美元）。【原文：Cyber attacks, launched increasingly often by foreign intelligence agencies rather than criminals, cost the German economy almost 300 billion euros ($354.99 billion) over the past year, according to a survey published on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/cyber-attacks-cost-german-economy-300-bln-euros-past-year-survey-finds-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4NKFOYLLBIBFOERWVVINGP5HE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 09:27:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宜家更换首席执行官，专注于资金短缺的消费者]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大家具品牌宜家家居的所有者周四表示，宜家家居集团首席执行官乔恩-亚伯拉罕松-林（Jon Abrahamsson Ring）将于今年年底卸任，由雅库布-扬科夫斯基（Jakub Jankowski）接任。【原文：Inter IKEA Group CEO Jon Abrahamsson Ring will step down at the end of the year, the owner of the world's biggest furniture brand said on Thursday, with Jakub Jankowski taking over as trade tensions and U.S. tariffs loom over the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/inter-ikea-switches-ceos-it-focuses-cash-strapped-consumers-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WD3LPNLRIBPFRCLYOJQEHIE6VQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 09:23:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢首席执行官希望公司快速发展，并对新想法持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[雀巢公司首席执行官菲利普-纳夫拉蒂尔（Philipp Navratil）周四表示，他希望这家瑞士食品公司能够快速发展，并对新想法持开放态度，这是他本月初上任以来首次发表公开评论。【原文：Nestle Chief Executive Philipp Navratil wants the Swiss food company to move fast and be open to fresh ideas, he said on Thursday, in his first public comments since taking charge earlier this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/nestle-ceo-wants-company-move-fast-be-open-fresh-ideas-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JARHIGAZRVLA3N2OOHEQBZJENU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 09:16:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deliveroo 首席执行官威尔-舒（Will Shu）将在 DoorDash 被收购后下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国送餐公司 Deliveroo 周四表示，一旦美国竞争对手 DoorDash 对其的收购生效，创始人兼首席执行官威尔-舒（Will Shu）将辞职。【原文：British food delivery firm Deliveroo said on Thursday founder and CEO Will Shu will step down once its takeover by U.S. rival DoorDash takes effect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/deliveroo-ceo-will-shu-step-down-after-doordash-takeover-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XN6S7YSMXZOJNNN5JQICTSVSXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 09:09:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国章鱼能源公司将分拆技术部门 Kraken]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着英国最大的电力供应商专注于核心业务，章鱼能源公司（Octopus Energy）周四表示将分拆其技术部门克拉肯技术公司（Kraken Technologies），并任命蒂姆-温（Tim Wan）为新分拆公司的首席财务官。【原文：Octopus Energy said on Thursday it would spin its technology arm Kraken Technologies off and named Tim Wan as the newly separated company's chief financial officer, as Britain largest electricity supplier focuses on its core operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/uks-octopus-energy-spin-off-technology-arm-kraken-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5AT4S6LENKMBBTWBQMCXRHQTU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 08:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国现代重工洽谈收购美国造船厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国现代重工公司（HD Hyundai Heavy Industries）的一位高级管理人员表示，该公司正在与多家公司就收购一家美国造船厂进行谈判，以寻求在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统的推动下重振美国萎靡不振的造船业。【原文：South Korea's HD Hyundai Heavy Industries is in talks with multiple companies about buying a U.S. shipyard, a senior company executive said, seeking to tap into President Donald Trump's push to revive America's ailing shipbuilding industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-koreas-hd-hyundai-heavy-talks-buy-us-shipyard-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGRME4HVMBNQNBAFYHB7GSXTRQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 08:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车将提高美国产量，因关税打击而降低利润率目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车（Hyundai Motor）周四表示，为了应对美国的关税政策，该公司计划到2030年在美国生产80%以上的汽车。【原文：Hyundai Motor said on Thursday it aims to produce more than 80% of the vehicles it sells in the U.S. in America by 2030 in response to U.S. tariff policies, as the South Korean automaker ramps up capacity at its Georgia plant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-ramp-up-us-output-trims-profit-margin-goal-tariff-hit-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSUDK4NWDRKBVFLG5HNGO5AOCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 08:49:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英美资源集团在澳大利亚布里斯班削减 "少量 "职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[英美资源集团（Anglo American）周四称，该公司已在澳大利亚布里斯班办事处和附近的煤矿裁减了 "少量 "工作岗位，作为该公司简化业务、适应煤炭价格下跌和成本上升的努力的一部分。【原文：Anglo American said on Thursday it had cut a "small number" of jobs at its office in Brisbane in Australia and nearby coal mines as part of the miner's efforts to simplify its operations and adapt to lower coal prices and rising costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/anglo-american-cuts-small-number-jobs-australias-brisbane-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7D2N6HYOEVI6PFO3RU2SS4RDUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 08:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[针对英伟达人工智能芯片禁令报道，中国表示愿保持对话]]></title><description><![CDATA[针对有报道称中国监管机构下令企业停止采购英伟达人工智能芯片，中国外交部周四表示，中国愿与有关各方保持对话，以保持全球产业链和供应链的稳定。【原文：China is willing to maintain dialogue with all parties involved to keep global industrial and supply chains stable, its foreign ministry said on Thursday in response to reports of the Chinese regulator ordering firms to halt purchases of Nvidia AI chips.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/china-says-it-is-willing-maintain-dialogue-response-report-nvidia-ai-chip-ban-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JR3J5VX7BNPEJK62R6OQ3AXNZ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 07:39:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称现代汽车将因安全带问题召回56.85万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周四表示，现代汽车公司将在美国召回超过56.85万辆帕利塞德（Palisade）汽车，因为在发生碰撞时，未能锁紧的安全带扣可能无法正确地束缚乘客。【原文：Hyundai Motor is recalling more than 568,500 Palisade vehicles in the U.S., as the seat belt buckles that fail to latch may not properly restrain passengers in a crash, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-recall-568500-us-vehicles-over-seat-belt-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUOOSSBBERN53NJHFFR5AGYZMU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 07:25:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）称，丰田将因仪表板问题召回逾 59.1 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车安全监管机构周四表示，由于仪表板显示屏存在问题，无法显示关键信息，增加了车祸或受伤的风险，丰田将在美国召回591377辆汽车。【原文：Toyota is recalling 591,377 vehicles in the U.S. due to an issue with the instrument panel display that does not show critical information, increasing the risk of a crash or injury, the country's auto safety regulator said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-recall-over-591000-us-vehicles-over-instrument-panel-issue-nhtsa-says-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BR7ZUIQL3NIGBH4SNQWZFZ3P7M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 07:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MBK 控制的乐天卡称近 300 万客户的个人数据被泄露]]></title><description><![CDATA[由私募股权基金 MBK 控制的韩国乐天卡公司周四表示，由于受到黑客攻击，约 297 万客户的个人数据已经泄露。【原文：South Korean credit card company Lotte Card, which is controlled by private equity fund MBK, said on Thursday that the personal data of some 2.97 million customers has been leaked due to a hacking attack.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mbk-controlled-lotte-card-says-personal-data-nearly-3-million-customers-leaked-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ILL5OGFYGNITTMYQKOIEJI22GI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 06:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>