<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:35:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:35:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美国 12 月 PCE 通胀上扬支持美联储按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 12 月份物价上涨，消费者支出激增，这表明美联储今年可能会推迟一段时间降息。【原文：U.S. prices increased in December while consumer spending surged, suggesting that the Federal Reserve could delay cutting interest rates for some time this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-us-dec-pce-inflation-uptick-supports-fed-hold-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITIQJN5EINNFPNSHDWHNGVSZ7I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 的 WhatsApp 称以色列间谍软件公司 Paragon 将数十名用户作为攻击目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta 流行的 WhatsApp 聊天服务的一位官员说，以色列间谍软件公司 Paragon Solutions 已将其数十名用户作为攻击目标，其中包括记者和民间社会成员。【原文：An official with Meta's popular WhatsApp chat service said the Israeli spyware company Paragon Solutions had targeted scores of its users, including journalists and members of civil society.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/metas-whatsapp-says-israeli-spyware-company-paragon-targeted-scores-users-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QAQ3MBHU2JJFVF66X5LW3PJ3JI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第四季度劳动力成本温和上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国劳动力成本在第四季度略有上升，这为美联储官员在2024年底降低通胀的进展停滞后提供了一些安慰。【原文：U.S. labor costs rose marginally in the fourth quarter, offering some comfort to Federal Reserve officials after progress lowering inflation stalled at the end of 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-labor-costs-rise-moderately-fourth-quarter-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J6YL4GQDKVJV5NOCYQES2ZE3LQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员押注美联储下次降息将等到 6 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，交易员们继续押注美联储将等到6月份再恢复降息，因为政府数据显示，12月份美国中央银行的目标通胀率上升至2.6%，符合经济学家的预期。
美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）在发表鹰派货币政策讲话的同时公布了通胀报告，在通胀报告公布后，以美联储政策利率为结算基准的期货交易商认为，美联储6月会议后短期借款利率为4.25%或更低的可能性约为70%，与当天早些时候相比变化不大。【原文：Traders on Friday kept bets that the Federal Reserve will wait until June to resume interest rate cuts, after government data showed inflation by the U.S. central bank's targeted measure ticked up to 2.6% in December, as economists had expected.
After the inflation report, released at the same time as hawkish monetary policy remarks from Fed Governor Michelle Bowman, traders of futures that settle to the Fed's policy rate priced in about a 70% chance that the short-term borrowing rate will be 4.25% or lower after the Fed's June meeting, little changed from earlier in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/traders-bet-feds-next-rate-cut-will-wait-until-june-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZCTUYAT75OARJIAOXWWVDXYM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月通胀率上升；消费支出加速]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 12 月份物价上涨，消费者支出激增，这表明美联储今年可能会推迟一段时间降息。【原文：U.S. prices increased in December while consumer spending surged, suggesting that the Federal Reserve could delay cutting interest rates for some time this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-inflation-rise-december-consumer-spending-accelerates-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAI5IBF3Z5KNVHHE4GACCUYLAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:40:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油生产商雪佛龙公司在特朗普发布更名令后使用 "美国湾 "一词]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国石油生产商雪佛龙公司（Chevron）在周五发布的第四季度新闻稿中使用了 "美国湾"（Gulf of America）而不是墨西哥湾，这是美国企业开始执行美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）为这一海洋盆地重新命名的命令的一个迹象。【原文：U.S. oil producer Chevron used the term "Gulf of America" instead of Gulf of Mexico in its fourth-quarter press release on Friday, a sign of corporate America beginning to implement U.S. President Donald Trump's order to rename the ocean basin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-producer-chevron-uses-term-gulf-america-after-trump-renaming-order-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LH6IZIBWURMILGOIJHMKDQJBWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍曼：通胀风险上行，进一步降息应谨慎渐进]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）表示，她仍预计通胀下降将允许今年进一步降息，但她认为工资上涨、金融市场活跃、地缘政治风险以及即将出台的政府政策可能会减缓这一进程，并使物价压力持续上升。【原文：Federal Reserve governor Michelle Bowman said she still expects declining inflation to allow further interest rate cuts this year, but feels rising wages, buoyant financial markets, geopolitical risks, and upcoming administration policies could slow the process and keep price pressures elevated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/bowman-inflation-risks-upside-further-rate-cuts-should-be-gradual-cautious-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZVKNT45NFLJJHQJKEXJBCLJSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 11 月国内生产总值萎缩 0.2%，下月可能反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大统计局（Statistics Canada）周五表示，由于内陆运输和港口停工导致大多数行业的经济活动萎缩，加拿大 11 月份的经济萎缩幅度超过预期。【原文：Canada's economy contracted more than expected in November as activity across a majority of sectors shrank due to work stoppages in inland transportation and at ports, Statistics Canada said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-gdp-contracts-by-02-november-likely-rebounded-following-month-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2PLTD65XJRKTFN7JJE6ST65GJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:35:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高露洁-棕榄因需求放缓导致年销售额下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[牙膏生产商高露洁-棕榄公司（Colgate-Palmolive）周五预测全年销售额将低于华尔街预期，此前该公司的季度销售额未达预期，原因是北美和拉丁美洲对其家用产品的需求疲软。【原文：Toothpaste maker Colgate-Palmolive forecast annual sales below Wall Street expectations after missing quarterly sales estimates on Friday, hurt by weak demand in North America and Latin America for its household products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/colgate-palmolive-sees-weaker-annual-sales-demand-slowdown-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEZICITPFFJDPIA2VBECBLG6EM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意法半导体可能在法国和意大利裁员 2000-3000 人 - 彭博新闻社]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引匿名消息人士的话报道，作为重组计划的一部分，法国-意大利计算机芯片制造商意法半导体公司（STMicroelctronics）正在考虑裁员，最多裁减其法国和意大利工厂 6% 的员工或 3000 名工人。【原文：French-Italian computer chip maker STMicroelctronics is considering cuts of up to 6% of its workforce or 3,000 workers in its French and Italian plants as part of a restructuring program, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing anonymous sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/stmicroelectronics-may-cut-2000-3000-jobs-france-italy-bloomberg-news-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IS3XDRBXJBMKPCD7Z5TF7NKXFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大比特币矿商 Bitfarms 考虑转向人工智能数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于多伦多的比特币矿商比特大陆（Bitfarms）周五表示，该公司已聘请两名顾问探讨如何改造其部分设施，以满足对人工智能数据中心日益增长的需求。【原文：Toronto-based bitcoin miner Bitfarms has enlisted two consultants to explore how it can transform some of its facilities to meet the growing demand for artificial intelligence data centers, it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/canadian-bitcoin-miner-bitfarms-mulls-pivot-ai-data-centers-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKGK4K4VFRMFZDKLICUFHJOPBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：特朗普的墨西哥关税威胁：都说了些什么，会有什么影响？]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普兑现承诺，对从墨西哥进口的商品征收 25% 的关税，那么长期以来的贸易关系将翻开动荡不安的新篇章，消费者也将受到冲击。【原文：If U.S. President Donald Trump follows through on his pledge to slap 25% tariffs on imports from Mexico it could usher in a volatile new chapter in the longstanding trade relationship with the impacts hitting consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trumps-mexico-tariff-threats-what-has-been-said-what-would-impact-be-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EH7RIBLTSJL5ZCXLMS2SJVUKIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[先锋集团（Vanguard）缩减美国公司董事会的多元化措辞]]></title><description><![CDATA[顶级共同基金管理公司先锋（Vanguard）取消了其对美国公司纳入女性和少数族裔董事的部分指导，这表明企业多元化努力的动态正在发生变化，受到了特朗普新政府的攻击。【原文：Top mutual fund manager Vanguard removed some of its guidance for U.S. companies to include women and minority directors, a sign of the shifting dynamics of corporate diversity efforts that have come under attack from the new Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/vanguard-dials-back-diversity-language-us-corporate-boards-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6YFWNWZGIFMCNFNDIONTXWZBAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拉塔航空公司称现在讨论 Gol-Azul 合作的影响为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉塔姆航空公司周五表示，现在讨论其在巴西第一大市场的两个最大竞争对手之间的合并计划可能产生的影响还为时过早，但该公司表示相信反垄断监督机构 CADE 会采取缓解措施。【原文：LATAM Airlines said on Friday it was still too early to discuss potential impacts of a planned merger between its two largest rivals in top market Brazil, but voiced trust in antitrust watchdog CADE to put in place mitigation measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/latam-airlines-says-it-is-too-early-discuss-impact-gol-azul-tie-up-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCHXBKED3RPXPH6H6HGX4NRE3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行 2024 年净利润增长 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行（Commerzbank）周五表示，该行 2024 年净利润增长 20%，比原计划提前近两周公布盈利，因为该行抵御了意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）对合作的兴趣。【原文：Germany's Commerzbank said on Friday that it posted a 20% increase in net profit in 2024, announcing earnings nearly two weeks ahead of schedule as it fends off interest in a tie-up from Italy's UniCredit .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/germanys-commerzbank-posts-20-rise-net-profit-2024-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTH6INPMG5ISFHMBH34C5NZY2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:54:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士法院认定 Trafigura 及前高管犯有腐败罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士最高刑事法庭周五裁定，在一起涉及向一名安哥拉官员付款以换取石油合同的案件中，Trafigura公司和一名前高管犯有腐败罪。【原文：Switzerland's top criminal court on Friday found Trafigura and a former executive guilty of corruption in a case involving payments made to an Angolan official in exchange for oil contracts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/swiss-court-finds-trafigura-former-executive-guilty-corruption-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5IUIKI5PFKDVHQ6S73O7HXSF4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利安德巴塞尔（LyondellBasell）因化学品需求疲软而出现季度亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[受欧洲和亚洲等主要市场需求疲软的影响，石化产品制造商利安德巴塞尔（LyondellBasell）周五公布第四季度业绩亏损。【原文：Petrochemicals manufacturer LyondellBasell on Friday reported a loss in the fourth quarter, hurt by weak demand across key markets such as Europe and Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/lyondellbasell-posts-quarterly-loss-weak-demand-chemicals-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6RNHJ7AMURN77NWQKZPLIISMGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾伯维预测 2025 年利润将高于预期，原因是有了新的免疫学药物]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯维周五预计 2025 年利润将高于预期，原因是其较新的免疫学药物 Skyrizi 和 Rinvoq 的强劲销售弥补了其旗舰药物 Humira 的急剧下降，Humira 目前正面临着激烈的竞争。【原文：AbbVie forecast 2025 profit above estimates on Friday, as strong sales of its newer immunology drugs Skyrizi and Rinvoq make up for a steep decline in those of Humira, its flagship rheumatoid arthritis drug that is now facing stiff competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/abbvie-forecasts-2025-profit-above-estimates-driven-by-newer-immunology-drugs-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SC5O7J5YRPK3KW76CMUGVHZLA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电装着眼于价格谈判，而非针对特朗普关税的恐慌情绪]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本电装公司（Denso）的一位高管周五表示，世界第二大汽车零部件制造商并不过度担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普即将对墨西哥和加拿大征收的关税，该公司可能会通过提价来控制成本的增加。【原文：The world's second-largest car parts maker is not unduly worried about U.S. President Donald Trump's looming tariffs on Mexico and Canada, and may seek to manage increased costs by raising prices, a top executive at Japan's Denso said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/denso-eyes-price-negotiations-not-panic-against-trumps-tariffs-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKMI2P6D5FP7ZIVLC5F6TS522U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:23:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 公司公布第四季度亏损低于预期，原因是可再生能源强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于可再生能源业务的增长抵消了炼油利润的急剧下降，炼油商菲利普斯 66 周五公布的亏损额小于预期。【原文：Refiner Phillips 66 reported a smaller-than-expected loss on Friday as strength in its renewables segment offset a sharp decline in refining margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/phillips-66-reports-smaller-than-expected-fourth-quarter-loss-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQK6XT5J6NJWLD7WGBSCVD77AI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 12:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[怡安商业风险解决方案部门业绩强劲，季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，保险经纪公司怡安公布第四季度利润增长，商业风险解决方案业务的强劲表现为其带来了帮助。【原文：Insurance brokerage firm Aon reported a higher fourth-quarter profit on Friday, helped by robust performance in its commercial risk solutions business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/aons-quarterly-profit-rises-commercial-risk-solutions-unit-strength-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VANCOBPVXBJMTJ7TYDC2TU43OQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃克森公司第四季度业绩超出预期，二叠纪和圭亚那产量增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃克森美孚周五公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，原因是石油和天然气产量的增加抵消了油价下跌和炼油利润率下降的影响。【原文：Exxon Mobil on Friday beat Wall Street's estimate for fourth-quarter profit as higher oil and gas production offset lower oil prices and weaker refining margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-beats-q4-estimates-with-higher-permian-guyana-output-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX7QC6UO7JO3PIEYVOWT4YBHPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普京下令允许向亚美尼亚基金出售高盛俄罗斯分部]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的一项政府法令显示，弗拉基米尔-普京总统已授权投资公司 Balchug Capital 收购高盛在俄罗斯的部门。【原文：President Vladimir Putin has authorised the purchase of Goldman Sachs' unit in Russia by investment company Balchug Capital, a government decree published on Friday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/putin-decree-permits-sale-goldman-sachs-russian-unit-armenian-fund-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQOY4IMBKROBTKWQLYTOX7GLYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街准备应对加拿大和墨西哥可能征收关税的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球政策制定者和华尔街分析师一直在为特朗普新政府的大规模贸易壁垒做准备。但在执政的第一周，特朗普政府将更多精力放在了国内方面，全球贸易格局基本未变。【原文：Global policymakers and Wall Street analysts have been bracing for massive trade barriers from the new Trump administration. But it focused more on the domestic front in the first week in power, leaving the global trade landscape largely unchanged.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-gears-up-fallout-likely-tariffs-canada-mexico-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQF3TNYXF5LRBLOQ6O3HE5GGRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 就业数据迫在眉睫，科技股抛售令投资者心惊肉跳]]></title><description><![CDATA[受本周科技股大幅抛售影响，美国投资者将密切关注即将公布的就业数据，以寻找经济持续复苏的迹象，这可能会加剧美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政策已经激起的通胀担忧。【原文：U.S. investors rattled by this week's sharp tech sell-off will closely watch upcoming jobs data for signs of continued economic resilience, which could fuel inflationary concerns already stoked by President Donald Trump's policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-tech-sell-off-jolts-investors-jobs-data-looms-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42QRSZXC4RJURH37GEUVSWG45E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:19:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电网电力提升项目将错过 7 月最后期限]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社对监管文件的审查，美国电网运营商正要求监管机构给予更多时间，以满足联邦命令的要求，即使用可将输电容量提高 40% 的设备升级现有输电线路。【原文：U.S. grid operators are asking regulators for more time to meet a federal order to upgrade existing transmission lines with equipment that can boost their capacity up to 40%, according to a Reuters review of regulatory documents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/power-boosting-project-us-grid-miss-july-deadline-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MKJOSYNPJMGBD2X2HOCEJEEXY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:17:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金四周来首次出现单周资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 1 月 29 日的一周里，美国股票基金四周来首次吸引资金流入，这主要是受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发表讲话后降息希望的刺激，以及科技股在周一下跌后反弹。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted inflows for the first time in four weeks in the week through Jan. 29, spurred by hopes of interest rate cuts following comments from President Donald Trump, and a rebound in tech shares following Monday's losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-draw-first-weekly-inflow-four-weeks-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWMU37HZXZNJXIBODXWCMBGE7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:16:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税最后期限临近，外汇市场为加拿大和墨西哥波动做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对其两个最大贸易伙伴加征关税的最后期限一到，全球货币市场就做好了波动加剧的准备，外汇期权发出了信号，加元成为众矢之的。【原文：A deadline for U.S. tariff hikes on two of its top trading partners has global currency markets braced for increased volatility, FX options signal, with the Canadian dollar in the crosshairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/forex-markets-brace-canada-mexico-swings-us-tariff-deadline-looms-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z6BK4NA42BMMDOB3ELLMCDBCVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道调查人员称，比亚迪巴西工厂的中国工人签订的合同存在滥用条款]]></title><description><![CDATA[从中国到巴西东北部为电动汽车制造商比亚迪建造新工厂的工人，每班工作 10 小时的收入约为 70 美元，是中国许多地区每小时最低工资的两倍多。对许多人来说，这让他们很容易就做出了加入的决定，但要退出就难上加难了。【原文：The workers who traveled from China to northeast Brazil to build a new factory for electric car maker BYD earned roughly $70 per 10-hour shift, over twice the Chinese hourly minimum wage in many regions. For many, that made signing up an easy decision - but getting out would be much harder.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-workers-byd-brazil-factory-signed-contracts-with-abusive-clauses-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BV4MV6L3JNC7OCBMQQPX4A2SE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:06:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[面对特朗普对仔猪和农作物征收关税，加拿大农民修改销售计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大农民正在与美国买家重新谈判牲畜合同，并为他们之前计划销往边境以南的农作物寻找本地市场，以尽量减少美国潜在的新关税带来的经济打击。【原文：Canadian farmers are renegotiating livestock contracts with U.S. buyers and finding local markets for crops they previously planned to sell south of the border to minimize the economic hit from potential new U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/facing-trump-tariffs-piglets-crops-canadian-farmers-revise-sales-plans-2025-01-31/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IUXW3W6ZNPEPK2ROHX3F2CEKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 11:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>