<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:39:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:39:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[制药业可能被征收关税，美股期货下跌；福特汽车下调业绩预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货走低，此前唐纳德-特朗普总统关于可能对制药业征收关税的言论再次引发了人们对贸易战影响的担忧，而一些业绩不佳的企业也拖累了投资者的情绪。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were lower on Tuesday after President Donald Trump's comments on potential pharma tariffs renewed worries of the impact of a trade war, while some downbeat corporate results also weighed on investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-fall-possible-pharma-tariffs-ford-pulls-forecast-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A3E3ZEIYG5LEXHK4LF5NS7KOYM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司重申2025年前景，称美国关税影响 "有限]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周二重申了其全年交付和财务前景，并表示美国迄今征收的关税 "影响有限"，不会影响其第一季度业绩。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer on Tuesday reaffirmed its full-year delivery and financial outlook, and said that tariffs imposed by the United States so far had "limited impact" that did not affect its first-quarter results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/embraer-reaffirms-2025-outlook-says-us-tariffs-have-limited-impact-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CU6KVIEIPBITLLYDBRRPHBXQOM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:25:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普 "解放日 "后并购交易签约创 20 年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普于 4 月 2 日发动全球贸易战之后，银行家和首席执行官们纷纷踩下了并购的刹车，签订的交易比 COVID-19 大流行和 2008 年全球金融危机最惨淡的时期还要少。【原文：Bankers and CEOs hit the brakes on mergers and acquisitions after U.S. President Donald Trump launched a global trade war on April 2, with fewer deals getting signed than during the bleakest days of the COVID-19 pandemic and the 2008 global financial crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ma-deal-signing-hits-20-year-low-after-trumps-liberation-day-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGJ7MNTYOJKNPFYUYSECOMWCJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉四月份德国汽车销量减少近一半]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国道路交通机构 KBA 周二表示，特斯拉 4 月份在德国的销量几乎减少了一半，尽管电池电动汽车的销量总体上有所增长。【原文：Tesla's sales volume in Germany nearly halved in April, German road traffic agency KBA said on Tuesday, even as sales of battery electric vehicles rose overall.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-german-car-sales-nearly-halved-april-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6ORIQD37RPADAKHVHZHCARKIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:08:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：特朗普加征关税，加拿大企业从美国转向新市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家为制药业生产胶囊和片剂的制造商正在亚洲寻找新的合作伙伴。一家在美国拥有 35 年客户基础的钢铁零部件制造商正在告诉客户，预计将支付更高的价格。另一家为体育或学校活动生产吉祥物服装的公司正在降低价格，以免失去美国客户。【原文：A manufacturer of capsules and tablets for the pharmaceuticals industry is scouting Asia for new partners. A steel component maker, with a client base in the United States stretching back 35 years, is telling customers to expect to pay higher prices. Another company, that produces mascot costumes for sporting or school events, is lowering its prices so as not to lose American customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-tariffs-sink-canadian-companies-pivot-us-new-markets-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPFFHS65IJKMZGV5CFOUGCZJ7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港推出新措施吸引更多科技和生物企业上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港周二推出了一项计划，为科技公司在其证券交易所上市提供更多便利，因为香港希望利用中国公司日益增长的离岸融资欲望。【原文：Hong Kong launched a scheme on Tuesday to offer smoother listings for tech companies on its stock exchange, as it looks to capitalize on Chinese companies' growing appetite to raise funds offshore.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/hong-kong-launches-new-measures-attract-more-tech-bio-listings-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAG2BVLKORO23DT6YSAFEK2R74</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多伦多 4 月成屋销售回吐近期跌幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[多伦多地区地产局周二的数据显示，大多伦多地区4月份的房屋销售量比3月份有所上升，但比去年4月份大幅下降，原因是购房者考虑到加拿大和美国之间的贸易紧张局势。【原文：Greater Toronto Area home sales rose in April from March but were down sharply from April last year, as homebuyers weighed trade tensions between Canada and the United States, Toronto Regional Real Estate Board data showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/toronto-home-sales-claw-back-some-recent-declines-april-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUDJX4HCQFNTTBCY3WWNY66H2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:03:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲冷落马斯克，特斯拉英国 4 月销量两年多来最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究机构 New AutoMotive 周二发布的数据显示，即使在电动汽车需求上升的情况下，特斯拉 4 月份在英国的新车销量仍同比暴跌 62%，创两年多来最低。【原文：Tesla's new car sales in Britain plummeted 62% year-on-year in April to their lowest in over two years, even as demand for electric vehicles rose, data from research group New AutoMotive showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-uk-sales-lowest-over-two-years-april-europe-snubs-musk-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UPSLHDSZCZI7TJZR43NUAZWGJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟在准备应对美国扩大关税时保持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易委员马罗斯-塞夫科维奇（Maros Sefcovic）周二表示，欧盟将针对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）在90天暂停期间对欧盟进口产品征收的大量关税准备反制措施，并将所有选项摆在桌面上。【原文：The European Union will prepare countermeasures to the multitude of U.S. tariffs imposed on EU imports during President Donald Trump's 90-day pause, with all options on the table, European Trade Commissioner Maros Sefcovic said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-keeps-options-open-it-readies-response-expanding-us-tariffs-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QJ6UJRO5SNMDFO34JBINFBGVYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:30:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲危机逆转"，货币因美元而飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着世界出口大国开始质疑几十年来将巨额贸易顺差投资于美国资产的趋势，亚洲出现的美元抛售潮对美元来说是一个不祥之兆。【原文：A wave of dollar selling in Asia is an ominous sign for the greenback as the world's export powerhouse starts to question a decades-long trend of investing its big trade surpluses in U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/asian-crisis-reverse-currencies-soar-dollar-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOOYPOS7Z5OIXLRCYJOJ3RX27I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业组织称欧盟应将半导体支出翻两番]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业组织 SEMI 周二在对欧盟即将出台的投资预算磋商做出正式回应时表示，欧盟应将芯片支出翻两番，并为其分配单独的预算。【原文：The European Union should quadruple its spending on chips and allocate a separate budget for it, industry group SEMI said on Tuesday in its official response to EU consultations for its upcoming investment budget.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-should-quadruple-semiconductor-spending-industry-group-says-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZLBIAS7BT5MC5OIX2GD3HPRHEU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:08:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[兰博基尼季度收入增长 29.6%，混合动力车型推动交付量增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利豪华跑车制造商兰博基尼周二报告称，尽管全球形势复杂，但受其新型混合动力车 Revuelto 和 Urus SE 全球强劲需求的推动，公司收入猛增 29.6%，达到 8.952 亿欧元。【原文：Italian luxury sports carmaker Lamborghini reported on Tuesday a 29.6% jump in revenue to 895.2 million euros, driven by strong global demand for its new hybrid models, the Revuelto and Urus SE, despite the complex global scenario.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lamborghini-quarterly-revenue-up-296-hybrid-models-boost-deliveries-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFDWESAQLVLXRCVTTUN2AB3GKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:56:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Aurizon 公司裁员 200 人，全年盈利可能受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚铁路货运运营商 Aurizon Holdings 周二盘后表示，在对其非经营性成本基础进行持续评估后，该公司正寻求在其业务范围内裁减 200 个全职岗位。【原文：Australia's Aurizon Holdings is looking to potentially cut 200 full-time job roles across its business after an ongoing assessment of its non-operational cost base, the rail freight operator said post trading hours on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/australias-aurizon-flags-200-job-cuts-potential-hit-full-year-earnings-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVIAIO3VQZJZJIKNJ6XQ2KV7UI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡海湾银行任命前美联储副主席为新成立的全球顾问委员会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡海湾银行（Singapore Gulf Bank）周二表示，已任命前美国联邦储备委员会副主席兰道尔-夸尔斯（Randal Quarles）为新成立的全球顾问委员会副主席，以支持这家数字贷款机构的国际发展战略。【原文：Singapore Gulf Bank said on Tuesday that it has appointed former U.S. Federal Reserve vice chair Randal Quarles as vice chairman of its newly formed global advisory board to support the digital lender's international growth strategy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/singapore-gulf-bank-names-ex-fed-reserve-vice-chair-newly-formed-global-advisory-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SW6XZPZ5AJPL3HVM4X2AUOQA7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[办公空间提供商 IWG 第一季度收入增长，维持全年预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[办公空间提供商 IWG 周二公布第一季度全系统收入增长 2%，并确认了其年度预期，称其核心业务并未受到美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收贸易关税的直接影响。【原文：Office space provider IWG posted a 2% rise in first-quarter system-wide revenue on Tuesday and affirmed its annual forecast, saying its core activities were not directly impacted by trade tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/office-space-provider-iwgs-first-quarter-revenue-grows-maintains-annual-forecast-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMLKNYESCZLXPCQHLUQO72P3QA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:36:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称欧盟将提议在 2027 年底前禁止进口俄罗斯天然气]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位欧盟官员告诉路透社记者，欧盟将于周二公布计划，在今年年底前禁止新的俄罗斯天然气交易，并在 2027 年底前逐步取消与莫斯科的现有合同。【原文：The European Union will publish plans on Tuesday to ban new Russian gas deals by the end of the year, and phase out existing contracts with Moscow by end-2027, three EU officials told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-propose-ban-russian-gas-imports-by-end-2027-sources-say-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7I2FJ7JYJOK7BLUMBPZG33ICU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:11:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DoorDash 将以 39 亿美元收购英国 Deliveroo]]></title><description><![CDATA[DoorDash 和 Deliveroo 两家公司周二表示，将以 29 亿英镑（约合 38.5 亿美元）的价格收购英国送餐公司 Deliveroo，这也是美国在线外卖平台进军国际市场计划的一部分。【原文：DoorDash will buy British meal delivery firm Deliveroo for 2.9 billion pounds ($3.85 billion), the companies said on Tuesday, as a part of the U.S. online delivery platform's plans to expand into international markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/doordash-acquire-uks-deliveroo-39-billion-deal-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPFQHUV6RVMVDK7IM5QRYTNYPU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:07:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雨果博斯公布第一季度收入高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国时尚集团 Hugo Boss 周二公布的季度收入好于预期，并确认了全年业绩预期。【原文：German fashion group Hugo Boss reported a better-than-expected quarterly revenue on Tuesday and confirmed its full-year forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hugo-boss-reports-q1-revenue-above-estimates-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLQVXQD45JKWFPMTUFUDEG7EAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 05:47:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飞利浦认为 2025 年关税将产生 2.5-3 亿欧元的净影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰医疗保健技术公司飞利浦周二表示，尽管有 "大量关税缓解措施"，但预计 2025 年关税将带来 2.5 亿至 3 亿欧元（2.83 亿至 3.4 亿美元）的净影响。【原文：Dutch healthcare technology company Philips expects a net impact from tariffs of between 250 and 300 million euros ($283 million-$340 million) in 2025 despite "substantial tariff mitigations", it said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/philips-sees-250-300-million-euros-net-impact-tariffs-2025-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOZXT4OQRNPIBOFKAP7ZGPJ2NE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 05:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zalando 超过第一季度收入预期，确认 2025 年目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲在线时尚零售商 Zalando 周二公布的第一季度财报显示，受新增客户和春夏季销售良好开端的提振，Zalando 第一季度营收强于预期，同时确认了 2025 年的业绩指导。【原文：European online fashion retailer Zalando reported first-quarter revenue on Tuesday that was stronger than expected, boosted by additional customers and a good start to spring and summer sales, while confirming its 2025 guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/zalando-reports-stronger-than-expected-first-quarter-revenue-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCDFT7HBYNMINEEHEQDJJWTCOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 05:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官认定非法垄断后，美国寻求分拆谷歌广告技术产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的一份法庭文件显示，美国司法部已建议 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌剥离其 AdX 广告市场和广告服务器 DFP，此前联邦法官认定该公司非法主导了两个在线广告技术市场。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice has proposed that Alphabet's Google divest its AdX advertising marketplace and ad server DFP, a court filing showed on Monday, after a federal judge found the company illegally dominated two online ad-tech markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-seeks-breakup-googles-ad-tech-products-after-judge-finds-illegal-monopoly-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJEI6KQ3IBPBRPP6OO7OJFFQOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美元抛售暂缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔-班纳吉（Ankur Banerjee）对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRN7Z3VZNFPIRCHBLAJY6BRKRQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将制定到 2027 年底停止进口俄罗斯天然气的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位欧盟官员告诉路透社记者，欧盟将于周二公布计划，在今年年底前禁止新的俄罗斯天然气交易，并在 2027 年底前逐步取消与莫斯科的现有合同。【原文：The European Union will publish plans on Tuesday to ban new Russian gas deals by the end of this year, and phase out existing contracts with Moscow by the end of 2027, three EU officials told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/eu-set-out-plan-phasing-out-final-russian-gas-supplies-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MJ42M4U3VMUNJURT5EOSSDF2M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBM 首席执行官争夺人工智能市场和更多美国投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[IBM 周二在拥挤的人工智能领域大展拳脚，兜售可以帮助客户为其关键业务应用管理人工智能代理舰队的工具。【原文：IBM on Tuesday made a play for more sales in the crowded artificial intelligence field, touting tools that could help customers manage a fleet of AI agents for their key business applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ibm-ceo-makes-play-ai-market-more-us-investment-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJRDF4A5GFMTBEXOL6H5Z2J6GA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾外长将访问德克萨斯州促进贸易关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾外长办公室周二表示，台湾外长将访问美国得克萨斯州，在一个关于人工智能（AI）的论坛上发表演讲，并促进商业和贸易关系，因为台北正寻求促进投资和抵御关税威胁。【原文：Taiwan's foreign minister will visit the U.S. state of Texas to speak at a forum on artificial intelligence (AI) and promote business and trade ties, his office said on Tuesday, as Taipei seeks to bolster investment and see off the threat of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-foreign-minister-visit-texas-boost-trade-ties-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPGRRHS5WROX5BDYBRIAJCKHXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[南华早报》报道：贸易战冲击香港货运业]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《南华早报》报道，香港的货运代理行业正受到中美贸易战的影响，从5月12日开始的一周内，从香港到北美西海岸的集装箱运力有41%被取消。【原文：Hong Kong's freight forwarding industry is reeling from the U.S.-China trade war with 41% of container capacity from the city to North America's west coast cancelled for the week starting May 12, the South China Morning Post reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hong-kongs-freight-forwarding-industry-hit-by-trade-war-scmp-reports-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GEDEMUY65ICNMU7D7V2TEWWDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市漂移，美元持稳，焦点转向亚洲货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，全球股市维持窄幅震荡，美元兑亚洲货币收复了近期的部分失地，原因是投资者再次对美国关税及其对经济增长的影响表示担忧。【原文：Global stocks held tight ranges on Tuesday and the dollar clawed back some of its recent losses against Asian counterparts as investors revived concerns about U.S. tariffs and their impact on economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKD2TM2ZHFNUZOOZZV2GV2LJ5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:46:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国假日消费增长，但贸易战影响服务业]]></title><description><![CDATA[五一小长假期间，中国游客的消费同比增长了 8%，达到 1,802.7 亿元人民币（合 249.2 亿美元），但仍低于疫情前的水平。【原文：Chinese travellers' spending rose 8% year-on-year during the May Day holiday to 180.27 billion yuan ($24.92 billion), but was still off pre-pandemic levels, while the country's services activity expanded at the slowest pace in seven months in April.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinese-tourists-made-314-million-domestic-trips-over-may-day-holiday-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZQULAYYCFLVNHTM3SELU4IVR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:59:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，中国服务业增速因关税影响创7个月新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二的一项私营部门调查显示，受美国关税带来的不确定性影响，4月份中国服务业活动增速为七个月来最慢，新订单增速较3月份有所放缓。【原文：China's services activity expanded at the slowest pace in seven months in April, with new orders growth slackening from March, weighed by uncertainty caused by U.S. tariffs, a private sector survey showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-services-growth-hits-7-month-low-tariffs-bite-caixin-pmi-shows-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MS524MFPEFL7REMJRUC6CPM2LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:54:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲同行大涨抑制美元走势]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，由于台湾货币史无前例地连续两天飙升，并波及其他地区同类货币，凸显了美元的脆弱性，美元走势举步维艰。【原文：The dollar struggled to make headway on Tuesday as an unprecedented two-day surge in its Taiwanese counterpart spilled over to other regional peers and highlighted the fragility of the U.S. currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-restrained-by-surge-asian-counterparts-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TQMZJO4OVMUVA4GRVXY4OFDYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:45:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>