<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:11:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:11:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创企业MiniMax集团在香港IPO募资6.19亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创企业MiniMax集团周四宣布，其香港首次公开募股最终定价为每股165港元，募集资金48.2亿港元（约合6.186亿美元）。【原文：Chinese artificial intelligence startup MiniMax Group said on Thursday it has set the final offer price for its Hong Kong initial public offering at HK$165 per share, raising HK$4.82 billion ($618.60 million).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-ai-startup-minimax-group-raises-619-million-hong-kong-ipo-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PJW4GX4K5IJNEAWSV4JM5J5CA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:53:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍金路伟任命米兰诉讼业务新合伙人]]></title><description><![CDATA[霍金路伟宣布，随着该律所全球范围内任命28名新合伙人和53名新顾问，其米兰诉讼部门的亚历山德罗·博雷洛已晋升为合伙人。【原文：Hogan Lovells said it had promoted Alessandro Borrello as partner in its litigation department in Milan as the law firm named 28 new partners and 53 new counsels globally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hogan-lovells-names-new-partner-litigation-milan-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUSO7JXYHFLORMIEA7BKN5K2JY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:48:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国国防部授予Mistral AI框架协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国国防部周四宣布，已与人工智能公司Mistral AI签订框架协议。【原文：France's Ministry of the Armed Forces has awarded a framework agreement to artificial intelligence company Mistral AI, it said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frances-armed-forces-ministry-awards-mistral-ai-framework-agreement-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y76VFE5V4VOQNJJVRXQ2OUNQZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:45:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国10月贸易赤字降至2009年以来最低水平，因进口减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国10月贸易逆差大幅收窄，降至2009年中期以来的最低水平，主要因进口减少。若这一趋势得以延续，贸易有望在第四季度再次为经济增长作出贡献。【原文：The U.S. trade deficit contracted sharply in October, hitting the lowest level since mid-2009 as imports declined, a trend that if sustained could see trade again adding to economic growth in the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-october-trade-deficit-lowest-since-2009-imports-decline-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KNL6XSZQVNABLTG2NA2BKICMQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员米兰表示，他预计今年将降息150个基点。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬·米兰周四表示，他预计今年将降息150个基点以提振美国劳动力市场。米兰的任期将于1月底结束。【原文：Stephen Miran, a Federal Reserve governor whose term ends at the end of January, said Thursday that he is looking for 150 basis points of interest-rate cuts this year to boost the U.S. labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-miran-says-hes-looking-rate-cut-150-basis-points-this-year-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYLI4N2NTRPKVHJGYEL6V7BWPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[赛亚公司估值达90亿美元，这家数据安全企业完成4亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据安全公司Cyera周四宣布完成4亿美元后期融资，其估值在短短一年多时间内翻了三倍，达到90亿美元，凸显出市场对人工智能驱动的数据保护工具需求激增。【原文：Data security firm Cyera said on Thursday it raised $400 million in a late-stage funding round, with its valuation tripling in little over a year to $9 billion, highlighting the surge in demand for AI-driven data protection tools.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/cyera-valued-9-billion-data-security-firm-raises-400-million-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5ZFF6ELVNJTXMU44GVJUFWJZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙重申其对华纳兄弟的收购要约优于奈飞的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙与天空舞蹈公司周四重申，其对华纳兄弟探索公司1084亿美元的收购要约优于竞争对手网飞，并补充称网飞要约核心部分——有线电视业务分拆的价值实际上毫无价值。【原文：Paramount Skydance reiterated that its $108.4 billion bid for Warner Bros Discovery was superior to rival Netflix on Thursday, adding that the value of the cable spinoff central to the Netflix offer is effectively worthless.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/paramount-sticks-30-per-share-bid-warner-bros-discovery-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZOLETALYRLBNNEJB6H7CBBJVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界经济论坛调查显示，2025年经商环境趋严]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界经济论坛周四发布的一项调查显示，由于全球在贸易、气候、技术和安全等议题上的合作恶化，2025年企业经营环境更为艰难。【原文：Companies found it harder to do business in 2025 due to a deterioration in global cooperation on issues including trade, climate, technology and security, a survey published by the World Economic Forum showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/davos/world-economic-forum-survey-shows-doing-business-got-tougher-2025-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZT6JOFSEOBINLKQ3PGA7OYAPYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度生产率增速创两年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国第三季度劳动生产率增速创两年新高，企业对人工智能的大规模投资有效抑制了劳动力成本。【原文：U.S. worker productivity grew at its fastest pace in two years in the third quarter as businesses invested heavily in artificial intelligence, depressing labor costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-third-quarter-productivity-rises-fastest-pace-two-years-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC4EQHR66BI2JCFTVW6G6QL6ME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税与库存短缺推高铝价，美国消费者面临创纪录成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铝消费者的支付价格已创历史新高，远超进口关税和运输成本应有的水平。全球供应紧张加剧了关税和美国库存低位的负面影响。【原文：Aluminium consumers in the United States are paying record high prices, significantly above the level import levies and transport costs would warrant, as tight supplies globally aggravate the impact of tariffs and low U.S. inventories.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tariffs-low-stocks-propel-aluminium-costs-records-us-consumers-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NPDY7YDBVPLBHL35OHFGJYWWQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周初请失业金人数小幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周美国初请失业救济人数小幅上升，表明2025年底裁员规模相对较小，但劳动力需求依然疲软。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits rose moderately last week, suggesting that layoffs were relatively low at the end of 2025, though demand for labor remained sluggish.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-marginally-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RATQ4FZBBZMQTOLBHKN4UFENHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:41:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈维利将收购合同软件公司Sirion的多数股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权公司Haveli Investments已同意对Sirion进行多数股权投资。Sirion是一家提供人工智能驱动的商业合同起草、存储和管理软件的公司。双方于周四宣布了这一消息。【原文：U.S. private equity firm Haveli Investments has agreed to make a majority investment in Sirion, which provides software that uses artificial intelligence to draft, store and manage business contracts, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/haveli-buy-majority-stake-contract-software-firm-sirion-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMHFEIXMZ5LETCSZW3LWR2QI2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥联储称美国12月失业率可能为4.6%]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联邦储备银行周四预估，美国12月失业率维持在4.6%不变。该数据表明劳动力市场仍陷于低招聘、低解雇的状态，可能为美联储未来进一步降息提供更多依据。【原文：The U.S. unemployment rate was unchanged at 4.6% in December, the Chicago Federal Reserve estimated on Thursday, a figure that suggests the labor market remained stuck in a low-hire, low-fire mode and may add to the case for more Fed interest rate cuts ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-december-jobless-rate-likely-46-chicago-fed-says-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NY73HWZIJNO7NFMPZHNHWKUHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:33:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[边疆航空母公司任命新任首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[边疆集团（Frontier Group）——边疆航空（Frontier Airlines）的母公司——周四宣布，董事会已任命詹姆斯·G·登普西（James G. Dempsey）为公司首席执行官。【原文：Frontier Group , parent company of Frontier Airlines, said on Thursday the board appointed James G. Dempsey as its Chief Executive Officer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/frontier-airlines-parent-company-appoints-new-ceo-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNUK6ICV4BPNHC4OAXXYKJS5GM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西12月年度通胀率可能进一步放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，巴西12月年度通胀率可能进一步放缓，连续第二个月跌破央行目标区间的上限。【原文：Brazil's annual inflation rate likely slowed further in December, a Reuters poll showed, falling further below the upper limit of the central bank's target range for a second month in a row.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-annual-inflation-rate-likely-slowed-further-december-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CD6RAOVLCRI4ZG5NNK4HRG52NI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:11:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国电力公司签署26.5亿美元燃料电池协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电力公司周四宣布，其子公司将以约26.5亿美元的价格收购固体氧化物燃料电池的大部分期权，此举是该公司开发和建设燃料电池发电设施计划的一部分。【原文：American Electric Power said on Thursday its unit will buy a substantial portion of its option for solid oxide fuel cells in a deal worth about $2.65 billion as part of its plans to develop and build a fuel cell power generation facility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/american-electric-power-signs-265-billion-deal-fuel-cells-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XIAFFJ43L5JRFHZ6TYDYZ4US2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:46:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，维托尔和托克正就委内瑞拉石油销售事宜与美国进行磋商]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，全球两大商品贸易商维托尔和托克正与美国总统特朗普政府就委内瑞拉石油的营销事宜进行磋商。【原文：Vitol and Trafigura, two of the world's largest commodity traders, are in talks with the administration of U.S. President Donald Trump about the marketing of Venezuelan oil, four sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/vitol-trafigura-talks-with-us-venezuelan-oil-sales-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VOMI7DFXZVIB3GV3VX54QXZ2RU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯利康任命内部人士里克·苏亚雷斯为美国生物制药部门负责人]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康周四任命公司内部人士里克·苏亚雷斯为美国生物制药部门负责人，领导这家制药商在其最大市场实施500亿美元的投资计划。【原文：AstraZeneca on Thursday appointed company insider Rick Suarez as the head of its U.S. biopharmaceuticals unit to lead the drugmaker's $50 billion investment plan in the company's largest market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-names-rick-suarez-head-us-biopharmaceuticals-unit-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CBBHKPDHZOZTL6MWBFD3NSRHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会已要求X公司将所有Grok文件保留至2026年底，发言人表示。]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会发言人周四表示，该机构已要求埃隆·马斯克旗下的社交媒体平台X保留其内置人工智能聊天机器人Grok的所有内部文件和数据，直至2026年底。【原文：The European Commission has ordered Elon Musk's social media site X to retain all internal documents and data relating to its built-in artificial intelligence chatbot, Grok, until the end of 2026, a commission spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/eu-commission-has-ordered-x-retain-all-grok-documents-until-end-2026-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y75EA6GH7JOU7MUR2DTPKBXVBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，蒙太奇科技计划于明年1月在香港进行最高达10亿美元的股票发售。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，中国半导体设计公司蒙特吉科技计划最早于本月在香港进行二次上市，拟发行8亿至10亿美元股票，这将进一步加剧香港融资市场的火热态势。【原文：Chinese semiconductor designer Montage Technology plans a second listing in Hong Kong via a $800 million to $1 billion share offering as soon as this month, said two people with knowledge of the matter, adding to the hectic pace of fundraising in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/montage-technology-plans-up-1-billion-hong-kong-share-sale-january-sources-say-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIZWW7T35NOWLJB4OKPKYEJQCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:01:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[晨间竞标：特朗普的可见之手]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STBEBJ5FXRPC7GAJUQU7LKA3XU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[若特朗普在最高法院败诉，进口商将为1500亿美元关税退税之争做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[公司高管、报关行和贸易律师正紧盯最高法院对特朗普总统全球性关税合法性的裁决——若裁决结果不利，进口商可能发起争夺战，要求美国政府退还已缴纳的关税，金额或达1500亿美元。【原文：Company executives, customs brokers and trade lawyers are bracing for a Supreme Court ruling on the legality of President Donald Trump's sweeping global tariffs - and a potential fight over obtaining perhaps $150 billion in refunds from the U.S. government for duties already paid by importers if he loses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/importers-brace-150-billion-tariff-refund-fight-if-trump-loses-supreme-court-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBETWI5QB5LZBNHSBSVYKNHJTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院审议特朗普紧急关税权限之际，市场风险持续攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院即将就特朗普总统动用紧急关税权力的裁决可能引发金融市场剧烈波动，尤其当法官们推翻关税决定时。【原文：A forthcoming U.S. Supreme Court decision on President Donald Trump's use of emergency tariff powers could jolt financial markets, especially if the justices strike down the tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/market-risk-mounts-supreme-court-weighs-trumps-emergency-tariff-powers-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VKINHB5OZRIE3NBHYRRM6Z2ULU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[制药商为欧洲定价之争做准备，此前特朗普在美国达成降价协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球制药商在2026年将面临一场争夺战，试图在欧洲为其处方药争取更高售价。此前在特朗普总统的压力下，这些企业去年已同意降低美国药价。【原文：Global drugmakers face a battle in 2026 to secure higher prices for their prescription medicines in Europe after agreeing to cut U.S. pricing last year under pressure from President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/drugmakers-brace-europe-pricing-fight-after-trumps-us-price-cut-deals-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5NKIXIFPROYLO4NC4B3ZPAJ5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货下跌；国防企业因特朗普预算计划上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四美国股指期货走低，因投资者在周五关键的非农就业数据公布前转为谨慎；与此同时，在特朗普总统呼吁制定1.5万亿美元军事预算后，国防类股逆势上扬。【原文：U.S. stock index futures moved lower on Thursday, as investors turned cautious in the run up to Friday's crucial nonfarm payrolls, while defense companies advanced after President Donald Trump called for a $1.5 trillion military budget.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-dip-defense-firms-climb-up-trump-budget-plans-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDCXEANR6VO7ZGVX5XDMC43LZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:40:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰银行称，金价可能在2026年上半年触及每盎司5000美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行周四表示，受地缘政治风险和债务攀升影响，金价可能在2026年上半年升至每盎司5000美元。【原文：Gold prices could rise to $5,000 an ounce in the first half of 2026 on geopolitical risks and rising debt, HSBC said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/gold-could-hit-5000-an-ounce-first-half-2026-says-hsbc-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQZYZDTSKFLWVOX5QASZ3CHSH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国西海岸喷气燃料对亚洲的溢价接近近两年来最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦金融交易所周四数据显示，美国西海岸即期喷气燃料对亚洲的溢价已升至近两年最高水平。炼油厂停产抑制了美国供应，而中国需求放缓则增加了该燃料在亚洲的供应量。【原文：The premium for prompt U.S. West Coast jet fuel to Asia has reached its widest in nearly two years, LSEG data showed on Thursday, as refinery outages curbed U.S. supply and slower Chinese demand increased the fuel's availability in Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-west-coast-jet-fuels-premium-asia-near-its-widest-nearly-two-years-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JK5AL6DFN5L4BOGCJU74EPRCJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:18:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构将于2月10日前就谷歌收购Wiz交易作出裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟反垄断监管机构将于2月10日前决定是否批准Alphabet以320亿美元收购网络安全公司Wiz的交易。这是该公司有史以来规模最大的并购案，欧盟委员会网站的文件显示。【原文：EU antitrust regulators will decide by February 10 whether to clear Alphabet's $32 billion acquisition of cybersecurity company Wiz, its largest deal ever, according to a filing on the European Commission website.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/eu-antitrust-regulators-decide-googles-wiz-deal-by-february-10-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPYGPPD3AJOT3JPDC4AKMSDWUU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:17:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车因倒车影像问题在美国召回逾41.3万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周四表示，瑞典汽车制造商沃尔沃汽车因后视摄像头存在问题，将在美国召回413,151辆汽车。【原文：Swedish automaker Volvo Cars is recalling 413,151 vehicles in the United States over an issue with the rearview camera, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/volvo-cars-recalls-over-413000-us-vehicles-due-rearview-camera-issue-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3G47EVONCBM3PFZV6CY5K4EPXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[笛卡尔公司称，受中国持续低迷影响，美国12月集装箱进口量下降5.9%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国集装箱进口量在12月下降5.9%，全年较2024年微降0.4%。供应链技术供应商笛卡尔系统集团周四表示，特朗普总统的关税政策导致中国货运量锐减，引发全球贸易动荡，并加剧了通胀担忧。【原文：U.S. container imports fell 5.9% in December to end the year down 0.4% from 2024 after President Donald Trump's tariff policies slashed shipments from China, shook up global trade and fueled inflation fears, supply chain technology provider Descartes Systems Group said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-container-imports-dropped-59-december-continued-china-slump-descartes-says-2026-01-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E42JKGIT3NLFNM6QHLJSODPSUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>