<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:35:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:35:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，波音 777X 将推迟到 2027 年面世]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，波音公司的 777X 喷气式飞机将于 2027 年初而不是明年开始商业飞行。【原文：Boeing's 777X jet is slated to start flying commercially in early 2027 instead of next year, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/boeing-777x-be-delayed-2027-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIUAVTLFBVIGDG6GJSHR7ALRSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:14:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院将重新审议航空公司收费决定]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家联邦上诉法院周四表示，将重新考虑其最近的裁定，即美国运输部有权制定航空公司费用披露规则。【原文：A federal appeals court on Thursday said it will reconsider its recent holding that the U.S. Department of Transportation has authority to write rules governing disclosures of airline fees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-appeals-court-reconsider-airline-fees-decision-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UREXMJAANVKYZKQHBLN6MRZDPQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会（NTSB）和美国联邦航空局（FAA）将调查亚马逊两架无人机坠毁事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国两家机构周四表示，他们将亚利桑那州托勒森市两架亚马逊 Prime Air 无人机撞上起重机的事件。【原文：Two U.S. agencies said Thursday they will the collision of two Amazon Prime Air delivery drones into a crane in Tolleson, Arizona.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ntsb-faa-probe-crashes-two-amazon-delivery-drones-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L65EBSXM6FIEJEKEQXC3K76WYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌与 NBC 环球达成协议防止 YouTube 内容停播]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌和康卡斯特旗下的 NBC 环球公司表示，他们已达成一项长期协议，将在 YouTube TV 上保留 NBC 的节目，包括 "周日橄榄球之夜 "和 "美国达人秀"。【原文：Alphabet's Google and Comcast-owned NBCUniversal said they had reached a long-term agreement to retain availability of NBC shows, including "Sunday Night Football" and "America's Got Talent", on YouTube TV.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/google-reaches-agreement-with-nbcuniversal-prevent-youtube-content-blackout-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYFY6XH6RBNAXEVA353GILE7SY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:47:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JBS 投资 7000 万美元重返巴拉圭，包括购买工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西肉类包装商 JBS 周四发表声明，宣布未来两年在巴拉圭投资 7000 万美元，其中包括收购一家鸡肉加工厂。【原文：Brazilian meatpacker JBS on Thursday announced investments of $70 million in Paraguay over the next two years, including the acquisition of a chicken processing plant, according to a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/jbs-returns-paraguay-with-70-million-investment-including-plant-purchase-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CR4UBXI2QZJLXIIC2ABYDJ2YDU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员呼吁波音公司结束长达八周的圣路易斯罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员伯尼-桑德斯（Bernie Sanders）在周三发出的一封信中敦促波音公司结束在圣路易斯地区长达八周的罢工。【原文：U.S. Senator Bernie Sanders urged Boeing in a letter sent on Wednesday to end the eight-week-long strike in the St. Louis area, where it produces fighters, munitions and other military aircraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/senators-call-boeing-end-eight-week-long-st-louis-strike-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GR2APOJ7QROPDPC2O4VQHCTORA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称巴西有望凭借扩张潜力领跑全球罗布斯塔咖啡种植业]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰拉博银行（Rabobank）周四发布的一份报告显示，受罗布斯塔咖啡对气候的适应能力和全球需求增长的推动，巴西正准备超越越南，成为世界上最大的罗布斯塔咖啡生产国。【原文：Brazil is positioning itself to overtake Vietnam as the world's largest robusta coffee producer, driven by the crop's climate resilience and growing global demand, according to a report by Dutch bank Rabobank released on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-poised-lead-global-robusta-coffee-farming-expansion-potential-report-says-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCIPWRT4GFK7NDKSNCVQCYDTQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡斯卡迪亚资本设立硅谷新中心，瞄准科技并购领域]]></title><description><![CDATA[精品投资银行卡斯卡迪亚资本（Cascadia Capital）的高管告诉路透社，该公司正在向科技并购领域扩张，因为它聘请了一位资深科技银行家，并准备在硅谷开设办事处。【原文：Boutique investment bank Cascadia Capital is expanding into technology M&amp;A as it hires a veteran technology banker and prepares to open a Silicon Valley office, the firm’s executives told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cascadia-capital-targets-tech-ma-with-new-silicon-valley-hub-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOOB3E6ZLVLOBFUG35BFNMRKCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）认为在关税提高的情况下全球通胀形势喜忧参半]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）发言人朱莉-科扎克（Julie Kozack）周四表示，IMF认为全球通胀形势喜忧参半，因为美国和其他提高关税国家的企业迄今已消化了大部分较高的关税，而中国等主要出口国的需求仍受到抑制。【原文：The International Monetary Fund sees a mixed inflation picture globally as companies in the U.S. and other tariff-raising countries have so far absorbed much of the higher duties, while demand remains suppressed in major exporting countries like China, IMF spokesperson Julie Kozack said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/imf-sees-mixed-global-inflation-picture-face-higher-tariffs-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3T7ZNYR2FFOKDH5MHXD4JNPHTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷债券摇摆不定，关注美国贝森特的支持承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）表示，即将在华盛顿举行的当面讨论将 "有意义地推进 "美国对阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱（Javier Milei）政府的财政支持承诺，但随后他在接受采访时又表示，美国 "不会向阿根廷投入资金"，此后阿根廷的国际美元债券在周四呈现震荡走势。【原文：Argentina's international dollar bonds zigzagged on Thursday after U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said upcoming in-person discussions in Washington would "meaningfully advance" the country's pledge of financial support for President Javier Milei's government, but later said in an interview that the U.S. is "not putting money into Argentina".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/argentinas-bonds-wobble-with-eyes-us-bessents-support-pledge-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFV5CWNP75NCTH3PABTHG57YUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026 年，Humana 将有 20% 的会员加入高评级医疗保险计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[Humana 周四表示，根据初步数据，该公司目前约有 20% 或 120 万会员参加了 2026 年被评为 4 星级及以上的医疗保险优势计划。【原文：Humana said on Thursday it has about 20%, or 1.2 million, of its members currently enrolled in Medicare Advantage plans rated 4 stars and above for 2026, based on preliminary data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/humana-sees-20-its-members-high-rated-medicare-plans-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5U3KSYKLQFMUJEYYWK6NKVSUXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:48:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果美联储降息削弱美国加元，加元将反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，由于美联储降息预期对美元构成压力，加元兑美元汇率将在未来一年走强，但美国-墨西哥-加拿大贸易协定的不确定前景可能使这一预测面临风险。【原文：The Canadian dollar is set to strengthen over the coming year against its U.S. counterpart as expected Federal Reserve interest rate cuts weigh on the greenback, but uncertain prospects for the United States-Mexico-Canada trade agreement could put that forecast at risk, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadian-dollar-set-rebound-if-fed-rate-cuts-weaken-us-counterpart-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6N3EWJOMRLSNCF7VDZMIDWQAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长维勒鲁瓦表示，扩大与受美国关税影响国家的联系可增强欧元的全球作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国央行行长表示，欧洲必须迅速采取行动，加强欧元的全球作用，因为这样做的机会之窗可能很快就会关闭，欧洲集团应寻求与受美国关税影响最大的国家加强联系，以帮助其实现这一目标。【原文：Europe must act fast to bolster the global role of the euro as the window of opportunity to do so may soon close, and the bloc should seek greater ties with nations most affected by U.S. tariffs to help it achieve that, the French central bank chief said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/expanded-ties-with-countries-hurt-by-us-tariffs-could-bolster-euros-global-role-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EEN6E53JFLJNJEQMFOBR3OT2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官裁定埃隆-马斯克不能将美国证券交易委员会对 Twitter 的诉讼移出华盛顿特区]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）未能说服华盛顿特区的一名联邦法官将美国证券交易委员会（Securities and Exchange Commission）对他迟迟未披露其在推特（Twitter）持股增加一事的诉讼移至德克萨斯州，此前他曾表示自己太忙，无法在美国首都为自己辩护。【原文：Elon Musk failed to persuade a Washington, D.C. federal judge to move a Securities and Exchange Commission lawsuit over his late disclosure of his growing Twitter stake to Texas, after saying he was too busy to defend himself in the nation's capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/elon-musk-cannot-move-secs-twitter-lawsuit-out-washington-dc-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WFUSEHKRTFPGVLCF35OLN3K6G4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席洛根称美国央行在降息问题上必须 "非常谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周四表示，美国央行上个月的降息行动适当地为劳动力市场的急剧恶化购买了一些保险，但需要对任何进一步的降息行动保持 "谨慎"，因为通胀率正在高于目标值，而且还在不断上升。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan on Thursday said the U.S. central bank appropriately took out some insurance against any sharp deterioration in the labor market with its interest-rate cut last month, but needs to be "cautious" with any further rate cuts because inflation is running above target and is heading upward.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-logan-says-us-central-bank-must-be-very-cautious-rate-cuts-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KMKPYGHPJ5ONPII36OZYPEFMYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西相信参议院将支持对富人征税以抵消中产阶级免税额]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三晚些时候，巴西下议院通过了一项扩大中产阶级所得税免税范围的法案，巴西政府表示有信心参议院将通过该法案。【原文：Brazil's government said it was confident the Senate would pass a bill expanding income tax exemptions for the middle class, after the measure cleared the Lower House late Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-confident-senate-will-back-taxing-wealthy-offset-middle-class-exemptions-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A2YE4AV4ORPN5JY3ZSU43Y5F5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:21:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：美国将支持大豆种植户应对中国大豆价格下跌，预计周二将有消息传出]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，鉴于中国拒绝购买大豆，联邦政府将支持美国农民，并将于周二发布公告。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Thursday the federal government would support American farmers in light of China's refusal to buy soybeans and that an announcement would be made on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-support-soybean-farmers-amid-china-lag-expect-news-tuesday-bessent-says-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXFTFIUIWJKZ7N3WTQKHO2AKWE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在电动汽车税收抵免到期前销量大增，交付量超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周四，特斯拉第三季度的交付量超过了分析师的预期，原因是在一项广受欢迎的税收减免政策到期之前，美国市场出现了抢购电动汽车的热潮，这足以抵消欧洲市场对特斯拉汽车需求的下滑。【原文：Tesla's third-quarter deliveries beat analysts' estimates on Thursday as a rush to buy EVs in the U.S. before the expiry of a popular tax credit more than offset slumping demand for its vehicles in Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-quarterly-deliveries-beat-analysts-estimates-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPTSPKXTB5P3FOFWTENGOCCIZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，阿玛尼曾就出售股份事宜与潜在买家接触]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士告诉路透社，阿玛尼的代表已经与一些潜在买家进行了非正式接触，以获得这家著名意大利时装集团的少数股份。【原文：Armani representatives have made informal approaches to some potential buyers for a minority stake in the renowned Italian fashion group, three sources with knowledge of the situation told Reuters, effectively starting a de-facto auctionfor a slice of one of the world's best-known fashion empires weeks after the designer's death.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/armani-approached-potential-buyers-over-stake-sale-sources-say-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ2AXREUUVLF3LLXEYKIAXC4QQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian 税收抵免到期前销售额大增，季度交付额超过预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian Automotive 公布的第三季度交付量激增近 32%，超过了分析师的预期，原因是越来越多的美国汽车买家赶在税收抵免到期前购买新型电动汽车。【原文：Rivian Automotive reported a nearly 32% surge in third-quarter deliveries, beating analysts' estimates, as more U.S. car buyers rushed to secure tax credits before their expiry by purchasing new electric vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-tops-quarterly-delivery-estimates-sales-jump-before-tax-credit-expiry-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPHLIHTUE5OWTA27K5SRRS3LRI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芝加哥联储：美国 9 月失业率可能稳定在 4.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[据芝加哥联邦储备银行周四公布的最新 "实时 "估计，9月份美国失业率可能为4.3%，与8月份持平。【原文：The U.S. unemployment rate likely was 4.3% in September, unchanged from August, according to a new "real-time" estimate from the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago published on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-unemployment-rate-likely-steady-43-september-chicago-fed-says-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJQ55FX6ZJPL3IOFMPZDNNS7QI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，中国的银行向沙特天然气项目提供贷款，而中国的基金却置身于贝莱德主导的交易之外]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的人士称，中国最大的国有银行正在向阿美石油公司的 Jafurah 天然气项目提供数十亿美元的贷款，尽管中国的基金放弃了投资该企业的机会。【原文：China’s biggest state banks are lending billions to Aramco’s Jafurah gas project, though its funds have passed on the opportunity to invest in the venture, three people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/chinas-banks-lend-saudi-gas-project-while-its-funds-sit-out-blackrock-led-deal-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PRH6PFLWNZME3MAHQ224MXC3X4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝马南非首席执行官呼吁与欧洲联合制定电动汽车电池战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[南非宝马汽车公司首席执行官表示，南非和欧洲应合作为电动汽车组件（如电池）建立替代 "价值链"，以减少对中国的依赖，他呼吁制定国家级战略。【原文：South Africa and Europe should collaborate on building an alternative "value chain" for electric vehicle components such as batteries, to reduce dependence on China, the CEO of BMW South Africa said, calling for a national-level strategy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bmw-south-africa-ceo-calls-joint-ev-battery-strategy-with-europe-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGPPMP3LBZOK5DYHNNFDT6ZQGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:10:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，埃里克-特朗普签约成为花旗集团客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的儿子埃里克-特朗普（Eric Trump）已签约成为花旗集团的客户，并设立了一个信托基金，持有其父亲的部分资金。【原文：Eric Trump, U.S President Donald Trump's son, has signed up as a client of Citigroup and established a trust that holds some of his father's money, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/eric-trump-signs-up-client-with-citigroup-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7MNIPOWQ5IGRFWUIEBYTAVXME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月裁员人数下降，但年初至今的计划招聘人数为 16 年来最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份报告称，9月份美国雇主宣布的裁员人数减少，但今年迄今为止的招聘计划却是2009年以来最低的，这进一步证明，由于政策和技术的进步，工人的供求量下降，劳动力市场停滞不前。【原文：U.S. employers announced fewer layoffs in September but hiring plans so far this year were the lowest since 2009, a report said on Thursday, adding to evidence of a labor market standstill as the demand and supply of workers fall because of policy and technology advances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/us-layoffs-fall-september-year-to-date-planned-hiring-lowest-16-years-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WFJMKVXFJJG7K7HO2ZCBMY6QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香槟制造商希望质量回升将使汽水重新受到追捧]]></title><description><![CDATA[香槟生产商周四表示，有利的天气提高了今年香槟葡萄的质量，在法国起泡葡萄酒需求减弱之际，这提供了一些好消息。【原文：Favourable weather has improved the quality of champagne grapes this year, producers said on Thursday, providing some good news at a time of fading demand for the French sparkling wine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/champagne-makers-hope-pick-up-quality-will-put-fizz-back-demand-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">THYXTDN2VNKXJIZ3ALTC524OX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[视频游戏发行商 EA 550 亿美元收购案聚焦游戏 IP 多样化]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子艺界公司（Electronic Arts）以创纪录的 550 亿美元杠杆收购沙特阿拉伯主权财富基金和其他两家公司，标志着电子游戏行业的一个转折点，因为各公司都希望通过媒体跨界利用知识产权。【原文：Electronic Arts' record $55-billion leveraged buyout by Saudi Arabia's sovereign wealth fund and two other firms marks a turning point in the videogame industry, as companies look to capitalize on intellectual property through media crossovers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/videogame-publisher-eas-55-billion-buyout-turns-spotlight-gaming-ip-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUZ7FOJUM5P2DJSB36K6L55NQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国监管机构要求标普中国 "整顿 "业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国证券监管机构已向 S&amp;P 的本地子公司发出警告，要求其 "整顿 "业务并加强质量控制，因为当局正在加大力度加强对评级行业的监管。【原文：China's securities regulator has issued a warning to S&amp;P's local subsidiary, telling it to "rectify" its operations and strengthen quality controls as authorities step up efforts to tighten oversight of the ratings industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/chinese-regulator-tells-sp-china-rectify-operations-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUXPXR2QTRKVPEOMYMAELYE6VY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西方石油公司将以 97 亿美元向伯克希尔公司出售 OxyChem 部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[西方石油公司（Occidental Petroleum）周四表示，将以 97 亿美元的价格向沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）出售其石化部门，这家美国石油和天然气生产商正寻求削减债务。【原文：Occidental Petroleum said on Thursday it would sell its petrochemical division to Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway for $9.7 billion, as the U.S. oil and gas producer looks to pare debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/occidental-sell-oxychem-unit-berkshire-97-billion-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRHDH5LK5FJEDEKARSEMWZP3GQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税抑制美国需求，智利葡萄酒在巴西蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[据出口数据和行业专家称，智利对其第一大市场巴西的葡萄酒出口正在蓬勃发展，帮助抵消了部分由于关税造成的对美国销售下降的影响。【原文：Chile's wine exports to its top market of Brazil are booming, helping to offset a decline in sales to United States partly due to tariffs, according to export data and industry experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chilean-wines-boom-brazil-tariffs-dampen-us-demand-2025-10-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZAIZDDOZYJKPBGCXGFMYFENM3M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>