<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 08:06:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 08:06:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[台湾与美国举行首次关税谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾政府周六表示，台湾官员周五与美国官员举行了首次关税谈判。【原文：Taiwanese officials held their first tariff talks with U.S. officials on Friday, the island's government said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-holds-first-tariff-talks-with-united-states-2025-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5CF2CCHN5JP3I3R254NDTUWHE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 03:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星和越南在特朗普关税战中的损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子董事长李在镕今年 7 月会见越南总理时，传达了一个简单的信息。【原文：When Samsung Electronics chairman Jay Y. Lee met Vietnam's prime minister in July, he had a simple message to convey.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/what-samsung-vietnam-stand-lose-trumps-tariff-war-2025-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NYZZ42CUFBI2XMVYGUP7BHYN7E</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 03:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》称，在与特朗普的加密货币公司进行交易谈判期间，Binance 试图遏制美国的监督]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》称，Binance 高管上个月会见了美国财政部官员，讨论了放松政府对该公司监管的问题，同时探讨了与唐纳德-特朗普总统的加密货币企业 World Liberty Financial 开展业务交易。【原文：Binance executives met U.S. Treasury officials last month and discussed loosening government oversight of the company, while exploring a business deal with President Donald Trump’s crypto venture, World Liberty Financial, the Wall Street Journal said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/binance-seeks-curb-us-oversight-while-deal-talks-with-trumps-crypto-company-wsj-2025-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KU2T3FOWP5NNXLR262GJXNKUTE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 01:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，Alphabet 和 Nvidia 投资 OpenAI 联合创始人 Sutskever 的 SSI 公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的消息人士称，Alphabet 和 Nvidia 已加入知名风险投资者的行列，支持由 OpenAI 前首席科学家伊利亚-苏茨克沃（Ilya Sutskever）联合创办的初创公司 Safe Superintelligence（SSI）。【原文：Alphabet and Nvidia have joined prominent venture capital investors to back Safe Superintelligence (SSI), a startup co-founded by OpenAI's former chief scientist Ilya Sutskever that has quickly risen to become one of the most valuable artificial intelligence startups months after its launch, a source familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/alphabet-nvidia-invest-openai-co-founder-sutskevers-ssi-source-says-2025-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKHHF5EIMBPFBO4FVGZTL2K5AY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 01:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一群前 OpenAI 员工支持马斯克停止 OpenAI 重组的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，十几名 OpenAI 前员工提交了一份法律简报，支持联合创始人埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）旨在保持 OpenAI 非营利地位的诉讼，这标志着有关这家人工智能公司未来的争议有了最新进展。【原文：A dozen former OpenAI employees filed a legal brief on Friday backing co-founder Elon Musk's lawsuit aimed at keeping the non-profit status of OpenAI, marking the latest development in the dispute over the future of the artificial intelligence firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/group-ex-openai-employees-back-musks-lawsuit-halt-openai-restructure-2025-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PIWM5KV63FOYVDKJ7GP55U42QQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 01:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国芯片制造商外包生产将逃避中国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[AMD 和 Nvidia 的股价分别上涨了 6% 和 2.6%，而高通公司则上涨了 1.1%。据中国芯片制造商信息论坛称，美国公司将能把其芯片产地归类为台湾。【原文：Shares of AMD and Nvidia - rose 6% and 2.6% respectively, while Qualcomm was up 1.1%. The US companies will be able to have their chip origin classified as Taiwan, according to an info forum for Chinese chipmakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-chipmakers-outsourcing-manufacturing-will-escape-chinas-tariffs-2025-04-11-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZVPLJLUDZMJXMZOPQHESF4NCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 23:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 将增补 Dina Powell McCormick 和 Patrick Collison 为董事会成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 社交媒体公司周五表示，前共和党官员迪娜-鲍威尔-麦考密克（Dina Powell McCormick）和金融科技公司 Stripe 首席执行官帕特里克-科里森（Patrick Collison）将加入公司董事会，自 4 月 15 日起生效。【原文：Meta Platforms will add former Republican official Dina Powell McCormick and fintech firm Stripe's CEO Patrick Collison to its board, effective April 15, the social media company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-add-dina-powell-mccormick-patrick-collison-board-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4X2WOXEHROYFPXR57H7QHVRII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 22:43:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，世界银行将宣布为阿根廷提供 120 亿美元的一揽子融资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士透露，世界银行准备在周五宣布向阿根廷提供 120 亿美元的一揽子融资计划，以补充国际货币基金组织预计批准的 200 亿美元阿根廷贷款协议。【原文：The World Bank is poised to announce a $12 billion financing package for Argentina on Friday, supplementing the International Monetary Fund's expected approval of a $20 billion Argentina loan deal, a source with knowledge of the plan said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/world-bank-announce-12-billion-financing-package-argentina-source-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7G57FMCUKJM5FN3P5ODX2GJKYA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 22:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，CVC 探讨以 750 亿美元竞购美国私人贷款机构 Golub Capital]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引几位知情人士的话报道称，欧洲私募股权公司 CVC 正在探讨以 750 亿美元收购私人信贷机构 Golub Capital。【原文：European private equity firm CVC is exploring a $75 billion deal for private credit lender Golub Capital , the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing several people familiar with the situation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/cvc-explores-75-billion-bid-us-private-lender-golub-capital-ft-reports-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FDCX6WHV5JJPBFN67LWY2YMSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 22:21:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，A16z 有意领投前 OpenAI 首席技术官的初创公司 Thinking Machines 的巨额融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位熟悉内情的消息人士透露，硅谷风险投资公司安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）正在与前 OpenAI 首席技术官米拉-穆拉蒂（Mira Murati）的初创公司进行谈判，以主导其早期阶段的大规模融资。【原文：Silicon Valley venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz is in talks to lead an outsized early stage funding round of former OpenAI chief technology officer Mira Murati's startup, according to four sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/a16z-eyes-leading-mega-round-former-openai-ctos-startup-thinking-machines-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6F7EXAAIVL5RIHWXOLX4NOEJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 22:16:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷放宽外汇管制，在国际货币基金组织（IMF）达成协议前进行重大政策调整]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷中央银行周五宣布将放松外汇市场管制，允许比索在1美元兑1000至1400比索的波动区间内自由波动。【原文：Argentina's central bank announced on Friday that it will ease its foreign exchange market controls, allowing the peso to freely fluctuate within a moving band of between 1,000 and 1,400 pesos per dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-eases-fx-controls-major-policy-shift-ahead-imf-deal-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K5AQR654UFNNFFFNKNGEOCGMIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 22:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 本周美国债券和美元大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6LM7KJQYURMXHKH42XKWTQ2BFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 20:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康要求医疗服务提供商偿还黑客贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两家医疗服务提供商周五透露，联合健康集团要求医疗服务提供商偿还去年其技术部门 Change Healthcare 遭到网络攻击后从该公司获得的贷款。【原文：UnitedHealth Group is demanding that healthcare providers repay the loans they received from the company after a cyberattack at its tech unit Change Healthcare last year, according to two providers on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-asks-healthcare-providers-hack-loan-repayments-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GOPOUMN6RKA7GKGAK4WDLTRWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 20:30:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总裁警告：油价下跌可能使 Ecopetrol 全年利润减少 28 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚国营石油公司 Ecopetrol 总裁周五警告说，油价下跌可能使该公司今年的利润减少高达 12 万亿比索（27.6 亿美元）。【原文：Lower oil prices could reduce Colombian state-run oil firm Ecopetrol's profits by up to 12 trillion pesos ($2.76 billion) this year, the company's president warned on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/lower-oil-prices-could-sink-ecopetrols-full-year-profits-by-28-billion-president-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KP4WDVWDXFP3FHXX3JLB36CFDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 19:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷大豆曾一度枯竭，如今却雨水充沛]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内专家表示，阿根廷农业中心地带的暴雨导致田地被淋湿，这引发了人们对大豆损失和 2024/25 年度大豆销售延迟的担忧，尽管即将到来的干燥天气应该会给生产者带来宽慰。【原文：Drenched Argentine fields due to heavy rains in the country's farm heartland are raising fears of soybean losses and delayed sales of the 2024/25 crop, although drier weather on the horizon should bring relief to producers, industry experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/land-use-biodiversity/argentina-soy-once-parched-now-has-too-much-rain-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P7VQEHE2AVM6ROEXZ6I3WBDNBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 19:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 资产波动扩大加剧关税困扰美股的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球市场的剧烈波动将使美国股市投资者在未来一周处于紧张状态，因为美元疲软和国债抛售加剧了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）推出全面关税政策后爆发的股市剧烈波动。【原文：Wild swings in global markets are poised to keep U.S. stock investors on edge in the coming week, as a weakening dollar and a selloff in Treasuries compound extreme equity volatility that erupted after President Donald Trump launched his sweeping tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-week-ahead-broadening-asset-volatility-intensifies-worries-tariff-tossed-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2OYE6Z2VJKC7MAS36AXGYLSJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[港口高管：特朗普贸易战可能打击美国最繁忙港口五月份的进口量]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶港执行董事吉恩-塞罗卡（Gene Seroka）周五表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对中国和其他贸易伙伴征收的关税不断升级，企业暂停订单，美国最繁忙海港的进口量最快可能在5月份出现下降。【原文：Imports to the busiest U.S. seaport could drop as soon as May, as companies pause orders in response to President Donald Trump's escalating tariffs on China and other trading partners, Port of Los Angeles Executive Director Gene Seroka said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-trade-war-could-hit-imports-busiest-us-port-may-port-executive-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7OKURPPHVPHNNE6VPGNMYVJ2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:51:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会就前先锋公司首席执行官请求修改埃克森公司命令一事征求公众意见]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周五表示，它正在就先锋自然资源公司（Pioneer Natural Resources）前首席执行官提交的一份请愿书征求公众意见，该请愿书要求委员会撤销一项涉及埃克森美孚公司（Exxon Mobil Corp）收购先锋公司的命令。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Friday that it was seeking public comment on a petition filed by the former CEO of Pioneer Natural Resources asking the commission to set aside an order involving Exxon Mobil Corp's acquisition of Pioneer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/ftc-seeks-public-comment-ex-pioneer-ceos-petition-modify-exxon-order-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GTHJJZF6GBJKTBXZP45EZ5GSNY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，美国消费者局驳回了对 Comerica 银行的起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局（U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau）周五驳回了对 Comerica 银行的诉讼，该机构此前曾指控该银行系统性地虐待了数百万主要是残疾人和老年人的客户。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau on Friday dismissed its lawsuit against Comerica Bank, after the agency previously accused the lender of systematically mistreating millions of mostly disabled and older customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-consumer-bureau-dismisses-case-against-comerica-bank-filing-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A6EEXOQA5JVRD3QMJKHT4ANU4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:45:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车将停止在安大略省生产电动面包车，以适应市场需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司和工会表示，由于销售缓慢，通用汽车将暂时停止其位于安大略省的装配厂的电动商用厢式车生产，直至2025年10月。据代表该厂工人的工会 Unifor 称，底特律汽车制造商将因此暂时裁员 1200 人。【原文：GM is temporarily halting production of its electric commercial van through October 2025 at its assembly plant in Ontario amid slow sales, the company and union said. The Detroit automaker is temporarily laying off 1,200 workers at the plant as a result, according to Unifor, the union representing workers at the plant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-halt-ev-van-production-ontario-adjust-market-demand-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CB4SZOQ7ZZON5LW5A33653PUBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:44:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫表示，特朗普对与中国达成协议持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫新闻秘书卡罗琳-利维特（Karoline Leavitt）周五表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对与中国达成贸易协议持乐观态度。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is optimistic about reaching a trade deal with China, White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt said on Friday, amid an escalating trade war between the two economic giants that has battered markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-optimistic-reaching-deal-with-china-white-house-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TY5Y7YLBN5IRHIXVAR6DKIWFEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:38:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部就 20 年期债券拍卖时间表和稳定币寻求交易商指导]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五表示，它正在寻求一级交易商对稳定币的指导，以及对 20 年期债券拍卖时间表的潜在改变，包括可能缩短何时发行期。【原文：The U.S. Treasury said on Friday it is seeking guidance from primary dealers on stablecoins as well as potential changes to the 20-year bond auction schedule, including possibly shortening the when-issued period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-treasury-seeks-dealer-guidance-20-year-bond-auction-schedule-stablecoins-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZL3VRQDA75IKZJ2LR56AEXM7AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯称美国石油钻井平台数量创 2023 年 6 月以来单周最大降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[能源服务公司贝克休斯（Baker Hughes）周五在其密切关注的报告中称，美国能源公司本周削减石油钻井平台的数量创下自2023年6月以来的单周之最，石油和天然气钻井平台总数连续第三周下降。【原文：U.S. energy firms this week cut oil rigs by the most in a week since June 2023, lowering the total oil and natural gas rig count for a third consecutive week, energy services firm Baker Hughes said in its closely followed report on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-oil-rig-count-falls-by-most-week-since-june-2023-baker-hughes-says-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOY256DJEVOWTORZQRPUJN2VRY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 17:15:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美关税战引导黄金突破每盎司 3,200 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，金价首次突破每盎司 3,200 美元大关，原因是美中贸易紧张局势加剧，令全球市场惶恐不安，促使投资者纷纷涌向被视为不确定性避风港的黄金。【原文：Gold prices vaulted over the $3,200-per-ounce mark for the first time on Friday, as intensifying U.S.-China trade tensions rattled global markets and drove investors into the metal seen as a refuge from uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-china-tariff-war-steers-gold-through-3200-per-ounce-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4XAGH6P5NILBENEAVBYYP3YXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国自行车手竞相在可能的关税之前购买哈雷摩托]]></title><description><![CDATA[在巴黎郊外的维利耶-马恩河畔哈雷戴维森经销店，销售十分火爆，法国摩托车手们认为，如果想在贸易战爆发前买到梦寐以求的美国摩托车，最好抓紧时间。【原文：Sales are brisk at the Villiers-Sur-Marne Harley-Davidson dealership outside Paris, where French bikers reckon they had better hurry if they want the American motorcycle of their dreams before trade war puts them out of reach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/french-bikers-race-buy-harleys-before-possible-tariffs-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZZ2DRPMFRIFLPUYEILNVTGF3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构拒绝重审亚马逊数据中心能源协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[政府文件显示，美国能源监管机构本周拒绝了一项重新审议决定的请求，该决定阻止了亚马逊的一个数据中心提高用电量，该数据中心直接与宾夕法尼亚州的塔伦能源公司（Talen Energy）核电站相连。【原文：U.S. energy regulators this week denied a request to reconsider a decision that blocked an Amazon data center, connected directly to a Talen Energy nuclear power plant in Pennsylvania, from ramping up its power use, government filings show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-regulators-deny-rehearing-co-located-amazon-data-center-energy-pact-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CS674XMQAZJTZPNS6XED4MHBEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府 6 个月信用违约掉期利差扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国政府债务的短期保险成本进一步攀升，显示出投资者的紧张情绪。【原文：The short-term cost of insuring exposure to U.S. government debt climbed further on Friday in a sign of investor nervousness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-government-6-month-credit-default-swap-spreads-widen-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6XQFWFOHSNOZTGDNHJWMCZKA7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:46:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度天然气公司 GAIL 寻求获得美国液化天然气公司 26% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度天然气公司（GAIL India Ltd）周五发布招标书，购买美国一个液化天然气项目最多 26% 的股份，同时达成一项为期 15 年的天然气进口协议，这有助于新德里努力缩小与华盛顿的贸易顺差。【原文：GAIL India Ltd issued a tender on Friday to buy an up to 26% stake in a liquefied natural gas project in the United States combined with a 15-year gas import deal, aiding New Delhi's efforts to narrow its trade surplus with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/indian-gas-firm-gail-seeks-26-stake-us-lng-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDPL5AQ2CNN6VLZ6A2HFQVIC7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，阿布扎比 ADNOC 考虑竞购 Aethon 的美国天然气资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道，阿布扎比国有石油公司 ADNOC 正在考虑竞购投资公司 Aethon Energy Management 的天然气资产，潜在价值约为 90 亿美元。【原文：Abu Dhabi state oil company ADNOC is considering a bid for natural gas assets of investment firm Aethon Energy Management that could potentially be worth about $9 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/abu-dhabis-adnoc-mulls-bid-aethons-us-natgas-assets-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RSEO42CXNOMDI2PVSCEYJV4Y4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔沃汽车公司首席执行官告诉《DN日报》，为避免关税，沃尔沃汽车公司可能需要长达两年的时间扩大在美国的生产规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞典沃尔沃汽车公司（Volvo Cars）首席执行官哈坎-萨缪尔森（Hakan Samuelsson）周五告诉《每日邮报》（Dagens Nyheter），该公司由中国汽车制造商吉利汽车（GEELY.UL）控股，将需要长达两年的时间来扩大其在美国的汽车生产，以避免被征收高额进口关税。【原文：Sweden's Volvo Cars , which is controlled by Chinese auto maker Geely (GEELY.UL), will need up to two years to expand its U.S. car production in order to avoid hefty import tariffs, CEO Hakan Samuelsson told daily Dagens Nyheter (DN) on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volvo-cars-may-take-up-two-years-expand-us-production-avoid-tariffs-ceo-tells-2025-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQ4CB3OILJKFNF3VGQWATVLRSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>