<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:16:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:16:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉反对向撤销马斯克薪酬的律师支付 56 亿美元赔偿金]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商埃隆-马斯克周五在法庭文件中争辩说，撤销埃隆-马斯克创纪录的特斯拉薪酬福利的法律团队只应得到他们要求的 56 亿美元律师费中的一小部分，因为他们的诉讼几乎没有给公司带来任何好处。【原文：The legal team that voided Elon Musk's record Tesla pay package deserves a tiny fraction of the $5.6 billion legal fee they requested because their lawsuit provided almost no benefit for the company, the electric automaker argued in court papers on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-objects-56-billion-payout-lawyers-who-voided-musks-pay-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCGI224IONKY3LF3TFA4SX42GU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威士卡和万事达卡在英国面临新的商户收费诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球支付处理商威士（Visa）和万事达（Mastercard）必须面对新一轮有关向零售商收费的诉讼，因为伦敦一家法庭周五裁定，代表商家提起的集体诉讼可以继续进行。【原文：Global payments processors Visa and Mastercard must face a new set of lawsuits over fees charged to retailers, after a London tribunal ruled on Friday that collective cases brought on behalf of merchants can proceed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/visa-mastercard-face-new-uk-lawsuits-over-merchant-fees-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFA4W7TJEZP3NL654G32RBVN5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 15:51:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[申银万国上市前的魅力攻势在欧洲遭遇障碍]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着在线快速时尚零售商 Shein 在英国加强上市前的魅力攻势，来自欧洲零售业和立法者的反击也越来越多。【原文：As online fast-fashion retailer Shein ramps up its pre-IPO charm offensive in Britain, pushback is growing too from Europe's retail industry and lawmakers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/sheins-pre-ipo-charm-offensive-hits-roadblocks-europe-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NO6MXU6DMBMVJMVAUJQY3XIOHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 15:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：为什么少数几家大型人工智能企业会让美国反垄断监管机构担忧？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国反垄断执法人员正在深入研究大科技公司在人工智能（AI）热潮中扮演的角色，探讨根深蒂固的参与者的商业行为是否扼杀了这一新兴领域的竞争。【原文：U.S. antitrust enforcers are digging into Big Tech's role in the artificial intelligence (AI) boom, exploring whether business practices by entrenched players stifle competition in the burgeoning space.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/why-few-big-ai-players-worry-us-antitrust-regulators-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RULBD37VN5JVBMLOOLA3RDWYAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 15:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 CNBC 报道，精神航空未考虑破产保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周五援引年度股东大会上的发言报道，精神航空首席执行官表示，该公司不考虑申请破产保护，并对其与捷蓝航空（JetBlue Airways JBLU.O）的交易失败后制定的计划感到 "鼓舞"。【原文：Spirit Airlines' CEO said the carrier is not considering a Chapter 11 bankruptcy and is "encouraged" by the plan it has in place after its deal with JetBlue Airways JBLU.O fell through, CNBC reported on Friday, citing remarks from an annual shareholder meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-not-considering-chapter-11-bankruptcy-cnbc-reports-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XGOU4PLUZNH7A4LD45IIGLFAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:31:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥投资者担心一边倒的投票可能威胁法治]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥执政党本周出人意料地取得了一边倒的胜利，这让投资者担心，该党可能会利用其职权，将长期以来一直让商界感到欣慰的对总统权力的一些制衡措施撇在一边。【原文：The Mexican governing party's unexpectedly lopsided victory this week has investors concerned that it may use its mandate to sweep aside some of the checks on presidential power which have long been a source of comfort to the business community.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/emerging/mexico-investors-worry-lopsided-vote-could-threaten-rule-law-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALUP5N7U25K25FUIETUWDZXXJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:02:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业市场保持强劲，美联储可能暂缓降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易员周五押注，美联储不太可能在 9 月份就开始降息，因为美国政府的一份报告显示，上个月雇主创造的就业岗位和支付的工资均高于预期。【原文：The Federal Reserve is far less likely to start cutting interest rates as soon as September, traders bet on Friday, after a U.S. government report showed employers created many more jobs and paid higher wages last month than expected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-may-wait-cut-rates-job-market-stays-strong-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2NSMMDTJRNKVMECNTYVWBDCYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 13:24:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[收益率下降，美国债券基金每周获得强劲资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 6 月 5 日的七天里，美国债券基金创下了四周以来最大的单周资金流入量，原因是经济数据疲软增强了美联储今年降息的预期，从而推动了国债价格的反弹。【原文：U.S. bond funds secured the largest weekly inflow in four weeks in the seven days to June 5, driven by a rally in treasury bond prices after softer economic data bolstered expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-bond-funds-gain-robust-weekly-inflow-yields-ease-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GBA4GB245K4FFKARN252SZL6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 13:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[让 GameStop 股价再次飙升的网络影响者基思-吉尔是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[基思-吉尔（Keith Gill），这位在网络上大放异彩的上班族，因看好 GameStop 而引发了零售交易狂潮，如今似乎正从默默无闻中重新崛起。【原文：Keith Gill, the office worker who shot to notoriety after his online personas and bullish bets on GameStop sparked a retail trading frenzy, appears to be re-emerging from obscurity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/who-is-keith-gill-online-influencer-sending-gamestop-shares-soaring-again-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XO7GX46J2VPZVDI3EIZKMCUV4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 13:15:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[反应令人 "瞠目结舌 "的美国 5 月非农就业人数跳增或令美联储宽松政策受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 5 月份的就业增长速度远超预期，这使得美联储有望暂缓开始降息。【原文：U.S. job growth accelerated far more than expected in May, keeping the Federal Reserve on track to hold off starting to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-eye-popping-may-us-payrolls-jump-may-set-back-fed-ease-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSH2PWVIIBIEPJXWKY7RZ76USU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[起亚汽车因起火风险在美国召回超过46万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局周五表示，由于前排电动座椅电机过热可能引发火灾，起亚美国公司将在美国召回462,869辆Telluride汽车。【原文：Kia America is recalling 462,869 Telluride vehicles in the U.S. due to a fire risk from overheating front power seat motor, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/kia-recall-over-460000-us-vehicles-due-fire-risk-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M45B6NIG4BLWNA3OIMYRTVR2BE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:53:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩资本将以 56 亿美元将 PowerSchool 私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[教育技术公司 PowerSchool Holdings 周五表示，该公司将被贝恩资本收购，交易估值 56 亿美元。【原文：Education technology company PowerSchool Holdings said on Friday it would be acquired by Bain Capital in a deal valuing the firm at $5.6 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-capital-take-powerschool-private-56-bln-deal-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIHQYULWAVNS3OLQPY4ZRC5QRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:17:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受降息押注影响，全球股票基金本周强劲流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至6月5日的七天里，全球投资者重返股票基金，原因是人们乐观地认为，随着通胀放缓，主要央行将降息，而美国债券收益率下降也提升了风险情绪。【原文：Global investors returned to equity funds in the seven days to June 5, powered by optimism that major central banks would cut interest rates as inflation moderated, while a drop in U.S. bond yields also lifted risk sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIHCRTU5XRITRMOPYHQKNVAL5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在中国升级车载导航软件，引入车道级引导功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周五在中国发布了车载导航系统的软件升级，引入了一些新功能，例如在地图上显示与实际道路车道相对应的车道标记。【原文：Tesla released a software upgrade for its in-car navigation system in China on Friday, introducing new features such as displaying lane markings on its maps that correspond to the actual lanes on the road.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-upgrades-in-car-navigation-software-china-introduces-lane-level-guidance-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VJNSPZMZJKVLCIFVJLA6RBZOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 11:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车希望为外部投资者准备充电业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车负责技术事务的董事会成员周五表示，大众汽车正在为其能源和充电部门寻求外部投资者做准备，并补充说，他对该部门未来可能的独立发展持开放态度。【原文：Volkswagen is preparing its energy and charging division for outside investors, the carmaker's board member in charge of technology said on Friday, adding he was open to different options for a possible standalone future for the unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-wants-prepare-charging-business-outside-investors-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSHNDXLPE5NMFJCLMRRDLAZ37M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 10:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop 季度销售额下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 周五公布的第一季度净销售额出现下滑，原因是顾客转而在网上购买视频游戏和收藏品，而该零售商主要依靠实体店。【原文：GameStop reported a decline in first-quarter net sales on Friday, as customers transition to buying video games and collectibles online, while the retailer largely relies on brick and mortar stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestop-posts-decline-quarterly-sales-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z32VSZ7QYBJOZNINLUFZ7OCQTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 10:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场为就业数据做好准备，期货持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国股指期货变化不大，投资者在等待一份重要的就业报告，以确认美国劳动力市场日益疲软意味着美联储有更大的降息空间。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were little changed on Friday, as investors awaited a crucial employment report for confirmation that growing slackness in the U.S. labor market meant the Federal Reserve has more room to reduce interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-steady-markets-brace-jobs-data-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXO5DNYYPFIDZF3DKOHC62V6CM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 10:14:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咆哮的凯蒂猫》预告直播，备忘录股世界屏息以待]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周五，网络影响者、2021 年 GameStop 股价令人瞠目的上涨背后的关键人物基思-吉尔（Keith Gill）将在 YouTube 上主持他三年来的首次直播，届时，Meme 股票交易者将目不转睛地盯着屏幕。【原文：Meme stock traders will be glued to their screens on Friday, when Keith Gill, online influencer and a key figure behind the eye-popping rally in shares of GameStop in 2021, is expected to host his first YouTube livestream in three years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/meme-stock-world-waits-with-bated-breath-roaring-kitty-teases-livestream-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H3YNLLAVGBMFFNDQFYQUF6DXJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 10:08:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻美国失业率低于 4%，中国进口放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-graphics-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3N2Q5WDX5OAHE3W63HVD2DWR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 10:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司在历史性机库交换中建造新的 A320neo 装配线]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司已开始在图卢兹建造一条新的 A320neo 系列飞机组装线，以取代效率较低的旧设备，并帮助从明年起加快生产速度。【原文：Airbus has started building a new A320neo-family assembly line in Toulouse to replace an older and less efficient facility and help speed up production from next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-builds-new-a320neo-assembly-line-historic-hangar-swap-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M7PA3PUATFOZ5G3OTNFQFVNLTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行决策者警告通胀挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）决策者周五警告说，将通胀率降至2%的最后阶段可能会特别艰难，但他们表示有信心政策正在按照预期发挥作用，有些决策者甚至认为2024年还有进一步放宽政策的空间。【原文：European Central Bank policymakers warned on Friday that the final stage of pushing inflation down to 2% could be especially hard but said they were confident that policy was working as intended, while some even saw room to ease policy further in 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecb-policymakers-warn-about-inflation-challenge-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YWPRW3535JOXHKNY4XRTOG2KE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:06:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[咆哮的凯蒂猫》计划重返 YouTube，GameStop 大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop 的股价在周五的盘前交易中飙升了 30% 以上，原因是投资者为 "Roaring Kitty "在 YouTube 上的回归做好了准备。"Roaring Kitty "是一位股票影响者，她最近在社交媒体上发布的帖子引发了所谓的 "备忘录 "类股票的上涨。【原文：GameStop's shares surged more than 30% in premarket trading on Friday as investors geared up for the YouTube return of "Roaring Kitty", the stock influencer whose recent social media posts have sparked a rally in so-called meme stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestop-surges-roaring-kitty-schedules-youtube-return-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PJTLF5OZE5IQNIBJ6LUN7MPIII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 08:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国议员呼吁将中国 CATL 和 Gotion 列入禁止进口名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，一群共和党议员称，中国电池公司 CATL 和 Gotion High Tech 应立即被列入禁止进口名单，他们指控这两家公司的供应链使用强迫劳动。【原文：Chinese battery companies CATL and Gotion High Tech should be added immediately to an import ban list, a group of Republican lawmakers said, alleging their supply chains use forced labor, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-lawmakers-call-add-chinas-catl-gotion-import-ban-list-wsj-reports-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFU7O7PSSFMF7C6QXIKS3G5IGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 06:28:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行称人工智能日益依赖大科技会带来新风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲银行业高管表示，人工智能的蓬勃发展将增加银行对美国大型科技公司的依赖，给银行业带来新的风险。【原文：The boom in artificial intelligence will increase banks' dependence on big U.S. tech firms, creating new risks for the industry, European banking executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/banks-say-growing-reliance-big-tech-ai-carries-new-risks-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXKDH4KOFZM3HJU3GRGHPXMVXE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 06:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称德国正考虑增购八架 F-35 喷气式战斗机]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位军方消息人士周五告诉路透社记者，德国正在考虑在已订购的35架F-35战斗机基础上，再购买8架美国国防巨头洛克希德-马丁公司生产的F-35战斗机。【原文：Germany is looking into buying eight additional F-35 fighter jets made by U.S. defence giant Lockheed Martin , a military source told Reuters on Friday, on top of the 35 jets it has ordered.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/germany-looking-into-buying-eight-additional-lockheed-f-35-jets-source-says-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQBYVYT5KFODHJEVLYC4GDWCX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:57:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于资本支出升级，日本第一季度国内生产总值降幅将小于首次报告：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，由于资本支出数据的上调，1-3月份日本经济的收缩速度可能略低于最初报告的速度，尽管风险继续给前景蒙上阴影。【原文：The Japanese economy likely contracted at a slightly slower pace than initially reported in January-March due to upgrades to capital spending figures, a Reuters poll showed on Friday, although risks continue to cloud the outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-q1-gdp-seen-falling-less-that-first-reported-capex-upgrade-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2TQXGZQTFOKTETPJITQ3PD5KY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:31:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯将在阿美石油公司股票发行中筹资 112 亿美元，定价在区间下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周五告诉路透社，沙特阿拉伯准备从石油巨头阿美石油公司（Aramco）股票的二次发行中筹集超过 112 亿美元的资金，此前定价为 27.25 里亚尔（7.27 美元），接近价格区间的下限。【原文：Saudi Arabia is poised to raise more than $11.2 billion from its secondary offering of oil giant Aramco's shares, after pricing them towards the lower end of a price range at 27.25 riyals ($7.27), people familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/saudi-arabia-poised-price-aramco-shares-727piece-sources-say-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVDHEXEHG5OIDP7CGACTQMOEGY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国人越来越挑剔，但仍在热销商品上消费]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者正在研究美国的信用卡消费模式，以确定哪些趋势（如果有的话）会在夏季给专业零售商带来推动力。【原文：Investors are scouring U.S. credit card spending patterns to size up which, if any, trends could give specialty retailers a boost in the summer months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/americans-are-getting-pickier-they-are-still-spending-hot-items-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDMTFQU2WRI4THIF4JJVL35I4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月就业增长有望保持温和步伐]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 5 月份的就业增长可能保持温和步伐，工资涨幅预计也将保持稳定，这将使美联储在利率问题上保持观望状态，但很可能会鼓励人们押注该央行今年至少会降低一次借贷成本。【原文：U.S. job growth likely maintained its moderate pace in May and wage gains were expected to hold steady, which would keep the Federal Reserve in wait-and-see mode on interest rates but likely encourage bets the central bank will lower borrowing costs at least once this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-growth-expected-remain-moderate-pace-may-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXE6J3N5QJO4JKPBGHDTHCL3YQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股票投资者发掘欧洲降息赢家]]></title><description><![CDATA[在欧洲中央银行（ECB）近五年来首次降息后，欧洲股票投资者正加紧寻找可能从借贷成本下降中受益的股票。【原文：Investors in European equities are stepping up their search for stocks that are likely to benefit from lower borrowing costs, after the European Central Bank's (ECB) first interest-rate cut in almost five years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/stock-investors-scout-out-europes-rate-cut-winners-2024-06-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N75DLSNOTNM5NMPTQ4AS3O4WDM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>