<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:06:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:06:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[前曼哈顿美国律师威廉姆斯离开保罗-魏斯律师事务所]]></title><description><![CDATA[前曼哈顿联邦检察官达米安-威廉姆斯（Damian Williams）已经离开了他于今年 1 月加入的保罗-魏斯律师事务所，成为这家华尔街律所自 3 月与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普达成协议取消针对该律所的行政命令以来，最新一位离职的合伙人。【原文：Former Manhattan U.S. Attorney Damian Williams has left Paul Weiss, the law firm he joined in January, becoming the latest partner to depart the Wall Street firm since it struck a deal with U.S. President Donald Trump in March to rescind an executive order against it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/former-manhattan-us-attorney-williams-leaves-law-firm-paul-weiss-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IFCNGEANZIC5MU6ESHSR762W4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[危机动摇，瑞士束缚了瑞银的全球梦想]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士周五宣布进行改革，使其最大的银行瑞银集团（UBS）更加安全，避免再次发生危机。【原文：Switzerland announced reforms on Friday to make its biggest bank UBS safer and avoid another crisis, hampering the global ambitions of a lender whose financial weight eclipses the country's economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/shaken-by-crises-switzerland-fetters-ubss-global-dream-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STAQWAX7FFKTRHT6PLJ6B3C3TE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管负担减轻，标普全球 "看好 "富国银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P Global周五表示，将富国银行的评级展望从 "稳定 "上调至 "积极"，这家美国银行本周早些时候被解除了1.95万亿美元的资产上限。【原文：S&amp;P Global upgraded its outlook on Wells Fargo to "positive" from "stable", the ratings provider said on Friday, after the U.S. bank was released from a $1.95 trillion asset cap earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/sp-global-positive-wells-fargo-regulatory-burden-lifts-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ETTDW6MO65LD5E7VHLL3FOTW5Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币公司双子座秘密申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币公司双子座（Gemini）周五表示，该公司已秘密申请在美国首次公开募股，这表明数字资产公司正采取行动，在市场条件改善的情况下利用投资者重新燃起的风险偏好。【原文：Crypto firm Gemini said on Friday it had confidentially filed for a U.S. initial public offering, as digital asset companies move to tap into renewed investor risk appetite amid improving market conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/crypto-firm-gemini-confidentially-files-us-ipo-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7B6KLGMZRFNC7H7D6ADKSYLTWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:04:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈克称今年仍有可能降息，因数据质量令人担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联储主席帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）在本月底即将退休之际表示，在经济形势非常不确定的情况下，今年仍有可能降息，同时他还对决策者用于决策的经济数据的质量表示担忧。【原文：As he heads toward retirement at month’s end, Philadelphia Federal Reserve President Patrick Harker says interest rate cuts remain a possibility this year amid a very uncertain economic landscape, as he also flagged worries about the quality of economic data policymakers use to make their decisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-harker-says-rate-cuts-this-year-still-possible-amid-data-quality-worries-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CN5AEGI5C5K7BFAGAELJBCUZIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，保时捷考虑将部分车型的组装工作转移到美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引知情人士的话报道称，保时捷正在考虑将其车型组装的某些部分转移到美国，以减轻唐纳德-特朗普总统对进口汽车征收关税的影响。【原文：Porsche is considering shifting certain parts of its model assembly to the U.S. to mitigate the impact President Donald Trump's tariffs on imported vehicles, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-mulls-shifting-parts-model-assembly-us-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHXWMQOSXFJKFCNSYZPUKYY5MY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称美国暂停向中国运输核电站部件的许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位熟悉内情的人士透露，美国最近几天暂停了核设备供应商向中国电厂出售核设备的许可证，因为中美两国正在进行一场破坏性的贸易战。【原文：The U.S. in recent days suspended licenses for nuclear equipment suppliers to sell to China's power plants, according to four people familiar with the matter, as the two countries engage in a damaging trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-suspends-licenses-ship-nuclear-plant-parts-china-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMDOND5Y25ORLJDTOI7D6MRJLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:22:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[稳定币公司 Circle 在纽约证券交易所上市后创下历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，稳定币发行商 Circle Internet 的股价攀升 41%，创下历史新高，延续了前一天在纽约证券交易所首次亮相便一鸣惊人的辉煌表现。【原文：Stablecoin issuer Circle Internet's shares climbed 41% to hit a record high on Friday, extending a stellar run after a blowout market debut on the New York Stock Exchange a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stablecoin-firm-circle-scales-record-high-after-blockbuster-nyse-listing-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGF5WIJ3W5MIHBKCFM4G45QUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在阿根廷，随着美元流出，储备增加停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据阿根廷中央银行的最新报告，在过去 11 个月中，阿根廷的资金净流出 123 亿美元，影响了中央银行积累储备的能力。【原文：The last eleven months have seen a net outflow of $12.3 billion from Argentina, affecting the central bank's ability to accumulate reserves, according to the bank's latest report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentina-reserves-build-up-stalls-dollars-exit-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2X3MXPU4T5NEPKKGNJCOEYI4UI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:49:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，X 为避免欧盟可能开出的罚单，大肆宣传蓝色勾选免责声明]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉内情的人士说，埃隆-马斯克的社交媒体公司 X 在其蓝色勾选标记上突出了一个免责声明，试图避免欧盟反垄断监管机构可能开出的巨额罚单。【原文：Elon Musk's social media company X has highlighted a disclaimer to its blue checkmark in an attempt to head off a possible hefty fine from EU antitrust regulators, a person familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/x-plays-up-blue-checkmark-disclaimer-stave-off-possible-eu-fine-source-says-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGXAGMJJ4RMRRBF35IZSMDNTPI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国向美国三大汽车制造商的供应商发放稀土许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的消息人士称，中国已向美国三大汽车制造商的稀土供应商发放了临时出口许可证，因为中国政府对稀土材料的出口限制已开始造成供应链中断。【原文：China has granted temporary export licenses to rare-earth suppliers of the top three U.S. automakers, two sources familiar with the matter said, as supply chain disruptions begin to surface from Beijing's export curbs on those materials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-issues-rare-earth-licenses-suppliers-top-3-us-automakers-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FK4ZV62VHFJ43BEHTHLZC3FMLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美欧数十亿美元的人工智能数据园区交易远未敲定]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士告诉路透社，由于对安全问题的持续担忧，一项利用美国技术在阿联酋建设全球最大数据中心之一的数十亿美元交易远未达成。【原文：A multi-billion dollar deal to build one of the world's largest data centre hubs in the United Arab Emirates with U.S. technology is far from being concluded due to persistent concerns around security, sources familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-uae-multi-billion-dollar-ai-data-campus-deal-far-finalised-sources-say-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7BUCHNMDVKALH5KMMFS5SWAFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:49:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储应将利率下调整整一个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）应将利率下调整整一个百分点，他同时重申了自己的观点，即美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在降低借贷成本方面过于迟缓。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve should cut interest rates by a full percentage point, President Donald Trump said on Friday as he reiterated his view that Fed Chair Jerome Powell has been too slow to lower borrowing costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-should-cut-interest-rate-by-full-point-trump-says-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7VLG3K46FOVPCR4QXSS3JUNAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉寻求阻止奥斯汀市政府公开机器人出租车试验记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉正试图阻止德克萨斯州奥斯汀市向路透社公开该电动汽车制造商本月计划在该市推出自动驾驶机器人出租车的相关记录。【原文：Tesla is trying to prevent the city of Austin, Texas, from releasing public records to Reuters involving the EV maker’s planned launch of self-driving robotaxis in the city this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-seeks-block-city-austin-releasing-records-robotaxi-trial-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56QJ7WIW4NNYVLPVFXUP2XWEHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼提出全面改革和放松银行监管的宏伟议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储新任最高监管官员制定了一项雄心勃勃的议程，重新审视和放宽众多银行规则和监督政策，她认为这些规则和政策已经变得繁琐和不必要。【原文：The Federal Reserve's new top regulatory official laid out an ambitious agenda for revisiting and easing numerous bank rules and oversight policies which she argued have become onerous and unnecessary.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-bowman-lays-out-ambitious-agenda-overhaul-ease-bank-oversight-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4BQMAEUOQ5O6TAU44DV7RHON5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度与美国的贸易谈判随着达成临时协议的最后期限临近而延长]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度政府消息人士称，印度和美国官员之间的贸易谈判已延长至下周，双方寻求就农业和汽车行业的关税削减达成共识，以期在7月9日的最后期限之前敲定一项临时协议。【原文：Trade talks between Indian and U.S. officials have been extended into next week as both sides seek consensus on tariff cuts in the farming and auto sectors, aiming to finalise an interim deal before a July 9 deadline, Indian government sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/india-us-trade-talks-extended-deadline-looms-interim-deal-say-sources-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHKYBIM7KRKDTNILXPPVXTCUEU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:46:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士要求瑞银增加 260 亿美元资本；股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政府周五对瑞银收购瑞士信贷后提出了更严格的规定，这可能会使瑞银多持有 260 亿美元的核心资本，从而证实了该银行对即将出台的新规定的一些最坏担心。【原文：The Swiss government on Friday proposed stricter rules for UBS following its takeover of Credit Suisse, which could make it hold $26 billion more in core capital, confirming some of the bank's worst fears about incoming new regulations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-faces-tough-new-swiss-banking-sector-rules-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PWMAL7IRJJG5CAQTTPZYQSJAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府：瑞银回购可能受资本新规影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政府周五表示，在提出瑞银应持有更高水平核心资本的建议后，瑞银未来可能会减少股票回购的次数。【原文：UBS may be able to carry out fewer share buy-backs in future following proposals that it should hold higher levels of core capital, the Swiss government said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-buybacks-may-be-hit-by-new-capital-rules-government-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IRG4QTNVSZOETLFVIXQ6YDFDGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国货币市场基金流入激增，因对关税持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至6月4日的一周里，美国货币市场基金出现了大量资金流入，原因是投资者对美国提高钢铁进口关税持谨慎态度，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与中国的贸易争端存在不确定性，以及周五将公布一份至关重要的就业报告，这些因素都刺激了投资者对更安全的投资渠道的需求。【原文：U.S. money market funds witnessed huge inflows in the week ended June 4 as investor caution over a rise in U.S. tariffs on steel imports, uncertainties over President Donald Trump's trade disputes with China and a crucial employment report on Friday, boosted demand for safer investment avenues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-money-market-fund-inflows-surge-caution-over-tariffs-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RNR47VYF2BJUPGUTJBCJYVRORE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点：美国 5 月就业人数增长放缓，失业率保持稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份美国就业增长放缓，失业率保持稳定，这可能会给美联储推迟恢复降息提供缓冲。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed in May, while the unemployment rate held steady, potentially giving the Federal Reserve a buffer to delay the resumption of interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-us-payrolls-growth-slows-may-unemployment-rate-steady-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHXT3TCYMRPF7JSC2S37F54FFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美官员在上海活动上就贸易问题互掐]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在上海一个美国商会举行的庆祝活动上，中美两国官员针锋相对，该商会呼吁中美两国为在华经营的美国企业提供更多的确定性。【原文：U.S. and Chinese officials traded barbs at a celebration held by a U.S. business chamber in Shanghai on Friday, as the chamber appealed to both countries to provide more certainty to American businesses operating in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-chinese-officials-exchange-barbs-shanghai-event-over-trade-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDRDUXFHEZNLVOZD6QTFOSC43Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:53:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国就业市场降温但未崩溃，美联储不急于降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在一份政府报告显示劳动力市场正在降温但远未崩溃之后，交易员们打赌美联储决策者没有什么理由急于降息。【原文：Federal Reserve policymakers has little reason to rush on rate cuts, traders bet Friday, after a government report showed the labor market is cooling but is far from collapsing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fed-seen-no-rush-cut-rates-us-job-market-cools-doesnt-crumble-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEJGMITXNVODNOLNXPRIZ4Z4XQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:51:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月就业增长放缓；失业率稳定在 4.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[在关税不确定性的影响下，美国 5 月份的就业增长放缓，失业率稳定在 4.2%，这有可能使美联储推迟一段时间恢复降息。【原文：U.S. job growth slowed in May amid headwinds from tariff uncertainty, while the unemployment rate held steady at 4.2%, potentially giving the Federal Reserve cover to delay resuming interest rate cuts for a while.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-job-growth-slows-may-unemployment-rate-steady-42-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YI2I47LBWZMPRIDWQQ6J2RIW5Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国法官警告：律师引用人工智能假案将面临制裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦高等法院周五警告说，使用人工智能引用不存在的案例的律师可能会被认定为藐视法庭，甚至面临刑事指控，这是生成式人工智能将律师引入歧途的最新例证。【原文：Lawyers who use artificial intelligence to cite non-existent cases can be held in contempt of court or even face criminal charges, London's High Court warned on Friday, in the latest example of generative AI leading lawyers astray.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/lawyers-face-sanctions-citing-fake-cases-with-ai-warns-uk-judge-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TX6G73LVZKWRKEVDMHOMJBUSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:18:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行决策者讨论通胀过低风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（European Central Bank）的政策制定者们周五欢呼战胜了通胀失控的局面，尽管有些人警告说，现在的通胀率有可能过低，这让人再次回忆起 "大流行病 "爆发前十年的低迷物价增长势头。【原文：European Central Bank policymakers hailed victory over runaway inflation on Friday even as some warned that it was now at risk of going too low, rekindling memories of anaemic price growth in the pre-pandemic decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ecb-policymakers-debate-risk-inflation-going-too-low-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73U6XF42FNIGHPEBQOCW4SY2BY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:14:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，马斯克的 xAI 公司预计到 2029 年年收入将超过 130 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，根据这家人工智能初创公司的银行家摩根士丹利披露的数据，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的xAI公司预计到2029年的年收入将超过130亿美元。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk's xAI expects to generate more than $13 billion in annual earnings by 2029, according to numbers revealed by the artificial intelligence startup's banker Morgan Stanley , Bloomberg News reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/musks-xai-expects-annual-earnings-over-13-billion-by-2029-bloomberg-reports-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJKPO5NIIFIIJKCPYOVSNPBIUE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国将终止对散户投资者购买加密货币交易所交易票据的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融监管机构将取消对消费者购买加密货币交易所交易票据（ETNs）的禁令，放弃此前希望不让散户投资者购买的立场。【原文：Britain's financial regulator is to remove a ban on consumers buying crypto exchange-traded notes (ETNs), ditching its previous position of wanting to keep them out of the hands of retail investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/embargoed-uk-end-ban-retail-investors-buying-crypto-exchange-traded-notes-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RXUTXBBWV5JXTE2XKLZ7XIC3XM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易政策担忧导致美国股票基金资金流出，欧洲央行降息前欧洲股票基金吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至6月4日，美国股票基金连续第三周出现资金外流，原因是对美国贸易政策不确定性的担忧挥之不去，而投资者在周五即将公布的关键就业报告前保持谨慎。【原文：U.S. equity funds saw outflows for a third straight week through June 4, as concerns lingered over uncertainty surrounding U.S. trade policies, while investors remained cautious ahead of a key jobs report due Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XJBA5WOTXZIKJP65QG5DAXBVVE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标特朗普与马斯克的争吵硝烟弥漫]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RR3GCIFWIZJ7JMYG7DFXJUSMFA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:17:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲杯门票销售大增，曼联提高盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[曼联周五上调了年度核心利润预期，原因是俱乐部在欧洲杯上的强劲表现带动了门票销售和转播收入。【原文：Manchester United raised their annual core profit forecast on Friday as the club's strong performance in the Europa League drove ticket sales and broadcast revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/manchester-united-boost-profit-forecast-after-europa-league-run-lifts-ticket-2025-06-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMZVMEUDFJPI5OOJVDJ5D4DB24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:11:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>