<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:11:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:11:40 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[雷诺第二季度销量持平，面包车需求下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，雷诺公布了第二季度销售量零增长的报告，此前欧洲对货车需求的骤降抵消了乘用车的增长。【原文：Renault reported zero growth in second-quarter sales volume on Wednesday, after a plunge in demand for vans in Europe offset growth in passenger cars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/renault-second-quarter-sales-volumes-flat-drop-demand-vans-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMIOYCUS55NCJCO35LPMOACEH4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:02:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Equinor 第二季度核心利润因油价下跌而如期下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[Equinor 公司周三发布的财报显示，由于油价下跌超过了天然气价格的上涨，该公司第二季度利润较上年同期下降了 13%，符合预期。【原文：Equinor's second-quarter profit fell as expected by 13% from a year earlier, its earnings report showed on Wednesday, as declining oil prices outweighed a rise in the price of gas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/equinor-q2-core-profit-drops-expected-lower-oil-price-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVZRZCY6KBJW5MLEDPBS6IQBE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:48:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标日本意外达成贸易协定让其他国家燃起希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DW433X4DGNPMDKGWV2XJE5VMHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾计划通过人工智能项目推动经济增长 5100 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾计划推出 "十大人工智能基础设施项目"，旨在到 2040 年创造超过 15 万亿新台币（约合 5100 亿美元）的经济价值，努力成为人工智能领域的全球领导者。【原文：Taiwan plans to launch its "Ten Major AI Infrastructure Projects" initiative, aimed at generating more than T$15 trillion ($510 billion) in economic value by 2040 as it strives to become a global leader in artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-plans-ai-projects-boost-economy-by-510-billion-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARQX63MJIJJSDBVL7H3UIDA7CY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:16:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》报道：麦肯锡禁止中国业务参与生成式人工智能咨询工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周三援引两位知情人士的话报道称，麦肯锡已停止在中国开展与人工智能相关的咨询工作。【原文：McKinsey has stopped its China business from undertaking consultancy work related to generative artificial intelligence, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday, citing two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/mckinsey-bars-china-business-generative-ai-consultancy-work-ft-reports-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKVAGELCLVMLNEQWR5IQ3ULDWY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:12:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本承诺在免关税配额内进口更多美国大米]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本首相石破茂（Shigeru Ishiba）周三表示，日本将从美国进口更多大米，但不超过现有的免关税配额，并强调东京在达成双边贸易协议时成功地保护了农业部门。【原文：Japan will import more rice from the United States but within the existing tariff-free quota, Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba said on Wednesday, stressing Tokyo's success in protecting the agricultural sector in agreeing a bilateral trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-vows-more-us-rice-imports-within-tariff-free-quota-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3BJ2VZU4BI7VCQZET6WS25WCI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚行称美国关税和贸易紧张局势将减缓亚太发展中国家的经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲开发银行（Asian Development Bank）周三在一份报告中称，美国提高关税和贸易的不确定性恶化了亚太地区发展中国家的经济前景，该行同时下调了亚太地区今明两年的经济增长预期。【原文：Higher U.S. tariffs and trade uncertainty have worsened the economic outlook for developing Asia and the Pacific, the Asian Development Bank said in a report on Wednesday as it lowered its growth forecasts for the region for this year and next.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/us-tariffs-trade-tensions-slow-growth-developing-asia-pacific-adb-says-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWCCRW5R55M7RJP7PRCASXNN5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行首席执行官称，他只需应对媒体对投资者投诉的报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行首席执行官周三表示，他只需 "熬过 "媒体对其管理风格和在客户活动中饮酒的投资者投诉的报道。【原文：National Australia Bank's chief executive said on Wednesday that he just had to "get through" media coverage of investor complaints about his management style and drinking at customer events.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/national-australia-bank-ceo-says-he-just-has-weather-media-coverage-investor-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3N7WI4BQ65I6ZGQITB5RUEX3A4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:22:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：摩根士丹利的客户筛选面临美国金融业监管局更深入的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周二援引知情人士的话报道，美国金融业监管局（FINRA）正在就摩根士丹利如何筛查客户的洗钱风险展开调查。【原文：The U.S. Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA) is investigating Morgan Stanley over how the firm screened clients for money-laundering risks, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/morgan-stanleys-client-screening-faces-deeper-finra-probe-wsj-reports-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5VHDI2XTLRPO3IG6HKLJRX7JZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:17:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安宏资本支持的 NIQ 在美国首次公开募股中融资 10.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由投资公司Advent International和KKR支持的消费者洞察公司NIQ Global [NIQ.N]周二表示，它在美国的首次公开募股中筹集了10.5亿美元。【原文：Consumer insights company NIQ Global [NIQ.N], backed by investment firms Advent International and KKR , said on Tuesday it had raised $1.05 billion in its initial public offering in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/advent-backed-niq-raises-105-billion-us-ipo-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDNGEE43OBIJNJQIVN63HJCX5A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:05:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行内田警告贸易不确定性将给经济带来下行风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行副行长内田伸一周三表示，由于贸易政策及其对国内外经济增长的影响存在 "极高 "的不确定性，经济活动和物价面临的风险偏向下行。【原文：Bank of Japan Deputy Governor Shinichi Uchida said on Wednesday that risks to economic activity and prices were skewed to the downside due to "extremely high" uncertainty over trade policy and its effect on domestic and overseas growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bojs-uchida-warns-downside-risks-economy-trade-uncertainty-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SL5LJIQMWFKKVJDUMB3S5UXGOQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 NHK 报道，日本和美国同意维持目前对钢铁和铝征收 50%关税的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[据日本公共广播公司 NHK 周三报道，作为双边贸易协议的一部分，日本和美国同意维持目前对钢铁和铝征收 50%关税的做法。【原文：Japan and the United States agreed to keep the current 50% tariff on steel and aluminium as part of the bilateral trade deal, Japanese public broadcaster NHK reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-us-agree-keep-current-50-tariff-steel-aluminium-nhk-reports-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RARZJIKQUZLNLIL2FHYKQ7WEVU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油因日本贸易协议和美国库存显示需求强劲而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价在连续三个交易日下跌后于周三早盘企稳，原因是美国与日本达成的贸易协议表明在关税问题上取得了进展，而且一项民意调查显示上周美国原油库存下降，表明需求强劲。【原文：Oil prices steadied in early trading on Wednesday after falling for three consecutive sessions as a U.S. trade deal with Japan signaled progress on tariffs and a poll showed U.S. crude stockpiles fell last week, indicating stronger demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rises-japan-trade-deal-stronger-demand-indicated-by-us-inventories-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMMZYI2YHZNNVB2OGU6SRPK7RQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国官员飞往华盛顿，将仔细审查美日贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国工业部长周三表示，首尔将仔细研究美日贸易协议的条款，在华盛顿举行关键贸易谈判之前，有望在能源和工业领域加强合作。【原文：Seoul will take a close look at the terms of a U.S.-Japan trade deal, South Korea's industry minister said on Wednesday, holding out the prospect of greater cooperation in the energy and industrial sectors ahead of key trade talks in Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-scrutinise-us-japan-trade-deal-officials-fly-washington-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPLTO3IC2JNANJUGHMGRUVD7YM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:42:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美日关税协议的主要事实]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）和日本首相石破茂（Shigeru Ishiba）周三表示，他们已达成一项贸易协议，其中包括对从日本进口的商品征收15%的关税。以下是我们目前了解到的情况。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump and Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba on Wednesday said they had struck a trade deal that will include a 15% tariff on imports from Japan. Here's what we know so far.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/key-facts-us-japan-tariff-deal-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XAC4FMGVRLATCB27QOD7F45RU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[底特律三大汽车制造商对日本贸易协议表示担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表通用汽车、福特汽车和克莱斯勒母公司施泰兰特的一个团体周二对一项贸易协议表示担忧，因为该协议可能将从日本进口汽车的关税削减至 15%，同时将从加拿大和墨西哥进口汽车的关税维持在 25%。【原文：A group representing General Motors Ford and Chrysler-parent Stellantis on Tuesday raised concerns about a trade deal that could cut tariffs on auto imports from Japan to 15% while leaving tariffs on imports from Canada and Mexico at 25%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/detroit-three-automakers-raise-concerns-about-japan-trade-deal-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEG67ZTMNROA7BETGDTDOKE3GA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴推出开源人工智能编码模型，被誉为迄今为止最先进的人工智能模型]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴集团周三宣布推出 Qwen3-Coder，这是一个用于软件开发的开源人工智能模型，中国电子商务巨头称其为迄今为止最先进的编码工具。【原文：Alibaba Group announced on Wednesday the launch of Qwen3-Coder, an open-source artificial intelligence model for software development that the Chinese e-commerce giant described as its most advanced coding tool to date.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/alibaba-launches-open-source-ai-coding-model-touted-its-most-advanced-date-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WXUXXLM6CZKXNB2DJNLD2YAK6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，美国核武器机构因微软 SharePoint 遭黑客入侵]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道称，美国国家核安全局是微软 SharePoint 文档管理软件被黑客入侵的对象之一。【原文：U.S. National Nuclear Security Administration was among those breached by a hack of Microsoft's SharePoint document management software, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a person with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-nuclear-weapons-agency-breached-microsoft-sharepoint-hack-bloomberg-news-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JN4MMQZQNVOHTLXERSPOJCWISI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本和韩国汽车制造商股价因东京贸易协定而大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布与东京达成贸易协议后，日本和韩国汽车制造商的股价周三大涨，消息人士称，该协议将包括把日本汽车进口关税降至15%，此举激起了人们对首尔也将达成类似协议的乐观情绪。【原文：Shares of Japanese and South Korean automakers surged on Wednesday after U.S. President Donald Trump announced a trade deal with Tokyo that sources said would include reducing a tariff on Japanese auto imports to 15%, a move that stoked optimism about a similar deal for Seoul.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shares-japanese-south-korean-automakers-surge-tokyo-trade-deal-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WW4EAU6B7FK5ZMFQTVVWIUC7JU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布日本贸易协定，日经指数反弹提振亚洲股市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布与日本达成贸易协议并燃起对未来更多贸易协议的希望之后，日本股市领涨亚洲股市，抵消了美国财报喜忧参半的影响。【原文：Japanese shares led an Asian share market rally on Wednesday after U.S. President Donald Trump announced a trade deal with Japan and fuelled hopes of more to come, offsetting mixed U.S. earnings that highlighted the drags from higher tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGG6IVFLHBJ65LJG625G5HC43Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[淡水河谷铁矿石产量增长 4%，主要矿山第二季度产量创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西矿业公司淡水河谷周二发布报告称，该公司第二季度铁矿石产量为 8360 万公吨，同比增长 3.7%。【原文：Brazilian miner Vale produced 83.6 million metric tons of iron ore in the second quarter, up 3.7% from a year earlier, the company reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/vales-iron-ore-output-up-4-with-record-q2-key-mine-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGQTPR6NQNLMXJY5VOM5X4N7KE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 对美国与日本达成贸易协议的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普表示，美国和日本已达成贸易协议，其中包括将对从日本进口的美国产品征收 15%的关税。【原文：President Donald Trump said the U.S. and Japan had struck a trade deal that includes a 15% tariff that will be levied on U.S. imports from the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/view-reaction-us-trade-deal-with-japan-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C2RGRYGTQNMU3JYSJ7JV7BL2NI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布与日本达成贸易协议，包括征收 15%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二宣布了一项与日本的贸易协议，他说该协议将导致日本向美国投资5500亿美元，并支付15%的对等关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday announced a trade deal with Japan that he said will result in Japan investing $550 billion into the United States and paying a 15% reciprocal tariff.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-announces-trade-deal-with-japan-including-15-tariff-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLFFWYJMRVIL3LZQT46MYOY4P4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 23:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[朝日新闻》报道：日本最高关税谈判代表在白宫会见特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《朝日新闻》周三报道，日本最高关税谈判代表赤泽亮世周二在白宫会见了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普。【原文：Japan's top tariff negotiator, Ryosei Akazawa, met with U.S. President Donald Trump at the White House on Tuesday, the Asahi newspaper reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-top-tariff-negotiator-met-with-trump-white-house-asahi-reports-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23MBADBPYVIB5PGMDTAUORW44A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 23:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各国央行应为气候对劳动力市场的冲击做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦经济学院（London School of Economics）周三发表的一份报告警告说，除非各国央行彻底改革其货币政策方法，否则它们有可能被气候对全球劳动力市场造成的冲击打懵。【原文：Central banks risk being blindsided by climate-driven shocks to global labour markets unless they overhaul their approach to monetary policy, a report published on Wednesday by the London School of Economics warned.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/cop/central-banks-told-prepare-climate-shock-labour-market-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IM4FJFNM2VKQ5JJD4U5I3PC7XU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 23:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[T-Mobile 的 5G 将助力 Comcast 和 Charter 的无线业务计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[康卡斯特和 Charter Communications 周二表示，他们将成立一家移动虚拟网络运营商 (MVNO)，使用 T-Mobile 的 5G 网络为无线企业客户提供服务，计划于明年推出。【原文：Comcast and Charter Communications said on Tuesday they would establish a mobile virtual network operator (MVNO) that will use T-Mobile's 5G network to serve wireless business customers, with plans to launch next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/t-mobiles-5g-power-comcast-charter-wireless-business-plans-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OAGEGUTS6VPWNAWFU3AHRDQQ3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司向工会成员发出合同要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二向在圣路易斯地区组装战斗机的工会成员发出了一份合同要约。【原文：Boeing sent a contract offer on Tuesday to union members who assemble its fighter jets in the St. Louis area.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/boeing-sends-contract-offer-union-members-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCTWORW5HZKPVNGWB2ULIRE37Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Enphase Energy 预计第三季度收入低于预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Enphase Energy周二预测第三季度营收低于华尔街预期，并表示唐纳德-特朗普总统的进口关税影响了其毛利率，导致这家太阳能逆变器制造商盘后股价下跌超过7%。【原文：Enphase Energy forecast third-quarter revenue below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday and said President Donald Trump's import tariffs had impacted its gross margin, sending the solar inverter maker's shares down more than 7% after hours.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/enphase-energy-forecasts-third-quarter-revenue-below-estimates-shares-fall-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2IMQ3PEVAVMBFENS6N7ZCGTUQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:53:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊将收购专注于人工智能可穿戴设备的初创公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊已达成收购旧金山 Bee 公司的协议，该公司是一家初创企业，生产一种人工智能手环，用于监听和转录对话。【原文：Amazon has reached a deal to buy San Francisco-based Bee, a startup making an artificial intelligence-enabled bracelet to listen in on and transcribe conversations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-buy-startup-focused-ai-wearables-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KS2NB2IIVVN4RKZAEXYNXVXJ2Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:41:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普官员称印尼将在美国贸易协议中削减关税和非关税壁垒]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼和美国周二表示，印尼已同意取消对99%以上的美国商品征收的关税，并取消美国公司面临的所有非关税壁垒，而美国将把印尼产品的威胁关税从32%降至19%。【原文：Indonesia has agreed to eliminate tariffs on more than 99% of U.S. goods and scrap all non-tariff barriers facing American firms, while the U.S. will drop threatened tariffs on Indonesian products to 19% from 32%, the two countries said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-cut-tariffs-non-tariff-barriers-us-trade-deal-trump-official-says-2025-07-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSEINEJOVRJW3NO3HGB3AQHYXI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>