<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:04:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:04:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Fed to go big on first rate cut, traders bet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Traders on Tuesday kept bets the Federal Reserve will start an expected series of interest rate cuts with a half-percentage-point move downward on Wednesday, an expectation that may itself put pressure on central bankers to deliver just that.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-go-big-first-rate-cut-traders-bet-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROIBAPSLARKHVFSP5EPXW367G4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:57:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US manufacturing output rebounds in August]]></title><description><![CDATA[Production at U.S. factories surged in August amid a rebound in motor vehicle output, but data for the prior month was revised lower, suggesting that manufacturing continued to tread water.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-output-rebounds-august-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZX7TBFAFGRK4ZLJVPSZTK4LBEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US SEC fines 12 municipal advisors for recordkeeping violations]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Tuesday fined 12 municipal advisors more than $1.3 million to settle civil charges that they failed to preserve electronic communications such as text messages.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-fines-12-municipal-advisors-recordkeeping-violations-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DWSGNC4V5JRFFE7GTH4VY4VE4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Philip Morris to sell stake in pharma unit Vectura for $198 mln]]></title><description><![CDATA[Marlboro maker Philip Morris International's unit Vectura Fertin Pharma said on Tuesday it would sell its subsidiary Vectura Group to Molex Asia Holdings for 150 million pounds ($198.09 million).]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/philip-morris-sell-stake-pharma-unit-vectura-198-mln-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYCTRTGPLZPXZJSLICAHKQJ2CY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:21:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Truckmakers say they are ready to go electric, but what about charging?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Major manufacturers, such as Daimler Truck and Traton , displaying their trucks at a transportation fair in Hanover this week say they are ready to go electric, but their e-trucks will not sell without massive investments in charging infrastructure.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/truckmakers-say-they-are-ready-go-electric-what-about-charging-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BJQNYAYJANM4XFCLJVSNML64LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:06:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW Canada's inflation cools to 2% in Aug, reaches central bank's target]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canada's annual inflation rate reached the central bank's target in August as it cooled to 2%, its lowest level since February 2021, data showed on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/view-canadas-inflation-cools-2-aug-reaches-central-banks-target-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WV2NBEFFFJPJ5ESUKLGUZCZWC4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Judge rules for ARC Global in breach of contract claim against Trump Media]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Delaware judge ruled for Patrick Orlando's ARC Global on a breach of contract claim over its stake in Trump Media &amp; Technology Group , although the judge rejected ARC's breach of fiduciary claim, according to an opinion published on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/judge-rules-arc-global-breach-contract-claim-against-trump-media-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32E2LJRL7ZIG3IPJ57KVF6POW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:58:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EVs could reach 24% EU car market share by 2025, T&E says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Battery-electric cars (BEVs) sold in the European Union are set to reach a total market share of between 20% and 24% by 2025, mostly because of cheaper selling prices, campaign group Transport &amp; Environment (T&amp;E) said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/evs-could-reach-24-eu-car-market-share-by-2025-te-says-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K4SEDI7RM5ID7HH2R3MUWNIHFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Google takes Chile data center plans back to square one on environmental concerns]]></title><description><![CDATA[Google will rework from scratch its plans to build a $200 million data center in Santiago after concerns were raised about its environmental impact on the Chilean capital, the U.S. tech giant said in a statement on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-takes-chile-data-center-plans-back-square-one-environmental-concerns-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3KGMSYDBRNLGTPK37RF36BEQXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:43:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US retail sales unexpectedly rise in August]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. retail sales unexpectedly rose in August, suggesting that the economy remained on a solid footing through much of the third quarter.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-retail-sales-unexpectedly-rise-august-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAX5KEWJLJMQLMZSQ4AZJA7IAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canada's inflation cools to 2% in Aug, reaches central bank's target]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canada's annual inflation rate reached the central bank's target in August at it cooled to 2%, its lowest level since February 2021, data showed on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-inflation-cools-2-aug-reaches-central-banks-target-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JRSUTUAYRBP5LBGBZBK4J54YLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UniCredit to seek ECB approval to potentially buy up to 30% of Commerzbank, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[UniCredit will seek ECB clearance to potentially buy up to 30% of Commerzbank , three people close to the matter said, in order to have the "flexibility" the Italian bank's CEO Andrea Orcel said he needs to plan his next move.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/unicredit-seek-ecb-approval-potentially-buy-up-30-commerzbank-sources-say-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZAUEL7C7VIHXCPICN7KSTEGIA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:31:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canadian housing starts tumble 22% in August]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canadian housing starts dropped 22% in August compared with the previous month as groundbreaking decreased on multiple-unit urban homes, data from the national housing agency showed on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadian-housing-starts-tumble-22-august-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYZXABKEEZO3ZMI6CVBHFPBRI4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Embraer's Eve taps former Rolls-Royce executive as chief commercial officer]]></title><description><![CDATA[Electric aircraft maker Eve has appointed former Rolls-Royce executive Megha Bhatia as its new chief commercial officer, the company said on Tuesday, as it continues to develop its "flying taxi".]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/embraers-eve-taps-former-rolls-royce-executive-chief-commercial-officer-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LWYRAGEAPNJA7PGUEW6JX5772U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Over-priced Fed rate cuts make T-bills unattractive, Federated Hermes says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Market expectations of substantial U.S. rate cuts this year are making short-dated debt unattractive as the Federal Reserve is unlikely to be as aggressive in easing monetary policy, said Deborah Cunningham, a money market fund manager for Federated Hermes, on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-money-market-funds-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IUWYRIVWWFMIRLWOQWX47RBKX4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:18:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intel's Amazon chip deal lifts investor confidence in money-losing foundry unit]]></title><description><![CDATA[Intel shares jumped 7% before the bell on Tuesday, as a chip-making deal with Amazon's cloud business provided a major stamp of approval for its struggling contract manufacturing business.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intels-amazon-chip-deal-lifts-investor-confidence-money-losing-foundry-unit-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q4I3UIS7JJJT7DDUQNEQZ6OUFU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:14:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Most brokerages expect 25 bps rate cut from Fed on Wednesday]]></title><description><![CDATA[Major brokerages expect the U.S. Federal Reserve to lower interest rates by 25 basis points at the end of its two-day monetary policy meeting that starts on Tuesday, even as financial markets price in a good chance of policymakers starting the easing cycle with an outsized rate reduction.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/most-brokerages-expect-25-bps-rate-cut-fed-wednesday-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XG4OSAPLWNNUTCRDLXMBLITHYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:10:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis working hard to avoid Volkswagen plant closure scenario, CEO says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis has already taken measures and is working hard to avoid the risk of plant closures facing rival Volkswagen , the carmaker's CEO Carlos Tavares said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-working-hard-avoid-volkswagen-plant-closing-scenario-ceo-says-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLCXJGKBDVKCNDYFECA52SWXD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:06:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ryanair seeing better momentum in bookings, less need to discount, CEO says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ryanair Group has seen better momentum in bookings since August and less need to discount prices, CEO Michael O'Leary said in an interview on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ryanair-seeing-better-momentum-bookings-less-need-discount-ceo-says-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7E2EZURA2RK4ZBHNIA5CL2XUWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instagram rolls out teen account with privacy, parental controls as scrutiny mounts]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms is rolling out special accounts with new privacy settings for teenaged Instagram users, it said on Tuesday, its latest effort to limit their exposure to harmful content on its apps amid regulatory pressure.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/instagram-rolls-out-teen-account-with-privacy-parental-controls-scrutiny-mounts-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGY6U4IJHVNPHE2NXS6A7KUXFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global defensive sector funds see surge in inflows on slowdown fears]]></title><description><![CDATA[Global defensive sector funds are in demand from investors as concerns about a slowdown in the U.S. economy forces them to seek assets such as consumer staples and utilities stocks that can withstand weakness in labour markets and commodities.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-sectors-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H73L7O7PEFKNVJQJMUTXLXPMBA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:57:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Express Scripts sues FTC over drug pricing report, court documents show]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pharmacy benefit manager Express Scripts has sued the U.S. Federal Trade Commission over the regulator's recent drug pricing report, asking a court to force the agency to withdraw its findings, according to court documents filed on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/express-scripts-sues-ftc-over-drug-pricing-report-court-documents-show-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD5ZSJPYSBKZJE6M3I6BBAZ5EI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:46:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Futures inch up ahead of economic data, Fed's rate-cut decision]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. stock index futures edged higher as investors awaited a batch of economic data and clung to hopes the Federal Reserve would deliver a supersized interest-rate cut at its monetary policy meeting, which starts on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-inch-up-ahead-economic-data-feds-rate-cut-decision-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WT2WPZHSM5IPTOP6K6VZ7YXHBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:25:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big Tech, calls for looser rules await new EU antitrust chief]]></title><description><![CDATA[Teresa Ribera will have to square up to Big Tech, banks and airlines if confirmed as Europe's new antitrust chief, while juggling calls for looser rules to help create EU champions.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/big-tech-calls-looser-rules-await-new-eu-antitrust-chief-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUWKF6D2YZPHRNZG5YIKTQSJLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:23:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMERICAS New highs, rotation as Fed meets with retail healthcheck]]></title><description><![CDATA[A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IIVTB2OORRLVRDNFHHT67GBJBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ignoring risk, investors still buying US junk debt with weak protections]]></title><description><![CDATA[When U.S.-based construction material supplier Wilsonart issued a junk bond to raise $500 million to fund an acquisition this summer, a research firm warned potential investors that the terms of the deal offered them weak protections.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ignoring-risk-investors-still-buying-us-junk-debt-with-weak-protections-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BPYBOZAWFKPVLY73GMYTKPLSY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kroger-Albertson's US anti-trust trial to end but other legal blocks loom]]></title><description><![CDATA[The trial where U.S. anti-trust regulators made their case to block Kroger's $25 billion bid to buy rival grocer Albertsons will conclude on Tuesday, but the deal's legal challenges have just begun, with two more trials this month to hear complaints the merger could jack up grocery bills.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/kroger-albertsons-us-anti-trust-trial-end-other-legal-blocks-loom-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WR7KYYC3NJMZAODRI7XV2JS4Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: US retailer holiday hiring set to be lower than last year]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. retailers will hire fewer seasonal workers this holiday season than last year due to a softer labor market and tighter consumer spending heading into the crucial shopping period, according to a report by Challenger, Gray &amp; Christmas provided exclusively to Reuters.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-retailer-holiday-hiring-set-be-lower-than-last-year-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BMQSVRZCBPR7P5KKNFXK6636E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fed rate cut uncertainties rattle balance sheet outlook]]></title><description><![CDATA[Uncertainty over the size of an initial interest rate cut expected Wednesday from the Federal Reserve has sparked a related debate over the possibility of an accelerated halt to the central bank’s balance sheet drawdown.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-rate-cut-uncertainties-rattle-balance-sheet-outlook-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23YFLA5G55KDNIG4V4VBYTZ2JU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bond investors debate recession risks with Fed easing finally at hand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bond investors are more cautious and divided over prospects for recession in the world's largest economy with the Federal Reserve poised to cut interest rates on Wednesday for the first time in more than four years.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bond-investors-debate-recession-risks-with-fed-easing-finally-hand-2024-09-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PHVGM4RD5RNYXKIDVO5JBHOP6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>