<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:37:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:37:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美达公司必须面对声称其偏爱外国工人而非美国公民的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家上诉法院周四恢复了一名软件工程师提出的集体诉讼，该工程师声称 Meta Platforms 公司拒绝雇用他，因为该公司更愿意把工作交给工资更低的外国工人。【原文：A U.S. appeals court on Thursday revived a software engineer's proposed class action claiming Meta Platforms refused to hire him because it preferred to give jobs to foreign workers who are paid lower wages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/meta-must-face-lawsuit-claiming-it-prefers-foreign-workers-over-us-citizens-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUFYRR2TGRJ5NA52D6PFIDAMM4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Webtoon 首次登陆纳斯达克，股价大涨 14]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线漫画平台 Webtoon Entertainment 周四在纳斯达克首次上市，股价比首次公开发行价飙升 14.3%。【原文：Shares of online comics platform Webtoon Entertainment surged as much as 14.3% above their initial public offering price in their Nasdaq debut on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/webtoons-nasdaq-debut-sees-shares-jump-14-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AO3YHNBVFRIWZCUEBNZNF2C46I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院对普渡制药公司做出裁决后值得关注的破产案件]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周四做出裁决，否决了奥施康定生产商普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）的破产和解方案，这可能会对美国破产法院如何处理旨在解决庞大诉讼的案件产生全面影响。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court's ruling on Thursday scuttling OxyContin maker Purdue Pharma's bankruptcy settlement could have a sweeping impact on how U.S. bankruptcy courts handle cases aimed at resolving sprawling litigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/bankruptcy-cases-watch-after-us-supreme-court-purdue-pharma-ruling-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPHLD7N4SBMZDM25VSBFPOS6GA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电网运营商称，得克萨斯州的电力需求将在热浪中打破 6 月和 7 月的记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州电网运营商预测，随着家庭和企业为躲避热浪而开动空调，用电量将在本周四打破 6 月份的高峰需求记录，随后将进一步攀升，并在下周打破 7 月份的记录。【原文：The Texas power-grid operator forecast electricity use will break the peak demand record for June on Thursday before rising even higher and topping the July record next week as homes and businesses crank up air conditioners to escape a heat wave.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/texas-power-demand-break-june-july-records-heat-wave-grid-operator-says-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MABMIEVZI5LTDK6ZDCIXOOV35I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国顶级运营商称漫游用户面临连接问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国主要电信服务提供商周四表示，由于一家合作网络提供商的问题，他们在海外旅行的一些用户遇到了连接问题。【原文：Major U.S. telecom service providers said on Thursday some of their users traveling overseas were having connectivity problems due to an issue at a partner network provider.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/top-us-carriers-say-roaming-customers-facing-connectivity-issues-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LYVSXKFWVMY7FL4RDVQBI5KOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:50:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥就有争议的采矿特许权寻求与中国锂企业达成协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统安德烈斯-曼努埃尔-洛佩斯-奥夫拉多尔（Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador）周四表示，他的政府将寻求与中国锂矿开采商赣锋达成一项协议，同时仍将捍卫墨西哥的权利。【原文：Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said on Thursday that his government will seek an agreement with Chinese lithium miner Ganfeng while still defending Mexico's rights, after the firm filed an arbitration case over a disputed concession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/mexico-seek-deal-over-disputed-mining-concession-with-chinese-lithium-firm-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVOGAL2ZPFNYLLI72WGZNWO5TE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国可能对欧盟猪肉采取的行动对巴西来说可能是把双刃剑]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和业内人士说，中国可能对欧盟进口猪肉实施反倾销措施，这对欧盟来说是一个灾难性的局面，可能会使巴西出口商受益，但也会影响巴西在其他地方的竞争能力。【原文：China's potential imposition of anti-dumping measures on European Union pork imports, a disastrous scenario for the bloc, could benefit Brazil's exporters but also affect the country's ability to compete elsewhere, analysts and industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/potential-china-action-against-eu-pork-may-be-double-edged-sword-brazil-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBPVS32S2NOTXBXQORUZNXJE3I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州最高法院允许对决的 "临时工 "投票措施继续进行]]></title><description><![CDATA[马萨诸塞州最高法院周四为该州选民决定是否应将优步（Uber Technologies）和 Lyft 等应用程序公司的司机归类为独立承包商扫清了道路，这些司机将有权享受一些新的福利，但在法律上不属于雇员。【原文：Massachusetts's top court on Thursday cleared the way for voters in the state to decide whether drivers for app-based companies like Uber Technologies and Lyft should be classified as independent contractors who would be entitled to some new benefits but would not be legally employees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/massachusetts-top-court-allows-dueling-gig-worker-ballot-measures-proceed-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBDVKHIPWFK4TFEMWO3JTETESI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:29:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行经受住美联储年度压力测试，但风险上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美联储年度压力测试的结果，美国大型银行拥有足够的资本来抵御可能出现的严重经济衰退，但其部分高风险业务今年可能会受到重创。【原文：Big U.S. banks had enough capital to weather a potentially severe economic downturn but some of their risky businesses could hypothetically take a major hit this year, according to results of the Federal Reserve's annual stress test.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-banks-weather-feds-annual-stress-test-risks-rise-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NEZLDP4WHNJANNLLXPSUIL4MLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院阻止普渡制药公司破产和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周四阻止了奥施康定生产商普渡制药公司（Purdue Pharma）的破产和解方案，该方案将使其富裕的萨克勒（Sackler）家族所有者免于因其在美国致命的阿片类药物流行中扮演的角色而被起诉。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court on Thursday blocked OxyContin maker Purdue Pharma's bankruptcy settlement that would have shielded its wealthy Sackler family owners from lawsuits over their role in the nation's deadly opioid epidemic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-blocks-purdue-pharma-bankruptcy-settlement-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X7S3J6TJPJOZVFC66YLO7IDKSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:10:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储博斯蒂克称通胀朝着 "正确方向 "发展，预计第四季度将降息一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联储主席拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）在周四发表的一篇政策文章中表示，美国的通胀 "似乎正在收窄"，这应允许美联储在今年晚些时候降息。【原文：Inflation in the U.S. "appears to be narrowing" and that should allow the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates later this year, Atlanta Fed President Raphael Bostic said in a policy essay released on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bostic-says-inflation-moving-right-direction-sees-one-q4-rate-cut-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVE4JE6NFBIAFEA2CIU3W3ASFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国五月未决房屋销售下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份，美国旧房购买合同出人意料地下降，这表明，随着潜在买家努力应对更高的抵押贷款利率和价格，销售可能在一段时间内保持低迷。【原文：Contracts to buy U.S. previously owned homes unexpectedly fell in May, indicating sales could remain subdued for a while as potential buyers grapple with higher mortgage rates and prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-pending-home-sales-fall-may-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TYZUHDCBXFPILMYL2L7CX37QAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪称，新保护措施可遏制垃圾债务交易中的漏洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪的一份报告称，受压的垃圾级公司正在想出新的债务重组办法，这对一些债权人来说比对其他债权人更有利，但为弥补交易文件中的漏洞而采取的保护措施也开始出现。【原文：Stressed junk-rated companies were coming up with new ways to restructure their debt which benefited some creditors over others but protections to close loopholes in deal documentations that enabled them are starting to emerge, said a Moody's report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/novel-protection-could-curb-loopholes-junk-debt-deals-moodys-says-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPGIKBXDNBNRDJ4WRU5IN6Y6IM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 与《时代》杂志签订多年内容协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[时代》杂志与 OpenAI 周四表示，双方已签署一项多年期内容协议，OpenAI 将允许 ChatGPT 厂商访问其新闻内容档案。【原文：Time magazine has signed a multi-year content deal with OpenAI that would give the ChatGPT maker access to its archive of news content, the companies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-signs-multi-year-content-deal-with-time-magazine-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YU562UD725JY7CZJWLD633ILNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:51:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月核心资本货物订单大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[5 月份，美国主要制造业资本货物的新订单出乎意料地减少，表明由于借贷成本居高不下，第二季度企业在设备方面的支出有所减弱。【原文：New orders for key U.S.-manufactured capital goods unexpectedly fell in May, suggesting that business spending on equipment weakened in the second quarter as borrowing costs remain elevated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-core-capital-goods-orders-fall-sharply-may-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPMCK5HS35KHPJCH5V2T4UBD5A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:12:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[H&M 将提供更多折扣，努力重振销售业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[H&amp;M 计划在今年下半年提供更多的折扣时装，试图从 Zara 所有者 Inditex 和 Shein 等公司手中夺回顾客。【原文：H&amp;M plans to offer more discounted fashions in the second half of this year as it tries to win back customers from the likes of Zara owner Inditex and Shein.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hm-offer-more-discounts-it-battles-revive-sales-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q6MSPJWNGNI6XL6VF7YSGWG6HQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[调味品制造商麦考密克因欧洲、中东和非洲地区业务强劲而实现季度业绩增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[受欧洲、中东和非洲市场对其香料和调味品的强劲需求带动，麦考密克周四公布的第二季度利润和销售额均超出市场预期。【原文：McCormick beat market expectations for second-quarter profit and sales on Thursday, led by strong demand for its spices and seasonings in Europe, Middle East and Africa.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spice-maker-mccormick-beats-quarterly-results-strong-emea-business-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISLSY7KGTRPUROELFQI6UZD4EE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周美国首次申请失业救济的人数有所减少，这可能会减轻人们对劳动力市场发生实质性变化的担忧。【原文：First-time applications for U.S. unemployment benefits drifted lower last week, which could allay fears of a material shift in the labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-drift-lower-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LT2VJSBKDFJELJGA7PDTYOBLOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约市广播公司预计反向股票分割将于下月生效]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约社区银行（New York Community Bancorp）周四表示，该地区性银行一拆三的反向股票拆细将于 7 月中下旬生效。【原文：New York Community Bancorp's one-for-three reverse stock split will become effective mid-to-late July, the regional lender said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nycb-expects-reverse-stock-split-take-effect-next-month-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OTXXUEYJ7VPPHEUXLU3LZLQQ2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，汽车支付能力影响汽车贷款市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[信用报告机构全美征信公司（TransUnion）周四表示，一项关于美国汽车贷款的研究发现，消费者预算减少对一些借款人的贷款支付产生了负面影响。【原文：A study on loans for buying automobiles in the United States has found that weaker consumer budgets are negatively impacting loan payments for some borrowers, credit reporting agency TransUnion said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/car-affordability-affecting-auto-lending-market-study-shows-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALW7SIJ7MZL4JFH4ETGTBAZJOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:11:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于批发业务依然疲软，李维-斯特劳斯（Levi Strauss）第二季度收入不及预期，业绩下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Levi Strauss 的股价在周四的盘前交易中下跌超过 15%，原因是这家牛仔布生产商的美国批发业务疲软，导致其第二季度营收下滑。【原文：Levi Strauss' shares tumbled more than 15% in premarket trade on Thursday after weakness in the denim maker's U.S. wholesale business led to downbeat second-quarter revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-slumps-second-quarter-revenue-miss-wholesale-business-remains-weak-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTP5PQRON5JAHAGWBKYSQIOXCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:54:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行将 2024 年国内生产总值增长预期上调至 2.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行在周四发布的季度通胀报告中将其 2024 年的经济增长预期从 3 月份预测的 1.9% 上调至 2.3%。【原文：Brazil's central bank bumped up its 2024 economic growth forecast to 2.3% from the 1.9% predicted in March, according to its quarterly inflation report released on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/brazils-central-bank-raises-2024-gdp-growth-forecast-23-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LZEZP3P2RMQTN2VVB6EDZFRPY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔格林下调 2024 年利润预期，宣布关闭门店]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔格林博姿联盟（Walgreen Boots Alliance）周四下调了 2024 财年的利润预期，并宣布关闭门店，理由是药店行业的发展趋势面临挑战，而且美国的消费环境也不如预期。【原文：Walgreen Boots Alliance cut its profit forecast for fiscal 2024 and announced store closures on Thursday, citing challenging pharmacy industry trends and a worse-than-expected U.S. consumer environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walgreens-cuts-2024-profit-forecast-announces-store-closures-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZ6BQUAYDNNH7DIHRWMXQEKOQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国财政部和美国国际开发署召集开发银行就极端高温问题举行紧急会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据美国财政部官员称，美国财政部和美国国际开发署正在召集多边开发银行的领导人召开一次紧急会议，讨论极端高温及其对发展中国家的破坏性影响。【原文：The U.S. Treasury and the U.S. Agency for International Development are calling leaders of multilateral development banks into an urgent meeting on extreme heat and its devastating impact on developing countries, according to Treasury officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/us-treasury-usaid-call-development-banks-urgent-talks-extreme-heat-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVW3WTOHUNN55CHRGY7T5K7TEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街希望总统辩论不带戏剧性，像关注政策一样关注行为举止]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者在观看周四举行的 2024 年大选第一场现场辩论时，希望听到美国总统乔-拜登和他的前任唐纳德-特朗普就财政政策、关税和税收等问题进行深思熟虑的辩论，同时密切关注他们的精神敏锐度。【原文：Investors watching the first live debate of the 2024 election race on Thursday hope to hear U.S. President Joe Biden and his predecessor Donald Trump argue thoughtful positions on fiscal policy, tariffs and taxes, while closely monitoring their mental acuity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-wants-drama-free-presidential-debate-watching-comportment-much-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RU6YUJTU6ZPSTL7Z3P5WFLH2M4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:03:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻美国电视对决引人关注，疲软日元企稳回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUJ4H2BRNNJPDCQMPLFINUTL3Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:29:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian 投资者将在投资者日上详细了解盈利之路]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这家美国电动汽车制造商宣布获得大众汽车 50 亿美元投资两天后，Rivian 股东将在周四举行的投资者日活动上了解该公司即将推出的车型以及削减成本方面的进展。【原文：Rivian shareholders will seek details on the company's upcoming models and progress in cutting costs at an investor day event on Thursday, two days after the US electric vehicle maker announced a $5 billion investment from Volkswagen .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rivian-investors-seek-details-path-profits-investor-day-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXZHDF7YWRILHB4DSOE2AC6GHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:28:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[经济数据公布前，美光拖累芯片股，期权下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周四下跌，原因是美光科技（Micron Technology）本季度业绩预测不佳，导致股价下滑，并拖累了其他芯片类股，而经济数据和总统辩论前的谨慎情绪也影响了市场情绪。【原文：U.S. stock index futures dropped on Thursday, as Micron Technology slumped after an unimpressive current-quarter forecast and dragged down other chip stocks, while caution ahead of economic data and a presidential debate also dented sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-dip-micron-drags-down-chip-stocks-ahead-economic-data-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLTZAWGAWJKG7IUESHN2Q2TC2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美光暴跌，因人工智能收入激增未达高预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美光（Micron）股价在周四的盘前交易中下跌了 6%，原因是这家芯片制造商本季度的营收预期未能打动那些希望在人工智能需求激增的推动下取得超预期业绩的投资者。【原文：Micron shares dropped 6% in premarket trading on Thursday after the chipmaker's current-quarter revenue forecast failed to impress investors looking for outsized results powered by the AI demand surge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/micron-falls-ai-revenue-surge-falls-short-lofty-expectations-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57TCMRE2CRI5NMW3EEPKOTLZHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rite Aid 寻求破产法院批准削减 20 亿美元债务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rite Aid 将于周四请求美国破产法院批准其重组计划，寻求削减 20 亿美元债务，并将公司控制权移交给一组贷款人。【原文：Rite Aid will ask a U.S. bankruptcy court to approve its restructuring plan on Thursday, seeking to cut $2 billion in debt and turn over control of the company to a group of its lenders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/rite-aid-seeks-bankruptcy-court-approval-cut-2-billion-debt-2024-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKKBUYFKOVOAFJ5LXLQRJYLHNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:11:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>