<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 18:37:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 18:37:01 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，X 不太可能受具有里程碑意义的欧盟技术规则管辖]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位直接了解此事的人士周五表示，埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 社交媒体平台不太可能受到欧盟旨在控制大科技公司权力的里程碑式科技规则的约束，因为它不符合规则中的 "守门人 "标准。【原文：Elon Musk's X social media platform is unlikely to be subjected to landmark EU tech rules which aim to rein in the power of Big Tech because it does not meet the rules' gatekeeper criteria, a person with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/x-unlikely-fall-under-landmark-eu-tech-rules-source-says-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7T2K2QBU5I2VM4BFZSHMOWCSA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 18:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席财务官称波音罢工对 MAX 目标和供应链构成挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司首席财务官布赖恩-韦斯特（Brian West）周五表示，波音公司美国西海岸工厂3万多名工人周五开始的罢工将使该公司更难实现737 MAX的生产目标和稳定供应链。【原文：A strike beginning Friday by more than 30,000 of Boeing's U.S. West Coast factory workers will make it harder for the planemaker to meet a 737 MAX production target and stabilize its supply chain, CFO Brian West said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-poses-challenge-max-targets-supply-chain-cfo-says-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5NCCPD4J5IADGQWRYBPM3EG2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:45:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，欧盟计划于 9 月 25 日就提高对中国电动汽车的关税进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周五援引熟悉该计划的人士的话报道称，欧盟计划于9月25日举行投票，对从中国进口的电动汽车征收明确的关税。【原文：The European Union is aiming to hold a vote to introduce definitive tariffs on electric vehicles imported from China on Sept. 25, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/eu-plans-sept-25-vote-raising-tariffs-evs-china-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWWOTGQ4DBOJNOBCF7QNRAXSCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:38:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》报道：白宫官员发出推迟美国钢铁公司收购决定的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周五报道，白宫官员表示将推迟就日本新日铁公司收购美国钢铁公司一事做出决定。【原文：White House officials have signaled a delay in taking a decision regarding the takeover of U.S. Steel by Japan's Nippon Steel , the Washington Post reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/white-house-officials-signal-delay-us-steel-takeover-decision-washington-post-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYRVUKCHJFPLPG3UFZJNYYBRKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:12:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称贝恩资本为出售英国 esure 物色顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士告诉路透社，私募股权公司贝恩资本（Bain Capital）已为可能出售英国汽车和住宅保险公司 esure 物色了顾问。【原文：Private equity firm Bain Capital has lined up advisers for the possible sale of British motor and home insurer esure, three people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-capital-taps-advisers-sale-uks-esure-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">362YASQENVMSBIHGTUSPPDEELM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[评级机构惠誉称波音公司长期罢工带来降级风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉周五表示，波音公司的长期罢工可能会带来信用评级下调的风险。【原文：Fitch said on Friday an extended strike at Boeing could pose a risk for a credit ratings downgrade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ratings-agency-fitch-says-extended-strike-boeing-poses-downgrade-risk-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMJRMT6T65N7NJIUI7246ZFCWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:29:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，欧盟暂时不可能向谷歌下达分拆令]]></title><description><![CDATA[直接知情人士透露，欧盟反垄断官员正在考虑向 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌发出命令，要求其停止广告技术业务中的反竞争行为，但不会像他们最初警告的那样发出解散令。【原文：EU antitrust officials are considering an order to Alphabet unit Google to stop its anti-competitive practices in its adtech business but will not issue a breakup order as they had originally warned, people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-break-up-order-google-unlikely-now-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YGOFCHG7NFJJZLGZHEQJWYMP6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息 50 个基点与降息 25 个基点的可能性几乎一样大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的利率期货合约交易显示，美联储下周大幅降息的可能性几乎与通常规模的降息一样大，因为金融市场认为美联储采取更激进行动的可能性更大。【原文：The Federal Reserve is nearly as likely to deliver an outsized interest-rate cut next week as a more-usual-sized reduction, trading in rate-futures contracts suggested on Friday, as financial markets priced in a bigger chance that the Fed will move more aggressively.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-seen-nearly-likely-cut-rates-by-50-bps-25-bps-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA5KKDCNZ5NZTC2QGLBYP7UVUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:09:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特鲁多称政府向加航和飞行员施压以避免罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理贾斯汀-特鲁多（Justin Trudeau）周五表示，加拿大政府将继续向加拿大航空公司及其飞行员工会施加一切压力，以避免可能最快于下周开始的罢工。【原文：The Canadian government will continue to put all the pressure it can on Air Canada and its pilots' union to avert a strike that could start as soon as next week, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trudeau-says-govt-pressuring-air-canada-pilots-avert-strike-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZR6PKHSGJOYBMPOJPXUJBQNGA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:56:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者押注 "重植"，美国制造业 ETF 赢得资产青睐]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者纷纷涌入交易所交易基金，重点关注那些正在美国恢复或扩大生产并利用政府补贴的公司。【原文：Investors are piling into exchange traded funds focused on companies that are reviving or expanding production in the U.S. and taking advantage of government subsidies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-etfs-win-assets-investors-bet-reshoring-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E7YRKTULYVLEJKHVDF7ZBKQAXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音罢工使等待交货的 737 MAX 客户成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司西海岸工厂的工人在一致拒绝了一份合同后，于周五早些时候离开了工作岗位，停止了该公司最畅销的 737 MAX 喷气式飞机的生产。【原文：Boeing's West Coast factory workers walked off the job early on Friday after they unanimously rejected a contract, halting production of the company's best-selling 737 MAX jet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-puts-spotlight-737-max-customers-waiting-deliveries-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WO3PZLXRXRLP3MXBIK3D6NFDTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 9 月消费者信心指数上升，通胀有所缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，尽管美国人在11月总统大选前仍持谨慎态度，但9月份美国消费者情绪在通胀消退的情况下有所改善。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment improved in September amid subsiding inflation, though Americans remained cautious ahead of the November presidential election, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-rises-september-inflation-eases-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWBEQXK4DBNAPLRNWUU5GNJV24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[普京的商品禁令威胁令俄罗斯企业和官员感到困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗拉基米尔-普京总统出人意料地威胁要限制战略商品出口以应对西方制裁，俄罗斯官员和管理者对此感到困惑，不知道能否在不对俄罗斯造成比西方更大伤害的情况下实现这一威胁。【原文：Russian officials and managers are perplexed by President Vladimir Putin's surprise threat to limit exports of strategic commodities in response to Western sanctions, and wonder if it can be realised without hurting Russia more than the West.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/putins-commodities-ban-threat-puzzles-russian-firms-officials-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVFRHRAKAFJRTMBLOAK2GLTYEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:27:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，巴西 Azul 公司接近与出租人达成新的债务协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉谈判的人士称，巴西 Azul 航空公司已接近与出租人达成新协议，该公司将向他们提供股权，以偿还约 6 亿美元的债务。【原文：Brazilian airline Azul has moved closer to clinching a new deal with lessors, three people familiar with the talks said, as the company offers them equity to pay off some $600 million in debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-azul-close-new-debt-deal-with-lessors-sources-say-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZU5PKVPWFPTJNMERPGBUQLJFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行将于 9 月 18 日加息 25 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，巴西央行将在下周三将基准利率上调 25 个点，这很可能是为抑制持续通胀趋势而采取的短期紧缩政策的开始，其行动方向与同行相反。【原文：Brazil's central bank will raise its benchmark rate by 25 points next Wednesday at what will likely be the start of a short tightening campaign to quash persistent inflationary trends, moving the opposite way to its peers, a Reuters poll found.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/brazil-central-bank-hike-rates-by-25-basis-points-sept-18-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7F4ALGHTTJKCRPDPQ45FIEDZ5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步和 Waymo 将自动驾驶汽车引入奥斯汀和亚特兰大]]></title><description><![CDATA[打车平台优步（Uber Technologies）周五表示，将与 Alphabet 旗下的 Waymo 合作，在得克萨斯州奥斯汀和佐治亚州亚特兰大市推出自动驾驶打车服务。【原文：Ride-hailing platform Uber Technologies said on Friday it would bring autonomous ride hailing to Austin, Texas, and Atlanta, Georgia, in partnership with Alphabet's Waymo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uber-waymo-bring-autonomous-ride-hailing-austin-atlanta-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3ZFNSTLK5PGVJBDYSHU25GG4Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金属资源丰富的哈萨克斯坦寻求在电池供应链中占据一席之地]]></title><description><![CDATA[哈萨克斯坦工业部长告诉路透社，哈萨克斯坦的目标是提高电动汽车（EV）电池所需金属的产量，并正在发放数百份新的勘探许可证，以吸引对该行业的新投资。【原文：Kazakhstan aims to boost output of metals needed for electric vehicle (EV) batteries and is issuing hundreds of new exploration licences to attract fresh investment in the sector, the country's industry minister told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/metals-rich-kazakhstan-seeks-niche-battery-supply-chain-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CK4JGP4B45IGVEBONPJP2UEYW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[增长困境和政治风险导致美国股票基金资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 9 月 11 日的一周内，由于经济数据疲软以及美国总统大选前政治不确定性的增加，投资者的谨慎情绪升温，美国股票基金经历了大幅流出。【原文：U.S. equity funds experienced significant outflows in the week through Sept. 11, as investor caution mounted due to weak economic data and growing political uncertainties ahead of the U.S. presidential election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-outflows-growth-woes-political-risks-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M65BVYXIEFN5ROFIJS57QX36RU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文股价上涨，预计2029财年销售额将突破1000亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[甲骨文公司周五在盘前交易中上涨超过 6%，此前该公司表示，由于人工智能的普及推动了对其云服务的需求，预计 2029 财年的营收将突破 1000 亿美元。【原文：Oracle shares rose more than 6% in premarket trading on Friday after the company said it expects to cross $100 billion in revenue in fiscal 2029, as the popularity of AI drives demand for its cloud services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/oracle-shares-rise-it-expects-cross-100-billion-fiscal-2029-sales-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEMJNKDUNBNH7FZHZ74FEILD3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:13:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯央行警告西方银行不要歧视俄罗斯客户]]></title><description><![CDATA[在西方监管机构的压力下，俄罗斯央行向留在俄罗斯的西方银行子公司发出严正警告，不得歧视俄罗斯客户，拒绝为他们提供向国外转账等服务。【原文：Russia's central bank has sent a stark warning to subsidiaries of Western banks remaining in Russia not to discriminate against their Russian clients by denying them services such as transferring money abroad, as the banks come under pressure from Western regulators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/russias-central-bank-warns-western-banks-not-discriminate-against-russian-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YKOZ3BECBO7HEEZANDNUHGIVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:12:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 8 月新增贷款增幅低于预期，预计将采取更多政策措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国新增银行贷款在 7 月份创下 15 年新低后，8 月份的增幅低于预期，因为中国央行继续保持宽松政策，并承诺推出更多支持性措施，以促进脆弱的经济复苏。【原文：New bank lending in China jumped less than expected in August after hitting a 15-year low in July, as the central bank keeps policy accommodative and pledges to roll out more supportive measures to bolster a fragile economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/chinas-august-new-lending-rises-less-than-expected-more-policy-steps-expected-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYAZFGB6GBJGVIZXBE66IFCZCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:10:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[8 月份美国进口价格创八个月来最大降幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于燃料和食品成本下降，8月份美国进口价格创下8个月来最大降幅，这表明未来几个月国内通胀将继续减弱。【原文：U.S. import prices dropped by the most in eight months in August amid lower costs for fuels and food products, suggesting that domestic inflation will continue to subside in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-import-prices-post-largest-drop-eight-months-august-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUUGOICWQNPO7K4JJPYS2HYVKI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：DSV 如何成长为全球最大的物流公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[DSV 同意以 143 亿欧元（158.5 亿美元）收购德国国有铁路运营商德国铁路的物流部门全球国际货运公司（Schenker），即将成为全球最大的物流公司。【原文：DSV is on the verge of becoming the world's biggest logistics firm after agreeing to buy Schenker, the logistics arm of German state rail operator Deutsche Bahn, for 14.3 billion euros ($15.85 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/how-dsv-grew-into-worlds-biggest-logistics-firm-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3NSM4APZZNQDE63APPFT43CII</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：四大会计师事务所在中国的规模有多大？]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国监管机构周五对普华永道在中国大陆的审计部门处以停业六个月和创纪录的4.41亿元人民币（6200万美元）罚款，原因是该公司对陷入困境的房地产开发商中国恒大集团进行了审计。【原文：Chinese regulators on Friday hit PwC's auditing unit in mainland China with a six-month business suspension and a record fine of 441 million yuan ($62 million) over the firm's audit of troubled property developer China Evergrande Group .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-big-are-big-four-accounting-firms-china-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXU2VDHNTZJDLI4B3JHQQ4FUBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:37:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司采用埃隆-马斯克的 Starlink 技术提供机上互联网服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周五表示，该公司已与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 Starlink 公司签署了一项新协议，以提供机上互联网服务。【原文：United Airlines said on Friday it has signed a new deal with Elon Musk's Starlink for in-flight internet services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/united-airlines-taps-elon-musks-starlink-in-flight-internet-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K75KCEQJM5JVZEQZOBJPPDD2YA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:22:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能软件竞争影响盈利预期，Adobe 股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Adobe 公司的股票在周五的盘前交易中下跌超过 8%，此前这家 Photoshop 制造商令人失望的季度盈利预测引发了人们的担忧，即其推动人工智能设计的回报需要更长的时间才能实现。【原文：Shares of Adobe fell over 8% in premarket trading on Friday, after the Photoshop maker's disappointing quarterly earnings forecast sparked fears that returns from its push towards artificial intelligence design will take longer to materialize.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/adobe-shares-slump-ai-software-competition-hits-earnings-forecast-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TKAHCEAVZPRPGNBBNCL4TNPHM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师称，富国银行新的监管麻烦可能会推迟资产上限取消的时间表]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街分析师周五表示，富国银行最近的监管挫折可能会推迟取消美国联邦储备委员会（U.S. Federal Reserve）规定的资产上限的时间表，并抑制其增长。【原文：Wells Fargo's latest regulatory setback could delay the timeline for lifting the asset cap imposed by the U.S. Federal Reserve and stifle its growth, Wall Street analysts said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/well-fargos-new-regulatory-trouble-may-delay-asset-cap-removal-timeline-analysts-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZP35UPNVLBIYLIYE4EIGATL2CE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 12:01:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黄金多头将目光投向此前创下的 3000 美元/盎司里程碑]]></title><description><![CDATA[黄金市场多头正在锁定金银价格飙升至新纪录，每盎司 3,000 美元的里程碑即将成为焦点，主要央行的宽松货币政策和紧张的美国总统大选选情为这一目标提供了动力。【原文：Gold market bulls are locking in bullion prices surging to fresh records, with a milestone of $3,000 per ounce coming into focus, fired up by monetary easing by major central banks and a tight U.S. presidential election race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-bulls-set-sights-previously-dismissed-record-3000oz-milestone-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZNS27RWR5KWZEFR2XH55W55SM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 11:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于对经济前景持谨慎态度，全球股票基金出现第二周资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至9月11日，全球投资者连续第二周净卖出股票基金，原因是对美国经济健康状况的担忧，以及在美国总统大选辩论前对政治气候的谨慎态度。【原文：Global investors were net sellers of equity funds for a second successive week through Sept. 11, driven by concerns over the health of the U.S. economy and caution about the political climate in the run-up to the U.S. Presidential debate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35EDWL6UINNJ3AIWRCPWCRNHDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 11:18:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将根据800美元的 "微量 "豁免采取措施遏制中国低价值货运]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周五表示，它正在采取行动遏制越来越多的低价值货物根据800美元的 "微量 "门槛免税进入美国。【原文：The Biden administration on Friday said it was moving to curb a growing tide of low-value shipments entering the U.S. duty-free under the $800 "de minimis" threshold that has been exploited by Chinese e-commerce firms such as Shein and PDD Holdings' Temu.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-take-steps-curb-low-value-chinese-shipments-under-800-de-minimis-exemption-2024-09-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZDQ7REGGZMWVI4XZCLFWE5VOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 11:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>