<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:40:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:40:04 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克称，在印度查获第二台设备后，"星链 "已停止运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）说，Starlink 卫星互联网在印度已停止使用，这是他在最近几周当局扣押了该公司的两台设备（一台在武装冲突地区，另一台在毒品走私案中）后首次发表评论。【原文：Elon Musk said Starlink satellite internet is inactive in India, his first comments since authorities seized two of the company's devices in recent weeks, one in an armed conflict zone and another in a drug smuggling bust.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/elon-musk-says-starlink-inactive-india-after-second-device-seized-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2OPIZADRRM6DPVC2AERV4VG6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产与本田的对比]]></title><description><![CDATA[据知情人士透露，日本汽车制造商本田和日产正在商谈深化关系，包括可能进行合并，因为特斯拉和中国竞争对手的挑战促使日本汽车业进行重组。【原文：Japanese carmakers Honda and Nissan are in talks to deepen ties, according to sources, including a possible merger, as challenges from Tesla and Chinese rivals urge a restructuring of Japan's auto industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/how-nissan-honda-stack-up-against-each-other-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZ5M7M3UORMGRIY35DQ77QY6QA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储有望将降息与 2025 年鹰派前景相结合]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储预计将在周三降低借贷成本，一些观察家将此称为 "鹰派降息"，与此同时，政策制定者还将更新利率展望和经济预测，内容涵盖即将上任的特朗普政府上任后的头几个月。【原文：The Federal Reserve is expected to lower borrowing costs on Wednesday in what some observers are calling a "hawkish cut" set to be delivered alongside policymakers' updated interest rate outlooks and economic forecasts covering the first months of the incoming Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-expected-combine-interest-rate-cut-with-hawkish-2025-outlook-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCJOEHVKS5M4TPMKKVPR6ARQPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:12:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲的难题：如何为国防开支提供资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟东部边境战火纷飞，俄罗斯构成威胁，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）向盟友施压，要求他们采取更多行动，因此欧盟迫切需要一个可行的计划，以确保获得数千亿欧元来加强防御。【原文：With a war raging at the European Union's eastern border, Russia posing a threat, and U.S. President-elect Donald Trump pressuring allies to do more, the bloc urgently needs a viable plan to secure hundreds of billions of euros to bolster its defences.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/europes-conundrum-how-fund-defence-spending-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEZ7BDYLSBLKZPELE2LQ5FKQSY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:09:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，"欧佩克+"对特朗普领导下的美国石油产量再次上升保持警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+"的代表们说，欧佩克+"对唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫后美国石油产量的再次上升持谨慎态度，因为更多的美国石油将进一步侵蚀 "欧佩克+"的市场份额，并阻碍该生产国集团支撑油价的努力。【原文：OPEC+ is wary of a renewed rise in U.S. oil output when Donald Trumpreturns to the White House, delegates from the group said, because more U.S. oil would further erode OPEC+ market share and hamper the producer group's efforts to support prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-wary-renewed-us-oil-output-rise-under-trump-sources-say-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SSXE3NTVFRJ3JK5Y6XTW4JOEGA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着比特币飙升，奢侈品牌考虑接受加密货币支付]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币价值的飙升引起了高端时尚品牌和零售商的注意，促使他们进一步关注提供加密货币作为支付手段，以挖掘新的财富口袋，并与加密货币投资者建立忠诚度。【原文：Bitcoin’s soaring value has caught the attention of high-end fashion brands and retailers, prompting further interest in offering cryptocurrencies as a means of payment to tap in to fresh pockets of wealth and build loyalty with crypto investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bitcoin-soars-luxury-brands-consider-accepting-crypto-payments-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HJHNSTK6AFL3XLTWV6IVHPZOGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行加息的争论从 "何时 "转向 "多高"？]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着对日本下一次加息时间的猜测升温，央行内部正在酝酿另一场辩论，即利率究竟能提高多少，这个问题可能会在本周的政策会议上讨论。【原文：As the guessing game over the timing of Japan's next interest rate hike heats up, another debate is brewing within the central bank over just how much higher rates can go, a question that could be discussed at this week's policy meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/bojs-rate-hike-debate-shifts-when-how-high-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HNVJJAQPFIOVG773DEXZRJ6LA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲 对冲基金看好中国科技在 2025 年引领人工智能潮流]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国的进一步限制措施可能于明年生效，但一些亚洲对冲基金仍将赌注押在小米和百度等中国领先的科技公司身上，因为这些公司受到人工智能创新的推动。【原文：Some Asian hedge funds are betting on leading Chinese tech companies such as Xiaomi and Baidu , buoyed by their artificial intelligence innovations, despite the threat of further U.S. curbs that could take effect next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/asia-hedge-funds-eye-chinese-tech-leading-ai-charge-2025-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7UIJUWJLBZO6ZO6B3YLOP3VCUA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:51:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：美联储迫在眉睫，欧洲迎来通胀数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vidya Ranganathan 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Vidya Ranganathan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXVTSNXQQRKL7MBGE3A4RKIVZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国央行称 "低通胀 "时代不会在未来一两年到来]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国央行行长周三表示，由于 "低通胀 "时代不太可能在一两年内到来，韩国央行将在下一次政策审查之前维持 2% 的通胀目标。【原文：South Korea's central bank will maintain its inflation target of 2% until the next policy review, as the era of "low-inflation" is unlikely to come in a year or two, the bank's governor said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/bank-korea-says-low-inflation-era-not-coming-next-year-or-two-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCNTOHXEW5KDXEKMF3AN6OV2JM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家探讨本田与日产深化合作的会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士周三表示，本田和日产正在商谈深化关系，包括可能的合并，这是一个最明显的迹象，表明日本曾经看似无与伦比的汽车行业正在被特斯拉和中国竞争对手的挑战所重塑。【原文：Honda and Nissan are in talks to deepen ties, two people said on Wednesday, including a possible merger, the clearest sign yet of how Japan's once seemingly unbeatable auto industry is being reshaped by challenges from Tesla and Chinese rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/experts-honda-nissans-talks-deepen-ties-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLSST6REEJK2DBRUMXZDMUC2PQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 04:20:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国 11 月工业景气指数创 8 个月新高，原因是旅游业和出口有所改善]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国工业联合会（Federation of Thai Industries）周三表示，由于出口和旅游业走强，11 月份泰国工业景气指数连续第二个月上升，达到八个月来的最高水平。【原文：The Thai industrial sentiment index rose for a second consecutive month in November, reaching its highest level in eight months on stronger exports and tourism, the Federation of Thai Industries said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thai-industrial-sentiment-hits-8-month-high-november-better-tourism-exports-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QREVUIPLEZOUDFMFZOF3YDNE4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:58:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司称已恢复 767 和 777 生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司周二晚些时候表示，该公司已经恢复了因西北太平洋地区机工罢工而停产的所有飞机项目的生产。【原文：Boeing said late on Tuesday it has resumed production of all airplane programs that had been halted by a machinists strike in the Pacific Northwest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-says-it-has-resumed-767-777-production-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FU2GTJORRFOVVCVVSF7WPERS2M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储会议前美元走强，日本汽车股受本田-日产消息影响大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在美国降息预期的倒计时阶段，亚洲股市徘徊在两周低点附近，美元兑澳元和新西兰元汇率创下里程碑式的新高。【原文：Asian stocks hovered near two-week lows and the dollar hit milestone highs against the Australian and New Zealand dollars on Wednesday in the countdown to an expected U.S. interest rate cut.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2IRRBEH3JITXOYFLTV25HPFKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:03:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南举办武器博览会，寻求促进国内国防工业发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南将于本周四在河内举行的国际武器博览会上展示本地制造的武器，以促进国内工业发展，并有可能出口军事装备。【原文：Vietnam will showcase locally made weapons at an international arms fair in Hanoi on Thursday, as it seeks to boost its domestic industry and possibly export military equipment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/vietnam-seeks-boost-domestic-defence-industry-it-hosts-arms-fair-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3UZJBEKMROH5EH7JUWYCHF7QA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 02:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储利率决议前油价变化不大]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三早盘，油价窄幅震荡，因为投资者在美国联邦储备委员会预期降息前保持谨慎。【原文：Oil prices traded in a narrow range early on Wednesday as investors remained cautious ahead of an expected interest rate cut by the U.S. Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-little-changed-ahead-fed-rate-decision-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5OLPB7K4Z5JLTOUSF3RR3CLI6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 02:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国会将就美国对华投资新限制进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会议员周二晚些时候表示，国会将在未来几天内就限制美国对华投资的立法进行投票表决，该立法是资助政府运作至三月中旬的法案的一部分。【原文：Congress is set to vote in the coming days on legislation restricting U.S. investments in China as part of a bill to fund government operations through mid-March, lawmakers said late on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/congress-vote-new-restrictions-us-investment-china-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HBLCWT5ZEVMDJGSIVR47AAQSXI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 02:20:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着竞争加剧，本田和日产将更紧密地合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士称，本田和日产正朝着建立更紧密合作关系的方向迈进，双方正在商讨成立一家控股公司，这是日本汽车业重组的最明显迹象，以应对特斯拉和中国竞争对手带来的巨大挑战。【原文：Honda and Nissan are moving towards a closer tie-up with talks of setting up a holding company, a source said, in the clearest sign yet of reorganisation in Japan's auto industry in response to immense challenges posed by Tesla and Chinese rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/honda-nissan-move-closer-tie-up-competition-intensifies-source-says-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BEIUBN76EZJVLM7IZNKRUJIJBM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 02:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚就消费者保护失误起诉 Binance 澳大利亚衍生品公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚企业监管机构周三表示，它已起诉交易平台 Binance Australia Derivatives，称零售客户被错误地归类为批发客户，从而被剥夺了消费者保护。【原文：Australia's corporate watchdog on Wednesday said it has sued trading platform Binance Australia Derivatives, alleging that retail customers were denied consumer protections after being misclassified as wholesale clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australia-sues-binance-australia-derivatives-over-consumer-protection-failures-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SNZFM32PZPXXGPLYUAHMZBOKI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 02:09:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来公司的阿尔茨海默氏症疗法在中国获批]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周二晚些时候表示，中国医疗监管机构已经批准了礼来治疗早期阿尔茨海默氏症的药物，这是继今年1月卫材和百健的Leqembi获得批准后，为患者提供的又一个选择。【原文：China's medical regulator has approved Eli Lilly's treatment for early Alzheimer's, providing patients with another option after Eisai and Biogen's Leqembi received approval in January, the company said late on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eli-lillys-alzheimers-treatment-approved-china-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MY3YFCW4KRJ5BGOPJZOTKKGI3U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着降息临近，2025 年澳大利亚自由支配零售业前景光明]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师称，随着购物者放松腰带，在电子产品和鞋类等商品上大肆挥霍，澳大利亚的自由支配零售商可能会从2025年的降息预期中受益。【原文：Australian discretionary retailers could benefit from expected interest rate cuts in 2025, analysts say, as shoppers loosen their belts to splurge on items such as electronics and footwear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/aussie-discretionary-retailers-face-brighter-2025-rate-cut-nears-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6FOTSCVLVLY7N7MOATVQJW6SA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:45:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息在即，美元兑其他货币持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑日元和其他主要对手货币周三持稳，因为投资者在等待美联储是否会在日本央行和其他央行本周开会前宣布鹰派减息。【原文：The U.S. dollar held steady against the yen and other major rivals on Wednesday as investors waited to see whether the Federal Reserve will deliver a hawkish cut before the Bank of Japan and other central banks meet this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-steady-against-peers-fed-rate-cut-looms-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6B65KWM5BMPNHRPTFHXKYYPZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:13:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩资本称将在未经富士董事会批准的情况下发起对富士软的要约收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权公司贝恩资本（Bain Capital）周三表示，即使未经目标公司董事会批准，该公司也计划发起对富士软股份的要约收购。【原文：Bain Capital plans to launch a tender offer for Fuji Soft shares even without the approval of the target firm's board of directors, the U.S. private equity firm said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-capital-says-it-will-launch-tender-offer-fuji-soft-without-fuji-board-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6MCAKSRBG5OH3OY4HXUTYTIYZA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:43:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝恩支持的芯片制造商 Kioxia 首次上市股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，Kioxia 首次上市时股价上涨了 3%，贝恩支持的这家芯片制造商的估值为 8,070 亿日元（52.5 亿美元）。【原文：Shares of Kioxia rose 3% in their market debut on Wednesday, valuing the Bain-backed chipmaker at 807 billion yen ($5.25 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bain-backed-chipmaker-kioxia-muted-market-debut-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQ2ZVLW5QJL4LHIXWSTFZSVX4U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:25:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敲定达美航空、美联航和美航在华盛顿的新航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部周二最终确定将从华盛顿里根国家机场向各大航空公司提供五个新的每日往返航班。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department on Tuesday finalized its awards of five new daily round-trip flights from Washington Reagan National airport to major airlines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-finalizes-new-washington-flights-delta-united-american-2024-12-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAGYHTELSNO53G5AV3ZPPRH62M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 23:56:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salesforce 完成 1000 笔付费 "Agentforce "交易，展望机器人未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[Salesforce 首席执行官马克-贝尼奥夫（Marc Benioff）周二表示，Salesforce 已为 "Agentforce "完成了 1,000 多笔付费交易，"Agentforce "是 Salesforce 利用人工智能创建虚拟代表的平台。【原文：Salesforce has closed more than 1,000 paid deals for "Agentforce," its platform for creating virtual representatives powered by artificial intelligence, its CEO Marc Benioff said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/salesforce-closes-1000-paid-agentforce-deals-looks-robot-future-2024-12-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GKNRJK7EFJM7IZM3E4APMQSXU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 23:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行监管机构考虑对 SVB 前高管采取法律行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一家主要银行监管机构的主席周二表示，该机构正在考虑对硅谷银行的六名前高管和十一名前董事采取法律行动。【原文：The chairman of a leading U.S. banking regulator said Tuesday his agency is considering legal action against six former officers and eleven former directors of Silicon Valley Bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-bank-regulator-considering-legal-action-against-former-svb-executives-2024-12-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FBIEU4BJ5JJR7OWYWIHTQZSTJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 23:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息称贝恩资本正在洽谈收购小凯撒运营商 Sizzling Platter]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周二表示，私募股权公司贝恩资本（Bain Capital）正在洽谈以超过 10 亿美元（包括债务）的价格收购经营 Little Caesars 和 Jersey Mike's 等餐厅特许经营权的 Sizzling Platter 公司。【原文：Private equity firm Bain Capital is in talks to acquire Sizzling Platter, which operates restaurant franchises such as Little Caesars and Jersey Mike's, for more than $1 billion, including debt, people familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/bain-capital-talks-buy-little-caesars-operator-sizzling-platter-sources-say-2024-12-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QYBYGK7EEVNH3ON7WYX4NGUUXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 22:37:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易法庭认定联想智能手机侵犯爱立信专利]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国际贸易委员会周二表示，联想旗下摩托罗拉移动公司生产的智能手机侵犯了爱立信公司的专利，如果这一决定成立，将导致美国禁止进口这些手机。【原文：The U.S. International Trade Commission said on Tuesday that smartphones made by Lenovo's Motorola Mobility infringe patents owned by Ericsson , which could lead to a ban on U.S. imports of the phones if the decision is upheld.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-trade-tribunal-finds-lenovo-smartphones-infringe-ericsson-patents-2024-12-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGCUQQIJHVNJNBRECASS46NQ6Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 22:11:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国企业承诺为特朗普就职典礼捐款]]></title><description><![CDATA[从金融巨头到硅谷巨头，各种公司都承诺向唐纳德-特朗普的就职基金捐款，因为商界领袖们急于确保在 11 月大选获胜后与这位美国当选总统保持良好关系。【原文：Companies ranging from finance majors to Silicon Valley behemoths are pledging donations to Donald Trump's inaugural fund as business leaders rush to ensure a favorable relationship with the U.S. president-elect after his November election win.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/corporate-america-pledges-donations-trump-inauguration-2024-12-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RYPBZ4FYFKBPGIZBMOWQAPCFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 21:57:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>